(Previously)
I've got a new target.
P'Fah?!
Teh.
Jimmy, my brother, Toh.
Don't fall for Jimmy.
Jimmy is a certified player.
I don't want you getting hurt.
Come on!
I wasn't thinking of anything.
I don't want my brother to fall for you.
I haven't thought of him that way at all.
You bastard, Jimmy!
What's your problem, Teh?
Look at this.
What the hell is this?!
It's obviously your house's camera.
Don't forget that I'm your
friend who knows you really are.
So what?
I just bought desserts to
thank your brother for dinner.
Didn't I tell you to stay away from my brother?!
- I don't trust you!
- So what?!
- Didn't I tell you?!
- What the hell?!
What's your game?!
I don't have a plan!
- Calm down, man!
- Spit it out!
- Just tell me, damn it!
- Take it easy!
Calm down!
What's wrong with you?
Both of you are too worked up. Let's talk later.
Move it.
- Come at me!
- Stop!
Come at me!
- Enough.
- Let me go!
Run, let go.
If you don't even like Teh's brother,
then why do all this?
What?
You jealous?
Please.
I've already moved on.
It's Book, a model.
That was fast.
Look who you're talking to.
I dragged you here to
talk some sense into you.
Teh's your best friend. Think about
things before you do something stupid.
I understand that you'd…
screw anything that moves.
But he's your friend's brother.
Leave him out of this.
Oh,
I heard that you're…
hitting on P'Fah?
How'd you know?
Ah…
Good luck with that.
He's way out of your league.
Yeah! Just watch me!
I'll make him mine.
Or didn't Jimmy think of P'Toh that way?
Forget it.
It already happened.
"Love Alert"
(Episode 2)
Teh is being such a pain about his brother.
How can I get close to Plaifah?
Maybe I can use P'Toh to get to him.
Yeah, P'Toh.
He's my best bet.
But how do I handle him?
This looks amazing, Jimmy.
It sure does.
You say it looks good,
but you're not looking at the food.
Did I ever say I was talking about the food?
P' Toh,
could you spill some
of the drink on your lips?
So I can wipe it off for you.
Just like this.
P' Toh,
there's something I must tell you.
It's important.
What… is it?
Teh's in love with P'Fah.
I don't know what to do about it.
R-really?
Yes.
Can you do me a favor?
Yes. What do you need me to do?
What's with the sudden party?
Aren't you supposed to be an “inverter”?
It's “introvert”.
An “inverter” is a part of an AC.
Fine, my bad. Excuse me.
What's the reason?
Nothing much.
I just want to cook for some
friends before the cafe opens.
Sure?
Are you a detective or something?
And who exactly are these “friends”?
Well, there's… Fah.
And that's it.
You have the nerve to call
that a party? That's a date.
You're coming too, so it's not a date anymore.
Unless... you're not joining?
No way! Half of the money
is mine. I need to eat my money's worth.
I'm heading out.
See ya.
Okay.
Study hard.
Hey,
What's with the long faces?
What are you guys doing?
How can I not be stressed?
I've been working on the group report
all night and it's still not finished.
Which report?
This one. For Professor Boss.
- Crap…
- I knew it.
- We're toast.
- We're screwed.
What am I going to tell him?
Will he let me turn it in late?
What do I do?!
Mr. Teh?
Yes, professor?
Do you want to revise your report? I can't let
you make changes after it's been submitted.
S… Submitted?
Yes, Mr. Jimmy dropped it off this morning.
I've had a quick look at it.
You guys did a solid job.
Yes.
Why did you put my name on the report?
Weren't you still pissed at me?
I don't take our problem personally.
Stop overthinking it, dumbass.
If I'm a dumbass, then you're a total moron.
I totally get you…
for being protective of your brother.
I can't help it. He's so cute.
Hey, watch it…
Chill out.
I'm just telling the truth.
You should know that
I'm worried about him.
I don't want him to get hurt.
As long as you don't mess with him,
we're good.
Need anything else? I'm running late.
Nothing.
I'm off then.
Wait!
We're having a party at
my house. You should come.
But no flirting with my brother.
I got it. See ya there.
Whatever.
Whoa!
Hi there, P'Toh!
I can smell it from the street!
Go wash your hands first.
Feed me then?
My hands are messy too.
Go wash yours and help yourself.
Meanie.
I won't eat then.
Gonna take a shower first.
Everything looks amazing.
I'm so jealous of Teh.
Oh, P'Toh,
I bought some drinks.
Thanks.
You said the food looks good,
make sure you eat a lot.
Of course.
I'll check it for you.
You're here for P'Toh?
You've got the right house.
I thought so.
I was sure I remembered the way.
So… is P'Toh inside?
Yep.
P'Toh.
Fah.
I told you not to bring anything.
I heard we're having roasted beef.
It goes well with
this wine. I even “borrowed” it from my parents.
That sounds like a killer combo.
Do you need any help?
Not at all. Wait for Teh to finish
his shower, then we can dig in.
Are you hungry?
I can go and hurry him up.
No need to rush him.
P'Toh, where's the toilet?
I want to use it.
It's near the kitchen.
Need my help?
Don't worry. Have a seat.
I'll take care of the rest.
P'Fah?
Hello.
Let's eat! I'm starving!
“P”?
So we're still at “P”?
Challenge accepted.
Yeah, you had a fever at the volunteer camp.
I still remember. If I hadn't sponged you down,
you wouldn't have made it off the mountains.
Yeah.
That camp was so much fun.
I'm going to wash my hands.
Do you like the beach?
Not really, I'm more of a mountain person.
P'Toh, let's go on a trip soon.
I'm craving a chill barbecue night.
Sure. Just name the date.
You said it.
I'll clear my schedule.
(Ask him.)
Is it “date” schedule for a boyfriend?
Study schedule.
Since my last breakup, I haven't been looking
for anything serious. Just one-night stands.
(Ask him more.)
So, is it true that you're seeing a girl now?
Yeah.
It's more comfortable than being with men.
Because all I ever met were players.
They act sweet to your face, then go screw
someone else behind your back. I hate that.
If you ever date someone,
I have to screen them first.
Okay?
Okay.
Are you full?
Yes. What about you?
Thanks for tonight.
Say bye to Teh for me. He knocked out
right after dinner and hasn't moved since.
Want me to wake him up?
It's fine.
I'll head out now.
Go home safe.
See ya, P'Toh.
See ya.
P'Fah?
Hello.
Let's eat! I'm starving!
“P”?
This is going to be fun.
That's the last of them.
Thanks. Go hang out with Teh.
I've got the rest.
No way.
We ate together, we clean together.
No. In this house, we don't
let our guests do the dishes.
P'Toh.
In my house, we don't sit around
while the host cleans up.
It's okay.
P'Toh.
It's fine.
- Come on.
- I mean it.
- No...
- P'Toh...
P'Toh!
Why didn't you tell me to sleep upstairs?
My whole body is stiff
from sleeping on a couch.
Why are you still here?
I was helping P'Toh with the dishes.
Good.
You can be grateful.
Finish the rest for us.
You're leaving me to do it all by myself?!
Duh, I took a shower and
don't want to get messy.
And what about P'Toh?!
He must sing me a lullaby!
Any questions, moron?
Why is my heart racing?
I like Fah, I like Fah…
I like Fah.
You like Fah, Jimmy.
You like Fah.
Finally! We're here!
(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
Fah,
Are you okay back there?
I tried to drive as smoothly as I could.
I took some meds beforehand.
Here, let me get that for you.
It's okay. I can manage.
You carry the cooler.
Fine…
Fah's barely talking to me.
You're being way too clingy.
What am I supposed to do?
Play it cool. Make him wonder about you.
Like your advice ever works.
I'm being this “extra”,
but he still ignores me.
If I “stay still”, I'd be…
invisible.
Whatever. That's all I can help.
Sure…
An advice from a single guy.
I'm single not because my methods don't work,
but by choice. Period.
Is there a problem between us?
Not at all.
I saw you taking photos and
didn't want to get in your way.
P-P'Fah?
Did you take a picture of me?
Yeah. Now, you're the subject.
But I'm not photogenic.
Come take a look.
I think…
I'm really into you.
And next time, drop the “P”.
Just call me Fah.
Got it?
Damn…
My heart's fluttering.
What are you up to?
Marinating the pork.
You startled me.
What do I have to do? Need a hand?
Put all the ingredients in and massage them.
Your hands are so soft.
Then… you finish the rest.
I'm going to… wash the vegetables.
Hold on, Jimmy.
You like Fah.
Want me to feed you?
So your hands are free for the guitar.
It's fine.
I wanna eat barbeque.
Then help yourself.
(What are you laughing at?)
(Good luck with that, moron.)
P'Toh.
Are you drunk?
You should head up to bed.
I'm not drunk...
You can barely keep your head up.
I'll take you to your room.
I'm getting sleepy anyway.
Don't worry. I'll take him.
You're still having fun. Just stay here.
I'll take my...
Stay right where you are.
If you go up, I know you'll
ditch me and go to sleep.
I've got this.
Come on, P'Toh.
Let's go.
Easy does it.
My head's spinning.
It's because you're wasted.
Get some sleep. You'll feel better.
Well…
I'm going.
Stay with me.
I'm scared of ghosts.
I had no idea you were a scaredy-cat.
Stay until I fall asleep.
If you're worried, just check on him yourself.
I don't want to leave
you here by yourself, P'Fah.
Just call me “Fah”.
“Just Fah”.
Much better.
I think that you've…
been avoiding me.
I haven't.
Don't you want to kiss me?
Fah,
Jimmy likes you.
But I don't like him.
And I'm not looking for anything serious.
It's late. We should head to bed.
Can I sleep in your room tonight?
Teh, don't give me that look.
P'Toh was scared of ghosts
and asked me to stay with him.
Why are you two headed back?
Run out of snacks?
No, we're heading to bed.
I'm driving tomorrow.
Can't risk a headache.
Let's go.
We're off to bed.
Goodnight.
Move it.
Now.
Damn!
Fah said goodnight to me.
What did you tell him?
Just that you like him.
For real?
What did he say?
He didn't say anything.
You've got to be kidding me!
Tell me. I wanna know.
Go ask him yourself.
I'm dead tired.
And turn down the AC.
It's frickin' hot.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's already at 19.
Why is it still hot?
What should we do?
We're going to be baked alive in here.
You better compensate us tomorrow,
or I'm leaving a nasty review.
Well? Can't they fix it?
It's past midnight.
The technicians are all gone.
Now what?
Sleep naked like me.
Hell no.
Or…
crash in P'Toh's room.
No, too cramped.
That's what I want.
Grab your blanket!
Hey,
I'll sleep next to Fah.
Whatever.
I'll crash on the floor.
Sleep next your crush like a K-drama.
Make sure your body
stays “stiff”. Nothing else.
Screw you.
I'll tell your brother the real you.
Go to sleep already.
Teh.
Now what?
I can't sleep next to Fah.
P'Tohs in the way.
And you're next to him.
Just sleep here with me.
Nah, my back will be trashed.
Teh.
What now?
I'll sleep next to your brother.
Yeah, fine. I'm out.
And stop bothering me.
I'm sleeping.
Can I sleep here with you?
My blanket got snatched.
I saw you at the club once.
But I guess you didn't notice me.
Really?
You're so charming.
No wonder you're always with someone new.
Can I ask you something?
Do you ever want something serious?
I used to,
but I don't really know what love feels like.
Every relationship I've had was just a thrill.
Once the spark is gone, I'm done.
So…
just one-night stands then?
I just feel…
if I can't love someone with my whole soul,
it's better to be alone.
How can it be love without devotion?
What if…
you finally find the one…
you can give all your heart to…
but they don't feel the same,
wouldn't that destroy you?
Well… At least I got to “love” someone.
Jimmy?
P'Toh.
Let me cover your ears.
Jimmy? Are you okay?
P'Toh…
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I just…
need a hug right now.
Damn…
You're…
so tempting like what Teh said.
No.
This isn't right.
At least he respects you, Toh.
(Next Episode)
There's one rule of mine you should know.
Do you realize you haven't
been yourself since the trip?
Did you tell P'Toh that I like Fah?
- How could you...
- I like Fah.
Or do you like him too?
Why don't you trust us?
I've been his friend for a long time.
I know exactly what he's capable of.