Are you sure about the complications
you're getting into?
Do you know what gives me courage?
-What?
-You.
I believe you now have eyes and ears
inside their organization.
You just have to believe in yourself.
I was practicing my… judo roll.
I told you.
Yes.
Doesn’t it feel a bit too much?
Do I really have to ride a private jet?
It’s scary.
Yes, sweetheart. And trust me,
it really suits you.
You actually look cute.
Dad,
can you slow down a bit?
Do you want me to introduce him
to the office already?
Dad.
Give us a couple of days first
to settle down. Okay?
And Mikoy still has some things to fix.
All right. Take your time.
‎All right.
Kian briefly woke up earlier.
The next time he wakes up,
please call me
and Agent Sianong immediately.
Because we need to talk to him right away.
-All right.
-Okay.
Bok, why did you talk
to the mom like that?
Did I say anything wrong?
"The next time he wakes up,
please call me and Agent Sianong
because we want
to talk to him right away."
Yes, I’m interested
in the new information
that Agent Kian can give.
But that doesn't mean
I don't care about his situation.
The most important thing right now
is that our teammate recovers,
and there is no new information
more important than his life.
That's my point.
Actually…
-Kian…
-Kian.
Mikoy is in danger.
Someone wants to kill him.
Jepoy.
I'm sorry,
I wasn't there when you needed me.
Who the hell did this to you?
PHILIPPINE UNIVERSITY
Bro?
Bro, is that really you?
-How are you?
-Nice outfit.
When did you get back?
Just suddenly,
and I told Mom and Dad
not to tell you yet,
because I wanted to surprise you.
So… Surprise!
I am suprised!
But now I know why
those two went radio silent on me.
They ignored me for days.
Turns out you were hiding
a surprise from me.
So, you came from home?
Yes.
Everything's actually good there.
Did you know there's
a new oven in Dad’s bakery?
It’s nice.
You know what, bro?
They really saved up the money
you’ve been sending.
Actually, they even want
to open a branch in the mall.
Huh? Nice.
They didn’t tell me anything.
Okay.
But…
What is it?
Why do you look like that?
How do I look?
You look like a big shot now.
-Did you marry a foreigner or something?
-Whoa!
You're crazy! What foreigner?
Not a foreigner.
But me.
Your brother Mikoy's girlfriend.
Hey, hey, hey. Easy.
That's my girlfriend.
Just keep calling. We need to warn him.
The subscriber cannot be reached.
Mikoy, please answer your phone.
Really?
Just one drinking session
and bro already got you?
Tell me about it.
He even said that he is
the nation’s top drinker.
What he meant was a "player".
-Huh?
-He got me with drinks first.
Then, when I got tipsy,
he suddenly made his move.
Whoa!
And me being soft-hearted…
Cut to I’m here, in Manila.
Living like a Disney princess,
"Part of your world."
You, bro!
You’re really something.
-You’re my idol.
-Whatever.
Hey, don’t believe her.
The truth is,
she’s the one who went after me.
-What?
-Yes, right.
Oh please.
What are you? A historical revisionist?
That’s bad! Don’t rewrite the story.
Okay, okay.
Fine, fine, it’s me.
But here’s the real good news, Angelito.
Chiara’s family has a company here,
and officially,
her dad wants me
to help run their company.
Wow!
That’s great, bro!
Sis, did you know?
It doesn’t show,
but he finished a business course
with high honors!
But you know, if only our bakery
hadn’t been pawned and gone bankrupt,
he would’ve studied here in Manila too.
But no,
he had to help Mom and Dad.
So he got stuck in our small bakery.
And because of me,
that’s why he went abroad,
so I could study in Manila.
But then…
all I gave back was shame.
What are you talking about?
I think I’ll leave you two.
You probably need to talk.
I’ll just be around
or wait at the parking area.
Thank you.
Pinagpala Special Torta.
Hello, ma’am. Good day to you.
We’d like to request a delivery
and also order some torta.
Sure, sir and ma’am.
What would you like to order?
It’s true, bro.
I really am embarrassing.
Imagine that…
I was supposed to study here,
but instead…
I got caught in a drug buy-bust.
What was that?
It’s so embarrassing for Mom and Dad.
But most of all for you, bro.
You were the one
who sacrificed so much for me.
What happened to you was not your fault.
You were just in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
I’m the one you should blame.
Because that wouldn’t have happened
if I had been there for you.
Come here. Stop being dramatic.
Come on.
I will avenge you, bro.
I’ll go after whoever did this to you.
There you go, Betchay.
This is very simple.
Go to the market now
because I already called Aling Pacing.
I ordered extra ingredients.
I ordered vanilla, eggs,
basically everything on this list.
Here! It’s very easy.
-Go now, hurry!
-Yes, ma'am!
I’ll take care of it.
It’s important. I need it right away.
Angel!
-You need to cook all of that now.
-Yes.
What are the extra ingredients for?
Honey,
someone ordered a huge amount of torta.
Of course, our ingredients aren’t enough,
since we only stock a small amount.
So I bought extra.
And where are they from?
Right! They’re from Manila!
-From Manila?
-Yes!
So someone already knows about our bakery?
Yes!
But they said they’re friends with Mikoy!
And Mikoy apparently told them
about our torta recipe.
So, yes! They ordered a lot.
I wonder who that is?
Oh no.
They said they’re really
friends with Mikoy.
And they even asked where Mikoy is now.
I told them he’s back from Prague
and now in Manila
and already has a new job.
I wonder who it is.
Where do you think you're going?
What are you doing here?
I should be asking you that.
That you’re already here in Manila.
If we hadn’t called your mother,
we wouldn’t have known where you are
or what happened to you.
Why did you call my mother?
I had no choice. I needed to talk to you.
Because there’s a threat against you now!
Yes! Yes!
Is there a problem?
Nothing.
I was looking for you.
Angelito’s university is really beautiful.
Yes.
No.
Ah, it’s her. She…
And I think you found
what you were looking for.
Yes!
Right! I was just asking around
because Angelito’s university is so big.
I couldn’t see you.
I’ll be late for my class.
Yes!
Thank you, ma’am!
Of course. Definitely. Where are we going?
-Let’s go!
-Come on!
Oh, how are you?
Chiara is there!
So, what happened? Did Chiara see you?
Yes! I was careless! Let’s go!
What the… Alex!
You know that’s dangerous!
She must not recognize you!
Why do you think we need
to be careful around Chiara?
Do you think she knows
what her parents are doing?
I don’t know,
but one thing I’m sure of,
we cannot trust her either. Okay?
And under no circumstances
should she recognize or see us.
Okay?
and she told me about
your worries at work.
About your being COO.
Well, that’s a valid concern.
Because this is new for Mikoy. Right?
Yes. There’s quite
a difference in managing,
running a bakery,
versus managing a big company.
Sweetheart, you don’t need to worry.
And if you have any problem,
you can always turn to me.
May I just ask something?
Why not let Chiara
run the company instead?
She’s capable.
Actually, this is a very good question.
Yes, indeed. Child, why didn’t you…
answer?
I just thought about it.
Of course, you’re super educated.
You graduated from a very prestigious
and very expensive school.
Of course, you also know
your daddy’s business.
For me, she’s really
the perfect one for this.
Why not?
Simple. I don’t want to.
I don’t want to do it. Period.
What do you want to do?
Excuse me.
Are you okay?
I don’t think that question
should have been asked.
But it is a good question.
No!
I should have thought of that.
By the way, that’s why you're mad
at your mommy and daddy.
You’re being forced
to take over their business.
Chiara, sorry.
I was really insensitive there.
It’s okay.
At least now
you know the life I’ve been living.
They say, the more you know someone,
the more you love them.
Isn’t it, the more you know,
the more you hate?
Really?
-No take-backs?
-Just kidding!
This one is no joke though.
Don’t worry.
I’m here.
If you don’t want to take over
their business yet,
then I will go first.
So you won’t be pressured
by your mommy and daddy.
Okay?
For coming into my life.
Believe it or not,
I just want a simple and normal life.
So, sorry,
because now you’re the one
in a complicated situation.
But I will be forever grateful
for your help to me and my family.
Okay.
Because starting today,
you will be handling very delicate
and sensitive information.
So, nothing must leak
from any information inside this agency.
Okay?
Here, we will see the clue
that we are all looking for.
Special Agent Sianong,
give me one good reason
why I should not suspend you without pay
and send you to Timbuktu!
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry, Sir.
I wanted a proper welcome
for our team members.
Sorry. Okay.
But unlike that video,
we don’t need to be afraid anymore.
Looks like we finally have a chance.
And here he is now.
You know, he could become a celebrity.
Looks like he’s really going to shine.
Is he going to be launched
as a new loveteam on primetime TV?
Not a loveteam.
But he is not slated for primetime.
Because he is now the new
Chief Operations Officer
of Vertex Global Holdings!
The company of the Valtrovis!
VERTEX GLOBAL
The past week, he was introduced
to the entire company,
and he was briefed
about company operations.
Here, Viktor Valtrovi taught him
the core business of Vertex,
and that is repackaging Filipino products
and exporting them
to various markets in Europe.
We have reason to believe
that Viktor is using this
to export illegal shipments to Europe.
But how does he do it?
How does he smuggle his illegal shipments?
Can our asset answer these questions?
If you're really struggling,
you can walk away from this mission.
You're saying it's okay with you
if I don't continue spying on them?
Against the Moravianos?
I heard that you want to kill Mikoy.
The one who ordered is your friend.
The name is Alex.
Who's that friend of yours, sweetheart?
How did you guys meet?