- Can you cuddle with me?
- Yeah, sure.
Sam, can you stop
moving, please?
I’m sorry.
‘Cause your behind is
brushing on my—
front.
- Surprise!
- Welcome to your bachelorette party!
- Yes, sir!
- I love you too!
Do you mind extending
the fun with me?
I may be the first
one to get married—
but I’m claiming it now.
All of us will get married
and have our
own happily ever afters
with people who truly love us.
OMG. It really is Samantha Vera!
Who’s that with her?
That’s not Haze.
Samantha Vera, are you cheating
on Haze Juarez?
It’s okay.
No.
Haze and I are just friends.
What’s your relationship
with Clyden Ramirez?
Are you two together?
- Yeah, are you two a couple?
- It’s okay, Avi.
Are you a couple now?
- Are you a couple now?
- Sam.
Sam, let’s go.
Yes.
We’re together.
So, stop asking now.
You can stop asking now, okay?
Let’s go, let’s go, let’s go.
Let’s go.
So is it true?
No doubt about it.
Yes,
we’re together.
So stop asking.
So is it true? Clyden Ramirez
is Sam’s boyfriend?
Baby daddy confirmed?
I thought Haze
was the baby daddy?
Sounds like Sam was seeing both
guys at the same time.
Sam never even admitted that
she and Haze were a thing!
I think she’s the one
in that blind item
about a girl with two guys.
And she’s not even sure who the
real father of her baby is!
Honestly, I’m so disappointed
in Samantha Vera.
I’m a huge fan.
I love her advocacies.
I thought she was
a decent woman.
What were you
thinking, Samantha?
I’m your manager!
I should’ve known about this.
Now I had to find out online
that you have a boyfriend?
I’m sorry. I should’ve told you,
but we weren’t sure of
our relationship yet, so—
I don’t care if
you’re official or not.
The fact that you’re
seeing a high-profile man
is a really big scoop
for the media, Sam.
The brands tied to your
name could pull out.
And don’t forget about
your morality clause.
And now look,
there are even more stories
coming out about you two.
I don’t even know
what’s real or not.
The truth is—
Clyden is my ex.
What?
Actually, he’s not just my ex.
He was my fiancé.
Our parents arranged
for us to be married.
But
when the scandal
about my family came out,
Clyden and I had to break up.
We haven't talked to each other
for years, until recently.
Shit, Sam.
I’m pretty sure that
they will dig into your past.
News spreads fast,
you know that.
Content creators are
now making money
off the drama of celebrities.
Just like you.
Hi, guys. We’re here today
at Ramirez Hospital.
Someone challenged me to
interview Dr. Clyden Ramirez.
Challenge accepted.
I’m gonna be a fake
patient for today’s video.
Nurse!
Nurse! It really hurts.
Help me.
I saw our target,
he’s on the other side.
Doc!
My stomach really hurts.
Where exactly does it hurt?
Here, doc.
Doc, how’s Sam doing?
Arah, what should we do?
I don’t want Clyden
to get dragged into this.
The moment you two
admitted you were dating,
he automatically
became part of the issue.
What kind of pain
are you feeling?
Is it like cramping?
Doc, you’re trending
online right now.
I don’t know what
you’re referring to, but sir,
can we please
focus on your health?
What happened was wild.
They said you guys
cheated on Haze?
Is that true, Doc?
What?
Come here.
- Get him.
- Where?
Get them out. They’re
pretending to be a patient.
- Get them out of here.
- Sir.
- Hurry.
- You need to leave now.
- Sir, please don’t.
- Wait.
- Sir, I’m not.
- Doc!
- Sir!
- Stop resisting.
Sir! Sir!
- Sir!
- Enough.
You’re still pretending.
- Sir!
- Busted! We got caught.
- Doc couldn’t even answer.
- Please don’t, sir. Sir!
So it looks like it’s true.
Doc, you’re being called
to the director’s office.
I will see what I can do,
but it’s not looking good.
I hope Clyden is not
having a hard time right now.
I’ve been getting
so many reports
about fake patients in the ER.
They’re wasting our resources.
There’s also
a lot of media outside.
What are you trying to do? Huh?
The hospital’s reputation is
ruined because of you.
Every time you get involved
with that woman,
there’s always trouble.
Damn it!
Just because of a woman?
What happened to
being the “perfect son”?
What good are you now?
Huh, Cy?
So if you still have
any shame left,
just resign instead of
causing more trouble.
Or you know what?
You’re better off just
going with that woman.
What’s her name again?
Samantha Vera?
That slut from a corrupt family.
Don’t you fucking dare
talk about Sam like that.
Let me remind you,
you’re only in that position
because I turned it down.
If I really wanted to, I could
easily take it back from you.
That’s why I’m not
gonna resign, Charles.
Because we both know,
between the two of us,
you’re the useless one.
In fact, I pity you.
A lot.
‘Cause this hospital is all you
ever have going for you.
So, go fuck yourself!
Fuck you, asshole!
So yeah,
it’s confirmed, Samantha Vera and Clyden
Ramirez were in an arranged marriage.
They say it was
for political reasons.
But when the scandal with
Senator Vera broke out,
the Ramirez family
suddenly backed out
so they wouldn’t
get dragged into it.
Maybe that’s why
the wedding was canceled,
to hide that the
Ramirezes were involved.
That Ramirez family
seems shady, too.
Looks like they already
made money off the Veras.
The hospital suddenly
expanded like crazy.
So, how true is it that
Clyden topped the boards
if people say it
was all paid for?
Honestly, I wouldn’t
be surprised.
He’s a nepo baby.
Everything’s just
about money now.
This is all my fault!
I did this to Cy! Fuck!
Sam: Hey, are you okay?
I’m so sorry for
dragging you into my mess.
Hello, Maui? Are you okay?
Hey, Clyden.
I’m really sorry, Cy.
This is all my fault.
I shouldn’t have said
we were together.
I should’ve protected you
from the public.
Hey, you don’t need
to apologize. I’m okay.
You didn’t do anything wrong.
I’m the one who should’ve
protected you from them.
So, how are you? No one’s
bothering you over there?
Stay off social media
for now, and don’t go out.
I know it’s not easy,
but it’ll help.
Thank you, Cy.
Even with everything going on,
you’re still thinking about me.
If anyone bothers you,
let me know, okay?
It's okay. I’m okay.
No one’s bothering me
here either.
Take care, okay?
Let’s go.
Hey, Samantha Vera!
My kid used to idolize you,
but wow, you’re such
a disappointment!
So many kids
look up to you,
and it turns out you’re
a terrible role model.
I’m burning all
of my kid’s magazines!
You’re disgusting!
You’re no different
from your father! Rotten!
How did this person
get my personal number?
You’re a bad role model!
You’re disgusting!
You’re no different
from your father!
I’ve tried my best to be
a decent person,
to be different
from my parents.
And yet just
one wrong move,
and people have been
so quick to judge me.
I know I’m not perfect.
But do I really deserve
this kind of hate?
Yanna: We’re booking
a flight home.
There’s no way you’re
facing this alone.
Luna: Sam, we’re right here.
Let’s just go for a drink!
Sevi: Stay strong, Sam.
Ignore the bashers!
They don’t know how
kind you really are!
Kierra: If you need
someone to talk to,
we’ll come see you anytime.
Via: Sam, just always remember
we love you, okay?
We’re here for you.
Auntie, are you okay?
Auntie, are you crying?
Auntie, don’t cry.
If you’re sad, then I’m sad too.
Auntie’s just going
through something, baby.
But I’ll be okay soon.
Everything will be
all right, Auntie.
I always pray to Papa Jesus
that he will protect you.
Eat this, so you’ll
be happy again.
Thank you, baby.
Thank you.
Sam?
Yeah.
Haze, can you take care
of Avi for now?
All eyes are
on me right now,
and it could stress the kid.
Hey, I’m involved in
the issue too, you know.
I’m sorry.
It’s all right. I can handle it.
How are you?
Not good.
That’s why I need your
help to take care of Avi.
Sure.
Avi will be much safer
here at our parents’ house.
I’ll just pick her up
at your condo.
No, actually, we’re already
on our way there.
There are a lot of reporters
and content creators
waiting outside the condo,
and things will get worse
if they see you here too.
All right. I’ll wait
for you here.
Thank you, Haze.
And I’m really sorry
for dragging you into this.
Don’t worry about me, Sam.
Focus on yourself
and take care, okay?
See you.
Let’s go, baby.
Look who’s here!
- Hello, love.
- Uncle!
Are you going to buy me lots
of toys and food again?
You’re spoiling her too much.
Wow! You’re one
to talk, huh?
Hey!
Go up to your
room first, okay?
I’ll prepare you
something to eat.
Bye, Auntie!
Bye, baby.
Don’t be sad, okay?
Okay, I promise.
Thank you for agreeing
to look after Avi.
But please don’t bring
her to your dates.
She’s just a kid; you gotta
protect her innocence.
So, what’s your plan now?
I’m sure there are tons of media
waiting outside your condo.
Yeah.
I already asked Kalix if
I could borrow his parking space
so they won’t see me arriving.
I see.
I saw your video.
“Haze and I are just friends.”
That kinda hurt, you know?
I thought we had
something special.
You just can’t be serious, no?
Anyway, I’m leaving now.
Okay then, take care.
Hey, one more thing.
If you’re going to
run from the media—
wear heels.
Arah: Sam, have you seen this?!
Your ex’s mom
just did an interview!
This is bad!
These allegations made me sick.
You know, my family and I
have cut ties with the Veras
ever since before
this incident happened.
And besides,
we’re in the medical field.
We value honesty
and integrity,
especially when it
comes to our patients.
And being involved with Senator
Vera is against our values.
That’s exactly why we
canceled our son’s engagement
with Samantha Vera.
So please, stop linking
their family to ours.
But ma’am, are you
aware that your son
is dating
Samantha Vera again?
Well, you haven’t heard anything
from my son, right?
So, those two are not dating.
OMG. So what now?
Did Sam force herself
on Clyden again?
What kind of
bribe did she use this time?
Is Clyden’s family throwing
her under the bus?
I feel like the mom’s
version is more believable,
because if they
were really dating,
- why won’t Clyden confirm it?
- Samantha Vera
delulu era it is!
I’m tired. So fucking
tired of all this.
When will it ever end?
Jaida Ramirez: Hello, Sam.
This is Clyden’s mom.
I’m on my way to
your condo. Can we talk?
Good afternoon.
Please come inside.
Would you like
a drink or anything?
Well, no need. This will be fast anyways.
And I need to clear
everything out for you.
I will, ma’am. I’m just waiting
for my manager’s call.
Well, I don’t know if you
and my son are really dating.
But please, stop tarnishing
the relationship
between my son and his dad.
They’re not even
talking anymore.
He refused another marriage.
He lost his inheritance.
And I’m sure you know
the reason why.
What? I don’t understand.
Well, my son hasn’t
accepted any of our help
since you two broke up.
I don’t want you anymore.
You’re nothing without
your family’s money.
I’m nothing?
My son doesn’t want to
accept any kind of help anymore.
I literally had to beg him
to take the hospital room
we were offering him.
At first, he refused.
But eventually, he accepted it
out of necessity.
But I believe he only took it so
the other residents could use it
Sam, don’t take this
the wrong way.
But this is the worst time to be
dragging my son into this mess.
He’s already struggling
with his life
without our support.
And a scandal like this
will burden him even more.
So please don’t add to it.
It feels like history
is repeating itself.
Maybe I really am
no good for Cy.
Yanna?
I’m here.
- Yanna…
- I’m here. I’m here.
Take a sit first.
You haven’t been answering
my messages or calls.
You haven’t even
checked in with the group.
We’re all really
worried about you.
I really thought something
bad happened to you,
that’s why I told Hiro
we had to come back.
Yanna—
I’m sorry I ruined
your honeymoon.
Go back. Don’t worry about me.
I’m okay.
How can I enjoy myself
knowing you’re not okay?
If you can drop everything
when I’m feeling down,
then I can drop
everything too—
even Hiro, just to be with you.
No. Hiro’s probably
mad at me right now.
He’s the one who
booked my flight, actually.
He understands.
Don’t feel guilty.
Give me your phone.
You’re not allowed
to read any comments
or posts tonight.
That won’t do any good
for your mental health.
You’re right.
Good thing you’re
here to stop me.
Yanna, can you stay
with me tonight, please?
I honestly feel lost
and scared right now.
Do you even have to ask?
I was already planning
on sleeping here tonight.
At least, I have Yanna.
I will always have Yanna.
- Morning.
Sam, I’m heading out
for a bit, okay?
I just need to fix something
at work real quick.
It’s okay, Yanna. Just do
what you have to do.
Thanks for staying here, okay?
And for cooking breakfast.
Of course.
But Sam...
Before you say thank you, can
you please take a shower first?
You smell like alcohol.
Even your breath!
You seriously smell
like alcohol!
Fine! I’ll shower, okay?
All right, I’m heading out now.
Eat your breakfast and
reply to my message, okay?
Yes.
- Okay.
- Yes, I will.
- Bye!
- Bye.
Thank you.
No, I should stop
reading comments online.
It’s not good for me.
But,
I’m just curious about what
people are saying about me.
I feel like I need to.
I want to know.
I really didn’t expect
that from Samantha.
I thought her image
was so clean.
She has so many
charity projects.
Now I don’t even know if
all of that was just for show.
Such a waste, she’s so pretty.
What’s the point of being pretty
if your attitude is trash?
How can they say
my attitude is trash?
That everything I did
to help others was fake?
They don’t even know me!
The same people who once
praised me for clicks and clout
are now the ones
attacking me.
Not even one person
is standing up for me?
They all left me?
Wasn’t there another
issue with her dad?
They said he killed his
mistress and made up
-some other reason to cover it up.
- Didn’t they have a child?
- Naomi, right?
- There haven’t been any updates
about Naomi.
People are saying
she was killed, too.
Maybe he got rid of her, too.
Even Samantha hasn’t
said anything about it.
Why?
Why are you dragging
Naomi into this, too?
I’ve had enough.
This needs to stop.
I need to be
stronger than this.
For Naomi, for Cy,
and for myself.
Arah, please organize
a tell-all interview.
I want to clear up all
the issues once and for all.
Let them judge me after this.
Sam, are you sure?
This won’t be easy.
Yes. I’m 100% sure.
I have to speak up.
I have to defend myself.
Okay. I understand.
I know a trusted journalist.
I’ll schedule an
appointment with her.
Thank you. Also, please,
book my flight to New York
as soon as possible.
I want to leave soon.
Okay. Give me at least
three days to prepare.
Sam? You got this, okay?
We’re here for you.
Thank you, Arah, for everything.
Cy.
Why aren’t you answering me?
I—
I’m sorry.
Sam, I’m sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
If I hadn’t approached
you again,
none of this
would’ve happened.
I shouldn’t have
told you I still love you.
Sorry, Sam. It’s my fault.
Don’t apologize, Cy.
I’m the one who should be
saying sorry to you.
This is all my fault.
Maybe it was wrong
to make you hold on to me.
I never wanted
to hurt you, Maui.
We’re both hurting.
Cy, please think
about yourself too.
It’s my fault your family got
dragged into this mess.
People are starting
to doubt your profession.
And I know you’re being
disturbed by the media.
Maui, I don’t even
care about that.
Why?
Why aren’t you
answering my calls?
Are you pushing me away again?
- Cy…
- I’m sorry.
I just love you so much,
and I was hoping and praying
that we’ll be together again.
That night, when you left me,
all I wished for was
for you to come back.
I was angry when
you walked away,
because how could you end
everything in one night?
Maui, was it my fault?
No.
Everything was just too
much for me that night.
Naomi, my parents, modeling.
And I didn’t want your
family to get caught up
in my family’s mess.
Part of the reason was that
I just wanted to save you
and your family’s reputation.
That time, I didn’t need
a savior, Maureen.
I just needed you
to stay with me.
Was it really that easy
for you to leave me?
No, Cy.
I just wanted to protect you,
and I failed.
Just like how I failed
to protect Naomi.
Your mom came to see me.
I found out about
your inheritance
and your relationship
with your dad.
Cy, I’m so sorry.
This is all my fault.
Maui, stop.
It’s not your fault.
I made that choice.
The hell with the inheritance
and another marriage.
If it’s not with you, I have no
intention of getting married.
Cy, I’m sorry.
I’m truly sorry
for everything I did.
For not fighting for us,
then and now.
For making you feel useless.
For making you blame yourself.
For making you feel
that I hate you.
None of those are true, Cy.
I love you.
I can’t love anyone else
the way I love you.
Maui, it’s really
not your fault.
You didn’t fail to
protect me or Naomi.
Do you know what
she told me before she left?
She talked to you?
She told me to
stay by your side
through all the highs and lows.
And to make sure I wipe
the tears off your face.
And that you should
never lose your smile.
And she also said,
“Sam is the happiest
when she’s free.”
You’re free when you're
at your happiest, Sam.
So let everything go,
even me.
Do something for
yourself this time, please.
Cy, can you please
confiscate my phone?
I can’t stop reading
all the negative comments.
I think I’m starting
to get addicted to it.
I don’t even
know why. Maybe,
I’m just looking
for a few positive ones?
But it’s so hard.
Why don’t you check
your friends' posts?
I’m pretty sure they
sent you messages, too.
Luna: These comments are
really getting on my nerves!
The way these people judge,
it’s like they actually know Sam
I swear I’m about
to respond to them!
Sevi: Too late. I’m already
replying to some of the comments
It’s so annoying.
Via: Hey, calm down, you two.
Don’t engage, it might
just make things worse.
Kierra: Yeah. We might end up
saying something
that’ll get Sam
into more trouble.
Sevi: What if I make
some dummy accounts?
Luna: Hey, Sevirous. We are not
turning into a troll farm!
Sevi: But I’m really
worried about Sam.
She’s not replying at all.
Kierra: Maybe she’s
not going online.
That might actually be better
than seeing all those
nasty comments.
Luna: @Sam, miss you.
We love you.
Luna: Should we just
go see her?
Sevi: I’m in!
Yanna: I’ll go.
I’m already on my way.
I’m really worried too.
Kierra: It might be better
if Yanna goes first.
Sam might get overwhelmed if
we all show up at once.
Via: Omg Yanna, yes please.
Be there for Sam,
and message us if she says
it’s okay for us to come too.
Luna: Tell her we love her!
Sevi: Let’s just post
encouraging messages for Sam.
- Who’s in?
- Luna: I’m in!
Sevi: Sam is one of the closest
and most generous friends I have.
Whether it’s a night out or
a breakdown, she’s always there.
She even supports me
at my basketball games,
even when I’m playing
against her school.
We love you, Sam!
Luna: Not a lot of
people know this,
but ever since high school,
Sam has always held charity
events every Christmas
or on her birthday.
That’s just the kind of person
she is, genuinely kind-hearted.
She doesn’t post
about it on social media,
but she’s helped
so many people.
Love you, Sam!
Yanna: This is Avi,
my daughter.
I got pregnant with her
while I was in college.
At the time, I didn’t think I
could handle being a mom.
But I felt like I could
get through anything
because Sam was with me.
I used to ask her why she
wouldn’t just deny
being Avi’s mom whenever
people assumed she was.
And she always say,
“Avi is like a daughter to me.”
That’s how much
she loves my child.
That’s how deeply
Samantha Vera loves.
Cy.
I feel guilty.
I feel guilty for thinking
that everyone left me.
I forgot that there are still
so many people who love me.
And I have such great friends.
You know why?
Because you're
a good person, Sam.
That’s why you
attract good people.
I’m tired of crying.
I wanna do something to
take my mind off everything.
But I can’t really
go out right now.
I know a therapeutic activity.
Really?
Really? The therapeutic activity
you’re talking about
is general cleaning?
Believe me.
It’s the best therapy.
Do you sleep with this?
No.
Of course not!
You know, Arah?
My manager.
She bought this as a joke.
One time, I ran out of PJs,
so I wore this.
But that was just one time.
That’s it, okay?
I can imagine.
I love this.
Just you and me
at home together.
Today has been a nice
escape from everything.
Arah: Hey Sam!
I e-mailed your flight details
to New York City.
You’re booked and
ready to go.
This is it Sam!
If only we could
stay like this forever.
Hey.
Should we save
some food for Yanna?
Isn’t she coming back?
No.
When she found
out you were here,
she said you should
take care of me for now.
Too bad, she won’t get
to taste my cooking.
Cy—
I’m leaving for New York
in three days.
Okay.
Give me strength, Naomi.
Hey.
You got this, okay?
Thanks, Cy.
I’m ready.
Samantha Vera, first of all,
how are you?
Honestly, I haven’t been well.
I’m hurt.
It hurts to see my personal life
being treated like
public entertainment.
And that’s why I'm here -
to tell my truth.
First of all, the issues with
my parents will remain theirs.
Like my dad’s lawyer said,
I already cut ties with them,
and I’m still not
ready to face them.
I’m on my healing journey,
and I’m not there yet.
But no matter what happens,
I will never justify or
condone what they did.
Is it true that you went
to New York for a while
to escape your parents’ issues?
No. I went to New York to
continue pursuing my dream—
modeling.
But what about your engagement
with Doctor Clyden Ramirez?
Is it true that supposedly,
it's an arranged marriage?
I’m confirming that I was once
engaged to
Doctor Clyden Ramirez—
the person I admitted
to dating days ago.
At first, the engagement
was forced.
And we didn’t like
each other, but—
we fell in love.
Clyden and I are very different.
Honestly,
his first impression
of me wasn’t even good,
but somehow, we clicked.
Only the two of us
truly understand
what the other
has been through.
We grew together and helped
each other during hard times.
We’re always there
for each other.
But we had to
cancel the engagement
because things were
too messy at the time.
Still, even after all
these years,
Clyden and I remained
each other’s comfort.
The love never left.
That’s why when
we saw each other again—
we just kept finding our way
back into each other’s arms.
That’s nice.
So it’s not true that you were
seeing Haze Juarez and
Clyden at the same time?
No. Never.
Haze is just my friend.
I never confirmed that
we were together.
People just assumed that.
All right. Now that everything’s
been cleared up,
can we say that
your relationship
with Doctor Clyden
has been rekindled?
We tried, but the timing
isn’t right at the moment.
We still have big
dreams to chase.
Nevertheless, we’ll always
have love for each other.
That’s very mature
of both of you, Sam
and Dr. Clyden. I admire
you guys for that.
As much as I don’t
want to overstep,
do you have anything
to say to your family?
I have something
to say to my sister.
I know she’s listening
right now… in the sky.
I want to go there.
Where?
To the moon,
or just beside it.
I wanna be one of the stars.
I love you the most, Naomi.
You’re such a good sister,
a good daughter,
and a good person.
No one could tell you otherwise.
I will continue to
reach for the stars
in hopes that someday,
I can hold you again.
Thank you so much
for your trust, Samantha Vera.
Okay, let’s cut it!
- Thank you, Sam.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- How are you?
- Good.
Thank you, girls.
I owe you one.
Don’t worry, when
we get to New York,
I’ll take you shopping.
No, no, don’t worry about it.
It’s my job, and my job is to
always take care of you, okay?
That’s right. That's why
we’ll never leave you,
because we love you.
Group hug!
Okay, we’ll leave you be.
And I think your knight in
shining armor is waiting for you
Thank you.
Hey.
You did good and
I’m so proud of you.
Everything’s going to be okay.
Thank you.
Sam doesn’t deserve
the hate she received.
#ApologizeToSamNow
There’s always two
sides of every story.
She was mature and
brave in her interview.
She didn’t have to explain.
You know, I’ve been
seeing a lot
of positive comments online.
I guess it really was a good
thing you did that interview.
Right?
People you’ve helped are
starting to speak up, too.
Good! Sevi almost turned
this into a troll farm.
Of course! I’m totally
ready to trash-talk
those bashers, for Sam’s sake!
You guys, seriously, thank you.
I appreciate you all so much.
Hey!
Why are you so quiet, Luna?
I’m just feeling a little sad.
Sam’s leaving for New York,
and then Via’s
leaving soon too.
And I’ll be stuck with
your face every day.
It’s kind of depressing, right?
Oh, come on!
I’ll still visit you guys.
Or come visit me.
Auntie, why are you leaving?
Will I see you soon?
Baby, of course!
Don’t be a bad girl, okay?
Be a good girl to your mom
and your dad, okay?
Okay.
Hey, Yanna. Are you crying, too?
I’m not used to you
not being here.
You’re making me cry, too.
Let me hold you, bestie.
You’re making us all cry.
We’re going to miss you, Sam.
Don’t go.
I have to.
Visit me sometime, okay?
Sorry, I can’t come with
you to the airport.
I can’t watch you leave.
It’s okay.
I don’t want to leave
while crying either.
Take care of yourself,
all right?
Don’t just keep accepting
work non-stop.
And know your limits, too, okay?
You too.
Take care of yourself, okay?
Don’t push yourself too hard;
remember to rest.
You’ll achieve greater things,
but to do that, you
need to stay healthy.
I will.
If you find someone else,
I hope she can
truly make you happy.
And she won’t make
you suffer like this.
I hope she never leaves you,
no matter what happens.
If you find someone else,
I hope he never
makes you cry like this.
I mean it.
I’m serious.
Choose a good woman, all right?
Promise me.
Okay. I promise.
I promise. So, will you
please stop crying?
I will miss you.
See me when you do.
Hey.
Hey. How did you—
I’m heading to Australia.
I have a conference
there in two days.
And I booked an earlier flight
just so I could see you.
You said you didn’t
wanna watch me leave.
I don’t.
But I want to spend
more time with you.
Even just for an hour.
Or even just a minute.
I guess it’s time
to say goodbye.
Make sure you eat, okay?
If something’s bothering you,
talk to someone
or message someone.
Don’t ever keep it
all to yourself.
Okay?
Maui, wait.
I just wanna say that I’m really,
really gonna miss you.
It’s time to go now.
You’re finally…
free.
- Sev!
- Welcome back!
You're really so famous now.
Luna!
I miss you!
So, how's your love life?
- Haven't heard anything for a while.
- You know what, guys—
- I’m still single.
- Seriously?
How is she, Doc?
Is it okay for you to be seen with me?
Shouldn’t I be the one asking you that?
Let’s raise our glasses and
toast to this brand-new start.
Welcome to Epitome! Cheers!
Where's your boyfriend?
He's not here yet?
Sam, sweetheart…