[If you don't turn yourself in,
your limbs will rot and you'll die]
[All characters and events are fictional,
and any resemblance is coincidental]
[Scenes with children and animals were filmed
safely under professional supervision]
Why did you ask to see me?
You've been featured on every TV program
covering the Kangseng Serial Murder Case.
You were involved
in the investigation too, right?
I thought you might know
whether I'm the real killer or not.
My opinion doesn't matter.
Your DNA has already been identified,
Mr. Lee Yong Woo.
I'm not sure about that....
Why do you keep denying the crimes?
The statute of limitations
has already expired,
and you won't be punished for this anyway.
Then why are the police digging up a case
beyond the statute of limitations?
You won't be able to convict me anyway.
This isn't about convicting you.
We just want to uncover the truth.
Nine innocent victims,
and their families
who were forced to let them go.
On top of that,
everyone who lived in Kangseng
back then
has the right to know the truth.
Because it changed so much of their lives.
Well,
that makes sense.
[Confession is the beginning of forgiveness,
and forgiveness opens the door to salvation]
But still, it wasn't me.
I didn't do it.
All right then.
Are you leaving already?
I'll come again tomorrow.
Stay out of my sight as much as possible.
It won't take long!
[Episode 2]
I don't plan on staying here long anyway.
Kang Tae Joo!
I'll take this case back.
And you too.
What?
I will
keep you by my side.
Like back then.
You psycho!
I missed you, Kang Tae Joo.
- You're splashing.
- Darn it.
Tae Joo!
Dead or alive?
Alive!
This is really not fun.
Tae Joo!
It's a joke, just a joke.
- You punk!
- Hey, hey!
Hold on, hold on!
Were you scared? Afraid you got shot?
You punk!
How dare you try to shoot a prosecutor?
Didn't you say we were friends?
Since we are friends...
why not...
It's a joke, just a joke.
A joke?
Well?
Not fun to you?
It wasn't fun to me, either.
Back then, your little jokes
weren't fun at all, either.
[Period for Reporting and Surrendering Spies]
I'll take this case back.
And you too.
Lee Seong Jin.
I got
released today.
It's all thanks to you, Detective.
[Kangseng Police Station]
You've been through a lot.
Live a proper life from now on.
For your mother's sake, at least.
Yes, sir.
I'm really glad
that you came back to Kangseng, Detective.
I really wanted
to tell you this.
Bye.
Well...
Glad?
It has now been confirmed that
the series of murders since October 1986
are connected as a serial killing case.
Yes?
So how many cases are there in total?
As far as we've confirmed so far,
there are four cases in total.
- Go ahead.
- Why is this only being revealed now?
Because the culprit's methods
changed slightly over time,
it took time before we could
make an official announcement,
but a joint police-prosecution task force
has already been formed.
We are doing all we can
to apprehend the culprit.
What do you mean the method changed?
Mr. Hwang is so busy lately.
I can barely see him.
It's killing me too.
All his other cases have been dumped on me.
Handling the student protest cases alone
is enough of a headache.
Why are you handling everything?
What about Mr. Cha?
Hand some of them over to me.
No way. How could I possibly...
It's okay. I've got plenty
of free time these days.
This is exactly when
we should help each other out.
Then, should I
- take the protest case at least?
- Yeah, let him take it.
I'd appreciate that if you would.
Alright, then.
It's been a long time.
Make sure you get a good close shot.
Stay for a meal.
Reporters,
lunch will be served at Seoul Hall
in the town center.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Okay.
I'm about to
lay out a really great spread.
But I don't like the guy holding the spoon.
It takes all the fun out of it.
Then give it to someone else.
I might have to grab a spoon myself then.
Well, are you hungry?
No. I'm already full,
thinking about the scoop I'm about to land.
We're having a scoop?
Clean your lens properly.
You'll be photographing
the arrest of a serial killer.
How would we know when or where
the suspect gets caught?
I know who will catch him.
Sir.
I watched your press conference.
Mr. Cha.
Why did you choose me over Mr. Cha?
I'm curious why you took the longer path
instead of the easy one.
I'm pretty good at reading faces.
Do I have a good one?
More like
that prosecutor over there
just doesn't look promising.
Why? Is there something on my face?
Huh? No, nothing.
So, do you have something to say to me?
Would you please make some time this evening?
I have something to discuss with you.
Ah, I'm not sure.
My son's home for vacation.
Cheol?
Wow, he's already in college.
Time flies!
- It sure does.
- Bring him to the office sometime.
I'd like to meet him.
Yeah, maybe.
Anyway, let's have that meal another time.
"Mom is cooking," done writing?
Yes!
Number 3, "I played with my friend."
"I played with my friend.'"
Good job today.
[Nurturing dreams with learning and love]
Alright, take care on your way.
- I'll get going.
- Bye.
Guys!
- Hello.
You almost got me there.
Oh, that was so close.
I thought I'd actually hit you this time.
Have you eaten?
Let's go grab something to eat.
- I'm hungry.
- You're hungry?
Yeah, with that growling.
They say Tae Joo came back here.
He came home completely wasted.
Life was peaceful while he was away.
Now to think about living
with him again is annoying.
Then,
want to live with me?
Let's get married.
Why are you proposing
in a rice soup restaurant?
Don't say yes.
It's not like that.
Why aren't you answering?
Don't you want to marry me?
I'm not sure.
Ma'am, I said no intestines.
Oh dear, I forgot.
What to do?
I can't swap it now that it's served.
I'll just eat it.
Sorry.
Wait.
I'm not asking you to decide right now.
Think about it carefully.
Wait a moment.
There.
Here.
Go on, have some.
You have some too.
Why are you moping alone?
Is something wrong?
Sang Beom.
Tae Joo is back.
Kang Tae Joo?
Wait, that punk is here?
Darn it.
He's not going to start cracking down
around here again, is he?
You little punk, you scared?
Well, it's not that I'm scared,
but he's a bit...
Anyway, be careful.
He's not someone to mess with.
Back then at least we knew his weakness.
If it's a weakness, we can find another one.
That's right.
[Kangseng Police Station]
Let's start by finding the victims.
But are there any surviving victims?
There aren't any.
No, there haven't been
any attempted murder cases yet.
- Exactly.
- He abducts, rapes, and then kills.
What if things went wrong
before it went all the way?
Attempted kidnapping, or attempted rape?
Or rape.
There's no way there'd be anything like that.
That punk is human too.
You think he never makes mistakes?
Alright, start by looking for any sex crimes
in Kangseng over the past two years
that bear even the slightest
resemblance to this case.
Any unusual details?
- When meeting victims of sexual crimes,
- I don't know.
make sure to bring along a female officer.
Thank you.
Where are we going next?
The end of...
this alley.
Okay, let's go.
There must be a witness
among them who saw him.
- Thank you.
- Eat a lot.
Oh my, Mom.
Looks like you really
like your second daughter-in-law.
I know, right?
Mother, you're making me feel left out.
There's nothing to feel left out about.
Oh dear, you should hurry
and have a baby first.
Mom.
Why talk about babies?
Even Ki Hwan doesn't have one yet.
Have a smart kid
who takes after you instead of him.
That way you won't suffer.
This one's all grown physically
but still just a kid.
Mom, you said I was your favorite, remember?
Ki Beom, did you properly
introduce yourself to Tae Joo?
Not yet.
Why? Does Tae Joo not like him?
No, it's just that
he hasn't hardly been home lately.
Well, with that serial killer case,
he must be swamped.
Yeah.
What kind of bad omen is this
with a wedding coming up?
The bride's family should set the date.
Go introduce yourself properly first.
Got it?
Got it.
Well...
What if Tae Joo doesn't like me?
Doesn't like you?
No way.
He might care about me as his friend's
brother, but maybe not as his brother-in-law.
I don't even have a decent job.
Honestly,
you are too good for me.
I'm the one who hit the jackpot.
Lee Ki Beom.
How many teachers do you think
there are in Kangseng?
I don't know.
About a hundred?
Teachers are common.
Then in Kangseng,
how many men are as handsome as Andy Lau?
Just you.
I'm the one who hit the jackpot, got it?
Comparing me to Andy Lau is a bit much.
Why? I think you're way more handsome.
- Really?
- Yes!
[Kangseng Police Station]
Hey.
Your socks and underwear.
You should've brought more.
How long are you gonna be away?
Go home now.
What kind of clothes are these?
Don't walk alone at night.
I'll tell Ki Beom to walk you home.
Already did.
Really? That's sweet of him.
Since when?
Maybe about three years?
Are you two dating?
We're getting married.
You'll come to my wedding, right?
When is it?
You pick the date. Whatever works for you.
- Wait...
- Gotta go.
- Hello.
- Oh.
Hello, how are you?
What's going on?
She told me
to set the date.
The date for what?
My little sister's wedding day.
- She's getting married?
- Seems so.
That's great news, congrats. And?
Well, I've only ever caught criminals,
but I've never set a wedding date.
Isn't it kind of similar
to catching a criminal?
Really?
What are you idiots even talking about?
Do you want to mess up
such an important family event?
- For a special day like that,
- Yeah.
you go to a good fortune-teller
and set an auspicious date.
Pay them well.
Well... Detective Kang.
I have something to tell you.
Alright.
About a month ago,
on her way home,
she said she was abducted by a man.
With her hands tied behind her back.
Please help me!
Please save me...
- Oh my.
- Oh, no. Are you alright?
Honey, call the police!
Call the police?
Miss, can you stand up?
[Police]
I don't want to report it.
What? Why not?
I'm too scared to do it.
She refused firmly,
so we just escorted her home.
So that's why there's no record.
Her hands were tied behind her back
with a handkerchief too.
I'm sure I told you
that I didn't want to report it.
Well, about that...
Nothing actually happened.
Really.
- But you said you were abducted.
- That's...
But I didn't die.
And nothing terrible happened.
You were lucky.
What kind of 'lucky' woman
goes through something like that?
I can't even be alone at night
because of what happened that day.
If a stranger talks to me,
my whole body freezes.
I can't live normally anymore.
And you call that 'lucky'?
After all, the other victims
didn't survive.
But you did, Ms. Park Ae Sook.
My goodness.
That day,
I was on my way back from a blind date.
We were supposed to have some tea,
but it turned into dinner and went long.
He was a nice guy.
I thought luck was finally
on my side that day.
Did you
happen to see something like a scarecrow?
I think I did.
Where are your stockings?
I...
Darn it.
Yes...
Yes, I have stockings.
I took them off because they were torn.
They're in my purse, I swear.
Your purse?
I dropped it over there earlier.
Stay here.
Okay.
I just knew
if I didn't run then, I would die.
I was so scared.
Afraid that man would come back any moment.
Oh dear, what on earth happened?
Are you alright?
Honey, call the police!
Miss, can you stand up?
Did you see the suspect's face?
I avoided eye contact.
I thought he'd kill me if I didn't.
I know this is hard,
but is there anything else?
Anything you remember helps.
He was thin.
Average height?
Just ordinary.
Did you not report it
because you feared retaliation?
My purse was gone.
The suspect probably took it, right?
My ID was in there.
That means he's got my name and address.
So
how could I report it?
Like you said, Ms. Park,
maybe you weren't lucky after all.
You went through something
you shouldn't have, like the other victims.
But what saved you then
wasn't luck, but yourself.
Your courage, Ms. Park.
When we catch him,
you'll be the first to know.
One more thing,
I'm not sure if this helps,
but that man's hand...
It felt soft... like a woman's hand.
[Kangseng Bookstore]
Hello.
I'm here
to pick up a reference book,
under Yu Jeong Rin.
You are not Yu Jeong Rin.
Do you remember
Jeong Rin?
Yes.
Hey, why are you crying?
Are you okay?
[Map]
It should be around here,
where Ms. Park met him.
It was a month
before Yu Jeong Rin was murdered.
Like you said, he's truly
obsessed with stockings.
He's a complete psycho.
He hides in places like this.
He waits and waits
for the right target.
Then he makes his move.
If he gets spotted,
he plays dead like a scarecrow.
And when the distance closes,
he attacks.
We'll never catch him with patrols alone.
Then...
We make him come to us on his own.
Get everyone
to the conference room. Right now!
Yes, sir.
How could that happen?
Jeong Rin
always kept her promises.
She must've wanted to keep her promise to you
about coming to buy the reference books.
Jeong Rin
had such a good friend.
Mister.
Yeah?
Could you at least remember Jeong Rin's name?
Me?
Jeong Rin would've liked that.
Alright.
Want more?
Yes, please.
That's...
[Please claim your lost items]
Someone must've left it,
but no one's come for it.
Is there any ID inside? Or a wallet?
I haven't opened it.
It's someone else's purse,
so rummaging through it feels wrong.
Well, they'll come get it, right?
You must be getting busy
with the wedding prep.
You've been thinking about your mother
a lot lately, haven't you?
She would be so happy
if she were still alive.
You think so?
- Of course.
- Good work.
Let's have a meal sometime.
Who is that? Even the principal
came out to greet him.
This way.
Ms. Kang Sun Young?
That's you, right?
Wow, didn't expect to see you here.
It's been a really long time,
hasn't it? Right?
Do you know me?
Of course, I do.
Well, you might not remember me.
It's been so long.
Oh my, you must be busy,
yet you even took interest in our school.
[Honesty, integrity, and diligence]
I don't know how to thank you.
This is my alma mater.
I'm happy to be of help.
And the county head is doing well, I hope?
My uncle is always busy.
I'll arrange a meeting sometime soon.
Sounds good.
By the way, how do you know Ms. Kang?
She's my friend's younger sister.
Oh, I see.
He's my high school buddy,
and he is a cop now.
Both siblings turned out well,
given their family's situation.
Family situation?
[Service, courtesy, and order]
Hey, everyone's here, right?
Well...
What are you talking about?
Why should we deal with some student protest?
That's not even our jurisdiction!
The Olympics are next week.
Jurisdiction doesn't matter now.
We get deployed
based on the size of the protest.
Why do you keep changing what you're saying?
Weren't we supposed
to be excluded for a while?
Mr. Heo, you heard that too, right?
Yes, that's right.
I don't know, either.
They say it's the new prosecutor in charge.
They're cracking down hard.
What am I supposed to do about it?
Who's the prosecutor in charge?
[Protect civic order, build a bright society]
Down with dictatorship! Fight for democracy!
Military regime, step down!
[Eradicate corruption]
Step down! Step down!
Down with dictatorship! Fight for democracy!
Military regime, step down!
Step down! Step down!
Down with dictatorship! Fight for democracy!
Military regime, step down!
[Protect civic order, build a bright society]
Step down! Step down!
Down with dictatorship! Fight for democracy!
- You're back?
- Whatever.
Chasing 'reds' by day
and murderers by night.
I'm dead tired.
Would be perfect if the killer
were among them.
Military regime, step down!
- Let's go, back to work.
- Step down! Step down!
- Forward!
- Move forward!
What is this?
What's going on?
[Espionage, Crime, Disaster,
Reporting Center]
You punk!
You little...
- Let go.
- Are you going to kill him?
What's the big deal? He's a commie.
Let go!
What are you doing?
What are you doing right now?
Act like a proper cop!
Not some thug with a badge!
Are you done talking, you punk?
Am I wrong?
You're acting like a street punk.
And what about you?
You got kicked out of Seoul!
Just do what you're told, you punk!
For God's sake, get a grip!
Hey! Stop right there, you punk!
Darn it!
Hey!
We have to go.
This way!
It's definitely Ki Beom.
Why would he...
Hey, you punk!
I lost him because of you!
Lost him?
Darn it!
How could you lose him?
Detective Do, I told you!
We can't afford to lose him.
I'm sorry, sir.
What are you waiting for? Go after him.
Yes, sir.
Was it you?
The one who pulled our station officers here?
Do you have any idea
what we're working on right now?
This is just as serious
as the serial killings.
It's a matter of national security!
Don't you ever
drag our detectives into this again.
Detective Kang.
You keep forgetting.
I'm the prosecutor
before I'm your friend.
- You!
- Wait!
I'm really annoyed too
in this situation.
[Kangseng Bookstore]
Tae Joo!
Why did you go there?
Why did I go where?
So I'm supposed to just
watch those students get beaten?
You might get hurt.
If I see you at a place like that again,
I'll lock you up then.
Remember that.
A sting operation?
[Investigation Team 2]
Yes.
The plan is simple.
We draw the suspect out
from wherever he's hiding
onto the street.
So you're suggesting
a female officer as bait.
- Yes, exactly.
- But how do we know where he'll show up?
As you know, he's got weapon.
No one knows what might happen
during the operation.
Anyone who doesn't want in can step out.
Sir, we're police too.
We really want to catch the suspect.
Me too!
One woman and two men.
Each team will consist of
at least three people.
The suspect has a habit of
disguising himself as a scarecrow.
If you see a scarecrow,
be sure to check it.
Good work.
Miss!
- Oh, Hye Jin!
- Kook Hee was taken away in an ambulance!
She was hit by a motorcycle
in front of the school.
- Which hospital?
- Probably Jeil Hospital nearby.
Let's take my car.
- Okay.
- Come here.
Let's go home. My goodness.
Hey, come with me!
Let's go!
Sun Young...
Thank goodness,
it didn't get any worse.
It's a relief.
She'll be discharged soon.
I'll drive you back.
It's okay. No need.
Come on. We're going the same way anyway.
Well, then...
[Closed]
Why does he keep blowing up the phone?
He said Sun Young got into
some guy's car and went away.
What?
What kind of car?
A Grandeur.
Pretty nice.
Sun Young isn't the type to go for money.
She cares about looks.
Oh, come on.
My mother always says
beauty doesn't last a few years anyway.
You can't live off looks.
There must be a reason.
Don't you trust Sun Young?
That's not it.
Hey,
who took this out?
What's that drawing?
Don't touch other people's things!
A customer left it behind.
[Kangseng Police Station]
Ms. Lee, you're off today's operation.
No, it's okay. I can do it.
You can't even walk properly,
- so how would you do it?
- But...
Just stay.
I can do it.
Have a seat.
Then what about our team today?
Mr. Park.
Want to try wearing a skirt?
It might suit you.
That's a bit...
Hey!
Got a substitute.
A substitute?
I'll do it.
I did good, right?
Mr. Heo, did you forget
this operation is classified?
She agreed to keep it confidential.
Mr. Heo, how can you trust a reporter...
Ouch!
You!
Take me off if you want.
I'll blow this wide open
in tomorrow's papers.
Sorry.
It's fine.
Don't wear stockings.
And Seo Ji Won, you listen carefully.
When you're out there,
if you see anything suspicious
like a scarecrow, run away immediately.
Suspicious scarecrow?
It might be the suspect.
Wow, your place is really close to mine.
From now on, ride in my car, okay?
No, thank you. But I appreciate the thought.
Why? The streets are scary
at night these days.
My fiancé picks me up
every day, so it's fine.
Oh, you are getting married?
Yes.
Congratulations.
What kind of family is he from?
Just an ordinary family.
Then, does his family know
about your mother?
Pardon?
I'm not trying to pry. It just came up.
Oh dear, don't worry.
I won't tell anyone about this.
I'm good at keeping my mouth shut.
So who do you take after, Sun Young?
Your mother?
Oh, right?
You must have gotten your pretty face
from your mother.
Let me out.
Why all of a sudden?
You're making this awkward.
Let me out. I'm uncomfortable.
What did I even do to make you uncomfortable?
Sun Young.
Is that what you think of me?
That's insulting.
I'm not someone
who deserves to be treated like that.
Do you even know
what kind of family I come from?
Do you know who my uncle is?
Calm down and stop the car!
Who are you to give orders?
You, daughter of a tramp!
Stop the car now!
Let go!
Stop the car!
Hey, let go!
You wench! Get over here.
Oh, it's chilly.
Why did he insist on no stockings?
A scarecrow...
There was a scarecrow.
And I think I heard stray dogs too.
Stray dogs.
No way.
When you're out there,
if you see anything suspicious
like a scarecrow, run away immediately.
Suspicious scarecrow?
It might be the suspect.
Police.
It's okay. Calm down.
Police, police.
I'm police.
It's okay now, it's okay.
You're safe now.
Where did that punk go?
Where is he?
Why are you here?
- Where is Ji Won?
- She's not here?
That's him!
Mr. Park, look after her
and go to the car first.
Report our location.
Yes, sir.
Ji Won!
Seo Ji Won!
Seo Ji Won! Answer me!
Ji Won!
Ji Won, wake up!
Seo Ji Won!
Ji Won!
Hey, stay with me!
Hey, Ji Won. Seo Ji Won!
Ji Won!
The surgery went well,
but whether there's brain damage is still...
Tae Joo.
I'll stay here, so you should...
I think you should go.
Where should I go?
Hey.
Your sister
is in this hospital.
Sun Young...
[Kang Sun Young]
Sun Young!
What on earth...
Still no word?
Wait, have you checked everywhere
he might've gone?
That's...
Sir.
Do you have time?
Yeah, I'll call you later.
I have something important to tell you...
Oh, come on!
What on earth could be so urgent
for you to make this big a fuss over?
Sir.
It will only take a moment.
Hey, you punk!
Relax, relax!
Listen.
Hey, lift your head.
Relax!
You punk!
Hyeon Cheol!
Hyeon Cheol, stay with me!
Dad...
Yeah,
I'm here.
What on earth happened here?
I told you to make some time for me, sir.
Was it you?
You're the one who did this to my son?
Sir, it's not about Hyeon Cheol
getting hit a few times.
Did you know
your son committed a serious violation
of the National Security Law?
What?
If you knew and turned a blind eye,
this won't be something
we can contain within the prosecution.
You punk!
Is it true the serial killer showed up today?
Has he been caught yet?
Let's leave before this gets any louder.
Jeez, how did things end up like this?
So she's the daughter of a bar madam.
I'm quite shocked as well.
- Hey!
- Stop!
- Stop it!
- What's going on?
Hey, what are you doing?
Hold back the reporters!
Block them!
Someone help!
- Hey, you punk!
- Stop it!
[Police officer arrested
for assaulting an active teacher]
What are you going to do about this?
Why are you targeting innocent people
instead of the real criminal?
He's not exactly innocent.
What?
But arresting Detective Kang?
How can you arrest someone
before an investigation?
Why not? He got caught red-handed.
After what happened to his sister,
what kind of brother wouldn't lose it?
So what, a police officer
can just beat a civilian?
And even in front of reporters?
The prosecutor in charge already
issued the arrest warrant, so what can we do?
- Officer Jeong.
- Yes.
Let me use the phone, quickly.
Come on, quickly.
No, you can't.
Bring it now!
Bring it, come here, Ji Hwan.
Hurry up.
I really can't.
It's fine.
Bring it here. Darn it.
I'll be quick.
This is a total mess.
Hey, bring it here!
Put the phone down.
I'll be quick.
Sorry, Mr. Kang.
Prosecutor Cha Si Young.
There's a critical patient.
I just need to check the patient's condition.
Calling won't wake her up.
Go get questioned.
On what?
The assault on Jeon Kyeong Ho.
That's my jurisdiction.
Jeez.
Are you seriously
going to lock me up over that?
You think the case is going
to be handed to you now?
It's already mine.
What?
I told you.
I'd take it back.
You, and the case.
He still hasn't come?
Well, he's exercising.
Exercising?
Yes, inmate 1045
has a morning exercise routine.
He'll be done soon, so please wait a little.
Lee Yong Woo is sure diligent.
He's like that about everything.
Health, woodworking, all of it.
I see.
Oh dear, I'm a little late...
Where did he go?
- Gone.
- Gone?
Yes, he said he'd come tomorrow afternoon.
So it doesn't interfere
with your workout routine.
Let's go, officer.
Detective Kang Tae Joo is being removed
from all investigations, effective today.
Let's just take his resignation
quietly and end it.
Don't worry.
I don't care about means or methods, either.
Do you really have to quit being a cop?
[Kangseng Bookstore]
Just catch him for me, sir.
Any last words?
Make sure to catch that punk
before he kills anyone else.
Sir!
Well, the body... It's another murder.
We found it!