(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
(All characters, places,
and organizations are fictional.)
(Children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
You did great.
The reason I asked to meet...
As you know, I was looking after
Jin Ju for a few years.
I think we should hold
her 49th-day memorial service.
- She's not dead.
- But there are no signs of her...
You think I don't know my own kid?
How would he know?
He never even raised her.
She's not the type to throw her life away.
She's putting on an act.
Would you write a suicide note
just as an act, sir?
Her eyes were sparkling.
With eyes like that,
she wouldn't take her own life.
Is he a face reader now?
You even brought cake?
Where'd you get this cake? It's amazing.
I'm not telling.
Just let me know when you're craving it.
What if I crave it every day?
I'll bring it to you every day.
Do you have so much time on your hands?
I have Manager Yoon
and Mr. Kim, the driver.
It's time to let go of Jin Ju.
In the end,
everyone goes their separate ways.
Look at me.
I'm doing just fine without my parents.
Pickles, did you hear that?
We'll take good care of you.
With love.
I can't believe I have my own dog.
Thanks, Yong Joong.
You're the one who made me want a dog.
I wasn't really interested before.
Just let me know
if it ever becomes a bother.
Once I get my heart set on something,
I don't change my mind.
I'm not sure if that's good or bad.
I guess his feelings for Momo
won't change either.
Is that a bad thing?
I don't know.
So you think it's one of my flaws.
Nobody's perfect.
What are my flaws?
I'll fix them if you tell me.
I've never thought about it.
I don't think you have any. None at all.
But aren't flaws what make us human?
Are you saying I'm human,
or that you aren't?
Interpret it how you want.
Well, if I'm the one who's human,
that means I have flaws you can point out.
So do you consider yourself not human?
To be honest, there are times
I feel less than human.
I had to live that way to get by.
Nothing ever came easy for me.
Like cracking a whip on my own soul?
I guess I was always very hard on myself.
That doesn't make you less human.
It's not like you were a burden to others.
You just did your absolute best.
From now on,
you should take care of yourself, too.
I know what you mean.
You deserve love...
and recognition, my little lady.
- Would you like an Americano?
- I've already had several cups.
How about a small 49th-day memorial
for Jin Ju, just among ourselves?
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
Goodbye.
Her "father" won't hold the service,
claiming she's alive.
Can you believe it?
And the police have already
closed the case.
He must not want to believe it.
Should we just do it
with her memorial tablet?
We should probably have
something she wore, though.
I wonder if Momo will come.
(Ba Ra)
Hey, Ba Ra.
- Is this a good time to talk?
- Of course.
I talked it over with James,
and we're holding a 49th-day memorial
for Jin Ju.
I was calling to see if you could come.
My 49th-day memorial?
But no pressure if you don't want to.
When is it?
Saturday, 2 p.m. at Eunkyungsa Temple.
Jin Ju was always so good to you.
She really was.
- The temple in Gapyeong?
- That's the one.
I'll drive you.
So you're coming?
Yes.
It's not like she was just anybody.
We should leave by noon, then.
Got it.
Thanks.
Don't mention it.
The articles are all over the news sites.
Have you seen them?
Yes. The trolls are having a field day.
I have to write one too. My editors...
Write whatever you want. It's okay.
Go ahead and make it even harsher.
I know everything there is to know
about Momo.
Why so flustered?
We were engaged, you know.
That was a difficult surgery,
so pull yourself together.
Yes.
And stop walking on eggshells around me.
Okay.
Open.
Look.
Deity,
is this really happening?
Yong Joong.
I came to pick you up.
Pickles!
You're so cute.
That's heavy.
Your shoulders are going to get lopsided.
You can take my other car today.
You're just asking for rumors.
Tell them you found a sugar daddy.
I'll walk him a bit. You go on up.
- Why?
- Because that's heavy and in the way.
Right.
Let's go.
They say dogs take after their owners,
so who do you think is his owner?
Should we try it? See who he comes to?
No, don't put him on the spot.
I might have been hurt
if you'd said hi to Pickles first.
Come on, you're not that petty.
I'd be hurt. It's not about being petty.
Your heart is as big as the ocean.
Spoken like a true reporter.
Most people in Gen MZ wouldn't even know
that expression.
Am I laying it on too thick today?
You're always laying it on thick.
Yong Joong.
What did you do?
This night
I will send the fireflies of that day
Near your
Window
Pane
I don't think I'll ever forget tonight.
It means
I love you
I remember
When we first met
And so
Whenever I close my eyes
I go to the most
Distant place
I guess I'll have to make lots of memories
with you.
But you can't force memories.
That doesn't count.
It wouldn't be forced.
Were you a good son? Or a rebel?
A bit of both?
Well, to me, you were the sweetest guy
in the world.
I love you.
Pickles.
She just blew off my "I love you."
I chewed it into tiny pieces
and swallowed.
I'm filled to the brim with love.
If I say even one word,
I'm afraid some of it might spill out.
- Why the sigh?
- This must be how dads feel.
You really haven't dated anyone
all this time, have you?
If you had, some other guy would be
next to you right now, not me.
No guy in his right mind
could ever leave you.
That kind of sounds like an insult.
Don't you go flirting with anyone but me.
Am I flirting? Is that what I'm doing?
- No.
- You said you didn't see me as a woman.
You said I was your little sister.
Is that something you'd say
to your little sister?
- That's not what I meant.
- What about me blowing off your love?
And calling me a flirt
just for winking at you?
To me, it's a wink,
but other guys might see it
as you flirting.
Not everyone's as innocent as me,
you know.
Right, you're just overflowing
with purity.
I've had my fill of pure, innocent love,
thanks.
So go pour it all out on Momo
to your heart's content.
Geum Ba Ra.
Are you really that mad?
Sorry. I didn't grow up with sisters,
so I don't really get it.
Didn't you say you dated older girls
in high school?
- Twice.
- And Momo?
It's just a one-sided crush.
At last year's Appreciation Night,
was Momo so captivating...
that you're still not over her?
What was so great about her?
That she's pretty?
Or a good dancer?
I don't know,
it was like an electric shock.
Like a...
jolt.
In your heart?
In your body?
If I'd had no self-control,
I would have held her.
Or grabbed her hand and ran off with her.
It was that intense?
I can't hide anything from you.
When I wake up in the morning,
I wake up thinking of Momo.
It's the same when I go to sleep.
Then you should just get it
off your chest.
- You want me to be a scumbag to Ju Shin?
- They're not married yet.
I can't just live my life
based on my own feelings.
Imagine if everyone did that.
What would the world come to?
It'd be chaos, with no morality.
But later,
if, by some chance,
she and Ju Shin break up,
what then?
Then, I'd be honest.
Without a second thought?
What else would matter?
Liking someone...
doesn't require reasons or conditions.
If only the one...
he was talking about were me...
Hey, he's pooping.
Go home and stay there.
The Cheongdam-dong house.
Don't even go near Hyeonmi-dong.
Okay.
As of now, Kim Jin Ju no longer exists.
Be extra careful
when you're around Geum Ba Ra.
Her job is one thing,
but she's also naturally perceptive.
You're right.
I just don't think
we should jump right into it now.
You'd need to be mentally prepared.
From now on,
I'm going to love you, too, Holy Father.
- Hello?
- This is Paul Kim.
About my piece from the other day...
Yes, Mr. Kim.
I put it up at my place,
and it looks amazing.
I'm glad.
Listen, the reason I'm calling is...
I saw the news a while back
about Kim Jin Ju going missing...
You know Kim Jin Ju?
I do. It's a bit of a long story.
Your studio's in Yangpyeong, right?
I'm in Seoul at the moment.
Where in Seoul?
Why don't you come over to my place?
Would that be okay?
Of course.
You can see your piece on display.
Goodness. So?
We did a DNA test, and we weren't a match.
I have a long story myself.
Kim Jin Ju's biological father showed up.
- Really?
- Yes.
The news didn't get into the specifics,
but I think she did what she did
because of her biological father.
(Kim Jin Ju 0342)
I guess her door code changed.
So you're running an errand
for my daughter?
To pick up her things?
No. Her 49th-day memorial service
is the day after tomorrow,
and I need to get an outfit of hers.
Where are you holding the service?
At Eunkyungsa Temple in Gapyeong.
In any case,
this whole thing feels like a setup...
I think you need to accept it.
- I know it's hard to believe...
- What is there to accept?
You tell my daughter...
that I'm going to find her no matter what.
Sir, I need her outfit...
I'm in the spot where Momo used to sit.
(Jaeil Apartments)
You look so elegant.
I went to get an outfit of hers,
but I couldn't even enter
because of Jin Ju's dad.
He's actually living there?
Yes.
He even had a DNA test done.
What are we supposed to say?
Technically, it's his daughter's house.
How did he get a DNA test?
Without her even being there?
He used Jin Ju's toothbrush.
They said it was a perfect match.
James confirmed everything too.
Jin Ju said that
when the weather was nice,
she wanted to go to an arboretum.
I just can't believe it.
She had such a strong will to live.
"Will to live?"
You know how many things she wanted to do.
If you knew her so well,
why were you so cold to her?
- Coffee.
- Okay.
Do we have to leave money when we bow?
I think so. I brought some just in case.
Feeling cheap?
I don't have to go in, right?
You worked with her for years,
and you won't even bow once?
(Kim Jin Ju)
Of all the pictures,
they had to use that one.
So tacky.
(Minjin Church)
(God Loves You)
(A Place of Dreams and Love)
(Please be sure to write down
the name and date of birth)
(Baby Box)
Jin Ju, you've had this
since you were a baby.
Hey.
I said look.
What was your connection to the deceased,
Momo?
She was my stylist.
The monk performing the rites
is very devout.
I'm sure her spirit has passed
on peacefully.
Master. Mr. Park is about to leave.
Excuse me for a moment.
Okay.
Didn't you want to cry?
You two grew up together at the orphanage.
It still doesn't feel real to me either.
The human heart is a funny thing.
Since her biological father
keeps saying she isn't dead,
and it's not like we saw a body,
I feel like she's really alive somewhere.
All signs suggest she fell into the ocean,
so how are we supposed to confirm it?
You're right.
Anyway, it's a shame
to die in the prime of her life.
It's like she never even had a chance
to fall in love.
My love has begun with Director Shin.
I found a Korean place nearby
with good reviews.
Eat something before you go.
I already have plans.
A friend invited me to a housewarming,
so I said I was going with you.
I contacted you because...
Kim Jin Ju's business card
had Lim Company.
I was very surprised too.
I was really hoping she was my daughter.
I see. What a strange fate...
That's Korea for you.
Word just spread from one person...
Are you leaving now?
Yes. You need your rest.
This is relaxing for me.
Please call me whenever you are in Seoul.
If you ever have a reason
to come to Yangpyeong...
Will one be enough
for her spirit to find peace?
A very devout monk performed the rite.
Please, wait a little bit.
Let me prepare something for you to eat.
- No, there's a place nearby...
- There are no decent restaurants nearby.
I'm a pretty decent cook myself.
And for wine?
Should we?
Today calls for it.
- We'll do the pairing.
- Very good.
We could've just eaten with James,
I wanted to talk, just the two of us.
Honestly, Mr. Ha talks way too much.
It's exhausting.
I guess I'd gotten
really attached to Jin Ju.
I just suddenly burst into tears.
I've gotten weaker after my mom died.
But I'm glad you pulled yourself together.
I figured you'd want to be alone,
so I didn't contact you.
But I was always worried about you.
Yes.
What's your annual salary?
You make 50,000 dollars?
After taxes and what I put into savings,
I'm not left with much.
Help me out.
Anything.
Quit your job and come work for me.
Yes?
But you have Manager Oh.
He's my business manager.
I wish you'd be by my side.
I don't want anyone else.
I'll double, no, triple your salary.
It's not about the money...
But you said you worried about me.
Do you really need me, specifically?
I do.
I could quit acting in a heartbeat
if someone close to me wanted me to.
- Let me think about it.
- That's just a nice way of saying no.
Am I wrong?
My seniors are finally recognizing me,
so just quitting out of the blue...
And it's been my life goal
since I was a kid.
It's a great career, I'll give you that.
But even if you prove your talent,
don’t you just end up
an old critic in the end?
Isn't being a gallery director
better than that?
Plus, there's no mandatory retirement age.
Just help me recover for 2 to 3 years,
and then the gallery is all yours to run.
You already know so many experts
in the art and cultural scene.
She's running late.
Don't think about it for too long.
Okay.
Bye.
Thanks, anyway.
I'll take that as a yes.
I envy you.
Why?
Everyone loves you...
And Yong Joong does too.
Things aren't always what they seem
on the surface.
(Contacts: Geum Ba Ra)
Hey.
Pickles and I are at your front door.
You're here?
It's the same number code as your place.
Have you been drinking?
With Momo.
It's hitting me now
since I'm home and can relax.
Hey, Pickles.
A last-minute workout was scheduled
for tomorrow.
How much did you have?
A wine pairing. Six glasses.
Yes, that'll do it.
And Momo?
She's been fine.
Drink this.
Leave it.
Is something bothering you?
Feeling queasy?
A little nauseous.
Go. I don't want you to see me this way.
Why not?
You must have seen Momo.
Yes.
Should I ask her to come back?
She can't have gone far.
Go on inside and lie down properly.
Do you want me to stay?
- Why?
- I feel like I should be here for you.
You seem like you're struggling.
Is it that obvious?
Whatever it is, you can tell me.
I don't want to.
I don't hide anything from you, you know.
I'm a little hurt.
I'm way more hurt than you are.
About what?
There's a difference between hiding things
and not expressing it.
You're not expressing yourself?
To me, of all people?
The bold Geum Ba Ra?
You think I'm bold?
That's just how I come across.
Never mind. I'm not upset.
Really?
If I hadn't come,
you'd have fallen asleep here, right?
No, I have to shower before I can sleep.
All right, I'll go then.
Go get cleaned up.
But you said you were staying.
Okay. Pickles and I will sleep out here.
Pickles?
Will you leave in a few hours
before the sun rises?
Yes. It's a business meeting,
so I can't miss it.
Don't you have any medication?
No.
Momo and I were catching up over drinks.
I don't want to sober up.
You want to know what we talked about,
don't you?
Stock the fridge with some food.
I'll come pick you up tomorrow evening.
If things get tough, call me anytime.
Isn't it pretty?
Where'd you get it?
Why does that matter?
I bought it for you.
Where'd you get the money?
The woman sponsoring me.
But she told me
to call her by her first name.
You wear it.
It looks prettier on you.
I wish we could grow our hair out.
The first thing I'll do
when I get out is grow my hair out.
Me too.
Oh, dear.
Hey, do you know the song "Mom"?
No.
Last night, Su Bin...
was crying while listening to that song.
Mom.
I wonder what it feels like
to call someone that.
How about we close our eyes
and pretend to call for our moms?
How?
Just close them.
I'll call out, and you answer me.
Mom.
Mom?
Your turn.
Come on.
Mom.
Why are you making your little sister cry?
She's not my sister. We're friends.
How old are you?
Twelve.
But she looks so little for her age.
She's a picky eater.
You must eat well to grow big and strong.
Don't be a picky eater.
I'll buy you a treat.
What a sweet friend.
To think I treated her so well.
And all she cares about is Momo.
(Geum Ba Ra)
Yong Joong, is now a good time to talk?
Hello?
Yong Joong.
- Yes.
- Momo asked me to quit...
and work for her.
Really?
But I'm not going to.
That's the right call, right?
You worked so hard to become a reporter.
- Yes.
- I'm so proud of you.
Is that why you adore me?
Am I?
Or was I just imagining it?
We're in love.
It's more than just being fond of you.
Don't say things like that in public.
People won't understand.
Does it matter what other people think?
Bye.
I love you. Sleep well.
You too.
I held on all this time
just for that tramp.
You have no idea who I am.
Send the van away. I'll take you.
Your limit is three glasses of wine.
Don't drink any more than that.
Are you still uncomfortable around me?
You look good in black.
Are you on mute?
Say something.
Those two nurses who can't speak,
what is their relationship?
- Brother and sister?
- No. What makes you think that?
They both ended up at the orphanage,
and my dad found out
they were both in that state.
He had us take special care
of them at our home.
We basically raised them.
Your father is such an admirable person.
They've never forgotten his kindness.
They'll do anything I ask.
As they should.
How much can Geum Ba Ra drink?
She had the same pairing as me today.
And things like dining etiquette,
did she learn them deliberately?
From James.
He often took her to
high-end restaurants, too.
You have an appointment with Attorney Kim
on Monday at two.
Review everything carefully
before you sign.
It's a good thing your signature
is simple, at least.
Darn it.
She's not dead.
You end your life,
but you don't even leave
a single picture behind?
My, it's beautiful.
I haven't even tried it on yet.
The smell of kimbap.
The star is starving to death,
and you're wafting food smells everywhere.
- I was so hungry...
- What about me?
You had snacks earlier.
Putting on a show for everyone?
Your dark circles are terrible.
You didn't sleep again, did you?
I was shooting a commercial until dawn.
It's a good problem to have.
You really have it all.
Everything except a Prince Charming.
There are princes all over the world
just waiting for you to pick one.
You didn't take the ice out.
You know I only take
exactly three ice cubes.
Seriously? You still don't know
after four months?
Witch.
Don't you ever think
Geum Ba Ra is a little too smart?
What's wrong with being smart?
That's because you
don't really know women.
I guess not as well as you do.
A person can't hide their character
or their aura.
Besides, to me, Ba Ra isn't a woman.
She's like a kid sister.
Do you think she feels the same way?
I've known her since she was 11.
Not consistently, you haven't.
People don't change.
They say you have to be reborn to do that.
If that's the case,
then everyone has been reborn, right?
But is everyone in the world
conscientious and kind?
Remember what I told you
about the great monk?
He said a person only changes
through spiritual training.
Even if you're reincarnated 10,000 times,
you won't change without that training.
Other than not having parents...
Which isn't a flaw. It's not her fault.
Her heart, her actions,
everything about her is proper.
And the things she does are endearing.
Anyway,
I just hope I never have to call her
my sister-in-law.
Don't worry.
Either way, don't be so prejudiced
against people.
- Good shot.
- Nice one.
- What's with this sudden rain?
- Quick, an umbrella, an umbrella!
- Bring the umbrellas! Umbrellas!
- Was it supposed to be this bad?
Hang on, take your swing again
under the umbrella.
- It's raining so hard.
- Here's an umbrella.
Goodness!
Geum Ba Ra.
Pickles.
(Yong Joong)
The person you have called is unavailable.
Please leave a message after...
Goodness!
I thought you'd be here.
I thought you two came together.
It was pouring, so we cut our game short.
Your scream startled me
more than the thunder.
I'm actually a little afraid of the rain.
You're afraid of the rain?
Yes.
- What can I get you?
- Sparkling water.
I'll have the same.
I came to make you jjajangmyeon. Surprise!
Where's Pickles?
In the living room.
He's not here.
- Pickles.
- Pickles!
Pickles!
- Pickles.
Goodness.
Dogs get scared of thunder.
Oh, Carrie?
That chihuahua James used to have.
- Her name was Oiji, right?
- Yes.
Aren't you hungry?
Starving.
- You should eat with us.
- Drop the formalities.
We're friends.
Just give me a minute.
I just need to stir-fry it up.
- Anything I can do to help?
- No, I'm good.
Just hire a live-in housekeeper.
That'd make me uncomfortable.
Here.
A friend of my dad's
runs a traditional medicine clinic.
He made this with his best ingredients
before passing the practice on to his son.
I don't take herbal medicine.
Still, he went to the trouble
of having it made for you.
- I don't need a health tonic.
- What, and you think I do?
Just take it.
It's got deer antler, agarwood, and musk.
All the best ingredients.
You said you liked this watch, right?
I bought one too.
How'd you get your hands on one?
If I want something, I get it.
You managed to get one, after all.
(Let the Duel Begin)
- That smells incredible.
- It's ready!
This is the real deal.
No guarantees on the taste, though.
The rain stopped.
It was coming down so hard too.
You did all this by yourself?
That's a lot of work.
It was nothing.
This is so much better than the hotel's.
It's not too sweet.
Pickles, go eat your own food.
Is this a recipe you found online?
Or did a chef teach you?
It's my own recipe, just how I like it.
A Geum Ba Ra original?
I wanted to thank you properly
for everything.
It's just a humble meal.
- Repay me for what?
- For that fancy, belated birthday dinner.
Did I cook it myself?
Even if the housekeeper made it,
the thought counts.
Can a woman take this tonic?
He said it was formulated for men.
I'll open a Chinese restaurant for you.
Hello?
- James. Hi.
- Do you think I could get an MRI?
Why? Are you feeling unwell?
I've been feeling a little dizzy.
Is it bad?
- How bad?
- It's not too bad.
And I had a bit of a headache
the day before yesterday.
We're fully booked,
so squeezing you in is tough.
I can do it early in the morning
or late at night.
Morning's best, even if it's early.
Okay, I'll check and send you a text.
Thank you.
I'm sure it's nothing serious.
If he had a burst blood vessel
or was having a stroke,
the headache would be extremely severe.
My brother's a bit of a hypochondriac.
That's a good thing, though.
- A cocktail?
- Not quite a cocktail.
There's wine in here.
Wine and two other things.
This is pretty good.
Without the housekeeper,
I figured you'd be alone.
I felt bad, so I came by to surprise you.
Was it okay?
It was perfect. Thank you.
If you're not drinking that, give it here.
You'll get drunk drinking that fast.
Getting drunk is for girls.
You don't have to force yourself
to drink it.
If you don't like it.
Just leave the dishes.
I already put them in the dishwasher.
Let's go to the grocery store.
(Manager, Nua Children's Home)
- It's me.
- Director.
Please email me Geum Ba Ra's file.
- Everything you have on her.
- Understood.
We'll run the scan,
but I'm sure it's nothing.
That would be a relief.
Take this after your scan.
- Herbal medicine?
- Yes.
I gave Yong Joong some too.
So enjoy all of it to yourself.
I'll enjoy it.
How did you know I love this stuff?
Sorry to make such a fuss
on your rare day off.
You personally came on a house call.
(Hope and Happiness Pharmacy)
Hi, how can I help you?
A pregnancy test, please.
That's five dollars.
What was up with Ju Shin
in the kitchen earlier?
My scream probably startled him
into doing something out of character.
He's probably kicking himself for it now.
I was the one who freaked out.
I thought it was you.
Are you that scared of rain?
This kind of rain, yes.
Especially with the thunder and lightning.
So what do you do when you're alone?
I just deal with it.
That can't be good for your heart.
Shouldn't you go check on James?
I'll stop by after I drop you off.
Yong Joong.
James told me to call him my big brother,
but I can't bring myself to say it.
Then don't force it.
Besides me, even Ju Shin...
Of course not.
The Director wouldn't allow it.
All the kids at the orphanage
adored the Director.
Especially Jin Ju.
He had this incredible aura about him.
Ju Shin?
Yes.
What about me?
You're all warmth and charm.
Aura versus warmth.
People are more drawn to that human side.
At least, I am.
Pickles will be waiting.
Let's pack this up to go.
You can make amazing black bean noodles,
but you keep your fridge totally empty.
Thank you. I'll really enjoy this.
Pickles, let's go.
(Student's detailed school record,
Student Record 2)
(Name: Geum Ba Ra)
(Awards, Awarding institution:
Principal of Minjin Elementary School)
I'm sorry.
Considering your future,
we've agreed to tell everyone
that you're annulling the adoption.
Don't let on, though.
I'll tell the Office Manager the truth...
and clear your name.
Hey, Yong Joong.
I love how you always answer right away.
It's weird. You only ever seem to call
when I'm free to answer.
Can you video chat?
Yes.
- Call for him.
- Pickles!
Where's that sound coming from?
Where is she?
- He's not interested.
- Pickles looks drained.
I played with him for a while.
You can't just think of your own stamina.
He's 9kg, and you're over 70, right?
I'm 75kg.
How is that even a fair match?
Have you showered yet? Are you done?
I was about to.
I've seen it all, so what's there to hide?
You look pretty.
One of your many great qualities...
is giving unconditional compliments.
I'm just telling the truth.
- Hey!
- What?
He's peeing while staring right at me.
Are you jealous?
- I'm hanging up.
- Okay.
Who's that this late?
I don't know. Let me call you back.
- No, don't hang up.
- Okay.
It's Momo. I'm hanging up.
Okay.
I didn't come here to be turned down.
Wouldn't it be better to just hire
another assistant instead of me?
What if they leak my private life online?
How can you trust someone
without getting to know them first?
Who were you drinking with?
You're the only one...
I can trust and rely on now.
(Pregnancy Test)
(Fast, easy, and 99 percent accurate)
- Hello?
- Is the party over?
Yes, I just got home.
Nurse Park will be there in 20 minutes.
Get a ride with him.
Where are we going?
Did you have fun?
It was fine.
It's from the garden.
When are you going to stop
that lip-licking habit?
Right away. Never again.
I can't let a senior
go to the hospital alone.
A lady once said a young guy
was giving her an attitude.
So she went, "I've been young before.
I know what youth is."
"But have you ever been old?"
"I have."
"So don't act so high and mighty
when you don't know a thing about aging."
The fact that you’re hurt shows
you've really gotten old.
Why, you little...
(Department of Radiology)
What are your thoughts on a brain swap?
Have you ever thought about it?
No, I haven't.
I heard that soon, AI will be able
to transplant entire human heads.
What if it were possible...
to swap only the brain
without changing the face?
By any chance,
are you talking about you, Director?
If it were possible,
who would I swap with?
(Doctor Shin)
- Goodness. Congratulations!
- Congratulations?
What if it were possible...
to swap only the brain
without changing the face?
By any chance,
are you talking about you, Director?
Do you trust people?
I have to, at first.
But I never want to be betrayed.
What if they do?
What's your relationship to her?
- I'm her father.
- I hold all the cards now, don't I?
Have I lost it all now?
You even talk like that?
Don't change the subject.
What's your type?
- Time to go.
- Can't I stay?
I know you're just saying that.
I'm not just saying that.
How dare you lie to me?
Lie?
Why would I?
How can you enjoy strawberries right now?
Like nothing's wrong?
Yes. I must be low on Vitamin C
because they're delicious.
Give me back my brain!
- Director!
- Please, help us!
Shin Ju Shin, you're under arrest
for the murder of Kim Jin Ju.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)