( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
Is that…
No way.
GREETINGS, DEAR SUBSCRIBER
You made it?
Who are you?
Let's see.
Seo Mi-rae, 29, heterosexual.
Right?
Yes.
Would you happen to be an actual person?
I'm your designated dating manager.
Call me Unni if you want.
But where are we?
I mean, what's with all those posters?
Just a sec.
Your hand.
Those who come here
are each given this ring.
It'll appear on you automatically
every time you log in.
Take it off, and you'll log out.
So you're saying this place
is a virtual reality, aren't you?
Yeah.
What about me? Is my body safe at home?
Probably?
All right. Let's get going now.
Where to?
THE MAN YOU THINK YOU KNOW
Enter.
What?
What the…
Wait a second.
This is Choi Si-woo.
Congratulations, Ms. Seo Mi-rae,
on meeting your first date!
I can't believe how handsome he is.
Are you okay?
Oh my God!
Who…
Take it off, and you'll log out.
EPISODE 2
CLICHE OR CLASSIC
BOYFRIEND ON DEMAND
DU showcases its technology.
Experience BoD with all five senses.
Boyfriend on Demand,
coming soon to redefine romance.
Concerns over addiction.
When the door to everyday life closes,
a new door opens,
and the date
you've been dreaming of begins.
Ready for another dreamy day?
This is a place where any romance
you desire becomes reality.
There are 900 themes just for you.
So who will you be dating today?
Min Jun-young, you bastard.
I respect the hell out of you.
When you experience something surreal,
it takes time to process it.
Ms. Seo.
Dong-min told me to bring this to you.
Oh, right. You can leave it there.
-I'll put it here.
-Yeah.
What? You want to move
Hwany's webtoon to Fridays?
Take a look at this.
It's the list of our Friday webtoons.
Don't you think it's outdated?
And just look at the ratings
for The Man to Know.
It's hopeless.
But Hwany's really catching on.
I doubt he'd want to compete with Ms. Yun.
That's why you should just
float the idea to him.
What's wrong? You don't want to?
No, it's not that.
I just don't see why
you'd have two popular authors
competing on the same day.
I have no intention of betting
this company's fate on one person.
Hwany does everything
you tell him to do anyway.
Just mention it to him, okay?
Well?
Sure. I'll do that.
Okay.
-All right. Get back to work.
-Yes, sir.
Sir?
Is Seo Mi-rae also aware of this?
She doesn't need to know.
If Yun Song finds out, we'll be done for!
We'll act first, think later.
I see.
This is uncomfortable.
It's just a drawing.
Get a grip.
NAEMO'S BEST FRIDAY WEBTOON
THE MAN TO KNOW
Was this here before?
CAN I… STAY THE NIGHT?
What?
WANT A SHARPER NOSE THAN A WEBTOON LEAD?
PEOPLE PLASTIC SURGERY
Isn't Choi Si-woo so cool?
I know, right?
THE MAN TO KNOW
THE MAN TO KNOW, VOL. 1
Everywhere I look,
there's Choi Si-woo.
THE MAN TO KNOW
NAEMO'S NO. 1 WEBTOON IN STORES
What? Where am I?
Eun Na-ra, the female lead
of The Man to Know, is a hotelier.
Am I supposed to experience the life
of a female lead in a webtoon?
APPROVAL REQUEST
"General manager"?
GENERAL MANAGER CHOI SI-WOO
It really is him.
He really was Choi Si-woo.
It appears an employee had the nerve
to sit on my desk.
Was I seeing things?
-No, it's just--
-Get out. Now.
What's his problem?
Wait.
I thought you wanted me to leave.
Have we met before?
There it is.
Oh my God. This is insane!
You, you must be from…
That's right.
But how are you here?
Because I work here?
I finally found you.
Ever since the day you saved me…
not a day has gone by
without me thinking of you.
Wait, what's he doing?
I never forgot about you
for a single moment.
I had forgotten
how cheesy The Man to Know was.
That's sweet,
but that came out of nowhere--
Wait.
Let me look for just a moment.
Look at what?
It's here.
What is?
The face I've been longing for
and desperately searching for
in my dreams…
every night.
Oh shit!
Is he deranged?
That's more cringe than anyone can handle.
It's here.
The face I've been longing for
and desperately searching for
in my dreams every night.
I can't take this.
Can't stand the sight of him?
Such disrespect
for a hero going off to war.
Poor Si-woo.
War? What are you on about?
-You haven't seen Hwany's Instagram?
-Nope. Why?
Yikes.
What?
Sir, is it true that Hwany's new title
will now be updated every Friday?
Yes, it is.
-You can't do that without telling me--
-Hey, you're not my boss!
Hwany's a big name. You should've told me!
It's been a while since Yun Song
had some healthy competition.
This is a good thing. It's for the best.
Was this, by chance,
proposed by Producer Park?
No.
It really wasn't.
It's not strong enough.
The ending has to be more impactful.
This is as impactful as it gets.
I might really top the chart at this rate.
You're daydreaming again.
Okay.
If I'm going to make it more impactful,
I'll have to speed up the early scenes.
And the manager scene in the next episode,
why don't we move it up a little?
Come on.
I told you to pick up right away.
You're the one who nudged me
And asked me out, aha
I'm not the one who nudged you
And asked you out, aha
SEO MI-RAE
You lied to me all the time
Saying you couldn't pick up my calls
Because your phone died
I hate you so much, aha
Say no more
And just hang up the phone
Hang up!
I don't want to talk…
Ms. Yun, why won't you answer your phone?
My phone is crying, and so am I
Holy crap! What the hell?
-What are you doing?
-Come outside.
You're hurting me! That hurts!
Seriously!
Are you out of your mind?
Hey, how did you know where to find me?
Your destinations are so predictable.
Do you even know
what situation you're in right now?
Yeah.
Then what are you doing here?
You're one to talk.
You should've dealt with
the office politics for me.
When they told you
he'd be moving to Friday,
were you just standing there
with your arms wide open?
That…
It was so sudden.
I couldn't do anything about it.
For the love of…
First place? Fine, let him have it!
What?
Ms. Yun, you can't do that.
Why not?
It's not like it would affect you much.
Excuse me?
What do you mean, it wouldn't affect me?
If your place drops the moment
I start working with you, what would Park…
I mean, what would people out there
say about me?
Plus, this kid had the nerve
to claw his way onto the same day as you
to steal your spotlight.
Shit.
Are you really going to let him
get his way this easily?
Damn it, seriously!
This is driving me crazy.
Thank you.
Is it okay if I head out now--
So freaking agonizing.
So-yeong, you can go home now.
Right.
I feel like we'll come up with something
if we think just a little harder.
-Got it.
-Oh, she's got it.
Ms. Yun!
We really need something new to happen
to Choi Si-woo right now.
Define "new" for me. You said you weren't
a fan of his aunt kicking up a storm.
My brain isn't working either.
Should I kill off Choi Si-woo?
If the main character dies,
everyone will come flocking, won't they?
Please stop talking nonsense.
Tell me.
Why do you think TMTK became
my most successful work?
Well, that's…
That's because it allowed your talents
to truly shine.
What are my talents?
Well, you're really good
at drawing handsome men.
Therein lies the problem.
That was the problem from the start.
It wasn't supposed to be a hit,
but it came this far
because Choi Si-woo was too handsome.
Choi Si-woo's looks are so immaculate
that people can't stop reading
this incredibly boring slog!
All because Choi Si-woo is too handsome!
Seriously!
I think I'm starting to understand
why Producer Cho left the company.
Honestly,
I want to end this series.
I'm so sick and tired of it!
Seo.
Please save me.
My whole life is falling apart.
YOUR DAILY WARMTH, A PERFECT MOMENT
Enjoying yourself?
We're dying here, you know.
Do you think he really likes me?
Hey, stop it.
You've been talking about him all day.
Do you like him that much?
It's just that he won't give me
a clear answer.
Just go and ask him
if he actually likes you.
Let's go ask him right now.
Right now?
Just go and ask him
if he actually likes you.
Let's go ask him right now.
Let's go ask him. Let's go. Just ask him.
Let's ask. Should we?
Let's go ask him.
Just ask him. Should we go ask him?
Let's ask him.
Ask him.
Come in.
What? Where am I?
What's this?
Why did you call me to your room?
Too many eyes watching outside.
I didn't see anyone.
The moment I step out, they'll swarm.
Hang in there.
Think about why you came here.
What's with that look?
But I must say,
he's just so damn handsome.
I have something to say--
I believe you were a supervisor?
-Don't come in starting tomorrow.
-What?
Stop coming in to work.
Wait, are you firing me right now?
You could say that.
I don't date company employees.
If I'm to date you,
I have to fire you.
He's oblivious to labor laws.
Why is he addressing me informally?
Anything to say?
I'm guessing every girl
you've ever asked out has said yes,
but I'm not like that.
-So?
-Show some effort.
Show me what you're made of.
You're more intriguing than I thought.
It sounds like you want me to seduce you.
Is that right?
Yes, seduce me.
Show me how it's done right now!
I'm in a hurry. We don't have much time.
On second thought, I won't fire you.
No! You have to fire me.
Didn't you want to date me?
I think I'll keep my eye on you
a bit longer.
Don't do that! I told you I'm in a hurry.
Yes, Mr. Choi.
Choi.
Reassign her to the secretary's office.
Yes, sir.
What is this now?
-Aren't you leaving?
-What?
I'm done talking. Leave now.
What even…
Allow me to introduce myself first.
I'm the chief secretary,
assisting the general manager
day and night, right by his side.
My name is Choi Min-ju.
CHIEF SECRETARY
CHOI MIN-JU
As I'm sure you know,
the secretary's office at SY Group
is a demanding department.
Though you may have parachuted in,
Mr. Choi insists
we follow at least the basic protocol,
so he specifically asked me
to carry out a simple job interview.
An interview? My interview?
Yes. I simply need your honest answers.
What is your favorite food?
Food?
I… Well, I like beef and pork.
BEEF, PORK
And… I just like all kinds of meat.
What about hobbies?
What kind of date would you like to go on?
Where would you like to travel?
-Is this really an interview?
-What is your ideal type?
He should be asking me himself.
Why is he having others do it?
Excuse me.
Yes, Mr. Choi?
Yes.
I see.
Allergies and shoe size.
Yes, I'll check right away.
Yes, I'll be right there.
Mr. Ko! Why haven't we left yet?
There's a car blocking us.
Mr. Choi insists that we hurry along.
Not going anywhere, are you?
Hey! My apologies.
This really brings me back.
Hey! You punk!
I'm going to take care of it.
Hey!
Wait, is that really necessary?
-It's okay.
-Hey!
Mr. Ko isn't your average person.
Taken care of.
Did they really need to include this part
from the webtoon?
Ms. Seo, Mr. Choi would like to see you.
This way, please.
Mr. Choi
does not like it when people knock twice.
Going forward, when you're knocking,
a single gentle tap will suffice.
-This is ridiculous.
-Excuse me?
Nothing.
Why don't you give it a try? A gentle tap.
A gentle tap.
Come in.
You may enter.
By the way, that was a little too loud.
That annoying woman.
She's just like in the webtoon.
What is all this?
Flowers.
The best way to win a woman over.
Hey! You shouldn't have.
Look.
I may be seducing you, but I expect
a bit more respect from you than "hey."
So? Do you like it?
Kinda.
You're picky.
So, what's next?
There's got to be a next step.
You have it all prepared, don't you?
How could someone be so shameless?
You didn't prepare a date?
Come with me.
This is weak.
What?
I said this is weak.
This will never satisfy our read…
I mean, do you think this will satisfy me?
What are you talking about?
It hasn't even started yet.
I figured you should eat
before we go on a date.
Try it.
It actually tastes like food!
No way.
How did I end up owing my life
to a woman like that?
A sudden trip to the department store?
Are you…
Given my social standing, I can't take you
on a date without stopping by here first.
Oh my God!
Go on.
Try them on.
Whoa.
Would you like to try it on?
YES
Do you like it?
Why would you rent the entire pool
if you're not going to swim?
Why? Do you not approve?
It's not bad.
Seo Mi-rae.
What do you think? Do you like it?
Not sure.
I think I might like it.
You're late.
I get it now.
This
isn't a cliché, but…
Ms. Yun! Open up!
You know what time it is?
Ms. Yun, I got it.
-I got it!
-Got what?
I realized what Choi Si-woo needs to do.
What?
Let's go back to the beginning.
The beginning?
You said this webtoon could become a hit
because of Si-woo's handsome looks.
I did.
Plus, the fantasy of him being a chaebol
who can give you everything you want.
But you said people are hating on it
because the chaebol thing was so cliché.
No, I was wrong.
-You were wrong?
-Listen.
Choi Si-woo is not a cliché.
He's a classic.
The definition of classic
that female readers desire.
Women were raving about TMTK
for offering an escape
from their harsh reality,
but all those cheesy lines you gave Si-woo
ended up giving them the ick.
So what's your point?
We've totally got this.
Let's get back to the drawing board
and give them a true chaebol romance.
First, the department store.
Let's start there.
-Yeah?
-The luxury floor.
The luxury floor?
Seeing Si-woo suddenly lose his composure
really made my heart flutter…
I mean, I'm saying it would.
-So, pull up his top?
-So-yeong.
We could use some darker coloring here.
-And the ring.
-The ring?
-The ring is too small.
-It needs to be bigger?
At least this big.
You heard her. Leave it to me.
Si-woo comes over, grabs her wrist,
and drags her away.
She will feel a vibe.
Game over. Classic.
EUN NA-RA, SHINE FOR ME, BY MY SIDE
-Here to buy coffee?
-Yes.
Iced latte, please.
One iced latte. That will be 5,000 won.
We'll be working late together
before every deadline.
I guess.
You know I didn't mean to.
You make it sound
like it was a car accident.
You seem mad at me. That's why.
I'm not.
Doors opening.
Is that your habit? Putting on a front?
Doors closing.
It shows, anyway.
You're terrible at keeping a poker face.
-Is that right?
-Yes.
Then why ask me, you jerk?
I guess you'll also be here for a while.
-Me?
-Yes.
I noticed you had two cups of coffee.
I got another one while the café was open
so I can have it on my way home.
It tastes bad when the ice melts.
I know. I plan on clocking out
before the ice melts.
Doors opening.
Me too.
1 MESSAGE
Damn it.
Shit.
Are you kidding me?
No. I shouldn't nag her.
Don't you nag her.
Come on!
YUN SONG
&lt;TMTK&gt; E110
It's over.
By now…
3: PlanC
HWANY
1: THE MAN TO KNOW
YUN SONG
First place!
First place, first place
First place is mine
First place
It doesn't change hands easily
Congratulations, Mi-rae!
Congratulations!
-Congrats!
-Hello.
Hi.
Congratulations!
Seo Mi-rae!
Hi.
Morning!
Oh dear.
Who turned you around?
Well defended.
Did something happen?
Hey, did something happen here?
Let's get to work, okay?
Nailed it, Yun Song!
She's finally back on track.
She poured her soul into this one.
A triumphant return for TMTK!
"Hella fun"? I wouldn't go that far.
Good times.
It's only a dinner.
Did you have to bring a private jet?
Don't approve of this either?
What took you so long?
I have to stick to my hours.
I'm just an employee, after all.
You make your boss wait,
then use work as an excuse?
Where are we having dinner tonight?
You'll see. Come with me.
Look!
Dolphins!
Let's get engaged. I'll handle my parents.
Engaged?
Are you mad?
You answered a chaebol's proposal
with a spit take?
Didn't I tell you?
We're just dating, nothing more.
What?
I told you not to fall for me.
It's so pretty.
Mi-rae.
Yeah?
Let's do it your way.
My way?
We don't have to get engaged.
In exchange…
can you at least be my girlfriend?
I've never asked anyone
for anything before.
Do I have to
ask for this too?
Is he…
What…
Dopamine overload!
Why look away?
Did I?
I got something.
I'm giving this to you as a boyfriend,
so don't turn it down.
That's all it means.
Si-woo!
Oh my God!
What?
What's going on?
What's happening?
Hello!
Ms. Seo Mi-rae, your 50 hours
of dating Choi Si-woo have ended.
What did you say?
SERVICE PERIOD EXPIRED
No!
Si-woo!
Damn it!
What was that?
"You can only date a male character
for up to 50 hours"?
No.
No!
We have a meeting with Mipare tomorrow.
Okay. Both of them are on the rise,
so we must sign their upcoming titles.
-Yes, sir!
-And Team 1?
I contacted Hwan-su,
but they want to finish the series first,
so that's on hold for now.
Choi Si-woo left a lasting impression.
What?
God!
So much so
that he threw my life off balance.
Looks that surpass
his webtoon counterpart,
great conversation skills,
and subtle thoughtfulness.
It was definitely too much…
and yet, his sexiness made it all okay.
Hella sexy.
HELLA SEXY
DEVICE SATISFACTION
USER EXPERIENCE REVIEW
As expected from a producer,
it's a very well-written review.
That's a relief.
It's fascinating that you got matched
with a character from one of your works.
So how was it?
Tell me what you really think.
What exactly do you mean?
I just want to hear your honest opinion.
It was fun. Well, more than fun.
Then why did you end it so soon?
I think I've experienced enough
to understand what it's about,
and Choi Si-woo set the bar
way too high from the get-go, so…
Ms. Seo.
Yes?
There are still 899 characters left.
What makes you so sure
Si-woo is the best one?
If you throw away your remaining hours,
you might regret it later on.
I think she knows she probably shouldn't,
but she can't help being drawn in.
Who is he?
-It's like I'm watching a movie.
-He drives women crazy.
-Totally.
-Yeah, those eyes…
He just melts your heart.
-He draws you in.
-The way he holds her hand!
Dopamine.
I need my dopamine!
There are still 899 characters left.
What makes you so sure
Si-woo is the best one?
If you throw away your remaining hours,
you might regret it later on.
He's right.
It's a one-month subscription trial,
so why don't I make full use of that?
Since when did I ever turn down freebies?
Stop kidding yourself.
Looks like you've lucked out
on another amazing pick today.
Hurry along now.
I did let Min Jun-young talk me into
returning, but I was still skeptical.
Could there really be a man more thrilling
and charming than Choi Si-woo,
a webtoon male lead?
What's wrong? Is there a problem?
Give me a second.
My, you're a handful.
Now…
Hey, don't push…
But once again,
Boyfriend on Demand managed
to far exceed my expectations.
Subtitle translation by: Daham Yoon