Yebin.
Think carefully.
It's all stated in the contract.
Very good.
Keep going.
Put on lipstick for her gently.
I'll add a bit more for you.
Our lips are matching.
[Morning,
in Lee Sumin's office]
[Ratings trend of Wonder-X's reality show]
Everyone is here, yeah?
I'm not one to beat around the bush.
Let's look at the data
of your last reality show.
The number of views, trending topics,
interactions, and Return on Investment
are all below expectations.
Way below expectations.
Because the agency values you
they've gathered connections,
capital, and time to invest in you.
But the data and reception are poor.
This is the harsh reality.
If you aren't consistently profitable,
you'll soon be replaced by other rookies.
So we need to adjust our strategy.
We need a more direct and intense approach
to create buzz.
That is, livestreaming.
It's not just a livestream
but a live commerce.
The agency has signed a promotion contract
for a lipstick series.
This is your chance.
What you need to do
is to highlight the product well,
promote sales,
and showcase your teamwork
to return to the spotlight.
What are the livestream
format and procedure?
The planning team is
still fine-tuning the details.
The key points are product experience,
interactive sales,
and the chemistry of you two.
In particular, you have to be natural
and show chemistry.
This is what the viewers and fans want.
You were too rigid
in the last reality show.
Of course no one would watch it.
Don't you agree?
But
we don't have
any livestreaming experience at all,
not to mention live commerce.
Then learn.
The agency will provide training;
how to frame yourself in the camera,
the script, and product knowledge.
The key is your attitude.
I understand
about your artistic pursuit.
But you have to remember this:
if you don't make money,
practice studios and platforms
won't be available to you.
The agency will give you
opportunities and resources,
which you need to use to create value.
The contract, live script,
and training schedule
will be relayed to you soon.
For the next week,
cancel all other irrelevant work.
Focus on the livestream prep.
Remember, this livestream
is not simply a promotion.
You need to show the agency
why your group is worth investing in
and worth the risk.
Yes, Mr. Lee.
Yes, understood.
Yes.
Good.
That's all for today.
Ji-eun, stay behind.
I have something to ask you.
Go back first.
Thank you.
If you want to debut,
you have to do well in this livestream.
Make sure you're in prime condition.
Yes, Mr. Lee.
I'll do my best.
Oh, right.
And about Yebin,
she seems more unstable than I thought.
You've been with her for the longest time.
Take care of her.
Tell me if you need help.
I hope this livestream will be a success.
I'll talk to the leader.
Good.
Go along.
Attention, everyone.
The livestream of Wonder-X will begin now.
Are you ready?
OK.
Three, two, one, action.
Hello, everyone.
I'm the host today again.
Our goal is to get 15 million viewers.
We prepared something fun today too.
Yebin-unnie, what are you doing?
Come sit down.
I'll teach you how to
say "lipstick" in Chinese.
Follow me.
"Kou hong."
"Kou hong"...
Unnie.
You sound so awkward!
Shut up.
Ji-eun, it's your turn.
You can do it.
"Kou hong piao liang."
[T/N: "Pretty lipstick" in Chinese]
Ji-eun!
Isn't she so gentle?
She has such versatile charm.
[Simulation of the couple livestream]
Yebin, don't look so tense.
OK?
Make your gaze gentler.
Show more of your charm.
Relax a bit more.
OK.
By the way,
why are your faces so red?
Yebin-unnie was staring at you
for so long.
Ji-eun, stop looking.
The live's starting.
OK. Good.
Yebin, keep this expression.
OK?
Ji-eun, make your gaze gentler as usual.
OK, OK, OK, OK!
Let's do it.
Maintain that.
Good.
Ji-eun, that's great.
So pretty.
Look sweeter.
Ji-eun, you're doing so good.
Smile sweeter.
[The couple livestream begins]
Are you ready?
It'll be your couple livestream next.
The most classic scene
the fans want to watch.
First, how you sit.
Ji-eun will sit on Yebin-unnie's legs.
Second, you have to
put lipstick for each other.
Apply the 707 lipstick for each other
slowly and gently.
Third, to conclude things,
look into each other's eyes for 5 seconds
after applying the lipstick.
You must look sincere
and not look away.
Fourth,
it's a one-take, so there are no redos.
Listen carefully.
We can't screw up this shoot again.
Song Minah will film
and liven up the atmosphere.
Just stick to the script.
Then we'll definitely get many views.
Yes, Mr. Lee.
I can't do this.
My legs hurt.
Your legs hurt?
Yebin.
Think carefully.
It's stated in the contract.
You have to pay 500 million won
for breach of contract.
Well, I'm sure you don't mind,
but Ji-eun's grandmother
has medical bills to pay next week.
The agency will no longer
financially support her.
And you'll be
the cause of it.
Can you take the responsibility?
Do it right.
Unnie.
Don't worry.
I'll stick to the script.
Good.
In this posture,
Yebin-unnie,
gently touch Ji-eun's lips.
Jung Ji-eun.
Stay still.
Why are your lips so dry?
Bin.
I can do it myself.
Don't move.
Do you like this?
No.
It tickles.
Yebin.
Hold up the lipstick.
Be elegant.
And...
Ji-eun.
Look at the lipstick in Yebin's hands
with a gentle gaze.
Good.
Now, Yebin-unnie,
look into Ji-eun's eyes
and say your lines.
Some colors
can only be used once in a lifetime.
Why?
Because once you like it,
you become addicted.
Very nice.
Keep going.
Put on lipstick for her gently.
I like your lip color.
I'll put it on for you too.
OK, good.
Keep going.
Make it pretty.
I'll add a bit more for you.
Our lips are matching,
don't you think?
65 cm.
3 cm thinner than last week.
Does it reach the standard?
Almost.
Here,
flex your abs.
From today's lunch,
make changes to your diet.
Add fruit. Dinner will be a salad
instead of a protein shake.
Really?
Don't get too excited.
It's just switching
from hell mode to difficult mode.
Yes, thank you, unnie.
Warm up now.
10 minutes of planks.
20 sets of sit-ups.
10 minutes of stretching.
We'll practice the new choreography after.
Yes.
Don't resent me too much.
Mr. Lee used to be a million times
stricter than this.
But thanks to him,
I'm where I am now.