( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
I’m not your enemy,
I'm here to help.
Do you think everything is as it seems?
Don’t hug anyone too tightly.
Before you realize it...
you’re already bleeding.
Moral?
Does this school still have morals?
Watch your language, Ace.
You may be the Supremo
but I am the headmistress of this school.
As the new SSG Secretary.
How many times do I have to tell you
that I'm not interested in that position?
Listen, Zein.
I'm a detective
at the same time, secret agent.
I can't give you any information.
Zein...
you can be a big asset
if you accept Ace’s offer.
And where do you think you're going?
The restroom...
to change.
No.
Change here.
I said move and get out of my sight.
You're catching on pretty quick.
I like that.
I still think Fritzy
should take the seat.
She's earned it.
The new SSG Secretary is here.
Why is that girl here?
And why is she
wearing my uniform?
Get out of your chair.
President Ace.
Fritzy is still
the SSG Secretary.
All of you
take my command.
And you...
get out of my sight,
Ms. Fritzy Saldivar.
You're no longer
allowed to wear that uniform.
Bitch.
From now on.
Ms. Zein Shion is
the new secretary of HU.
And I no longer want to hear
any complaints
or questions about it.
Respect her like you respect me.
Maybe you're forgetting
that she's in the
top nine of the highest ten.
It may be low in comparison
to your position, Mr. Ty
but you should
respect her because I said so.
And Zein
now that you're part of the council
you have but one responsibility
and that's to stay present with me
or at the office.
No questions asked.
What do you mean?
I- can't say no!?
Music is structure.
Order.
Carefully arranged notes
all in service of a higher purpose.
That is why you learn music here.
If anything that will bolster
your weak, feeble minds.
The kind of minds
that end up late in class.
Right, Ms. Shion?
Find a seat, Ms. Shion.
Surely you can do at least that.
Where are your music sheets?
It's okay ma'am. We can share.
Hopefully, that will be
the last interruption this class will have.
You have your music sheets.
Today, we are learning
vision fugitive.
Follow the tune
of the metronome.
Let's begin.
Replaced?
Just like that?
It's like I didn't do
anything as his secretary.
Don't let it get to you
you're still one of the
big dogs in Hell U.
Just adapt to the situation
and play your cards right.
Don't let this put
you down, Fritzy.
Fine
but she'll regret this.
I'll make sure of it.
Need some help?
Oh my god.
I'd appreciate that.
Sorry
you've been saving my
ass since earlier.
Hold on.
Wow, you're so good at that!
I just practice a lot.
I appreciate this,
I hope you tuning this
won't be in vain.
I didn't catch your name.
My name is Nazzer Lumia.
Is there a problem?
You're the leader of
the Black Blood Gang?
I am, my lady.
Don't take anything
you see in face value.
You should be wary
of people's intentions.
Because when the facade breaks
they can be worse than demons.
Number nine, huh?
That's impressive.
But your life doesn't hold value to us
or the rest of the people here.
You're going to die soon.
I'll make you an offer, hmm?
There's nothing
that you have that I want.
Calling it an offer was a courtesy...
join us or die.
Be one of us
and I will protect you.
I don't want to.
What a waste.
I can kill you now.
You'll die soon.
Hmm?
Kill me, then.
They're right about you
you are not afraid of death.
The grim reaper
might be afraid of you.
But you won't die yet
we can still use you.
What did I tell you, Paulo?
He likes to hangout here.
Didn't I tell you
if you talk to my girl again
you're a dead man.
She wasn't complaining about it.
Is he being serious, bro?
You think you're brave, huh?
Come on, stand up!
Not so brave now, huh?
Use this!
Stop it!
Hey
it's the Supreme Secretary.
Our apologies, my lady.
This guy has been talking
to my friend's girl.
We just want him
to learn a lesson
like what you guys do in
that council, right?
My lady, don't let him affect you.
He's worthless.
Why did you stop?
Listen to them, my lady.
Let them release their anger. Shit!
Where's your bravery now?
Huh?
I'll kill you!
Are they done with him yet?
Doesn't look like it.
This is so boring.
Aren’t you going to help him?
Aren't you one of his underlings?
Help him?
You're funny, aren't you?
Miss Secretary!
I can't help him
but
you see those three guys?
They'll be the next ones to die here.
I think there's chocolate in it
I think so. Is that
alright? I think its better -
Let's go.
She's not done eating.
Haven't she informed you?
Fine, let me.
As the new SSG Secretary.
Zein is not allowed
to talk or be with you
unless I allow her.
That's crazy.
Why would you make her do that?
Because she has responsibilities.
Now
if you'll excuse us.
Miss Shion.
Let's go.
Matt.
She isn't done eating yet, is she?
Matt...
Sorry guys.
Sorry, Supremo.
Name?
Name!?
F-Ferry Marcos.
SSG!
Follow me.
The Dark Hell Jail
is waiting for you.
Zein...
Zein!
Excuse me!
If I were you, Zein.
I'd step aside from your position.
You won't like it when
he shows his true colors.
I'm not afraid.
Really now?
I'm honest enough
to admit that I am.
I've witnessed his anger
his demonic anger
and if you see that for yourself
you'd be scared too.
I don't want to die yet.
Please, I don't want to die.
Supremo's word is law.
It's final.
Supremo.
Supremo... I don't want to die yet.
Stop resisting.
I'm begging you.
Faster!
Supremo
I don't want to die yet...
Don't make me push you inside.
I know you, Supremo.
I know your secret.
I know.
That's why I brought you here.
I know your secret too.
How did you find out?
Do you think I
would stoop so low
that I'll bring you here
because you spilled juice on me?
I know your secret
you killed Grace.
And you're scared
that if Jane finds out...
she'll never forgive you.
Grace is the girl whose death
you've witnessed, Zein.
Don't tell her, please!
I won't
if you go to Dark Hell Jail
right now.
Let's go
we still have work
to do for the council.
This is our job, Miss Shion.
We need to punish the rule breakers.
Even if that punishment
is death.
Onelski
can you tell the cafeteria staff to
cook the Tuesday special again?
It's so delicious.
Anything for you, Fritzy.
It's like nothing has happened.
- It's like they just placed
- Supremo can you
- an animal in a cage.
- ask them to change...
the cafeteria decor?
I'm so done with that color.
Now I understand why
everyone is so afraid of them.
Their punishments are lethal.
Let's go.
I don't want to stay any
longer with these demons.
I need to find the hidden laboratory asap!
Supremo! Supremo!
I'm Jane.
I'm Ferry's girlfriend.
Supremo, I'm sorry for the interruption
but maybe we can still talk
about Ferry's punishment?
You're too late.
Jane...
Jane, right?
Please calm down.
Number nine?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for bothering you.
You're wasting time with the likes of me.
But maybe you can help me?
Maybe you can reason with Supremo
to release Ferry from
the the Dark Hell Jail?
We still have time.
They already took him.
The ones inside already took him.
It's like they weren't human.
Jane, I'm sorry.
But we can't do anything more for Ferry.
I didn't like what happened either.
Wow...
it's my first time to hear an apology
from an SSG member.
My lady, you've been too kind and generous.
May I know your name?
Zein.
I'm sorry for bothering you
your kindness has made me remember
more peaceful times at this school.
I don't know how to repay your kindness.
I can't believe that there were
peaceful times at this school
if you really want to repay me
tell me everything.
How did peace arrive
here in Hell University?
Since the last five years,
no newcomers have entered this place until.
But before you
there were others.
But Hell U has taken their lives as well
except for the three newbies.
But one girl prevailed
because of her peace was restored in HU.
For the first time, bloodshed was halted.
Her name was Samantha.
We all thought it would last forever
but nothing is certain here in Hell U
besides bloodshed and death.
Everything went back to the way it was.
What's scarier is
the demons became more gruesome.
Jane...
I'm sorry, my lady.
I'm happy to know that both of you
I'm happy to know that
has given us hope for peace.
If I'm being honest,
you've outdone her.
She got into the top ten in two months but
you've done it in a month.
Please don't compare us.
Sorry to say.
Hell U is still in chaos.
You said that everything
went back to chaos?
What happened to the girl?
Why couldn't she stop it?
What went wrong?
Because the headmaster's
son fell in love with her
the former Supremo.
Huh, really?
That’s crazy.
Crazy...
I'm still not used to
how they treat you, Zein.
It's Supremo's command
to make all the students respect us.
You'll get used to it.
I don't think I will, Zein.
Math equations are easier
than getting used to this.
I get it.
After all the things that happened
the teachers are still pretending
that everything is normal.
True.
Alright,
go find a seat for us
and I'll get the books I
need for my assignment.
Okay.
Alright.
Excuse me,
is this seat taken?
Number nine?
Secretary please, the table is.
- No, it's okay.
- all yours.
We can all fit in this table.
Are you, Zein?
Yes, ma'am.
The rumors are true.
What do you mean?
You infiltrated the
council fast and got the
ninth ranking.
Impressive!
I'm just a student
like everyone else.
There's nothing special about me.
Really?
Oh!
Is that your friend?
Yes, she is.
Are they aware?
Of what?
What are you talking about?
So they could join the ranking
They're keen on studying
and escape this place?
But you on the otherhand
you're already in.
Why aren't you leaving this hell?
Stories, Ms. Shion.
That's what holding you back, isn't it?
You get swayed by their stories?
But you already know
the truth but you still
let them fool you?
Remember, Zein.
Stories always have holes.
No one can help you
besides yourself.
Even your friends can't help you.
Don't trust anyone.
History always repeats itself
but I hope this time, you prevail.
Be careful, Zein.
What's wrong with you?
Are you okay?
What happened to you?
Vanessa...
you want to get out of Hell U, right?
Of course, that's obvious!
Why? Don't you want to leave?
Of course, I want to leave.
But seriously, are you okay?
What happened to you?
Miss Leonora's spewing nonsense.
She's so weird.
But you know...
Now I understand why Mia reacted that way.
Right?
I know right! She's so weird.
I can't explain it but
there's something about her
but whatever.
Let's not overthink
the things she's saying.
Let's keep the good vibes.
Right, good vibes.
Okay.
Shit!
What's wrong?
My elective!
I keep reminding you not to be late!
- Hurry!
- Good luck with the assignment, okay?
They should be careful of you, bye!
Where can I find the answer here?
This is so hard.
Here.
Are you aware that if the
faculty is short on people
they recycle assignments.
I've already had that
assignment in my class.
Ahh...
You know usually if someone
is trying to help you out
there is something you should say.
Thank you.
There you go!
You know how to talk.
I'll teach you
but wait.
I'm Liam.
Vanessa...
Page 256.
Is that true?
That's where you can find the answers.
To what you’re looking for.
Are you done?
There's still a few more.
Thank you.
Oh, you can just keep that book.
I'm already done with that.
I just wanted to know if you're
done with your assignments.
Yeah, I'm good.
You can have it back.
Do you still have class?
I have one later.
But why are you in a hurry?
Come with me to the cafeteria.
Let's go get lunch.
My treat.
Let’s go.
Yeah, okay.
Wait, I left my assignment!
Hold on!
Are you ready to order? Ma'am? Sir?
Yes, give me your most expensive meal
most expensive drinks,
most expensive dessert
and use your most
luxurious cups and plates.
Since it's your treat, right?
Thank you.
How about you, sir?
I'll have what she ordered/
I'm sorry for her behavior
I think she forgot
that everything here is free.
Your order should be ready, sir.
Thank you.
You're blushing.
Are you blushing out of embarrassment or
because I asked you to eat lunch with me?
As if.
Why are you so annoyed with me?
I didn't do anything wrong.
As a matter of fact,
I even helped you out.
Because
you used your kindless as leverage
so I would owe you something.
Even if I was clear
that I didn't want to go
but you forced me, right?
You don't care about
other people's feelings.
Sorry.
My emotions got the best of me.
I feel like this place
is really getting to me.
You know...
I feel like you need a friend.
I want to be your friend if that's okay.
Friends?
Okay, fine.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Order's complete.
Sorry...
am I late?
Sorry for what?
Weirdo.
And you are?
Liam.
Bro.
That's good to know.
Jerome.
Hey, you guys.
You're leaving us out here.
Hi, I'm Dave.
Matt.
That's Zein and Mia.
So Liam
I have a question for you.
Who's your top five in Hell University?
The highest ten?
Highest ten?
I meant the girls
preferably the sane ones.
Mia, what are you hinting at?
You're new friend
all the girls have a crush on him here
and now you're having lunch with him?
I didn't know he's your type.
Look at you!
She's feeling guilty.
Stop it, guys.
You can assume all you want.
There's this instance
I almost died from fear
when she told me.
"Jerome, I will not tolerate
any of your obnoxious prattle."
They're so noisy. I'm getting irritated.
Do it again, Jerome.
Do it again!
Obnoxious prattle.
Hold on.
Right?
He’s so funny!
Shit!
Oh my gosh.
All of you!
You’re too noisy!
Look what you did, the glass is broken!
Roxane?
Are you okay?
No.
The glass is broken.
They're too loud!
Seriously?
She's overreacting.
Who is she?
Why is she acting like that?
Do you know her?
No.
My thigh, oh my gosh!
There's a cut on my thigh!
Is there a cut? I can't see anything.
Crazy.
Are you annoyed
or are you jealous?
Ew!
They can stay together in hell.
Gross.
Calm down.
All of you!
This is all your fault
you'll regret this!
Oh really?
Don't touch me, I said don't touch me.
Sorry about all of that, guys.
Roxane was a little extra.
She's so entitled.
Well, she's Roxane Alister.
Girlfriend of Raze Silvenia.
Really?
( Watch on kisskh.club Support officail Website )
If Raze
is the undisputed king of Hell U
then by association
Roxane is the queen.
Is that the reason why the
students seem afraid of her?
Think of it this way,
if you cross Roxane
you have to face Raze.
That's why if I were you guys
stay away from her.
Why is this here?
Remove this corpse!
It's getting in the way!
All of you
what are you looking at?
You're getting in the way too!
You're not going to do anything?
Aren't you supposed to
look for whoever did this?
What do you want us to do?
Waste time on this worthless trash?
If you want justice, find it yourselves.
I have better things to do.
Excuse me.
Someone died and no one cares.
This is how they treat people here
this is how they'll treat us.
People's lives have no meaning to them.
They don't value any of it.
Aren't you guys used to it?
They don't care about whoever killed him
and they don't care about the dead.
Whatever
I'll go back to the dorm.
He's right
we should just rest
and it'll be safer there.
You guys are right about that.
Alright, it was nice meeting you all.
Sorry this is the
ending. I'll take my leave.
Let's go.
Let's go, guys. Let's go.
Zein, are you alright?
Let's go.
It makes sense.
If the student population
gets lower every day
there's no use for
classrooms and buildings.
What Matt said was right
they don't value our lives here.
Do you see those three guys?
They're next in line in hell's gate.
Where are you?
Who's there?
Who are you?
It wasn't my fault.
You're Paulo, right?
It's not my fault...
This isn't my fault!
I won't hurt you.
I just want to talk.
Put down the knife.
I can't...
This wasn't my fault, okay?
It isn't.
It's not my fault.
I didn't want to do it.
I didn't want to!
Paulo, what have you done?
If you won't tell me
I can't help you.
You believe me, right?
Right?
What do you mean?
You believe in me, right?
Do you?
You should believe that
I didn't want to do that.
Number nine!
My lady!
Number nine...
Don't you believe me?
Number nine?
Number nine.
Number nine!
Number nine?
Why can't you believe me?
Number nine.
It wasn't my fault.
I didn't want it to happen.
My lady!
Why can't you try to understand me?
Why don't you want to believe me?
Paulo...
I believe in you.
Julse!
I believe in you, Paulo.
I'm sorry.
I believe in you.
My lady...
my apologies.
My friend is going through a tough time.
Looks like it
I'm glad you arrived.
Raven...
I know.
The corpse in the cafeteria?
Yes.
Our friend...
It's Raven.
Why did you do that...
to your friend?
Just like that?
My lady.
When the gangs have made you their target
you will never know peace.
If you don't follow their commands
just like what Paulo did.
No one's safe.
They'll kill Raven.
The gangs will kill him.
How about you, my lady?
Do you think
you can kill someone to save yourself?
Because me.
I'd rather choose.
To be free.
I don't want to be the
gangs' target anymore.
No!
Stop it!
Please stop!
Stop!
Why did you do that?
Why did you have to kill him?
There are other ways.
I just want to be free.
This fucking place!
Look at what it's doing to us!
You should get used to
this place, number nine.
What about you?
Will you be able to use this knife?
Did you do anything about
the corpse in the cafeteria?
I'm going to guess and say "none".
Why would you waste your time helping
someone without gaining anything in return?
Because that's what a decent
person would do, Ms. Kath.
Or are you implying that
you're no longer human?
Only lucky people can
afford that kind of mindset.
I thought you already had a
grasp of your situation here, Zein.
This is the reality inside Hell University.
This is the reality...
that's what everybody keeps telling me.
But I don't buy that
you really believe that.
You're just scared to take action.
Don't tell me that's what you really think?
I...
It's such a hassle
the corpses are lying everywhere.
They're disgusting.
There are more deaths?
Two new deaths.
Oh, God.
Supremo's going to be
mad when he finds out.
Are they already dealt with?
Yes.
One body in the abandoned wing
named Paulo.
The other one
was found in the cafeteria again.
No one can identify him.
Julse.
His name is Julse.
I'm sorry.
Ms. Shion.
Maybe you want to postpone the
meeting so you can have your snacks?
Supremo
with all due respect.
Stop overreacting.
You're not the only one
dealing with the killers.
Don't be dramatic.
You know Zein, you love
your friends too much.
Ms. Shion.
I feel like you've redirected
that love to someone else.
That Supremo...
you two are getting too close.
Looks like our Supremo
has a soft spot for you.
Well, well, well
so the rumors are right
you're the new secretary of
the Supreme Student Government.
I said move!
You're just dirt on my shoes.