In the years gone by,
the arts programs on the radio
once brought
a lot of joy to the audience.
Today, the arts channel
will provide you
with more and better programs.
This also fulfills
the decades-long dream
of the older generation
of radio arts workers.
Speaking of fulfilling dreams,
I'm reminded of someone
and a true story.
It happened right here,
and it's not far from us at all.
=Eight Hundred=
(Year 1997, Fengyang Town, Jiangbin City)
♪Perhaps everything
has slowly passed us by♪
Fengyang
has produced coal since the Jiaqing era.
But the quality isn't good.
It doesn't burn well.
(Provide more coals. Make more contributions)
You can dig for a whole day,
and it still won't sell for much.
Back when the country
was liberated,
there were only about
thirty households in this town.
But look at it now.
(National Fitness Activity)
It has grown to cover
an 800-meter radius area
with thousands of households.
Those years
were difficult times.
National resources were scarce.
It was under those circumstances
that the Fengyang Coal Mine
was established.
Suddenly,
thousands of people poured in
from all over the country.
That's right.
Hongbing, back then
your father and my father
were part of them.
I remember when our fathers arrived,
they were only in their early twenties.
They were all young men.
Liang, it took two generations.
- Two whole generations.
- Exactly.
With their unremitting efforts,
they finally built
"Little Hong Kong, China" in the valley
within an 800-meter radius.
See how prosperous
our place is.
Right?
Come on.
Director Liao, let me give you a toast.
Liang,
let me use your phone.
Here.
Hello?
What's the matter?
Master, something happened
at the Beimianling coal gangue dump.
Fine,
I'll head over right now.
Pay attention!
Protect the scene.
- Limin!
- Put up two more tape lines there.
Master.
What's the situation?
We received a report from a villager
who saw a fire at Beimianling.
They called the police,
and a body was found
after the fire was out.
So they notified us.
We preliminarily suspect
it was a spontaneous combustion
of the coal gangue.
Coal gangue?
Did you notify the municipal PSB?
Director Tong was calling when I came.
- Director Tong.
- Okay, thanks.
- Han.
- Hello, Director Chen.
Let us borrow your tent
and some caution tape.
What's wrong?
Is it bankrupt?
Don't always divide things
into yours and mine.
Well, you have a gun too.
Does that count as mine?
If I give you a gun,
will you fight the fire with it?
I wouldn't dare.
- Come on.
- Shao,
bring that tent over here
- and ten more meters of caution tape.
- Yes.
Twenty meters.
Fine, give him everything in the car.
Let him wrap Fengyang in a circle.
Look,
it's completely charred.
It's a coin.
It's a commemorative coin
for the Year of the Ox.
Someone stay here tonight
to keep watch with me.
Limin, go and check
if anyone is missing.
(Year 1972)
(The female corpse
is clearly charred.)
=Episode 1=
(Burning)
Hey!
What are you doing?
I'm talking to you.
I'm Liu Na from the municipal PSB.
Hello,
I'm Chen Hongbing from
the Fengyang Police Station,
the Deputy Director
in charge of public security.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Tang Yimei, Technical Detachment.
Just call me Yimei.
Hello.
Let's see the scene.
This way, please.
The body hasn't been moved, right?
No.
I've been watching over it all night.
By the way,
right next to the body,
I also picked up
a commemorative coin.
The director of
the local savings office said
there are
two coins in a set.
One has a yellow ring and white core,
and the other has
a white ring and yellow core.
If you want to exchange for them,
you must book in advance.
In Fengyang,
no one has made a booking yet.
Where is the coin?
Here.
Haven't you had any police training?
I'm a veteran officer
with years of experience.
I didn't touch it with my hands.
Chief Liu, we haven't received
any reports in Fengyang
regarding a missing woman lately.
I've already sent people
to the mountains and the villages
to ask around and see if there are any
missing women under thirty-five.
How do you know
it's a female under thirty-five?
It's simple.
Look at this.
It is
the plastic sole of a shoe.
This is a heel, and it's so small.
This must be
from a thin high-heeled shoe.
In Fengyang,
those who wear these kinds of heels
are generally
women under thirty-five.
What's this?
A glass shard.
For now, it's possible
that this shard slit the carotid artery.
We'll need to wait
for the lab results for details.
After the body is moved,
sift through the surrounding soil again
to see if there are more like it.
Understood, Chief Liu.
Have some water.
Thanks, Director Chen.
The victim's carotid artery was slit.
There are glass shards at the scene,
suspected to be the weapon.
Yimei is reconstructing them.
Right.
There are quite a few shards.
They're being verified.
The preliminary suspicion
is homicide.
- Master!
- We're confirming
whether the coal gangue dump
was the primary crime scene.
How's the search going?
I checked
no women are reported missing
across the 17 villages of Fengyang.
Director Tong.
Yimei, how's the reconstruction?
All processed, Chief Liu.
Good.
Hongbing,
get someone to take the body
to the municipal PSB for an autopsy.
Alright. Limin,
you go with Yimei.
Help her carry the cases.
- Let me help you.
- No need.
- It's fine. It's heavy.
- Thank you.
I'll head out first, Chief Liu.
Tell them to investigate the coin
and the glass shards immediately.
Alright, I've got it.
Go ahead.
Stay safe.
Drive slowly on the road.
This is the first big case
in Fengyang in five years.
We have to cooperate
with the municipal PSB
and crack this case as soon as possible.
Definitely.
(Provide coal for the country,
contribute to Fengyang)
Chief Liu,
when you solve cases,
(Fengyang Coal Mine Guesthouse)
where do you usually start?
We'll first confirm
the victim's identity
and then investigate
their social circle.
The body was burned like that.
It'll be hard to confirm
their identity, right?
What are your thoughts?
Twenty-five years ago,
on May 8,
a similar incident
happened here in Fengyang.
A young woman named Gao Ying
was burned to death
at the coal gangue dump.
I believe these two cases
were likely
committed by the same killer.
So do you think it should investigate
the case from 20 years ago?
Of course.
If we investigate two cases together,
there will be
more clues.
Wasn't the case solved back then?
At the time, they thought it
was an industrial accident.
But
I think this case
is suspicious.
Then why didn't
you say so at the station?
I just wanted to
clear clues first.
After all,
this happened over 20 years ago.
Merging cases is no small matter.
Let me think about it.
What's there to think about?
Report it to the leaders
at the municipal PSB.
A quick phone call is all it takes.
You can leave now.
We'll talk tomorrow.
Alright, Chief Liu,
I'll go back and quickly organize
the materials.
Let's strive
to solve the case soon.
It's settled then.
Thank you.
Director Chen.
See you tomorrow.
What are you doing?
You came back and just started digging
through everything here.
I'm looking for my things.
What are you looking for?
Just tell me.
If you rummage like this,
everything will be a mess,
and I won't be able to find anything.
The candy box,
the tin box with a little panda on it.
Where was that?
The one with Gao Ying's things, right?
Did you drink at dinner tonight?
Who drank?
What makes you think I drank?
If you didn't drink,
why are you acting crazy?
Those things are from so many years ago.
Why are you digging them up?
It's official business.
Official business?
Gao Ying has been gone
for over 20 years.
Even if it's official business,
it should be settled by now.
The municipal PSB wants to restart
the investigation into
Gao Ying's cause of death.
Is it the municipal PSB
or is it you who wants to restart it?
I'm a police officer.
Isn't it the same thing?
How can it be the same thing?
We've only had a good life
for a few years.
Other families are moving forward.
What are you doing?
Do you drag me backward?
Stop being unreasonable.
How am I being unreasonable?
You're the one
acting crazy for no reason.
Just tell me where that is!
Come on.
Go ask Hui.
(Yingxiong Roller Skating Rink)
♪Perhaps there are
too many things I don't understand♪
Hello, Songge.
- Songge.
- Lei,
(Yingxiong Roller Skating Rink)
you brought your friends here?
Yeah, we just got here.
Yan Jun,
- go home early today.
- I know.
Don't let your dad
catch you at the rink again.
Be careful going in. Don't fall.
Han Ning,
I brought you some barbecue.
When you're finished, you should rest.
The shop can open anytime,
but you only have one life.
Thanks.
Where did Chen Hui go?
Over there.
♪Don't break my heart♪
♪Be gentle once again♪
♪I don't want to see your silence♪
Chen Hui.
♪Waiting alone♪
♪Enduring in silence♪
Songge?
You're back.
Xing from the photo studio
ordered new costumes.
I brought his catalog over.
He wants us to take a look.
Let's go see it together.
Let's go.
(A Terra-Cotta Warrior)
Can you take a photo like this with me?
A Terra-Cotta Warrior.
This is my favorite movie.
The movie is quite good,
but the story is too tragic.
The female lead dies in the end.
After she died, she lived again.
Then she lived and died again.
And finally, she lived again.
Who is it?
It's me.
Hurry.
Mr. Chen.
- Dad.
- Hui.
Songge,
how has your health been lately?
It's good.
Dad, what's up?
Did you see
that iron box
of mine?
It's here with me.
Find it for me quickly.
I have a use for it.
I know where it is. I'll go get it.
Okay.
It's under the drawer.
Alright.
Why are you touching
my things for no reason?
Mom found it while she was cleaning.
She's been nagging about it.
So I brought it here quickly
to keep her from getting upset.
Tell me before you take things.
You...
It made me in a tough situation today.
What happened?
Did you
have a fight at home?
Your mother
is unreasonable.
Would I fight with her?
Is it even worth it?
Mr. Chen,
is it this one?
Yes.
Good.
Chief Liu.
Who is it?
I'm Yang Baichun,
manager of the guesthouse.
Director Chen said you haven't had
something to eat.
I had the kitchen
prepare something for you.
One moment.
Come in.
I didn't know what you like to eat,
so I just made a few things.
If you need anything, just let me know.
Thank you.
Mr. Yang,
I'd like to ask you about someone.
Do you know someone named Gao Ying?
Which Gao Ying?
In 1972, the coal gangue dump
at your mine
spontaneously combusted,
and she was burned to death.
I know her.
She was a temporary worker
at our guesthouse.
What happened to her back then?
At that time,
I had just started working.
I wasn't very close to her.
I was in charge of purchasing then.
But I heard from others
that she might have
been in a hurry that day.
She took a shortcut home
past the coal gangue,
right when it caught fire.
And she was gone.
The coal gangue caught fire
and burned a passerby to death.
Is that normal?
You don't know
the area around that coal gangue
is full of gas.
As long as there's a tiny spark,
it'll explode into a massive fireball,
and people just get sucked right in.
We have rules at the mine.
If any kid goes there to play
and their parents find out,
they'll get their legs broken at home.
Does she have any family left?
You'll have to ask Director Chen.
Back then, Director Chen
was about to register their marriage.
Director Chen? Chen Hongbing?
That's right.
Gao Ying was Chen Hongbing's fiancée?
Yes.
Dad, I'm going
to get the marriage certificate.
(Year 1972)
(Slow)
(Civil Affairs Office, People's Committee
of Fengyang Town, Jiangbin City)
You must be Huo Kaiming.
I'm from the Security Department.
What is it?
The coal gangue dump caught fire,
and it was my wife who burned to death.
You were the attendant on duty then.
Tell me
how the coal gangue could
spontaneously combust.
How could it combust?
I don't know.
What do you mean?
- You were on duty and you don't know?
- They're fighting!
Tell me how it combusted!
Let go of me.
- Let go!
- I won't!
I don't know!
I just don't know!
Explain clearly how it combusted.
I feel terrible that someone died too!
Let go of me!
(People's Public Security,
Jiangbin Municipal PSB)
Chief Liu.
- Director Chen.
- You're finally here.
Look.
I've found all the witnesses.
They're just waiting
for your questioning.
What witnesses?
Witnesses for Gao Ying's case back then.
These are all people
related to that incident.
I didn't agree to investigate that.
Chief Liu,
let's just get
some background info first.
Director Chen,
I have already known
about your relationship with Gao Ying.
Chief Liu,
let me tell you.
After that incident happened back then,
I felt something was wrong.
Fengyang Mine
is a state-owned coal mine.
The coal gangue dump
has thorough safety regulations.
How could it spontaneously
combust for no reason?
And Gao Ying and I had plans that day.
After she got off work,
we were going
to the Civil Affairs Bureau.
Why would she run off
to the coal gangue dump
for no reason at all?
Isn't this all a mystery?
I'm here to investigate
the body-burning case at Beimianling,
not to solve your puzzles.
Chief Liu,
you agreed to it yesterday.
Agreed to what?
Look,
didn't I say it yesterday?
I said it is settled.
And at the time,
you didn't say a word.
Currently, there's no evidence
to show these two cases are linked.
First, it might mislead
our investigation's direction.
Second, it will drain our resources.
So let's not waste time.
Chief Liu,
sorry.
Look.
I don't want candy.
This isn't candy.
This is a person's life.
All the materials on
Gao Ying's case are right here.
Let's talk about it.
No need.
Why can't you just say something?
It doesn't cost anything to talk.
Is it really that hard to communicate?
Limin, let's start the meeting.
Zhou.
Wait a second.
Let the witnesses go home. Dismissed.
Everyone, you can go home now.
Thanks.
That's all for today.
According to the forensics report
from the municipal PSB,
it's confirmed
that the victim was killed
(Weapon, glass shard)
by a glass shard to the carotid artery.
Based on the reconstruction
of the shards,
the shards are from
a Peidun Cough Syrup bottle.
Peidun Cough Syrup
is produced overseas.
Since it contains
high levels of Kejianin,
it is a banned substance in our country.
(Peidun Cough Syrup)
Even overseas,
it is strictly controlled.
Since it's an overseas banned substance,
how did it end up
in a small place like this?
By the way,
a while ago,
the truck driver
involved in the accident
supposedly said
he'd had too much cough syrup.
Then let's investigate
the syrup he drank.
If it's the same brand,
it means someone is selling it here.
It could even be
a killing by a drug trafficking ring.
A drug trafficking ring?
Hongbing,
what do you think?
I think Chief Liu is right.
There are
a lot of migrant miners.
The population is quite complex.
All sorts of bad things can happen here.
Even coal gangue
can spontaneously combust.
What else couldn't happen?
I think
interrogate the truck driver again.
Confirm whether anyone
is selling Peidun Cough Syrup
in Fengyang.
That should at least
give us a starting point.
Fine.
Let's go with Chief Liu's plan.
Hongbing, you go ahead and arrange it.
Chief Liu
and Limin
will go to the detention center again
to interrogate the guy
who drank the syrup.
Chief Liu,
does that arrangement work for you?
That's fine.
It's settled then.
Also, we need to identify
the victim as soon as possible.
Let's split up and investigate.
Let's try to solve this case early.
Dad, why did you bring
those things back again?
Keep them safe for me for now.
Don't lose them.
Didn't they stop the investigation?
How did you find out?
Mr. Chen,
we know.
- Yeah, Mr. Chen, we all know.
- Right, we all know.
Go ahead.
You rascals.
It's a family business.
Don't go telling everyone everything.
It's rare that I get off work this early.
Play one of those
good videos for me.
Let's go.
What time is it?
Just past six.
That was a good sleep.
I feel refreshed.
Dad, how long do you plan on hiding?
I'm a police officer.
Whom do I hide from?
Hiding from Mom, obviously.
In Fengyang,
who else can handle you but her?
Is it even a question?
What happened today
really caused quite a stir.
Your mother definitely knows.
I wanted to stay here for a bit.
So you won't help me?
Dad,
don't blame me for it.
It was all so long ago.
Why can't you let it go?
With all the noise you make every day,
how do you think Mom feels?
I'm a policeman.
Investigating cases
is my job.
Regarding Gao Ying's matter,
even though it's a cold case,
as long as there's a chance,
I still want to clear things up.
Can you clear it up today?
What do you mean?
Go home, of course. What else?
Do you really want to stay at my place?
I guess you've grown up.
You're already kicking me out.
The groceries are ready.
I'll go back with you
and have dinner with Mom.
That's the spirit.
You should have said so earlier.
Let's go.
Have you thought of how
to deal with your mother?
Just one trick.
What trick?
Keep things worse.
Brilliant.
That's truly brilliant.
Current News.
Recently, in Beimianling of Fengyang,
a murder and body disposal case
occurred in the coal gangue mountains.
According to the investigation,
- the victim was female,
- Checkmate.
aged approximately 30 to 35 years old.
Because the body was charred,
identification is difficult.
Currently,
the municipal criminal police are working
with the Fengyang Town station...
I'm back.
Why are you so late, Mom?
You didn't tell me
you were coming back for dinner.
If I'd known, I wouldn't have scheduled
those last two patients.
Dad asked me at the last minute.
Welcome home, Ding Yue.
Hui, bring Grandpa over to eat.
The food is ready. Wash your hands.
I'll wash my hands.
Grandpa,
time to eat.
What?
Fly a kite?
It's so late.
Your mom won't agree to it.
Mom isn't home.
- My mom isn't home.
- What?
Why didn't you say so earlier?
Let's go.
Let's go fly a kite!
Dad!
Where are you going?
Yeah, Grandpa.
Didn't you say it's time to eat?
Come on, let's eat.
Are you
trying to set me up?
Hui, Grandpa is going for
a gastroscopy the day after tomorrow.
Please go with him.
The hospital is full of people you know.
Would I even know
what's going on if I went?
I'll go.
Come on. Let's eat.
Better let Hui take Grandpa.
When he sees his old colleagues,
he will feel proud.
Exactly.
Let them have a look
at my grandson.
Fine, then I'll go.
I'll let you stay home
and have some alone time.
What a good son.
You're getting
more sensible, aren't you?
Thanks.
I heard Gao Ying's case
isn't going smoothly.
Mom,
you're married to a policeman.
You're sure prying into police business.
Just eat.
She has been with me
for most of her life.
What doesn't she understand?
She is just worried about me.
You know?
Let's not talk about work while we eat.
Look at this,
steamed pork with rice flour.
I made this especially for you today.
Try it.
Is salt free nowadays?
It's salty?
It shouldn't be.
I was being careful.
You call this salty?
Being a doctor,
your standards are way too high
and too strict.
Hui, give it a taste.
Let me try.
It's not salty.
Look at this.
It's quite tasty.
Mom, you should still be
the one cooking from now on.
(Outpatient Department,
Jiangbin Municipal People's Hospital)
Hey,
let me ask you something.
How long have you been on dialysis?
Four years.
What's up?
How much have you cost for it
in four years.
I've only just started.
One dialysis session costs over 300 yuan.
It's such a money pit.
When one person gets sick,
it ruins the whole family.
How are you?
Feeling uncomfortable anywhere?
No,
everything's fine.
Have Mr. and Mrs. Chen made up yet?
They've stopped bickering, I suppose.
Your hands are so cold.
The hospital told me to notify you.
A kidney donor for your elder sister
has been successfully matched.
The next step
is to proceed with the transplant.
Wait here for a second.
- I'll let the doctor see the report.
- Really?
Yes.
You need to prepare
the 300,000 yuan surgery fee first.
After that,
(Hemodialysis Room A)
follow the ward doctor's orders.
It's not easy waiting
for a donor kidney.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
It's fine.
- This is what we should do.
- Thank you.
Go and tell her.
Okay.
Dr. Liu,
these are Songge's test results.
Please have a look.
For now,
her condition is fairly stable.
But in her situation,
we generally recommend
a kidney transplant within two years.
Otherwise, as she gets older,
the risk of complications
will keep increasing.
Look at these indicators.
They aren't as good as before.
Her daily diet
must be strictly controlled.
Keep a detailed food log.
I've got it all in my notebook.
Thank you, Doctor.
Dr. Liu,
is there still no donor kidney?
We've been on the list for so long.
Can you see if there's any way to help?
I'll do anything you ask.
All patients have to wait their turn.
I've told you so many times.
Once a suitable kidney is available,
we will notify you immediately.
Go home and wait for news.
Take your medicine.
Thanks.
You should get some sleep too.
I want to tell you something.
Go ahead.
I think
Hui and Songge
are dating.
You noticed too?
I've felt it for a long time.
But they won't admit it.
How are we supposed to ask?
Then we need to prepare in advance.
Prepare for what?
Wait, you really want Hui
to be with Songge?
When they are dating,
can parents interfere?
Songge
is a sick child.
If Hui stays with her,
won't his life be over?
Hui's skating rink
is doing well.
As for the dialysis money,
you don't have to worry too much.
Besides,
isn't Songge waiting for a donor kidney?
Once the child gets a transplant,
she'll be just like a normal person.
But is a kidney really
that easy to wait for?
Besides,
the money from the skating rink
is barely enough for dialysis.
Your monthly salary
is only a few hundred bucks.
That surgery costs over 300,000 yuan.
Who does have the money
for her transplant? You, I or Hui?
What are you getting at? Just say it.
Tomorrow,
go find Hui and tell him to break up
with her as soon as possible.
No. Why don't you go do it yourself?
Hello?
Master, there's a new development
in the Beimianling case.
Director Tong said we should
have a meeting to go over it.
Okay.
I'll be right there.
(Efficient and Pragmatic.
Fair and Honest)
What's the situation?
Master, Chief Liu and I went
to the detention center this morning.
What the driver who caused
the accident drank wasn't
regular cough syrup.
(Peidun Cough Syrup)
Is this the cough syrup you drank?
No.
What I drank was a tube popsicle.
The kind they sell on the street?
No.
This one was pretty expensive.
30 yuan each.
Don't play games with me.
Who would buy
a tube popsicle for 30 yuan?
Tell the truth.
The guy told me
it wasn't an ordinary tube popsicle.
He filled them himself.
There was
cough syrup.
He said it gives you a real rush.
So I kept buying them from him.
Where was the location?
Over on the west side.
At the gas station
by the suburban highway.
He set up a stall there.
Then why did you say
you just drank too much cough syrup?
That's also what he told me to say.
He said
if anyone asked,
just say I drank
too much cough syrup
I bought at a pharmacy.
What was the person's name?
What did he look like?
His name was
Lu Yuan.
It's hard to say
what he looked like.
He always wore
a dark red hat and a mask.
He pulled the brim down very low,
showing only his eyes.
I couldn't see his face.
Can we confirm Lu Yuan's real identity?
We checked.
In our town,
there are seven people
registered as Lu Yuan.
One of them has already passed away.
Two are over 70 years old.
As for the other five, none of them
(Resident Identity Card)
match the truck driver's description.
So I suspect
that Lu Yuan
is a fake name.
Did you go to the gas station?
People there said
Lu Yuan did have a small stall,
but he hasn't shown up
for the last two days.
This cough syrup is addictive.
The truck driver
drank it and that's
what caused the accident.
We must quickly find
the source of these sales.
But we only have information
on this one seller, Lu Yuan.
Whether the source is
is hard to say.
Only by finding this Lu Yuan
can we get the next breakthrough.
What about this?
Investigate from both
the sellers
and the buyers.
During the day,
I can head into town and look around.
(People's Public Security)
I'll see if they're selling those
(Fengyang Town Police Station, Jiangbin Municipal PSB)
twenty or thirty-yuan tube popsicles.
I'll also ask around
to see if anyone has seen Lu Yuan.
At night,
we will organize
a surprise nighttime inspection.
Anyone
who tests positive for Kejianin
will definitely
be linked to this gang.
(Bear Cub Tube Popsicles)
This way.
Let's go.
Master,
we caught five people
who were using the tube popsicles.
Take them back.
Hurry up and take their statements.
And see if you can
track down the supplier
of these tube popsicles.
Got it.
(Did you talk to Hui?)
I can't go back with you.
I have something to do.
What's up?
Just do your own job well.
Sure.
(Entertainment.
Endless fun all day long)
Dad.
Where's Songge?
She went to the city for dialysis.
What's wrong? What's going on?
Let me get you a drink.
It's fine. Don't bother.
There are a few important things
I need to tell you.
What?
Your mom
is busy right now,
so she asked me to talk to you.
I'm mainly here to tell you
about you and...
Is this about Songge and me?
With something this big,
as the head of the household,
shouldn't I be allowed
to ask about it?
Are you and Songge
really in a relationship?
You're a policeman,
so did you just notice?
What's the matter?
Is Mom unhappy?
You should understand
what your mother means.
It's all for your own good,
isn't it?
Dad,
what's your stance?
I don't have a stance.
I just want to tell you
that every parent
hopes their child
lead a good life.
Getting married and starting a family
are major life events.
Your mother and I
have to look out for your future.
Dad,
it's impossible for me to leave Songge.
No one is forcing you to leave.
But I have to tell you
if you're going to be with her,
you need to be mentally prepared.
I am prepared.
I'll just work hard to make money.
Once she gets a kidney transplant,
she'll be just like anyone else.
Anyway, I'm telling you
I've already conveyed
your mother's and my opinion.
You think it over carefully.
You sell tube popsicles here too?
I'd have one.
You're too old to be eating these.
I just saw everyone else eating them
(Bear Cub Tube Popsicles)
and wondered what they tasted like.
How do you open it?
Let me open it for you.
Have you seen anyone selling these
at stalls on the street?
Aren't they sold everywhere?
I mean the ones that cost 30 yuan each.
30 yuan?
I sell only one-fifty each.
30? That's crazy.
Forget it.
Even if I told you,
you wouldn't understand.
Think carefully about what I told you.
- I know.
- I'm off.
(Bear Cub Tube Popsicles)
My dad knows.
Stop the transaction.
♪I always thought
once we see the full picture♪
♪We could understand
each other with empathy♪
♪I always thought
the path we never took♪
♪Must have had more beautiful scenery♪
♪Keep moving forward
and don't look back♪
♪The shore is only reached
by the road ahead♪
♪Too much debt has accumulated♪
♪In this short life♪
♪Between right and wrong,
how to choose?♪
♪Regret is inevitable in the end♪
♪Even so-called love
is repaid with pain♪
♪I hear the laughter
and follow the crowd♪
♪Into the streets and alleys♪
♪On that brightly lit night♪
♪Unfortunately, the breeze in town♪
♪Can no longer catch up to the children♪
♪Times have changed♪
♪Now, everything♪
♪Is no longer what it used to be♪