=Eight Hundred=
Hai,
over here.
I didn't expect you
to still be using a PO box.
I have no choice.
If I left a letter
addressed to the PSB
at the front desk every day
and never actually sent it,
any idiot could tell
there was a problem.
A PO box is different.
It's just a string of numbers.
No one at the hotel
knows who it's for.
So every day,
you leave a letter
at the hotel front desk?
Hui,
this is your territory.
I wouldn't dare step out the door
without some kind
of protection in place.
But it's not every day.
All's fair in war.
I'll keep you guessing.
So, what have you decided?
Are we continuing
our partnership?
Where are you taking me?
(Public Security)
(Jiangbin Municipal PSB)
What's the meaning
of bringing me here?
I just want one thing from you.
What will it take to let me go?
I told you yesterday.
Did you forget?
If you won't do it,
then wait for your prison cell.
Hello, Limin.
I'm at the entrance
of the municipal PSB.
Okay.
I'll wait for you.
What are you trying to do?
The person coming out
in a moment is a cop.
He's in charge
of cough syrup for the city,
and he was my father's subordinate.
Let's settle this right here today.
Whatever you have to say,
say it to him.
Do you think I'm easily intimidated?
Hai,
you're getting old.
You forgot that my father was a cop.
Fengyang's "Lee Rock".
As long as your report letter
reaches the municipal PSB,
it'll be in my hands within half a day.
I don't believe your father
can cover everything up.
If you don't believe it, try me.
But I'm warning you,
if you haven't left
by this time tomorrow,
I'll let you experience
what the detention center here
is like.
You win.
Safe travels,
Hai.
- Hui.
- Limin.
What brings you here?
Who was that just now?
I was dropping a friend off in the city.
I happened to be passing by,
so I came to see you.
Alright, dinner's on me.
Great.
=Episode 14=
(The Kite)
(Jiangbin Municipal People's Hospital)
Hello.
Could you please connect me to Room 306?
I'm looking for Mr. Tian Jinhai.
I'm sorry,
Mr. Tian has already checked out.
Checked out?
Are you sure?
Yes.
When did he leave?
Mr. Tian left early this morning.
Well,
did he leave anything
at the front desk?
No.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Songge.
In a bit,
after dialysis,
let's go buy some groceries.
I'll cook you something nice.
What's the occasion?
Why are we celebrating?
No reason.
I'm just not busy today.
A dish I just learned.
I'll show you my skills.
Are you free for the rest of the day?
I'm just spending the day with you.
That friend of yours
who topped up his account
hasn't come back these past few days?
If he doesn't come, he doesn't come.
Just consider it a gift for our opening.
His accent
didn't sound local.
That's right.
Because he's not a local,
he probably went back.
He just came this once,
put in so much money,
and then went back?
You're not lying to me, are you?
Why would I lie to you?
Songge, you're too tense.
Don't worry.
Come, let me give you a massage.
(Provide coal for the country,
contribute to Fengyang)
(Ding Yue Clinic)
Sorry, we aren't seeing patients today.
You're Chen Hui's mother, right?
You know Hui?
We are good friends.
We met back when he was in Jin'gang.
I never heard
that he had friends in Jin'gang.
I was the one
who transferred the equipment
for his roller skating rink to him.
He didn't have a penny then.
He still owes me.
If we weren't friends,
would I help him without taking money?
In that case,
you are a benefactor to Hui.
I wouldn't say that.
I like your son
very much.
He's smart and capable.
You flatter him too much.
You're here to see Hui, right?
He's been staying in the city lately.
He hasn't been
back here for a long time.
I've already seen him
in the city.
Today, I made a special trip
to visit you and his father.
How is it?
Is it good?
It's delicious.
What you cook
is better than what I cook.
If it's so good, why don't you smile?
Is that a new camera?
This is called a Polaroid.
You can see the photo immediately
after taking it.
Let me see.
There's really an image.
This is so much fun.
It's a birthday gift for you.
But my birthday is still a long way off.
The shop only had two left.
I was afraid
someone else would grab them.
This is so amazing.
Do I press here?
I'll take this call.
Hui.
Didn't I make myself clear?
What are you looking for me for?
I'm at your house.
Are you kidding me?
I'm not kidding.
Your mother's cooking is delicious.
And your father is right here.
Do you want to say something?
I have nothing to say.
You two talk.
Alright, then I'll just chat
with your father.
That's all.
Okay, bye.
Songge,
I need to go out.
Go ahead and eat, don't wait for me.
The soup is here.
- Be careful, it's hot.
- Thank you.
Mr. Tian, please take your time.
My father-in-law isn't in good health,
so I'll take care of his meal first.
Sorry for the trouble, Mrs. Chen.
It's no trouble.
Mr. Tian,
- please, don't be formal.
- Alright.
Okay.
It's delicious.
Are you
from Jin'gang?
I've been doing business
in Jin'gang for over ten years.
In Jin'gang,
what business are you in?
I'm in trade.
Trade?
What kind of trade?
Clothing.
Clothing, huh?
Now that you're in Fengyang,
where are you staying?
I'm staying at that...
What's it called? A guesthouse.
A guesthouse?
That must be the Coal Mine Guesthouse.
Yes.
They told me
it's the best hotel in all of Fengyang.
Did you see Mr. Yang,
the manager?
Mr. Yang?
He
is very nice
and very welcoming.
He was the one who told me
where Hui's mother's
clinic was located.
He didn't offer to take you
for a tour around Fengyang?
He was so enthusiastic.
I told him I was a guest at your home,
but he insisted on waiting
at the guesthouse for me.
He's taking me out tonight.
This person is quite interesting.
Yes, he's a good man.
I've got it.
Thank you.
Director Tong,
hurry
and arrange for men
to do a night inspection
at the guesthouse.
Check for what?
Prostitution.
A man came to our house today
named Tian Jinhai.
He's someone Hui met
while working in Jin'gang.
All the equipment
in Hui's roller skating rink
was transferred from him.
He didn't ask for money,
and it was on credit.
Don't you think this whole thing
is too suspicious?
Hypothetically, if Hui
is really selling cough syrup,
then he must have
established that connection in Jin'gang.
Then, opening the roller skating rink
is just a front.
(Mistaken Identity)
Tian Jinhai
could very well be Hui's
supplier for the cough syrup.
Exactly.
Director Tong,
I'm sure
that Tian Jinhai is suspicious.
It's just that we don't
have enough evidence yet,
so you can't arrest him.
If we can catch him
for solicitation tonight,
then at the very least,
we can detain him for ten days.
This time
would be incredibly precious to us.
If I want to inspect
the guesthouse tonight,
I'll have to notify
the factory security department.
No, Yang Baichun
is too well-connected
here in Fengyang.
So tonight, all officers
participating in the operation
must hand in
all communication devices.
Not a single word must leak out.
Fine.
Notify the men.
(Vienna)
Hai,
how do you like
the "Little Hong Kong, China?"
It's much more fun than our place.
If you like it, stay a few more days.
I guarantee you something new every day.
Then, I'll have to come every day.
Hai's giving out tips!
Listen to me.
Request another song for Hai.
When Tian Jinhai comes out,
just point him out to us.
We'll carry out the mission,
and you stay in the car.
Take your medicine, Dad.
Dad.
Dad!
Hello, Yun.
Are you on duty?
What's up?
My father-in-law is in shock.
It looks like kidney failure.
Send an ambulance over right away.
Okay, right away.
Hello, Fengyang Police Station.
Is Director Chen in?
Mrs. Chen?
Director Chen has gone out.
Where did he go?
On a mission.
Do you have a message for him?
That's Tian Jinhai.
Good.
Mr. Yang, is everything okay here?
It's safest here in Fengyang.
Don't worry.
Then, I'll get to it.
See you tomorrow.
Don't let anyone see you.
Come, you...
Take the room card.
Wait for me in the room.
Director Tong,
Yang Baichun wouldn't be
keeping watch outside, right?
He isn't that sharp.
Wait until he fully takes the bait,
then we'll close the net.
I'm here.
Dr. Ding, where's the patient?
In the back room.
Quick, over here!
Come on.
Be careful.
Dr. Ding,
don't worry too much.
We'll be at the hospital soon.
Sun,
is there a phone in the car?
I need to contact my son.
I haven't been able
to get through to him.
There is.
Here.
Thank you.
Strictly implement
provincial government regulations.
Control the number of personnel
working underground.
Ensure the number of workers
in the mining area
does not exceed one hundred people.
Hello, Mrs. Chen.
Hello, Songge.
Is Hui with you?
He went out and hasn't come back yet.
What's wrong?
Grandpa fainted.
We're on our way to the hospital.
I can't get through to Hui
or his father's phone.
Mrs. Chen, don't worry yet.
I'll head over right now.
Hui.
Where's Tian Jinhai?
Who is Tian Jinhai?
I'm asking you, where is Tian Jinhai?
The presidential suite.
Who are you talking to?
Show some respect,
you brat.
Something's wrong! Quick, let's go!
Move!
What's happening?
What's going on?
Open the door.
Open the door!
Hui, what are you trying to do?
The police are here. Get out!
Director Tong.
Director Tong,
what's all this?
What were you doing at my house?
Take your hand off me.
Let go.
You think I'm easily intimidated?
Take me to the station.
Put on a show,
and then maybe I'll believe you.
Good thing you came to me now.
Otherwise, tomorrow,
I'd have gone
to your old man for a showdown.
This...
Director Tong.
Nobody move.
Police.
What's this all about?
What are you doing?
Routine inspection.
You two, check that room.
Mr. Tong.
Sit down.
Officer,
is it illegal for friends
to have a drink and a chat?
It's not illegal.
But you must cooperate with us.
Name?
Tian Jinhai.
Show me your identification.
This must be a misunderstanding.
How can I do business like this?
How am I supposed
to explain this to the mine?
Shut up.
None of your business.
Wait outside.
Call me if you need anything.
Mr. Tong, look at what you've done.
Okay, thank you for your cooperation.
Fall out.
Hello?
Why haven't you come to pick me up?
I'm about to get off work.
Go back by yourself.
I'm busy today.
Are you out carousing again?
With whom would I be carousing?
The police station
is doing a night inspection.
is doing a night inspection?
Is Chen Hongbing there?
Haven't seen him.
Director Tong.
Where is he?
I see him. He just got here.
What's wrong?
(Fengyang Coal Mine Guesthouse)
Dad.
Tell me.
Why are you here?
I'm here discussing business.
You didn't do it sooner or later.
Why does it have to be at this time?
At what time?
- Well...
- Stop playing dumb with me!
Get out of the way!
- Tell me!
- Hongbing!
You're lying to me.
Your father was taken by Ding Yue
to the municipal hospital
for emergency treatment!
- When?
- Just now!
The ambulance is here.
- Careful.
- Slow down.
Mrs. Chen,
the emergency doctor is ready.
Mrs. Chen.
The blood test results are out.
They're out.
Go check if the CT results are out yet.
Two vials of erythropoietin,
one of lanthanum carbonate.
Hurry and pay for the medicine.
I'm waiting inside.
I'm going now.
Adrenaline, 2 mg,
IV push.
Patient is in V-fib.
Prepare to defibrillate.
Second shock.
Third shock.
Why did you stop?
The phone has been vibrating.
(Incoming Call: Songge)
It's Mom.
Hello, Mom?
- Don't worry.
- Give me the phone.
- Give me the phone!
- You're too loud.
Speak slowly, Mom.
Don't rush. Go ahead.
Hui...
Your grandpa...
He's gone.
(Jiangbin Municipal People's Hospital)
What did your mother say?
What did she say?
Grandpa is gone.
(In mourning)
(Deeply mourning Mr. Chen Xuefeng)
(In mourning, deeply mourning)
Take it easy, Chief Liu.
Kang Limin.
Liu Na.
Hui,
you need to get well soon.
You said
you'd fly kites with me.
My mom isn't home.
Let's go! Let's go fly a kite!
Let's go!
(Filial Piety)
Hui,
I heard your grandfather passed away.
I came to see you.
This condolence gift
(Condolence money)
is for your grandfather.
Get the heck back
to where you came from.
Stop putting up a front.
You said your father
was the Fengyang's Lee Rock.
I thought he
really embezzled 500 million.
Turns out he's a good cop.
You were bluffing me
from the very start.
You even said you
weren't afraid of my report letter.
I'm glad I didn't believe your nonsense.
I'm giving you two choices.
First, keep selling goods for me.
Second, get ready to go to prison.
Why won't you just leave me alone?
I said I'm not doing it.
I'm not doing it anymore!
If you want out, you're out?
If you want to quit, you quit?
To tell you the truth,
all my money
was gambled away.
I lost it all.
I'm still millions in debt.
So, you have to do this for me.
Don't test my patience.
I really don't know
what I might do.
Give me two days.
I need to finish
the funeral at home first.
Fine.
Out of respect for the dead.
Limin,
Tian Jinhai
got a real scare from us this time.
I suspect
he won't give us another chance.
Trying to follow
Tian Jinhai's lead for evidence
will be hard now.
In that case,
I'll file a report with the Bureau
to pull Tian Jinhai's file
and see if we can find a breakthrough.
The key is that we have to
get this cleared up quickly.
If this continues,
Hongbing's family
will fall apart.
Hongbing.
Okay.
Let's leave it at that.
Thank you.
Director Tong, Limin.
How is it?
Is everything arranged?
It's mostly settled.
Hongbing, does Ding Yue know
about your suspicion of Hui?
Let me give you a heads-up.
Regarding Ding Yue,
you need to be
fully prepared mentally.
Prepared for what?
We are the police.
If my son really broke the law,
you should arrest him
and sentence him.
Once he's reformed in the future,
he'll still be my son.
Master,
there's something
I should tell you.
Chief Liu has submitted his resignation
to the Bureau.
Chief Liu.
Director Chen, what's wrong?
Why are you being so mysterious?
I heard
you submitted your resignation.
Is it because of your health?
My health is getting worse lately.
I can't do this job anymore.
With you leaving,
it's quite a loss
for our police force.
It's fine.
There are still other comrades.
Take care of yourself.
Director Chen,
do you really think
it was Hui?
I'm worried it was him.
I no longer have the standing
to be involved in this matter.
It's in God's hands.
You shouldn't worry too much either.
If I can,
I'd like to help you one last time.
Thank you.
(In mourning, rest in peace)
Grandpa,
when we meet again,
I'll definitely fly kites with you.
Your grandfather
was a hero of our Fengyang Mine,
a role model.
(In mourning, deeply mourning)
When we were young,
your grandfather taught us
to be upright
and honorable.
Dad,
I am a police officer.
I won't let this family
have any stain on its name.
Dad,
rest in peace.
♪You ask what is outside the window♪
♪You ask what color the light is♪
♪You say hope is a dancing bubble♪
♪So colorful and free♪
♪Yet popping at a single touch♪
♪So I hope this world protects me♪
♪Just like when we
were innocent children♪
♪Back then, the distance was in sight♪
♪The road had no end♪
♪Say "see you tomorrow"♪
♪And there would surely be a future♪
♪The moonlight shines on the bed♪
♪Memories tucked in an old pocket♪
♪Wind whistling through empty sleeves♪
♪Just pretend
you're holding my hand again♪
♪The moonlight shines on the bed♪
♪Flames flicker, the heart feels hollow♪
♪Climbing high towers,
wandering alleyways♪
♪The four seasons remain,
but people have grown old♪