(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
Mr. Zhou.
Let's go. Hurry.
Careful, miss.
Go. Quick.
=Echoes of Gang City=
=Episode 11=
(As Long As You Are Back)
Stay here.
If they find out
Shuyi didn't die in the fire,
there'll be another operation.
Shen City
isn't safe for her now.
We've arranged for her
to leave Gang City.
When does she leave?
2 AM cruise tonight
through the Xiangshao route.
♪Tonight the rain falls soft and slow♪
♪Blending with letters left unread
drifting through the air♪
♪You turn and look back at me♪
Pontoon Bridge No. 3 is closing.
Move faster.
♪It feels like our souls are in sync♪
♪Past or future,
love goes on beyond memory♪
♪When you hold me, broken as I am♪
♪As the stars flow,
fate holds this moment still♪
♪How many letters have I written
just for you?♪
♪If only you could truly hear
what my heart is trying to say♪
♪From this life on
no distance could keep us apart♪
♪The promise we made♪
♪Will find its way to be fulfilled
one day♪
♪At last, your late reply arrives♪
♪At last, I hear your answer clearly♪
Sir, we...
♪As long as you're here, I have it all♪
♪The whole universe♪
Let's go.
Mr. Shen.
(Peiwen School, Chinese Workbook)
This is today's homework
graded by Mr. Zhou.
Go play.
(She has arrived in Gang City)
(safe and sound.)
Any news?
Nothing from Miss Lin.
Since Mr. Zhou said
he lost contact with her,
she hasn't come to class for a week.
Have the cargo ship to Gang City
deliver this letter to Shuyi
in your name.
Keep her identity hidden.
Do not expose her.
Understood.
Qianmo, I'm here.
I'm here.
Mr. Shen said
you must bring back news of Miss Lin.
Alright.
I'm going.
Make sure you do!
You must bring back her news!
Hurry.
Come.
I've lost contact with Mr. Zhou.
There's also no news from Shuyi
in Gang City.
Go there in person
and deliver
these important things to her.
Sir,
the situation is tense.
Are you sure you won't come with me?
I have something more important to do.
Madam Liu.
That boy.
Where is Miss Lin?
Where is she, Madam Liu?
Did she receive the letter?
Say something, Madam Liu.
Answer me.
Miss Lin...
She sacrificed herself.
Sacrificed?
Quick.
Over here.
Hurry.
There's no time, miss.
You must go now.
Miss, hurry.
Make sure this reaches Shen Gu.
Miss.
- Go.
- Miss.
- Miss!
Miss!
Run!
Miss.
Miss!
(Name List)
Miss...
She received the letter.
This is her reply to Mr. Shen.
(To Shen Gu)
But she died protecting us.
Miss...
No.
This can't be true.
You can't lie to me
just because I'm a kid.
Qianmo,
Miss Lin is gone.
She's really gone.
Extra!
President Shen Gu of the Shen City
Chamber of Commerce is dead!
Shen Gu is dead!
President of Shen City
Chamber of Commerce.
A reward of 500 silver coins
for the killer.
What are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
Hey! What's your problem?
Don't take my things!
Don't take my jade!
Don't touch my things!
Don't!
No!
♪But I want more
than just that fleeting gaze♪
(President Shen Gu is dead)
Give it back.
That's Mr. Shen's token for Miss Lin.
It's an heirloom jade
of the Shen family.
Give it back.
♪When regrets begin to turn around you
will hear it all♪
(President Shen Gu is dead)
We can hang a red ribbon
and pray for good fortune.
You have three wishes.
I'll write them down.
First, may Grandfather have a long life.
(First, may Grandfather
live a long life.)
Second, may Minghui
prosper forever.
(Second, may Minghui)
(prosper forever.)
Third, may Shen Gu
(Third, may)
get what he wants.
(Shen)
Need me to get you a ladder?
Grandfather.
This ancient tree is too old
for you to climb.
Are there any rules when we make a wish?
The higher you hang it,
the more likely your wish will come true.
I want to hang it at the very top.
I'll go get a ladder.
Shen Gu.
What did you wish for?
♪Tonight the rain falls soft and slow♪
♪Blending with letters left unread
drifting through the air♪
♪You turn and look back at me♪
♪In those same eyes familiar tears
quietly appear♪
♪It feels like we have carried so much♪
♪So many questions time itself
could not make clear♪
♪The moment you walked into my life♪
♪Every dream I had became something
I want with you near♪
♪How many letters have I written
just for you?♪
♪If only you could truly hear
what my heart is trying to say♪
♪From this life on
no distance could keep us apart♪
♪The promise we made♪
♪Will find its way to be fulfilled
one day♪
♪But I want more
than just that fleeting gaze♪
♪Still I have not heard your answer♪
♪Can we still rewrite the ending
we face?♪
♪When regrets begin to turn around you
will hear it all♪
♪Everything that leads me back to you♪