Yo! Aloha! I My name is Dream.
Mhong.
They are thinking of your
debut in showcase next month.
If you want something, you
need to give something first.
I need to trade it.
I really like the song
you just played for me.
Can I have this song?
Liar!
Can you please tell me that you
didn't do it because you wanted a song?
Did you have any feeling for me?
If I wanted something, I needed
to give something in return, right?
Will you be my girlfriend?
Be his girlfriend!
The girl should have just accepted
it. She didn't have to do that.
If the girl didn't start it, he wouldn't
have had enough courage to ask her.
It's okay. It's alright, bro.
I felt bad for that DM girl. Poor thing.
He didn't even ask for consent.
He used others to pressure the girl.
This label trained
artists to be this cringe?
In the end, the label
issued an announcement.
MHONGMUANGTHAI
Termination of trainee.
Pink Lava Chicken Nuggets.
New! Chicken nuggets with pink lava sauce.
Deliciousness shining through your mouth.
Fuck!
This is so cringe, everything is so confusing.
I Hilarious. She should focus on being funny.
It's funny but the song keeps haunting
me. I This commercial is so annoying.
I laughed so hard at
the dress, is this serious?
What the heck?! I lost my appetite.
What's your name? I Tokyo.
Somon. I Alright, Tokyo and Somon.
You guys dressed so
cool. Can I do a drip check?
What are you wearing? I I thrifted
this top from Red Building Vintage.
I got the pants from Japan. Not
sure how much but I love them.
How much are you wearing?
I Around 50,000 baht.
Oh my gosh! Second-hand items cost 50,000!?
It's nothing much, right?
Nothing much. I I see.
What about you, Somon?
You think you got the drip? I Sure I do.
How much would you rate
your style? I 10 out of 10.
Wait! What? Are they
part of your school uniform?
So chic! I Shoes from school uniform?
Giving Mary Jane vibe. I What?
So cool. Last question.
Who's the right guy to be your guy?
Right now. I want him right now.
I mean guys from what
country? What nationality?
Come on! I I want him right now!
That's it. Okay, thank you so much.
Have a nice day, bye. I Have a nice day.
I need to see styling items for Ida.
See you tonight. I Sure.
I saw your commercial,
you're bouncing or something.
So funny.
I don't like it one bit.
They didn't tell me when
they reached out to me that
it would turn out to be this funny.
Well, you made funny song.
And the commercial just matched
the vibe. That's why people
think that it's funny. Why're you so moody?
Look at Kimia, she's so gorgeous.
I just want to be pretty like her.
I understand you.
Hey, are you free tonight?
Yeah.
I'm gonna take you to showbiz.
Have you ever heard of.
Cobra House?
What?
You said you're gonna take me to showbiz
but you invited me here for Mookrata?
Want some?
I don't know how to smoke cigarettes.
Oh my gosh!
This is not just a cigarette.
Don't you know that this is
a golden ticket to get into showbiz?
You think that I'm that talented
to help out Ida?
When you're drunk, you'll
strip off your social status,
your mask, your everything
and you can be your true self.
When you're getting drunk with someone
and you're matching up their vibes,
then the rest will fall into
places smoothly, you hear me?
There're so much for you to learn.
Attagirl!
Bitch! You're done?
You're taking too long!
Let me get a refill.
What's with the face?
Can I ask you something. I What is it?
You have long hair, why
don't you get a boob job?
I like the way I am. I feel
confident with this body.
Look at my sexy body moving.
What's going on? You want some boobs?
Want to get bigger boobs? I I don't know.
I want people to come
talking to me like Ida, look.
Since she got her boobs done,
men are chasing her like
crazy, like non-stop crazy.
Listen to me, Ida saw
herself with big boobs
and I saw myself without big boobs.
You need to ask yourself about it.
I don't know
which way is the right one for me.
I just feel lonely.
You're lonely? I Yeah.
Listen to me,
The first thing you gotta do is to
forget about your ex first, then
you can think about the next one.
Ouch! Too harsh.
Bambi, you done?
I'm coming.
Look at your outfit, it's hard to wear.
Come with me.
Where?
Sorry, excuse me.
Mother, this is my friend, Bambi.
Her look is styled by
me. I OMG! Turn around!
Yes! Yes! And Yes! I You think we
should include her in shooting next week?
It could turn out great. I Wait.
Yeah. I can see it.
It's gonna be a shooting next week.
They're looking for new faces.
Yeah? I I think you are it.
You look great today. I Really?
Yup. I Really.
Why would I lie?
So right, just right.
What do you say? I I'm in.
See you next week, honey.
Okay. I Let's dance.
Hi, how are you?
Forget about your ex first.
Tokyo, the city of fashion,
wasn't built in a day,
but he was built with love
and understanding from both Mom and Dad.
The CSR project that
our engineers installed
solar cell panels in Tak was completed.
That's right. The villagers
are happy about it.
I gotta go, I'll inform you
about the updates later.
No matter how nature created Tokyo
but to be surrounded by
unconditional love like this
has formed Tokyo
to be a person who can
love oneself wholeheartedly.
What do you think? You like it?
Let me help you with that. I Here.
So pretty.
You can wear whatever you like.
You're my angel no matter what.
But our lives can't be completed
with just loving yourselves.
Foreign exchange students camp, USA
I When starting your reproductive years,
you will start liking
others, hoping that / Hey!
They will like you back. I
You picked the same thing.
To meet Jay, his middle school classmate, in
another side of the world, / I picked it first.
Loneliness caused people to
long for familiar faces. I What is it?
You hand is freezing.
Aren't you cold? It's freezing outside.
And they started to get closer.
You feel warmer?
What is it?
Your hands are freezing too.
Can't you get anything warmer?
What about this?
Just a little.
Hey, Jay!
You're not hanging out outside with Pod.
Sure. Let's go.
But getting closer didn't mean
that he'd think of you like that.
You haven't eaten yet?
I'll have some outside. I Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
People can't choose how they
were born, but we can choose
how we could accept
ourselves or change ourselves
so that someone would see our values.
I'm not sure about photo shooting.
It's okay. I'll help you out.
See you tomorrow, fashion people.
This one is cute.
This one'd suit you well.
Julia Fox once said that
fashion is fun.
It's more than just beauty of cuteness.
If you can tell your
stories through clothes
then you're a genius.
Fashion is also a political statement.
All done. I Thank you.
Well, well, well… long time no see.
Who decided not to show up?
Are you still have to join the shooting?
Not a my more. I'm done.
We can see each other more often.
What is it with Mhong?
Did you talk to him?
I haven't talked to him.
Actually, it's my song.
I should love it.
Can you please change the music?
Okay. I Thanks.
After this,
I'm going to audition in a play.
Yeah? For real?
You have time for that?
Not really. Busy as usual.
But from what you said the other day,
I had enough courage to ask them.
Thank you so much.
Can I get free tickets in advance?
Give me 500.
Joking.
Do you think Tokyo is
acting strange lately?
I see.
Someone is in love.
Were you just talking about me?
Nope. Nothing.
I heard that, you bitch! I
You're eavesdropping?
I heard you two loud and clear.
It's not like you're whispering.
Let's go. I Go ahead.
I'll catch up later. I See you.
Love stinks.
You're in love?
Are you going to the foreign
exchange students reunion?
I miss you, really want to see you there.
What if they do this?
Good.
Turn the other side.
Your leg, move your leg.
Easy there. I Don't look up.
Easy, easy.
I think you look a little too stiff. I Right.
Can you smile with your
eyes, not your lips. I Right.
Bambi, I think you
should pose with no hands.
Easy, you need to pose it gently.
Relax yoru lips. Smile through your eyes.
Smile with your eyes, but not too much.
Okay, let's give it a try.
You're still stiff, Bambi.
Please relax it.
We should close it.
I don't think it'd work.
I don't think I get it.
Bitch, you keep saying that you
don't get it. When will you get it?
Just give it another
try, you're here already.
You think so?
You can do it. I believe in you.
Let's try it.
Okay? Give me your best shot.
Smile with your eyes, be seductive.
Wow! Looking great.
Look at her eyes.
This is great, I like it.
Got pictures already.
It's getting better. I Better.
Let me fix her hair.
She can feel it. I She can.
That's right. It's getting better.
Give me more attitude.
I Give strong attitude.
Great. I So great.
Wow! Your friend is super great.
I told you.
This is the best, I'm about
to burst. I You're bursting?
So spicy / Spicy!
You can move.
Finally. I You're so pretty.
She's my girl!
See? I told you that you could do it.
I really like this feeling.
Can I be fashion people now?
Breaking news! Photoshoot of Bambi and
Pure will be showcased at this exhibition.
You're all invited.
Woah! I Super!
Are you really excited, Lukjan?
I'm inviting you all, are you coming? I
Sorry, need to go to Germany with my grandma.
Pure, you and I have
somewhere to be that day. So No.
Damn, can't go.
Diesel? I I don't think he'd
go. He only plays games.
So it's just gonna be Bambi and I, right?
You're free? I Super free.
What should I wear? I
Don't sweat it. I got you.
But I need to see a man first.
Fine.
Tokyo, hi.
Hurry up. I Sorry.
You're always late. I Don't tell me
off, do we need to boil tomatoes?
You don't eat spicy foods?
You think? I No idea.
You're always joking.
You SUPER LUV'ED me.
If I didn't, you wouldn't see me.
I'd be blended in with some other guys.
When did you come back
from the US? I didn't know.
You didn't?
You didn't care about me.
You care that I didn't care?
Stop playing around. I What is it?
I'm not.
Let's take a picture. I Come on.
Let's get closer. I Can
you bend a little for me?
One..two…three.
Can you check them? I I should check them.
Can I see the pictures? I Sure.
Hello, where are you
at? I'm about to leave.
Diesel, I'm not in the mood
right now, okay? Rain check?
What? What happened?
But I booked the restaurant already.
Can you just cancel it?
I'll take you to a fine dining
restaurant later, okay?
Cancel what? Where're you at? I Bye.
What the fuck!
You can go hang out
with your friend, I can wait.
Don't you say a f... king word.
Are you online to play?
Let's play.
I'm about to leave my place.
Why're you calling me?
Hey, wanna hang out?
Dream?
It's me, Diesel.
Nainoi (Little Boss)
Hey! Wait!
Where're you going?
Something is coming up. Sorry. I Urgent?
But you wanted to eat here.
What's your deal? I drove all the way here.
You can drive to get here
and you can drive to get back.
It shouldn't be a burden
to someone like you.
Someone like me?
I don't think this is the reason.
What's going on? You can tell me frankly.
I don't like your father.
He sued people and sent them
to jail for nothing, many people.
You think I'm a big fan of my Dad?
I am the one who invited
you out, not my Dad.
And you were the one who
told me not to judge people.
Look at you.
What is it called? So good.
You've never had spicy
clams growing up? Like how?
How're you getting back
home? Will your Dad pick you up?
He can't fucking come here.
I can give you a ride.
No need to.
I can take a bus.
Why would you trouble
yourself by doing that?
Fine, if you don't want me to
give you a ride, I can call you a cab.
No need to.
I said no need to.
We have to wait.
So you don't like your Dad?
You want to compete? What level?
Woah! To the max.
Why did you hate him?
What if your Mom was in jail,
would you help her out, if you were a dad?
Sure I will.
My Dad won't.
This one?
Action.
I'm so fucking tired of this kind of life.
Today I held a pen
and I run down the stairs for 11 floors,
then I stopped at the window.
DAD!
LISTEN TO ME!
Why did I bother to
work at this stupid office?
I don't even want to.
What I like is not here.
What I like is over there.
CUT!
Tang, they gave me the
part, they really liked it.
I see.
I'm glad to see you happy.
But..
They sent me the schedule. I And?
It's quite a lot.
Can you help me with the time management?
I can boost my energy here.
Please? I You don't have enough on your plate
already? You don't even have time to eat.
Fine, I'll talk with Joe.
But you need to work on your BL couple.
They wanted you to boost
up your chemisty with him.
If you can do it, I believe that
you two can go further than this.
You know that I try.
Here, have some.
We still have more to go.
I'm hungry.
Slow down.
Let's go. I Thank you.
I'll be there in a minute.
Hello?
Bambi? You're free?
Why do you want to
meet after everyone left?
I passed the audition for the play.
The director really liked me.
I'm so glad.
Thank you so much.
What are you doing?
What is it?
If you don't think of
me that way, don't do it.
But I think of you that way.
What about you?
Do you think the same?
Should we go?
Bambi..
Will you be my girlfriend?
Let's go. I I'll walk you off.
So chic!
See you later. I Sure.
See ya. I I'll see you later.
Well, you famous star.
From being Princess of
Trash to your new look.
Oh my goodness!
My model. I How are you, sis?
Love your outfit. I Who's your stylist?
Of course it's you. But
who styled you anyway?
Why?
Sweet look. I haven't
seen you like this before.
I want to look pretty, so what?
Spread positive energy
in negative ways.
Well, you look beautiful,
I didn't say otherwise.
Hey, Miss Duangtawan is here.
Who is she?
She's the owner of Devi.
This is a witch of fashion world.
When she comments on someone,
they will either be famous or a flop.
Who can impress her
will be a bigger star like Kimia.
I need to say hi to her. See you.
You go and say hi.
No. You go and say hi.
Duangtawan, hello.
How is it? Do you like it?
It's nice.
This girl is good.
You know her?
Of course I know her.
Bambi..
Hello. I She's my friend.
I'll let you two talk.
Hello, Miss Duangtawan.
My name is Bambi.
This is a great photo.
Thank you.
Jib,
her outfit is cute.
Did you put it together by yourself?
Yes. I You're good.
No stylist?
Nothing.
If I have a chance, I'd
really love to work with you.
Are you free tonight?
Yes, I am.
Free tonight?
I'm outside, about to head
home, what's up? I Yeah?
Can I see you?
What? Why? I I want to see you.
Get water in
and interaction happens inside.
Don't take it off.
I'll do it now.
Just relax.
Mine is barely getting hard.
Can we change position?
Go ahead.
Feel so fucking good.
Fucking good.
Let me ask you something.
You know that.
I really like you.
You're gonna see me as
a sex object, just like that?
It's not like that. I What
do you think of me?
I like you.
I wanted to flirt with you.
But I was too young back then.
So I wouldn't dare to.
Stop pouting, okay?
I'll start flirting with you now.
Okay?
I don't know.
Come on, let's cuddle.
Sure, man.
First day of being mine.
You're talking nonsense.
Isn't it true?
Yup.
You like to play with boobs?
Sure, I do.
Hello.
Make yourself at home.
I got my new collection here
and some archive pieces.
You can pick your favorite pieces and then
style them for me.
Okay.
Nothing serious, just see
it as playing paper dolls.
Right, Jib,
about the meeting…
Why don't you visit my
showroom for a Go-See?
What? Go-See?
What the hell did you do to get a Go-See?
Can you tell me what it is?
This is your chance.
If you go to hang out with her
and she likes you, this is
your chance to work with her.
Who'd have know,
this could be the next DEVI girl.
If everything is all set, then
I want to do it next week.
So we don't have to rush
it, what about Wednesday?
Sure.
Well…
It's fine.
What's your passion?
I like fashion.
People who are standing right here
have a passion for fashion, all of them.
But what's your other
passion beside fashion?
I think I really like
fashion, Ms.Duangtawan.
Do you know Tom Ford?
Yes.
Do you know that before
Tom Ford became a designer
he liked art history
and architecture.
When he started his
fashion journey, he used it
to film industry.
It's not enough to have
only one passion for fashion.
And do you know
what Tom Ford didn't like the most
in clients coming to buy his clothes?
I don't know.
He didn't like it when
they bought the whole look
right off the runway
looks that he styled them.
Those people
don't even know what they like.
They don't even know who they are.
Isn't that pathetic?
I invited you here
because I wanted to get to know you better.
But you chose the same look at Kimia.
You wasted my time, you know that?
You said that you didn't have any stylist,
were you lying back then?
My friend helped me out.
Some people see
fashion as something so shallow.
Actually, fashion is a way
to tell history, economic,
and politics in different ages.
Let me ask you something,
models with no thoughts, no knowledge,
full of lies,
or claiming ideas of others,
are no better than clothes
hangers, don't you think?
I used to believe that
taste is something ones can learn
but you're the first person
who makes me question about my belief.
You can walk back, right?
I feel like
I poured my heart and soul
into this work, like really meant it,
I thought I could
communicate to the audience,
but when it's launched
people didn't get it, they
didn't even understand it.
Shine through my mouth.
So I am the only one who gets it.
I will divide my troubles into two piles.
The first one is something
that I can manage or control.
And the other one is something
that I can't control at all.
Selling nuggets or jokes. I What the heck?
So funny. I Confusing.
This type of problem is the one that
I can't manage or control.
When I know that I can do nothing about it.
The only thing you can
do is to live in the moment.
I need to live with it.
We don't like ourselves today but.
Bambi's new look is the best.
It doesn't mean that we won't like
ourselves tomorrow or the days after that.
Face, hair, outfits are
well put. I So pretty.
She's here to slay. I A
star can shine anywhere.
We don't like ourselves today but
it doesn't mean that we won't like
ourselves tomorrow or the days after that.
Ms.Duangtawan is the
one who started it all.
I really need to thank her because
nobody knew me five years ago
but she invited me to be her muse.
That's when people
started to know me better.
And it gave me a chance to
work with many global brands.
Oh my!
A model who claimed ideas from others
- is no better than a clothes hanger, right?
- Duangtawan.
I wrote a piece, can you
share it for me? I I can't.
You haven't talked to her since the fight?
When you're super mad,
what did you do? I Like this.
Fucking Name!
I met Mhong. I What happened?
What is it like to be a wealthy person?
Can I join your Mom's birthday party?