You did amazing today, little director.
I trusted you today.
Trust you with what?
Trust me to take care of you
as your boyfriend.
I'm glad you and Aurora made up.
It's all thanks to Sun.
Which one is that?
This one.
Isn't this Teacher Solar?
Sun?
[Class 2/1]
The English class play results are out.
We won first place!
Yay!
You guys were amazing,
so I got you something.
Here.
I printed these photos
for you to keep as a memory.
So you'll remember
we did something fun together.
Wait. What about Sun's photo?
The secret one comes last!
Come get yours.
Here you go.
Here.
If things keep going like this,
we probably don't have to worry
about Sun anymore.
That's a relief.
By the way, how's your guitar practice going?
Have you started yet?
You haven't?
What are you waiting for?
Well, I'm already exhausted
from teaching the kids.
Give me a break.
That's exactly why
you need to hurry up and practice
so you can take a long break.
Or do you want to keep dealing with Sun
every other day?
Do you want me to help you practice?
It's okay. I can manage on my own.
You might want to hurry,
because in the parent group chat I'm in,
they're starting to get suspicious about Sun.
It could blow up into a school-wide issue.
But no matter what,
I'm sure
our acting principal can handle the chaos.
My kid has been complaining
that the food at school
isn't really to their taste.
Please look into this, Principal.
Of course. I'll handle it.
Could you please check
the school supply purchase documents?
Of course. Let me handle it.
[Ms. Pang (The Picky One)]
Still sure about that?
I made it through another day.
You're pretty hardworking, huh?
You always take all the problems on yourself.
Wanna try letting others help for a change?
Listen, Teacher Jee.
I take on these problems
because it's my responsibility.
It's not right to burden other people, is it?
If you need to vent,
you can always vent to the two of us.
That's exactly what I need.
My spiritual journey is beginning.
Just think of it as nourishing my soul.
Basically, he'll be dumping
his work on me for months.
Miss Fresh, I'm sure you'll grow from this.
Goodbye.
Grow from this? My ass!
He's clearly just dumping
all this crap on me!
Oh, my inner voice is getting so loud
these days.
Gosh, I'm so freaking annoyed!
How can someone just leave their job
for that long?
Isn't what Principal Maximoff is doing
a violation of employment law?
How could the main campus let this slide?
The main campus is actually
letting it happen.
Wait, no.
I think it was Ms. Pang who approved this.
Ms. Pang, who you said is
the main campus' stickler?
Super strict. Always gets what she wants.
Double standards?
No.
Not double.
Ten standards.
Oh, I'm so glad people are talking about me.
Ms. Pang.
It's been a while, Principal Sodchuen.
Wait, no.
Acting Principal Sodchuen.
What are you guys doing?
Ms. Pang came to school without notice.
What?
Ms. Pang, the main campus representative?
Please don't worry, Ms. Pang.
While I've been Acting Principal,
I've been sending regular email updates
to Principal Maximoff.
I'm well aware of that,
but I'm here today
because something caught my attention,
and I'd like to look into it.
This is Teacher Solar, isn't it?
Yes.
Why?
Several parents have reported
that this teacher often behaves like a child,
claiming it's role-play,
and often says bad things to the kids.
It's quite an interesting matter, isn't it?
Yes.
May I know where Teacher Solar is?
May I see him?
I'd like to have a little chat with him.
Unfortunately, Teacher Solar has a free period
this afternoon,
so he asked me for permission
to go out for personal errands.
That's alright.
I may not see him today,
but I'll certainly see him
on the annual school inspection day.
Please excuse me.
Let me walk you out.
Here.
Please, go ahead.
Hey, what are you guys doing?
Sodchuen, what should we do now?
Teacher Jee,
please inform all the teachers immediately
to make sure everything is
as ready as possible.
I'm sure Ms. Pang will move up
the annual inspection.
Noted!
Pobmek, this is not an order, but a plea.
Please work on your guitar
as soon as you can.
I'm begging you,
so that Solar can get back to being Solar.
Okay.
I'm counting on you.
Pobmek, why are you even doing this?
I didn't send you to school
for this kind of thing.
How's it going?
Are you getting the hang of it now?
Hey. I'm sorry.
I just got excited.
It's alright,
Take your time, okay?
Yup.
Let's go. Lunch break is over.
- Let's get ready to teach.
- Jeez! I can't get up!
Help me.
What are you talking about? Let's go.
Come on!
I need a Solar fix.
Hey!
Hey! We're outside!
No!
Come on, let's go!
[Kiss Voucher]
[1 kiss/hour]
Are you really going to use that here?
Hey!
Are you two in a BL series?
Hey! No teasing!
Why aren't you in class?
Why are you hiding here?
I don't understand anything anyway.
The class is so boring.
Yeah.
I know how you feel.
I went through the same thing as a kid.
Right, Teacher? Math is so not fun.
I know, right? How can math be...
Hey! That's my subject!
No!
Hey! Are you going to write me up?
No, no, no, no!
No!
Stop teasing the kids.
Of course.
I'll look into it as soon as possible.
Thank god you found out in advance
that Ms. Pang is coming tomorrow.
And luckily, tomorrow is Solar's day.
Good.
This is my first year being at school
during inspection day.
I'm pretty nervous.
It's not just you. I'm nervous too.
I think someone's even more nervous
than we are.
Hey, are you really a P.E. teacher?
That little run
already got you out of breath.
Stop teasing me. We're in big trouble.
Ms. Pang, are you here on business?
This is quite sudden.
I'm here to do the inspection today instead.
Oh, welcome.
Our school is always ready.
We just did a clean-up together, right?
No wonder I can smell it.
Does it really smell that clean?
Smells like it's just for show.
Actually, we help each other
clean like this every week.
Oh?
Please come in, Ms. Pang.
All the teachers are ready to welcome you.
Aren't we going to welcome the parents
as well?
May I ask why you're here?
Of course, we had to come.
Someone said
there's a parents' meeting today.
A meeting? There isn't one.
If there were, I'd know.
[Urgent Parents' Meeting at 11 AM tomorrow
- Ms. Pang]
Here.
There must be some misunderstanding.
I didn't receive that message.
Of course, you didn't.
Ms. Pang created that group chat,
and you're not in it, Principal.
Parents, please come in.
Solar!
I'm Pobmek.
No, I mean go take Solar home now!
- Solar!
- Go!
We use the sprinklers
to water the trees every morning.
It saves a lot of work.
Let me get straight to
what I'm concerned about.
Who's Sun?
Sun, let's go!
- What?
- Let's go.
- What, Uncle?
- Oh.
I think that's just a nickname
the teacher and students use playfully.
It's probably nothing important.
Where are we going?
Teacher.
What's going on, Uncle?
Why did you drag me here?
Keep quiet, Sun!
I have a big secret to tell you.
You see that woman?
Yeah.
Actually, she's a witch.
Huh?
She disguises herself during the day,
plotting to take the kids' hearts.
Huh? Seriously?
Yes!
We have to hide from that auntie.
We cannot let her find us.
Got it?
Okay.
What is this violence?
Oh, let me explain.
Teacher Jee really loves nature.
Every day after school,
he comes here to lie on the ground
and soak up the sun.
Girls, do any of you know Teacher Solar?
What's he like?
The way you're asking us to help you,
and you even brought dessert to convince us.
What do you call this again?
This is called bribery.
But it's normal in our country.
Girls, please don't think of it that way.
Just think of it as helping each other out.
Okay. I want to help Teacher Solar anyway.
What would you like us to do?
Teacher Solar is kind.
He's a good teacher.
We're happy.
Is there anything else
you'd like to say about Teacher Solar?
Whoever speaks honestly
will get a reward from me today.
Actually, it's nothing serious.
It's just that Teacher Solar
keeps switching back and forth
between acting like a kid and an adult.
Teacher Solar just gets into character,
remember?
But sometimes it's a bit weird.
Maybe there's something
we don't know about him.
Like something unusual.
Yeah. Something unusual.
Excuse me?
There's a teacher who's unusual?
He's the one I think has a problem.
Girls, has Teacher Solar gone home?
Not yet.
He was just playing with us earlier.
Wow! You're so sweet!
Here's your reward.
We should go find Teacher Solar.
I think he's still at school.
Let's go.
[Principal Sodchuen: Run!]
Let's go!
What should we do?
What are you doing, Teacher?
Four, King, help me!
What do we get in return?
Hey!
You kids always want something in return!
Come on, Teacher.
Just a little snack would be enough for us.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
I don't have anything to give you right now.
What do you want?
Oh, come on!
Hey!
Why are you hiding over there?
Oh, my shoe's loose.
Sun!
Oh, where did Sun and Pobmek go?
I don't know either.
They probably got away and went home.
Teacher Solar has probably really left.
I didn't see him
while I was cleaning the school.
That's alright. I can come back another day.
Thank you, Teacher...
Pobmek.
Thank you, Teacher Pobmek.
Teacher Pobmek.
Why haven't I heard your name before?
I'm usually aware of everything
that goes on in this school.
If you don't mind, could we talk for a bit?
[Pobmek: Ms. Pang caught me.]
Sodchuen, is something wrong?
What did you study?
Accounting.
So you didn't want to be a teacher
in the first place,
since you didn't major in education.
Are you qualified enough?
I definitely am.
I have the knowledge, the experience,
and the techniques...
But the skills
to teach and handle elementary students
are specialized.
That's not what you studied.
What about your teaching license?
Do you have one?
I'm about to get it.
What?
Do you even have a lesson plan
for your students?
Teacher Pobmek has a clear lesson plan.
He prepares everything as best as he can
for the kids.
I'm sorry.
What happened to your face?
My face?
What's wrong with it?
Forget it.
Honestly, without a license,
it's already over for you.
What about you, Mr. Jee?
- I have a license.
- You do realize
that having a license doesn't mean
you can get away with this, right?
Protecting Mr. Pobmek like this
violates the teacher's code of ethics.
Hold on, Ms. Pang. I think...
I thought the problem was just Teacher Solar,
but now I see that
no one's doing their jobs properly,
especially you.
Don't make me take this
to upper management.
Your last chance is to fire
Teacher Solar and Mr. Pobmek.
Hold on.
Isn't that going too far, Ms. Pang?
If you don't follow my recommendation,
it will go much further.
Just go!
Get out!
It's okay, Sun.
The witch is gone.
Yay!
We're safe from the witch
and the zombies now!
Yeah.
Everything's back to normal.
Let's go home.
Sodchuen...
Don't tell me you've been
pacing back and forth in here all night.
Yeah.
I was the cause of everything
that went wrong yesterday.
How could I let it go so easily?
Sodchuen.
I...
I've been thinking about this all night.
I've decided to quit.
No, you can't do this.
You can't quit.
Then you're not quitting either.
Sodchuen.
Why are you helping me?
I'm a terrible teacher.
The kids don't even like me.
No one wants to learn from me.
I don't even know how to be a good teacher.
That's not true at all, Pobmek.
You're not only a good teacher.
You also helped someone else become one.
So, there are four stages.
Young kids are sensorimotor.
Kindergarten kids are preoperational.
Elementary kids are concrete operational.
And teens are formal operational.
Got it, babe?
Solar! Are you even listening to me?
What are you doing?
I'm helping you study
even though it's not even my major.
Stop it.
You're the one who should stop.
Don't you know that when you're teaching,
you're so sexy?
What's wrong with you, huh?
Get up! Study!
Come on! No!
I've been studying since morning.
I'm about to throw up from all these words.
- That bad?
- Yeah!
Okay. Wait here.
Where are you going?
I've been preparing all this for you,
since I heard you have to
take the certification exam.
Whose boyfriend are you? You're so cute.
That's not all, bro.
[Kiss Voucher: 1 kiss/hour]
Ta-da!
- What's this?
- This is to give you a boost
when you're too tired to keep going.
You can use it with me.
But there's one condition.
You can only use it once every hour.
And you have to study.
- Got it?
- Yeah.
Okay.
You're even timing how long you study?
That's more like it!
No.
I'm timing how many minutes are left
until I can kiss my boyfriend again.
- Hey!
- Keep studying!
"Keep studying!"
- Are you going to study or not?
- "Are you going to study or not?"
Your support helped Solar
become the teacher he is today.
Both Solar and I believe...
that you can do it.
Sodchuen, I'm going to pass
the teacher certification exam.
And I'm going to fight for my students!
We're not quitting anymore!
Wow.
I'm going to cry.
Because you're touched by what we said?
Because of these paper scraps!
My OCD is screaming!
Sorry.
I'm glad you're not quitting.
And that you're determined
to pass the certification exam.
And I'm so happy
you're standing up for our students.
Solar, I'm ready to fight.
I'm so fired up!
But I still don't know
what to do with all of this.
No need to worry about that.
I think I have a plan.
Principal Sodchuen called
this urgent meeting.
What do you think it's about?
It can only be about one thing.
Teacher Solar.
There she is.
Hello, everyone.
I've called this urgent meeting
because there's something
I'd like to confirm.
The rumor that one of our teachers
is acting unusually...
is true.
Who is it?
Really?
What does that mean?
And the teacher in question is Teacher Solar.
Hello.
My name is Solar.
I'm the homeroom teacher of Grade 2, Class 1.
On the day I'm filming this,
I'm my adult self.
But on the day of the parents' meeting
where you're watching this clip,
I'll be Sun.
Hello.
My name is Sun.
I'm 7 years old, in Grade 2 Class 1.
On the days when Solar is his adult self,
he gives his full effort to his work.
He shows up to teach effectively,
and he's loved by both students and teachers.
On the days he's absent,
other teachers take turns
covering his classes.
We may not be able to stop things like this
from happening,
but we can help each other.
Actually,
my concern is not only Teacher Solar,
but also Teacher Pobmek.
No, I don't think I can call him
a teacher yet,
because he doesn't even have
a teaching license.
Huh?
Why's that?
I admit it,
and I apologize to all the parents.
It's true that I don't have
a teaching license yet.
Thank you for admitting that,
but it'd be better if you resigned,
because disregarding the rules like this
could never make you a good teacher.
Auntie Witch, you didn't have to be so harsh
on Teacher Pobmek.
Auntie?
You're calling me Auntie?
Teacher Pobmek is kind,
tries his best to teach,
and he really cares about us.
If you don't believe me, look at this.
Sun, that notebook is so small.
Who's going to be able to read that?
I thought you get farsighted
when you're older.
What Sun said is true.
Teacher Pobmek works really hard,
and he really cares about us.
Hey!
Are you writing our names down
to tell our parents?
You can't do that!
I'm not writing your names down
to tell your parents.
- I'm going to give you grades.
- What? Really?
You're going easy on us?
Yay!
I'm not going easy on you!
I'm going to give you two
some intensive tutoring.
Huh?
Once we really paid attention to
what Teacher Pobmek taught us,
- math became super easy.
- Good job!
- Yay!
Teacher Pobmek
and all the other teachers here
work really hard to teach us,
and that makes us want to come to school.
Sweetie, you're just one of
over a hundred students.
I can't just go by your opinion alone.
Actually, we can.
The heart of learning is the students, right?
- That's true.
- Agreed.
As the acting principal,
I admit I may have always given in to others,
but this time, let me be selfish for once.
I insist that I will not fire Teacher Solar
or Teacher Pobmek.
I agree.
Let's give them a chance.
I'm sorry,
but I'm here on behalf of the administration.
I really can't let this slide so easily.
That said, I'll respect your decision,
Acting Principal Sodchuen.
Thank you.
Don't thank me yet.
I have one condition.
I'll allow this for one year only.
I hope the teachers with issues
will be able to sort themselves out.
Thank you, Ms. Pang.
Thank you, parents.
Thank you,
beautiful Ms. Pang.
Thank you, everyone.
[Teacher Certification Exam Study Guide]
What are you doing?
Laundry, of course. Can't you tell?
This is weird.
Well, you've had a long day, Uncle.
So many people were bothering you.
I don't want to make you any more tired.
You've really grown up, huh?
Of course.
I'm all grown up now.
You don't have to tell me what to do.
I can handle things myself.
Besides, you have something else
to do, right?
I can do my own laundry.
You don't need to keep teaching me.
Use that time to practice your guitar.
Come here, you little troublemaker.
Let me hug you.
So nice.
I feel twice as encouraged now.
Put the clothes in the machine
and go take a shower.
I know! I said you don't need to teach me.
[Jak - Ka - Jee:
No need to extend your temp license.]
[You've been studying
for your graduate diploma for a year.]
[Just go for the full license mid-year.]
[Pobmek: Okay.
Jee, I need your help with something.]
[Kiss Voucher]
[1 kiss/hour]
You want to use this again, right?
I can save it for later.
Then this time,
I'll give you one for free.
My amazing boyfriend deserves it.
These are in the way.
What? You're at my condo?
Your mom just came to visit.
Why are you so stressed?
I haven't told my mom.
- Hello.
- That I'm dating a guy.
This is just like a BL series!
You two are so cute.
Your mom seems kind.
Aren't you overthinking?
My mom is the reason I feel this way.
I can do it now!
I guess life is like this.
There's so much more to learn.
Well said.