Wait, we didn't make a single penny,
and spent 200 yuan on car repairs.
Can you even drive properly?
Huh?
What?
A-Are you listening to me?
No...
Please don't.
What are you doing?
Were it not for these two jerks,
would you pay the 30,000 yuan
for car repairs
out of your own pocket?
-Bro!
-All right, enough.
That's enough.
Do you know why?
I know.
The car repair
costs 50,000 yuan this time.
W-Wasn't it 30,000 yuan?
70,000 yuan.
Then 50,000 yuan is fine...
E-Enough, cut it out.
120,000 yuan in total.
Can you pay it off in a couple of days?
Can you?
-Yes!
-No!
-Yes, yes.
[Born with Luck]
[Episode 18]
That's not right.
43 million.
For 9.
It shouldn't be 47 million.
It should be
4.77 million...
and 777.
I pressed an extra zero.
Thank God I didn't transfer it.
So embarrassing.
[Liu Bei's Location] [Pinghe]
Can you snatch our things again?
[Rongcheng]
Hello,
this is Rongcheng.
Hello?
Uncle,
it's all done.
Where is the stuff?
I got it.
Where is he?
I'll bring him back in a bit.
Okay.
I'll sharpen the axe.
Uncle,
I just checked Liu Bei's phone.
The last call was made
to Rongcheng Group.
You suspect Liu Bei was
instructed by Zhou Rong?
I don't know.
I can't tell.
Come back first.
Who is there?
Ren,
it's me, me,
Du Cong, Du Cong.
What are you doing here?
Yeah,
w-what am I doing...
Out with it!
Ren is asking you!
Are you tailing us?
No!
I...
I... I-I was being tailed.
You were being tailed?
Who was tailing you?
I don't know, either.
I... I was planning to go back
to the company
to check if I turned off my heater.
But as soon as I got out of the car,
2 people rushed toward me.
I got scared and hid here.
Oh, please.
Who do you think you are?
Why would you be tailed?
What?
You think you're a target
for assassination, huh?
W-What's wrong, Ren?
Where are the people tailing you?
I'm not sure.
I hid in the car
and didn't dare to look outside.
Are you telling the truth?
I'm a bastard if I lie to you.
I remember your girlfriend
has been asking to borrow your car,
right?
But I've never lent it to her.
Ren,
if she asks to borrow it again,
I'll break up with her.
Don't. She's a nice girl.
Give me the key.
Drive my car
and give it to her right now.
You're almost 30.
You finally got a girlfriend.
You definitely can't break up.
Take this.
Ren.
I...
Get in the car!
We're staying here tonight.
Ren, what's wrong?
Hope I'm overthinking it.
Hello.
Li.
Don't hang up, don't.
Who said I wouldn't lend you the car?
You know what? Because of this,
I even had a fight with my boss.
I told him,
"If you don't lend me the car,
I'll quit."
See?
Why would I brag to you?
Ren gave me the car key himself.
I'm on my way to your place.
Don't worry.
I absolutely won't delay
your use of the car.
[Xiangji Temple Intersection]
Found it!
Five o'clock,
at Xiangji Temple Intersection.
[Xiangji Temple Intersection]
Liu Bei went in and never came out.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Alright.
No matter what, we have to get
our first deal tonight.
But no one is taking the bait.
What?
I'm saying,
w-well,
no one is taking the bait.
Could it be that
they see two people in the car
and don't dare to get in?
You've got a point.
What are you doing?
You
go find a target yourself.
When you find one,
bring them to the river.
I'll wait for you there.
Then it's settled.
No, w-why should I go?
Because you can drive.
Go!
Curse my life.
Where are you going?
You can put it in the trunk.
It's fine.
My stuff...
Why is it so heavy?
It can't be out of my sight.
Go around, go around.
You may go around.
Hop in from this side.
Get in from this side.
Just go around.
[Police]
How are we supposed to find him?
Let's split up to search.
Yes.
Let's go.
Chief!
The blood.
It's in the sand pile.
Walk close along the edge.
Bastard.
[Liu Bei's Location] [Pinghe]
How dare you run away?
I'm going to kill you.
-What are you doing?
-You scared me.
What is this? It's so heavy.
-Didn't you tell me you'd come that way?
-And then I came from this side...
You go first.
Tinggang, you know what?
I was so smart just now.
That guy put the suitcase
in the back seat.
-I said...
-Drive.
Right! You understand me!
So I drove...
I'm telling you to drive!
Understand my foot.
Disgusting.
I didn't mean
I understand you.
I meant you didn't understand me.
I know.
Yes,
understand my foot.
Hurry up.
They're catching up.
[Liu Bei's Location] [Pinghe]
Don't. Don't.
Be gentle. Gentle.
Why is it so heavy?
Don't break it.
[Pingjiang Road]
[Binjiang Road] [Zhoujia Town]
Why is it gone?
[Pingjiang Road]
[Binjiang Road] [Zhoujia Town]
[Setting] [Reboot]
[Your device will reboot.] [Yes.]
[Leading 3G life]
What treasure is inside?
Nice treasure.
What treasure?
Take it slow.
What are you doing? Don't be too excited.
I'm opening it.
Open it.
How is it?
Is it good?
Just tell me if it's good.
Is it gold?
Is it...
Brake! Brake!
Brake!
[Pingjiang Road]
[Binjiang Road] [Zhoujia Town]
It's you two again.
Bro.
C-Cut it out!
R-Run now!
Sorry!
[Honey]
Honey, I'm waiting for you.
Remember to fill up the tank.
Karma is going to come for this woman!
Hello?
Ren.
I got hit.
What happened?
Ren.
It really isn't
my fault this time.
It's definitely not your fault.
Really.
Please believe me.
Of course I believe you.
You don't need to pay for the car repair.
Just rest assured
and go wait at home.
Ren.
Chief Zhang, Captain Wang.
Liu Bei brought the sand inside,
cleaned up the blood on the floor,
and then swept the sand out.
After a couple of days,
the bloodstains could hardly be found.
He is indeed a veteran.
Why would
Liu Bei be the murderer?
Why couldn't it be
that Liu Bei was killed?
Liu Bei can fight,
and he is a desperado.
Would he be killed by others?
A desperado who can fight
is not necessarily invincible.
Why couldn't it be that another desperado
with greater strength
killed Liu Bei?
That makes sense.
That makes sense?
But we haven't seen the body.
How can we confirm
that Liu Bei was killed?
With that amount of blood
in the sand outside,
the person definitely couldn't survive.
You haven't tested the blood yet.
How can you be sure it's human blood?
Chief Zhang, Captain Wang,
Lang Bowen was beaten up at Fenglinwan.
Who did it?
We're still looking into the details.
Lang Bowen has been sent
to the People's Hospital.
Should we go there?
Yes.
I'll go there with Li Qian.
You two keep an eye on things here.
Okay.
Doubt the doubt of the doubt.
Get to work.
What are you wondering about?
What do you think?
Let's assume that Liu Bei is really dead.
It must have something to do
with the transaction
in Zhou Rong's villa today.
What do you mean?
This method is too professional.
It's not like the work of ordinary people.
The only ones I can think of
are Zhou Rong's gang.
It might also be the seller.
After all, anyone who dares
to resell bianzhong
is surely no ordinary person.
Why
couldn't it be that Liu Bei
killed the other one?
That's unlikely.
Liu Bei was being hunted.
Even if he killed someone,
he wouldn't spend so much effort
cleaning up the scene.
Escaping mattered more.
But
Zhou Rong or Zhu Yifei's gang
would do this to cover their tracks
and continue
the transaction.
Therefore,
can this case now be merged
and handled with Zhou Rong's case?
That's for the higher-ups to decide.
I wouldn't dare to say too much.
You're very meticulous, girl.
Why are you sighing?
I just drank too much
and got into a fight.
It's nothing.
Hurry up and go home.
I'll stay here with you tonight.
Why would you stay with me?
Can you give injections
or change dressings?
What if you need
to use the bathroom at night?
There are so many people outside.
I don't need you to help me.
Just leave now.
Bowen,
Zhang Yi'ang is here.
Hurry! Go to the bathroom!
Hide in the bathroom for a bit.
Did we go to the wrong room?
Chief Zhang.
Oh, it's you.
Officer Li.
What happened?
I've been waiting for you.
What's wrong?
I got beaten up by someone.
You got beaten up?
By whom?
How many of them were there?
Two.
[Patient's bedside card]
[Name: Lang Bowen]
Three.
Four.
Five? Or six?
Lang Bowen,
we don't have time
to joke around with you here.
Look at me.
I'm in no mood to joke around with you.
Chief Zhang.
I don't know
if it's because I drank too much
or if it's from the beating
that I might have a concussion.
When I look at you now,
I see double.
D-Don't move.
If you move, I see four.
Oh, no, I feel nauseous.
Nauseous?
Did you also not see clearly
what they looked like?
Let me think.
Take your time to recall.
I didn't see clearly.
Fenglinwan has surveillance cameras.
You can go ask Lu Yibo
to check the footage.
Since it's about me,
he wouldn't dare take it lightly.
Oh, right.
The surveillance system was upgraded
last night.
All cameras in Fenglinwan
were down for 2 hours.
For real?
For real.
You've checked?
Get well soon.
Rest well.
Chief Zhang,
you can't just leave like this.
I was beaten up like this
for no reason.
You can't just
ask several questions and leave.
You can't do this to me.
Let go.
We can talk properly.
Let go of me.
Chief Zhang,
who beat me up?
Why did they do this to me?
I won't dare to go out
until this is figured out.
Chief Zhang,
is this still a society ruled by law?
Did you notice anything?
He's injured, but still quite strong.
You can't do this to me.
A wasted trip.
What's wrong?
Two.
There should be two people who beat him.
He paused for a second
and then said three or four.
He said three or four
just to confuse us.
The truth is in the details.
And when he talked about
the people who hit him,
he said "they."
"They" means it wasn't just one person.
Most likely, there were two.
Zhou Rong was also robbed by two people.
Could these two
be those two?
"They" could also mean three or four.
Five or six.
See?
Why must it be two?
I told you
he said two at first,
then paused,
and said three or four.
He said three or four
just in order to confuse us.
These are the details.
Eight pieces.
Uncle.
Everything's ready.
Where is the stuff?
I already got it.
I put Liu Bei's body
in the box for the bianzhong
to bring back.
I went outside to take a taxi.
Just as I put the box in the car,
the driver ran away.
Oh, my god.
Zheng,
you got robbed
by a taxi driver?
It definitely wasn't
an ordinary taxi driver!
He must be Zhou Rong's man, Uncle!
Uncle,
shouldn't we make some preparations?
Prepare for what?
Take our weapons!
For what?
To fight Zhou Rong.
Zheng, Zheng.
Some things shouldn't be rushed.
Hang it up
and let the wind blow.
Let's go to sleep.
Let the wind blow?
So many people in Fenglinwan
couldn't stop these two?
Both of them were too good at fighting.
So you tried to stop them but failed.
By the time we got the news,
they had already run away.
Yibo!
Bowen is one of our own.
We should've looked out for him
on our turf!
Rong,
you have no idea.
Lang Bowen was drunk
and stirred up trouble
in every private room.
Other than you,
who else could keep him under control?
Are you saying
Bowen asked for it?
Exactly.
He just ran into two tough guys.
Mr. Zhou,
if you had been there,
I would have definitely
fought them to the death!
Save it!
Mr. Zhou.
We found them.
Look.
This is the clearest one.
Look, the ones who came to your house
and beat...
There's nothing else. You can leave.
I-I'll get going.
The ones who came to your house
and beat you up last time
[Lobby 1]
were also these two, right?
I'd recognize those two
even if they were reduced to ashes.
Right after snatching the phone,
they went to find Lang Bowen.
They must be trying
to get the phone password.
Last night, Du Cong was
hit right after leaving the company.
Du Cong said
the ones who hit him this time
are the same ones from last time.
The car he drove last time
was the one you usually ride in.
They wanted to mess with me?
Could it be Zhu Yifei?
But what's in it
for an antique trafficker like him?
It definitely has something to do
with him.
Could it be that
someone is pulling the strings behind him?
I don't care who it is.
Who was the last person in Sanjiangkou
to mess with me?
Lu Zheng.
Even the Chief
of the Public Security Bureau is gone.
Why would I fear an antique trafficker?
I'll take some men right now
to find Zhu Yifei.
Wait a minute.
Have Li Penggai
go find the phone.
You come with me
to visit Lang Bowen.
Okay.
[Sanjiangkou People's Hospital]
Mr. Zhou.
Stay still.
Well.
Mr. Zhou.
How are you doing?
I...
It hurts.
I just had the doctor
give me a painkiller.
You're in high spirits.
Seems like you're not hurt too badly.
I have a bone crack.
The doctor said I need to improve
my blood circulation
to recover quickly.
Watching this can speed up
my blood circulation.
Did you get an X-ray?
Yes, I did.
Mr. Zhou, Ren, you're here.
Yangyang.
Why are you here again?
I brought you food.
Bring out the X-ray film for me.
Here you are, Mr. Zhou.
Read that report
to Mr. Zhou.
[Scan Report]
Imaging findings show
a proximal diaphyseal fracture
of the lower leg.
The fracture line is transverse
and located in the middle of the tibia.
The fracture line is clearly visible.
Both ends
of the fracture are well-aligned
with no obvious dislocation.
No abnormalities are seen
in the surrounding soft tissue.
Didn't you say it was a bone crack?
How come it is a fracture now?
It doesn't matter.
How long will it take to heal?
A bone injury like this
will take at least 100 days.
You see,
I can't move at a crucial time like this.
Have you found those two jerks?
We're still looking for them.
I can't be of much help.
Focus on your recovery.
I need to recover,
but the work still needs to be done.
Take all the guys outside
with you later.
No way.
You need people around you
in this condition.
Mr. Zhou,
I can get the priorities straight.
At a crucial time like this,
finding the phone
matters more than anything else.
How about I find you a specialist
in the provincial capital
to get a second opinion
and avoid a misdiagnosis?
Don't bother.
It's just a minor injury.
Doctors in Sanjiangkou can handle it.
Bowen,
caffeine
comes from coffee cherries.
So, every cause has an effect,
and every effect has a cause.
Bowen,
Mr. Zhou means
that in some matters,
we are all in the same boat.
I'm very curious.
Why did you go to Fenglingwan
to drink and pick a fight
right after I called you
and talked about the lost phone? Well...
It's weird, isn't it?
If my suspicion is wrong,
I'll lose this hand of mine to you, Bowen.
But there's no knife.
Yangyang.
Go find a scalpel.
Jianren,
come at me if you have a problem.
Don't scare my brother.
And I must correct you.
What do you mean by "in some matters,
we are all in the same boat"?
In all matters,
we are all in the same boat.
Am I right, Mr. Zhou?
Exactly.
Who are you trying to scare?
Yes, Mentor.
I see, Mentor.
Don't worry, Mentor.
Chief Zhang, time for the meeting.
What's wrong?
Who on earth has got such a big mouth?
The news about Li Qian getting injured
at Zhou Rong's place
has been spread to my mentor again.
Not me.
Sorry, Yangyang.
Mr. Zhou, why would you say that?
Letting you see that scene just now,
I owe you an apology as your big brother.
Please don't say that, Mr. Zhou.
Are you also wondering
how I could suspect your brother
since we've known each other for 20 years?
[Nurse Station]
Actually, I also understand
that he doesn't want you
to know about our business.
But this time,
it's really serious.
It's a matter of his life and death.
But look at him.
Even at a time like this,
he still acts like he doesn't care.
Mr. Zhou,
may I ask what it is?
Yesterday, two people
broke into my house
and stole a phone.
That phone
stores the only evidence
that your brother killed Lu Zheng.
Do you understand?
But now his leg is injured.
What should we do now?
You may go back
and take care of your brother.
Go back.
Bowen, why are you out of bed?
Is your leg okay?
I'm just getting my blood flowing.
What's in that barrel?
Didn't you think the hospital food
tasted awful?
I made some especially for you.
Thank you.
Do you think I dare to eat what you cook?
If you really want me to get well soon,
buy me some more of these nuts.
Is Zhou Rong
very unhappy?
Mr. Zhou told me
that the phone you're looking for
stores the only evidence
that you killed Lu Zheng.
He even told you that?
Is it true, brother?
Zhou Rong is really getting desperate.
Bowen,
I'll go help Mr. Zhou find that phone.
Help who?
He's crazy.
Are you crazy, too?
Zhou Rong is about to flee.
Flee?
Why would Mr. Zhou flee?
Because he's scared.
When people are scared,
they just want to run away.
Have you ever thought about
what you'll do if he runs away?
I don't know who wants to mess with him,
but it definitely has nothing
to do with me.
Then let me ask you a question.
When did you change your phone?
How would I remember?
I remember.
The day after Lu Zheng died,
you changed your phone.
What Mr. Rong said is true.
You killed Lu Zheng.
Go tell the police.
Go now.
Bowen,
we can't let Mr. Zhou run away.
If he escapes and his phone
falls into the hands of the police,
you'll be done for.
Just don't meddle in the business,
my dear brother.
Just put your mind at ease.
Your brother
will even get through this obstacle
safe and sound.
Just don't worry.