Previously on Seducing Drake Palma.
Next!
Closer! A little closer, miss!
A little more!
Come on, just a bit more!
Like, dance with me?
Excuse me, he’s my date!
Drake, everyone’s staring!
Don’t mind them.
But—
Why are you dancing with me?
Those girls are annoying.
Am I not annoying?
You’re annoying.
But that’s fine.
She’s dancing with Drake,
then now with Sheen?
I have something in mind, girls.
Like what?
Hey!
So, they really went through
with their plan.
Wait! Hold on!
For your information,
I’m beautiful.
You know Drake Palma?
The arrogant and handsome guy
all the girls are chasing?
He’s my boyfriend!
Do you know what time it is,
Alys Zyril Perez?!
Psst.
What time is it?
Tss.
6:15.
He said it’s 6:15.
Why did you come home late?!
We’ve been trying to reach you!
We couldn’t sleep
worrying about you!
Lord, guide my mother.
Give her calmness
and providence.
Let her see the light!
Does a decent girl
come home in the morning?
Isn’t this better than
staying late in the evening?
Work on it, my cuteness.
You didn’t even notice
that you left your phone!
We’ve been trying to reach you
all night!
And Aya had to drop
this one off before heading home.
What are you doing?!
Get inside!
And where do you
think you’re going?
What’s your name, young man?
Drake Palma.
Okay, Mr. Palma, come inside.
My husband and I would
like to have a word with you.
Lord, it’s all up to you now.
I love you, Drake Palma!
Why did you come
home just now, Alys?
Well, Mommy, I got locked
inside the stock room last night.
But I was alone,
Drake was not there
with me.
Promise.
I was surprised when he
was carrying me home this morning.
Mommy, please don’t be mad!
Is this true, Mr. Palma,
that you weren’t together
last night?
Alys?
Since when did
you learn how to lie?
No, Mommy,
that’s not what happened.
Drake, come on, tell the truth!
You weren’t with
me last night, right?
Uh, Hon, have a seat.
Let them talk first.
Alright, Alys, what happened?
It’s because the “like” girls
locked me in the stock room.
Why?
Like someone’s looking for you.
Meet me inside the stock room.
Urgent.
Wait, hey!
But Drake really wasn’t with me.
Thank you!
Wait! Hold on!
Pervert!
It was...
So, who are you?
I promise, I won’t tell.
Pinky swear!
I’m…
Neil?
Yeah, Neil.
Who’s Neil, Alys?
Our batchmate, Mommy.
Do you know this Neil, Palma?
There’s no Neil in our batch.
Alys!
What did I
tell you about lying?
Lying means no
technology for two weeks.
Good.
So, are you ready to tell us
what really happened last night?
So, you want war?
Then prepare yourself, Drake Palma!
I’m sorry for the white lie, St. Collete.
I was with Drake last night!
And he touched me!
What?!
She asked for it!
Hey!
You’ve got some nerve!
You’re a liar!
Hold on.
Are you my daughter’s boyfriend, Palma?
Drake Palma...
You’re my boyfriend now!
According to your daughter,
yes sir—
I am her boyfriend.
She followed me one afternoon.
She introduced herself
to my dad as my girlfriend.
I am his girlfriend!
I’m Alys. Alys Zyril Perez,
soon to be Palma!
Hello!
Actually…
Yes, I’m really his girlfriend!
As in girlfriend!
As in one word, girlfriend!
We’re really a couple!
Right? Right, Drakey baby?
How long have you been together?
Five minutes?
Princess, I didn’t think
you were like this.
I thought you liked Sheen—and
now you’re with Drake?
Because, Dad, he doesn’t
treat me like a girlfriend!
Hey, Drake!
You’re only my boyfriend
in front of Sheen and Kei!
Just in front of them!
You think I like you?
Keep dreaming. You’re ugly.
That’s why I forget sometimes.
Right, boyfriend?
Because you always
hurt my feelings.
Right, girlfriend?
Oh, so you’re talking back now?
Alright, that’s enough.
Drake, maybe your parents
are looking for you—go home.
Hon, calm down.
Nothing even happened.
They’re just teasing each other.
Puppy love!
Yuck, Dad!
Puppy love’s gross.
But yes, nothing happened.
Okay, fine.
But you’re still grounded!
No gadgets. And you'll stay
at home all weekend.
Understood?
Bestie!
I missed you!
What happened?
Was the weekend
really that long?
Why are you clingy?
Because I was
grounded all weekend!
I miss you and your loud mouth!
You’re probably just hungry!
Let’s eat, your treat!
I’ll treat you, Bee!
Who’s Bee?
And why are you talking to us?
Who are you?
You don’t know me?
I’m the Student Council Vice President.
Okay.
Kent Justin Valdez, at your service.
Do you need something,
Mr. Student Council Vice President?
Not from you.
But from Aya, I do.
Bee, what’s with your face?
Stop calling me Bee!
I’m Aya! A-ya!
You are Bee!
‘Cause I’m your honey!
I’m courting Aya.
The bee to my honey.
Seriously?
You’re so full of it!
Leave me alone!
Don’t push me away, Bee.
I’ll only fall harder!
You’re so cute, Bee!
Wait, why isn’t Aya
yelling or hitting Kent?
Does this mean
she likes him, too?
So, are you hungry?
What do you want?
That! That one!
That pizza! That one!
- Then that pasta!
- Pizza, pasta…
And all the desserts! That
one too! That banana split!
Bee, what was that again?
Buy everything!
Pizza, pasta, dessert!
That Kent is so annoying!
He’s been flooding
me with friend requests,
texts and calls,
and now he’s bothering me
in the cafeteria, too?
What kind of life is this?
You finally met your match!
That’s your karma, bestie!
Why does your karma look happy?
Huh? What do you mean happy?
Tada! Here you go!
Kent Justin Valdez!
What did you do?
Your wish is my command!
You told me to buy everything.
Here it is.
Let’s eat!
Here.
Alys, right?
You’re Drake’s girlfriend, right?
Why?
Nothing.
Sheen just mentioned it.
It seems my bestie hit the jackpot.
She got the Student
Council Vice President.
Here comes the
choo-choo train!
- And Kent looks cute like Sheen my loves.
- Bite a little.
- Good job, bestie!
- Good baby!
Does he know something
about Sheen and Kei?
Here, drink some water.
Uh, Kent!
Are you close with Sheen?
We’re okay. Why?
I was just wondering if he
got back together with Kei.
Oh, we don’t talk about that.
I never asked either.
- Eat up, Bee!
- Don’t pretend!
Looks like you’re nosy, too.
I am not.
Only when it’s about you.
Aya babes, eat now!
Choo-choo train!
Good for Aya.
Geez.
When will I have a real love life?
Do you want dessert?
[sigh]
Or do you want hotdog again?
There.
Kei...
- listen to me—
- Sheen, stop it!
Didn’t we talk about this?!
I thought you wanted me to be happy.
Of course, Kei.
Then tell Alys to back off!
Alright.
I’ll try.
Tss.
Bestie.
Bestie!
Alys.
Sheen.
Oh no.
Sheen my loves still looks sad.
He also lost weight.
Kei has a really
strong effect on Sheen.
It seems they haven’t
gotten back together.
Wait.
Does that mean there’s still
a chance for us?
Sheen...
Excuse me.
Wow!
Is Drake Palma
trying to mess with me?
What right does he have to
come between me and Sheen?
Since when did he become
an attention-seeker?
Alys...
Can we talk after dismissal?
Dad wants to see you.
I’ll see you after dismissal.
We don’t need your
Mission Impossible:
Seducing Drake Palma!
You can see it
in your imagination
that you’ve succeeded!
Step by step, you succeeded!
Stop it, Gabriella!
Don’t call me “Gabriella’”.
That’s gross.
Then, shut up.
You’re talking nonsense!
Wait, are you really going
to Uncle Steve’s later?
What? Of course not!
I’m going to see Sheen my loves!
Stop talking about
that cry baby!
You’re not getting
anything from him!
Well, it’s true!
And stop talking about Drake!
Why?
Just because you
have Kent now!
You’re nuts!
- Yiee, you like Kent!
- Okay, class,
go back to your seats!
I wonder where he is.
Drake.
Can we talk?
Tss.
Chill out, brothers.
Your veins are about to pop out.
Okay, I’m leaving now.
Aya babes might
be looking for me.
Just chill, okay?
No fistfights!
Okay?
What?
Did you get your assignment?
Tss.
Leave Alys alone.
I’m serious.
Quit messing with my best friend.
I don’t want.
You don’t love her, right?
It’s obvious how you treat her.
Your attitude doesn’t surprise
me anymore, Drake Palma.
I’ve known you for a long time.
Ever since elementary,
you only cared about yourself.
And the worst part?
You never cared who gets hurt.
As long as you get
what you want.
You’re not capable of
loving anyone, Drake.
I might try.
I might try falling for her.
- What’s taking him so long?
- Oops, sorry!
Where are you going, Bee?
Should I stay here?
Where are you staying?
- Come on.
- I’ll stay here.
What now, Aya?
I’m going to see Sheen!
This is frustrating.
Relax, bestie!
Drake is taking too long!
Are you sure you saw
Sheen and Drake talking?
Yes, I saw them.
But maybe it’s over by now.
It’s taking so long!
My bag is so heavy!
Catch!
Wow, that was a hard throw, Bee!
You’re abusing my feelings!
You want to know my
definition of abuse?
- Mhm.
- Good!
- You asked for this, didn’t you?
- Mhm.
- So deal with it.
- Yes, ma’am!
Drake!
Come here, hurry!
- There you go.
- Ouch, Aya!
Since Drake’s here, we’re leaving.
Go, DraLys! Bye!
“We?”
You mean “us”?
Come on, Bee!
I know those moves!
Where are we going?
Is this a date?
You know what,
they actually look cute together.
Like us.
So if they’re
“DraLys,” what are we?
“KenYa?”
Can yah go on a date with me?
What “KenYa” are you talking about?!
Date your butt, I’m going home!
Bee, wait! Alys!
I’m coming!
Introduce me to your parents!
Wait, Bee!
Bee, come on!
- Wait up! I’m coming!
- You’re annoying!
- You’re relentless!
- I’m coming with you!
Leave me alone.
This is perfect, I’m finally
meeting your parents!
Meet your face.
Future mother-in-law,
future father-in-law! Right?
Bestie’s doing a good job.
She charmed the playboy
of St. Collete High.
While I’m stuck with this
annoying jerk.
It’s frustrating.
I’ll just go to Sheen.
Ouch! Let go of me!
I’m still mad at you!
I got grounded the entire
weekend because of you
and your nonsense!
Tss.
Ouch! Let me go!
Noisy.
I said let go!
I’m going to see Sheen! What?!
What?
You got a problem?
You’re my girlfriend.
Act like one.
Maybe I should just go home.
- This is so embarrassing.
- Alys, Drake!
Oh no, Uncle Steve saw me.
There’s no backing out now.
Perfect timing! Your Aunt Katrina and I
brought something for you.
Oh no. About that, too.
Time to eat.
Give me that!
I’m not ready to see Aunt Katrina yet.
The last time I saw her,
I was sitting on Drake’s bed
with three inches distance
of our faces.
What am I going to do?
Alys? Alys?
Thank you, Uncle!
Is Aunt Katrina inside?
She left this morning.
She needs to do something
for the wedding.
What a relief.
It’s good she’s not here!
Is that so?
Too bad I didn’t get to say hi but…
maybe next time.
That’s okay.
There’ll be another chance!
Let’s go inside.
Look at him.
After saying “You’re my girlfriend.
Act like one.”,
he’s leaving me out here?
What a jerk.
Let’s go, Alys!
Alright, Uncle.
Bee, wait up!
Bee, wait!
It’s hot out here.
Here.
Are you okay?
Bee, hold on!
Bee!
Just a sec!
Sorry.
Bee! Bee!
Bee, wait up!
Wait for me! Wait!
Uh, sorry, sorry!
Bee, come on!
Bee, wait...
Bee, wait up!
Bee, are you tired?
Here, go to sleep.
I’ll wake you up later.
Am I a kinder student?
Who has nap time?
Well, you said you
were tired earlier.
Sorry, Bee.
Thank you!
So pretty!
It’s looks good on you!
Try this one, try it on!
It fits you!
You and your
girlfriend really match!
Tss.
You’re a match.
Uh, Uncle Steve,
why did you want
to see me again?
What?
Who said I was looking for you?
Tss. Wedding.
Oh no.
Uncle Steve!
I’m way too young
to get married!
And your son hasn’t
even proposed to me yet!
And if this is about
that thing he said,
that I forced him to touch me—
I swear I won’t press
charges! Promise!
Uncle Steve, please,
we can’t get married yet.
Please, Uncle Steve!
Alys, come on..
That’s not what Drake meant.
He was talking about
Katrina’s and my wedding.
Of course, Uncle Steve,
I was just joking!
Obviously, I knew you were
talking about your wedding!
But wait, what exactly
is Drake accusing you of?
- Huh?
- What are you saying?
We were together last night.
He touched me.
- What?!
- She asked for it!
Hey! You’ve got some nerve!
You’re a liar!
Oh no, Uncle, just ignore me.
I was just saying nonsense.
It’s nothing.
Please forget I said that.
Drake, where are you going?
Alys, why don’t you
have some snacks first?
Thank you, Uncle!
- Kent.
- Yes, Bee?
Aya. My name is Aya.
I’m serious—
stop bothering me.
I’m serious too, Aya.
I’m not going to stop.
But why?
Why me?
Why don’t you believe me?
I like you, Bee.
I’ll do anything for you.
Isn’t it obvious?
You treat me like a slave.
I like you, Bee!
Why are you yelling?!
Bee, please!
Please?
Thank you again, Uncle Steve.
Do you need anything else from me?
For the wedding?
Yes, Alys.
Did anyone tell you you’re
part of the entourage?
Really, Uncle?
It means I will be wearing a gown?
Mmm-hmm!
I’ll just tell Drake
to bring you here
for the gown fitting and
and rehearsals.
Wait, did Drake tell you
he switched sections?
What?
I wonder where he is now.
You didn’t know?
A girlfriend should be the one
to know first.
Why didn’t you know?
Uh…um…
he didn’t really mention it.
He hasn’t said anything to me.
But why did he switch?
From what I know, it’s
because of his high grades.
Oh, I see.
How about you, Alys?
What’s your average?
It’s okay. It’s fine!
Hold on, Alys.
I need to take this call.
Where could he be?
Should I just go home?
I knew I shouldn’t have come here!
But sometimes it’s hard to stay mad.
How are you supposed to stay mad
at someone that good-looking?
Mind you, he’s just wearing house clothes.
Oh my.
It’s the Drake Palma Way.
Hey!
You switched sections?
What about our business report?
Print it.
Nice! So waiting this
long wasn’t a total waste!
Anyway,
I’ll head out.
Tell Uncle Steve thanks for this!
It’s cute!
Thanks again! Bye!
What?
Tutorials.
Forget it.
I’m not in the mood to study.
Tss.
Bird brain!
You’re rude!
Did you just call me bird brain?
Why?
It’s obvious, right?
Remember this.
Next quarter,
I’m transferring to your section.
Not with that
bird brain headband.
Whatever, I’m out of here.
I’m going home.
Alys.
Wow, being grounded
lets you catch up on reading!
Anyway, I’m lifting
your punishment.
You’re no longer grounded.
Really, Mom?
Thank you, Mom!
You know we don’t
like it when you lie.
Right?
It’s okay to have a boyfriend—
as long as you focus on school.
We have a dream, right?
From St. Collete High,
you have to make it
into St. Collete Academy.
So how’s that going to happen
if you don’t do your best?
Sorry, mom.
I know you’re sorry,
but you have to try harder.
Do you want to follow your sibling to
the U.S. just to get your act together?
So try harder.
I know you can do it.
Don’t worry, Mom!
I’ll work on getting my grades up!
I’ll get into St.
Collete Academy,
because I’m not a bird brain!
Of course not!
Who said you were a bird brain?
Bird brain.
No one.
Anyway, Mom,
I’ll make you proud!
That’s my girl!
I love you so much, Mom!
But don’t forget to study, okay?
Just chill.
Alys, are your grades
worth celebrating?
I think they’re fine, Mom.
Well, make sure
that “fine” and “I think”
can get you into a good
college—if not the best!
Alys, you know the dream, right?
You need to get into
St. Collete Academy.
- Yes?
- Yes, Mom.
Hey! Classmate!
Hey. How are you?
Oh.
A miracle’s happening!
Is it a crime to study now?
Just because I touched a
book, it’s already a miracle?
Sorry, bestie!
Why are you so cranky?
What are you studying?
Here.
Let’s study!
No, thanks.
I’m happy with
what I already know.
Why are you suddenly
into studying, anyway?
Is it end of the world?
Sshh!
Just be quiet!
I need to focus!
Alright, fine!
Then, focus.
Wow, you’re tired already?
Shut up!
- I just remembered something!
- What is it?
We’re bridesmaids for
Aunt Katrina’s wedding!
Gross!
I don’t want to be part of that
cradle snatcher’s wedding!
Over my dead body!
You’re harsh.
It’s still Uncle Steve’s wedding.
After everything he’s done for us?
I hate this.
Fine!
I’ll think about it.
[bell rings]
Okay, class.
Please stay if you have
tutorial sessions.
Ugh!
I thought today was
a Drake-free day!
Why do you look so happy?
Because there’s a tutorial.
That means I won’t see Kent today.
Then, good for you!
I’ll go and see Drake.
Good luck, bestie!
Aja!
Aja.
One more.
Aja!
Aja.
Okay.
Uh, Sheen.
What?
- Let me be the one to—
- What happened to you?
—tutor Aya babes, please!
Hold on, I’m fixing my things!
Let me be her tutor—
she needs me!
Fine!
Just tell Mr. de Juan
that you’re taking over, okay?
Okay!
Thank you, bro! I owe you one!
Thank you.
Drake!
What?
Let me tutor Alys.
Tss.
Drake, are you okay with that?
No.
Why not?
You don’t even like Alys, right?
Why?
Who’s smarter between us?
Hmm?
If you make Alys cry,
you better hide.
Where is that CB?
Why is he making me wait?
He didn’t even call or text.
He’s so annoying!
Hi, Bee!
Why is this
liitle pest here again?
I thought today was
Kent-Justin-Valdez-free day, too.
Hello, the honey to my bee!
What are you doing?
Snacks. For you!
Here you go!
Where’s Sheen?
Sheen’s not here.
Cover your eyes.
This is for you!
Where’s Sheen?
I told you, he’s not here!
Starting today,
I’ll be your tutor.
Why you?!
Bee, lower your voice.
It should be me,
so we can have quality time.
Right?
My gosh! Shame on you, Kent!
Why should I be
ashamed of my feelings?
You’re so gross!
Love you too, Bee!
Okay!
Where do you want to start?
Nice!
What’s with the face?
Huh?
You’re happy my score is low?
Nothing.
What is it?
Mr. de Juan said
we can extend tutorials
over the weekend
if your grades are that bad!
And your grades
are that bad, Bee!
Nice!
Weekends with Bee!
- Aya, what are you doing?!
- Let’s start.
Back to Chapter Four.
Read this first.
Read the instructions carefully.
Hey,
aren’t you going to teach me?
I’ve been sitting
here at the library
and you’re not even helping me!
Tss.
Why would I?
Look at you.
Who’s really the
dummy between us?
You’re my tutor, remember?
Tss.
Hey!
I don’t want to teach you.
Fine, don’t! I’ll report you to sir!
Fine!
Break even point or
BEP is calculated by
dividing fixed
costs by contribution
margin per unit.
Selling price or SP
minus variable cost
or VC equals
contribution margin.
So,
BEP equals fixed costs
divided by selling price,
minus variable cost per unit.
Ugh!
Why are you staring at me?
Alright, fine. I’ll teach you.
Nice!
See, I knew you’d
give in eventually!
Finally.
- I really can’t do this alone.
- But…
What’s the condition?
But what?
Kiss me.
What kind of drama is
this, Drake Palma?!
- Sssh!
- Ssshhh!
Why are you always shouting?
We’re in the library!
How can I not shout?
You’re saying you want to kiss me here?
Kiss you?
In your dreams, Drake Palma!
You know what,
if you want a kiss,
go to your Katrina!
Drake.
What?
Let me tutor Alys.
Drake, are you okay with it?
No.
Why not?
You don’t even like Alys, right?
Why?
Who’s smarter between us?
Right?
If you make Alys cry,
you better hide.
I know that you’re only
doing this for Kei.
You’re only going to hurt Alys.
I don’t want you to hurt her.
On the next episode of
Seducing Drake Palma.
Hey, Drake.
Do we…
Do we have a monthsary?
Tss.
Come on, let’s go.
I said I’m tired,
Drake Sebastian Palma.
Hop on.
I know!
Let’s just say we got
together on September 31!
Stupid.
There’s no such
thing as September 31.
Enjoy your special day.
- Alright, go ahead!
- Happy monthsary!
Enjoy!
- But, Uncle!
- Wait!
Oopps!
Oh, sorry!
I didn’t mean to!
You know what would
work best right now?
Just take your clothes off!
Can you still handle
the heat, bestie?
Do you want some juice?
Let’s just celebrate every 31st,
so we only have to do it
seven times a year, okay?
You really think we’d last a year?
Dream on!
Who says that I’m gonna
break up with you?