Oh my god, he’s here.
Who?
My new crush.
Stay low-key, don’t look their way.
Don’t– Come on–
You like that guy from Katipunan, don’t you?
The one with Sam’s crush.
You’re into him, huh?
Admit it.
Yes.
He’s a ten,
but so stern.
What’s your name again?
- Louisse Natasha Valeria. - Too long.
You can call me, “Love.”
I’ll be starting the operation–
- Hashtag - Hashtag
LuKal!
Lu-Lukal?
Luna and Kalix!
Wow, you guys have a love team already?
The company has been looking for somebody
who can fill up the position of Head Legal Counsel.
Were you able to find someone? Kalix?
No, I’m not ready to meet him.
Architect Valeria.
It’s been a while.
Yes, almost ten years.
Not that I’m counting.
What happened to you?
Are you okay?
Nothing.
Attorney Martinez, you’re early.
Good morning, sir.
I met a client nearby, so I decided to come early.
That’s fine.
Perfect timing, let’s have a chat over coffee.
Luna, join us.
No. Uhm–
As much as I would love to,
I still have meetings to attend to.
What meeting?
Do you have a new project?
The big project in Sta. Rosa.
It’s on hold for now, dear.
I still have to brief the new architects.
Let Kierra handle that.
This meeting is important so you need to join us. Let’s go.
Freshen up first then follow us, okay?
It's almost done.
Kierra: Are you okay? 15 missed calls and no answer? Wow!
Via: WTF Luna, what do you mean you’re going home? I have your keys!
Sam: Hey thry asking whwre yiu r Whwre r u?
Yanna: Bitch where are you someone said you left the club with a guy?! Good luck!
Kierra: ARE YOU REALLY NOT GONNA ANSWER ME, LOUISSE NATASHA? I’M GONNA TELL ON YOU!
Luna: Hey guys, I’m fine. Kalix brought me to his house. Don't be mad.
Wow.
Thank you for breakfast,
for the bacon, egg, and water.
And there’s even brewed coffee.
Uhm…
Did something happen last night?
I can’t remember anything.
You wanna know what happened?
I can’t hear you, it’s too loud!
I’m heading out, I’ll be out.
Are you drunk?
No, I'm not drunk.
Where are your friends?
Huh? I don’t know.
Bro, she’s too drunk.
Yeah, I'll go look for her friends.
- Where are you going? - Home!
Bro, follow her.
- Are you bringing me to my friends? - Yes.
Wow, such a gentleman.
Your head, be careful.
Sam, answer your phone.
Stop honking the car.
Yo bro, have you and Leo found her friends?
We can’t find them here in the bar.
Maybe they went home already.
Bro, better take her home.
All right, all right.
Hi.
Where the hell are your friends?
Huh? Where the hell are my–
Oh! Kierra called earlier, before I fell–
–for you.
No, she said they were going to Sam's place.
Sam’s?
Yes, I’m going to Sam’s.
I’m going home to Sam’s place.
Me and Sam live in the same building.
I can take you there.
But are you sure they’re at Sam’s?
Sure.
As sure as I am with you.
Seat belt.
Ding-dong.
- Sam! - Ding-dong, ding-dong.
Sam! Sam, are you home?
Sam!
Luna, there’s no one here.
Do you have Sam’s keys?
You’ve been wanting a kiss since earlier.
Luna, keys for Sam's condo.
Call Sam.
Is that in here?
Sam!
Sam, open the door.
I need to go to the bathroom, I’m gonna pu–
Luna, don’t vomit.
No, don’t vomit. Don’t vomit, no.
Okay, all right.
Take it out.
You're good, you’re good.
This isn’t Sam’s bathroom.
It’s not Sam’s.
It’s my bathroom.
Kalix.
That’s bad. Why are we here? You’re naughty.
You are a mess.
A mess? I’m a beautiful mess.
Come on, let’s get you to bed.
Bed scene? We’re not even done with the bathroom scene yet.
We’re going for the bed scene already?
Gosh, Kalix.
Kalix, why are we in your room?
Come on, we can’t do this.
This isn’t allowed, we have to date first.
Luna, be quiet.
What the hell are you doing?
Huh?
I stink.
Wanna take a sniff?
You want?
Look, you can sleep here tonight just–
do not vomit on my bed.
Okay.
Kalix!
Yes?
Are you leaving?
I miss you, stay a bit.
Stay, come here. Come here.
Such a snob.
Sorry.
We're not staying at Sam’s.
We all agreed that
they'll stay over at our place.
I wasn’t able to change clothes?
Obviously not.
You fell asleep.
I didn’t touch you.
If that’s what you’re worried about.
I know how important consent is, Luna.
No! That’s not what I meant.
Uh– I was thinking maybe I did something.
Thanks, by the way, for taking care of me and bringing me here.
Oh, and also for the food.
Did I vomit a lot? You want me to clean it up?
No need.
Let me at least wash the dishes.
Just eat.
Maybe I should just take you on a date.
Just kidding.
I’ll just eat now.
The egg is good.
This guy is just perfect.
You were saying?
Ah–
No, nothing.
I was saying
that it’s just perfect timing for me to leave now.
Hmm.
You might say,
that I’m invading your privacy.
Since last night, actually.
I let myself get drunk because of you.
What?
Nothing!
I said you were such a snob last night.
You were ignoring me.
Who was the guy you were with last night?
You guys seem pretty close.
Ah!
Some guy I just met.
‘Cause I’m so pretty.
You're jealous?
That’s why you were ignoring me?
Jeez!
Why would I be?
Such a snob!
My bag, thank goodness you found it.
It was under the bed.
Ah…
Sorry, I’m such a restless sleeper.
I’ll just give this hoodie back later.
I’ll wash it first.
I’ll make it up to you, I promise.
We’ll go on a date, okay?
Fine.
I’ll go home now.
Come on, you don’t have to see me out.
Ah…
Okay, I’m leaving.
Take care, Luna.
Hmm?
Take care.
Of course! For you, I’ll take care of myself. Jeez!
The door.
Amazing!
I’m glad you thought of coming home.
Damn, Luna. If you’re gonna be flirting around,
at least let us know. Don't ignore our messages.
If something happens to you, what would I tell your parents?
What happened to you last night?
Do you have a hangover?
And–
Is that Kalix’s hoodie?
I wanna join them but my head hurts so bad.
I’m just glad you’re alive, Luna.
Don’t get mad right now, please.
Forgive me already, okay?
Whatever! You owe us an explanation.
Come on, start!
What?
Okay… Okay!
- So slow. - Summary first.
Okay.
He brought me to his condo.
I slept at Kalix’s place.
‘Cause he couldn’t find you guys.
- Oh, so it’s our fault now. - It was so embarrassing...
I puked all over his bathroom.
I can’t tell if you were really embarrassed.
You seem giddy about it.
Fuck! Go into detail. Get to the exciting part.
Nothing.
- Nothing my ass! - Nothing?
Nothing, really! But that– that’s Kalix’s jacket.
- Nothing happened. - You fucker.
I’m serious, he even said–
“I know how important consent is.”
- See? - Oh my god!
Oh my god, green flag.
- Right? - So, what?
Are you in love with him?
We’re still in the “talking stage.”
But you know what? Kalix is a catch.
So I won’t be surprised if you fall for him.
Me too.
But you seem to have a lot of rivals.
You know what?
Just move on from that talking stage.
- Go all the way. - All the way!
Stop! That’s too much!
Can’t we just enjoy how things are right now?
We’re enjoying this.
Let’s get to the sad part next time.
By the end of all this.
And–
I gotta take a bath now. I really stink.
Yes, glad to know you’re aware.
- So that was it. - Come and eat first.
Kalix: message me when you’re home.
What is it?!
- What is it?! - Luna...
Nothing… It’s nothing, I just feel so gorgeous–
- Hey! - Oh! What? Why?
You’re blocking my gorgeousness.
Bitch! You little slut!
Keep it up! You better not fail.
Raise your skirt up more.
Kalix: are you home?
Look at him following up on me when I didn't response.
Luna: sorry for the late reply!
Luna: I just showered.
Luna: yup, i’m home now :)
Kalix: K
Luna: miss me already?
Kalix: *seen*
Kalix: *typing*
Huh?
Was I just ignored?
Amethyst...
Who is this girl?
Studying but busy taking photos?
Lots of time in your hands, huh?
Here, have some snack.
Is there something wrong?
Look at this.
Do you think they’re together?
They look like they’re just friends.
- I'm not sure. - Friends?
They’re always together.
So? We’re always together, too. But–
we’re just friends.
Hmm, point taken.
I should just ask to be sure, right?
You can!
Or, you can just ask his friends.
Why do you even have a crush on him anyway?
Good question.
You wanna know why he’s my crush?
He’s hot.
He’s tall too and really smart.
You know when I got drunk,
he took care of me and even brought me to his place.
- Really? - Yes.
So I know that he’s a good guy.
That should be expected.
If you’re a decent guy,
you would never take advantage of a drunk woman in a bar.
You’re right.
That should be the norm, right?
And that’s why you’re my friend, Sevi.
You set better standards for guys.
Especially since you’re the team captain.
No to toxic masculinity.
Hey, it’s your crush.
Sevi, do I look good?
Do I have dirt on my face? Am I pretty?
You look like a zombie.
Huh?
Hi, Kalix! Glad to see you here.
This is my friend, Sevi.
Sevi, this is Kalix.
Uhm, my friend.
Hey bro, Sevi.
You’re Sevi.
Luna, I’ll go ahead.
We still have practice.
Okay, take care! Thanks for the snack.
Are you close with him?
With Sevi? Yes.
We’ve been close since high school.
What are you doing here?
I thought you were studying in the library?
How did you know I was there?
Wild guess.
So why are you here? Are your friends in Dapitan?
I came here to see you.
Me?
Why?
You still haven’t returned my hoodie.
Oh…
You came here just for your hoodie?
You’re really making an effort.
Wanna get it from my condo?
I’ll cook dinner for you.
Don’t worry, Kierra’s there. I’m not gonna do anything to you.
Kidding! Only if you want to. If not, then maybe next time.
You know how to cook?
Of course!
I’m multi-talented, Kalix.
Okay then.
- Okay? - Let’s go.
Okay!
All right!
Let’s go!
Just feel at home. Don’t be shy.
Ke?
Ke!
I’m home.
Ke?
- Luna? - Where are you?
I’m with my groupmates. We’re still finishing up our plates. What’s up?
Kalix and I are here.
I thought you were here in the condo.
What time are you coming home?
I might be home late. Hey! Flirt responsibly.
All right, take care.
Ke will be home late.
That's an invasion of privacy.
I’m not intruding, you invited me here.
Just kidding! Come on.
Well, is it good?
You made this?
Yes, this too. Pretty, right?
It’s great.
You don't need to flatter me.
No.
You should design my house.
Really?
Mhmm. Okay then.
Someday, if you'll hire me
I'll give you a discount.
I’ll take note of that.
Wanna know what else you should take note of?
I’m really good at…
I’m really good at cooking! Come on.
I’ll just prepare the food and change clothes.
Don’t miss me too much.
Kidding!
Eat well.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Taste it.
Well?
Is it good?
It’s okay.
Huh? What do you mean, it's okay?
This is delicious.
This is my specialty.
Yes, it’s good.
Why couldn’t you just admit it?
Wait, let’s get to know each other.
What do you want to know?
Why do you want to be a lawyer?
Do you want to be a corporate lawyer or a criminal lawyer?
I’m fine with both.
You can’t have both, don’t go two-timing now.
Just pick one.
Criminal lawyer, as of now.
Wow! Why do you want to be a criminal lawyer?
So I can get you out of jail.
Don’t be silly!
I’m an angel. Look at me.
With that mouth of yours, I doubt.
Gosh!
Now, let's talk about your personal life.
Are you in a relationship?
What?
Are you into someone right now?
You’re quite focused on your studies.
I’m just curious if you’re in a relationship now
or if you have any past relationships.
All flings but nothing serious.
Let’s just not talk about that.
Do you have a crush on Amethyst?
I do not have a crush on Amy
or on anyone else, Luna.
Too bad.
What?
I actually thought you would be in a relationship soon.
I was willing to be your wingman.
Aren’t you interested?
Hey!
Let me do that. Come on.
Let me.
Look, I have to go.
Thanks for the dinner.
Huh? Are you mad?
You’re confusing me, Luna.
Luna: Ke! Come with me! Please!
Kierra: How did you even have a lovers’ quarrel?!
Luna: No idea! I just asked him if he had a crush on Amethyst. Then he just walked out!
Kierra: Come on, Luna! Why did you even ask that? Isn’t it obvious?
Kierra: Kalix has been making moves on you!
Luna: Idk Ke… I just don’t understand Kalix. Sometimes he’s sweet, sometimes he's cold.
Luna: He has this huge wall around him! But I seriously wanna break that wall.
Kierra: You’re in too deep! It’s the thrill of the chase.
Kierra: Since it’s your first time chasing after someone!
Luna: So come with me pleaseeee
Relax, Luna.
Kalix usually comes here around this time, so just wait.
What do you call a plant that goes to the bathroom?
- What? - Toilet-“trees.”
She said relax, not get stunned.
It’s Kalix.
Kalix is here, don’t look! Don’t look their way!
I just said, don’t look their way!
Don’t look.
You came all the way here just to avoid him? Don’t be stupid.
He might think that I went here to see him.
But that's the truth, right?
Yes, but let's just pretend that you’re the reason why I'm here.
Just so I can still keep my pride.
You know, Luna…
You better get your ass moving.
A lot of people here on campus have a crush on Kalix.
Everytime we have a school event, Kalix gets the most flowers.
So, if you’re still playing hard to get,
someone else will get him first.
It’s your chance, talk to him.
You can do it. Follow us.
Breathe in…
breathe out.
- Okay! - Okay? Okay.
- Okay, go. - Okay.
- Go on now. - You can do it!
May I have a chicken shawarma?
Thank you.
Hey! You’re here.
Wha– wow!
What a… coincidence!
We came here to visit Sam.
H-have you been here long?
What are you buying?
W-water!
Water.
Miss, I’ll get this water, please.
I see.
Well…
It’s just so hot, so we need another bottle.
Okay, I’ll go back now.
Let’s just go home. I don’t want this, I can’t talk to him anymore.
What happened now?
Really? After my pep talk?
It’s just so embarrassing, my pride is hurt.
I didn’t even do anything wrong.
Come on, I just asked a question. And now he’s with Amethyst.
He’s also with Leo and Adonis.
I’m done. I'm never gonna speak with him.
If he doesn’t wanna talk, then fine with me.
Your water.
You forgot it.
Thank you.
Can I sit here?
Of course.
Yes. Sure, Kalix.
Yes.
Ke, I need to buy something.
Will you come with me?
Sure, come on.
We’ll go ahead guys, okay?
We’ll be back.
Enjoy!
Is it okay with your friends to just leave them?
They’re grown ups, they can function without me.
So…
About last night–
What were you saying about being confused?
Confused with what?
Nothing.
What do you mean?
Let’s talk about it some other time.
Hey!
We’re going to the coffee shop to study, do you wanna join us?
You guys go ahead.
Well, if you change your mind, text me so I can order your usual.
Stop glaring at her.
Huh?
Glaring?
I’m not glaring at her.
All right.
So, you’re not gonna join them?
You ask too many questions.
I know you just want to be with me.
Did you miss me?
Come on, let’s study together.
I can’t today. I have some errands to run.
I’ll pick you up tomorrow at your school.
Okay!
It's not a problem. See, I don't have to ask you.
I know you just really missed me.
That’s all for today. Class dismissed.
- Bye, ma’am. - Bye!
- Ke! - Yes?
Help me apply eyeliner, hurry.
Such a flirt. You’re just gonna study with Kalix,
why would you need an eyeliner?
Can you make it winged?
You even want it winged!
Of course. Just because we’re studying doesn’t mean I’m not gonna flaunt it.
I still have to be pretty, especially I’m with my happy crush.
Glad that you and Kalix are good now.
Why did he even sulk anyway?
Just because you asked about Amethyst?
He didn’t tell me.
He doesn’t want to talk about it.
Maybe he’s just not ready to open up about his personal life.
Didn’t you say his wall was way high?
Maybe it takes time to know people like them.
Yes, I know.
But you can’t blame me
for asking about his relationship status
or if he’s seeing someone else.
For me, a good relationship is built on honesty.
So, as early as now I might as well ask about him and Amethyst.
I’m just being careful, you know.
Then this is the right time to get to know Kalix.
You should really observe mysterious guys like him.
They’re the perfect example for “actions speak louder than words.”
So what are Kalix’s actions telling you?
I’m not actually sure.
It’s Kalix!
Hello, Kalix.
Hello, Luna?
I just have an emergency.
So, should we just cancel today?
No, we can still study later.
I just have to pick up someone.
- Someone’s joining us? - Yes.
Can you meet me at the restaurant instead?
I’ll text you the address.
Okay.
All right, see you.
Sure, bye.
Darn it!
I thought I could finally spend time alone with Kalix.
- He’s bringing someone. - Who?
I don’t know.
Oh well.
Maybe it’s just Adonis or Leo.
Don’t get ahead of yourself.
What’s important is that you get to spend time with your crush.
Let the other one become the third wheel.
YOLO, you only flirt once with someone for the first time.
Just savor the moments you have.
Will you finish this?
You talk too much.
- Make it pretty. - Then stop moving.
I wonder who he picked up...
Oh my god!
Is he your younger brother?
Kio, this is Luna. Say hi.
Hi!
Hello, Kio! How are you?
I’m okay.
Is Kio your nickname?
My name is Kian Oliver.
You're so cute!
I had no idea who you were picking up, I thought I'll be jealous.
Hey, I’m sorry I asked you to meet me here last minute.
There was no one home.
It’s okay.
Kio, do you want to eat?
Yes.
Come on, let’s eat.
Sit here.
How was school?
It’s okay.
It’s okay?
Waiter? The menu please.
Eat this.
Where is the cake?
You have to eat a proper meal first.
But I want the cake.
Kio…
Oh no.
Kio’s sulking now.
Kio.
Maybe we should just ask for the cake?
Don’t spoil him.
He should learn how to wait.
Kio, hey.
You trust me, right?
Then I promise you, you’ll eat the cake.
But first you have to eat this.
Okay?
Okay.
Yes? All right, good.
Waiter? Water, please. Thank you.
You’ll finish all of it, right?
Yes.
Okay, very good.
Is he your son, sir?
So cute!
No. He’s my brother.
Oh, sorry.
You and your girlfriend look cute together too.
She said we’re cute together.
I think we'd make cute babies together.
Right?
Eat.
With everyone that I joke with,
you’re the only one who doesn’t respond.
Is it really that corny?
Joke.
You joke a lot.
Then let’s just make it real.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Just eat.
Fine, I’ll eat now.
How’s the chicken, Kio?
It’s okay.
Kio’s so cute.
Are you close with him?
He still wants to be with you even after we brought him home.
Yes.
He says I’m his favorite brother.
Favorite brother? But you’re his only brother.
That’s right.
He’s such a jokester.
Don’t you miss him since you just go home every other weekend?
I do miss him.
But I prefer staying at the condo rather than at the house.
I need my freedom.
You know, with siblings,
it’s quite uncommon to be close to each other when you have a big age gap.
You and Kio look so cute together.
He’s like my
tiny best friend.
Mom and Dad are always so busy.
So is my big sister.
Growing up, I always felt alone
and I don’t want Kio to feel the same way.
So that’s why I try to do my best to be there for him. All the time.
Thank you for dinner. I had fun.
Me too.
Kio seems to like you.
Really?
I like Kio, too.
Kalix.
Yes?
I think…
I like you.
Excuse me, sir. Here’s your order.
- Thank you. - You’re welcome, sir.
So, I heard you topped the bar?
Yes, I guess I did.
Good for you.
Thank you.
And now you have your own law firm?
I’m really impressed, Attorney Martinez.
Blood, sweat, and tears, ma’am.
Hard work pays off.
Luna,
are you okay?
Yes, mom! Of course.
Why wouldn’t I?
So, I hope you guys are ready to work together.
No problem with me, sir.
I’m very much looking forward to working with Architect Valeria.
Good.
I hope you feel the same way.
Of course, Attorney Martinez.
I am beyond thrilled to work with you.
Kalix: Are you free tomorrow? Let’s study.
Ke won’t be able to come home.
She said there's flood on the road going home.
Is it okay if I spend the night here?
Hurry up! He’s in the parking lot.
Are you picking me up?
I really came here to see you.
We didn’t know you’re here.
I’m sorry, are we interrupting something?
I’m Amethyst, by the way. I don’t think we’ve met yet.
Kalix.
Do you still think about our first night together?
My parents just texted,
they’re asking me to go home.
It's supposed to be just a happy crush.
Why am I feeling this way?