笙ｪShrugging off past burdens笙ｪ
笙ｪBeneath the mask, who am I?笙ｪ
笙ｪRelease and find wider shores笙ｪ
笙ｪLove's a riddle, and rain pours heavy笙ｪ
笙ｪCrossed paths, now downward fall笙ｪ
笙ｪFrom dust arises starlight's spark笙ｪ
笙ｪTearing through
the night's dense blockade笙ｪ
笙ｪHeart's flame illuminates all solitude笙ｪ
笙ｪLet time's sails drift endlessly笙ｪ
笙ｪThrough wandering exile笙ｪ
笙ｪBreaking free from the cocoon,
I start anew笙ｪ
笙ｪMoon as song, life as flame笙ｪ
笙ｪNameless heart clings fiercely笙ｪ
笙ｪLet me笙ｪ
笙ｪCharge toward the next raging river笙ｪ
笙ｪMoon darts, snow falls笙ｪ
笙ｪWe tread rugged paths to reunite笙ｪ
笙ｪHands held tight笙ｪ
笙ｪWe forever live for love's sake笙ｪ
笙ｪShadow's spear burns fiercely笙ｪ
=Legend of The Female General=
=Episode 22=
Gentlemen,
fate brought us together
at the academy.
Why don't you talk things through?
Cheng Lisu,
you may not know.
There is no misunderstanding
between us.
Right.
No misunderstandings.
In the end,
I'm nothing
but an oath-breaker.
Look!
(Hua Youxian)
Hua Youxian?
She was
the top of the Ruyun House,
unmatched in Yaojing.
How could she end up in Chonghuai?
Bravo!
Great!
You are
gracefully charming.
You truly deserve
the Ruyun House's reputation.
Your heavenly voice
lives up to its fame.
Our money
was well spent indeed.
Years have passed.
How have you been?
All is well.
Miss Hua,
and you?
I'm well, too.
Speaking of which,
I share a special connection
with you all.
Back then,
I received
a love letter from one of you.
Certain people
always chase after beauties.
It must be his work.
Back then, I ranked
second to last at Xianchang Academy.
I couldn't even
write proper essays,
let alone love letters.
To prove your innocence to Miss Song,
you're exposing this.
Huaijin excels in
arts and martial skills.
He always ranked first
at the academy.
I bet this letter
was his doing.
See? He's not denying it.
It's a yes.
A penalty drink.
Definitely him.
Who knew you would
have such a romantic side?
General Fengyun, since you are here,
as the local magistrate,
I should host you.
Tomorrow, I'll prepare a banquet
and hope you'll come.
It's rare for me to come.
Miss Hua, would you like
to drink with me?
Of course,
I would like to.
Mr. Yang,
why the long face?
Speaking of which,
Miss Hua,
what brought you to Chonghuai?
I met a gentleman.
Believing him
to be
my lifelong partner.
I bought my freedom
and married him.
So
you are married?
Yes.
But
my judgment failed me.
Eventually,
we divorced.
Why the separation?
I entrusted myself
to the wrong man.
You were
once renowned across the land.
I heard of your legendary fame, too.
Choosing marriage at your career's peak
meant you held
deep affection for him.
When I left the Ruyun House, the madam
asked me,
"Have you ever seen a moth fly
into a flame and end well?"
I was young then
and firmly believed
that even a fleeting moment
of warmth would be worth chasing.
I naturally fell for him
and left with him
without hesitation.
Later,
our affection dissipated,
so I left him.
Isn't that human nature?
Now,
I live freely
in this city,
self-sufficient and unbound.
So joyful.
I've never regretted
any decision I've made,
be it past or present.
Your clarity of purpose
is admirable.
Let me toast to you.
Thank you,
Miss.
You have sharp eyes.
Your dance is captivating
and famous.
Now, you're single.
Our garrison has
many outstanding young men.
Perhaps
some might suit your standards?
Your brave warriors
are certainly worthy of me.
Xiao Jue.
What do you mean?
(He's egging him on.)
Both are unwed.
Why not play
the matchmaker?
It's my marriage.
None of your concern.
I...
Miss Hua is beautiful and skilled in
song and dance.
She deserves
a promising young partner.
Why do you object?
Exactly. Huaijin.
Go introduce her
to some brave ones
of your men.
Naturally.
Xiao Jue.
Youxian.
The love letter
was from you, right?
Her ex-husband
is also you.
So it was you all along.
Back then,
we were both young.
I want to buy your freedom.
I wonder
if you would like
to become my wife?
Our backgrounds are worlds apart.
Marriage isn't a game.
There's too much at stake.
Let me think again.
Stop right there!
Dreaming of marrying a courtesan?
You'll disgrace our family!
Defending a traitor against your father?
Leave now,
and you're no longer a Yang!
Don't come back ever!
Why torture yourself?
Come away with me.
Alright.
I'll go with you.
(Yang Mansion)
I'm worthless.
Tell me.
What's truly burdening you?
Tell me!
Give back my wine.
Enough.
Let's divorce.
May we
never meet again.
I'm unworthy.
Mingzhi,
how could you be so blind?
You never compromised your will
or dignity.
So free-spirited and open-hearted.
Truly admirable.
You should be our role model as women.
I'm flattered.
Life is too short
to waste on self-compromise.
Youxian.
You...
failed the Commander
and then Miss Hua.
A blind and foolish man.
I was thinking
back then, the Commander
lost both parents,
his comrades fell in battle,
and his friend betrayed him.
Knowing something was wrong
but finding no proof.
That feeling of helplessness
must have been unbearable.
As for Miss Hua,
who became your wife,
she deserved your respect,
but you neglected her.
Did you think
avoiding violence
meant keeping
your gentleman's code?
Don't you know
complete indifference and neglect
hurt more than blows?
It means
from your heart
to your eyes,
she ceased to exist.
My father's wrongful conviction
has nothing to do with you.
I never expected
your single word
to change everything.
I did resent you
for your disrespectful remarks,
but that's in the past.
We're but specks
in the vast river of time,
gone in an instant.
I won't lecture you,
nor should you trap yourself.
When you're at rock bottom,
every step taken
is upward progress.
Escapism and despair achieve nothing.
I'll find the truth to clear
my father's name
and restore honor
to the Xiao Army.
That day will come.
As for Miss Hua,
rather than feeling guilty,
take action instead.
Self-pity
is utterly useless.
Stop drinking.
You'll be drunk.
Do you have troubles, Miss?
I made a righteous lecture earlier,
but I'm just a deserter myself.
What right do I have
to criticize Yang Mingzhi?
How ridiculous.
You must have
your own struggles, too.
My minor troubles
pale compared to his suffering.
They're insignificant.
But I see your pain.
Youxian.
I was wrong.
I won't ask your forgiveness.
I just wish
to return to your side.
If possible,
I want to make up
for the hurt I caused.
It is
none of my concern.
Youxian.
That's my only wish.
You can ignore me,
reject me,
but I want to stay with you
because I truly love you.
Actually...
Actually, I...
How much did you drink tonight?
Will you hate me?
Commander.
He Yan let me
deliver this letter to you.
(By the riverside pavilion,
awaiting our conversation.)
(I'll be waiting.)
You see each other every day.
Why write letters instead of
speaking directly?
Mr. Xiao.
Miss Hua.
I came here
to thank you.
Why?
You went to great trouble
to help
Yang Mingzhi and me.
I'm deeply grateful.
I wanted to beat him up,
but the opportunity slipped away.
So you're blaming me, Mr. Xiao?
His choice to be with me
is his freedom.
And how I choose to respond
is mine.
Good then.
I'm sorry.
I have to go.
By the way,
someone came with you to Ruyun House
back then too.
I remember very clearly.
Delicate yet determined,
wearing a mask,
refusing to reveal the identity.
Where is the person now?
All things pass away.
Not worth mentioning.
So,
you two have grown distant?
Right.
You've been battling everywhere.
It must've been hard
for you to stay in touch.
After all, she's a lady.
What?
Don't you know, Mr. Xiao?
She wore a chest binder
and acted so nervous.
When I casually teased her,
she became flustered.
That shy, nervous demeanor
could only belong
to a young lady.
My eyes never deceive me.
(Yunlai Inn)
Strangely enough,
He Rufei's sister
is also called
He Yan.
A woman like you
joined Yezhou Garrison as a new recruit.
There must be a hidden story.
The day will come
when your secrets are uncovered.
What secrets could I have?
We were simply
meant to meet each other.
Beware of He Rufei.
He made me hold back
General Xiao's plea for help
for a few days.
Beware of whom?
(Who are you really?)
(Miss He Yan from the He family?)
(Or He Rufei, the one)
(from back then who was afraid)
(to show his true face?)
(If you're He Rufei,)
(then who is the current He Rufei?)
(If you're the He Rufei of old,)
(why would you)
(abandon us in our direst hour?)
Commander.
You do know the Xiao's sword techniques.
You've found out.
The Qinglang Sword Style
is known by the Xiaos
and one other person only.
Exactly.
I was once He Rufei.
That's not my true name.
I am He Yan,
the stepsister
of the current He Rufei.
From childhood,
our identities were swapped.
You exchanged identities?
I've been He Rufei
for as long as I can remember.
They claimed
my brother wouldn't live long.
I had to impersonate He Rufei,
or the family's noble title
would be revoked.
So I had no choice
but to live as He Rufei.
But I refused to submit to
such a fate.
So I left home and joined
the Fuyue Army.
I earned merits
and received honors,
but my brother who should've died young
was still alive.
When he returned home,
he poisoned and blinded me.
Then he stole General Feihong's identity
and even tried to kill me.
Perhaps God
took pity on me,
giving me another chance at life.
That's how He Yan came to be.
I am He Yan,
but also He Rufei.
I told you I wanted to earn glory.
That wasn't a lie.
Because I have to
rise to his level
to expose his lies
and prevent him
from harming
more innocent people.
Anything that belongs to me,
I will reclaim personally.
Xiao Jue, sorry
for keeping it from you.
I just didn't know
how to face you.
Only a question.
In the Mingshui Battle,
was it you who delayed
the reinforcements?
Yes.
I sent
late reinforcements...
30,000 Xiao Army soldiers died,
and my parents died one after another.
There's a conspiracy in the battle. I...
After lying to me for so long,
how can you expect me
to believe your one-sided claims?
You're right.
I deceived you.
How could I demand
your immediate trust?
But I will find evidence
to uncover the truth.
If you don't want to see me again,
I'll leave.
笙ｪPerhaps I'll regret saying goodbye笙ｪ
笙ｪMaybe we can't share sorrows and joys笙ｪ
Commander,
if you don't do it,
let me kill her!
Commander,
she killed so many.
How can we let her go?
Letting her walk free
is too merciful.
笙ｪBefore fate is confirmed笙ｪ
You will stay in Yezhou Garrison.
You can't leave there
until the truth is uncovered.
笙ｪLifelong devotion turns into a vow笙ｪ
笙ｪThat's my last wish笙ｪ
笙ｪAwaiting the spread of moonlight笙ｪ
How about...?
- Commander.
We're here.
(Today,)
you can
do everything you wish to do
without worries.
Just be your true self
as you've always been.
Whatever you like
and dislike,
(say it outright.)
(Cheer yourself up.)
(Can I truly)
do whatever I want?
Do as you please.
Okay.
Do as I please.
笙ｪWhat is there to fear?
We'll move forward together笙ｪ
笙ｪThrough endless dawns and dusks,
to eternity笙ｪ
笙ｪAwaiting the crescent moon's
reflection in your heart笙ｪ
笙ｪSplendor fades from your eyes笙ｪ
笙ｪCrimson threads entwine like rings,
binding our first vow笙ｪ
(Only a hundred.)
(As long as it pleases you,)
(it's worth it.)
笙ｪZither and harp
accompany our dancing dreams笙ｪ
笙ｪThe brocade moon writes our vow,
keeping this promise笙ｪ
Does it look good?
Yeah.
笙ｪAwaiting the crescent moon's
reflection in your heart笙ｪ
笙ｪSplendor fades from your eyes笙ｪ
笙ｪCrimson threads entwine like rings,
binding our first vow笙ｪ
笙ｪTime lingers as you and I share
overlapping palm lines笙ｪ
笙ｪZither and harp
accompany our dancing dreams笙ｪ
笙ｪThe brocade moon writes our vow,
keeping this promise笙ｪ
My bottom.
You really did it!
Wang Ba.
Can you smell meat?
Oh, really.
No, stop. Stop fighting.
I didn't eat lunch.
Let's stop.
Wait...
Where's it?
Meat.
Take a rest.
He,
you're getting stronger these days.
He was skilled.
Now, he trains every day.
He naturally keeps improving.
But sustaining this long-term,
how can his body endure it?
Commander, Mr. Shen.
Commander.
Make way.
Focus on training.
笙ｪLight shines upon my heart笙ｪ
笙ｪUnveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream笙ｪ
笙ｪThe resonance of courage
rings loud and clear笙ｪ
笙ｪIt's the boldness
that defines existence笙ｪ
笙ｪI've seen the mountains笙ｪ
笙ｪAnd trodden through ice笙ｪ
笙ｪDay after day, I venture alone笙ｪ
笙ｪDestiny is my creed笙ｪ
笙ｪIdeals surge beneath the surface笙ｪ
笙ｪIgniting the flame against the winds笙ｪ
笙ｪA restless yearning in my soul笙ｪ
笙ｪGazing through the mire笙ｪ
笙ｪWho cares about this boundless void笙ｪ
笙ｪCharge ahead with blazing fervor笙ｪ
笙ｪStubbornly fighting with my life笙ｪ
笙ｪSoaring across the world's expanse笙ｪ
笙ｪThere must always be a longing笙ｪ
笙ｪDisregard the wounds to seek the light笙ｪ
笙ｪLight shines upon my heart笙ｪ
笙ｪUnveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream笙ｪ
笙ｪThe resonance of courage
rings loud and clear笙ｪ
笙ｪIt's the boldness
that defines existence笙ｪ
笙ｪChasing the light within my heart笙ｪ
笙ｪBurying frailty,
embracing life through death笙ｪ
笙ｪYou'll meet gazes where storms brew笙ｪ
笙ｪWith our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me笙ｪ
笙ｪSoaring across the world's expanse笙ｪ
笙ｪThere must always be a longing笙ｪ
笙ｪDisregard the wounds to seek the light笙ｪ
笙ｪLight shines upon my heart笙ｪ
笙ｪUnveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream笙ｪ
笙ｪThe resonance of courage
rings loud and clear笙ｪ
笙ｪIt's the boldness
that defines existence笙ｪ
笙ｪChasing the light within my heart笙ｪ
笙ｪBurying frailty,
embracing life through death笙ｪ
笙ｪYou'll meet gazes where storms brew笙ｪ
笙ｪWith our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me笙ｪ