In the previous episode,
the match between
Nankatsu and Shutetsu
ended in a draw.
Now everyone
is getting ready for
the national tournament.
The best players from
the local schools' teams
will be chosen
to form a new team
that represents the city.
From the Nankatsu School,
Tsubasa, Taro and Ryo
were chosen.
Meanwhile, Roberto requested
to Tsubasa's parents
to allow him
to go to Brazil
so Roberto can train him
and make him
the best player of all time.
Shocked by the news,
Tsubasa happily agrees
and tells Roberto that he
will go with him to Brazil
once the national
tournament is over.
It's a once in
a lifetime opportunity
for Tsubasa.
[opening theme]
Episode 10:
Kojiro Appears.
MEIWA 4 ICHIEDA 0
Stop him! Don't let Kojiro near the goal!
-Yeah!
Their attacks are
so pathetic.
They can't stop me!
If you want to fight me,
it has to be to the death!
So arrogant! I won't let you
score anymore goals!
No way!
You idiots!
What in the world is
wrong with you, Kojiro?
Why would you do that?
-My leg!
-You're the worst!
You don't have to hurt
others to play soccer!
That's not right!
Just shut up!
Soccer is only for
the strongest players!
You're miserable!
This was supposed to be
a practice match
before the trials!
I won't let you hurt
anymore players!
The game is over!
Captain!
-Hm?
-Don't you think
it's enough for today?
Excuse me?
You're not planning
on listening
to those fools,
are you?
Well, let's see then...
how you manage to qualify
without me.
-What?
If you don't like
how I play,
then that's fine by me.
I'll stay on the bench
from now.
Someone else can be
the captain for all I care.
But, Captain...
I'm Kojiro Hyuga,
and this is how I play.
Victory is for the strong!
You must be aggressive
if you want to win!
Tsubasa!
Excellent shot, Tsubasa!
Thank you!
Now is your turn, Taro!
I wonder if it was
the right call.
Huh?
The captain leaves
in two weeks.
And if I take Tsubasa
to Brazil with me...
his mother would be
all alone in Japan.
I can't do that to her.
Even if he chose to
go to Brazil with me,
without any doubt,
-he would miss his childhood
-Roberto?
with his parents.
-Roberto!
-Huh?
-Oh!
-What's the matter?
You looked really worried.
Oh it's...
It's nothing.
How about a little break?
-Okay.
Ryo, how is it going?
What's wrong, Ryo?
We're just getting
started here!
What?
Did you get tired already?
Your grandpa works all day
and he doesn't get tired.
Oh, that's harsh!
Even my grandpa
takes a break!
I just need five minutes
to catch my breath!
That's okay.
But for sure you won't
get one tomorrow.
Why are you so mean to me?!
Tsubasa, Taro and you
were chosen after
the first eliminatory round,
and we'll make sure
you stay.
So you better do your best!
That's right.
Tsubasa and Taro
are surely gonna pass,
but you need more training.
We have to make sure.
That's so mean! I thought
you believed in me!
Yes, we do!
We just want to make sure
you stay in the team.
That's why we
want to help you
reach your potential.
Thanks everyone!
I hope he gets to stay.
He'll make it.
Yeah!
SHUTETSU VS. MATSUKAWA
He stole the ball!
Defenders! Don't let him
score another goal!
Uhh...
Humph!
Oh!
SHUTETSU VS. MATSUKAWA
I did it!
You're really good!
This is not even close
to what Nankatsu will face
on the national tournament.
Oh no! He managed
to get past him!
Captain!
Tsubasa, next time,
we'll be playing
on the same team.
Here!
Got it!
No, it can't be!
Genzo won't let them score!
That's the end of the match!
I'm... I'm sorry!
Hey, guys,
this new team is supposed
to be really strong, right?
If Tsubasa, Taro,
and Genzo are in it,
I'm sure we'll win
the national tournament.
Yeah! With them,
we will win for sure!
I wouldn't be so sure.
All the teams participating
in the tournament
are very good.
Oh, I get it!
You're saying that because
you've played with
most of them before, right?
Exactly.
For example,
against the team
from Chiba...
They train every day
on the beach,
and they are really strong.
players there are.
The Naniwa team from Osaka
has the tallest players,
and because of that,
they are experts at
intercepting the ball.
The Hakata team from Fukuoka
has members of all ages
and they take advantage
of what they learn
and they are
very unpredictable.
Wow! There sure are many
different kinds of teams.
Yeah, many.
If we manage to go to
the national tournament...
our strongest opponent
will surely be
the Meiwa team
from Showa...
Its captain's last name
is Hyuga.
He is really strong...
with skills that almost
match Tsubasa's skills.
-Huh?
What?!
That's impossible!
There's no way
he matches Tsubasa!
He's the only one
that managed
to score a goal to Genzo!
Kojiro is a striker.
A very different type.
His nature and game style
is very different
than yours.
Kojiro Hyuga,
from the Meiwa team.
I can't keep up
much longer.
Hi, Genzo!
I suppose you're
heading home, right?
What happened to you, Ryo?
You look a little beaten up.
Am I right?
Just shut up!
It's only because
I trained really hard
for the try outs, okay?!
But without any talent,
the effort is pointless.
Come here and
I'll show you my talent!
What's the matter?
It's nothing.
Don't worry, I'm fine.
You know what,
Roberto?
I can't wait to meet
that kid, Kojiro.
Taro told me
he's nothing like you.
But I'll tell you,
just like him...
all the other players
are very different.
I believe you.
I'm sure that in Brazil
the players are
very different too.
If you come to Brazil,
you won't get back
until you've become
a professional player.
Yeah!
No matter what, I'll be
a professional player!
That's my dream
and I won't stop
until I finally get it!
Then I'll be able to play
soccer every day!
Yes, but first, you must
qualify for and win
the national tournament.
Otherwise, you won't get to
come with me to Brazil.
I'll win
the national tournament!
It's not that easy.
Look closely.
A professional must
be able to do this.
Uh-huh.
Of course, you're still
very young to do this.
Your bones haven't
fully developed yet.
If you try this,
you'll only hurt yourself.
Yeah, I get it.
By the way...
About Genzo...
I want to tell you
that I noticed
he was slightly limping
on one of his legs.
Huh?
And so, the day
of the first practice match
for the Nankatsu team
arrived.
Out of the 30
chosen young men,
only 15 will be able to
stay and play
in the national tournament
representing
the Nankatsu city.
Okay, we will divide
the group
in the following way,
since we have
a lot of players
from the Shutetsu team.
Pay attention!
SHUTETSU VS. MIXED
Team A will be composed of just Shutetsu players.
The rest will form the other team.
SHUTETSU VS. MIXED
You heard that?
A match against Shutetsu!
We haven't seen them
since the last match.
Yeah! And we will play so
that the 15 players selected
are only from Team Shutetsu!
-Yeah!
If you're ready,
then we will begin!
All right,
looks like it's time
to have some fun.
Okay, let's go team!
We won't let you!
We will be the ones
to play
on the national tournament!
Listen up!
Just pass the ball around
to confuse them!
You're Genzo, right?
Huh?
And who are you?
I'm from the Meiwa team.
I'm Kojiro Hyuga.
So you're...Kojiro?
I've come to challenge you!
What?!
Huh?
Coach, look over there.
Teppei!
-Got it! Thanks!
-No way!
I'll be the one to score
the first goal!
-Huh?
-What the--?!
Get ready, keeper!
I'm going to crush you!
-That's Kojiro!
-What?
Don't tell me that's...
That's Kojiro, the captain
of the Meiwa team!
What do we do now, Captain?
Calm down!
I'll accept his challenge.
Coach, we should stop this now.
So that's him.
He is Kojiro.
Hey, who do you
think you are
to come here and
ruin our training?!
Beat it, fool!
Hey, what's wrong with you?!
Shutetsu!
Stop him now!
Now I get what
you were talking about.
His style really is
very different.
That's right. If we think of
you as kind when playing,
then Kojiro is the most
aggressive player there is.
What are you doing,
Shutetsu?!
Stop that terrible bully
now!
Go get him, Shingo!
I'll trust you'll be able to
knock some sense into him.
Yeah!
Why did you hit him?!
You did that on purpose!
Hey, shut up!
My game style is not
lame and pathetic
like all of yours!
Get ready, keeper!
Let's see if your reputation
is as good as they say
or you're just a fraud!
Watch out, Genzo!
Stop the ball!
That's the goal keeper
everyone keeps
yapping about?
You couldn't even react
to my shot.
That's so pathetic.
What's up?
Tsubasa, I understand
how you feel,
but you should not
fight him now.
Taro?
Hey, Kojiro.
Long time no see, Taro.
Hey, don't tell me
you moved to this town.
You know what?
If you're part of this team,
then you should...
just tell them
that the winner
of the national tournament
is going to be
the Meiwa team from Showa.
See ya!
Kojiro, if you came here
to spy on us...
then you should have
stayed a little longer.
Now you'll hav to go home
without watching...
the skills of Tsubasa Ozora.
Captain...
I can't believe it!
How is it possible that Genzo lost
to that arrogant idiot?!
Genzo left the field
without saying a word.
-Huh?
Genzo!
CAPTAIN TSUBASA
We'll be right back
with Captain Tsubasa!
AFFILIATION: SHOWA FC
BIRTHDAY: AUGUST 17 HEIGHT: 158 CM
I'm really sorry
for what happened.
So then you hurt your leg?
That's why you
couldn't react
to that crazy kid's shot.
No, you're mistaken.
Even if I had been able to,
I probably couldn't have...
stopped that shot.
It was too powerful.
Oh...
Besides...
I will not use my injury
to avoid my responsibility.
I lost.
Tsubasa,
surely we'll go together
to the national tournament,
and I bet that Kojiro
will also be there.
I'll get my reputation back
when I fight him.
Ah!
Yeah!
Hello, good morning, son.
Good morning.
Will you work all day
today again, Mom?
Son, don't you
worry about me.
I'll be all right.
I just want you to go and
enjoy your favorite sport.
I will, Mom!
My life is set on soccer!
Since Dad died,
my mom has had to take
several jobs.
I can't enjoy playing soccer
and watch my family suffer.
SAKAMOTO GREEN GROCER
Good morning!
Would you like some help?
Thank so much, kid!
Be careful, though.
It's heavy!
It's okay. I'll use it
as training, sir.
I need to earn
all the money I can
for when my siblings
get older.
I'll need even more
if I want to make it
to high school.
But my siblings are first.
Here.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, sir.
I'll become
a professional player
and I'll take
my family along with me.
I won't let them
struggle anymore.
They are my priority.
That's why I have to
get better
as a soccer player.
I must win
all the games I can
and qualify for
the national tournament!
Hey, Big Brother.
Good morning.
Good morning!
I see you're already up!
Big Brother, did Mom leave?
Yeah, but don't worry.
I'll make breakfast today.
Well, family, today,
I'll embark on another trip.
Now that you decided
to go to Brazil,
I probably won't see you
when I get back, son.
So please, take care
and train hard.
I will!
Actually, Captain,
Tsubasa promised me something
before going to Brazil.
And what is that?
That if he doesn't win
the national tournament,
then he won't be able to
come with me to Brazil.
That's quite a challenge!
But I don't think there
will be any problem!
I'm sure my little
soccer player will get it!
Thanks, Dad!
Really!
Listen, Tsubasa,
I want you to promise me
something too.
Huh?
If you can score three goals
on today's game,
then I'll let you
go to Brazil, got it?
I thought you said
that he could
go to Brazil already,
though, huh?
Yes, darling, but I need to
make sure of
his commitment to the trip.
Of course, Dad!
I'll do my very best to
score those three goals!
And I'll make sure to get
the moment on tape!
The way it seems,
it looks like this might be
the last game
of Tsubasa in Japan.
Hmm...
MEIWA ELEMENTARY
Captain, wait for me!
Please, Kojiro, don't go.
Are you really not going
to be in the play-offs?
What? Didn't I
tell you to play and win
the national tournament
on your own?
I mean...
since you don't
want me to play,
let's see how you do it
on your own.
Why is he always
so stubborn?
Now what are we gonna do?
We can't win without him.
I don't understand why
he is risking everything
knowing what he got
on the line.
-Doesn't he care?
-What's on the line?
Well, it's just that
I heard that
the captain's dad
died last year.
Yeah and that's not all...
I heard his mom has
several jobs now
to provide for the captain
and all his siblings.
I don't know why he risks
everything like that.
Captain Kojiro needs
to win the tournament
to become
a professional player.
He only thinks about
finding a way
to help his mother
with this.
I understand!
He has to win because
there'll be
tons of scouts
in the national tournament!
If that's the case,
then we can't let him down!
We have to win for him!
-Yeah!
Finally,
all the teams have gathered
to start
the national tournament.
I made it at the end!
All right, Genzo,
let's do our best.
Yes, I will!
Let's do it!
How's your leg feeling?
It's better now. That's why
I'm here, Tsubasa.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the third match of
the first round will be
NATIONAL JUVENILE SOCCER TOURNAMENT
SHIZUOKA TOURNAMENT, DAY 1 ROUND 1
NANKATSU SC FUJI FCbetween the Nankatsu SC and the Fuji FC.
This is your first match.
Give it your best!
-Yes!
Come on!
Why am I benched?
Tsubasa!
We're here to support you!
Dad!
Remember!
I want three goals!
Yeah!
Tsubasa!
You are truly the best!
And the Nankatsu team
makes the first move.
Just you wait.
I'll show everyone
my skills.
When the scouts see
what I can do,
they will want me
and I'll become
a professional
soccer player!
And there it goes!
The first goal
of Nankatsu!
That's right!
One down!
My destiny is in MY hands.
And Nankatsu
scores its second goal!
Now Tsubasa is heading
straight for the goal!
And to think that I was
worried about my leg.
At this pace, I won't
even have to move at all.
Go for the third, Tsubasa!
Go Tsubasa!
Pay attention!
I want you to stop him!
Tsubasa
makes a one-two pass
to Taro Misaki!
Yeah! You better know
the golden duet!
Tsubasa
gets ready and strikes!
And goal!
The keeper didn't even
see it coming!
Tsubasa manages to get
a Hat-trick on this match!
-Unbelievable!
-Dad! I did it! Did you see?
That's amazing!
Now I can get to the docks
as the proud father I am!
I want you to win
the national tournament,
go to Brazil
to acheive your dream
and become
a professional player!
Yeah!
Take care, Dad.
I love you!
Sail carefully.
Yes, honey.
I promise you I will.
NANKATSU SC FUJI FC MOVING ON TO THE SECOND ROUND
Final score, Nankatsu SC 7, Fuji FC 0.
Hello, my son.
Why are you outside?
Welcome home, Mom.
I made your dinner
so you can eat.
But it's late.
Don't you have
a soccer match tomorrow?
Yeah, but don't worry.
They'll win for me.
But why won't you play?
Oh!
The Nankatsu team
won their first match.
And continued
the winning streak
in the following matches.
On the other hand...
What a goal!
I told you
we could do it!
We did it!
All right!
This is bad.
We barely won the last game,
but now, this is worse.
Without the captain,
it's practically impossible
to win.
Captain...
It looks like the team
needs my help, doesn't it?
Let's go, Takeshi.
All right!
Let's go do it!
[ending theme]