SUNWOL FOUNDATION
It hurts, doesn't it?
Do Do-hee.
Your heart is about to split in half.
Like a ripe apple.
See you in hell.
Director Jeong!
Director Jeong.
That bastard!
-Director Jeong.
-Someone's on the ground.
Someone call an ambulance!
Someone get Do Do-hee here, please!
Get Do Do-hee!
Do Do-hee!
I know that you're not the culprit
better than anyone, Ms. Do.
But the higher-ups were pressuring me.
When will I be released?
You can leave
once the warrant is reviewed.
It'll be dismissed
since there's no evidence.
Detective Park.
-What is it?
-It's…
BP and pulse are dropping.
More fluid, please.
He's going to be okay, right?
Please save him.
Please let me go see him.
He got stabbed!
He's dying as we speak.
Please?
Seok-hoon.
I have to get out of here.
I have to go see Jeong Gu-won.
I have to go see him.
More gauze, please.
Increase the IV flow.
Are we ready for surgery?
Yes, everyone's on standby.
Send the patient to the OR…
Please save him.
Hang in there, Jeong Gu-won.
Just a little longer.
How is he, Doctor?
We've sutured the wound,
but he's already lost too much blood.
And his heart valves
are seriously damaged.
He might not make it through the night.
Do something.
Do whatever it takes to save him!
Please save him.
I beg you.
-Hurry.
-This is your fault.
All of this happened because of you.
You killed Director Jeong!
-Let go!
-Stop it.
Pull yourself together.
We have to save Director Jeong first.
Come with me.
Please wait outside.
It's too late.
I was too late.
You were always there to protect me.
But I…
couldn't…
You're heavy. Will you move?
Jeong Gu-won.
Your crying face from up close
is hilarious.
It's so funny that I can't even die.
I thought you were dead!
Are you not fully healed?
It worked only halfway again.
Useless powers.
I'll get the doctor.
Just give me a second.
I need to charge up.
Director Jeong…
She saved him.
She doesn't know how
that will come to threaten her own life.
Poor thing.
EPISODE 8
THE FATEFUL CHOICE
Do-hee.
I'll be back soon.
I won't leave you alone for too long.
Star Jin.
I looked everywhere for you.
Until now,
I was content…
with being Director Jeong's
human companion.
Because I was more special
than other humans.
No other woman came before me.
But then she showed up.
Do Do-hee…
cut in front of me.
Why aren't you asking anything?
Because you wouldn't tell me anyway.
Thank you.
You don't have to say those things to me.
Things like "Thank you" or "I'm sorry."
I'm okay
as long as you're safe.
That's all I need.
Let's hurry. We don't want to get
Detective Park in trouble.
Do Do-hee.
Is he still not up?
The doctor said
that he should get better now.
Why can't he recover?
What on earth is happening to him?
Well…
How's Mr. Jeong?
He's still in critical condition.
Director Jeong.
Director Jeong!
Are you okay?
Does it hurt that much?
It's just…
I had a nightmare.
Director Jeong.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
Where's Do Do-hee?
The result should be out by now.
Detective Park.
What is it now?
The warrant has been reviewed and…
it's been dismissed.
Why would you pause?
You scared me.
How's Jeong Gu-won?
He's awake.
That's a relief.
HANKOOK UNIVERSITY GENERAL HOSPITAL
Get me some water, Mr. Park.
You want water?
Not this.
I want cold water.
You want cold water.
It's ice-cold.
Come on. Where's my straw?
You can sit down.
What's that?
I know how much you love your sweets.
I tried some, and they melt in your mouth.
Sit down.
Okay.
Scratch my back. It itches like crazy.
-A little higher.
-Here?
-A little lower.
-Around here?
Are you scratching
the wrong places on purpose?
Why did you stop?
You certainly were a nobleman
in your past life.
You're a natural when it comes to
bossing people around.
-Around here?
-No.
Yes, there you go.
You can sit down.
I may look okay on the outside,
but I'm a wreck on the inside.
How far along are you in your recovery?
I'd say I cheated death by a whisker.
It's a miracle that you survived.
I thought I'd never get to see you again.
What are you talking about? I'm a demon.
As an apex predator, I…
Hit that pain relief button.
Pain relief…
It hurts like crazy.
-What are you doing?
-I pushed it.
Keep going.
-But…
-More.
Keep going.
Do Do-hee?
Delivery.
-Delivery?
-What is it?
This way.
Put them over here.
GET WELL SOON, BOSS
WILD DOGS
Goodbye.
Do they think this is a funeral home?
What kind of fool sends funeral sprays
to someone recovering?
"Wild Dogs"?
Who are they?
We must protect our boss.
-Let's protect him!
Sir.
Boss.
-Boss!
Who's the scumbag that did this to you?
Boss, I'll find the bastard and--
I'm not your boss, and I'm not dead yet.
So get rid of the flowers.
Are you in pain, boss?
-Nurse! Doctor!
-Help!
-Get me the hospital director!
-Get lost!
-Come on!
-Hurry!
If you so much as approach me
within a 5 m radius,
I'll make you regret it.
-Back up.
-Keep going.
-Back up a bit more.
-Jeez, that's long.
That's 5 m, sir.
Our boss has made
his historic first order.
Do not cross over this line.
Everyone move over here!
BARK, BARK, BARK, BARK, BARK
WE BARK TO SHOW OUR LOVE FOR THE BOSS
What's wrong with them?
I'd rather get another hit on the head.
Definitely.
Disgusting.
Sir.
Guys, the boss's wife is here.
-You look beautiful, ma'am!
Your boss's wife?
Don't look them in the eye.
Sir.
The bed is way too high.
Getting on it feels like rock climbing.
-Jeong Gu-won.
-Do Do-hee!
Is it okay for you to move around?
Of course. I'm fine now. Watch this.
You shouldn't move around yet.
Lie down right now.
I'm really fine, I swear.
Sure you are.
Who are those men in black outside?
Director Jeong happens to be popular
with people from all walks of life.
Let's go home now.
If I stay here,
those punks will keep bothering me.
Your treatment isn't over yet.
Being with you is the best treatment.
Oh, my heart.
All right.
Mr. Jeong may have had an attitude,
but he was good at heart.
Even those who accused Ms. Do of murder
are now supporting us
after hearing about what happened to him.
That's because they feel guilty!
What's the point of all that now?
Why are you crying?
Don't be like that. We have work to do.
Let's show Ms. Do a neat chart
illustrating the shifts
in public opinion of her.
That is Mr. Jeong's parting gift
for Ms. Do!
We have to get back to work!
My goodness.
Mr. Jeong is fine.
-Sorry?
-What?
I knew it! I picked a good card today!
You did?
Mr. Jeong!
He saw my face. He'll come for me.
Damn it!
He's coming.
He's coming for me.
We're not even getting any static,
let alone sparks.
Perhaps we could speed up charging
if more surface area came in contact.
That makes perfect sense.
Then…
should we try hugging?
That's a good suggestion.
Then…
should I do this?
No.
More like this.
How about…
How does it feel?
I feel like I'm charging up nicely.
The lengths I go to charge you up.
All of this happened because of you.
You killed Director Jeong!
You're up.
Yes.
Don't move.
Let's go find the scumbag.
I saw his real face,
even if it was just half of it.
Now I can find him.
You're not going anywhere
in this condition.
Recovery comes first.
Revenge comes first.
I'll find him and burst his heart right…
You're not ready for any revenge yet.
It's working.
Not anymore.
I guess you need a lot more.
But still…
Breathing's gotten a lot easier.
You should get better
the more you charge up.
I have to go to work.
Can you take the day off?
-No.
-A flat-out no?
But you're the CEO.
Why don't you celebrate my survival
by declaring today…
the company's anniversary?
Rest up.
Then just five more minutes.
Let me charge up a bit more.
It was quite chaotic last night.
For the peace of mankind,
let's make up.
We didn't fight,
so there's no need to make up.
Also, I couldn't care less
about the peace of mankind.
There once lived a man
who loved eating pork.
Let's call him K.
One day,
K met a very special pig.
Imagine K developing affection
for this specific pig
and eventually
for all the pigs in the world.
Wouldn't K become a vegetarian then?
What do you say?
Let's work together
to turn K into a vegetarian.
What a load of bull.
She doesn't seem to realize
the peace of mankind is in our hands.
A demon is on the verge
of becoming a guardian.
Wait up.
Let me come with you.
Don't take your injury lightly.
You barely escaped death.
So stay home and rest for today.
Look what he did to me.
Who knows what he might do to you?
I have another bodyguard
waiting at the office.
So don't worry and--
No. I can't trust anyone right now.
What if the bastard shows up
disguised as a bodyguard?
I'm going to protect you myself.
Stop right there.
I forbid you to do so.
Who gives you the right?
As your butler, I put your safety first.
-You can't guard anyone in this state.
-Then you're fired.
You're no longer my butler,
so stop butting in and go home.
Is this how little you think of
our friendship forged by capitalism?
Do as he says.
You do as I say.
-I feel hurt!
-For crying out loud!
As a matter of fact, there is a solution.
This car is spacious enough
for all of us and then some.
Am I right?
Shouldn't you work on the performance
instead of following me around?
We'll put it on hold.
How could we carry on
when you just got stabbed?
I don't really see a correlation there.
An AI like you wouldn't understand.
You need to charge up
whenever you can to recover.
You said I can't in front of others.
We're officially married now.
Upon an anonymous person's request,
I accused Ms. Do Do-hee
of murdering Chairwoman Ju Cheon-suk.
I caused Ms. Do Do-hee immense damage.
I sincerely apologize.
Are you keeping logs of
the articles and comments by keywords?
-Yes, sir.
-Also,
Sunwol Foundation's general manager
is coming with Mr. Jeong.
I wonder if the general manager
would be just as handsome as Mr. Jeong.
Be careful
or you might fall into the mirror.
Here they come.
The man with the twisted head?
Right, it's him.
I apologize for the other day.
You scared me!
-I just…
-I'm okay.
I wanted to celebrate
Mr. Jeong's discharge from the hospital.
Is everyone okay?
Are you all good?
Following the confession
made by Clickbaity News yesterday,
as well as the attack on Mr…
I mean, the attack on Director Jeong,
the public opinion on Ms. Do
has shifted dramatically.
Favorable comments and news articles
about the two of you are also increasing.
Those who accused you of murder
are showing their sympathy for you now.
That's right.
Now they're eager to find out
who tried to bring you down
and kill Mr. Jeong.
No one can stop you
from running for chairwoman now.
This is all thanks to Director Jeong,
who risked his life for Ms. Do.
A round of applause!
I actually prepared a cake for you,
but I didn't bring it out earlier
as the party popper alarmed all of you.
What kind of cake? Strawberry? Chocolate?
Ta-da.
I'm not a fan of green tea
or whipped cream.
No, that's not it.
It's a black tea chiffon cake.
-Is that right?
-One, two
-One, two, three, four
-Congratulations
-Dear Director Jeong
-Congratulations, dear Mr. Jeong
-On your discharge
Should I make a wish?
-Sure.
-Go ahead.
One, two, three.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
-What's the matter?
-What do you mean?
Why were you so startled?
I've never seen you so scared before.
Me? Scared?
I'm a demon.
Nice try, but you can't fool me.
Go back to the theater
if you're going to keep talking nonsense.
Suit yourself then.
I'll spill everything to Do Do-hee
so she'd have you stay home.
You can't do that.
So just tell me what's going on.
I had this dream.
I was engulfed in huge flames,
and my whole body was on fire.
I can still recall
the feeling of my fingertips burning.
It's driving me crazy.
Was it spontaneous combustion?
Is this what humans call
fear?
Director Jeong.
I guess
I'm becoming mentally soft
as my powers weaken.
Once I recover,
everything will go back to normal.
I'm here to see Mr. Jeong.
He's not in at the moment.
Then I'd like to see Ms. Do.
Please proceed as suggested.
Thank you.
Ms. Jin Ga-young is here to see you.
Would you like some coffee or tea?
No need.
I'm not here for a chitchat.
Stop taking advantage of Director Jeong
and let him go.
We need each other.
Each other?
You mean you need him.
You're leading him around by the nose,
exploiting his weakness.
He almost died because of you.
Just how selfish are you going to be?
Sort out your mess on your own.
Stop exploiting Director Jeong
by threatening him with his tattoo.
I checked the CCTV at the theater,
and you were right.
The book was stolen.
An hour of the footage was missing
on the night the book disappeared
as well as the day you were attacked.
The culprit installed malware
to meddle with the CCTV at certain times.
Then that means
he knows what I am.
Mr. Jeong.
Someone was asking for you earlier.
Who?
It was a tall woman.
I don't know who it was.
Director Jeong!
I'm relieved to see you're okay.
Thank goodness.
I'll call a taxi.
You can go ahead, Mr. Park.
I'd like to talk to the director.
About what?
Let's just go, Star Jin.
It won't take long.
I heard that your powers were flickering.
No need to worry.
They'll be fine once I get my tattoo back.
I'm not so sure.
Do Do-hee is the reason
your powers are weakening.
It's not like that.
That's what you want to believe.
Deep down, you know it too.
Everything points to her as the problem.
That's none of your business.
Is she special to you now?
Does she hold a special place
in your heart?
You're becoming more and more human
because you keep experiencing
human emotions because of her.
Because you're…
in love with her.
Nothing is more human than loving someone.
-Stop it.
-You're the one who should stop.
If you're a demon, act like one!
Didn't you say so yourself
that humans are
insignificant and weak beings?
Is that what you want to be?
You have to stop.
If you don't,
it won't end here.
Would you like some music?
No, thank you.
Okay.
Did Ga-young say anything stupid to you?
Not really.
She just invited me
to watch her performance.
Did she say something to you?
No, she didn't.
Please do come.
It's put on hold for now,
but not for too long.
Swords will be flying through the air.
I will.
Ms. Jin must've been shocked
by what happened to you.
I could feel how sincerely
she cared about you.
Madam Ju.
Should I
keep pushing forward?
Jeong Gu-won almost died because of me,
even though he had
nothing to do with this fight.
I don't know if I should
keep pushing forward
at the expense of someone else.
But…
if I give up here,
it'll be unfair to you.
Don't worry about a dead person.
I'm just worried
it'll be frustrating for you.
I am frustrated.
I'm so frustrated and upset.
I lost my dear family,
and I don't even know who did it.
But you have a new family now.
Don't lose your new family
because of your dead one.
Still…
Do what's best for you.
Do what's best for me?
What's best for someone you care about
is also what's best for you.
Then what about you?
What's best for you?
What's best for you…
is what's best for me.
Seok-hoon.
I need to talk to you.
Are you okay?
Are you in pain?
I'm fine.
Did you take the painkillers?
I don't need them.
I feel great
because I've been charging up.
We should get ready for work.
Mr. Jeong.
I heard you got hurt.
I saw on the news
that someone attacked you.
Don't believe everything
you see on the news.
They even accused
an innocent person of murder.
Let's go inside.
Run away if you want to live.
Everyone by Do Do-hee's side
ends up dying.
Should I go beat him up?
Even I could beat him to a pulp.
Don't mind him.
I guess Seok-hoon can't make it.
Do Do-hee's only loyal ally
would hardly miss this meeting.
He's probably running late again.
Let us begin the special board meeting.
Today, we will take a nomination vote
for the next chairperson of Mirae Group.
I have something to announce.
Each candidate will get a chance
to make a speech later.
It's an important matter
related to the vote.
All right, go ahead.
To prevent any further
conflicts and disputes,
I hereby withdraw my candidacy.
What on earth is she playing at now?
We need to talk.
Later.
Then let us take a vote
on whether to propose Mr. Noh Suk-min
as the sole candidate
for the chairperson position
at the stockholders' meeting.
IN FAVOR, AGAINST, ABSTENTION
What do you think you're doing?
Let's talk outside.
You made a difficult decision.
I appreciate it.
What are you playing at?
I've decided to forgive and forget.
I'll also renounce my inheritance.
So let's put an end
to the war.
I'm glad you made
a wise decision in the end.
Good job.
Tell me why you're doing this.
I'm tired of it all.
Is that it?
I can't keep living in anxiety and fear.
I can't even go to work
or take a walk by myself.
I want to live in peace like everyone else
and go back to my normal life.
So I got rid of the reason
they wanted to hunt me down.
No.
You're lying.
Look me in the eye.
And tell me the truth.
I can't trust you anymore.
What?
You can no longer protect me.
You've become so weak
that you can't even protect yourself.
Does that answer your question?
No…
Why isn't he here yet?
Why?
There's something wrong with his powers.
What is she thinking?
What's her next move?
She really caught me off guard this time.
Maybe she just gave up.
She's too young to handle
everything that's happened after all.
Like I said many times,
that's not how she is.
I'm sure she's making us
let our guard down
only to stab us all in the back.
Her bodyguard was also recently attacked.
That probably scared her.
No way. She's not the one
who was attacked.
She's someone who wouldn't give up
even at gunpoint.
Whatever the reason,
I'm glad she finally realized her position
and gave up.
Great job, honey.
He's not the chairman yet.
Isn't it too early for a toast?
Do-gyeong.
-Thank you for the meal.
-Stay seated until everyone's done.
I have plans.
Noh Do-gyeong.
Sit back down right now.
Shall we?
Open the door, Director Jeong!
Director Jeong!
You can no longer protect me.
You've become so weak
that you can't even protect yourself.
You mean you need him.
You're leading him around by the nose,
exploiting his weakness.
He almost died because of you.
Just how selfish are you going to be?
Run away if you want to live.
Everyone by Do Do-hee's side
ends up dying.
RESULTS OF MIRAE GROUP
SPECIAL BOARD MEETING
CEO NOH SUK-MIN TO BE SOLE CANDIDATE
FOR THE CHAIRPERSON POSITION
I'm going to give up, Seok-hoon.
I'll withdraw my candidacy tomorrow.
Do-hee.
I've done my best.
I'm sure Madam Ju would understand.
It's not like catching the culprit
will bring her back to life.
I think I just needed something
to take my anger out on
after losing Madam Ju.
That's why I couldn't let go.
Once I let go,
everyone will be happy.
Are you doing this
for Mr. Jeong?
Because you don't want him
to get hurt again?
I don't want to lose someone
I care about again.
You knew everything, didn't you?
What happened?
I'm sure she told you everything.
Why did she suddenly give up?
If you're so curious, ask her yourself.
She won't tell me anything!
Didn't you tell me
she must have her reasons
for not saying anything?
You should've talked her out of it
by any means necessary.
Don't you know how important it is
for her to find Ju Cheon-suk's killer?
I do know. I know it all too well!
Do-hee has always
blamed herself for her parents' deaths.
She'll now blame herself
for my aunt's death as well
because of you!
What?
You're the reason why she gave up.
She didn't want you to get hurt again.
Do Do-hee!
GU-WON THE SAVIOR
All the flowers have withered.
Madam Ju.
You never got to see
your prized plants bearing fruit.
Are you really okay?
I'm sorry, Madam Ju.
I'm so sorry.
Let's go back.
If you're giving up because of me,
let's go back and fight again.
It's not like that.
Do Do-hee.
Do what's best for you.
Because that's what's best for me.
They're all dead.
Madam Ju,
Mom, and Dad.
Everyone I've ever loved is dead.
And you'll die…
because of me too.
I don't care.
Even if my feelings for you
make me insignificant and weak,
you are my fate
that I cannot defy.
What's best for you
has become what's best for me.
I'm not giving up on Do Do-hee
no matter what.
Hubby, give me a piggyback ride.
I feel so free and happy.
You call yourselves the Wild Dogs?
I have a task for you.
If you fail,
I forbid you to show up
in front of me ever again.
-Let's go!
-Yes, Detective?
-We found the culprit, Ms. Do.
His name is Gi Kwang-chul.
He's currently on our wanted list,
so we'll be able to track him down soon.
The hide-and-seek is over.
The clocks. They've stopped.
My powers weren't just flickering.
They're completely gone.
Subtitle translation by: Min-jin Kim