[Fated Hearts]
[Episode 21]
Your Majesty, here, have one.
Come on, Your Majesty,
try this.
Have some wine too.
Have another one.
I missed it again.
Your Majesty,
I've sent
the Prince of Zhennan and his party
to the Rongyang Palace.
So?
Did they like it?
Here.
Bai Shouzhuo,
I like your honesty.
You don't butter me up
or lie to me.
The prince didn't show much reaction.
But the Princess of Zhennan
didn't seem very pleased.
The Princess of Zhennan…
Also,
the wife
of Vice Revenue Minister Huang
is coming to the palace tomorrow
to visit her sister.
Bai Shouzhuo,
earlier today,
I saw the dress
that princess from Susha was wearing—
absolutely stunning.
Get one just like it
and send it to Mrs. Huang.
Yes.
Also…
Go tell the Prince of Zhennan
that since he's back,
I'll hold a banquet
to welcome him.
Let's…
set it for tonight.
Don't forget
to tell him to bring
the Princess of Zhennan.
Yes.
Go now.
Do you think what Ling Feng said
is true?
Is Feng Pingcheng really dying?
A matter this serious
wouldn't be fake.
If the Emperor could die at any moment,
then fortune is on our side.
But Prime Minister,
you don't seem pleased.
What are you here for?
Be careful. Feng Suige might catch on.
Fu Yixiao has figured out
who I really am.
But Feng Suige still doesn't know.
I haven't given Fu Yixiao
any chance to approach him.
Later,
I'll find a way to keep Feng Suige
in the palace.
You think Fu Yixiao will just
do as you say?
She cares a lot about Feng Suige,
so she won't risk
calling my bluff.
I've warned her—
if Feng Suige learns the truth,
I'll kill the Emperor.
Let me remind you:
without my orders,
you must not kill Feng Pingcheng.
The heir to the throne
hasn't been decided.
If Feng Pingcheng dies now,
Feng Suige will be next
in the line of succession.
You must not act on your own.
We've already removed Hou Jing
from the Ministry of War.
You now control the central court
and all six ministries.
If you kill Feng Pingcheng
and make Feng Chengyang take the throne,
who could stop you?
Now is the best time
to kill Feng Pingcheng!
I'll say it again—
without my order,
you must not kill the Emperor.
I was just joking.
I wouldn't dare act recklessly.
Regicide is a serious crime.
Of course I'll listen to
your instructions.
You can put on an act
for others,
but spare me that spoiled
young marquis attitude.
You can't hide
your true intentions from me.
I'm really making a fool of myself.
I'm nothing compared to you—
a wily old fox
who manages
to pass as a loyal, upright statesman
and make the whole world believe it.
That's something
I need to learn from you.
All right.
I'm leaving.
I just hope that once it's all over,
you and I can sit down
and celebrate together.
But do you think by then,
we'll really be able to sit down
and enjoy a drink?
Let me warn you:
the truth will eventually come out.
I can keep Feng Suige in the dark for now,
but not forever.
If Fu Yixiao tells him the truth,
everything will come to light.
Prime Minister,
think about the consequences.
Murong Yao
looks like a harmless noble heir,
naive and easy to read,
but in truth,
he's anything but.
[Wutong Mansion]
Actually, he's calculating and meticulous.
His eyes and ears are all over
Feng Suige's residence.
The four ladies
who are always with him
should all be his trusted operatives.
Yes.
Chunhan, Xiachen,
Qiuxi, and Dongxiao—
the four of them are
Murong Yao's
most trusted subordinates.
The two assassins
who came after me that day
were Chunhan and Qiuxi.
So,
his frequent visits to pleasure houses
and daily debauchery
are all
deliberate acts
to fool everyone.
Yes.
He's always surrounded
by beautiful girls.
But that's just his disguise.
He's very ambitious,
and he's never
let any woman distract him.
Miss, your beauty is unmatched
and captivating.
May I ask your name?
I feel like we've met before.
It must be that night!
You're the very girl
I saw in my dreams.
When he first saw me in Yujing,
he was testing me
to see if I recognized
Meng Junran's identity.
Who does he care about the most?
Feng Suige.
He's just pretending.
And…
and Elder Marquis Murong.
Elder Marquis Murong?
Murong Yao is a filial son.
He obeys the Elder Marquis completely
and hates to upset him.
You advised me to leave Yujing before.
But I don't want to give up so easily.
If he can be so cruel,
I'll fight him
to the bitter end.
You're no match for him.
His methods are ruthless,
and he has so many guards.
I don't want you
to get hurt again.
Don't worry.
I won't act impulsively.
I'll observe patiently
and wait for the right moment.
Then I'll make him
pay the price.
Be very careful.
If you need anything,
come find me at Zhengnian Hall.
If I'm not there, leave a note.
I'll see it.
Thank you,
Miss Yixiao.
I didn't know.
He never told me
about his illness.
Chengyang,
go to your father now.
Go stay with him.
Mother,
what about you?
You go first.
I still have a few things to discuss
with your grandfather.
All right.
Mother.
Alright.
Go now.
Okay.
He never told me about it.
I didn't know.
I knew nothing at all.
I'm the Empress of Susha,
his wife.
Yet he kept hiding it from me.
What matters most now is
who will take the throne
after His Majesty dies.
After…
after His Majesty dies?
By right,
you are the Empress,
and Chengyang is your son.
But His Majesty still hasn't
named an heir to this day.
I used to think
he just couldn't decide.
But he's been terminally ill
for 15 years.
How could he not make arrangements
for after his death?
There's only one reason
he kept it from you—
the heir he chose
isn't your son.
I didn't know.
He never told me anything.
That's because he doesn't trust you.
Remember this—
I'll make sure Chengyang
takes the throne.
Things won't be peaceful for a while.
Keep your eyes on Chengyang
and stay sharp.
Now's not the time
to grieve.
[Rongyang Palace]
What?
Are we under house arrest here?
Can't I go out for a walk?
Palace grounds are off-limits.
No outsiders allowed.
Please go back.
No outsiders allowed?
Not even the Prince of Zhennan?
We've been ordered
to prevent anyone from trespassing
on the palace grounds.
[Rongyang Palace]
This path marks the boundary.
Please do not cross it.
Got it.
[Rongyang Palace]
Your Highness.
There are guards at the gate.
They say
the palace grounds are off-limits.
Looks like
we're under house arrest here.
They're watching us so closely.
We can't do anything.
I figured as much.
Someone just came to say
the Emperor is hosting a welcome banquet.
Let's see if
an opportunity comes up then.
Xia Jingyan is very hostile toward you.
In my view, this welcome banquet
is a trap.
He wouldn't dare kill me.
He did everything he did
in the Empress Dowager's palace today
just to make
the whole world know
he's not afraid of me.
To make it clear
that my life is in his hands.
I'm afraid by now,
every official in court knows
he threatened me with a knife.
How childish.
Even if he won't kill you,
he'll certainly
humiliate you.
Now that we're in Shengjing,
this kind of thing
is bound to happen.
Mother has let you live until now
only out of respect
for Father!
Last night, Father
passed into the afterlife.
You won't live much longer either.
How satisfying!
Why are you just standing there?
Hurry and pull him up.
Take this.
I've circled some names.
Memorize them.
You might need them one day.
[Dai Jin] [Wang Encheng]
Understood.
Where's Her Highness?
Bai Shouzhuo
just sent some servants
to help her settle in.
She's a princess
but is forced
to live in a place
as rundown as Rongyang Palace.
It's hard on her.
It truly is.
The floor needs to be cleaner.
Yes.
Move all these away,
and this.
Potted plants…
Put them over there.
-Yes.
Put them on that table.
The plants in the courtyard
need to be tended to daily.
-Yes.
Thank you.
Your Highness is back.
I asked them
to wash all those
old curtains.
The old furniture
can't be replaced right away,
so I had it cleaned thoroughly.
With everything in order,
I hope it helps
lift your spirits a little.
I never expected
Your Highness would adapt so quickly.
You thought I was spoiled
and would complain
when I saw how old and shabby
the Rongyang Palace is?
Your Highness thought the same?
As long as I'm by your side,
no hardship scares me.
Do you have any wishes?
If it's something I can help with,
I'll fulfill it for you.
Military Advisor Xiao,
would you give us a moment?
Everyone, come out with me.
-Yes.
You just said you'd fulfill
my wishes for me.
What does that mean?
You're clever, Your Highness.
I believe you already know.
I helped you escape Yujing.
You don't want to be indebted to me,
so you want to help me
fulfill a wish.
If one isn't enough,
you can have three.
Just one is enough.
My wish
is
for us to be deeply in love
and stay together forever.
I'm sorry,
but I cannot do that.
♪ Flying alone ♪
♪ With no need for direction ♪
♪ Flying up to the clouds ♪
In that case,
♪ Yet the sun is hiding ♪
you'll just owe me a favor.
I'll tell you when I think of something.
♪ Roaming freely ♪
♪ Unafraid of wind or frost ♪
♪ Don't cry, don't cry ♪
♪ I'll remember the way home ♪
Brother,
I've learned about
Father's illness.
Even Lord Ling,
with all his skills,
can't do anything?
Will Father
never wake up again?
Don't worry.
His Majesty will certainly wake up.
Really?
Suige,
when Father wakes up,
we should persuade him
not to
work so hard anymore.
I know,
you don't say it out loud,
but deep down,
you care about Father.
Then why is it
that every time you two meet,
you end up arguing?
There are things you don't understand.
And I hope
you never will.
Maybe I don't understand,
but I just
wish
you and Father
could get along.
Now that Xiyang
has left Susha,
Father only has
the two of us by his side.
You've grown up.
Much more sensible now.
Officail Website : kissasian.be
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Uncle!
Uncle.
I'm back.
Forgive me, Uncle.
No loud voices
inside the ancestral hall.
Uncle,
as soon as I received your message,
I rushed back as fast as I could.
Just now,
I was so happy to see you
and forgot myself a little.
Please forgive me.
Are you very happy?
In your letter, you said
that old man Feng Pingcheng
is terminally ill.
Of course I'm happy!
Heaven is smiling
on us.
No.
It's Brother Jingheng
blessing you from above.
He's helping you from above!
Stupid pig!
Stupid!
-Stupid!
-Uncle.
Stupid!
Uncle, sorry.
Forgive me.
Stupid!
Uncle,
at least tell me
what I did wrong.
Listen,
Feng Pingcheng has to die,
but he must die by my hand!
I can't wait to tear him to pieces!
I will not allow him
to die of illness!
I won't allow it!
All these years
of grieving my son's death—
I have sworn
to make him pay a hundredfold,
a thousandfold!
I want him
to watch Feng Suige
die miserably before his eyes.
I want him to kneel at my feet
begging me to spare Feng Suige's life!
All these years,
I've been imagining the day
when Feng Pingcheng, old and grey,
buries his young son.
I want...
I want to see him living
in hell with my own eyes.
How could I let him die from illness?
I summoned you back
because I have a task for you.
I await your command, Uncle.
He's been unconscious
for five days.
I can't let him die just like this.
You must find a way at any cost
to wake him up.
Even if it means poison,
you must wake him up!
I want him
to be fully conscious
when he sees
Feng Suige
suffer and die!
Understood.
[Memorial Tablet of My Late Aunt Wang]
[Ancestral Virtue and Familial Merit]
Father.
Why are you back?
Your birthday is in two days.
Of course I had to come back
to celebrate it with you.
I came back secretly
just to surprise you.
You're busy
with military affairs out there,
serving the country.
That already makes me very proud.
You didn't need to go through
all this trouble to come back.
I'm old now
and don't care about birthdays anymore.
You're not old at all.
You're still strong and vigorous.
Your best days are
yet to come.
By the way,
I've prepared a special gift
for your birthday
this time.
You coming home
already makes me happy.
No need to fuss
over gifts.
A gift is necessary.
It's a surprise.
I won't tell you yet.
I'll go check
how the preparations are going.
Prime Minister,
Elder Marquis Murong is here.
So secretive.
If there's something,
you can just send me a message.
Why force an old cripple like me
to come here in person?
If it weren't something huge,
I wouldn't have
disturbed you.
His Majesty is terminally ill.
Are you aware of this?
What did you say?
So even you didn't know.
His Majesty kept everyone in the dark.
I wonder
who he actually trusts.
Terminally ill?
His Majesty has been
unconscious for so long
because he's...
I just found out today,
so I invited you over immediately
to discuss it.
You called me here tonight
surely not just
to tell me about
His Majesty's condition, right?
Back then, we fought for this kingdom
with all our old friends.
We weathered the storms
and rode across battlefields.
Now, among those still alive,
aside from His Majesty,
there are only the two of us left.
Some things
can't be left unspoken forever.
I've heard
that while His Majesty lay ill,
you filled all the key posts
with people
from the Zhuang family.
You know the proposed candidate
for Minister of War—
Liu Qin, Vice Minister of War.
He's not a Zhuang.
But in the end,
he's still your man.
Are you saying
you haven't placed
your own people in the court?
Li Liang at the Court of Judicial Review,
Liu Jin at the Censorate—
aren't they your longtime associates?
And your nephew,
Murong Jie,
holds a key post in the Jinwu Guards.
You've placed quite a few people yourself.
Zhuang Shen,
you called me here today
for the matter
of naming an heir, right?
Yes.
I just want to hear your opinion.
To hear my opinion?
My opinion doesn't matter at all!
Stop beating around the bush.
Even if
His Majesty and the First Prince
fall out
completely,
I'll still advise this:
the heir should be
the eldest legitimate son!
So,
your preferred heir is
the First Prince?
He fought on battlefields for years,
winning one battle after another.
The people of Susha
are all well aware of this.
Who can inherit the throne
depends not on military achievements
but on virtue.
Enough!
You just want your grandson
Feng Chengyang on the throne.
Listen,
unless you can control the whole court,
as long as
I still draw breath,
I'll never agree!
[Zhuang Residence]
Give me a hand.
This is the medicine
your father needs to take tonight.
I suggest
you have an imperial physician examine it
so no one will gossip
and accuse me of harming your emperor.
You persuaded Lord Ling
to come back during the day.
Although he's agreed
to continue treating His Majesty,
he's still angry.
Who do you mean?
Me?
I'm still angry?
You think I'd stoop to their level?
Ma Qiming,
I think you're the one who's angry.
You resent me
for revealing Feng Pingcheng's illness.
I know what you're thinking!
I wouldn't dare.
I remember
everything you've done
for His Majesty
all these years.
I'm grateful to you
for saving His Majesty's life.
Eunuch Ma.
Yes.
From now on, if anyone in the palace
dares to speak ill
of Lord Ling again,
just give them 30 strokes of the cane.
If any trouble is caused because of it,
I'll take responsibility.
Yes.
I understand.
Lord Ling.
How is he doing now?
In a day or two at least,
or ten days at most,
he will wake up.
As for how well he'll recover,
that depends on his fate.
Great!
Isn't this my brother,
the Prince of Zhennan?
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Yesterday,
you nearly died by my blade,
and today you still dare
to attend the banquet.
You truly don't fear death.
Your Majesty, please don't go too far.
Even if the Prince of Zhennan
has displeased you,
he's here at your invitation.
Humiliating him like this
is a step too far!
Brother,
your wife is defending you so fiercely.
Are you moved?
You may rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Come.
Brother,
let me introduce you to everyone.
Wang Encheng, Vice Minister of Revenue.
Lu Wang, Minister of Rites.
Shan Huaiqing,
Minister of Imperial Stables.
They're all pillars of the court.
Brother,
you should get to know them well.
Be seated.
You may not know this yet.
My brother now
holds a new role in addition to being
the Prince of Zhennan.
He's also the live-in son-in-law of Susha.
For lasting peace between our two nations,
Your Majesty agreed to
the Prince of Zhennan staying in Susha.
But the prince has returned on his own.
Doesn't this make Your Majesty
appear to go back on your word?
Leaving Susha
was entirely my decision.
It had nothing to do with His Highness.
If Your Majesty wishes
to punish someone, punish me.
The princess eloped with the prince.
Such a bold act
is truly admirable.
We are deeply impressed.
Enough.
We'll just enjoy ourselves tonight.
Stop talking about that.
I'm in such a great mood today.
Brother,
you must
have a good drink with me tonight.
Go.
Serve His Highness properly.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Please.
You can't even serve wine properly.
Why should I keep you around?
Guards!
Your Majesty, spare me!
Drag her out and beat her to death.
Your Majesty!
See?
Someone died because of you again.
Go.
Pour wine for His Highness.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
Please let me
serve His Highness.
Lady Zhuang Jingyuan,
virtuous, gentle,
and graceful,
has pleased me greatly.
She is hereby promoted
to fourth-rank Consort Yuan.
End of the decree.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Congratulations, Consort Yuan.
Come to me.
Your Majesty.
Congratulations, Your Majesty.
Her Majesty has given birth to a princess.
Wonderful.
Congratulations, Your Majesty.
Now, Your Majesty
has both a son and a daughter.
Yeah, indeed.
Your Majesty.
One day,
I shall also bear
a prince for you, if you wish.
Of course.
Let's go see the Empress.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Her Majesty hasn't eaten her dinner.
She's been sitting there
for several hours
without saying a word.
What are you doing here?
It's so late.
Why are you still up?
Mother,
please take care of yourself.
Don't grieve too much.
[Murong Residence]
Elder Marquis, we're home.
Elder Marquis?
Elder Marquis.
Elder Marquis is missing!
What should we do now?
What happened?
How did my father go missing
after one trip out?
I…
I truly know nothing.
It took us over an hour to get back
from Prime Minister Zhuang's mansion.
I checked the carriage when we arrived,
and the Elder Marquis was
already gone.
Think carefully.
Did anything unusual happen on the way?
Aside from a cow blocking the road…
I got down and led it away.
Nothing else happened.
After moving the cow,
did you check whether my father
was still in the carriage?
No.
I didn't hear a sound,
so I thought
he had fallen asleep.
Where did you see the cow?
Past Yudai Bridge,
at the third intersection.
Right,
there's a crooked tree by the road.
Search every house
in that area.
Even if we have to turn the Yujing City
upside down,
we must find him!
Yes.
Fu Yixiao,
I know it was you.
When I catch you,
I'll skin you alive
and cut you into pieces!
Who are you?
How dare you
abduct me
right under the Emperor's nose?
Officail Website : kissasian.be
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
No wonder you're
a battle-hardened marquis.
Even in danger,
you stay calm
and unafraid.
So you know who I am.
It seems you're my enemy,
but I don't recognize you.
I spent decades guarding the borders,
fighting countless wars.
I've made more enemies than I can count.
Which side are you on?
What grudge do you have against me?
Go on, say it.
I'm all ears.
Years stationed in the freezing north
left your legs in bad shape.
And even so,
His Majesty still wouldn't
let you come home
to enjoy your retirement.
Is that why the Murong family
hates His Majesty?
That's all?
I don't even know
what you're talking about.
My loyalty to His Majesty
is as clear as day.
I have never hated His Majesty.
Then why is your son, Murong Yao,
plotting mutiny?
It seems you don't believe me.
I joined the army as a boy
and spent decades on the battlefield.
You have no idea
how many people
have tried to frame me for treason
before His Majesty.
If you're going to slander me,
at least come up with something new.
Yao is plotting mutiny?
Sure, he's always been a handful,
but I've never thought of him
as ambitious.
I actually wish he were different
so he wouldn't
spend every day in debauchery
and waste his life.
You think I haven't tried to pull strings
for him
in the army and the court?
He just refused.
He won't even take an official post,
but you're saying he's plotting mutiny?
This is the biggest joke
I've heard all year!
Murong Yao conspired with Jinxiu
to assassinate the First Prince.
Do you know what?
Now I know who you are.
You're that female general from Jinxiu—
one of Suige's people.
A Jinxiu general
is accusing Yao
of colluding with Jinxiu?
A dissolute playboy
from a noble family
who goes around
with four pretty assassins—
who does he want to kill?
Do you really know
your own son?
Do you know
who he associates with
and who he keeps around him?
You were always away at the border.
Do you really know
what he's been doing
here in Yujing?
You call yourself
the most loyal official in the court,
but are you sure your son is
as loyal as you?
If he really was
some playboy
without ambitions like you said,
why did he take the job
with the Imperial Guards?
That was arranged by His Majesty.
You just said yourself
that all his life,
he's never followed orders.
He…
My son…
I just feel sorry for you.
Back then, you fought
alongside His Majesty
and ended up with all these injuries.
His Majesty knows this full well,
so why did he still send you to that cold,
barren place in the northwest?
Murong Yao and Feng Suige
are the closest of friends.
But he threatened me,
saying to my face
that if I ever told Feng Suige
his secret,
he'd find a way
to kill Feng Pingcheng,
who's lying in bed in the palace now.
I don't care
if Feng Pingcheng lives or dies.
But I won't allow anyone
to hurt Feng Suige.
Impossible!
Yao would never say something like that.
He and Suige
grew up together like brothers!
He would never commit treason!
No matter what method Murong Yao has
to threaten Feng Pingcheng,
as long as I have control over you,
I'm confident
he won't dare make a move.
Elder Marquis,
I apologize.
Are you feeling unwell?
-Are you alright?
-Your Highness.
Why did you drink so much?
Could you please go get a towel,
Your Highness?
Wait for me here.
Did you see Wang Encheng
just now?
Yes.
You marked his name
in the Daily Chronicle.
And he looks the part too.
I've long heard about
Xia Jingyan's peculiarities.
I just never thought
that what the Daily Chronicle mentioned
about his affairs with officials' wives
was actually true.
That Wang Encheng—
see if you can find a way
to get close to him.
Yes.
By the way,
when we went in just now,
was anyone standing guard?
Just two eunuchs stayed in there.
Looks like Xia Jingyan
truly believes you've submitted.
You don't understand him.
Removing the guards
was just his way to test me.