( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(Lee Na Young)
(Jung Eun Chae)
(Lee Chung Ah)
(Honour)
(Supported by the Culture Ministry
and Korea's Creative Content Agency)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and animals were
filmed under production guidelines.)
- To LnJ!
Yoo Jeong.
Oh, my gosh, what happened?
What happened? What's wrong?
Help her up. We need to get out of here.
I
Killed someone.
- What's going on?
- She said she killed someone.
- She did what?
- Oh, gosh.
Jun Hyeok.
Jun Hyeok. Lee Jun Hyeok.
Someone.
I think someone's hurt.
I heard a scream too.
It's a house in front of the park
in Jungam-dong, Seongin-go.
Okay, we have your report.
May I have your name, please?
(Episode 2)
Where are you? We're at Hankuk
Hospital. You need to get here...
Shin Jae.
Come pick me up. Hurry.
- You go on ahead.
- Is that Hyun Jin? What's wrong?
I don't know. I'll call you.
Are you hurt?
Okay, then.
Shin Jae.
Jun Hyeok is...
He's dead.
What?
Jun Hyeok...
He's dead.
(Operating Room)
Attorney Yoon. What
happened? How's Yoo Jeong?
Yoo Jeong.
- How is she? Is she okay?
- Fortunately, the wound isn't deep.
For now, we're moving
her to a regular room,
and the doctor will explain
it all when they come out.
Guardian, this way, please.
You need to handle the admission paperwork.
Yoo Jeong. What do you
mean you killed someone?
Who did you kill?
Reporter Lee Jun Hyeok.
What? What are you talking about?
We're moving her to her room now.
Ms. Jo Yoo Jeong's guardian?
We've stitched up the abdominal wound.
There was some bleeding,
but she's stable now.
However,
there's trauma to her genital area,
and she has severe
internal bleeding in her pelvis.
Sexual assault. Is that
what you're suggesting?
Leave the clothes. I'll get rid of them.
What in the world just happened?
Shouldn't we go to the police?
Then why did you take Reporter Lee's phone?
Did you sleep with him that
night? With Reporter Lee?
My conversations with him are on it.
If the police get ahold of
this, Seon Kyu will find out.
I wasn't in my right mind. Not
today, and not that day either.
Shin Jae.
I can't do this.
- I should just tell the police...
- Hwang Hyun Jin.
Get a grip.
Our DNA...
The police still have it.
Attempting to destroy
evidence, fleeing the scene...
You're the prime suspect right now.
If you're investigated, do you
think your past won't come out?
(Ra Young)
- Hello?
- Are you with Hyun Jin?
Yes, she's right here.
Reporter Lee has been murdered.
It's not in the news yet.
I know.
- You know?
- I need you both at the hospital
right now.
(Hankuk University Hospital)
That you murdered the
victim, Lee Jun Hyeok.
Do you admit it?
Where did you murder the victim?
At his house.
Reporter Lee's house.
Why did you go to the victim's house?
I was at my lawyer's house,
and he called and asked me to come over.
What was the murder weapon?
A knife from the kitchen.
And where did you stab him?
In the stomach.
Is that true?
Why did you attack the victim?
Let me ask you again. Why
did you murder the victim?
Reporter Lee... He...
He raped me.
Can you describe the circumstances
of the assault in more detail?
That's enough for today.
You have a sufficient confession.
She'll give any further
statements at the next session.
(Forensics)
(Detective)
You're here. Let's head in.
For goodness' sake.
My gosh.
This isn't my fault, is it? It's yours.
You're the one who
taught me this bad habit.
Are you going to make the forensics
guys do all that extra work again?
How many times do they
have to filter out your DNA?
Hey, we got a full confession.
Why check for butts? Let's go.
Gosh.
What is it?
The Korean Journalism Award?
See? You can't trust people
who act all high and mighty.
They're the ones who are
always rotten to the core.
A reporter, of all people, preying on a kid.
It is pretty shocking, though.
Why? You know him?
Not me. Hyun Jin does.
Your wife does?
- Sir!
- Yes.
I got it.
What is it?
Detective!
Yes?
- What is it?
- This was wedged in the mattress.
- Is this the victim's?
- We'll have to run it and see.
What do you mean, "The Kang
Eun Seok Seductress Murder Case"?
You can't just post
such a malicious article!
Yes, the press release will go out shortly.
Why haven't you taken
down the unblurred photo yet?
What do you mean, a server issue?
This is Yoon Ra Young. Take it
down in three minutes, or we file a suit.
Penalties are harsher for a
minor. You have three minutes.
- You're here.
- What's all this?
Case law on self-defense.
We have to try and make it stick.
Attorney Yoon, here's the
schedule for the current affairs show.
They'll replace another
panelist if you agree to come on.
The topic is confirmed, right?
Expanding the scope of self-defense.
- Yes.
- Great. Book it.
- Ra Young.
- Also,
we must prove diminished capacity,
so get Yoo Jeong's psych med history.
Hold on, nothing has been decided yet.
- What hasn't?
- I said,
we still haven't decided
whether we're taking this case.
What is there to decide?
Of course this is our case.
We need to talk.
I don't believe Yoo Jeong's story.
- What part of it?
- The murder and the sexual assault.
Yoo Jeong committed murder?
And in such a brutal way?
And it just doesn't make sense
that Jun Hyeok would hurt a source.
- Look, Jun Hyeok is...
- Not the type of person to do that?
That's the one thing
we've always hated hearing.
"He'd never do something like
that." "He wouldn't hurt a fly."
And where are all those people now?
We're the ones who put them away.
Jun Hyeok was murdered
right after he offered me the files.
Am I really the only one
who finds this all strange?
Yoo Jeong confessed herself.
Why would she lie about that?
If it's about defending the
person who killed Jun Hyeok...
Hey, who said that's what this is about?
In any case, what's clear is that
Jo Yoo Jeong has already lied.
And she still hasn't told us the truth.
As for us taking Jo Yoo Jeong's case...
One vote for, one vote against.
It's not that I'm against it.
I'm just saying we should hold
off until we can confirm the facts.
I also vote to hold off.
The forensics report comes
out soon. We'll find out then.
Whether she's telling the truth this time.
So we're just supposed
to do nothing until then?
Who said anything about
sitting on our hands?
Go meet with Jo Yoo Jeong.
Check her statement thoroughly.
I don't care if it's hard on her.
It's better than getting
blindsided in the courtroom again.
All right, next. Give me
Reporter Lee's phone.
You brought the evidence
here? Are you crazy?
- I wasn't thinking straight.
- Hwang Hyun Jin!
I slept with Jun Hyeok!
All of my conversations
with him are on that phone!
What's done is done. Just
figure out how to stay afloat.
You took out the SIM right
away. What's the password?
I don't know. I can't unlock it.
We have to unlock it
somehow. It might be on here.
The files he was going to hand over to you.
The data on that prostitution scandal.
- Let me take it to Dong Je.
- Okay.
Hwang Hyun Jin, seriously.
Ms. Kang.
About the budget proposal that came in...
And something about the numbers seems off.
(Mom)
The person you called is unavailable.
Leave a message after the tone.
Is this finalized? This
budget won't last us all year.
We have three consultations
booked today alone.
Should I cancel them?
That won't be necessary.
Proceed as planned.
Yes, ma'am.
Mr. Kwon. Do you know where my mom is?
What's done is done, and I
guess we're both in this mess.
So get a grip, at least from now on.
I know you're upset about Reporter Lee,
but you're being way too emotional.
And you're not seeing too
much of yourself in Yoo Jeong?
Ra Young. That's not what I meant
I wish it were only with Yoo Jeong.
When I look at my other clients,
I always see myself in them.
Get it together, Hyun Jin!
You lose the trial. A
murderer crashes the venue.
I'm surprised you still have
the nerve to say anything.
Still, are you cutting our
budget by 50 percent?
You're basically telling
us to shut down LnJ.
Then you should have won, shouldn't you?
- Mom!
- That last outfit and the shoes.
What are you doing?
Aren't you going to change?
By the time I turned 42,
I thought I'd at least be
able to wear what I want.
It won't matter if you're 50 or
60. You'll still be my daughter.
My daughter.
The person who leads Haeil
has to have a certain class.
You remember CEO Baek Tae
Ju from the ceremony, don't you?
Their company is going to bid
on the gov't smart city project.
And Haeil will be
handling the legal advising.
I'm putting together a
task force. You're in charge.
I'm not going back to Haeil.
Then the budget cut stands.
The career you wanted for me,
the marriage you wanted for me.
What more do I have to do
for you to finally let me go?
Once you take over for
me, and only after that,
you can do what you want
with LnJ. It'll be up to you.
Why do you have to be
the one doing that work?
You have Hyun Jin and Ra Young, don't you?
Because this is all I know.
How not to end up like you.
Is that so?
But in the end, you'll
turn out just like me.
Having everything I have,
doing everything I've done.
Because that is your
destiny as my daughter.
I hear you're thinking of taking on
that murder case from yesterday.
If you don't lead the task
force, you'll have to drop it.
Because your new budget
won't even come close.
Mark my words.
I have never failed to get what I want.
I'm late for my appointment.
I don't have time to give her a ride.
Yes, ma'am.
Are you free today?
I'll give you the files.
I've changed my mind.
Reporter Lee
raped me.
Ten-minute break.
Hyun Jin.
- What are you doing?
- Hey.
Honey, you know those earrings you love?
What happened to them?
My earrings?
Why do you ask?
No reason.
I just feel like I haven't seen them lately.
But what are you doing home at this hour?
I just came to grab some clothes.
I won't be home for a few days.
You caught a case? For how many days?
Is five enough?
- Hyun Jin.
- Yes?
Reporter Lee Jun Hyeok.
He was murdered. Last night.
Right.
Did you hear?
That's why I came home early.
You know
about Jun Hyeok and me.
I just came from the crime
scene. I was pretty shaken up too.
What do you mean?
I'm telling you I just came
from Lee Jun Hyeok's house.
Wait, so
are you saying you're on Jun Hyeok's case?
Let's talk about the details later.
I'll get my things. You should rest.
No, it's okay. I'll do it.
Honey, can you get me
something for my headache?
- My head is killing me.
- Okay, I got it.
How are you feeling?
I can't really tell. I've
been heavily medicated.
I heard you haven't been eating, either.
What's going to happen to me now?
The maximum for minors is ten years,
and that's for involuntary manslaughter.
If the charge is murder,
the maximum is 15 years.
If we want to fight this, I have to know
everything that happened to you that day.
Every single detail, from A to Z.
What difference would that make?
Can you turn back time?
To the way things were?
I don't feel like talking today.
You're right. You can't turn back time.
But we can make time move forward again.
Eat something.
You have to eat to live,
and as long as you're alive,
this isn't the end.
("Deontology")
(Do Jun)
- Hey, Do Jun.
- The forensics report is in.
Jo Yoo Jeong's prints on the
blade, and the blood on her clothes
was confirmed to be
Reporter Lee Jun Hyeok's.
So
That means Jo Yoo
Jeong was telling the truth?
- Namaste. Good work, everyone.
- Thank you.
It's been a while.
I was wondering where you've been.
I've been enjoying your show.
The camera loves you too.
So, when are you going
to take my divorce case?
- Excuse me.
- It's Hong Yeon Hui.
I believe I already told you,
divorce law isn't my specialty.
I could find you another
attorney if you'd like.
And I told you.
- I only want you, Attorney Yoon.
- Then I guess we're done here.
Let me know if you
change your mind. Anytime.
(Hong Yeon Hui, Head of the Forensics Lab)
(Dong Je)
I got into the phone, but...
What about his notes for
the story? Find anything?
No. Not on the cloud or the phone, but.
I think you'd better
come take a look at this.
The files?
Nothing on his phone.
Given the forensics report,
it's pretty clear what happened.
Reporter Lee raped Jo Yoo
Jeong, and was killed in the process.
I get it.
From now on, I'll keep
my feelings out of this...
Things have changed.
We're handling Jo Yoo
Jeong's case. Ra Young and I.
Hey, Kang Shin Jae.
I thought Seon Kyu is handling this.
This is yours, isn't it?
We found it at Reporter Lee's
house. How were you not caught?
I knew I'd lost it,
so I bought a replacement.
I just didn't know where.
You got lucky.
Anyway, now you get it, right?
Why you have to be off this case.
This is too risky.
If Seon Kyu finds out you
were at Reporter Lee's house...
Okay. I get it.
So what? Should I just take a vacation?
Are you serious? You think
the only rapist in Korea
was Reporter Lee?
I'm sorry.
For the way I spoke to you.
You'll forgive me, right?
You big dummy. How
could I ever be mad at you?
That jerk, Lee Jun Hyeok...
We're not in our prime anymore, you know.
Come on.
- Why does this taste so weird?
- It's decaf.
More than two cups of caffeine a day is...
Whatever.
Don't worry about Hyun Jin.
In a way, this is for the best. For her too.
How's Jo Yoo Jeong?
She's somewhere between
despair and depression.
She's going to be a
real handful for a while.
What about you? Are you okay?
- About what?
- I saw the budget.
What did she say this time?
She wants you to remarry?
She can't force me into
that so easily anymore.
I warned her for my next
divorce, I'll be at fault,
and drain the entire family fortune.
The one and only daughter of
Seong Tae Im, the CEO of Haeil...
How on earth are you
going to lose a divorce case?
I told her I'd have a child out of wedlock.
- With green eyes. I like green.
- That's awesome.
She told me to come back to Haeil.
That's what my mom said.
That she's never one time
failed to get what she wants.
That's true. You know what she's like.
But as for who her daughter
is the spitting image of,
I guess she still hasn't figured that out.
Yes, that's true too.
The budget proposal won't pass.
And handling Jo Yoo Jeong's case
shouldn't be a problem either.
It's not like I was worried.
Worry about me. Just a little. Come on.
(Phone: Attorney Hwang Hyun Jin)
(Phone)
(Laptop)
(Attorney Hwang Hyun Jin)
Hey, Gi Jeong.
I wanted to ask you something.
By any chance, do you have...
Jun Hyeok's laptop?
Stolen?
I need to see you. I'll head
to the office now, okay?
- Where are you going?
- I'm just heading straight home.
(Jo Yoo Min)
Yes, Yoo Min.
Okay. I'll be right there.
Don't say a word until I get there.
How did you say you were stabbed again?
During the rape,
I ran to the kitchen and grabbed a knife.
Stay back! If you come
any closer, I'll kill you!
But Reporter Lee grabbed
me and took the knife away,
As I was fighting back,
I got stabbed.
So, is that when you got
the bruise on your arm too?
- Yes.
- And then?
I picked up the knife
that had fallen beside me,
and I was so scared,
and so angry,
that the next thing I knew,
there was blood everywhere.
Please strike that last
statement from the record.
- The "so scared and angry" part.
- Attorney Yoon.
Didn't I tell you that an emotional
statement could be used against you?
Ra Young.
What is going on? Why did
you start the interrogation
without her counsel present?
I think there was a miscommunication.
Don't you know excluding her
lawyer will cause legal problems?
"Exclude"? Give me a break.
She's the one who insisted
on being questioned alone.
- Hey!
- Sir.
Since when must we tell an attorney
the schedule for an interrogation,
- and get her permission?
- Come on.
- Step out. I'll handle it.
- Wait.
We're restarting the
interrogation. Yoo Jeong is a minor,
and her guardian strongly
insists that I be present.
I don't need a lawyer.
What is wrong with you?
You're the attacker, not the victim.
You took a life. Do you
want to go to prison for life?
Is that what you want?
Yes. I don't need one. I
said I'll just go to prison.
I killed him. I'm the one who killed him!
So what more do you want from me?
I'll just... I'll just go to prison, okay?
Please, just leave me alone!
- Yoo Jeong. Jo Yoo Jeong, honey.
- I...
Ma'am, please!
What do you mean the laptop's gone? When?
I don't know. It's not
at Jun Hyeok's place,
and it's not at the office either.
Did you tell the police?
I did, but they're just
treating it like a simple theft.
Your firm is defending the
suspect in this case, right?
Do you believe it? That
Jun Hyeok raped that girl?
I pulled the building's CCTV
footage because of the laptop,
and I found something really strange.
This was on the footage.
What is all this?
It was filmed the day
before Jun Hyeok died.
Something just doesn't feel
right. The laptop, this video,
and the girl's statement.
About the story Jun Hyeok worked on...
Did you hear anything, Gi Jeong?
You know how private Jun
Hyeok was about his work.
Thanks, Gi Jeong. I'll be in touch.
The person you called is unavailable.
Leave a message after the tone.
(Lee Seon Hwa)
(Mom)
I'm broke.
Hello.
- Painkillers. The strong ones.
- Just a moment.
Take one pill after a meal.
If it's really bad, take two.
- How long does it last?
- About four hours?
You can't take that many at once...
The cops are cracking down hard these days.
I'll be toast if they find out I
drove you all the way here.
Can we just drive in silence now?
She ruined the mood with clients,
so her madam kicked her out.
She's not getting much work. She
was passed around some agencies.
Sunday Motel, Room 302.
Lee Seon Hwa.
The lawyer lady?
Are you sick?
Should we go to a hospital?
Just leave me alone. If you
want to help, stay out of it.
Is this withdrawal?
What are you doing here anyway?
Look at this.
What do you think you're doing?
The sex trafficking scandal
Jun Hyeok was chasing...
What exactly was it?
You're still on about that?
You know what it is, don't you?
You know, so please tell me.
Was it an organization?
Who's involved in it?
I told you to ask Reporter Lee yourself.
Jun Hyeok is dead.
What did you say?
A teenage girl who
was one of his sources...
He raped her.
She was Kang Eun Seok's
sexual assault case victim.
And she's the one who killed him.
The day he died, Jun Hyeok promised
he'd give me his research materials.
And that's when he was murdered.
The day before that, he was
even attacked by some thugs.
Do you really think all of
this is just a coincidence?
Just go.
- Lee Seon Hwa.
- I've nothing more to say. Just go.
What on earth are you pulling?
She's just someone I know.
Please, go. Now.
You haven't made a dime in days.
Think you own this place, you wench?
He was stabbed countless times.
He died with a knife lodged in his stomach.
The Jun Hyeok you knew.
Did he deserve to die like that?
Did he?
(Sunday Motel)
Lawyer or not, I don't give a
darn. Come back, and she dies first.
(Motel)
(Lee Seon Hwa)
Hello?
Look into Connect.
Connect?
Connect In. It's an app for prostitution.
Ordinary people can't even get on it.
They wouldn't even let someone like me in.
That's all I know.
Thank you.
A few months ago, Reporter
Lee asked me that too.
I told Reporter Lee the same
thing, but I didn't take any money.
I didn't take anything at all.
There can be at least one
person like that in this world, right?
Even someone like me
can help a good person for once, right?
That's the kind of person Reporter Lee was.
Reporter Lee, a rapist?
That's complete nonsense.
Connect.
(Session in progress)
Where did my baby go?
Fooled you.
(Session in progress)
(Session time has ended.)
Are you sure I'm not going to die?
You're not dead, are you?
I don't mean today.
That's up to you.
(Complete, Sunday, August 31, 2025, 9:00pm)
(134 Hanyun-ro, Namyangju-si,
Gyeonggi Province)
(Connect In)
Mr. Kwon.
How did you find me without calling first?
Have I ever lost at hide-and-seek with you?
I knew it. You don't love your
books more than me, do you?
- Of course not. Books don't drink.
- I like the sound of that.
I'm ordering something expensive.
Be my guest.
Thank you.
So, what made you "it" this time?
Establishing a public foundation.
I need your help.
You're asking me to stab
your mother in the back?
- It's not as bad as all that.
- It's worse than that.
You'd put LnJ under the
foundation to break away from Haeil.
That goes against your mother's
goal of making you her successor.
Who would dare rain on that parade?
You would.
Haeil is the only major law firm
in the country that's family-owned.
When my mom steps down,
I'm going to change that system.
Haeil will be incorporated,
and the person to lead it then
has to be you.
Why me?
Because Haeil needs you more than anyone,
and you want Haeil more than anything.
And I
trust you more than I trust myself.
Let go of my mother's side,
and push my swing for
me. Just like you used to.
Your mother always used to say
she could never understand you.
What do you really want, Shin
Jae, if you're giving up Haeil?
Obviously
what I'm already doing.
Yoo Jeong could be like this for a while.
The trauma from the sexual assault,
the guilt of committing murder...
It'll be hard for her to
recover from this despair.
Still,
I'm not giving up on Yoo Jeong.
From now on,
I will be present for all questioning.
Understood.
To think we'd meet
again on a case like this.
Hyun Jin will be taken off this case.
It's for the best, given the circumstances.
I doubt Hyun Jin would want to anyway.
Defending the person who
murdered her ex-boyfriend.
It's more that
she doesn't want to make things
hard for her detective husband.
I guess I can be petty like that.
Hey, what are you doing?
- We're working late again. Come on.
- I'm sorry
about earlier.
What? Yes. Whatever.
Come on.
I should get going for today.
Are you heading back to the station?
After we finish the search.
We still haven't found his phone.
Jo Yoo Jeong confessed
she took it and threw it away,
but it just isn't turning up.
She said she threw it away?
That's what Yoo Jeong told you?
Yes.
We should get dinner
with Hyun Jin sometime.
Yes, Chief. Okay.
You awake?
Where's my sister?
I sent your sister home
to get you some clothes.
You should go home too.
And don't come back.
If I have to go to prison, I'll
go. I'll rot there for life if I must.
I'll handle this on my own now.
What did you do with Reporter
Lee Jun Hyeok's cell phone?
- I threw it out.
- Why would you do that?
- So they'd never know I killed him.
- When?
Right after I left.
I already told the police all this.
This is getting annoying.
I told you to stay out of it!
When you lied and said you
met Kang Eun Seok at a club.
You tore up your hands
just like you're doing now.
Then and now.
Why are you lying?
The person who killed Reporter Lee
wasn't you, was it?
You're the one who told me to live.
You told me I should keep living!
So please, just go.
I'm begging you, go!
Detective!
From this point on, I
refuse to see my lawyer.
We're not finished here.
- Don't ever let her in here again.
- Jo Yoo Jeong!
You'll have to leave now.
Don't think this is over.
I will find out why you're doing this.
You can count on it.
(Connect In app)
(No results for "Connect In app")
(Ra Young)
- Yes?
- You were right.
It's not Yoo Jeong.
I know. And I know who killed Jun Hyeok.
Who is it?
Connect.
It's a secret prostitution
app called Connect In.
Jun Hyeok was tracking the app,
and they used Yoo Jeong
to kill him. To shut him up.
- Connect?
- I'll send you a picture. Zoom in.
The statue of Nike.
Stay back. Come any
closer and I'll kill you!
Are you going to kill me too?
That's up to you.
I see it. Have you told Shin Jae?
(Honour)
Connect is a prostitution app, right?
It wasn't me.
We underestimated them.
Don't you think it's suspicious
that everything is so clear-cut?
I know someone who works for Connect.
They took a DNA sample?
Can you put a rush on the
evidence I submitted yesterday?
- This isn't a favor, it's a deal.
- Don't you have a conscience?
This is the ID of the first
person who called 911.
- It's them again.
- Nothing is going to happen to you.
I won't let that happen.