YUMI'S CELLS 3
EPISODE 7
LOW POWER MODE HUMAN
AHN DAE-YONG, KIM JU-HO
ANDERSON
- Go back, go back! Go back!
- Hurry, hurry! Hurry!
It seems there are two types of people.
The type that gets energized
when they're with people
and the type whose energy drains
in a crowded place...
Like me.
See? I told you they could do it.
Hey, did you see that?
Did you see the speed?
Yes, I saw it.
- Wasn't that amazing?
- It was amazing.
Get a hit!
Get up, Shin PD. Do it with us.
Shout!
Get a hit!
- Get a hit!
- Go, go!
- A home run is fine too!
- How?
- Hit a satisfying one for us
- Get a hit
- A hit!
Get a hit!
The producer called, so...
Hit a satisfying one for us
Right now!
Yes, yes.
Then I'll check again and send it to you.
Okay.
If I weren't the editor for a writer
who writes baseball novels
I would have no reason to come here.
To reduce energy loss
I live in Low Power Mode
when I'm outside my house.
That's why during the day
only Rational Cell works.
Look at that.
When did all those flowers bloom?
- They really did.
- Gosh, the weather is so nice.
It makes me want to go out and have fun.
I know.
Should we ditch work and run off?
- Really?
No, of course not.
What was that?
Rational Cell isn't sentimental,
so it gets work done quickly.
On top of that...
- Would you like another drink?
- No, I'm fine.
- I was given these chocolates.
- Well.
I'll be leaving now.
- Okay.
- It's good at refusing offers.
And it reduces energy consumption
by drawing boundaries.
Our calm and rational Soon-rok.
I like you.
People think of that as
being calm and rational.
- Three-pitch strikeout!
- Chief Editor Ahn.
- Mr. Kim.
- Here you go.
- Three-pitch strikeout!
Three-pitch strikeout! Strikeout!
They should keep going like this.
- Three-pitch strikeout!
- However
all the cells are inactive
outside the house.
- Here, help yourself.
- Hey, thanks.
- This crab looks great, right?
- My mouth is watering.
Eat a lot.
Although I'm not the one paying.
No, eat a lot.
Eating is the only thing that lasts.
What else is there to life?
- I can't even taste what I'm eating.
- Oh, right.
You know the movie
Attack on Bats is out, right?
- Who wants to go? Hands up!
- Me! Me!
- Let's go!
- I've been wanting to see that.
We have to go! We have to go. Yeah.
I'm sorry, but I...
Shin PD. You're coming, right?
- Well...
- If Shin PD won't go, I'm not going.
- I'm not going.
- Come on, Shin PD.
- What's with you guys?
- I'm not going.
- Let's go together!
- Shin PD!
- Come on, the producer has to go!
- Shin PD! Shin PD!
- Shin PD!
You're no longer needed here.
Does Sung-hee always work on herself?
She thinks she's capable of solving
everything on her own, does she?
What a conceited egotist.
She's a typical Korean.
A workaholic...
Ouch! The popcorn's spilling.
Goodness!
Please leave a message after the tone.
Using your phone is so rude.
I can't even focus on the movie.
Hey, I wonder if it's too late.
Oh, here he comes, here he comes.
This movie was longer than I thought.
- I'll be going now.
- Bye!
- Get home safe, Shin PD!
- Don't tell them you were with us.
Hello.
On top of that, I'm in a rush.
Door closing.
Hello.
- Hello.
- In a team that's still unfamiliar...
I'm sorry. I'm a little late.
And an animal shows up...
Shin PD, do you have anything to say?
I'm in big trouble.
I can't focus on the script.
How can a person in love be calm?
I'm sorry, but what are you talking about?
"How can a person in love be calm?"
What does love have to do with being calm?
Maltese. Right.
Let's just talk about the Maltese.
You don't need to understand the Maltese.
But Maltese dogs aren't very smart.
Maltese dogs have low intelligence?
- I thought they were smart.
- Their intelligence isn't high.
Yes, that's it.
Way to go, Soon-rok.
Let's use the Maltese
to get through this crisis.
When I'm in a bad mood,
she stays quiet next to me
and when I'm happy, she knows it
like magic and brings me a ball.
And she barks when her owner video calls.
How smart is that?
Isn't that something all dogs do?
Unless they're a lizard?
Right. That dog and lizard
example was good.
Going down.
Good work today.
- You worked hard.
- You got this.
- Koko, bye!
- The doors are closing.
- Bye.
By the way, don't you think
Ms. Kim was a little offended?
- Why?
- Shin PD said Maltese are dumb.
She seemed a little upset.
I said the Maltese was dumb, not her.
Why would she be offended?
- Still, from a pet owner's view...
- But it's not even her dog.
Still, it's a matter of feelings.
Ah, Shin PD is so cold.
You're just too rational.
What are you talking about?
Ms. Yu-mi isn't a Maltese,
nor is she a Maltese owner
so why would she be offended?
Goodness.
I just don't get it...
A day like today is too much.
I worked all day by myself.
Yeah, I know.
But it's okay.
Because I'm home now.
Because I'm...
a complete homebody.
It's always a struggle
when you leave home.
Home is the best.
All my senses only awaken
when I'm at home.
Perfect.
My sense of taste awakens.
My sense of hearing awakens.
That's it!
Good eye.
Bases loaded!
Baseball is best when you watch it on TV.
Is he dead?
And movies are best watched
from the front row of your room.
At home, my emotion is at its peak
so I can read the writer's intentions
between the lines.
Then...
"Did he leave his phone?"
The phone rang
and Seon-ju's gaze turned toward it.
Whose call could it be?
It was that forgotten name, Eun-young.
Seon-ju realized in that moment.
How calm she was.
MISSED CALL
YU DA-EUN (INTERN)
(Go back in)
How can a person in love...
be so calm?
The Maltese wasn't the important thing.
Ms. Kim, this is Shin Soon-rok.
I'm sending you additional feedback.
A homebody's night is always too short.
The worst thing for such homebodies...
JANG SU-HYE PD
- Hello?
- Sorry, Soon-rok. Are you home?
- Nothing special going on today?
- No.
But why?
Right now?
...is a day like today.
A sudden weekend business trip.
Okay, I understand.
Jeez, what the heck?
But it's Saturday.
There's no time. Let's just go.
Hello.
SEOUL, BUSAN
My glasses.
You forgot your glasses too?
Oh, no. I'm already drained,
and it's only morning.
What am I going to do today?
I'm sorry.
Are you going with the writer
looking like this?
You didn't even wash your face.
What about your image?
This is great.
I was getting bored of going alone.
Have a seat.
- Let's definitely sit apart.
- It's all right.
My seat is over there.
You don't even know the trip schedule yet.
I'm a mess, and I don't have my glasses.
Gosh, today is the worst.
Yes, I received the materials
for the Book Talk.
But I don't have the contact details
for the person in charge.
Yes, thank you. Bye.
Wait, I'm sorry. And the car...
It's a rental car. Got it.
I'm just going to sit
next to you for a second.
What's going on?
Ms. Yu-mi is saying something.
Let's talk, Shin PD.
Are you unhappy working with me?
What? What did she say?
Ouch. What did she just say?
What does she mean
if you're unhappy working with her?
I'm not sure what she means either.
Could you tell me specifically?
I think I need to hear it.
What does she want to hear?
Specifically?
What is she talking about?
Is Ms. Yu-mi angry right now?
Why would she be angry?
She just brought me a drink a moment ago.
Why is she acting like this
all of a sudden?
Huh?
- I don't understand what you mean...
- I want to know the real reason.
The reason you're leaving our team.
Didn't the Chief Editor tell you?
- Our schedules kept clashing-
- That's an excuse.
An excuse?
Shin PD.
I've been patient for long enough, okay?
I don't usually get this worked up
but I've been so irritated lately.
What? I think something's gone very wrong.
Everyone! Wake up, all of you!
This is an emergency!
Oh no!
We're in big trouble.
Soon-rok has run out of battery.
Shin PD?
EPISODE 8
BOLT OUT OF THE BLUE
Shin PD?
He's smiling.
He's smiling right now, isn't he?
Why is he smiling? Yu-mi is being serious.
Are you kidding? I said to answer.
So why the hell are you smiling!
Yu-mi revealed her true feelings.
So why won't you say anything, you jerk!
What's this? Not a cloud in the sky,
but all of a sudden?
Why...
Shin PD, why are you smiling...
JANG SU-HYE PD
I'm sorry. It's an urgent call.
Yes, hello?
Yes, we'll arrive in an hour.
No, we should stop by the hotel first.
And...
Sorry?
This stop is Singyeongju,
Singyeongju Station.
Please exit after the train has come
to a complete stop...
Was that schedule shared
with the Chief Editor as well?
I think he thinks
it's the 12 o'clock train.
Okay, then I'll check again
and get back to you.
- Okay, bye.
- The doors are opening.
Yes, PD.
Yes, about tomorrow's event.
Yes, right.
Yes, I heard a little about it,
but what kind of video...
What?
What the...
What is with this guy, seriously?
What? What was that?
I don't know.
Why is this happening out of the blue?
Guys, I'm getting anxious.
Could it be Hysterius?
HYSTERIUS
Hysterius is in the cryo-base.
Don't you think he woke up
because he got so mad at Soon-rok?
That's it. Hysterius has woken up.
Let's go see.
He just subtly smiled,
took a call, and left.
His methods are quite...
Not a chance, buddy.
I'm going to hear everything
and confront you.
- What time should I send it by?
- The doors are closing.
Okay.
The train is now departing.
- Hello?
- Oh, I see.
- If you send the video,
- Hello?
- I'll watch it, and then decide...
Okay, thank you.
- Okay, okay, I understand.
- Excuse me!
- Bye.
- Hello?
Hey!
- What in the world...
- Ms. Kim.
Ms...
Why did you...
This is a disaster.
You even missed the train?
I'm doomed!
THE KTX FOR BUSAN HAS DEPARTED
I mean, what the...
What kind of...
What...
Did he really miss the train?
This is absurd.
Did he do that on purpose?
- Because he wanted to avoid Yu-mi?
- Hey! You son of a bitch!
Ms. Kim, I'm sorry.
I missed the train
while I was on the phone.
I'll take the next train right away.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm honestly speechless.
All right.
I'll grab your luggage and get off.
Thank you.
This guy is unbelievable, huh?
Oh, seriously.
Hey, Fishing Cell.
- Are you going home already?
- Yeah, but I'm empty-handed today.
Why?
But today was the day
Yu-mi was the most pissed off.
You didn't catch any Angerfish?
There were a lot of Angerfish.
There really were a lot today.
Wow, I bet I'll get a full catch today.
They were killed by lightning?
Yeah, in an instant.
Wait, if all the Angerfish died...
That means Yu-mi's anger disappeared.
But Yu-mi was totally pissed off.
Hysterius probably got out...
Oh, he's here.
- Hysterius is sleeping?
- Then what was it?
That's strange. Sudden lightning
is a first for Yu-mi's Village.
Is this strange weather happening
because Yu-mi is getting older?
Like, menopause symptoms?
But there's no way Yu-mi's already
going through menopause.
Why?
What is it?
What is it? Oh, come on!
The light's on.
Let's get to work, Soon-rok.
We have a load of work to do.
BUSAN STATION
Ms. Kim, I'm on the train.
I'm scheduled to arrive in 15 minutes.
SHIN SOON-ROK PD
I'll be waiting at Platform 9.
How many minutes are left?
Five minutes left.
- That's a relief.
- Okay.
That jerk will be here in five minutes.
Let's not get swept up by that jerk again.
If he smirks, fakes a call,
and pulls his usual stunt
we're not letting him get away with it.
We have to crush him.
We have to destroy him.
- How many minutes left?
- One minute left.
He's almost here.
The train is now arriving.
- He's finally coming!
- Let's crush him.
Let's destroy him!
Where is that jerk?
Huh? I don't see him.
Did he ditch us again?
If he ditched us again, I swear...
- There he is!
- That jerk showed up!
That son of a bitch!
- What's that?
Ms. Kim, I'm sorry.
I made such a ridiculous mistake...
I got off for a moment
and was about to get back on...
I'm sorry.
Right, well...
They said they'd send a car,
but it hasn't arrived yet.
But I'm glad we seem
to have some time to spare.
We should probably head out now.
Oh, and...
I couldn't answer you earlier
but it really was because of my schedule.
There was no other reason.
If you misunderstood, I apologize.
Look.
Love is gone.
Love woke up?
Why?
I don't know.
Where did Love go?
LOVE CELL
Wait a minute.
Then that lightning bolt...
Let's go.
This is the kind of scene
you'd only see in Yu-mi's novels.
Is this for real?
Can you really fall for someone
in a flash like that?
GONG FOR PUBLIC, SA FOR PRIVATE.
EPISODE 9
PUBLIC AND PRIVATE LIVES
All right, next up is
the author of a hit novel.
Please welcome Kim Yu-mi, author of
Sincerity Smells Like Oranges
HAEUNDAE BADAMUN ART HALL
20TH ANNIVERSARY BOOK TALK
Yes, hello. I'm writer Kim Yu-mi.
All right, we'll now begin
the Q&amp;A session.
A question for writer Kim Yu-mi...
Actually, being a writer was just
a vague childhood dream of mine.
Now that I'm older...
It was a short but enjoyable time.
I'll be back with another great book.
Thank you.
- Ms. Kim, I'm a fan.
- Thank you.
Please smile.
- What's your name?
- Jin Hui-jeong.
Jin Hui-jeong...
- Thank you.
Ms. Kim, all your photos came out great.
You got a bouquet too?
Ms. Kim, you're a total superstar!
How pretty.
- Here's the cake you ordered.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Have a good one.
Ms. Kim, I'm here.
Oh, you're here?
Did you have a good trip to Busan?
Yeah.
I saw your blog's Book Talk photos.
So many people came!
Yeah. More people came than I expected.
See? I told you you have a ton of fans.
That's not it.
There were several guest writers.
But Ms. Kim, you seem very calm today.
- I do?
- Yes. You seem unusually calm.
There's nothing to get excited about.
It's the same every day.
Is that so?
Calm, my ass.
She has no idea
but the village is a complete wreck!
Just look at the state of the village
these past few days.
But I can't let it show.
If I look calm, I've succeeded.
- Should we go to the hospital?
- Yeah.
They have symptoms of partial memory loss
after being struck by lightning.
Partial memory loss?
When he took off his glasses
and let his hair down,
Soon-rok looked like a puppy.
And when he smiled, it was incredible.
So cute!
- Right!
- What was that?
- But you guys were
furious with Soon-rok. Don't you remember?
Oh, were we?
Right, I think we were angry.
But why were we angry?
Soon-rok...
Because he was leaving?
- That's right!
- I think that was it.
Love disappeared.
Naughty Cell also.
Man-Patrol Squad.
Tongue Cell disappeared, too.
Why did Naughty and Tongue Cells wake up?
She doesn't even have a boyfriend!
What are they going to do
now that they're awake?
Those useless things!
They only woke up because of the lightning
so I don't think they woke up
for a specific reason.
Hurry and find them all!
Before they run wild again!
Without them, I...
No, Yu-mi was so at peace!
It just glitched from the lightning.
It's no big deal.
Everything will be back to normal soon.
It's not like we'll see
Shin Soon-rok anymore anyway.
That's true.
In a few days,
it'll be as if nothing happened.
Let's start the meeting.
- What's this? A cake?
- Yes, a birthday cake.
A birthday cake?
I didn't know,
but today is Shin PD's birthday.
I set a reminder on my messenger,
and it popped up this morning.
It works out perfectly
since we have a meeting today.
It's pretty, right? It's a low-sugar cake.
I guess I forgot to tell you.
Shin PD isn't coming today.
- Why?
- He's off our team starting today.
- What?
- Last week was his last.
- I forgot to tell you.
- But, why?
He said his schedule was a mess
since he was managing too many teams.
Let's eat the cake ourselves.
It looks delicious.
I'm so disappointed.
This is a major disappointment.
Come on,
how is it a "major disappointment"?
I liked Shin PD.
Did you come to the meeting
for personal reasons?
We're not even having a farewell party?
- Let's at least have a team dinner.
- A party? We only met a few times.
It's his birthday.
Let's have a farewell and birthday party.
He won't be coming here anymore.
If you're that disappointed,
wish him happy birthday yourself.
I guess I should.
I sent it.
You sent him a happy birthday message?
I said I'm very sad
that he quit so suddenly.
I never knew you liked him so much.
He was surprisingly cute.
He looks just like a puppy
without his glasses.
He took off his glasses
for a moment the other day
and he was so cute.
So I told him to wear contacts.
And do you know what he said?
What did he say?
I wear them to look cold.
What does that mean?
He said he wants to look cold.
So that people won't bother him.
He's so cute and funny.
It's Shin PD.
Hello? Oh, hello.
Yes, I'm at the meeting now,
and I heard from Ms. Kim.
Yes, at her studio.
Oh, really?
Yes, okay. Bye.
Shin PD is nearby right now.
- Really?
- He said he'll stop by for a bit.
- Now? He's coming here?
- Yes.
He asked if he could come up,
so I told him to.
That's great.
We'll cut the cake when he's here.
Let's surprise him.
What? Things were just calming down.
Why is he coming?
-Thump, thump, thump, thump.
-What's this sound?
- Thump, thump, thump, thump.
- Hey, Koongsimi! Kwangsimi!
- Why are you two beating the drums?
- Thump, thump, thump, thump.
- Thump, thump, thump, thump
Why is your heart suddenly pounding?
- Ms. Kim, I'll put this away for now.
- Okay.
He's unbelievable.
He quit when he wanted.
Why is he suddenly back?
- He's here.
- Okay.
Ms. Kim, can I put some on too?
- Put on what?
- Lip gloss. I didn't bring mine.
Didn't you just put on some?
Well, yeah...
My lips keep getting chapped.
I like that it has color.
Hey!
Why the sudden lip gloss? Huh?
I told you.
My lips are chapped.
- Hello.
Ms. Kim, Shin PD is here.
- Thump, thump, thump, thump
- Thump, thump, thump.
- What? Why is this happening again?
Exactly! Why is this happening again?
- Thump, thump, thump, thump
Ms. Kim, hello.
You came.
Did you rest well after Busan?
Yeah, sort of.
- But how...
- I had something to do nearby.
I was going to stop by anyway,
and Na-hee contacted me.
I see.
I came to give you this.
What's this?
The Book Talk organizers
sent you some high-res photos.
I picked a good one and had it framed.
You look pretty in it.
You shouldn't have. Thank you.
Ta-da!
Happy birthday, Shin PD!
It's your birthday today, right?
- How did you know?
- I just knew.
How did you know?
Na-hee is quick with these things.
- Okay, let's sing the birthday song.
- No, that's okay.
Ms. Kim, let's start.
Happy birthday to you
- Happy birthday to you
- Wait!
...to you
I have to say "dear" next.
To Shin Soon-rok!
It's a song you sing even to an enemy
on their birthday. What's so weird?
No, but still, to Shin Soon-rok...
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, dear Shin PD
Is Yu-mi blushing? But why?
- Blow them out.
- Okay.
Happy birthday.
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
I'm so flustered.
Have some cake before you go.
- Yes, have a seat here.
- Okay.
- Ms. Kim, I'll get it.
- It's okay. I'll do it.
- You can cut the cake.
- Oh, okay.
I bought the right number
of candles, right?
- Your 30th birthday.
- What? Shin PD is only 30?
- No. I'm not 30.
- I knew it.
We must be only a year or two apart.
To be exact, I'm 29.
Really?
- Then we're only one year apart.
- Yes.
That's crazy. He's in his twenties?
No, then what's the age difference
between him and Yu-mi?
- One, two.
- Why are you counting? Huh?
- What use will that information have?
- It hurts!
I'm going to make some coffee.
Anyone want some?
Can I get an iced Americano then?
- Of course.
- Thank you.
- I'll do it.
- No, it's okay.
- You too, right?
- Yes.
Shin PD, did you have your birthday soup?
- No.
- Why not? Do you live alone?
Yes. I moved out during college.
He lives alone?
What about your parents?
My parents retired, built a house
in the country, and moved.
- To Yangpyeong.
- So you go visit them every weekend?
I go sometimes.
I need to rest at home on the weekends.
- So you're a homebody, Shin PD.
- I'm a total homebody.
Oh, he's a homebody?
- He's just like me.
- Any plans for your birthday?
Perhaps a date?
Who would I go on a date with?
That was a good question.
Soon-rok doesn't have a girlfriend.
So?
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
I'll enjoy it.
The coffee is delicious.
- The coffee is smooth, right?
- Yes. And the cake is delicious too.
Thank you.
I didn't buy it. Na-hee did.
- I bought it.
- The cake is delicious.
But, Shin PD, this is the most
I've ever seen you talk.
- Really?
- Right, Ms. Kim?
That's right.
It must be because I'm not here for work.
I feel more relaxed.
So you've felt uncomfortable
coming here until now?
I'm the type
who's very strict about
separating work and my private life
so it just happens
without me realizing it.
It's not a good personality trait.
- Come visit outside of work sometime.
- I will.
It's your birthday.
What are you doing this evening?
- If you're not going on a date?
- I'm going to Busan.
- Busan again?
- Yes.
We're having a publisher's workshop.
It's for four days,
and all the writers are going too.
I heard you weren't going
because of the Busan business trip.
Oh, yes, that's right.
Because I didn't want to go again
just two days later.
And I'm going again just two days later.
That must be tough,
especially on your birthday.
Well, I'll be on my way.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
- Goodbye.
- Take care.
Why did I say
I wasn't going to the workshop?
- Everyone is going.
- Hey.
Waste a week when I have to write?
But Soon-rok is going...
So?
- I'm just saying.
- Hey! Why are you like this too?
You're Rational Cell. Get a grip!
- The workshop isn't bad for work.
- It is bad.
I said it's bad!
Especially! Now! Even more so!
Shut up and let me just write.
Then what if the Maltese disappears
while she's taking out the trash?
The Maltese goes out the open door,
gets on the elevator, and disappears.
The male lead finds out and is
furious with the female lead...
That's a good idea too.
Or, she finds the Maltese is sick,
and she takes it to the vet.
But her phone died...
- She looks for the Maltese...
- That's also...
good.
- But, you know, Na-hee.
- Yes?
Should we end our meeting
a little early today?
- Sorry?
- Something came up.
How about we wrap up today
and meet online tomorrow?
That last idea was good.
I think we can finish up quickly.
Okay.
You're an idea bank.
Why, why is she like this?
Why is she being like this again?
We only started the meeting
a little while ago!
Don't you know why she's acting like this?
You still don't know
why Yu-mi is acting like this?
Love! Where were you hiding?
She's here! Get her!
You fools!
How can someone in love be calm?
Wha... what are you talking about?
The world has changed, Writer Cell.
The moment lightning struck,
Yu-mi changed.
Hello? Ms. Kim!
Jang PD.
Are you in Busan?
Yes, I came down this morning
with the Chief Editor.
I'm thinking of going to Busan, too.
Are there any rooms available?
Gosh, you're coming?
Yes, well, it's not often
I get to see all the writers
so I figured I should go.
Of course, we'd love for you to come.
Please come.
- Okay, I'll take the evening train.
- Okay.
The Chief Editor will be happy.
- Hurry and come down.
- Okay, I'll call you when I arrive.
Okay.
I'm crazy. I'm crazy.
- I'm reclaiming my Prime Cell spot.
- What?
And you'd better hand over
this castle, too.
That's crazy. Hey!
Who said you could be the Prime Cell?
Hey, what are you doing? Get her now!
What do you think you're doing,
Kim Yu-mi, huh?
What are you doing? Seriously.
You're crazy!
You're really crazy.
You can't separate your personal
and professional lives.
Unlike someone who's so strict about it.
I'm crazy. I'm crazy.
SEOUL METROPOLITAN CITY
How old are you?
- You must be crazy...
- Excuse me?
It's nothing.
I'm crazy. I'm crazy.
Hello, Jang PD.
Ms. Kim, you aren't
on the train yet, right?
- I was about to buy my ticket...
- Oh, that's great.
Shin PD is on his way down.
He's still at the station.
- What?
- How about coming down with Shin PD?
I'll tell him to get you a seat.
Okay.
This is seriously crazy.
Why am I so nervous? It's not a big deal.
Ms. Kim.
A CRUSH HAS BEGUN
Fine, I admit it.
I...
like Soon-rok.
Hey.
You think you can take my spot?
I've been working on this for years.
I'm still the Prime Cell!
Bring it on.
Let's see who the final winner will be.
That's ridiculous.
Shin Soon-rok isn't even
interested in Yu-mi.
He even hates her!
He's probably scared of her.
After she threw a fit like that.
He has to deal with her. For work.
Don't you get it?
- Please take a seat.
- Thanks.
Earlier today, you said
you weren't coming...
Right, I did...
but the meeting ended early.
And Jang PD kept insisting that I come.
Oh, I see.
- So that's how we came together.
- The train is now departing.
Right.
Would you like some coffee?
- No, thank you. I already had some.
- Okay.
GOING HOME
See?
Are you going to have
a hopeless, one-sided crush?
- I don't care.
- What?
What's important is...
that I have woken up.
that Yu-mi's bland daily life is over.
A CRUSH HAS BEGUN
YUMI'S CELLS 3
- It's Soon-rok!
- He's so cute.
Yu-mi, get a grip.
This is Writer Kim Ju-ho.
Oh, yes. It's nice to meet you.
- Sorry, what year did you start school?
- Wait.
Why would you suddenly ask that?
You're sure Ms. Kim
doesn't have a boyfriend, right?
It looks like you all plotted
to set me up with that writer.
Don't they look good together?
They don't look good together.
With confidence,
let's go for flirting stage!
- Flirting stage!