(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
ALL FIGURES, INCIDENTS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, AND OTHERS ARE FICTITIOUS
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS WERE FILMED
SAFELY IN ACCORDANCE WITH GUIDELINES
SEOUL HIGH PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
How are you acquainted
with Mr. Jeon Sang-ho?
He was my client.
You were his attorney?
What were you defending him for?
That…
I cannot disclose it
due to my duty of confidentiality.
Then, when were you first
acquainted with him?
Not long ago.
Are you saying
it was just before his death?
Kind of.
Mr. Shin, are you playing games with me?
My son-in-law's attorney?
It seems Mr. Jeon retained him
before he passed away.
That's totally new to me.
I saw traces of him
at the attorney's office.
I compared it with his handwriting
at the lab, and it looked the same.
He had a habit of writing on the wall
or anywhere to prove what questioned him.
Now, tell me.
Why did my son-in-law's attorney
come here?
Why did he go on a rampage?
Oh, that.
I think he's got a mental issue.
He sees and hears things.
If you'd like to sue him, I can…
No.
Su-jeong's second instance
is enough of a headache.
Let's not add more to it.
Of course.
It's late. Let's call it here.
Why didn't you tell me
that Mr. Jeon's research was
about developing a cure
for your wife's Concello disease?
That…
has nothing to do with this case.
According to people around you,
Mr. Jeon wanted to drop the research.
Is this true?
Who said such a thing?
If it's true, it may be seen
as a powerful motive for murder.
It's already been 17 years now.
-Honey, the soup is ready.
-Okay.
The Korean section was a bit hard,
but I could handle everything else.
Why don't you take private lessons?
I don't want to.
Or…
why don't I help you?
That's worse.
Honey, are you okay?
I'm okay.
Maybe it's because I couldn't sleep much.
Shouldn't you go see a doctor?
It's already the third time this week.
The MRI scan result says…
That was the beginning.
Her disease destroyed our family.
Honey.
Mom.
From then on, I took her to the
best doctors to find an optimal solution,
but nothing worked.
Still, I couldn't give up.
Since I was a scientist,
I decided to resolve it myself.
I wanted to save my wife
with my own ability.
When did you come, Dad?
Su-jeong.
God doesn't exist.
What can save your mom
is only science.
Repeated failures made me anxious.
And I realized
that I needed someone better than me.
That was Mr. Jeon Sang-ho, wasn't it?
But he called a halt to the research.
You must've hated him enough to kill him,
Mr. Kim Tae-jun.
PITTER-PATTER BUTCHER-STYLE BBQ
SHIN I-RANG LAW OFFICE
Prosecutor Kim.
Yes?
The forensic analysis result is out.
Shin I-rang's fingerprints
were found inside the gloves.
It's way off Jeon Sang-ho's estimated time
of death too.
They assume the fingerprints were
from when he dug up the body.
Does this mean Shin I-rang is
only the first discoverer of the body?
As it stands now, yes.
He went up the mountain
and found the body by himself?
Who made the report?
It was through an emergency call,
but who reported it is unknown.
Jeon Sang-ho?
How did he do it?
There has to be something.
I collected and checked
all footage within a kilometer.
Fortunately, you weren't captured.
Still, I terminated it all.
Good job.
Oh, right.
Tail Shin I-rang for some time.
Yes, sir.
You'll be asked to come in again soon.
Keep your phone on
and be ready to take the call anytime.
Okay.
-I-rang.
-I-rang. Are you okay?
Mom?
You're supposed to have pure white tofu
for a good change,
but the store isn't open yet.
TODAY SOY MILK
ORIGINAL
I was feeling hungry anyway.
Thanks, Bong-su.
I bought all kinds, so drink all you want.
This one is warm.
Anyway, did you stay up all night
in the car?
Why did you? You should've waited at home.
I couldn't do it
when my son was somewhere cold.
Bong-su, I have a place to go with I-rang.
Go back with the Father.
Okay.
Are we going somewhere? Where?
You'll know when we get there.
-Have some.
-I'm good.
-It's all right.
-No, thank you.
What is this about?
You're scaring me.
Mom.
I knew it from the start.
It didn't seem bad,
so I asked the priest and Bong-su
to assist you.
But this isn't right.
What's wrong with you, Mom? Stop it.
I should've done this in the beginning.
I should've burned them all
when I discovered it.
Mom, this is my office. This is my work.
What if something bad happens to you?
What if you get hurt?
That's not going to happen.
I won't get hurt.
What if you harm someone?
I won't.
I swear it won't happen again.
How can you be sure of that?
Because it's all…
my fault.
What?
I lied to Sang-ho about the trial.
In case he went out of control
and things got complicated,
I hid the truth from him.
Let alone getting murdered,
he found out that the only person
listening to him was fooling him.
I can only imagine how angry he was.
That's not your fault.
You weren't meant for this kind of work
in the first place.
If not me…
If not me,
who's going to listen to their stories?
-I-rang.
-In the holding cell, I stopped to think…
about why my life was turning this way,
where it started to get messy,
and what wrongs I committed
to deserve such difficult tasks.
But then,
I realized that the happiness I got
from both Gang-pung and Su-a
was much bigger
than the difficulties I faced.
Rather than money, fame,
or anything like that,
I realized how precious it was
to help souls
and how lucky I was
to be able to help them.
So,
you'll continue?
Yes.
I want to.
I'll do it.
Just who do you take after?
What if something like yesterday
happens again?
Then,
I'll do as you say.
Are you sure?
Can you really put an end to this?
Yes.
I'll burn these all myself.
Be careful, okay?
You must never get yourself hurt
or hurt others. Got it?
Okay.
I'll be very, very careful.
I promise.
Don't worry.
I'm not like Dad.
Thank you, Mr. Attorney.
Don't say that.
I'm the one who's sorry
and also grateful.
Anyway,
did you think
the culprit was your father-in-law?
Is that why you went to him?
What led you to such an idea?
Is it hard to tell me?
I'm not trying to hide it,
but I want to check it
with Su-jeong first.
And when I become sure,
I'll tell you everything.
You want to meet her?
She's locked up in the detention center.
I don't think it's a good idea.
If you see her,
you'll lose your calm for sure.
Then yesterday's ruckus may repeat.
Right.
I'll ask her on your behalf.
Tell me all that you want to ask her.
What about me?
Of course, you'll wait outside
so that you won't possess me.
Somewhere as far as you can be.
Right.
Far away.
Hello.
Prosecutor Kim.
I have a favor to ask of you.
Answer me first.
I heard you took Attorney Shin's family
to Mr. Kim's house.
What happened?
I honestly can't explain it.
Maybe I got swept up in the moment.
You aren't one to get swept up
in the moment, are you?
Is the interrogation date scheduled
for Ms. Kim Su-jeong?
There won't be an interrogation.
She refused to do it.
The walls are closing in on her.
I wonder what's gotten into her.
Beats me.
I need the list of suspects,
the case materials,
and Mr. Jeon's autopsy report.
I'm making an official request
as Ms. Kim's attorney.
Hello?
Attorney Shin just entered
the Seoul Detention Center.
Why?
Jeon Sang-ho's wife, Kim Su-jeong,
is locked up here.
Do you know any guards there?
I hope you're doing well. Yes.
Don't worry.
Recording is a piece of cake.
What was that?
Inmate 1023, Kim Su-jeong.
Where did my pen go?
Gosh, maybe I forgot to bring it.
Mr. Attorney.
What are you doing here? Go away.
Do we have a problem?
No, not at all.
-This man--
-Leave it up to me and just go.
I must stay here.
It's our rule to have a general visitation
accompanied by a guard.
Oh, this isn't a general visitation.
I'm an attorney.
I see.
I wrote it on the visitation request too.
Oh, I guess I missed that part.
Will you leave me alone now?
Sure.
Wait.
That…
W-What about it?
Could I borrow it?
I'll make sure to give it back to you
when I leave.
Yes, thank--
I mean…
Please make sure you return it to me.
Yes, of course.
Okay.
Oh, no.
I heard…
you found my husband's body.
Was it really him?
Was it really my husband, Sang-ho?
Yes.
Unfortunately, it was Mr. Jeon Sang-ho.
It really was him…
Mr. Attorney.
He did nothing wrong.
If he hadn't married me, he would've
lived happily as a successful scientist.
He died because he was unlucky enough
to marry someone like me.
I feel so sorry for him.
Attorney Shin?
Why are you crying?
Su-jeong.
Excuse me?
It's me, Sang-ho.
Your husband,
Jeon Sang-ho.
What are you saying?
Are you out of your mind?
Excuse me.
-Guard.
-I'm peckish.
I'm peckish.
I'm suddenly feeling so peckish.
I'm peckish too.
Everyone seems hungry.
Should we eat something?
Sounds good.
What should we have?
Because it wasn't easy for me
to say "I love you,"
instead of using "love"
"peckish" became our secret signal.
Is it really you, Sang-ho?
Our first kiss was
on September 4, 2018
in the closet of my house.
We were excited to pick January 2,
Isaac Asimov's birthday,
for our wedding date.
I looked so much for you.
Why?
Did you think I hid the cure
before I died?
That's not it.
Right.
Honestly,
I was attracted
to how much you loved your family.
I admit it.
You sacrificed your everything
for your beloved family.
I felt like I'd become happy
if I married someone like you.
But
I couldn't be part of your family
in the end.
Why aren't we getting any good news yet?
What if it ends up falling through?
Wait patiently, Dad.
Let's count on Sang-ho.
I've waited all this time!
I'm only saying it
because there has been no progress!
To your family,
I was just a stranger you chose
out of necessity.
No.
I didn't come to you
just because of the cure.
Just if,
like the police said…
you were dead for real…
I wanted to let you know how I felt
by any means possible.
Stop lying.
Your father killed me.
You even confessed.
Don't lie.
My dad killed you?
What are you talking about?
When I confessed,
it wasn't because he killed you.
Then…
why did you turn yourself in?
No one is there to prove…
that Dad was home
when the murder took place.
If he gets arrested…
You know it well enough.
Mom needs Dad at every second.
You confessed to what you didn't do
for that ridiculous reason?
What about U-ju?
Without you, U-ju…
U-ju needs you!
U-ju…
can survive without me.
Mom will die without Dad.
I had no choice.
I'm sorry, Sang-ho.
Geez, my eyes are red.
I'm sorry.
You shouldn't have come.
I told you not to.
I didn't mean to.
Pen.
The pen.
Oh, right.
I forgot to give it back to him.
It's not just a pen.
It's a recorder.
What?
Gosh, I'm lost for words.
What is it? Did something happen?
Where is the voice recorder?
Look.
That Shin I-rang or whoever is a lunatic.
Excuse me. You still have my pen.
Don't touch me.
I said, give me my pen back.
I may be a bookworm,
but don't underestimate me.
Even a worm will turn.
And a cornered rat will fight back.
Get it?
Someone's watching me?
Yes, 100%.
There are no other possibilities.
Let's figure that out later.
What did Ms. Kim say?
Is her father the accomplice?
No.
Then, who is the culprit?
Su-jeong.
Until the actual culprit gets caught,
people need to think she's the murderer.
He quit developing a cure?
In case it was considered
a motive for murder,
Kim Tae-jun kept his wife's disease
and Jeon Sang-ho's research a secret.
So that motive for murder applies
to both Kim Su-jeong and Kim Tae-jun.
Which one are you suspecting?
For now, I have a third person in mind.
There's another suspect?
Yes, but I'll have to look into it.
You're not a detective, Attorney Han.
Kim Su-jeong declined legal presentation.
Pulling out is important
when there's good reason.
Kim Su-jeong will be found not guilty
if the actual culprit can be proved.
So what's your plan?
I'll meet someone who can prove it.
U-ju…
can survive without me.
Mom will die without Dad.
That's the end.
So, you tried to develop a cure
for your mother-in-law.
The three of you wanted to protect
the ones you loved.
I fully understand how you felt.
Where are you going?
To a restaurant, to eat.
What?
I'll stuff myself, regain energy,
and find the real culprit.
But if that's Kim Tae-jun,
I'll put him behind bars.
That's my duty as your attorney.
Shin I-rang?
From the start, he knew
exactly where the murder took place.
Kim Su-jeong murdered her husband
brutally in the bathroom.
Her denial is a lie.
He also knew
where Jeon Sang-ho's body was.
He probably knows more.
So?
I'm going to make use of him.
I can also pull tricks.
Apologize?
I lost my temper in your office that day.
I misunderstood you
without bothering to hear you out.
I was harsh on you too.
I'm sorry.
Do you believe me, then?
And that Sang-ho's spirit is here?
I believe you.
Isn't that what matters?
What a relief.
Actually, your last remark
was quite hurtful.
You said I used other people's suffering.
That's…
I see.
It's okay now that I know how you feel.
Why don't we go to my office
instead of talking here?
I'll officially introduce
you and Sang-ho to each other.
OKCHEON BUILDING
I hate this.
This is Attorney Han Na-hyun.
She's Ms. Kim Su-jeong's attorney.
And this is
Ms. Kim's husband, Jeon Sang-ho.
Hello.
Good.
It's not as awkward as expected, is it?
Do you have any questions for Sang-ho?
I have a lot of questions
about the case.
There are a lot of lingering doubts,
but Ms. Kim wouldn't tell me.
Then, ask him.
He'll tell you everything he knows.
I want to know
if there was anything unusual
on the night of the murder.
After arguing with my wife,
I went to my study.
She went upstairs straightaway to sleep.
He went to the study
after arguing with Su-jeong.
And Su-jeong went straight to sleep.
It's odd now that I think of it.
Are you sure you didn't hear anything
on the night your husband got murdered?
No.
I fell asleep as soon as I lied down.
When I woke up, the sun was already up.
She was mentally unstable
and that day, she even had a bad fight
with her husband.
How was she able
to sleep deeply enough to hear nothing?
It was probably
because of her chamomile tea.
After U-ju was born,
Su-jeong suffered from serious insomnia.
But the chamomile tea from Hyo-jung
helped her sleep well.
Chamomile?
He says a man named Hyo-jung
got her chamomile tea.
Hyo-jung?
Is this about Gu Hyo-jung?
Yes, that's right.
How do you know him?
I went to check Mr. Jeon's lab
and met him there.
I see.
I guess this man is quite the caring type.
Or maybe
he has a crush on Su-jeong.
I doubt he still does.
Then, he used to?
Gu Hyo-jung used to
have a crush on Su-jeong.
I discovered it by chance.
He didn't make any moves
after our wedding,
so I figured he moved on.
Obsessive love is a motive
for quite a lot of murders.
Not him.
I hear the culprit is
taller than 180 cm and sturdy.
But he's around 170 cm tall and slim.
Gu Hyo-jung is short and--
I know he's short and small.
But he…
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
He had a slim but toned physique.
His palm was hard with calluses.
Besides, he gave me
information that I never asked in detail.
We even have a dorm for researchers.
We can't go home often due to work.
As if he were subtly making a way out.
I see.
Sang-ho had the best research outcomes,
and the Chief used him to save his wife.
At the same time,
he led me to suspect Kim Tae-jun.
What are you talking about?
-I acted like I didn't follow…
-Ms. Kim took the blame for whom?
…and he snapped at me.
Isn't it obvious?
The Chief.
Obsessive love sure is
a major motive for murder,
but it was only an old-time crush
in Gu Hyo-jung's case.
Do you have other reasons
behind suspecting him?
Gu Hyo-jung's research
was on animal cloning.
Kim Tae-jun ceased that research.
…A HALT TO UNETHICAL RESEARCH…
Most of all, Gu Hyo-jung believes
that Kim Tae-jun forced
his daughter to marry Sang-ho
out of his blind desire
to develop a cure for his wife's disease.
And what solidified
my suspicion of Gu Hyo-jung
was the autopsy report on Mr. Jeon.
POSTMORTEM PHENOMENA
The culprit couldn't deliver
a fatal blow in one go.
…REPEATED STRIKES…
He hit the wrong spot several times.
I wondered why.
Then, I remembered
his glasses.
Given the thickness and shape
of the lenses,
he had to have serious farsightedness.
The murder took place in the bathroom.
Glasses fog up more easily
the older they are.
With his farsightedness
and fogged-up glasses,
he must've had to strike several times.
The problem is
the estimated time of the murder.
Gu Hyo-jung has a solid alibi.
I checked all the researchers' alibis,
and Gu Hyo-jung was
at the lab all day that day.
He said he slept in the dorm.
In fact, the CCTV camera by the entrance
captured him entering and not leaving.
The lab
has a passage without cameras.
It was made to handle dead animals
under the radar of animal rights groups.
No CCTV cameras are installed there.
But…
No.
This assumption is too irrational.
There's no reliable evidence whatsoever.
Do you have the autopsy report with you?
Why do you ask?
I said he had a solid alibi.
Sang-ho says there's an exit
without any CCTV cameras at the lab.
And he saw something
the moment he was attacked.
The medical examiner's opinion
on the murder weapon
might help him recollect his memory.
You said you believed me.
"The murder weapon is assumed to be
a round metal stick
that is 7.5 cm in diameter
with a hook-shaped end."
A round metal stick that is 7.5 cm
in diameter with a hook-shaped end?
Hey.
You've gained weight.
You must find it quite comfortable here.
What are you doing?
Oh, hey.
I was playing with them.
Don't do that.
You may find it fun,
but the animals don't.
Why did Hyo-jung…
Hyo-jung is a senior researcher.
That means
he's likely to be the next chief.
And a few days ago,
Kim Tae-jun resigned.
CERTIFICATE OF APPOINTMENT
GU HYO-JUNG
From the sad incident…
INAUGURATION CEREMONY
…about our former researcher's death…
to the sudden resignation
of Chief Kim Tae-jun,
our lab is going through hard times.
But at a time like this,
I believe we must reflect on the past
and make plans for the future.
As your new Chief,
I plan to resume
our animal cloning research,
which was ceased by the former chief.
Thank you.
PITTER-PATTER BUTCHER-STYLE BBQ
SHIN I-RANG LAW OFFICE
Hello.
We're here to deliver an extra meat order
to the staff cafeteria.
Just a moment.
They said it was urgent.
If we're late, you might not get
to have your spicy pork.
I know. It's people's favorite.
-The spicy pork here is to die for.
-Right.
The meat might go bad.
-Great, it's open. Thanks.
-Thank you. Have a good day!
JEON SANG-HO
WEAR AN ACCESS CARD
AND PROTECTIVE GEAR
-Bong-su.
-Oh, is it open?
Where could it be?
Let's quiet down the animals
with some food first.
Okay.
Goodness. All right,
here comes some delicious fruit.
Wait a little.
One for you.
Good. It's all right.
Enjoy.
This won't do.
Hold on.
This is prime Korean beef.
I told your mother
that we needed some meat for the case,
and she packed this.
Geez, I barely get a chance to have it.
The animals have become quiet.
Should we save this for ourselves?
-Should we?
-Let's do that.
You said we had something to find.
What does it look like?
It's a meter-long metal stick
with a hook-shaped end.
Hook?
ATTORNEY SHIN I-RANG
Hello?
-Where are you?
-At the prosecutors' office.
To request a compositional analysis
of Ms. Kim's chamomile tea
and an investigation on Gu Hyo-jung.
I doubt that will work.
Even if a sedative component is found,
that won't be conclusive evidence.
If we aren't careful,
Gu Hyo-jung may catch on.
Then he may run off.
This is more reasonable than relying
solely on Mr. Jeon's memory.
You have a point.
But relying on that unreasonable method,
I found the murder weapon.
You found the murder weapon?
Where?
At the lab.
Are you sure about it?
Yes.
Except that
there's more than one.
But I'm sure it's one of them.
Even if you're right by luck,
it must've been washed
with water or chemicals,
so Gu Hyo-jung's DNA
isn't likely to be found.
Besides, anyone at the lab
has access to it.
It can't be a way to specify him.
You're right.
Speaking of which,
I've come up with a new plan.
I need your help on this.
My help?
ATTORNEY HAN NA-HYUN
Hello?
Hello, this is Attorney Han Na-hyun.
Do you remember me?
Yes, you're Su-jeong's attorney.
How may I help you?
Did you perhaps know
that Mr. Jeon had an attorney?
No, it's news to me.
I sent you a picture just now.
Please take a look at it.
This is Sang-ho's handwriting. What is it?
I visited that attorney's office
a while ago.
It was written on the blackboard.
Really?
And he said something strange.
That the culprit was someone else.
He went outside in a rush after that.
I'm following him right now.
I think he's heading to the lab.
I'll go there now.
I'll get back to you when I'm nearby.
ATTORNEY SHIN I-RANG
Gu Hyo-jung is coming to the lab.
Good job.
What now?
I'll make him confess.
You see,
I'm quite good at that.
A-Are you sure?
Yes, I saw him enter the animal lab.
Actually, there's something
I didn't tell you.
The prosecution is keeping it hush-hush,
but the attorney is
the one who found Mr. Jeon's body.
R-Really?
This may sound weird,
but he's said to be psychic.
Sang-ho's spirit possessed him.
That's how he wrote in his handwriting
and found his body.
Do you still think we're okay on our own?
Sang-ho got killed
and Su-jeong got arrested.
Things are already crazy.
I'd like to handle it myself.
Why are you shaking so much?
Are you scared of ghosts?
Not at all. I'm a scientist.
Ghosts don't exist.
I'll go alone from here.
Why? I'll go with--
No, don't. Well…
It stinks,
and some of the animals are violent.
You better not go inside.
Okay.
RESTRICTED AREA
Hello?
Anyone here?
Is anyone here?
You've come, Gu Hyo-jung.
W-Who are you? Are you the attorney?
You haven't come to your senses yet.
Do I still look like
an attorney to you?
If not an attorney, what--
He's coming.
He's coming!
W-Who's coming?
The one you killed. Jeon Sang-ho.
-Sang-ho?
-He asked me
to summon him if he died.
This is ridiculous.
There.
He's come.
That's the formula for the cure.
Why did you do it?
I did nothing wrong to you.
No.
Why did you kill me?
It's a ghost! Help!
A ghost…
ONE HOUR AGO
I'm so nervous. It's my first time
acting as a real-life person.
How do I look?
You kind of look like Sang-ho.
Really? That's good.
What about the voice, though?
This is an AI voice-changing device.
You just have to speak through it.
Oh.
Good.
Listen.
If my acting works,
he'll freak out and try to run off.
And when the flying fake ghost
maximizes his fear,
I'll lead him to confess.
You just have to film it.
Right.
Have you calculated the electricity?
This much overvoltage might cause a fire.
-Bong-su.
-What?
Sang-ho is asking
if you've calculated the electricity.
What matters isn't the calculations.
Movies are all about the feeling.
Geez.
Confess.
Confess that you killed me!
Where are you?
Show yourself!
How could you do that to me?
That time you broke
expensive lab equipment,
I took the blame.
Sang-ho?
I even paid for your mother's surgery.
How could you possibly do that to me?
Is it really you?
I was so good to you.
This makes no sense.
Did you think killing me would do?
That I'd be gone for good, then?
I saw you die before my eyes.
Yes, that's how I died.
But look.
I came back
because I was resentful.
I couldn't rest in peace.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Sang-ho.
Wait. I-I need to record this.
Hold on.
Why isn't it working?
Oh, no! I-rang, there's a fire!
Darn it.
Right, a fire extinguisher.
I'm sorry, Sang-ho. I'm sorry!
I thought it was unfair.
Su-jeong and the Chief depended
only on me until you joined the lab.
I couldn't stand them
turning their back on me.
I didn't mean to kill you from the start.
Liar!
You even prepared the murder weapon.
T-That's…
That, I…
Do you know how dreadful death is?
Do you even know how wretched it is
to leave your beloved family?
What…
What the freak?
It's all fake!
-You fooled me.
-Wait.
Put that down. Let's talk it out.
Talk it out?
Talk what out?
You discovered all that I did!
Just die.
It's for the best.
Attorney Shin!
I told you to wait outside!
Why didn't you listen?
Wait!
No, don't!
Attorney Han!
Thank you!
My name is Shin I-rang.
-Kim Dong-jun.
-Here.
When I was young, kids often teased me
for how my name sounded.
-Shin I-rang.
-Here.
Where is it?
What is?
You like to w-rang-le
with shin-ful ghosts, don't you?
With a ghost!
It didn't bother me much while growing up,
but who knew
I'd actually come to help ghosts?
It's not so bad, though.
No.
I even feel proud when justice prevails.
And there's one thing I newly realized.
Revenge isn't necessarily the reason
why ghosts visit me.
It worked.
The cure was developed
thanks to the work of the kind Sang-ho.
-Mom. Can you hear me?
-Honey.
Su-jeong's mother is
slowly getting better.
And her family has regained peace.
Mom, this is U-ju.
Thank you, Sang-ho.
Thanks to you,
we've gained the strength to live on.
I'll do the best I can
to raise our son
so that you won't be worried.
I love you.
I love you, Dad.
Let's go, U-ju.
Hello.
Thank you so much.
You created a miracle.
It wasn't me. You know that.
Yes, I do.
It was my husband, Sang-ho.
But it would've been impossible
without you.
Thank you so much.
Mr. Attorney.
I hope you rest in peace.
I will.
As for me,
I've come to realize the great value
of those who keep my side.
He's unharmed.
That's good, then.
My indifferent but caring mom.
-It's good.
-Is it good? I want one too.
-How is it?
-It's good.
Prime Korean beef bulgogi!
I-rang is going to love it.
Thank goodness. Uncle's face
didn't turn red like a monkey's butt.
And my openly caring family.
SHIN I-RANG LAW OFFICE
There's one more.
Attorney Han who chose to believe me
despite how absurd it sounded.
PARTNER HAN NA-HYUN
Just what is with Shin I-rang?
Attorney Han!
Thank you!
Whatever.
I won.
WON
CLIENT KIM SU-JEONG
YOUR PACKAGE HAS ARRIVED SAFELY
Attorney Shin sent the voice recorder
to the guard
with a note that said
he was sorry for taking it with him.
Is he kind or just stupid?
Play it.
That recording will help me
figure out what he's up to.
VOICE RECORDING 001
You follow me from behind
But I race forward
I run across the table you're seated
I don't care
If you mess with me, you'll pay the price
I'm hot, hot, hot, hot, fire
Before I go wild
Somebody, please stop me
Stop me
Stop me, stop me, stop me
He's a damn nutcase.
Attorney Shin, are you okay?
Yes.
It's probably because I couldn't
sleep much for the past few days.
You look pale.
I think you should get some rest.
Okay. I'll go home
after sorting some papers a bit.
I'm all right. Go home without me.
-Don't stay too late.
-Okay.
OKCHEON BUILDING
ATTORNEY SHIN I-RANG
Again?
Ghosts aren't coming?
He's cleaning
for his future living clients.
He's so excited.
Hooray for I-rang's independence!
-Want a case?
-You're the best.
I'm very experienced
in pre-construction sales cases.
Attorney Han?
-Why are you here?
-It's not your business.
What's with you people?
It's Seongmyeong Construction,
a shady company that runs
a pre-sale fraud scheme.
-A construction gang?
-You're good at fighting, right?
You little punks!
Subtitle translation by: Eunjin Erica Kim