Previously on
Seducing Drake Palma.
Hello?
Why are you calling?
He’s asleep!
I’m not going to wake
him up for you! Duh!
What are you doing
in Drake’s condo?
Take a guess.
Shai–!
- Dad?
- I’ve been looking for you.
Who is this with you?
- Oh, I’m Alys-
- My girlfriend.
I’ll introduce you
to Tripp’s cousin.
Let me just call Drake.
Are you accusing me
of cheating on you?
Why, aren’t you?
What’s going on?
Family reunion.
Tristan! Tristan!
Hey! What’s up?
This is Drake’s girlfriend.
She is Alys.
I’m going to take this home.
Maybe this is the reason
for Tripp and me to talk.
Drake and I might end up
fighting if that happens.
I’ll take this since
he won’t eat it, anyway.
Oh my gosh!
Unbelievable!
I need to avoid Tripp,
so Drake and me will get
along peacefully.
- Sorry, Ma’am!
- Excuse me!
Sorry!
Look at your face!
I love you, Drake Palma!
I wonder when I’ll get
to talk to that guy again.
Honestly, class is boring
the whole day.
In fairness, he’s really fun to talk to.
Oh, Alys, what mess did
you get yourself into?
What’s that?
What’s that? It’s ruining my
main character moment!
I’ve got so much on my mind–
Dane, you’re here!
You look ugly, Alys!
OMG!
- My baby Dane is so big now!
- Stop! I’m not a kid anymore!
But you’re still my baby!
Get off!
Oh my gosh, Dane,
you’ve grown so much!
You’re too much!
Your sister’s just excited
that you’re here, okay?
Why didn’t you text me
that you were here already?
Blame mom.
She wanted to surprise you.
But you were surprised, right?
Of course!
- My baby Dane is here–
- Get off!
Hey...
Why?
Are you scared that your girlfriend
will see that you’re still our baby–
Alys, stop it already!
Stop!
Because you’re big now?
- Are you really that grown-up?
- Stop!
Because you’re
still our baby Dane!
- Alys!
- Hi, Alys!
Felice!
Hi, baby girl!
Oh wow, the love birds are here!
Let’s have snacks!
Nanny–
No, we’re going out.
Right away?
You’re leaving already,
but you just got here.
It seems baby Dane
didn’t miss me.
You’re so corny.
- We’ll be back right away.
- It’s okay.
Felice is just gonna
show me around.
Okay then.
- Just be back by dinner, okay?
- Yes.
Bye, Alys!
It was so nice to
see you, though.
Nice meeting you, baby.
Okay.
Take care of her.
Puppy love.
They’re so sweet.
I wish everyone had that.
You’re really avoiding me, huh?
Goodness, Tripp Marco Palma!
I had two successful days,
but failed on the third day.
Oh my gosh!
What am I supposed
to tell Drake if he asks?
I really hate lying.
Hey.
What?
Are you avoiding me?
No, I’m not.
You’re just too sensitive.
Sorry, Tripp.
You don’t deserve the
stupidity I’m doing, but...
I really love Drake.
Okay. I shouldn’t
have entertained Tripp.
But it’s so hard,
it’s sad having to go home
every break time
because I have no one
to talk to at Brenford.
Should I face him?
I really feel guilty
everytime I ignore him.
Is he coming closer?
Lord, please, give me strength.
I’m close to giving in
and talking to Tripp.
Well, happy birthday.
After all, you don’t want
to talk to me, anyway.
Tripp...
I missed you.
Tripp…
Where are we going, Ma’am?
Sir, do you know how it
feels to be guilty?
What?
It’s because I’m
avoiding my friend.
I feel so guilty.
That’s why I’d rather go home,
because I don’t want to see him.
I feel like I’m
such a bad person.
Oh…
All he ever did was make
me laugh, make me feel better.
And then what,
this is how I’ll treat him?
I don’t know what kind of
friend I am.
Ma’am, that looks more like
a lover, not just a friend.
Alright, Sir, let’s go.
Where to?
Southville, Gate 3.
Alys!
- You’re here!
- Mom.
I thought your class was later?
We got dismissed early.
Are you alright?
- Alys?
- Huh?
I said are you alright?
Yes, mom. I’m okay.
I’m just really tired.
Well, I know something that
will make you very excited.
Your gowns are here!
Oh right!
My debut is tomorrow!
Well, aren’t you
excited to try them on?
Of course, Mom, I’m very excited!
Well, they’re upstairs,
go try them on!
- Okay?
- Okay.
Alright, see you later.
Okay.
Sigh.
I thought my debut would be fun,
since Drake agreed
to be my escort.
But why don’t I feel happy?
Is it because Tripp
is ignoring me already?
Gosh, life is such a mess.
Baby Dane, you’re here!
Hi!
What are you doing here?
Don’t you have
plans with Felice?
She went out with her friends.
Mmm.
What happened to you?
You are ugly,
but you’re getting even uglier.
Are you really my sister?
Good thing I still have
my super cute brother!
Stop!
You know what?
You’re the only one who
makes me happy these days.
Making you happy?
But you’re hurting me.
Come on, I was just being sweet.
You’re acting like I’m not
your big sister.
It doesn’t really seem like it.
You’re crazy.
What makes you say that?
Because I’m cool,
and you’re not.
Fine, you win.
You’re the handsome one,
the honor student,
and everyone’s favorite,
including me.
I’m not sure about
being the favorite.
Life’s so unfair!
But you know what,
I’m super happy that you’re
here for my birthday.
I love you.
Baby!
Stop!
Dane!
Stay right there, okay?
I need your honest opinion.
Whatever.
I look so pretty, my gosh!
Who is this?
I look so cute, wow!
That’s right.
Just love yourself.
Admit it. It suits me,
and I look gorgeous.
Wow, he’s speechless!
Was the impact that strong?
Oh my gosh,
my little brother!
Admit it. The gown looks
great on your beautiful sister!
Whatever.
Is that so?
- Mom!
- Fine!
- He said the gown is – !
So, what? Is it beautiful?
Does it look good on me?
Your boyfriend will like it.
Wait, there’s one more.
In fairness...
Even though you’ve been in California
for two years, we’re still close, right?
Because there’s just the two of us –
what choice do I have?
Wow! Are you forced?
Hey, let’s eat.
- Come on, let’s eat!
- Have a seat.
I missed this food!
Wow, this is a lot!
Come on, eat!
What took you so long?
You’ve been gone long.
Because Alys couldn’t
stop admiring her gown.
I’m sorry, okay?
I told you she’d love your work.
Of course, Mom made that.
It’s going to be beautiful.
Well, is Drake really sure about
being your escort for your debut?
He said yes.
He better.
Oh, scary!
This tastes so good!
Glad you like it!
Come on!
Why are you so grumpy?
Mmm, Alys, by the way,
here’s the program flow.
Check them out and let me
know if you’re okay with it.
Wow, Mom, there are so
many 18 things here.
But I love it.
Thank you, Mom.
That’s good. Come on, eat.
You know, Mom...
Mmm?
Nana keeps on scolding me
just because I talk to a lot of
girls at school.
It’s not my fault if
they think I’m being flirty,
I’m just being friendly.
Well, because you’re my baby,
you’re a cute
baby of Mommy!
Stop, that’s not true!
Oh, what?
You look like Mommy!
I don’t look like you.
I’m so blessed with my family.
Thank You, Lord,
for giving me the best.
- Who did I take after?
- You look like your dad.
Your Mommy.
- You were found in a garbage can.
- Mommy?
Wow!
And my big sister speaks!
Hey!
Why are you reading that?
That’s a magazine for adults.
So?
“So?”
Kids these days!
Alys…
Mmm?
Do you believe
the number of
girls I played with
would be the amount
of times you would cry
because of someone?
Why would I cry?
Have you made many
people cry?
I don’t know,
but if that theory is true,
I think you need to
brace yourself.
I’ll sleep in your room.
Why in my room?
Go sleep in yours!
I don’t like it there.
Well, that’s fair.
You’re not here that often, anyway.
Better for you to sleep there.
Theory?
What if that’s true?
Hey, Dane!
Who are the girls
you’ve made cry, huh?
What’s taking her so long?
Here she comes!
- She’s here. Hurry, go!
- She’s coming. Wait.
She’s coming!
- Wait.
- Hurry!
Who’s going to count? Go.
Sshh!
- Alys!
- Happy birthday, bestie!
- Happy birthday!
Hello! Thank you!
Wow, why are you
throwing me a surprise!
I didn’t expect this, since I’m
always the one who goes to SCA.
Oh, right.
Sorry, bestie, it’s our
first time dropping by.
But of course, we won’t let this
day pass without surprising you.
Thank you, bestie.
We brought something
for you. It’s here, a cake!
Thank you so much, bestie!
Of course, bestie, it’s just
school separating us, right?
But we’re still friends.
Happy birthday, bestie!
Happy birthday to you…
Wait!
Come on, sing!
To me!
Happy birthday, happy birthday…
- Happy birthday to you!
- To me!
- Okay, that’s enough!
- Blow the candle, Alys.
- Blow the candle.
- Stop, wait!
Wait!
Make a wish, bestie!
- Oh, okay.
- Yes, that’s right!
- I got excited.
- That’s right, make a wish.
Okay.
I wish Drake would
be my husband.
Just kidding!
Okay.
- Yay!
- Thank you!
You’re welcome, bestie.
Anyway, I still have class.
- My gift –
- She has really changed.
My gift – I’ll give it
at the party later.
Alright.
- Thanks so much. You take care.
- Happy birthday!
Thank you!
- Happy birthday, Alys!
- Bye, Kent!
Thank you for coming!
Would you like me to...
...bring this for you?
I thought you were
going with them?
My class isn’t until
an hour from now.
Let me carry this for you.
Okay, thanks.
Do you want to eat
at the caf?
Your treat?
Seriously, it’s my birthday
and it’s still on me?
Fine, let’s go!
- Even on your birthday, it’s your treat.
- Okay, fine!
- Okay, go!
- Well, I don’t come here often.
Here.
Wow!
This is your treat?
Yes!
I might have to pay for this.
Fine, later.
Happy birthday again, Alys!
Thank you, Sheen.
It’s still early but
I’m already so happy.
Are you ready for
your party later?
Uhm...yes.
I’m a bit nervous,
since Mom invited so many people.
Seems like our entire clan.
Of course, my friends
are coming, too.
Even the kids of Mom and Dad’s
friends are invited, too.
The venue will be packed.
You know what, I missed
your craziness a lot.
I missed you too, Sheen.
I used to get so giddy
when Sheen smiled at me.
But now, I’m just genuinely
happy when he does.
How are you doing
here in Brenford?
You must be happy, right?
Have you adjusted?
Honestly, I’m still so sad,
because it’s almost half the
semester and I still don’t have friends.
Do they really hate me just
because I’m Drake’s girlfriend?
Hey, Alys!
Huh?
I said, how are you in Brenford?
Are you happy?
Oh, I’m fine.
I’m happy.
You know, too bad
you’re not in SCA.
We’re always having fun
there with Aya and Kent.
But it’s good to know
that you’re happy here.
How about you, Sheen?
How’s your love life?
Love life?
What is love life?
I don’t even know what that is.
Hey, it’s been a long
time since Kei left.
Time to move on already, okay.
I’ve already moved on.
Why do you know whether
I’ve moved on or not?
I’m just a third wheel with
Aya and Kent, but it’s fun.
You know those
two, they’re so playful.
What does “third wheel” mean?
Hmm...
I’ll just ask my playboy brother
the meaning of third wheel?
Oh, Alys, wait.
I need to go.
Mmm...
Why, are you finished already?
You ate so fast.
- I’m sorry.
- Are there worms in your stomach?
Time went by so fast.
I’ll just see you later, okay?
Happy birthday again,
see you later.
- Thank you!
- Bye!
- Happy birthday!
- See you later!
Even if you say you’re
doing okay,
I know you better, Sheen.
But don’t worry, best friend.
Time heals everything.
Oh no, what should I do?
Should I greet him, or just walk
straight like I didn’t see him?
What to do?
What just happened?
He didn’t say hi or smile?
There’s nothing.
Is he really that mad
because I ignored him?
This is hard.
I miss Tripp already.
Before refrigeration existed…
Did that idiot
really forget I exist?
Early Filipinos used salt
and vinegar to preserve food.
- This is my first time losing a friend.
- And that’s how adobo started.
- It actually hurts.
- Even before the Spaniards came,
our ancestors already
knew how to preserve food.
Adobo was not just
- created for its flavor.
- [In French] Only you.
- It was first created for survival.
- [In French] Happy birthday, Alys.
What’s with him?
Sometimes it’s like playing
“decode the message” with Drake.
Miss Perez, anything
you want to add?
[In French] Only you.
What? Are you cursing me?
Uh…
No, Ma’am.
I’m sorry.
You better not.
Sit down.
Alys, you’re 18 years old already.
Behave yourself, please.
Yes?
Why are you still not dressed?
Mom said come down already.
Why are you speaking all posh?
Hurry up.
Or you’re gonna hear
more nagging on your birthday.
That kid is so grumpy!
You go, girl.
You can do this.
Aja!
My daughter looks beautiful.
You’ve become a woman, my baby.
Aww, Mommy!
Dad!
Dane, stop laughing!
They’re having a nice moment.
Mom, don’t cry.
It’s a special day.
We should just be happy.
You’re so beautiful, baby.
Where are you?
Alys...
- Are you okay?
- Mom...
Is there any problem?
Uh, nothing.
Well, you seem uneasy.
Are you nervous?
A little bit.
Well, we when we get
to the hotel later,
just have fun, enjoy,
it’s your day, okay?
Okay, Mom, thanks!
Alright!
Dane, let’s go, it’s late!
Oh, where’s Drake?
Oh, uhm...
On the way.
He said he’s on the way.
Great.
Are you feeling too giddy?
Stop it.
Alys, let’s go!
Yes, Mommy!
- Daddy!
- Hi!
Hi, Aunt!
- Hello!
- Happy birthday!
Thank you!
You look nice.
You look gorgeous, Aunt.
And so do you, Dad.
Thank you.
Enjoy the party.
I’ll go greet my other guests.
- Alright.
- Okay.
Enjoy!
- Thank you for coming!
- Okay, have fun.
Please eat, okay?
- Oh, hello!
- Happy birthday!
Thank you!
Hi!
- Thank you!
- Happy birthday!
- Hi, Alys!
- Mom, hi!
- You look so pretty.
- Alys, happy birthday.
Do you remember your aunties?
Of course, hello po!
Happy birthday, dear.
Thank you, Aunt.
- You look stunning.
- Thank you!
Wow, time really
flies, doesn’t it?
Tell me about it, my friend.
Mom, I’ll just
greet my friends.
Is that okay, Aunties?
- I hope you don’t mind.
- Sure, dear.
- It’s your party, just enjoy.
- Okay.
Okay, thank you!
Excuse me.
Okay, see you later!
Oh, thank you!
- Bestie!
Happy birthday, Alys!
- You look so gorgeous!
- Hi, Kent!
You look beautiful, too.
Happy birthday!
- Happy birthday!
- Thank you!
Thank you!
Thank you for coming!
- Sure!
- Of course!
Wherever Bee is, I’m there too.
Wow, looks like you didn’t
come here for the birthday girl.
Oh, it seems like you’re
not used to him.
Oh, by the way,
where’s Sheen?
He’s on his way,
but maybe he’ll be here soon.
- Maybe he got stuck in traffic.
- Yes.
Okay.
Where’s your escort?
Exactly, I still haven’t
heard anything.
But before I left, he said
he was already on his way.
Just let it be,
he’ll be here soon.
I hope so.
You’re ready for the
cotillion dance, right?
We already rehearsed.
Of course!
We already practiced.
Right, Bee?
Hi, Aya!
Aunt!
Oh my god!
You look so pretty!
Thank you!
Oh, Aunt! This is
my boyfriend, Kent.
I’m proud to be.
Hello, Aunt.
- “Proud to be?”
- "Proud to be?”
Hi, Kent!
Nice to meet you!
Oh, by the way, can I
borrow Alys for a while?
- Yes!
- Go ahead, Aunt.
You don’t even
have to return her.
Just kidding! Go ahead!
Happy birthday!
Go now, baby girl!
Bye!
Alys, where’s Drake?
The program is about to start.
Mom, I don’t know.
Actually, I texted him a while ago,
and he said he’s already on the way.
Oh gosh, Alys!
Anyways, don’t you worry.
Your Dad and I will check if he’s here.
For sure, Drake will come.
No, Mom. Can I be the one
to check on him at the lobby?
I’ll feel better if I get
to see him first.
Oh, baby girl, don’t stress out.
Enjoy the party.
It’s your day. Okay?
Alright, smile.
So we’re always pretty.
- Okay?
- Thanks, Mom.
- Alright!
- Love you.
Love you.
See you later, okay?
- Okay, Mom.
- Alright, bye.
Okay.
How are you doing there?
Where could he be?
Happy birthday!
Tripp, really?
If you only knew how much I
wanted you here at my debut.
This is so hard.
Drake!
Oh no! This can’t be!
It’s my birthday today!
Drake!
Wait, maybe...
he just forgot something.
Maybe he left my birthday gift.
Or maybe he’s wearing slippers
and forgot to change into shoes.
Oh my god, Drake!
Drake, please!
Drake, answer me, please!
Drake, pick up
the phone, please!
Alys.
Hello, Drake?
I’m really sorry, Alys.
I really need to go.
I didn’t mean to disappoint you.
Wow.
Happy birthday, Alys.
Happy damn birthday.
My worry is that there are just
too many guests already.
Mommy can’t see me
like this.
I can’t be seen like this.
What do I even say?
Drake says sorry, but
he can’t come anymore?
That can’t be!
Mom will be mad
and disappointed!
Alys, please! Think!
Please, use your brain cells,
even just a little, come on!
Oh my god!
Please, please!
Sorry.
Sorry, I know this is selfish.
I’m so sorry.
You called?
Tripp, please…
Please, come here.
Wait.
Hold on, are you crying?
Please, Tripp, come here.
I don’t have a partner.
Please!
Come on.
Don’t leave me.
Do you understand
what you’re saying, Alys?
If I go there,
I’ll make my joke real.
I won’t leave you alone.
Maybe this is what happens
when I’ve had enough.
Are you sure that’s
what you want?
Please, Tripp.
I’ve cried five times already.
It’s a lot, actually.
Don’t you feel sorry for me?
Come on, please.
Even Tripp doesn’t like
me anymore?
- Aya?
- Aunt?
Have you seen Alys?
No, Aunt.
Is there a problem?
No, I’m just looking for her.
Sorry, Aunt.
Uh, Sheen, have you
seen Alys outside?
Uh, I didn’t notice, Aunt.
I just got here, too.
Maybe Alys is in the holding area.
I’ll go check for her, okay?
- Okay, Aunt.
- Alright, see you later.
- Sheen, what happened to you?
- Where were you?
What took you so long?
I’m having diarrhea.
Keep it down.
It’s embarassing.
You stink.
Why are you like this, Drake?
I let go of Tripp for you,
but you’re the one
who let go of me now.
Where’s Sheen?
He’s the only one I have left.
You’re so selfish, Alys!
That’s why everyone leaves you.
Miss Alys?
Ma’am...
Excuse me, Ma’am Alys,
shall we introduce you now?
Are you ready?
Um, okay.
We’re holding this event
for over an hour,
my guests might
be starving already.
Thank you, Ma’am.
Wait, I’ll just call you in.
Please standby, we’re ready.
Thank you.
You can do this, Alys.
Let’s go, Alys.
Aja!
Tripp…
I will stop at nothing.
You know that, right?
Sorry for making you come here.
I didn’t know that Drake
won’t come to my debut.
I’m so stupid.
This is the 5th time, Alys.
You know what that means.
I’ll do everything to
make you leave Drake.
What did I do to
deserve this, Drake?
Why are you hurting me so badly?
Why are you laughing
at my husband?
“Husband?”
You made me hold on to a
relationship that’s very uncertain.
Today, we’re okay.
Tomorrow, we’re not.
The next day, we’re okay again.
Why, Drake?
I’m so tired.
Drake?
My gosh, I just had
so much fun with you, Drake.
Am I hard to love?
Why do you keep
hurting me over and over?
This is supposed to be
the happiest night of my life.
My debut.
I don’t deserve this, Drake.
Drake!
This can’t be happening,
it’s my birthday today!
Drake!
Thank you so much, Tripp.
Stop thanking me. You’ve
said it too many times already.
Still, I want to thank you.
That’s your last “thank you”.
I don’t want to hear it again.
What do you want
me to say instead?
“I’m sorry?”
No.
Next time, I want
to see you smiling.
Smile for me?
Thank you so much for coming!
Please eat!
- Happy birthday!
- Thank you!
-Thank you for coming, thank you!
-Happy birthday, Alys!
Mom!
Oh, hi!
You remember Uncle Allan?
Of course!
Hi, Uncle Allan!
- Thank you for coming.
- Happy birthday, dear.
Enjoy your dinner.
Mom, I’m just gonna go
say hi to my friends again.
- Okay?
- Okay, go ahead.
Alright, see you later!
Thank you for coming!
Hello?
Okay.
Where’s your boyfriend?
I don’t know, okay?
Let’s just talk
about it next time.
You know, if he’s being
such a jerk towards you,
ditch him.
You’re my sister.
You deserve
nothing but the best.
You really are mature
for your age, Dane.
I don’t wanna see you crying, Alys.
We rarely see each other,
then you’ll cry in front of me.
Where would that put me?
I’m not crying!
Yeah. And who are
you fooling, anyway?
When will you tell me
where’s that noble boyfriend of yours?
- Hey, don’t tell Mom—
- You know what –
as your only brother,
if he’s hurting you that bad,
don’t you think it’s time to
forget him and move on?
Hey, Dane.
Who’s older between us?
You or me?
I’m just reminding you –
you’re only fourteen!
Whatever.
I’ll look for Felice.
Look at him, he left me here.
Bestie!
Alys!
Hey!
You’re really gorgeous tonight!
Am I beautiful just
for tonight?
Well, that’s a pity.
Yes, only for tonight.
You too, huh?
- Wow, I’m a comedian now!
- Happy birthday again, Alys!
- Happy birthday, Alys!
- Thank you!
- Hope you had fun!
I had fun.
Hey, Sheen,
thank Kei for me—
she even sent a
gift from Russia.
Oh, wow!
Who would have thought
that you will be friends
with the other bestie.
“Bestie?!”
Yes, Bestie!
- Bestie-friends now, see?
- Yeah, yeah.
Alys…
Hey, Tripp.
Can we talk?
Aren’t we already talking?
No, I mean...
...outside.
Okay.
Can we grab something
to eat first, is that okay?
- Okay.
We’ll just eat.
Alright!
Tripp, where are you taking me?
Tripp.
Just follow the light.
He prepared that for you, Zyril.
I’ll head back upstairs.
When he explained himself
and you really don’t want anymore,
you know where to find me.
Happy birthday.
Hopefully, I’m still not late.
Thank you for coming!
Hello?
Okay.
What do you want from me, Drake?
Thanks for coming.
For old times’ sake,
help me out, Tripp.
I really messed up with Alys.
At least you know.
So please,
I’m asking you as family –
bring Alys here.
She won’t answer my calls.
I love her, Tripp.
I really, really love Alys.
I’ll try.
Thank you.
I’m really sorry, Alys.
I’m making up to you.
I hope she can forgive me.
I really messed up this time.
I cannot lose you, Alys.
On the next episode of
Seducing Drake Palma.
So, how’s the single life?
It’s been a week, huh?
How is it going?
- Like this.
- Ouch.
Good morning, Alys.
No more Drake talks, okay?
I’m moving on!
Tripp!
- Tripp, hello!
- Here comes this squid again!
Oh, Alys.
You’re here, too.
I didn’t notice you.
Uh, Zy, have you eaten?
What’s your passcode?
Come on, let’s eat.
I’ll whisper it to you.
What?
1-1-3-1?
Why’d you shout it out?