It’s okay to be afraid.
Everyone’s afraid of pain.
Well, does it hurt?
Before I forget…
You can keep it.
Then why did you
agree to meet me?
Isn’t it obvious?
I wanted to see you.
Oh my god.
You and Haze are trending.
Your photos during the fashion
show are circulating.
Special delivery!
It’s never gonna be enough.
It doesn’t matter what we do,
it’s never just gonna be
fucking enough.
Fuck the system, man.
Yeah, fuck! Fuck the system.
- Fuck the system.
Fuck the system.
Can you spend your
next free day with me?
I want to see the dogs.
Sure.
They miss their mom too.
Hey!
How’s Paris?
Probably the best month
of my life.
I bought you a gift,
but I’ll give it to you later.
Where are we going now?
Did you miss me?
Don’t ask two questions
at the same time.
Give me your suitcase.
Did you miss me?
Let’s go to the
parking lot first.
- Come on.
- Hey! Did you miss me?
I have a surprise for you.
Hey, where are we?
Just wait. You’ll see.
- Okay.
- Okay, let’s go.
Slowly.
Step.
- Wait…
- Okay, step.
We’re in the stairs. Step.
A bit to your left.
- To my left. Okay.
- Left and left. Yeah.
Wait.
I’m scared. Wait.
Wait, hold my hand.
Okay.
Left, left.
I’m here. I’m here.
Where are we going?
Is this safe?
Just trust me.
Be careful.
- Just follow my lead.
- Okay.
We’re going up, okay?
Huh?
- Again.
- Again?
Wait.
Wait… Okay.
- Just follow my lead.
- Wait, stairs again?
Step.
One more.
Okay.
Almost there.
One more step.
I got you.
Our house.
So, did that answer your
question a while ago?
I missed you so much.
But what does this kiss mean?
It’s good you were able
to take care of this house.
The house still looks nice.
Even if so much has changed.
Yeah, I actually thought
about selling it
since it was given to us
by our parents.
But at the same time,
I didn’t want to let go
of our memories here.
I agree.
We really do have a lot
of memories here.
Yeah.
I’m leaving for New York.
Let’s just make the most of
the time that you’re still here.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Is something bothering you?
Do you remember
what happened that night?
When you got drunk at my condo?
What happened that night?
About our conversation
back then.
What did we talk about?
Seriously?
No, I’m just joking.
I remember everything.
- Everything?
- Everything.
I remember everything
we talked about.
And… I also remember you said
you’re moving to New York soon.
So, you know that I’m leaving…
Why did you still kiss me, then?
What did that mean?
Because I still have
feelings for you, Sam.
Even if we can’t be together.
That’s why
I just want to enjoy
every moment
with you while you’re still here.
I practiced a lot.
I’m excited to eat.
It feels so good
to be back here, Sam.
Wow! You really look
like a model, Sam!
Try a different pose.
I miss you.
We have a gift for
my favorite sister.
Thank you, Sam.
Thank you, Clyden.
Merry Christmas.
More years to spend together.
I’m claiming it.
I’ll always be your
number one fan, Sam.
Hey.
Why are you still up?
You’re not sleepy yet?
I don’t feel like sleeping yet.
Staying up late
isn’t good, you know.
I just want to make
the most of my stay here,
to remember all the
good memories in this house—
With you…
and with Naomi.
Hey…
I miss her, too.
And I’m sure
she’s in a better place now.
Can you sleep with me?
Huh? Why?
I just want someone
beside me tonight.
Can you cuddle with me?
Yeah, sure.
Is this okay?
I guess.
Sam, can you stop
moving, please?
I’m sorry.
‘Cause your behind
is brushing on my—
front.
Samantha, do not think of
erotic things right now!
You need to sleep!
Good morning.
Morning.
You’re up early.
I couldn’t sleep.
I probably only got around
four hours of sleep.
Why? Are you okay?
Are you sick?
It’s all your fault.
What did I do to him?
I just slept.
I can’t remember
doing anything.
Was I moving around a lot?
Did I sleep talk?
Did I say something offensive
before we went to sleep?
Then how is it my fault?
Spoon?
Maybe I’m just not used
to sleeping next to someone.
Maybe.
Eat up. We’re gonna
walk the dogs.
Is it good?
She’s really enjoying herself.
Yeah, Solar loves walking.
Cy, can I ask you something?
Yeah, sure.
How did Summer pass away?
Well, she was already old.
And after giving birth to Solar,
that’s when she really
started getting weaker.
Actually, Solar was supposed
to have a sibling, too.
But that one passed away.
Did you know that
during Summer’s last breath,
she was waiting for you.
What?
Are you tired?
Do you want to rest now?
You're still waiting for her?
I'm sorry, Summer.
Mom can't go home.
It’s okay, Solar.
Your mom’s gonna be fine.
It’s okay.
I should have been there.
I’m sorry I wasn’t.
It’s okay.
She died happily.
Our good girl.
And I’m sure
she’s at peace now, too.
And she left another angel here.
You know what, she reminds me
so much of Summer.
Yeah. Solar, my baby.
She’s a sweet reminder
that I once had Summer.
Yup? Hello?
Yeah, okay.
Let’s finalize that.
I’m sure Yanna will like it.
Okay. Yeah, bye.
That was Luna. She just needed
to confirm something.
Yanna’s gonna have
a bachelorette party.
Can I come?
What? Of course not!
That’s for girls only.
Hiro’s having
a bachelor party too
and I’m sure
there’ll be girls there.
It’s the same with Yanna,
so all’s fair.
If you’re inviting other men,
then invite me too.
No way.
You don’t get it.
We will have fun with—
Why? Can’t you have fun with me?
It’s not like that.
Okay.
Well, have fun and
enjoy the party.
Just behave and promise me
you’ll be a good girl.
Or else?
Or else,
you’re gonna
have fun with me too.
They’re here.
- Be careful.
- You walk too fast.
Okay, I’m sorry.
Wait, I’ll just close the door.
Okay…
Okay.
You’re making me nervous.
What is this, Samantha?
Don’t be nervous.
You’re safe with me, come on.
Okay, stand here.
Are you ready?
What is this? What is this?
Okay.
Can I open my eyes now?
- Surprise!
Welcome to your
bachelorette party!
Bitch, I thought I got kidnapped!
You guys really went all out.
As if you’re not
used to being blindfolded.
Why? You’re not Hiro,
you know?
Excuse me!
Seriously, guys!
You really went all out!
I don’t even know how
I deserve friends like you.
I love you guys!
- I love you too!
You know, if younger
Yanna heard this,
she’d be grossed out. She was
so grumpy back then.
Okay guys, enough with
the drama. Let’s party!
- Yes.
- But, before we start…
You’re gonna love this. Look!
- Okay, okay.
- What’s this?
You need to put this on.
- Wow!
- Oh!
Are you serious?
Wait, not just that.
This too.
Oh my gosh.
This is the best part!
Is this it, guys?
Come on, this is too easy.
What’s going on?
Are you ready?
Now blow.
Oh my god!
- Blow it!
Blow it!
- Just the tip! Just the tip!
Is it good?
You guys are too much!
This is way too sweet!
Oh my god. Here it comes!
Here it comes!
Oh my god!
- What is this? Where’s Hiro?
- Yes!
Oh my god, this is too much!
Girl, just enjoy it!
Hiro’s having
fun too! It’s okay.
Lower.
- Oh, that’s good!
- Lower.
Girl, you still have
icing on your lips!
Wipe it off!
- Oh my god!
- What are you guys doing?
Take it off, good sir!
- Via, look!
- He’s too much.
- He’s showing off his abs!
- Hiro… Hiro…
Oh my god!
They’re so wild.
Okay, shake it. Shake it!
Haze: The party’s
starting here.
I invited your ex.
It’s a little unfair for him
to just let you have fun
on your own, don’t you think?
Sam: What?
You better make sure
he will go home safely! Do not
let him drink too much!
Haze: He could say
the same to you.
We’re just on the
other side of the hallway,
but follow the rules.
You can’t go here,
and they can’t go there.
Everybody, be quiet!
I’m drunk.
It’s fine! Go girl! Enjoy it!
Yes!
- Wait! What’s happening?
- Oh my god!
I’m bleeding, Sam!
- Huh?
- Oh my god, oh my god.
Boys, stop! Stop!
You can leave now.
Go, go, go, go!
Hold on.
Wait, hold on.
What’s happening?
I’m so dizzy.
Wait.
- Girls.
- What’s going on?
She needs help.
Don’t touch it.
Oh my god. Wait.
Sam: Sorry to disturb you.
Do you have a first aid kit
or something?
Cy: Yeah, I have one in my bag. Why?
Sam: There’s a minor accident
here in the girls’ suite.
We need help.
Cy: On my way.
Okay, okay.
Don’t worry.
Help is on the way.
That’s fine. Just don’t touch it.
Don’t touch it.
Guys. How are you?
What happened?
She’s wounded.
- Yanna! How are you?
- Hi!
What’s he doing here?
He’ll treat—
Okay, let’s go now.
- Let’s go, you’re drunk.
- Hey!
You’re taking her home already?
Yeah, she’s drunk.
Guys, you can continue
the party, okay?
Enjoy!
No—
Be careful.
We’ll be in the bedroom, guys.
You can take care of yourselves.
Okay.
You too?
Yeah. I’m sorry, I’m heading
to another party.
- But—
- Can I see?
Just what in the world were
you doing to end up like that?
Why do you care?
Just go to the nearest hospital.
Just to be sure.
Okay.
All right. I’ll take her there.
Wait! Hey, let me go.
Wait.
Her sh—
Her shoes.
They’re all gone.
So,
are you going to sleep here?
Well, I have my own hotel room,
but I think I’ll take
care of the girls.
Who knows what might happen.
You know, just
call somebody else
to take care of them.
And then let’s go to your room.
I don’t think I can drive
home anymore.
Oh shit.
Just call somebody else.
Okay.
Hey, Samantha.
What time do you think it is?
Sev! Sev! This is urgent.
Can you please
come to the hotel?
Yeah, and please take care of—
Luna! Via, ‘cause—
What am I, a babysitter?
Why? What happened
over there?
Well, they’re super drunk and
I can’t look after them, so—
Damn it! I’m sure
Luna’s too far gone.
Go ahead, keep drinking
until you pass out!
Next time, I’ll let St. Peter
watch over her!
Okay, I’ll just get ready.
Yes! Thanks, Sev.
Please, please come here.
Take care.
No, no…
- Okay! I’ll wait for you, okay?
- Oh my god.
Take care!
Did you have fun?
Yeah. It was chaotic.
But you know what?
I feel bad for Yanna.
I don’t even know
if she liked it or not.
Did you have fun
with the macho dancers?
I don’t mind.
As long as you
had fun with them.
Did you?
Yes.
Well, do you mind
extending the fun with me?
Do you wanna shower with me?
Maureen.
I love you.
I still do.
Eyes on the camera, Sam!
Good. Nice!
You’re doing great.
Energy, Sam. Energy.
More energy!
Okay, continue.
Eyes on the camera.
We’re good. Thank you.
Sam, we’ve got the shot!
See the photos?
Nice!
I don’t think I’ve seen
you like this before.
You’re really shining today.
You seem inspired.
In love or dating?
I’m just happy.
Thanks for today.
Thanks as well.
Hold on a sec, okay?
I’ll just fix my stuff there.
- Yeah. I’ll see you.
- Okay, bye.
I’ll see you later.
Sam: I’m flying to
Coron this weekend
for Yanna and Hiro’s wedding.
I’m staying there for three days.
You really can’t come?
Cy: I’m sorry. I really
want to, but I can’t go.
Sam: It’s okay.
I knew that already,
but I still wanted
to ask you.
Cy: Enjoy the wedding.
Cy: Take care, love.
Sam! Your New York
rental apartment application
got approved!
So, what now? Should we
pay the down payment?
Part of me wants to stay in Manila.
To be with Cy.
To hold on to what we have.
But then,
there’s New York.
With all its possibilities
and opportunities.
Send the landlord
the holding deposit for now
to reserve the apartment.
Okay.
This is it! It’s your
wedding day. Are you nervous?
Who wouldn’t be nervous?
You know, I really thought
you’d be the first one
among us to get married.
I probably wouldn’t be
this nervous
if you had already
gone through it.
Well, shit happens.
Just enjoy your wedding day
with the love of your life.
You waited a long
time for this, right?
And lucky you,
you found someone to love,
and who’ll love you
for the rest of your life.
And then Avi came as a bonus.
In a life filled with
unexpected twists and turns,
it’s a miracle when two people
who truly love each other
make it to their wedding day.
Where did you
even get that line?
But you’re right.
It feels so good knowing
we’re finally getting married.
Right?
So instead of worrying,
just put your trust
in your relationship.
Everything will work out.
I’m so glad you’re my maid
of honor and my best friend.
Out of all the maids of honor,
you’re the first honor.
- I know, right?
- I know.
You look so gorgeous!
Everything is on point!
Yeah, such a goddess.
Thanks, guys.
You know what, I still can’t
believe Yanna’s old motto,
“flirt responsibly,”
actually brought her here.
You’ll be officially
a wife in an hour!
Yanna, I know there’s going to
be “kiss the bride” part later.
There are kids,
so keep it PG, okay?
Hey, I can’t promise that.
After all, I’ll be married already.
Thank you, guys.
I may be the first one
to get married—
but I’m claiming it now.
All of us will get married
and have our own
happily ever afters
with people who truly love us.
Group hug?
Come here.
Come here, you talk too much.
- Guys, let’s take a photo!
- So pretty!
One, two, three, smile!
Hello, Princess.
So, are you back together?
Are you two the
next ones to get married?
Not exactly. Why?
Are you waiting for us
to get back together?
Are you playing cupid now?
That’s not my thing at all.
I just think that
when two people
clearly love each other,
they should stop with all the
bullshit and just be together.
Right?
Ma’am, Sir.
We’re about to start,
so please fall in line.
Look at Sam,
she’s already in tears
just seeing Yanna walk.
You’d think she’s
the one getting married.
This is it Yannah.
I’m so happy for you.
When I look back at my life,
I realize
all the moments I cherish
the most are with you.
And I want to spend
the rest of my days
creating more important
memories with you and Avi.
I know life is far from perfect,
but I promise you this, Yanna.
I will love you more
than any amount of distance
that will keep us apart.
I remember when I was a kid—
I didn’t believe in true love.
And I believed
no one would ever love me.
But deep inside my heart,
I always wanted
to be loved and seen.
Then all of a sudden,
you came into my life.
Who are you checking out?
Right there.
OMG, girl. That’s Hiro!
You changed everything
I believed about love.
Because of you,
I started to believe in love.
You made love look so easy.
And from this day on,
I’ll keep reminding you
how much I love you—
how much Avi and I love you.
I promise,
it’s only going to be you
for the rest of my life.
We will love you
above and beyond
what airplanes could ever fly.
Ashianna Fernandez
and Avrielle Haven,
I love you above and beyond
airplanes could ever fly.
I pronounce you
husband and wife.
You may now kiss the bride.
More!
- More!
One more!
More!
Good afternoon,
ladies and gentlemen.
Please help me welcome
Samantha Maureen Vera
to say some heartfelt words
for the newlyweds.
Well, hey to the both of you.
So, I don’t know how to start.
I just want to tell you, Hiro, that
I’m Avrielle’s first dad.
You know what,
I actually hated you back then
because I saw how
Yanna cried her eyes out
every night because of you.
Ever since you started that
little deal between
the two of you,
I already knew that she
would fall for you because
who wouldn’t?
But she wanted to prove
that she was strong.
Well, she’s an idiot.
But even if she is,
she loves you so much.
Hiro, please take care
of my best friend.
Not that you need me
to remind you, but
she’s very special to me.
She may look so
strong on the outside,
but she’s really fragile.
So,
please stop making her
cry because of pain.
Well, you can make her
cry for other reasons.
Kidding aside,
I wish genuine happiness
for both of you.
Raise Avrielle well.
And know that I’ll always
be here for you
if you need any help, okay?
Cheers!
- Cheers!
Go, Auntie!
Wow.
Thank you, Sam.
Thank you.
I love you, my best friend.
I love you.
Thank you so much for being
with me on this journey.
I’m always here for you.
I’m always here for
both of you and for Avi,
if you need any help. Okay?
Come here, you.
You had a rough time
or something?
Well, it was kind of rough.
He was rough.
Thank you for trusting me.
Only a few friends and
family know I’m bisexual.
You should feel honored.
Cy doesn’t know?
No.
It’s not like
I’m hiding it from them.
But if they asked,
I would’ve answered honestly.
I do get seen with
other men a lot.
Yeah, you’re right.
Why? Why’d you ask?
Are you jealous of me?
I know I’m hot and a flirt, but
I don’t like your guy.
Dude, I have a type, okay?
Really? So what’s your type?
In girls or guys?
Well, in girls,
it’s pretty simple.
You.
I liked you at first glance.
Did you really like me, or
did you just want
a one-night stand back then?
I genuinely liked you.
Honestly,
if I hadn’t met Clyden first,
I would’ve fallen for you.
But it’s a good thing
I met him before you.
You probably
would’ve just hurt me
or left me in tears.
You’re right.
I’m not the type for
a long-term relationship.
What about you? Are you okay?
Is something bothering you?
Well,
I’m leaving for
New York in a few weeks.
I want to settle down there.
There are more
opportunities there, and
I won’t have to keep flying back
and forth anymore.
I’m just really
worried about Clyden.
I’m sure he can manage.
I heard he’s busy
with residency.
So even if you stay,
your relationship
would still be stuck.
That guy’s passionate
about his dreams.
And so are you.
Time isn’t on your side yet.
It just
pains me to leave him again.
I wish I hadn’t
come back at all if
I was only going
to leave him again, right?
But he said
I should still hold on to him,
even if
I will leave him in the end.
Well, if he knows about it,
then he should be ready.
You are your own woman.
If you want to settle
somewhere else,
then go.
Do it.
It’s your life.
You’re right.
It’s selfish to actually
make him wait for me, right?
Maybe I should just let him go
if I don’t even
plan on coming back.
Well,
I don’t know. I’m not him.
But if I were really
in love with you,
you wouldn’t even
have to ask me to wait.
I’d wait for you.
Maybe I’m just
fucking dumb like that.
Thank you for coming.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Take care.
Well?
The conversation seems
a bit too serious.
Let’s wait for them.
Yeah.
- Finally.
- Long live the newlyweds!
Congratulations, you guys!
Thank you.
All right, let’s play!
Let's go!
Truth or dare.
Okay.
- Let’s go.
- Game.
Awesome!
- Truth!
- Go!
- Let’s go.
- Okay.
Are you and Haze dating?
No!
How lame, that was easy.
Okay. My turn.
Who’s next?
Yanna.
- Yanna.
Okay, truth!
- So, truth?
- Oo. Truth, truth.
Okay.
Who was your first kiss?
Ouch!
Who?
I’ll just drink.
I poured a lot
just for you guys.
Okay, drink.
- Bottoms up.
- Drink, drink, drink!
- Bottoms up!
That was quick.
Bitch!
Okay, next!
Me again? What the heck?
Okay, fine.
Truth!
Okay, you already did truth earlier.
Go for a dare this time.
Hey!
- No coaching.
- Okay, okay.
How about this?
Send an extreme confession to
the last person you messaged.
Something you haven’t
told anyone, okay?
Even to Yanna.
Go on.
- The last person.
- Go on.
Fine, whatever.
Sam: I still want to marry you
and have kids with you.
What the heck,
that’s so wholesome!
Come on, it’s an
extreme confession.
Okay.
- Oh, he replied immediately.
- What did he say?
I’d rather read it by myself.
- Excuse me.
- What?
That’s unfair.
- Let us in on it.
- Such a buzzkill.
Why did you even play?
Cy: Are you drunk?
Sam: It’s a confession.
Cy: Do you still love me?
Cy: Never mind. Don’t say it.
It’s better this way.
Now that I’ve confessed,
what’s next?
The decision is still on me.
Who’s next?
Your turn again!
Someone else should be next.
- Okay, someone else.
- Okay, let’s go.
- This is the last.
- Go.
Okay, for real this time.
- Truth or Dare?
- Dare?
Send—
Wow!
Avi, be good to Auntie, okay?
Yes!
We have lots of goodies for
you when we get back.
I love you, mommy and daddy!
We love you, Avi!
All right you guys,
you might miss your flight.
Thanks a lot, Sam.
Anytime. Enjoy your honeymoon.
- Bye now.
- Bye!
Take care, guys.
Bye.
Eat your ice cream.
Is it yummy?
Yes.
Auntie, can we go somewhere too?
Okay, baby.
But let’s just do
it tomorrow, okay?
It’s a bit late now.
Okay, eat your ice cream.
Cy: Hi. You’re back
in Manila?
Sam: Yes, I arrived a while ago.
Cy: Can we meet
tomorrow morning?
I’ll be at the hospital.
Sam: Okay. I’m going to bring Avi.
She’s staying with me for a few days.
Cy: All right. See you.
It’s going to be the last few
times we’ll see each other.
That’s good. Thank you.
Hey.
Avi, do you remember
Doctor Clyden Ramirez?
Hello, Doc!
Hi, Avi.
Oh, hi.
Daddy said you only
kiss people you like.
Do you like Auntie?
Yeah.
I like your Auntie.
Is that okay?
It’s okay.
Do you want to know a secret?
I will become just like you!
Really? You want to become
a doctor too?
Yes!
I thought you wanted to be
a pilot like your daddy?
I will be a pilot-doctor!
Okay.
But if you want
to be a pilot-doctor,
you need to eat
a lot of veggies
and get plenty of sleep
so you can stay healthy.
- Okay?
- Okay, Uncle.
I’ll get lots of sleep
and eat many veggies.
Uncle?
How was the wedding?
It was so beautiful.
I cried many tears of joy.
We played truth or dare, too.
Yeah.
Is that why you sent that message?
Yes. But honestly, I felt
that way nonetheless.
Auntie, you said we’re
going somewhere fun.
Yes, baby. We’re going
there later, okay?
I’m free for
the rest of the day.
Can Uncle join you guys?
- You want to?
- Both!
Yeah. Both?
- Both?
- Yeah!
- Both of us?
- Yeah.
Auntie, thank you for bringing
me here. I’m so excited!
Really?
Hold on, guys, go there.
Okay.
Excuse me. Reservation
for Samantha Vera.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
She’s so excited.
- Let’s go.
- Let’s go, baby.
Be careful.
I got the cheese!
Good job, baby!
Auntie’s not getting anything!
- Teach Auntie how to do it.
- Go, I want more!
I got that fair and square.
She got one.
We got four both. It’s a tie.
- Go, Auntie! Go!
- Go, go!
Go! Auntie, go!
There you go.
We’re awesome!
Auntie, I wanna do the bazooka.
Maybe next time baby, okay?
Hey, how about the goo catcher?
Okay!
Samantha Vera?
OMG. It really is Samantha Vera!
- Can we get a photo with you?
- It really is her!
- Can we get a photo?
- Yeah, sure.
- Just don’t include them.
- Avi, come on. Stay here.
Thank you.
Let’s go.
- Wait a minute.
- Oh no.
It went blank.
- Thank you.
But who’s that with her?
Yeah, that’s not Haze.
How did you two meet?
Are you together?
Avi, come here.
Are you the son
of Christopher Ramirez?
The owner of Ramirez Medical?
The one who topped
the board exams, right?
Samantha Vera, are you
cheating on Haze Juarez?
Doc, you’re trending
online right now.
I don’t know what
you’re referring to,
but sir, can we please
focus on your health?
We both know you’re
really the useless one
between the two of us.
Fuck you. Asshole!
We’re not even close
with the Vera family anymore
and we even cancelled
the engagement of our son.
Why aren't you answering me?
I’m sorry.
He’s already
struggling with his life
without our support,
and a scandal like this
will burden him even more.
So please don’t add to it.
If you find someone else,
I hope she can truly make you happy.
Don’t cry now, baby.
You’re making me cry, too.
Let me hold you, bestie.
You’re making us all cry.