ظآزI've braved the storms, walked through the rainظآز
ظآزSeen the highs and lows along the wayظآز
ظآزBut you stay quiet, never changeظآز
ظآزLike a child who dreams beneath the starsظآز
ظآزI've read the story in your eyesظآز
ظآزAnd finally, nothing's left to hideظآز
ظآزYou won't give in to a world so coldظآز
ظآزSo you wander through it on your ownظآز
ظآزMaybe fate has drawn us nearظآز
ظآزJust to help you learn to believeظآز
ظآزEverything you've questioned deep insideظآز
ظآزI'll be the proof you needظآز
ظآزI've made my choiceظآز
ظآزFor you, I'll be brave and break the rulesظآز
ظآزWhat's there to fear even if the world is right and I am wrong?ظآز
ظآزOne day, all of this will turn into memoriesظآز
ظآزEvery storm we faced will turn into our life's sceneryظآز
ظآزFor you, I'll be brave and break the rulesظآز
ظآزWhat's there to fear even if the world is right and I am wrong?ظآز
ظآزEven if, in the end, the whole world turns against meظآز
ظآزI won't regret having loved youظآز
ظآزWith all my heartظآز
ظآزI've held you closeظآز
ظآزWalked by your sideظآز
ظآزAnd loved the fire that burned inside youظآز
[The First Frost]
[Adapted from the novel of the same name by Zhu Yi on www.jjwxc.net]
I heard that someone saw them holding hands
on the first day of school.
Really?
- For real? - Yes.
Are you serious?
No wonder
they've been late together these past couple of days.
Rumor has it they were already a thing in middle school.
Middle school?
That's interesting.
Yeah.
But isn't that too early for middle schoolers?
Guess that's just the way it is these days.
Girls, let's hurry up.
The boys will be coming in to change soon.
Did you hear
what they said?
Are you just going to let them gossip?
What else can I do?
Do you think those guys
have a crush on you?
Are you
not changing into your sports uniform?
I am.
ظآزBaby, I want to give my all to youظآز
ظآزNo more tears from now onظآز
Why are you secretly following me?
I'm following you openly.
Wen Yifan
do you know
there's a profession called a pacer?
I don't.
A pacer is someone who runs with others to help them train.
ظآزI'm completely captivated by youظآز
I can't go on.
So, are you
my pacer?
You're the one
pacing me.
Can't run anymore?
Your shoelace came undone.
ظآزI love youظآز
[Episode 4]
[Rumors]
ظآزI love youظآز
[3063 Days]
[Day 1 of official cohabitation]
Helping with the move, sir?
- Yes, 1701. - Don't move.
Sorry about that, you go first.
What's going on?
Sorry.
What's going on here?
Nothing
just adding some furniture.
That's quite a lot.
Enjoying the sunshine?
Sorry, this isn't mine.
Your boyfriend told me to put this here.
Did they deliver this to the wrong address?
It was a bundle deal with a discount.
The cat tree was a free add-on.
If you don't need it, feel free to get rid of it.
ظآزThe dust of lies and your woundsظآز
ظآزAll hide in your eyesظآز
ظآزJot down the wishes you've made beforeظآز
ظآزWill you cherish my heartظآز
ظآزWhich belongs only to you...ظآز
ظآزDon't wander off in your dreamsظآز
Dian
Sang Yan got this for you.
ظآزIf I kiss you through lightظآز
That's a lot.
[18
ظآزCan you hold me in your freezing night?ظآز
ظآزDon't you ever hideظآز
[Accept Transfer]
[520. Accept transfer]
What's this supposed to mean?
Here, play with this.
This is the money I'm returning to you.
Why is it such an awkward amount?
[Expense Breakdown]
Don't misunderstand.
This is the expense breakdown.
You sent more than necessary
so I returned the extra.
Do you
want to double-check?
[18
[200 for electricity, 90 for water, 105 for internet
[200 for property management, and 900 for parking]
Would he think I did it on purpose?
It's okay, I understand.
It's just a miscalculation.
This is beyond embarrassing.
Thanks for reminding me.
Sorry, I...
It should have been 505.
I sent 10
no, 40
I mean 15 more by mistake.
You can just refund me on WeChat.
Why did I send him 520 and make it look like a love confession?
I'd rather be a fool and send 250 instead.
Qiao.
Mom
why are you calling when we're both at home?
Is breakfast ready?
You're thinking about breakfast?
You were out all night
and now you wantظخ?
I
was out the whole night?
Mom, I'll hang up now.
I'll be home soon.
Why was the curtain suddenly opened?
How did I end up here?
Who are you?
Why are you here?
How should I know?
What's wrong with you?
Sang Yan
I guess you're not completely heartless.
I already gave you the pickup code.
I don't want the bag anymore.
You can leave now.
We used to go to the same school
so I thought I'd check in on you.
Are you okay?
Does drinking like that even taste good?
Don't worry.
That's just how he is after a breakup.
We
are all used to watching him chase after lost causes.
Pass me the drink.
Here's your whiskey.
Go easy on it.
Stop nagging. I can hold my liquor.
Then I'll drink with you.
What do you want?
Where are my clothes?
How would I know where your clothes are?
This is your place. Why are you asking me?
Did
we...?
We didn't.
It's all a blur.
I can't remember.
We probably didn't if I don't remember.
We definitely didn't.
I'm sure of it.
Yes. That's good.
What's that supposed to mean?
What?
I could be the one being taken advantage of.
Where's my top?
Did you hide it?
What about my clothes then?
Stop running around my house!
Your place is such a mess.
That's why I told you not to run around.
How did I even get in here?
See?
Please explain
why you're following me.
The driver made me get out of the car.
Wasn't it you who brought me back to your place?
You were throwing up so badly.
[The main entrance to the Upper District]
I just helped you up.
I didn't want you to come with me.
You could have just let me sleep there.
Why did you help me?
Do you think I'm that kind of person?
Of course, I had to help you up
but I didn't expect you
to cling to me.
[Outside the elevator]
Why did you carry me on your back?
I never said I would carry you.
You got on my back by yourself.
Show me the proof.
- Why are you blaming me? - Keep playing.
Keep playing.
You even asked me to dance.
Look at yourself.
[Inside the elevator]
Honestly
from what I saw on the footage
it looked like a mutual thing.
So, why is it
no longer mutual now?
None of your business.
Just keep watching.
[Outside the elevator on the third floor]
Bye.
Our cameras
can only monitor up to here.
What happened
after you closed the door
is out of our hands.
We didn't do anything.
Help yourself.
Dig in.
Why aren't you eating?
You...
Is it not to your taste?
No.
I'll eat it.
We've cleared up the misunderstanding.
Come on, let's have a toast.
[Xiang Lang: Qiao, I've landed. Where are you?]
All right, I'll be there soon.
I'm done eating.
I'm off.
On the right.
How do you open this door?
It's probably because of the dry weather lately.
Thanks.
He drinks such high-quality coffee.
Hello, Qiao.
Dian
I've found you a roommate.
A roommate?
Dian.
Xiang Lang?
Didn't I ask you to hide?
Now there's no surprise.
It's still a surprise.
Qiao, how come
you didn't even tell me?
I told you before, okay?
I've told you several times
that he's coming back.
You just didn't listen to me properly.
I might have accidentally forgotten.
Where are you guys now?
At the airport.
I originally thought of
asking you to come pick him up with me
but they said they were worried about you being busy with work
and didn't want you to get up so early.
Morning.
I did just wake up.
Xiang Lang also needs to rent a place now that he's back.
Maybe you two could be roommates?
I forgot to tell you
but I found a roommate.
Who is it?
Should we pick a day
to hang out together?
We definitely should.
It's been years.
How about Thursday?
I'm not working that day.
Just don't bail on us.
Don't worry. I won't.
Thursday it is then.
Bye.
Love you.
Are you going out?
My old friend, Xiang Lang
is back in the country.
We were in Class 17 in high school
and he and Qiao were in Class 15.
The three of us
grew up together in kindergarten.
You must know him, right?
It doesn't ring a bell.
Have you picked a spot for the gathering?
Not yet.
How about Overtime?
Since we're roommates
you can help bring in more customers.
Has your business gotten so bad
that you need to personally bring in customers?
I've told you before that it's not making much money.
We have to find ways to promote it
and get more customers.
What do you think?
I can give you a roommate discount.
What's the discount?
Let's say
1 percent.
Come again?
How generous.
I'll consider it.
It's decided then.
Thursday.
I've saved you a spot for Thursday.
Honestly, the first time I went to your gastropub
I spent ages looking for it.
It took me forever to find the Overtime sign.
I didn't exactly want to walk in
looking at it from the outside.
What do you mean?
I just mean the sign isn't obvious
and it doesn't really look like a place to eat.
It looks more like a barbershop.
But of course
that's just my personal opinion.
No need to take it to heart.
Since it was so unnoticeable and so bad
why did you come in the first place?
Headliner.
Oh, it's because you...
I got it.
I'll think about your comment
but I won't change it.
Thursday, okay?
[First News, All Ears for You]
So, here's the story.
Since she's my roommate
I didn't feel right saying no
so I ended up buying these low-quality products from her.
She's clearly taking advantage of me.
I'm going to sue her
and I won't stop until she loses everything.
A 1 percent discount.
Isn't that taking advantage of me, too?
She swindled all my savings away.
I worked for two years to earn that money.
What's the rush?
She took all of it
a total of 50
You seem a bit down recently.
Here's a coffee for you.
Thank you, Mr. Zhang.
No worries.
Eat this
to regain some energy.
Isn't eating not allowed in the cutting room?
I call the shots in this room.
Eat.
Thanks.
This software
has a shortcut key.
Here, let me show you.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, I...
Sorry, I'll go find someone to clean this up.
Is that necessary?
Everyone knows what you are like.
Let's go.
Wen
you've seen the newspaper today, right?
Your article wasn't included.
Sorry, sir.
I'll keep trying my best.
It's actually quite simple.
Do you know
where
the problem lies?
I know
but I can't do it.
Also, please don't text me
in the middle of the night anymore.
Yifan
why are you here alone?
Are you okay?
Or have you heard about it?
Heard about what?
Lately, everyone's been gossiping about you.
They say when you were at Yihe Daily
the boss's wife came after you
and then the local press blacklisted you.
You couldn't handle it anymore
so you secretly returned to Nanwu.
Those who spread rumors really overestimate me
saying I was blacklisted.
Pretty girls always get caught up in rumors like this.
I've told them that it's definitely not true.
You should go explain it to them quickly.
Do you think they'll believe me even if I explain?
You vixen, wait and see how I deal with you today.
Get out of the way!
You're Wen Yifan, aren't you?
You vixen.
You're the one who sent late-night messages
to flirt with my husband, right?
Shameless!
You shameless wretch!
What are you doing with your phone?
Let me tell you.
I won't believe a word you say today!
Take a good look.
It's your husband who's been sending me messages
and I've never replied with anything inappropriate.
I don't want to hear your nonsense.
You'll see
how I deal with you today.
It takes two to tango.
Keep this up, and you'll make the headlines.
It's clearly the wrongdoer's fault
yet the victim
bears the blame.
Do you really believe
those words were said unconsciously because he was drunk?
I'll write an investigation report and send it
to the president
and the newly formed supervisory committee.
However, I'm not sure
what the result will be.
Why?
He must have his side of the story.
After all, this isn't the first time.
But if you don't say anything
they'll assume you're admitting it.
Whether I admit it or not
they'll only believe
what they want to believe.
Rumors are like wounds.
If you don't pay attention to them
they'll stop hurting after a while.
Don't worry about me.
I'm fine.
What time is it now?
It's almost three o'clock.
I'll go out for an interview now.
All right, Mr. Chen, let's get started.
Could you walk us through
what happened during the incident?
That night
my daughter was helping me out
at the snack stall after school.
Three men at a table were drunk.
My daughter's only sixteen
but they kept harassing her.
At that moment, all I could think
was if they laid a finger on her
I'd...
Dad.
- Are you okay? - Dad.
- Careful. - I'm fine.
Are you all right, Dad?
It's all my fault.
You are hurt because of me.
This injury's nothing.
I'd be heartbroken
if I hadn't kept you safe.
It's because of me.
It's all my fault.
It's not your fault.
Yifan
this child is only sixteen.
Yet their family had to go through such an ordeal.
It's like misfortune always targets the most vulnerable.
But I filmed everything that happened just now.
That kid was crying, and it was heartbreaking.
Wen Yifan?
It really is you.
How come you're back in Nanwu?
I moved back to Nanwu.
- Yifan, maybe I should... - No need.
We're busy right now.
Let's get in touch later.
Who do you think you are?
Who wants to get in touch with you?
Yifan, how about I go back to the car first and sort things out?
You guys can chat.
Thank you.
Why are you back if there's nothing wrong?
Why can't I come back even if nothing's wrong?
I didn't mean it that way.
Don't worry
I won't be staying at your place now that I'm back in Nanwu.
Let's just pretend we never met today.
As long as you don't say anything, no one will know.
I never said you couldn't come to my place.
You didn't.
Why are you being so annoying?
Fine.
I was at fault back then.
I was young and didn't know better.
I was wrong to ask you to leave my house.
All right.
I don't want to bring up the past
nor do I think we need to catch up.
That stuff is heavy, right?
Go check on the patient.
Will you go back home for the Spring Festival?
I have to work during the Spring Festival.
All right, let's add each other on WeChat.
No need.
I just want to live my own life.
You...
My return to Nanwu has nothing to do with anyone.
I won't stay at your place
and it's not because I'm afraid of you.
Every decision I make is for myself.
I'm actually busy. I'll get going now.
Dad, look.
It's snowing outside.
It really is snowing.
Pretty, isn't it?
Yes.
Isn't it lovely?
It is.
Are you happy?
Yes.
Let's have a snowball fight later.
It's snowing.
Let me lift you up.
Jiang, do you know
how you got your nickname?
I don't.
It's because
you were born
on the day of Frost's Descent.
What exactly is Frost's Descent?
Frost's Descent happens
in late September of the lunar calendar
when the sun
is farther away
from Earth.
It's the day
with the largest temperature difference
between day and night
making the night
particularly cold.
But I'm afraid of the cold.
Don't be afraid, Jiang
I'm here.
ظآزLeaving me lost in the crowdظآز
ظآزBefore we metظآز
ظآزEvery long night was meaninglessظآز
When you're cold, just come to me.
I'll hold you tight
and you won't feel cold anymore.
ظآزThe things we lose will be returned in the endظآز
ظآزAll the detoursظآز
ظآزAre part of the journeyظآز
ظآزWhat was lostظآز
ظآزWill be regainedظآز
ظآزI'll wait for you, so don't worryظآز
ظآزAbout being late.ظآز
Wen Yifan
I have a little flaw
about me.
Only one?
I'm very safety-conscious.
If I don't lock the door before going to bed
I can't sleep.
I always lock the door.
If you're tired, go ahead and sleep.
I'll lock it if I get back late.
I'm talking about before sleeping.
I remember telling you explicitly
before we started sharing the apartment
that I frequently work overtime
and have an irregular routine. You agreed to it.
Then please let me know
in advance
if you're coming back after 10 p.m.
Why?
It's a matter of mutual respect.
If you don't come back all night
wouldn't I
have to spend the night in anxiety and fear?
I'll let you know next time.
Can I go rest now?
Who is he?
I forgot to tell you.
He's my friend.
Hi
I am Duan Jiaxu.
I heard from Su Haoan
that Sang Yan didn't date a single girl during his four years at university.
He spent all his time hanging out with a campus heartthrob
named Duan Jiaxu.
Duan Jiaxu
I've heard a lot about you.
I also have a flaw:
my safety awareness is stronger than someone else's
and I remember we have a contract clause.
I don't quite recall.
You should inform me in advance before bringing friends home.
All right.
I remember now.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
We're still getting used
to living together
so small mistakes are excusable.
I'll let it slide this time.
You two catch up.
I told you to leave earlier, but you didn't listen.
You even spilled food on your clothes.
So, where do you think we should go on Thursday?
How about Overtime?
It's opened by Sang Yan.
Sang Yan?
You are still in touch?
I only met him recently
and it was at his gastropub.
So, uh
I need to tell you something.
Remember I told you I have a roommate?
Well, that roommate
is Sang Yan.
He said if we go to his place, he'll give us a discount.
You're actually sharing a place with Sang Yan?
And what discount do we get?
Let's talk about it when we meet.
I still have to get some work done tonight.
I'm going to log off now.
Wait. How much of a discount are we getting?
1 percent.
1 percent?
I'll log off now. Bye.
Wait, did I hear that right?
Is a 1 percent discount still considered a discount?
Let's go with Dian's choice this time.
We've always picked the places before.
It's rare for her to have an opinion.
You're totally on her side, huh?
Wait until we meet
I'll crack open her brain
and see what's going on in there.
Why would she share a place with Sang Yan?
I really don't get it.
It's getting late, Qiao.
You should go to bed now.
All right, then.
Goodnight.
Night.
Hello.
Dian, are you ready?
We're here.
You are already here?
So soon? Just give me a moment.
The car isn't allowed to enter
so I've just parked it at the entrance.
All right, I just finished washing the clothes.
I'll be out as soon as I hang them up.
It's okay. No rush.
Take your time.
Who says there's no rush?
I'm about to die of hunger.
Dian, hurry up.
I'll save your life in a minute. Got to go now.
Hey
did you save a spot for us at Overtime?
We're going to eat first.
We'll be at Overtime around eight.
Are you heading out too?
When did you change your clothes?
Are you going to the garage?
Well...
We haven't reached the basement level yet.
This is the first floor.
[Uptown Flower City]
Let's go.
Dian.
It's been a while.
Why are you two acting shy?
The Nanwu Trio is finally united.
From now on, we'll overcome all obstacles and be invincible.
Who is this?
Is this your boyfriend?
What boyfriend?
This is Xiang Lang.
Xiang Lang.
I remember.
You are from Class 15.
Yes.
- I'm Su Haoan. - Hi.
Sang Yan.
Long time no see.
Didn't we agree that you'd drive your car?
I can't be bothered to drive.
I drove here.
Where do you need to go?
It's fine.
We'll just find somewhere to eat.
Didn't you guys already make plans?
You can go ahead.
We really haven't met in a long time.
We should definitely catch up.
It's been a while since we last met as well.
Why make such a big deal of it?
You're not really close with them.
Even if we're not close, we can still catch up
right?
Yeah. So you want to go with them, right?
Is it all right?
I don't think so.
I think it's pretty all right.
Where's your car?
Open the door.
Yes, boss.
It's amazing how fate works.
You haven't seen a friend in seven or eight years
and then you just run into them like this.
If Sang Yan and Wen Yifan can be roommates
what else is impossible?
Since there are so many of us
I'll tidy up the car first.
I'll help you.
I know
this is definitely something worth bragging about.
What are you talking about?
There's no need to bring up
our shared rental to everyone.
We'll manage if the five of us squeeze a bit.
This should be all right.
Dian, you sit in the passenger seat
and help me with the navigation.
My legs are too long.
It's uncomfortable sitting in the back.
You can just go straight.
Okay.
It's fine, I'll sit in the back.
Is that okay?
Sure. No worries.
I can't see the road with you like this.
Well, then pay attention to the road.
Have you got a girlfriend?
No.
I still haven't met the person I like.
I just thought of a rumor.
Sang Yan, Xiang Lang, and Wen Yifan
they said you three were in a love triangle.
Is it true?
It was all just rumors.
It got passed on
and started to sound like it was real.
It simply wasn't true.
What do you mean by "sound like it was real?"
You're really into gossip and just making things up.
What I'm saying is true.
If you don't believe me, ask Sang Yan.
He even got into a fight over it.
I heard from Zhou Zhiming
that Pretty Face Wen doesn't actually like Sang Yan.
She only got together with him
because he kept pursuing her.
So, when she met someone better
she immediately cheated.
Who's better?
It's Xiang Lang from the class next door.
If I didn't tell you
would you think Pretty Face Wen is this kind of person?
It's really quite disgusting.
Indeed.
But why?
She thinks being good-looking makes her great.
There are a lot of good-looking people out there.
Surely they won't all act like this.
Let me tell you this.
With an attitude like yours
what's the point of being pretty?
Apologize.
I'm sorry.
I'm not asking you to apologize.
Zhou Zhiming
do I need to teach you?
I won't apologize.
I was just joking earlier
and I'm not the only one saying this.
Joking?
You're a man with such a sharp tongue
aren't you embarrassed?
Let me make this clear today.
If anyone dares spread such rumors again
the consequences will be the same as his.
I don't have many hobbies.
I just like holding grudges.
Talk.
Pretty Face Wen...
No
Wen Yifan
I'm sorry.
It was me who told others you were cheating
but I had no proof.
I was just making things up.
I won't say it again in the future.
Is that enough?
Can you let me go now?
What about me?
Am I not also a victim?
Sang Yan
I'm sorry.
Why are you a victim?
Can you spread rumors according to the facts?
What do you mean the other person found someone better
and dumped me?
If I were actually pursuing them that hard
they'd be completely
captivated by me.
Understand?
Yes.
Louder.
Yes!
Thank you.
He doesn't even know who's better.
Sang Yan has always been
a stickler for details since he was a kid.
He doesn't talk much
but whenever he does, he's ready to fight.
He has a terrible temper.
I'm all right.
See? He loves hitting others.
Wen Yifan
I'm sorry
I didn't tell you in advance
about Sang Yan moving in.
I heard it shocked you.
I'll pay for the meal later.
No need.
This has nothing to do with you.
Sang Yan
did you know in advance
that your roommate would be Dian?
Yes
that's why I decided to move in.
ظآزThe dust of lies and your woundsظآز
[Episode 4]
[I'll Dispel the Rumors for You]
ظآزJot down the wishes you've made beforeظآز
I thought of another rumor.
ظآزWhich belongs only to you...ظآز
ظآزDon't wander off in your dreamsظآز
[The story is not over yet...]
ظآزMy dear, don't say goodbyeظآز
ظآزCan you hold me in your freezing night?ظآز
ظآزDon't you ever hideظآز
ظآزThis time?ظآز
Why is she still here?
Excuse me.
Our dance class has booked this slot.
I think I still have ten more minutes left.
She's new here, isn't she?
Who cares whether she is or not?
Her dancing isn't impressive.
I don't know why she's trying so hard.
She's just arrogant.
We booked this dance studio.
Can you leave now?
You're just dancing around by yourself
taking up all this space.
It's really unnecessary.
Didn't she say there are still ten minutes left?
Also
who says she's by herself?
She even found someone to help her.
Does she really think she's so great?
So what if you've brought help?
Can you two just take over the whole dance studio?
Who is she?
I've never seen her before.
ظآزIf there are still nightmares, keep me by your sideظآز
ظآزI will be your moonlightظآز
ظآزSo you can rest peacefully with your eyes closedظآز
ظآزA child who loves to act toughظآز
ظآزGently coaxing you to slowly unravelظآز
ظآزAll the expectations that have been locked awayظآز
ظآزMy dear, don't say goodbyeظآز
ظآزEven the strongest heartظآز
ظآزCan waverظآز
ظآزAnd doubt its fireظآز
ظآزBut you never lost faith in meظآز
ظآزIn every battle, every dream I chasedظآز
ظآزThere is meaning in every step I madeظآز
ظآزThrough the storm, through the endless nightظآز
ظآزYou were there, shining like a lightظآز
ظآزWarm and brightظآز
ظآزStanding right by my sideظآز
ظآزIt was you, striding toward me through the stormظآز
ظآزIt was you, always cheering me onظآز
ظآزThe road is roughظآز
ظآزThe rain won't stopظآز
ظآزBut with you hereظآز
ظآزI fear no darkظآز
ظآزEvery thought, every memory is filled with youظآز
ظآزMarking our youth with every step we tookظآز
ظآزWhen the downpour falls from the skyظآز
ظآزYou're the one holding out an umbrella for meظآز
ظآزWhen the white dove brings the newsظآز
ظآزYou're the first I want to tellظآز
ظآزI won't give up. I'll stay right here with youظآز
ظآزIt was you, striding toward me through the stormظآز
ظآزIt was you, always cheering me onظآز
ظآزThe road is roughظآز
ظآزThe rain won't stopظآز
ظآزBut with you hereظآز
ظآزI will never give upظآز
ظآزYou are my courage, my hope for the sky beyondظآز
ظآزYou are my light, shining through every nightظآز
ظآزEven if I have to walk alone somedayظآز
ظآزI'll never truly be on my ownظآز
ظآز'Cause knowing you're hereظآز
ظآزI can brave the dark aheadظآز
[Huge thanks to everyone involved and to all the fans of The First Frost!]