KING THE LAND
RESUME
Is this you?
I put on a little weight.
I don't need a high salary.
I hope I don't have to stand all day.
I have flat feet.
- Excuse--
- Where do we eat?
Communication is key
for a hotel concierge.
Will you be able to communicate…
I'm super fluent in Korean.
I majored in political science
and international relations.
I will lead the conversations
from the guests' perspectives…
I'm shy. Please don't look at me.
Excuse me…
2015 KING HOTEL TRAINEESHIP INTERVIEW
Number 511, please come in.
What's with Number 511?
Don't we require a bachelor's degree?
I apologize.
There must've been a mistake
during the resume screening process.
Hello, I am interviewee number 511,
Cheon Sa-rang.
2015 KING HOTEL TRAINEESHIP INTERVIEW
Your hobby is playing the piano.
Can you play for us?
- Right now?
- Yes, right now.
But there's no piano here.
I know, right?
INTERVIEWER
Your hobby is playing the piano,
yet you played "Chopsticks."
It's my hobby, not my specialty.
I'm not that good, but I enjoy playing.
Can you smile for us?
Hey.
You really did that?
Yes. What else was I supposed to do?
But still, it was King Hotel.
You should've at least
played something by Beethoven.
Wonderful.
You pass.
Thank you, ma'am. I'll work hard.
Hey, Beethoven or Mozart.
None of that matters.
They require bachelor's degrees
from mere one-month trainees.
Then why did you go for the interview?
Just because.
I wondered how Korea's best hotel
conducted their interviews.
If you've satisfied your curiosity,
join me at the duty-free shop.
Don't listen to her.
Be a flight attendant with me.
No, I'm going to work in a hotel.
Come on. Why?
I just like hotels.
More than you like me?
Hey, you like nightclubs
more than you like me.
How upsetting.
How could you say that?
It can't be helped.
Let's go clubbing.
Right now?
Let's go where?
- Let's go!
- What are you talking about?
Excuse me.
I've been watching you for a while.
Would you care for a drink?
I'm sorry.
We were in the middle
of something important.
You can just give me your number.
Hey.
There we go.
I'll get in touch with you.
Hey, why would you
give your number to a stranger?
What do you mean by "stranger"?
We're acquainted now.
Didn't I tell you to start a relationship
after you developed feelings
instead of regretting it later?
Hey, love doesn't happen in stages.
I'm dying to know
who you'll get married to
with that mindset.
Are you crazy?
Why would I settle with one person
for the rest of my life?
Even the thought is frightening. Let's go.
Let's go.
I'll pass. I'm so tired.
- That's why you go clubbing.
- I mean…
You just got off your flight.
You should get some rest.
No sleep at all is better
than just a few hours.
Grab her.
- I'm not in the mood today.
- Goodness.
I'm feeling pumped already.
Who is it?
Hello?
Yes, I'm Number 511, Cheon Sa-rang.
Sorry?
Really?
I did?
But why?
No, that's not what I meant.
Okay, thank you.
Why? What's wrong?
What's the matter?
I passed.
I got an offer from King Hotel!
Congratulations, Sa-rang!
- Hello?
- You landed in the wrong place.
- Sorry?
- It's the building next to you.
Over here!
EPISODE 1
The most important quality of an intern
is not how good they are at their job.
It's having common sense.
No matter how nimble you are
or how hard you work,
it's over for you
if people find you thoughtless.
The end.
Consider arriving late
on your first day of work
and saying, "I thought it was
the building next door."
What ridiculous excuse is that?
What are you…
Where did you buy your shoes?
I bought them in Milan.
Milan?
A three-piece suit and shoes from Milan.
You could be mistaken for a nobleman.
- You should laugh along.
- Yes, sir.
You need to laugh now
if you want to be seen as mindful.
All right. Starting now,
I'll teach you what it means to have…
This is fake, isn't it?
No.
It's authentic?
Look at you. Goodness. Hold on.
How much does your outfit cost?
Are you a chaebol?
Well…
- No.
- See? I knew it.
Look at you.
He's acting like one.
You're on the path of self-destruction.
This is what you call being thoughtless.
While you're in my charge,
don't think of doing anything
and just follow my orders.
- Yes, sir.
- Louder. Got it?
- Yes, sir!
SALES SUPPORT TEAM
INTERN GU WON
This is your first internship, right?
Don't be late tomorrow.
I wasn't late.
If you come to work on the dot,
it means you're late.
Come to work
at least 30 minutes early. Got it?
But why are you speaking so casually?
Because we're coworkers.
We have to get through
this unfriendly world together.
Don't just sit there.
Uncross your legs and do something.
Do what? There's nothing to do.
You still have to act
like you're doing something.
Here. I'll give you a calculator,
so press some buttons.
I said uncross your legs.
And you heard him earlier, right?
You shouldn't wear
expensive suits or watches.
Wear something old like mine if you must.
Do I have to? Why?
Wearing something more expensive
than your superiors is considered mutiny.
You can flaunt your money outside of work.
I never flaunted it.
My goodness. You're absolutely clueless.
One would think
you were parachuted into the job.
You're right.
I parachuted here.
What?
I had to rush in from Jeju Island.
Is there something wrong?
You're driving me crazy.
Listen carefully.
This is my fifth internship.
If you keep acting like this,
you won't even be able to land a job
as a contract worker. Get it together.
- Interns!
- Yes, sir. No Sang-sik reporting.
- Interns.
- Yes, No Sang-sik here.
Why did you come alone?
- Did we only hire one intern?
- No, sir.
I thought you were just calling me.
Where are you going? Just call him.
- Right.
- What are you doing?
What? What is he doing?
He needs to sit when he works, you see.
Goodness. He got up.
Look at how relaxed he is.
How cool. I thought you were the chairman.
It's because this is his first internship.
I'll help him out.
- Yes, please help me out too.
- Yes, sir.
- To general affairs.
And make three copies of each.
Take your hand out of your pocket.
Make copies. Yes, sir. Here.
Go.
HOW TO USE A COPIER
You're still not done?
I didn't know how to use this,
so I was looking it up.
How could you not know that?
Since I've never used it before.
Are you a young master or what?
Have your servants
been doing these chores for you?
Also, this is the scanner. Don't use this.
Look. Just press this button.
We have to replace the toner cartridge.
- Interns, what are you doing here?
- Yes, sir?
It says we need to
replace the toner cartridge.
Gosh, we asked for a new machine ages ago.
The machine has a sensor issue.
Just give it a shake.
- Shake it?
- Yes, shake it.
Yes, sir.
How cute. Are you going to be that gentle?
- Shake vigorously.
- What if it explodes?
- I said, shake it vigorously.
- Yes, sir.
- That's it. Good job.
- More.
- Yes, sir.
Darn it. Who messed with the copier?
My goodness. I can't believe you guys.
You're driving me insane.
- Who was it?
- Darn it.
I'm sorry.
I was told to shake it so…
That's not even that expensive.
You could've just gotten a new one.
Are we living in the '80s?
Why would you shake that?
Well, the thing is…
You have a lot to say
after causing trouble. Just be quiet.
I'm sorry.
Why did they hire a blockhead like you?
- Clean the mess!
- Yes, sir.
Why are you sorry?
You didn't do anything wrong.
Of course I'm at fault.
- It's all my fault. Why…
- How so?
Hey.
What did you just say?
I said it wasn't
Intern No Sang-sik's fault.
Why not?
He just followed orders
because he was told to.
If it resulted in a negative outcome,
isn't the person
who gave the order at fault?
Stop it.
- What?
- I believe it's not right
to blame your juniors
without determining the cause.
Also, this only happened
because the copier was not replaced
when it should've been.
So the company is most at fault.
How dare an intern criticize the company?
Even a mere intern
can tell right from wrong.
- Darn you.
- I'm sorry.
This punk has no sense in him.
Clean up this mess at once and get lost.
And don't come to work starting tomorrow.
No, I have to come to work.
- I'm sorry.
- Okay.
- I'll do that.
- What?
You'll what?
Don't move! Where are you going?
- You said to clean up the mess.
- Yes, right here.
Hello, it's me.
Can you send some cleaners
to the sales support team?
Yes.
The copier also needs to be replaced.
All right.
- He said he'll send them.
- Who?
The cleaners.
Who said that?
- Director Choi.
- Director Choi?
By Director Choi…
The only Director Choi here
is the one who works
in the chairman's secretary's office.
That's right.
If you don't mind me asking, who are you?
I'm an intern,
and my name is Gu Won.
Gu Won?
Then are you Chairman Gu Il-hun's…
That's right.
Goodness.
Goodness, you look amazing in this suit.
Then I guess
I won't come to work
starting tomorrow as you ordered.
No, ignore what I said. I'm sorry.
Don't apologize. I'm a mere intern.
I just need to do as I'm told.
Excuse me, Mr. Choi.
Choi Tae-man at your service.
Thanks to you,
I now have a good grasp of
what thoughtlessness is.
I'll be born again.
Hello, Mr. Choi.
What's wrong with the copier?
Are you hurt anywhere?
I'm fine. Please just handle the mess.
Hold on.
I was told to
manage your attendance strictly.
If you leave now,
the chairman will be furious.
I just…
got fired.
- No, it was a joke.
- I'm leaving.
Won.
You come over here.
- It's all your fault!
- I'm sorry.
- Why did you have to shake that?
I can't get fired though.
- I need to stay here.
- I can't believe this.
I didn't know
that shaking the cartridge would…
You're back, sir.
Do you want to go with me?
- Me?
- As coworkers,
we need to get through
this unfriendly world together.
You said staying here won't even
guarantee you a contract position.
Come with me
and you'll get a full-time position.
I will serve you
with my utmost sincerity, sir.
- Do I need to clean this?
- I'll take care of it.
- Okay, then.
- Sure.
- Here you go.
- You may give it to me.
- I hope you'll be born again.
- Thank you.
Let's go, sir.
Coming through. Please make way.
- Gosh, why did you…
- Are you in your right mind?!
I told you to learn from the bottom up.
And you left on the first day?
I didn't choose to leave.
I got kicked out.
Either way, I already told you
that I'm not cut out for this.
I'll go back to the UK.
- What will you do there?
- Dad.
That's enough.
He can start slowly after studying more.
And I know it's good
to start from the bottom,
but an intern was too much.
Why can't you be
half as good as your sister?
Who does he take after?
Don't be too harsh on him.
I'll try talking to him.
Can we talk?
Go to the hotel.
It's a hassle.
I'll stay here tonight.
Who are you to stay here?
Don't be mistaken.
This isn't your house.
You're right.
I forgot for a second.
Stay at the hotel
and fly out as soon as possible.
Whatever you choose to do,
I'll support you financially.
So don't even think about
lurking around the house or the company.
You know,
I'm loaded too.
But thanks for looking after me.
You almost moved me for a second.
Where's Won?
He said he'd stay at the hotel
for the time being.
I insisted that he should at least eat.
That imbecile.
That wasn't even an earful,
but he ran away without eating.
He still has a long way to go.
If you keep tugging,
he'll only run farther away.
Letting him be
might be a good option for now.
All right.
Make sure you don't
give him a hard time either.
The guest is what?
- The guest is king.
That's right. The guest is king.
Why?
Because guests pay
service charges at hotels.
Because of that, it is our duty
to treat our guests like the king,
and it gives them the right
to be treated like one as well.
We aim to provide the guests
with satisfactory service
as well as to move their hearts.
We have to forget about our emotions
for the sake of our guests.
If you feel you're not up to it,
you may leave now.
No one?
Are you all ready to serve the king?
- Yes.
Quality customer service
starts with a smile.
This is the high-end smile
that only King Hotel offers.
Hermès!
- Hermès!
A smile is the greatest sword and shield.
Beautifully, Hermès!
- Hermès!
Hello, Manager Kim.
What's wrong with the floor?
We just cleaned it.
Clean it again and again
until it's sparkling clean.
She's a trainee.
Hello, I'm Cheon Sa-rang.
I'll take a look around.
- Teach her from A to Z.
- Yes, ma'am.
You're uselessly pretty
for a one-month trainee.
- Pardon?
- You'll be gone in a month.
Go and wipe the butt sweat.
"Butt sweat"?
If you go over there,
you'll see the beautiful butt sweat
left by our guests.
You'll be in charge of that for a month,
so don't miss a single drop
and wipe until it's sparkling clean.
Yes, ma'am.
Hey you.
Hermès!
Hermès.
Cotton swabs and cotton pads
should be filled to 90%.
It's difficult to take one out at 100%.
Anything under 90%
makes it look like we don't care.
Yes, ma'am.
Why are you so smiley?
I was taught to maintain
my Hermès smile while working.
That applies to concierges.
We still work in the hotel.
The true hotel working experience
starts in the lobby.
We wear sportswear
while they wear uniforms.
Plus, you're only here for a month.
You don't need to get used to Hermès.
I should still try my best while I'm here.
Try all you want.
No matter what happens,
you won't be able to go near the lobby.
Even I've been stuck here for five years.
At least you're a full-time worker.
Well…
I'm better than you in every aspect.
If you're done here, go out and wipe
until everything's sparkling clean.
Okay. I'll wipe
Let's get up early tomorrow
so we can eat something before our flight.
Pyeong-hwa, look up some famous places
nearby and make a reservation.
We have the hotel breakfast reserved.
I asked for a famous restaurant.
Find a rare restaurant with food
that is unique to this place.
Yes, ma'am.
I will look for a rare restaurant.
We're checked in.
Who wants to share a room with me?
Then should I choose?
Who will share a room with me?
I wonder who it will be
Eeny, meeny, miny…
moe!
You win!
Be done in ten minutes.
Don't use the restroom while I'm sleeping.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Unplug all the TV
and fridge cables.
I can't sleep if it's noisy. Understood?
Yes, ma'am. I…
RARE RESTAURANTS IN JEJU ISLAND
Didn't I tell you that I'm sensitive?
I could sense the electromagnetic waves.
I'm sorry.
- Turn off your phone.
- I put it on silent.
I can sense that too.
Thank you. Please come again next time.
- Da-eul.
- Yes?
The manager said
she doesn't like the cafeteria menu.
She wants some gimbap to eat in the back.
All right. I'll be right back.
Sorry. Coming through.
One tuna, two beef,
and one kimchi rice ball to go.
Okay, I got your order.
I'm really sorry, but in the tuna gimbap,
could you please reduce the rice,
add a lot of tuna and mayonnaise,
and take out the spinach?
Sure.
I'm really sorry again,
but for one of the beef gimbap,
can you leave out
the sesame oil and carrots?
Why don't you make it yourself?
I'm sorry. My seniors are picky eaters.
Just for today. I can't cater to
your needs when I'm busy.
Thank you so much.
I'm really sorry again…
- What now?
- Along with the other requests,
for the other beef gimbap,
can you take out the eggs
and apply the right amount of sesame oil
to make it give off a slight scent?
- Get out. I'm done with you.
- I'm sorry.
Please help me out.
- I need to buy the gimbap.
- Get out!
I'll make them.
At least allow me to make them. Please.
Excuse me. Sorry.
I'm back. I'll get everything ready.
The manager went to the cafeteria.
Sorry?
What about these?
Didn't you hear me? She wants
the pork cutlet from the cafeteria.
Let's go.
Where's the water?
- Hello.
- This is Alanga.
- This is King Hotel.
- Over there.
- Yes, ma'am.
Apologizing doesn't solve the problem!
Welcome. May I check your boarding pass?
Coming!
I can't believe my eyes.
Sir, I'm here.
Next.
Are you purchasing your clothes here?
Why would I bother shopping in person?
The comfort of the rich is beautiful.
What do you think of this?
There are only three in the nation.
Give me all three.
I'm sorry, but one has already been sold.
Then give me the remaining two.
I'm okay.
Matching shirts seems a bit too much.
I appreciate your gesture though.
Matching shirts?
Why would I?
Weren't you going to give one to me?
Both of them are mine.
Also, I hate it when someone else wears
the same thing as me.
Just go and get ready for the UK.
We're leaving in a week.
Be prepared not to come back.
The UK all of a sudden?
I don't have a passport.
Is that even possible?
Have you never been abroad?
I never had the opportunity to do so.
I was busy interning.
Apply for a passport this instant.
By the way, sir,
will I really become a full-time employee?
What if I follow you
and end up hanging in the wind?
Hello?
It's me.
Can you promote No Sang-sik
to a full-time position?
Yes, thank you.
Happy now?
Of course, sir.
Hello.
I'm the front desk manager, Kim Su-mi.
Yes. And?
I heard that you're returning to the UK.
Already? Even I just found out.
Well, you're very famous.
I see.
I am pretty popular,
which could be a bother at times.
Please feel free to give me a call
if you need anything before you leave.
I'll help you right away if you call me
directly, and not the front desk.
Is there something in your eye?
- No.
- All right, then.
As expected from the chairman's son.
He's nonchalant.
He's so charming.
Good work.
- Good work.
- Excuse me, sir.
Can you please keep it down?
- What?
- Other guests keep complaining.
Please cooperate with me.
This is my routine.
I apologize, sir.
Ms. Park Bo-yeon?
You have a refreshing way of approach.
- You like me, don't you?
- Pardon?
I'm afraid I have bad news.
You're not my type.
She's my type.
Hey.
Here.
Do I have to deliver your tips to you?
Sorry?
It's from the tiger back.
You're really something.
You're already being tipped.
Tiger?
I noticed you following me around.
I'll accept your cunning advances.
This is for our steamy night together.
What a pervert.
How disgusting.
That darn butt sweat!
Excuse me, sir.
Sir?
Why is this…
Hey--
Sir, do you think I'm a joke
because I wipe people's butt sweat?
That doesn't give people like you,
who have poop for brains,
the right to walk over me.
If you ever do this again,
I'm going to kill you.
Please keep that in mind, Mr. Pervert.
What in the world…
Excuse me. Stop right there.
Did you not hear me?
- Hey!
- What are you doing?
This space is for members
and hotel guests.
Who are you
to raise your voice in my hotel?
It's not your hotel yet.
- What?
- I'm also a guest.
A guest who rooms in a suite at that.
If I file a complaint,
it'll only get uncomfortable for us both.
Why don't you be more polite
to your guest,
Director of King Hotel?
I'll leave as soon as I'm ready.
So please try to treat me
like a guest while I'm here.
Hello, Ms. Gu.
What brings you here without notice?
Am I not allowed here?
Of course not. This entire hotel is yours.
Hello.
How's the work treating you?
It's a bit tough since it's my first time,
but I find pleasure in learning.
Thank you for hiring me.
I will do my best.
- Did you go through all the training?
- Yes.
I received basic training.
What are the deposit precautions?
I'm sorry.
She's a trainee,
so she hasn't been taught that yet.
The deposit precautions are to check
if the name on the reservation
matches the name on the card
and to check if there's a signature
on the back of the card.
- What is happy hour?
- It is a period during slow hours
in which the price of snacks and drinks
are reduced or served free
in venues such as the lounge
or cocktail bar.
Inform me in English.
Promote her to the lobby.
Pardon?
Excuse me, Ms. Gu.
She graduated from a two-year college.
Why would you leave
a competent girl to rot?
She needs to be seen.
She's a one-month trainee. Are you sure?
- Then let her stay for a year.
- Sorry?
The lobby is the face of the hotel.
She has a nice smile.
Everyone here can speak English
as well as you.
You should be able to speak
at least two foreign languages.
You can't speak Chinese, can you?
From 3 to 5 p.m.,
the hotel lounge will offer
complimentary snacks, coffee, and tea.
Please feel free to enjoy them.
At this rate,
you might even speak Japanese.
From 3 to 5 p.m.,
the hotel lounge will offer
complimentary snacks, coffee, and tea.
Please feel free to enjoy them.
It's always been my dream to become
a concierge, so I studied hard.
Foreign languages aren't everything.
The lobby isn't a place
for someone like you.
"Someone like me," ma'am?
You're uneducated, incompetent…
and unattractive.
Must I spell it out for you?
So don't show off and just do as I say.
Do you understand?
Yes, I'll do anything you ask
to the best of my ability.
Thank you.
FATHER
You just barged into a guest's room.
It's past your checkout time.
- Get out.
- I will.
You don't have to call Father.
I'll let him know.
The services at this hotel are great.
I'm the owner, after all.
Why don't you just settle down there?
Coming back will only
make things harder for you.
That's for me to decide.
But
I definitely won't be coming back,
so don't worry.
I hope you'll keep your word.
Bye.
- Congratulations
- You now work in the lobby
- Thank you.
- Congrats.
You went from wiping butt sweat
to working in the lobby.
Goodness, I'm so proud of you.
So triumphs the human spirit.
You're the first two-year college graduate
to become King Hotel's full-time employee.
My term has just been extended by a year.
Hence,
the "almost full-time employee."
One year will become two,
and two years will become three.
In a few years,
we'll become cool seniors, right?
Probably.
But where in the world
are those cool seniors?
I'm only surrounded by a bunch
of mothers-in-law on power trips.
We can become cool seniors.
I swear I'm not going to end up
like my seniors.
You're right.
Let's not turn into old witches.
I don't want to become like them.
Why are you so quiet?
I don't have any wishes.
I'd be thankful
if no one gets on my nerves.
This won't do.
You need to go to a world
filled with hopes and dreams.
Where might that be?
Club Gold.
I'm a VIP.
Everything is on me tonight!
Come on!
Come on! I need you to be louder!
Let me hear you scream!
Thank you.
KING HOTEL BEST TALENT AWARD
RECIPIENT CHEON SA-RANG
I can't believe you left me
I can't believe you abandoned me
It's hard to forget about
Our deeply-engraved memories…
ACTUAL FULL-TIME EMPLOYEE
Congratulations!
You're finally
an actual full-time employee.
All right.
To your full-time employment.
- Cheers!
THE PRESENT
GU WON
PERSONNEL RECORD
HAN MI-SO
It's me.
Book a flight to Korea at once.
Korea?
Out of the blue?
Something came up.
But my parents are visiting this week.
Can we go next week?
I'll go first then. You can come later.
No, we need to go together.
We promised
to stick together for eternity.
How long will you stay in Korea?
I don't know.
But I need to know that to pack my things.
You can just buy
your clothes and shoes in Korea,
but I need to take my things.
Okay then. Get packed in ten minutes
and meet me at the airport.
Then will you buy me new clothes
and shoes in Korea?
He hung up.
Sorry.
KING HOTEL CONCIERGE TRAINEESHIP PROGRAM
Congratulations on taking your first step
as a concierge.
I'm Cheon Sa-rang,
who will be in charge of the training.
The fundamental
of a King Hotel employee is
to love and show kindness to our guests.
Welcoming the guests
wholeheartedly comes first,
and expressing it
is the service we offer here.
In other words,
insincere kindness is not true kindness.
We need to be ready
to put on a genuine smile at all times.
Hey!
Ms. Cheon Sa-rang?
What happened?
What exactly did you do wrong?
- Me?
- What did you do
for a suite guest to come down
to the lobby and look for you?
Are you sure you didn't make a mistake?
No.
I even made a wake-up call this morning.
Hurry over.
Make sure the complaint
doesn't come to my end.
Is that clear?
Yes, ma'am.
You guys can practice smiling.
Hermès!
- Hermès!
How does it feel to come back
to Korea after a while?
It's the same.
Don't think of leaving again.
Start working.
Hotel, Air, or Distribution?
Which do you prefer?
He's just visiting.
You're getting ahead of yourself.
He's not done with his studies either.
It won't be late
even if he takes his time.
Seven years was more than enough.
Since we're on the topic,
move back to Korea.
I'll start working.
What?
But I want to work at the hotel.
What's your reason?
I like hotels.
All right.
Go ahead.
Okay. Let's have a drink.
I'm delighted to see
our family gathered like this.
You probably can't even imagine
how long I've waited for this day to come.
Won, you'll need to climb up the ladder
by competing with your sister.
What do you mean?
Won is just now starting out.
I should help him.
Both providing and receiving help
reflect competence.
I'm only going to consider
your competence from now on.
Either one of you
could become my successor,
or it could be neither of you.
I know. That's your management philosophy.
Also,
live here with us
instead of staying at the hotel.
It's more comfortable there.
Won is all grown up now.
Let him do as he pleases.
I'm not going to repeat myself.
Come back home
before your mom's memorial service.
Which mom do you mean?
I don't even know
what my mom looks like
or if she's even alive or not.
Stop with the nonsense.
Just move in if I tell you to.
You take after your mom.
You're reckless just like her.
I'll be fine on my own. Go home.
Let me join you. The rain feels nice.
- Don't follow me.
- Whatever.
I know you don't have a friend
to drink with.
I like how you're smart-mouthed.
- True.
- And how you don't force a laugh.
I do though.
What will the starting rank be by the way?
I don't know. It doesn't matter.
What do you mean?
I'm asking for myself.
You got the wrong idea.
I need some authority to protect you.
Who's going to deal
with your toxic personality? I will.
Let me be bold.
Department manager, please.
I went too far, didn't I?
Senior manager?
Take the car and go home.
I'll find my way to the hotel.
Don't follow me.
No, I'm going with you.
I should.
Gosh, the weather
is perfect for me to become a manager.
What kind of weather is that?
Please make me a manager.
- Let go.
- Please.
My goodness!
- Why is it raining so hard?
- I know, right?
- Darn it.
- Cheers!
That's refreshing.
This place has good beer.
Hey, this place
is very popular these days.
There's a line on the weekends.
What's wrong? Are you okay?
My stomach hurts for some reason.
Are you stressed?
This usually happens when you're stressed.
It's obviously because of Gong Yu-nam.
Who's that?
Your boyfriend?
Right. You have a boyfriend.
I totally forgot.
That's enough.
Isn't it about time you broke up with him?
I guess he didn't cross the line yet.
She's so lenient
when it comes to her boyfriend.
I'm more lenient with you guys.
Couldn't you tell?
Hey, holding a hot cup of tea
and saying, "It's hot,"
will only burn your hands.
Don't bottle everything up.
Get it off your chest.
Mom! Aunties!
If you drink here,
you'll destroy my reputation.
I worked so hard to build it.
All right, we'll stop drinking.
Go and play, my daughter.
Your daughter is scarier than you.
I know, right? I'm too scared to drink.
I want to dance
under the lights all night long
holding a bottle of beer.
That sounds great, and it really was.
But I forgot how to dance, so I doubt
I'll have as much fun as I used to.
I don't even remember
what a nightclub looks like.
Gosh, my blood pressure.
Do you need to wear a vest?
It seems like a hassle.
This is how you should wear a suit.
As expected,
you have a classic style.
When are you going to fix this?
Should I get it fixed?
It's okay.
You look amazing today.
It's finally our first day.
Let's start the day with a smile,
Head Manager Gu.
That's what I hate the most.
Faking, putting up a front…
Faking a smile.
I was just saying
that you shouldn't feel too stressed
since all of this will be yours one day.
Maybe it's time for you to lose your job
seeing how you're bossing me around.
No one else would stick around you.
You should be grateful to me.
You're consistently impudent.
True.
If it wasn't for my impudence,
I would've run away ages ago.
Who else would stay by your side?
- My phone.
- You may head inside.
I'll tell them to bring it.
Congratulations on your first day of work.
The papers.
Mr. No.
Mr. No?
Yes.
All right. We'll bring it
to you right away.
Excuse me, Ms. Kim.
I need to use the restroom.
Head straight to the suite, find a phone,
and take it to Ms. Gu's office.
Wait, I'm sorry,
but I have a really bad stomachache.
To the point of crapping on the way?
- Yes.
- In that case,
finish the errand quickly and then go.
But this is urgent.
Exactly. Hurry up and hop to it.
Yes, ma'am.
My phone…
I almost died.
What is this?
The bathroom is bigger than my house.
He only took my phone.
This is so cool.
KING THE LAND
Please welcome Head Manager Gu Won
with a big round of applause.
We…
meet again.
Welcome, Head Manager Gu!
We made eye contact again!
I warned you
to never let me see you again.
I'll do my best to avoid you from now on.
You said you'd do your best to avoid me.
Even over my dead body,
you are most definitely not my type.
Subtitle translation by: Stephanie Jung