Alien, please let us join your club.
Guys, stop it right now.
Why are you cornering her like that?
Has she always been like this?
Yes.
Aylin is interested in space.
Her classmates thought she was strange
and started calling her Alien.
Your birthday is coming up.
What will you do this year?
Planning to meet up with someone?
Meet up?
I'm not.
Invite him to come.
It's my birthday in a few days.
Can we meet up?
What?
I don't think it's gonna work.
It's your birthday, for goodness' sake.
That guy can't do this to you.
I've made up my mind.
I'll give Earth one last chance.
I'll ask him to meet me this evening.
Ongsa!
Earth sent me a present.
Happy birthday, my Sun.
And sorry.
Pretty?
Ongsa,
you've been stressed out lately.
Is there a problem?
Alpha, does your sister have
a problem in school?
I'm just tired.
The mid-term exams are approaching.
Let me know if you need help studying.
It's okay, Alpha.
I can manage.
Will you excuse me?
I need to go study.
Are you full?
You ate so little.
There's plenty of food left.
I'm full.
Excuse me.
Aylin,
will you go talk to her?
She might be willing
to listen to an alien.
In exchange for a veggie-free meal.
Human, your door is locked.
Are you hiding something?
Aylin, please leave me alone.
Is it because of the Sun?
Human, if you don't tell the truth,
you're going to keep suffering.
If the Sun finds out,
the Earth will come to an end.
Soon…
the Earth will surely come to an end.
It was my birthday gift from Earth.
Cute, right?
Very cute. He has good taste.
But he didn't show up.
Why so mysterious?
It's like he just wants to
keep Sun a secret.
Dear, don't kill the vibe.
Your friend is in love.
Whatever. He didn't show up
when he promised he would.
He isn't being honest with Sun for sure.
Earth must have his reasons.
Reasons? More like excuses.
I'm saying this
because I'm concerned about you, Sun.
Don't overthink it, Dear.
Earth isn't a bad person.
See? You're so nice.
Someone so nice
shouldn't be with such a fickle guy.
Step back before you get hurt.
But
I trust Earth.
I have no idea why.
Even though we've never met,
I feel like he's always by my side.
I guess I like him very much.
I'm sorry, Sun.
Sorry.
I'm such a terrible person.
Do you know that guys
can wear makeup in everyday life too?
Because cosmetics aren't gender-specific.
And today, I'm teaching you all
how to put on a natural look.
I'm telling you…
Cute, huh?
The longer I look,
the more cuteness I see.
Right.
Hey, Ton.
You were ogling them with heart eyes.
What are you talking about? No way.
-Hey.
-What?
Let's talk first.
You've got a crush, right?
No.
Handsome, listen.
Love is good.
A Dhamma-loving, optimistic,
and self-assured girl like Charoen
is perfect for you.
I don't like Charoen.
Mawin, Charoen is gentle and sweet.
She also loves Dhamma.
-Seriously, she isn't the one I like.
-She's sweet.
Mawin, you can just tell me.
Look.
Isn't she so cute talking to her friend?
I like Tinh, not Charoen.
Right. Because Tinh is nice
and Dhamma-loving…
What?
I like Tinh, not Charoen.
You got it?
I like T…
Shit! Why am I telling you this?
Dammit.
How was I so wrong?
It's a lip balm. Focus on my lips.
That's where you should focus.
Okay. Let me zoom in.
That's too close.
I won't be able to use that.
Then don't.
-I'm gonna cut it out.
-Wow, Charoen.
Does nobody like you at all?
This is…
Space junk.
It isn't junk, student.
It's a treasure.
I know it looks kind of rusty.
That's why I want you guys to renovate it
so it can be our club's decoration
and a legacy for your junior members.
Sound good?
-Yes, ma'am.
Ongsa?
Did you hear what I said?
She's spaced out.
Ongsa…
Has Sun found out?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I need to poop. May I take a toilet break?
What's going on with Ongsa?
I'll leave this with you.
Sun, can you help me
find a spaceship model?
Of course, ma'am.
Human senior.
What?
Your face tells me you need help.
You're a living thing with wisdom.
Cut to the point.
What do you do to make humans confess?
Confess?
What do you mean?
Ongsa and Sun.
What?
What's going on with Ongsa and Sun?
It's a long and complicated story.
Fill me in.
STUDENT COMMITTEE
Hey, Mawin.
No one is helping you clean up?
But I can handle it by myself.
In that case, let me help.
No, it's fine.
I can manage.
You can?
But you're the only one here.
I don't think so. Come on, let me help.
It's nothing.
I just accidentally flicked it.
You sure you're okay?
I am.
I read somewhere that an asteroid
will hit Earth in the next 23 years.
Can it just happen in 23 minutes?
I can't bear it anymore.
Ongsa, have you fed Latte?
I have, Mom.
Please, come in.
The door isn't locked. Come on in.
Ongsa, your friends are here.
What?
Didn't Aylin tell you that your friends
would be sleeping over tonight?
Yes. A human friend and a human senior
will spend the night.
What?
Hot outside?
Hello, ma'am.
Hello, there.
Hi, Ongsa.
Is this what they call the apocalypse?
Please, come in.
Come.
Aylin, why is Sun here?
To work on the club's project. That's why
she's spending the night, human.
When did you guys arrange this sleepover?
We talked at the club
after we were given the assignment.
Why didn't I know about it?
You were spaced out
and then you went to poop.
Human.
This is your chance to tell Sun
that you're Earth.
I have no clue how to tell her, Aylin.
Don't worry.
Alien and the human senior will help.
Hey. I heard you're talking
to someone, Sun.
Who told you the gossip?
Was it you, Ongsa?
No.
I never said anything.
Oh, please. You're a popular girl.
I bet everyone in school knows your story.
Is it the guy named Earth?
The one you're talking to online
but haven't met.
Yes.
We met on Insta.
He's funny.
After talking for a while,
I fell in love with him.
Have you ever talked on the phone?
We haven't.
That's because
Earth is more comfortable messaging.
Honestly, I am too
so I don't mind.
Don't you wonder
why he refuses to call
or send you pictures of himself?
Only messaging
is somewhat suspicious to me.
I know that everyone is concerned
for me about Earth,
but the Earth I know isn't a bad guy.
I trust him.
I believe he has his reasons.
And if one day you meet him
and it turns out he isn't
what you imagine him to be,
will you be able to take it?
I think so
because I like who he is inside.
No matter what he looks like,
my feelings will not change.
This is your chance, human.
Sun, it's…
Yes, Ongsa?
I…
Why are you acting like that?
Don't smile like that.
It's because you're acting funny.
Whenever you smile,
I just don't know what to do with myself.
So, what is it?
Well…
I…
It's…
I need to use the scissors.
Of course.
You were supposed to tell the truth,
not ask her to pass the scissors, human.
I'm sorry.
So, where should I and Sun crash?
I can sleep in the living room.
No, you can't.
You should sleep in a bedroom.
Human senior, you sleep in Alpha's room.
Human friend, you sleep in Ongsa's room.
Right. I will sleep in Aylin's.
-You're not allowed in my room, human.
-Why not?
I want Sun to have some privacy
and to feel comfortable.
You can take my room, Sun.
You don't have to give up
your room, Ongsa.
I do! I'm scared.
I toss and turn and there's also Latte.
You won't get a good sleep.
It's fine. I will.
Okay, okay. Don't argue.
Let's do this.
I will share Aylin's room.
Sun will share Ongsa's room.
Why would you do that?
Why don't you go to Alpha's room?
Because Alpha studies late.
I don't want to bother her.
Don't come into my room.
You guys find a solution yourselves.
My room isn't an option.
See? Come on.
Is this your room?
-No, human senior.
-Come in. Get in.
Don't you see the sign? No humans allowed!
Then, may I share your room tonight?
Is it that one?
Yes.
Wow. This is so cool.
You can't look, human senior.
What? Why not?
It isn't something you must know.
Come on.
Don't be stingy. Learn to share, will you?
We're in the same club after all.
Be generous.
Why are you so stubborn?
I don't want you to see.
What are you doing?
You don't want me to see.
Why are you doing this, human?
What you like
and take an interest in is cool.
There's no reason
to be embarrassed about it.
You should even be proud.
One day, you'll find someone
who shares the same interest.
Like now.
I also like what you like.
This is new.
What is?
A human being liking what I like.
I told you, I'm not human.
I'm a moon.
Can I observe now?
There are more over there.
What's the name of that one?
"Friend."
Is it stubborn like this one?
Aliens aren't stubborn.
Then why is this alien stubborn?
Sun, you take the bed.
I'll sleep on the floor.
Ongsa, you're the host.
Why would you sleep on the floor?
Sleep on the bed.
It's fine. I'll sleep on the floor.
You sleep on the bed, Sun.
I'll be mad if you sleep on the floor.
Why would you be mad?
You want me to get mad?
When I'm mad, I can be quite frightening.
Okay.
I'll sleep on the bed.
You're a good girl, Ongsa.
Come. Let's get some sleep.
Come on.
Come to bed.
Thank you.
Good night, Ongsa.
Good night, Sun.
It's beautiful.
I like it.
Sun.
I…
have something to tell you.
It's about Earth.
What about Earth?
Well…
I…
Is there something on your mind?
Seems like you've been
wanting to say something.
I want to tell you that…
Thank you for being my friend.
I'm glad to be friends with you, Ongsa.
Aw, I didn't think
this was what you'd say.
Actually, there's one more thing.
Yes?
What is it?
You're so cute when you smile.
I like your smile.
Please.
This is it?
You're making me blush.
I might never stop smiling
and you'll get sick of it.
I could look at your smile all day.
You're exaggerating.
I don't believe you.
Let's get some sleep, Ongsa.
I'm sleepy.
I'm sorry, Sun.
I still want to see your smile.
Sorry for being selfish.
Are you up yet?
I guess not.
You must have been too busy
to reply to me yesterday.
It's okay.
I understand.
Have a good day today, Earth.
Sun, you're awake?
Ongsa,
are you Earth?
Why did all the messages I sent to Earth
appear on your phone?
Sun!
I'm sorry.
Actually, I am…
Earth.
I'm sorry for covering this up.
-That…
-Then what was it that we had?
Am I a joke to you?
Why didn't you tell me?
Sun, I'm sorry.
I have no excuses.
I'm really sorry.
Stop apologizing!
You know
how I feel toward Earth.
Explain it to me.
Why did you do this to me?
Sun, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
-I didn't mean to. I'm sorry…
-Stop saying you're sorry.
Just explain what this is.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what it will be like,
the day the Earth ends,
but I think it will feel
something like this.
The world without the Sun
isn't livable, Ongsa.
Ongsa, Sun, are you guys up yet?
Humans, wake up.
I'm hungry.
Where are they?
Aylin, I already left.
I found out that Ongsa is Earth.
Human Sun knows about Earth.
What?
Where is Ongsa?
How should I know?
Gosh.
Let me call her.
The number you've dialed
cannot be connected…
Her phone is off.
That human being
caused trouble again, didn't she?
Let's go find her. Come on.
Come on.
How should I feel about you, Ongsa?
Human.
Ongsa.
GROCERY STORE
Human.
Ongsa.
Human senior.
Found her?
No.
She must have fled the Earth.
Then I guess we must tell her family.
Human cousin.
It's human Ongsa.
She…
Ongsa!
-Do you hear me?
-Where are you?
Ongsa.
-Human.
-Ongsa!
Ongsa.
Ongsa, are you here?
Ongsa, where are you?
-Ongsa, baby.
-Ongsa!
Mom, Dad, this way.
Where is she?
-Ongsa.
Ongsa.
Are you all right, honey?
What happened?
Did someone do something to you? Tell me.
Ongsa.
What happened?
It's okay, Ongsa.
I'm right here.
Come here.
Just cry if you want.
It's okay.
Thanks, Alpha.
We found Ongsa.
She's home.
Safe.
Don't worry.
I like it.
It's beautiful.
Ongsa is Earth.
Earth is Ongsa.
You don't have to call me "senior."
My name is Sun. What's yours?
My name is Ongsa.
Whenever you smile,
I don't know what to do with myself.
I like someone.
How likely is it that that person
will reciprocate my feelings?
Very likely.
Of course.
That person must like you very much.
Ongsa!
Earth sent me a present.
It's good that Ongsa is Earth.
Ongsa, I have something to tell you.
Ongsa, what happened yesterday?
Nothing, Mom.
It can't be nothing.
You disappeared for hours.
Ongsa,
it's okay if you're still uncomfortable
and not ready to tell us.
I just want you to know that
your mom and I,
Alpha, and Aylin are your family.
We will always be there for you.
Yes, Dad.
I know.
Thank you all so much.
I'm gonna
go out and get Latte some food.
He's out of food.
Should I go with you?
It's all right.
It's just nearby.
I'm coming with you, human.
It's fine, Aylin.
It won't take long.
Why did you let her go by herself?
Aren't you worried about her?
Of course I am.
But don't forget that
she's a grown-up now.
Don't worry too much.
I understand your concern,
but there are some problems
we just can't fix for her.
She must solve them herself.
All we can do is support her
through the difficult times.
I think when the time comes,
she will tell us.
Be patient.
Don't worry.
Sunny.
Ongsa.
Did you get my message?
I sent it to you last night.
I saw it but was too afraid to read it.
Don't you want to talk to me anymore?
How can I talk to you, Sun?
I feel bad beyond words right now.
I want you to talk to me directly.
I don't have the guts.
Can you please talk to me?
I don't have the right.
Ongsa!
Ongsa, wait.
Ongsa.
How are you?
Doing okay?
You know, I couldn't sleep.
No one said goodnight to me before bed.
It's awkward talking to myself, you know?
It's just me talking in the chat
and it's just me talking now.
I'm sorry.
For what?
For being a girl.
I'm not Earth.
I'm not a guy like you prefer.
Do you see me?
I'm not a guy.
So?
We can only be friends.
I doubt we can even be friends.
Why did you come up with that by yourself?
Why didn't you ask me?
Well, I'm a girl.
Girl or guy,
Ongsa or Earth,
the one I talked to is you, Ongsa.
I don't want you
to disappear from my life.
All this time we've talked,
it's felt great.
I'm thankful to you
for always being by my side.
For making me smile and laugh.
I've been happy.
Anyway, I must admit that…
I'm not sure…
if you and I,
a girl and a girl,
can actually happen.
I understand.
Things between us can never happen.
But because I'm not sure,
I'd like to get to know you again, Ongsa.
I really want to know you.
Ongsa,
I don't know what the destination will be,
but can you please stay with me
until we reach it?
Then, all of a sudden, the universe
gave me a chance to start over.
Hi.
I'm Sun.
And this time, I won't screw up.
I won't drift away
from my orbit around her.
Hi. I'm Ongsa.
It's nice to meet you, Sun.
Ongsa, do you like me that much?
I do, but I'm afraid
you'll feel uncomfortable.
How about we take it slow?
I don't want you to think
you're inferior to anyone.
Ongsa is Ongsa.
That's enough for me.
You two humans, are you girlfriends now?