You refuse to hand Charlie over?
What do you mean? Explain yourself, Phil.
It's just how it sounds.
Why should I have to
hand over my private property?
It was something that had no owner.
And I happened to pick it up.
Deputy Graham. As I'm sure you're aware,
we're investigating terrorism
and murder here.
We need to question Charlie.
Like I said, that's fine.
On condition that it's recorded on video
and my designated lawyer is present.
Assuming you aren't planning on
stealing Charlie, what's the problem?
You leave me no choice.
Phil, hand over your badge.
You're suspended from duty indefinitely.
On what grounds?
Grounds?
Well, let's see.
You let Feyerabend get away,
you're hampering the investigation.
Take your pick.
As sheriff, I'm well within my rights
to stand you down.
Look, Philip.
I don't know what nonsense
that congresswoman's put in your head,
but are you gonna toss away
your career and your pension?
Think it over care...
Hey, Phil.
I see. I'll support you as far as I can.
But I can't intervene
in sheriff's office HR matters.
That'd be an issue.
I get it.
But never mind that.
Can you do something about the media?
They've already sniffed out where I live.
I was the one who leaked your address.
What?
They'd have found you sooner or later.
And with them watching,
the FBI won't try to get heavy-handed.
Just put up with it until
the transfer procedures are in order.
I'll be in touch.
Damned politicians.
This is truer than principles
Discovered by geniuses like XY
You are so captivating
That I can't take my eyes off you
We are merely beings who are just living
But we are beings unlike any other
You make me wonder
Actors caught in a drama
Unaware of the ending
Our "relationship chart" is still blank
And it bothers me
We only want to share laughter
Yet somehow end up hurting each other
It wasn't supposed to be like this
I wonder what principles or clues
Apply to our relationship
A stereo yearning to blend
Like left and right
Could it be love?
I don't know
Are we at odds?
I don't think so
It's a frustrating thing
And I can't even tell if it's real
Just how deep is our relationship?
Why can't it be measured?
I want to know you
I want you to know me
And what's the level of expectation
When we get to know each other?
I know nothing else but the long-sought
Love, and I want to seek it out
You make me wonder
Just beyond words
EPISODE 12
SEXUAL DIMORPHISM
It's the deputy sheriff. Roll the camera.
Can't get a good shot.
Should we just come back tomorrow?
I'm back.
I bought what you asked for.
Check if anything's missing. Grace?
Thanks.
That's a big help.
Those people never let up.
Oh, looks like they're leaving.
They sure have it tough.
How's Charlie? Nothing new?
Nope. He's been home all day.
Did you know, Phil? He's really smart.
I gave him a book of crossword puzzles
and he solved them all in no time.
Really?
I'm glad you're both getting along.
Hi, Charlie. How've you been?
What are you calling on? Your phone?
It's a tablet. Phil gave it to me
after you left last night.
Nice. So how's the new place?
Things going well?
'Cause we're almost out.
Geez. We've got enough of it.
Grace is always fussing over me.
That probably means it's going well then.
Charlie.
What about you though?
Me?
I mean… you're all good?
Yeah. I've got my regular checkup
at the Kornberg Institute this weekend.
I think I'm pretty healthy though.
My body's lighter somehow.
And I feel extra strong.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
My senses are really sharp too.
I think
someone other than Phil and Grace
used to use this room.
Suspended?
Yeah. I'm sorry. I...
Oh, well, what can you do.
And it's a dangerous job,
so maybe it's for the best.
We've got Charlie to worry about too.
Hey…
I know, the two of us could open
a massage parlor here. What do you think?
At this hour? Is it the press again?
Wait, let me...
Yes, who is it?
Oh, Ronnie.
Evening, Grace.
What a surprise.
We hardly ever see you here.
Come on in.
That's okay. I was in the neighborhood.
Just thought I'd drop by.
Mind if I borrow Phil for a bit?
Sure thing.
I won't even charge you interest!
Grace hasn't changed a bit.
Yeah, she's basically led
a sheltered life. Never had it rough.
Don't you wanna make sure
it stays that way?
You understand, don't you, Phil?
That monkey's like a spark to dry tinder.
That may be.
But it's the folks 'round here
who're feeding the fire.
You put the Humanzee in there?
In your dead daughter's room?
That's ancient history.
If you say so.
Better head home. Here.
Ronnie.
Take it.
You deserve it
with all the good work you do.
That coward ain't sheriff material.
You should stand for election next time.
I'll drum up the votes for ya.
Good one, Ronnie.
Call me if you need anything.
I couldn't keep a lid on the violence.
I'm responsible too.
Hi, Charlie.
How do you like your new home?
It's comfortable.
Sorry for lying to you last time.
This is my wife, Grace.
Nice to meet you. It's my first time
coming to a research lab.
We're happy you're here. Please, this way.
Okay, Charlie. We just need to measure
your physical strength, then we're done.
Everything looks normal.
I wasn't sure how'd he be,
but I think we can relax for now.
Weird.
This was custom-made to Humanzee specs.
What on earth's going on?
Dr. Fowler. It's…
Something's abnormal with Charlie?
Yes. Compare this
with the data from last time.
You can see that his bones have
suddenly become thicker,
and his muscle mass has
increased significantly.
His blood testosterone
and androgen levels have also spiked.
If he were human, he'd probably be
at Stage II or III on the Tanner scale...
Whoa there, Doc.
We're not college professors, remember?
Explain it in language we can understand.
Apologies.
To put it plainly, right now, Charlie is…
Hitting puberty.
I got to the ceiling.
Should we redo it?
Puberty? As in puberty puberty?
Yes. He's developing what we call
secondary sex characteristics.
Humans and chimps go through
the same sexual maturation process
to reach adulthood.
However, for some reason
Charlie never showed any signs of it
when he reached the normal age
for either species.
Frankly speaking,
I'm not sure why it's happening now.
Perhaps Dr. Grossman arranged
things this way.
Or maybe the recent drastic changes
in Charlie's environment
have flipped some genetic switch.
Losing his adoptive parents,
in particular,
must have caused him
a great deal of stress.
But there's nothing wrong
with him, is there?
It just means he's growing up.
Instead of worrying,
we should celebrate with a cake.
S'pose so.
Can't say I remember
my own folks sitting me down
to talk about
secondary sex characteristics.
S'cause you're a guy.
Well, so's Charlie.
Anyway, Doc, "abnormal" sounds like
a little bit of an overstatement.
Shouldn't we just leave him be
and let nature take its course?
No one knows what course it will take.
Charlie's the only Humanzee
on the planet, after all.
His species is a complete unknown.
That's a new record.
A perfect 1023 moves with no mistakes
in under five minutes. Incredible.
You owe me ten bucks.
Sorry.
I'm hungry.
Do you like it, Lucy?
Yeah. It's delicious.
I think I'm getting the hang
of the flavors.
Phil, you could try eating the vegan food
I make for Charlie too.
It's good for you,
and it might get rid of that beer belly.
Gimme a break.
I'll take my weekend beer and steak
over my health, thanks.
Even if I end up senile
in an old folks' home.
What if you end up with no teeth?
I've never lost a tooth.
So you still have your baby teeth?
Phil, are you in contact
with Representative Linares?
Yeah, though I can hardly ever
get a hold of her from this end.
It's always her getting in touch with me.
"Sign this, sign that."
What about the court case
for Charlie's citizenship?
Right, heard about that.
Well, check this out.
It's a book she wrote ages ago.
Her take on animal rights
in here is pretty radical.
Her opinions are
way more extreme than I realized.
Pretty fascinating, but I'm surprised
she managed to get elected.
Lucy, how many Americans do you think
read what the candidates have written
before they vote?
It's true.
Charlie definitely needs
some kind of rights.
Way things are now,
he couldn't even get a driver's license.
But animal rights?
That's a ridiculous idea.
Sure, I'm against senseless cruelty
to animals, same as the next guy.
But it's only natural
for humans to put themselves first.
Then what about Charlie?
Charlie, well, he's half-human, ain't he?
They can just make
a special Humanzee category for him.
You think so?
Yeah. After all,
he's got nothing to do
with the rest of the animals.
Rights are something humans thought up
for human society.
Charlie, put that book down
till after dinner.
Well, I guess maybe
that is the default attitude.
I mean, I'm avoiding animal products
as much as I can now,
but I'm not like Gare, I don't feel guilty
about my past behavior,
and I don't feel like eating steak is
the same as cannibalism.
It does gross me out when I see
celebs wearing fur though.
I know. Totally inconsistent, right?
Maybe it's speciesist of me to say this,
but can we really ever
get rid of all that stuff?
Like, could we give animals legal rights?
It's no good. I can't get it all straight.
This problem's way too big
for one high schooler.
Like Phil said, it's got nothing
directly to do with your problem, Charlie.
My problem?
Dr. Grossman.
You're going to look for him, right?
Yeah.
If he's still alive,
I need to find him as soon as possible.
Why's that?
Well, Feyerabend's searching for him too.
That's what he said, at least.
What if Grossman joins up with the ALA?
Yeah, that would be
a truly bad combination.
He's not just a danger to human society.
He's a danger to us too.
We don't know why
Dr. Grossman created a Humanzee.
That's why you want to find him?
Yeah. That's why I want to meet him.
I want to know who I am.
And why was I born.
I told you before
that it's just me and my mom, right?
Yeah.
Well, I was conceived
through artificial insemination.
- You were?
- Yep.
Neither my mom nor I have ever met him.
The sperm bank keeps
its donors' personal info private.
All I have is his IQ and academic record,
and the age he was
when he donated the sperm.
Plus this one blurry photo.
I've never told anyone all this before.
It just seemed like
it would be a pain in the ass.
Though to be honest,
I don't feel like it's that big a deal.
My mom was super matter-of-fact about it
even when I was little.
It wasn't about infertility or anything.
She just said,
"You don't need a man to have a kid."
Weirdly, it's kinda like your situation.
Born through
unnatural reproductive technology,
never met my dad,
though you're obviously a much rarer case.
Apparently tons of kids in the States are
conceived using sperm banks now.
It's just, Feyerabend made it
pretty clear that he knew.
- When you were in that cabin?
- Yeah.
He actually broke into my house, so I'm
sure he's done all kinds of snooping.
But it really shook me
when he brought it up.
And since then,
something about it's been nagging at me.
Is that why you wanted to be friends?
Because we were both born through
unnatural reproductive technology?
Nah, not at all.
I just thought you were interesting.
And I never get bored talking to you.
Does that mean you like me?
Maybe, I guess?
Then do you want to mate with me?
Oh, right, humans don't say "mate."
Fuck? Have sex?
Why… with me?
Because I want to.
Sure.
Does that mean you consent to mate?
Consent? Well…
It means I don't hate the idea.
But…
Wait, hang on. Do you mean now?
Or whenever.
I'm flattered,
but I think I'd rather not right this sec.
Why not?
Even though you don't hate the idea?
I mean, I guess
I don't wanna do it
unless it's something I really want.
And that's not how I feel right now.
Would it be different if I were human?
What? If you were human?
'Sup, Lucy. Hop in.
I don't really know.
I mean, what about you?
Do you think you can let go of the fact
that you're a Humanzee, Charlie?
It's Mom! I better get back. I'll get Phil
to take me since it's past dark.
Sorry I couldn't give you what you wanted.
That's okay. See you.
For now, how about this.
See ya.
Oh yeah, by the way,
maybe call it "making love" instead.
It's kinda old-fashioned,
but it's romantic.
I meant to kiss him on the cheek,
but maybe that was his mouth?
JEFFERSON CITY, MISSOURI
This way. The doctor's given permission.
Though I doubt there's much point.
He won't even speak to his lawyers.
Thank you, Mr. Prosecutor.
We'll take it from here.
You've got 15 minutes.
Major Lesley K. Lippman.
Joined the ALA after you were discharged.
Hoping for some juicy plea deal, huh?
Okay, here's a deal for you.
Tell us everything you know about the ALA,
and we'll let you choose between hanging
and the electric chair. How's that sound?
Major. Your war is over.
You lost. The ALA are powerless now.
You shat all over your shiny war record.
But then you know that.
Got nothin' to say?
Catch Charlie.
That's the FBI's goal, isn't it?
To get him on a tight leash.
You… Let go!
Hey, what're you doing? Get away from him.
That's it, you're done here.
Wait, our time's not up yet.
Too bad. His lawyers are here too.
Now get out.
NORTH DAKOTA
Secretary Alcott.
Tell us about the alleged
illegal donations.
Is it true you worked to kill
the proposed animal welfare bill
for the benefit
of the food processing industry?
Secretary Alcott.
There are reports you're under
investigation by a citizen's group.
That's absurd.
As I've just explained to its supporters.
But it's a huge issue!
- Mr. Secretary.
- Secretary Alcott.
- Please answer the question!
- Sir!
Sir, please.
What? You got that? We need to avoid
an indictment at all costs.
I'm headed back to Washington now.
Tell the president...
Hey, what gives?
This isn't the way to the airport.
Hey. Did you hear me?
That mask… You're…
You might be the one I'm searching for
Make this moment last for evermore
Starting my day just the same as always
Even when night ends
And then the dawn finds its way
Hey, that's why I rush back into the flow
Facing all these
Super crazy hectic days I know
Singing while it's stabbing my brain
Just like filling up the holes remained
I'll keep on breaking through
Without stopping
Even if insane
Are you sure?
I know it's boring, right?
I pray softly
Even if I live how I want, I'm lonely
Stacking fragile things
That will fade someday
Just same as you
I am also just lonely, fall away
Turn It Up!
There's no way I can stop now
Let it sway with a gentle sound
Turn It Up!
Every thought I have of you
Riding straight to happiness too
Subtitle: Annie Chen