"Time is not a straight line.
The past, the future,
and the present coexist.
Humans live through several ages
and several lifetimes,
separated only by time." - Hermann Hesse.
"Across every age and every lifetime,
our fate remains the same:
to be royally screwed." - Shaji Paappan
War...
A battle for freedom that has raged
for aeons across the world.
A single enemy for everyone.
The Organisation.
A colossal private entity
that rules the whole world.
They overthrew every government
and every democratic institution.
Some of them were bought.
Anyone who resisted was eliminated.
Only a few people like us
continue to fight without stopping.
What I'm about to tell you now...
I've wanted to tell you this
for a very long time.
And today, the right moment
has finally arrived.
How did this Organisation
conquer the whole world?
Do you have any idea?
No.
I have the answer.
They time travelled.
First, they gained mastery
over time and its eras.
How?
All because of this.
Star Dust.
A rare and mysterious relic.
They became capable of controlling
timelines by harvesting its energy.
Now what, Baba?
That is a profound question!
No one can defeat them
with weapons alone.
I've been saying that for ages.
The timelines must be corrected.
For that to happen, the Star Dust
must return to the righteous.
Right now it is in the hands of people
whom we would normally
never see or interact with.
Total strangers.
Their decisions will determine
the fate of the entire world.
Baba, these strangers...
Are these people heroes?
Heroes...?
Yes.
But they are also
a bunch of idiots.
[It's me,
Shaji Paappan]
As always,
I'll kick this off myself.
I am Arakkal Abu.
Since it's been a while
since we last met,
let me catch you up.
Moonga's family packed him off
to Saudi for a forced detox.
To fill his spot, his younger brother
Moosa showed up!
God knows why!
That's not enough!
If it were you, only a village
would roast you!
But honestly, we never knew
your brother goes around
getting roasted all across Kerala!
♪ The cutest little goat ♪
♪ The sugary sweet goat ♪
Mom!
If the court case ends soon,
won't Paappan get the gold trophy?
Once he sells it,
won't Paappan become rich?
Then he can buy
our house back, right?
Oh, yeah?
Our house deed is still pledged to that
loan shark 'Iron' Abdullah, isn't it?
We used to live in our own house,
now we're stuck in a rented one.
I won't let that crook Paappan
set foot in this house!
As always, Ammachi refuses
to let Paappan in the house.
Hey, Paappan...
Ammachi isn't budging.
Better stay away for now.
What else am I supposed to do?
Only this time,
he's banned from the rented house too.
We were so punctual with the rent
on the first of every month that
the old club owner kicked us out.
We've moved
to a new club headquarters now.
New place, same old unpaid rent.
Cleetus is still the same old Cleetus.
♪ Captain Cleetus ♪
A total nuisance!
♪ Everyone else is a worker ♪
♪ But Cleetus is the Big Boss
of the world ♪
Cut! Cut! Cut!
- Shucks!
- What's the issue?
When you say "money money,"
laugh with a nice bright ring to it!
Give me that filthy rich vibe!
- Get another bundle of notes now.
- Okay.
Ugh, I can't stand
looking at Lolan's face!
Looks like a chopped yam!
Dude!
You mock me if I grow a beard!
You mock me even
if I shave it off!
What next,
should I chop my head off?
Action!
What the hell are
you doing, Cleetus?
Those are dollars!
If Paappan finds out...
Pick it all up!
Yes.
Paappan is making
one last desperate attempt.
He's trying to take the ten lakh dollars
we got from the fake healers
all the way to America
to exchange it into Indian rupees
and finally make it in life.
And we're in on it too.
Though it's taking some time,
Paappan says everyone's travel papers
are getting cleared.
Cleetus, however, can't go.
Why, dude?
You don't have a certificate showing
you failed 10th grade like we do, right?
Yeah!
Didn't you drop out in third grade
once they stopped the free breakfast?
So,
you won't get a passport...
because...
you don't even have
the documents required to apply.
Go on, cry your heart out.
Cleetus may be sad and jealous,
but we don't care.
Because those dollars are our last shot
at becoming winners in life.
Why are you sitting alone, Captain?
Where is Paappan?
They must have gone to America.
To America?
For what?
And then, for no reason at all,
Rachel decided to strike up
a conversation with the Captain.
Well, Captain...
The American President, Trump...
is attending a youth meeting
at the Coimbatore stadium.
You should go and meet Trump
with those Dollars, Captain.
Then you should tell Trump,
"This is your Dollar.
Give me Indian money."
He will personally hand you
mint-fresh Gandhi notes right away.
- Simple!
- Is it?
If you have any doubt,
just say, "I'm a tourist,
I'm a tourist."
She was only kidding.
But of course,
Cleetus took it seriously.
Paappan!!!
♪ Captain Cleetus ♪
Wait and watch!
[Winners Club - Pothumukku]
Krishnan!
What's wrong?
Did a snake get in? Huh?
What is it?
- Yikes!
- Jesus! Where did the dollars go?
What is this?
Konkani?
To deerest Peppan,
I'm leaving with the door.
I'll return as a rick guy.
Why take the door there?
Why not call the rick guy here?
- But the door is right here.
- That's right! Read the rest.
Drum is combing Koya bathroom.
I'll comb back after mating him.
- What's he going to comb?
- Read the rest.
If I say I will comb,
I will comb!
I swear on Madam!
Yours sin-seer-lee,
Cleerus the Claw.
Who on earth swears on a Madam?
With him,
anything is possible.
You're reading it all wrong!
To dearest Paappan,
I'm leaving with the dollars.
I'll return as a rich guy.
Trump is visiting Coimbatore.
I'll come back
after meeting him.
If I say I will come,
I will come!
I swear on Mother Mary!
Yours sincerely,
Cleetus. Signed.
So it wasn't 'The Claw'?
How did you even read this?
I'm the one who wrote it
for Captain!
Oh!
- What are you doing?
- Uploading it as my status update!
- Oh!
- Leave that.
What will I tell Paappan?
What will I tell the travel agent?
Hey, where's our vehicle?
Let's grab him in Coimbatore
before he does something stupid.
Here at the Venkatachalam Stadium
Coimbatore,
the final media rehearsals
and mock sessions are going on.
As you can see,
the security is already beefed up,
since the threats have
always been there.
♪ Captain Cleetus ♪
Trump, my man!
Here I come!
At least today, I'll prove
to Paappan that I'm smart.
All this police security
just to receive me?
Anyway, I'll deal
only with the big man.
- Hey, stop!
- Huh?
[In Hindi] Who are you?
What do you want?
[in broken Hindi] This... from the bag...
inside... uh... from Trump... dollars...
Give Indian money.
[In Hindi] What nonsense
is this idiot saying?
How do I explain
this to him?
What?
[in broken Hindi]
I talk you... talk you.
Huh!
These are all dollars.
Is Trump done
with his tea break?
- What's going on?
- Sir...
[In Hindi] He wants
to exchange dollars.
- Give it to me.
- Okay, sir.
- This is fake currency.
- Fake?
It's fake, man.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Are you crazy?
Didn't Rachel teach me something?!
- Yes! I am a terrorist!
- What?
Put the guns away!
No need for that!
I'm telling the truth.
If you don't believe me,
call Paappan and check.
You rascal!
You're pulling a gun out?
As soon as Lasar got his hands on
the money-mint, he burst out laughing.
So did we!
Whenever we ask where
he got the dollars from,
he's been feeding us this same load
of crap for four days straight.
The guy looks
mentally unstable.
I've got his address and details.
We'll see.
How can you be so sure
my dollars are fake?
Tell me.
This is a real American dollar note.
And this here
is Benjamin Franklin.
He never wore glasses
in his life.
Really?
But on your notes,
Franklin is wearing glasses.
How come?
Let me see that.
Huh!
You sneaky little devil!
You stole Gandhi's glasses,
took a photo wearing them,
and printed it
on your currency notes, huh?
Sir, you must charge him
under every law in the book!
You saw that, right?
He's trapped!
If we don't step in now,
Cleetus will rot in jail forever.
So,
we decided to put our
brains to work.
No one usually
blocks our vehicle,
but sometimes,
we block theirs.
[In Tamil] Why are you slowing down?
There's a vehicle
crossing the road, sir.
And when we block them,
you guys should already have taken
positions on both sides of the road
without drawing any suspicion.
You remember everything
we planned, right?
As soon as Abu fires,
blast it immediately!
Copy that!
- Who is that?
- Hey! Who is that?
Hey! You're
deafening me!
Go there and ask him.
- Okay, sir.
- Just go ask him.
Hey! Who are you?
Why have you parked across the road?
Sir, I've got a flat tire.
I don't have any tools with me.
The mechanic is on his way
with the tools.
Now all he needs is a parrot
and some tarot cards.
By the way,
where are you headed, sir?
Hey! You're asking us
where we're going!?
Call the mechanic!
Are you just making up stories?
♪ Abu is terror untold,
A devil ruthless and bold ♪
♪ Wingman to the Lord of Doom
Blood is his sweet perfume ♪
♪ With a machete he combs his hair,
Chopping heads is his hobby... beware! ♪
Character change!
Minus the rage!
♪ Wingman to the Lord of Doom
Blood is his sweet perfume ♪
♪ With a machete he combs his hair,
Chopping heads is his hobby... beware! ♪
Here he comes, sir.
Hurry up, you rascal!
He is a superb mechanic.
He'll probably mess up
the vehicle even more.
- Hurry up!
- Sir, just two minutes.
He is a lazy ox, sir.
He's always like this!
Crazy guy!
What are you staring at?
Want a slap?
Try it.
I'll teach you a lesson!
Ready?
♪ Chapathi chapathi
chapathi chapathi ♪
♪ Parotta Sambar ♪
Sir...
It's a bicycle pump. How can they
inflate a van tire with that?
- Am I the one doing it?
- No, sir.
You idiot! Go ask him!
♪ Chapathi chapathi ♪
Hey!
Are you trying to be funny
inflating it with a bicycle pump?
Get your vehicle off the road!
This is how we do it
back home, sir.
Just five minutes, sir.
Right when the fight
is about to break out,
that's when Paappan
makes his grand entrance!
SHAJIYETTAA!
♪ Paappan, Paappan ♪
♪ O Paappan, Paappan ♪
♪ Even Haji Mastan would salute the man,
The brave and mighty Shaji Paappan ♪
♪ Even an atom bomb would surely fizzle,
Before Shaji Paappan's lethal sizzle ♪
♪ Even Haji Mastan would salute the man,
The brave and mighty Shaji Paappan ♪
♪ Even an atom bomb would surely fizzle,
Before Shaji Paappan's lethal sizzle ♪
Explosive!
A barrage of fireworks!
A festival indeed!
♪ O precious Paappan,
O priceless Paappan ♪
Hey! Who the hell are you?
Paappan!
Shaji Paappan!
Release my boy right now!
Hey! What the hell have you
guys been doing for so long?
It's nothing, sir.
Hey!
This is your final warning.
Move your vehicle and leave.
Or else, I'll bury you
right where you stand!
Son of a b****!
Huh!
Use that language with your father.
Try it with Paappan,
and that head of yours
won't stay on your neck!
- Destroy him, Paappan!
- Oh, yeah!
No sentiments,
no compromise!
Hey! Zip it!
Why are you still standing there
talking to him?
Shoot him!
Now that's what
I'm talking about!
Blast!
Oh no!
♪ The festival bursts with joy in the air,
Cheers and euphoria everywhere ♪
♪ Rope in hand for the tug-of-war,
Here comes the little army with a roar ♪
♪ Drums roll loud, storm-clouds proclaim,
Sirens and war-cries hail their fame ♪
♪ The world shall bow
to their blazing palms ♪
♪ Like pearls that fall
from shattered dreams ♪
♪ Like lightning racing for the sky,
Their daring hearts find paths to try ♪
Cleetus!
Come get in the vehicle!
Why should I get in that vehicle?
You should get in
this one instead, Paappan.
Then we'd have two junk
vehicles of our own!
Cleetus...
I'm not even going to ask
how you pull this off!
But how did your father
even pull this off?
Get out here, you swamp-rat!
♪ Where firework rebels gather bold,
Defy the sun that burns the road ♪
♪ O fearless legends brave and free,
Swimming across the roaring, raging sea ♪
♪ With burning embers in their veins,
With fiery wings that break their chains ♪
♪ War-drums roar across the land,
The world now trembles at their stand ♪
♪ Crouching panthers shiver in dread,
Their pride bows down its head ♪
♪ All who stand before their might,
Soon call it quits and quit the fight ♪
Hey, Shukkoor...
Yeah...
I didn't even have to fire the gun.
The cops did it
themselves!
- That was so stupid, Cleetus!
- Why?
Didn't you see how much
money we just blew?
- Plus we had to use our brains!
- Exactly!
So what? Isn't it a good thing
I got caught?
Instead, if you had taken
those fake notes to America,
and their cops caught you,
would you ever get out?
You should be thanking me!
Cleetus, thank you!
Thank you! Welcome!
Why can't you thank me?
Thank you!
Why is Paappan wobbling like that?
Have you ever seen
Paappan ride straight?
- Oh no! Look! Shajiyettan!
- Shajiyettan!
Oh no!
- Paappan!
- Shajiyettan!
- Oh no!
Hit the brakes, Abu!
- Over there!
- Get out of the van!
Stop the van, fast!
- Paappan!
- Pull over, Abu!
Seems like Paappan is done for!
Abu, hold me gently!
My eyes suddenly went dark.
Funny… for crooks like you,
you look just like cops.
Who's that?
Paappan!
Everyone bolted the moment
the cops showed up.
But I stayed back
and surrendered.
The ones who ran won't have
their photos in tomorrow's papers.
But you and I will be in
tomorrow's papers, Paappan.
How's my brain?
Your brain works overtime
just to stay stupid, Cleetus.
♪ Captain Cleetus ♪
Sir...
So what's the plan now?
Are we going to the hospital first
or straight to the police station?
Phew!
[In Tamil] This charge sheet says
Cleetus printed
counterfeit American dollars
and tried to exchange
them with Donald Trump
during his visit to Coimbatore.
- That's all.
- So, isn't he the prime accused?
Yes, Your Honour.
Usually, Paappan is always
the prime accused.
I'm the prime accused this time?
Thank you!
Is this really the place to brag?
Let them know
it's not only the lawyers,
we've got enough cases too.
While prime accused Cleetus
was being brought to court,
Shaji Paappan was arrested for throwing
a crude bomb to help him escape.
He is the second accused.
- Correct?
- Yes, Your Honour.
Yours truly!
Is there no one here
to represent them?
- That--
- I'll argue our case, Your Honour!
Let the arguments begin!
We're ready! Are you?
[TV game show style]
I'll treat you
to parotta and gravy.
Just don't get us
the death penalty!
Relax.
This is a walk in the park!
Hey! What's going on?
Sir, our intelligence team ran
a background check in their hometown.
The locals say these guys
are complete lunatics,
and we'd be even bigger lunatics
for trying to arrest them!
That's why we haven't
arrested anyone.
Sigh!
Hey officer! Come over here!
See? They got scared
as soon as I said I'd argue.
Yeah, I was a bit scared too.
Hey, I suspect this is Kerala
trying to mess with us!
Should we throw these guys
in jail, feed them,
and waste our tax money?
Let the people of Kerala deal
with the mess these guys caused.
Why should we be the ones
to suffer for it?
These guys must pay compensation
for the damage they've caused.
- Got it?
- Sir, but--
No! Don't say a word!
- Shaji Paappan!
- Yes!
Do you know Tamil?
I can't speak it,
but I can't understand it either.
Yes.
Your Honour,
we're starving here.
What do you do for a living?
[in Malayalam]
What is your job?
Tug-of-war!
And I am his tugger!
You call that a job?
Why do I always get
these ridiculous cases?
Just my luck!
I am closing this case.
What about my defence
and legal arguments?
Zip it, you moron!
There are plenty of other states.
You'll get your chance soon.
Much obliged, Your Honour!
- Let's get out of here.
- Paappan! Paappan!
- Wait! Wait!
- Don't go.
Calling from behind?
Bad omen!
[In Tamil] This court orders you
to pay ₹4 lakhs as compensation
for the damages caused by you
to the Police Department
and the Jail Department.
Ah!
That's a fair ruling. Good.
I can contribute
maybe ₹500 myself.
Happy now?
You owe me ₹300, Cleetus.
Oh no!
Silence! Silence!
Everyone here appreciates
your generosity, Paappan!
Sigh! Tell them not to build
a temple for me!
- Paappan!
- My Lord!
People like you would not have existed,
not in this world...
not in any other world
or timeline.
Oh, that's just your
misconception, Your Honour!
I bet there were bigger hustlers
than us back in the old days.
I swear!
Alright then,
see you soon!
Ah, Michael Sir!
Your research
isn't finished yet?
Not yet.
The pre-synopsis is next week.
I'm just adding
the final touches.
Damn it!
The "Royal Tusker's Pearl"
we've chased for ages
finally falls into our hands today.
But how will we trick
the "Ghost of the High Range"
with an empty briefcase?
Come with me.
The moment I got this location,
I deployed a hundred of our men.
And he will be done
and dusted forever!
We've brought the payment
as agreed.
Can we see the stuff?
Finally!
So pleased to meet you, Mr. Ghost.
What's your real name, man?
♪ The burning fire,
The burning fire ♪
Oh my GOD!
♪ The burning fire,
The burning fire ♪
♪ The High Range's highly dangerous
underworld kingpin renowned ♪
♪ Striking like high-voltage
lightning crashing to the ground ♪
♪ Satan Xavier ♪
Satan Xavier!
You are damn right.
That's the name.
Hey!
Down! On the table!
I'll forgive the fact
that you sent assassins to kill me.
Trying to trick me
with an empty briefcase...
I'll forgive that too.
But stepping into
my High Range hills
and asking who I am
to my face?
That I won't forgive.
Six-seven!
♪ Satan Xavier ♪
♪ The High Range's highly dangerous
underworld kingpin renowned ♪
That's how I met my Satan sir
for the first time.
When did you see him after that?
I met him many times after that.
And now...
Look at him, huddled in that cloak
like some budget Darth Vader!
He's covered in cobwebs!
- He needs a clean-up!
- Sir...
Sir... it's me, Soman.
- Say something to him.
- Like what?
- Good heavens!
- He's a complete wreck.
Come, let's see if there's
any alcohol here.
- Hey, Simon...
- Yeah?
At this rate,
we'll starve to death.
Oh, Mother of spirits!
Bless the Prime Minister
who gave us demonetisation!
That's not all.
He wanted to become the next Ambani
by printing crores with that money-mint.
The whole underworld found out.
It was so humiliating!
Yeah.
Dude Sir and I
put so much effort into it!
- Who's this "Dude" sir?
- Not Dude, I meant Dad.
- Err...
- Whatever!
Wait, who is this guy?
That's Michael Sir.
- Who's he?
- Xavier sir's cousin.
Take a look at this.
Just look at this, man!
I know you've been feeling low.
Sigh... damn it!
Xavier...
Just trust your cousin.
Please!
This might be the El Dorado
you've been searching for.
Maybe, this could be your greatest quest.
No change at all, huh?
No, Cousin sir.
He's been curled up under
that blanket for five or six months.
Sir, he has high compression.
- Yeah.
- It's depression!
Yeah.
Xavier...
I know a good psychologist.
There's no shame
in getting help.
I'm leaving it here, man.
Just in case...
El Dorado!
Yeah!
Soman!
Simon!
Our good old glory days
are coming back!
[Timeline 3 - A.D. 1790
King Padmanabha's Kingdom]
♪ Vareeth ♪
- Get Kunjukunju here.
- Okay.
♪ Vareeth ♪
I heard you were
seeking me, sir.
Where were you, you idiot?
I was pondering an idea.
Go on then, speak.
Why not bring in more men
to finish this bridge sooner?
Indeed.
Bring in more men
when we cannot even pay
the ones we already have!
What a brilliant idea!
I knew you would like it, Master!
What do I even--
Pathetic!
What of my idea
to bring in more men, Master?
Ugh!
- Kunjukunju...
- Yes?
Do you know something?
No.
When I was an engineering student
in London,
the learned Father Victor
once told me this.
What?
Hey Vareeth...
You shall accomplish great feats.
You shall rise to great heights.
But you shall never
find peace in your life.
I remember those words each morning
when I see your face, Kunjukunju.
I see.
- Master...
- Yes?
As the learned Father said,
when you rise to great heights,
by God's grace, we shall both
stand by your side forever.
- Yes.
- Ugh!
Forever? Really?
Yes.
Oh Jesus...
Are my prayers
worth nothing to You?
Water Sahib is coming!
Hey! Hold that bottle straight!
You'll have me out of work.
Move that umbrella!
Good morning!
At noon? Get lost!
Everyone! Hear ye!
To inspect the progress
of the Nagathan bridge works,
here comes the Honourable
District Magistrate, Water Sahib.
My poor back will be
pounded to pulp again today!
Not Water Sahib, you idiots!
Walter!
District Magistrate
Lieutenant Colonel
Walter Joseph!
Do you understand?
Who's that fool
on the other side?
Oh no!
My Master!
- Who is this?
- Doomed!
- My bridge works are doomed!
- And so is my job!
Stupid idiots!
Nobody knows a damn thing.
Sahib...
Sir...
What is this?
A native remedy.
Good for all sprains.
- I don't want it.
- Go.
You fell because of me, Sir.
Please have the mercy
to try this remedy.
Give it now.
He'll have it.
Oh no!
- Mr. Vareeth Mappila!
- Sir.
Here is the East India Company's
final instalment for the
bridge construction fund.
Have the funds
from Padmanabhan arrived?
The King will release it
in two days, Sir.
Bloody hell!
Why is Padmanabhan delaying everything?
Word is the Viceroy himself
may attend the inauguration.
I've been a nervous wreck
ever since I heard it.
- Don't delay the work.
- I won't, Sir.
- Don't let me down.
- Never, Sir.
The Viceroy must never regret
appointing this Lieutenant Colonel
Walter Joseph as Magistrate.
No! Certainly not, sir!
The name, Mr. Walter Joseph, must be
remembered for generations.
- No, Sir.
- What?
I mean, it will be remembered
until the end of the world, Sir!
This bridge is my dream, Vareeth.
This bridge is going to
change our fortune forever.
I know it in my heart.
Don't worry, Sir.
The money will be here shortly.
Manager Narayanan Nair has
stepped up tax collection at the market.
A golden opportunity to pay taxes
to the royal treasury!
Merchants, come forth!
This way!
Chathunni, two coins.
Shankunni, one coin.
Look there!
The Royal Manager arrives!
Is the tax collection complete,
Achuthan?
Nearly so, my lord.
Some merchants insist
they cannot pay the tax.
- They cannot?
- Yes, my Lord.
Who are those wretches who claim
they cannot pay the King's tax?
Climbing out of pits?
What are you, an ant-lion?
You call that wit?
Nair, blame no one else
for refusing to pay the taxes.
From this day forth,
none of us will pay.
That is my decree.
Valiya Kelu's decree!
And might I ask
why you refuse to pay?
A merchant who thinks himself
greater than the King?
Hah! Your so-called King!
Shame upon him!
While the whole land starves,
he plunders the poor
in the name of taxes,
while he and his queen alone
wrap themselves in silk
and glitter with gold,
living in luxury!
Aye!
Well said, Master Kelu!
Insolence and treason
in one breath!
Where is my royal sword?
- Take this!
- Oh no!
Got it!
Where am I?
I'm of no Paanan, Parayan,
or Pulayan caste!
- Aren't you from the Nair caste?
- And you are no Emperor!
Shall we partake in some spirits?
Oh no! Huh!
You actually struck me?
Yes.
Your Majesty!
Behold!
Sovereign of the lands and peoples
between Travancore and Greater Kochi,
Emperor and Guardian of the Realm,
Master of the Whip-Blade...
Make way for His Majesty,
Sree Padmanabhan Thampuran!
♪ Grandmaster of the duel,
sovereign of the land ♪
♪ War-dance titan
none may ever withstand ♪
♪ Lord of the realm,
great master of valour ♪
♪ O fearless guardian,
protector of the order ♪
♪ The Infinite One,
Scion of the royal bloodstream ♪
♪ Despot of Empires,
Autocrat Supreme ♪
♪ Monarch of the blade,
king of every crown ♪
♪ Behold the mighty Padmanabha,
great king of renown ♪
♪ O valiant warden,
steadfast and brave ♪
Royal Manager Narayanan...
♪ Padmanabha, the mighty,
lord of the brave ♪
What grave cause
has summoned this gathering?
Are you unaware
that this is the hour when I play
my game of dice with the Queen?
Forgive me, Your Majesty.
Our merchants refuse
to render the tax
Your Majesty has decreed
for the royal treasury.
It is indeed true.
Kelu and his men
laid hands upon me at the market
when I went there in person
to levy Your Majesty's taxes.
Right here... and here.
I was left bruised and broken.
That too is true.
They demand a reduction in taxes?
Tell me, how great a reduction
do they demand?
A total exemption.
A total exemption, you say?
Do not attempt to frighten us
with your sword.
Moreover, we have no intention
of paying taxes from this day forth!
We have collectively
resolved to pledge
our allegiance
to King Kuttan of Kottayam.
Reduced to ruin by the tribute
you pay to mighty rulers
such as the Zamorin of Calicut
and the King of Thrissur,
while you live like a pauper within
this thatched hut you call a palace...
We consider it a disgrace to be
living as your subjects, Your Majesty!
Furthermore, we--
One leader will suffice here.
I have already assured Walter Sahib
that the King would settle
the payment in two days.
Who gave you permission
to say that?
Your Majesty!
Have my subjects
grown so audacious
as to question my authority?
In beheading the insolent
who dare defy the throne,
this King Padmanabhan
has always found great delight!
I thought he auctioned off his weapons.
Where did he dig that up from?
- Chop their heads, King!
- Shut up!
♪ Lord of the realm,
great master of valour ♪
♪ O fearless guardian,
protector of the order ♪
Oh no!
Isn't he dead?
Naraya...
Oh no!
Doomed!
My bridge construction
is doomed once more!
Rohini!
♪ Rohini ♪
- My King!
- Oh no!
Rohini, something just struck
the very middle of my spine, my beloved!
I cannot straighten myself.
What has befallen
the King, Chief Physician?
His back has sustained
a grave injury.
- This matter lies beyond my expertise.
- Heavens!
It would be prudent to summon
the Supreme Healer, Aandava Kaimal.
Aandava! (Oh Lord!)
He will not hear you
from this far away.
Silence, you imbecile!
- Who goes there!
- Yes, My Queen!
Dispatch someone to summon
the Supreme Healer Aandava Kaimal!
Yes, My Queen!
It will not do to send
just any fool.
Send a fool we can rely on.
In that case, summon
Koran the Charioteer at once.
- Hey...
- Yes?
You said we would marry
once the sun and rain were gone.
But the sun and rain
have not gone yet, my spring.
Koran!
The King has fallen on his back.
The Queen is summoning you.
I hope the King drops dead!
Oh dear...
- Your Majesty...
- Yes.
Koran the charioteer is here.
Koran… tell… tell…
- Tell what? I just got here!
- Not you!
Tell healer Kaimal
he is needed at once!
As you wish, Your Majesty.
What shall I say if he asks
about Your Majesty's condition?
Just tell him
the King has departed.
- Truly?
- Silence!
Is my end near?
No.
Koran, simply tell him
the royal back has broken.
- Huh?!
- Very well. I shall say exactly that.
One more thing, Your Majesty.
Since I must travel through the night
to meet such a distinguished healer,
to explain the gravity
of the situation,
may I be accompanied
by the Queen?
Very well, you may.
You may talk to each other along the road
and come back without going astray.
That will not be necessary!
He will proceed alone.
You ought to have let her
go with him.
Poor fellow!
To preserve my honour
before the British,
I must pay my share
for the bridge.
Between the merchants rebelling
by refusing to pay their taxes,
and the current condition
of my back,
we have no choice
but to unleash
Commander-in-Chief Kurup.
Once Kurup is unleashed,
he will not rest until the marketplace
is drenched in the merchants' blood.
Is such violence necessary?
Yes, yes.
It is absolutely necessary.
I want to witness the tears of those
merchants, especially Valiya Kelu.
Tell Commander-in-Chief
Koma Kurup
to return at once
with Maadan Kandappan's head.
♪ Commander of the Legion,
a hero of might ♪
♪ Upon his unsheathed steel,
his courage shines bright ♪
♪ Astride the war-cadence,
he lunges through the air ♪
♪ A blazing sun of fire,
with a blinding glare ♪
♪ Commander of the Legion,
a hero of might ♪
♪ Upon his unsheathed steel,
his courage shines bright ♪
♪ Astride the war-cadence,
he lunges through the air ♪
Salutations to the dwellers of Madanmala
from Commander-in-Chief Koman Kurup.
I have arrived to bring
a final end to your tribulations.
The brigand, Madan Kandappan,
intends to attack our village
once more tonight...
or so my spies have reported.
None of you need to be afraid.
I... I shall cut him to pieces.
This day's sunset
shall be Kandappan's final sunset!
Should I fail,
I swear by the gods of Kalari,
that my two loyal aides
at my left and right
shall lay down their lives
by striking their heads upon
the altar of your guardian deity!
- Count me out!
- Me neither!
Commander-in-Chief...
- It's Kandappan!
- Hmm.
♪ Commander of the Legion,
a hero of might ♪
Don't eat the dirt,
Commander-in-Chief!
The whole world will know
the palace has run out of food.
Huh?
Commander-in-Chief,
look at his arrogance!
How dare you stare at us!
- Kandappan!
Huh!
- Who here is the Commander-in-Chief?
- You.
Right!
Kandappan...
Today you meet your end!
- Huh?
- Huh!
What move is this?
Truly spectacular!
Wait, is he actually dead?
Whom did I dispatch
to the netherworld?
Whose army's banner is that?
Commander-in-Chief...
What is approaching us?
Heavens!
Tipu Sultan's army!
Tipu's Commander-in-Chief,
fresh from conquering the Zamorin...
Azam Khan!
♪ Azam Khan the King,
a lion of might ♪
♪ The valiant knight ♪
♪ Shoulders squared to reach the skies,
Bearing the lamp of justice high ♪
♪ The One of boundless glory
drawing nigh ♪
♪ Azam Khan the King,
a lion of might ♪
♪ The valiant knight ♪
♪ Shoulders squared to reach the skies,
Bearing the lamp of justice high ♪
♪ The One of boundless glory
drawing nigh ♪
Commander-in-Chief Koma Kurup!
What shall be
our next strategic move?
Huh! Oh no!
Commander Kurup!
Did you forget to take
something?
- Shall we come with you?
- Out of my way, you corpse!
Oh no!
Get going!
Commander-in-Chief!
What are we supposed to do?
You stay and fight!
I'll return with reinforcements!
What reinforcements
is he talking about?
We are the reinforcements!
- Lord Padmanabhan!
- Huh!
- Dragon!
- My Lord...
Proclaim that the rightful king
has arrived!
[Praying]
- Dragon!
- My Lord...
Should this kingdom
not know of your Lord's arrival?
Certainly!
They must know, my Lord!
Fire the cannon!
Let the land tremble!
After a crushing setback
in the local body polls,
and staying away from the media
for the past seven days,
Home & PWD Minister
P.P. Shashi
is reportedly arriving shortly
at the Painavu Guest House.
Yes, he's arriving now.
We believe he will finally
address the media today.
That's why the media has gathered here.
♪ Deep in the emerald wild
where the dark woods abide ♪
♪ Raising the revolt's immortal red banner
where raging clouds collide ♪
♪ O Crimson Star who shattered
the chains of slavery; our pride ♪
♪ Red Salute ♪
Aashaan, why have you been avoiding
the press since the election results?
And how do you respond to the opposition's
allegation that you were in hiding?
What is the party's present situation, sir?
As a senior leader,
is fear the reason for your silence
after such a staggering defeat
for your party?
Fear, you say?
After pocketing the welfare pension
and every benefit from the government
and stuffing their bellies,
they shamelessly voted
for someone else!
That's what happened.
This has nothing to do
with fear or failure.
Whose money do you think
tax revenue is?
- It belongs to the public.
- What tax money?
This is all borrowed money,
you... you "presstitute"!
I won't give anyone even a penny now,
even if they're starving!
Not a chance!
It's because they still
have the strength to stand
that they keep changing their vote
whenever they feel like it.
- Hey George...
- Yes.
Invite that annoying reporter
who asked the last question
for an "exclusive interview"
near the dam tonight.
- Done deal, Aashaan.
- Good. Go.
Hey, Hyderali!
The fish at the dam
haven't been fed for a while!
They keep barging in!
They ask whatever they like,
and I must answer
exactly the way they want!
These losers follow me
everywhere I go.
So annoying!
As if I am...
Aashaan!!!
Where did this guy pop up from?
You scared the life out of me!
- Who are you?
- Xavier.
People call me Satan Xavier.
Ah, I know who you are.
You're the one
who owns those estates, right?
What are you doing here?
I prefer a direct approach,
just like you, Aashaan.
That is precisely how I operate.
So I will come
straight to the point.
I need you to do me
a favour, Aashaan.
And there is something
in it for you too.
Consider this a small sample.
It is a diamond, Aashaan.
A genuine diamond.
Do you really think
a diamond is enough to sway me?
No, no, this isn't for you, sir!
I am not foolish enough
to think I can sway you with a bribe!
Even children in Kerala know
you cannot be bought that way.
This stone is for the development
of your High Range hills.
Sell it and it will
fetch a fortune.
That money can go straight
into your High Range development fund.
Don't rely on the bankrupt
government treasury.
If the job gets done, I'll give you
many more stones like this.
The development you could bring
by selling all those diamonds
could turn our High Range
hills into another Bolivia.
Then the people shall hail you
as the "Che Guevara"
of the High Range hills!
Did he stop breathing?
♪ Deep in the emerald wild
where the dark woods abide ♪
♪ Raising the revolt's
immortal red banner ♪
[background score
goes Spanish mode]
♪ O Crimson Star ♪
♪ Red Salute ♪
♪ Saludo Rojo ♪
- Rajesh...
- Yeah?
- Handle this with care, okay?
- Alright.
Don't get caught by anyone.
- Catch you next week.
- See you then.
Yes, sir.
It's definitely Rajesh,
the Urban Naxalite.
He has entered
the building complex, sir.
I'm tailing him closely, sir.
Yeah, fine. And you?
- Hey!
- Hey! Stop there!
- Out of the way!
- Move, move!
Stop there, you!
♪ Left, Right,
Left, Right ♪
♪ If valour ever claimed a name,
If the fight for truth ignites a flame ♪
♪ Who is the man emerging,
drenched in citrus sting? ♪
♪ O Sarbath ♪
♪ Shameer... Shameer...
O Sarbath Shameer! ♪
♪ Shameer is in town, yeah ♪
♪ Left, Right,
Left, Right ♪
S.K.!
Make it tight.
It's a convention
with nearly a thousand people.
At least a hundred of them
need to go down.
Only a hundred?
- Let's make it 150 then.
- Fine.
- It's Rajesh.
- Okay.
♪ Shameer... Shameer... ♪
Get in!
Good morning, sir.
Good morning.
Oh my God!
Do you think you can trick Sarbath Shameer
by showing extra respect?
Rascal!
Thomachan...
Film everything!
Okay, sir.
Huh!
Flattened rice, flowers,
and ghee coconut.
Are you heading
to Sabarimala Temple, Jesus?
You've got balls
in all shapes and sizes, old man!
Even at your age,
you're still itching for action, huh?
I'll fix that!
Get over there!
Sir!
A for "Aashaan"!
You swapped Apple for "Aashaan,"
didn't you?
- Dhanaya!
- Sir!
What on earth is this?
It's a brilliant plan, sir.
This right here is "Physics."
And that over there is "Chemistry."
And that up there
is "Diplomacy," sir.
These are nothing but
cunning schemes!
- Total frauds!
- I'll go and start the vehicle.
Even if you had spent half
this energy on studies,
you'd already have
a government job!
- Dhanaya!
- Yes!
They didn't laugh!
- Run! Run! Run!
Can't you rascals laugh
when sir cracks a joke?
Huh!
Sir, they've disappeared!
- Oh no! Where did they go?
- Who knows!
Good heavens!
They locked us inside!
- Why weren't you watching?
- I was learning from you, sir.
Then why carry a gun
and call yourself a cop?
You told me not to carry the gun,
so I left it in the police locker.
Otherwise, I'd have shot them
through the window--
Just shut up!
You'd have botched it anyway!
I told you not to take a gun
because I didn't want civilians
killed by your stray bullets!
- Oh!
- Did you know?
After leaving that lodge,
they drove the police vehicle for fifty
kilometres and fled into the forest.
Then they removed its battery.
And punctured
all four tires.
As if that wasn't enough,
the video of you being dragged out of that
locked room is now all over social media!
- Oh no!
- That humiliation is a separate issue.
What sort of fools are you?
- We're the best in the High Range, sir!
- Shut up!
Oh no!
Aashaan!
He's coming to hand-deliver
my suspension papers!
I should never get caught.
Great. Both of you
blocking the way like a dam!
No wonder
the state treasury is empty!
Move, move, move!
- I'll deal with you later!
- Get over here!
Where is that moron Shameer?
Shameer was here, sir.
He was here,
and now he's gone?
- Go find him now!
- Sir!
The moment I step into his station,
I start itching.
Hey Shameer...
Yeah!
♪ If valour ever claimed a name ♪
Are you busy, Shameer sir?
I was looking for
something I lost yesterday.
If that something is your brain,
don't bother.
You won't find it.
Even if you had just whistled,
I'd have come running.
Whistle or shout,
how could you reach me
while you were locked in by Naxalites?
- Well, then I--
- Stop!
If you open your mouth,
I'll change my mind.
So keep your mouth shut
and just listen to me.
Shameer...
I need you
to do something for me.
No one else should know.
It must be strictly confidential!
For you, Aashaan,
I would--
I've seen this quite a lot.
No need to fall
at my feet.
Just get the job done.
Consider it done.
Your humble slave
will do it, Aashaan.
Otherwise,
your cap and your head will end up
on my desk again as paperweights!
Stay still. Hold.
Hey! Show a little of your brother
Moonga's energy!
Are you trying
to yank my spine out?
We might have to pour
some concrete into that spine, Paappan.
- Shajiyetta!
- Yeah, and then bury you in it.
Shajiyetta, look!
Your mom's here!
- Mom?
- And she's brought your Stella with her!
- Huh?
- Good heavens!
♪ No, Paappan ♪
♪ She'll ditch you, Paappan ♪
- Oh, Stella...
- ♪ No, Paappan ♪
♪ You'll be in deep trouble, Paappan ♪
- Please wait for five minutes.
- Okay.
♪ You'll be in deep trouble, Paappan ♪
Mom, I was just about to--
I didn't come here
to speak with you.
I only came because she said
she had something to tell you.
- Go on, tell him.
- Okay.
I'm not staying away because
Mom doesn't let me enter the house.
He's staying away because
she's always home.
Don't I know how things are, Paappan?
I got a marriage proposal
from Erattupetta last month.
My father is going
to fix the marriage.
Oh no!
Since you never gave me
a solid promise...
I said yes.
So sad!
So that's gone too!
We're still rejoicing
over Paappan's house being seized!
Don't talk to us
so heartlessly!
Ugh, this guy!
- Captain!
- Did I say anything wrong?
Alright then, Paappan.
- Hope I'll see you again somewhere.
- Okay, bye. See you.
- Aunty...
- Yes?
Let's leave.
Why should I waste my time
being around these losers anyway!
Come, let's get out of here.
What will you do now, Shajiyetta?
What can I do now?
I'll just pray to God
not to give her
a happy married life.
Huh?!
Mom!
- What now?
- Just hold on a second.
- Did he feel bad?
- Yeah.
Err...
Your marriage is fixed, right?
You carry on. Let me talk to mom.
What is it now?
I've been meaning to visit you.
Why?
Happy Birthday!
Well...
I don't have a gift for you.
I'm completely broke.
Oh, my son...
This is all I have.
Okay.
Shaji, my son!
What would I ever do
without you, old lady?
Aww!
- Cute mom and son.
- Yes.
Like Baby Jesus and Mother Mary!
Mark my words.
You'll make it big!
- Shall I leave?
- Yes.
This scene would move
anyone to tears.
True!
Let it go, man.
- Hey...
- Yeah?
Didn’t you say the rent
for our new club was overdue?
It’s been due for a while now.
We'll settle that today.
- Huh?
- How exactly?
I have my ways.
Just watch.
Shaji, my son...
Come over here a second.
She's calling you!
- What is it, Mom?
- Come, we might get something too.
- What is it?
- Son...
Mom forgot to give
one little thing to you.
- What?
- This right here!
Yikes!
Give me my necklace!
What... nec... nec... necklace?
Not "What... nec... nec... necklace!"
I'm asking you to return
my necklace!
The moment you kissed me,
I knew you’d at least
try to steal a kidney.
- Give it back!
- Why does the hen need eggs?
- What?
- No, I thought...
I'd keep it safely
so you wouldn't pawn it off.
Oh, shut up and give it back!
Hand it over!
Listen, girl!
You’re better off marrying
someone else, sweetie.
Or else he'll strip you
of everything you own!
Get in.
- Shall we go?
- Paappan...
So, what about
the unpaid club rent?
Well, it’s back to being overdue.
Anyway, your luck
is at an all-time low.
Lost the girl, got caught during
a robbery and got thrashed!
Who knows
what calamity awaits next!
Why don't we consult that Babaji?
Which Pav Bhaji?
Not Pav Bhaji.
Let's go to Raman Panicker.
You mean that dark sorcerer,
Chudala Raman?
He's no sorcerer.
He's a top-tier wizard!
Hey, move aside.
A sorcerer will be perfect.
If he ties Paappan down
and hammers a nail into his skull,
everything will be solved!
Pick up a six-inch nail
on the way there.
And drive it
right into his mouth!
We can settle
for three inches too!
A threat over our heads!
The bridge called Nagathan!
- Sir...
- Yes?
We've all seen
the Nagathan bridge.
Why demolish
a perfectly good bridge, sir?
Did you shake the bridge
to see if it was weak?
- No, sir.
- Well, Aashaan did!
If Aashaan says it's weak,
we demolish it.
- Sir...
- Yes?
The one leading the slogans
at the front...
Isn't that Kokkachi Kareem
who got bail last week?
Then what? Should they bring Chachaji
instead of Kokkachi to raise slogans here?
Zip it!
Long live the people's protest!
In these terrible times!
A threat over our heads!
[Josettan's Tea Shop]
Hand me that newspaper.
Here you go, Paappan.
Come on, Paappan,
what's wrong with what I said?
Just give it a rest, will you?
Nothing's wrong.
Go on, Kunjikka.
You think the scrap business
is a bad idea?
You'll be rolling in millions!
And you already have the perfect property
to start your scrap business.
Why don't we
kick things off with that?
I'm not selling Cleetus
for scrap!
No! I'm not talking about Cleetus!
I'm talking about your van!
Even Mammootty offered to buy this van,
and we turned him down.
And you think we'd sell it
to you, Kunjikka?
Are you trying to kill me
before my time?
Well, just think about the van
and let me know.
Fine, I'll think about it.
- Tea's on me.
- No, no!
You may go.
I'll pay.
I'll keep in touch then.
- Sure thing.
- Alright then.
About the van--
Enough about the van.
Just get your butt moving!
Hey! Stop right there!
Where do you think you're going
without paying?
You're asking us
where we're going?
Even your dad
wouldn't dare ask that!
He might not.
But I will. Pay up!
Hey!
You little brat...
While you were still running through your
dad's veins, I was running the show here!
Do you know who I am?
No.
Paappan.
Shaji Paappan!
Oh! So you are Shaji Paappan!
Wait a minute!
Just a minute.
Ah!
You owe us ₹8500.
Leave only after
paying the money!
You show the debt book
to anyone who says their name?
This isn't a joke book.
It's the debt book.
Pay up!
Where would I go
without paying you, dear?
- Paappan!
- I'll pay up.
Yeah!
I'll leave and never
come back. Okay?
- You! I'll send your middle stump flying--
- Hey!
If you dare to touch my boy...
Get moving, you pest!
Convey my regards to your dad!
- Who'll pay a year's bill?
- Not me!
Were you busy, Paappan?
Yeah, busy doing nothing.
What's up?
It's this classic Paappan humour
we need for the closing speech.
A closing speech?
Yes, the vote of thanks.
Paappan, the Village Council is holding
a cultural summit on the 17th.
See that flex board there?
As part of the event, we'll honour
many personalities from our village,
who've made significant
contributions in various fields.
And how could we ever forget
your legendary contribution to Tug-of-War?
You must definitely attend the ceremony
and accept this honour, Paappan.
You'll come, right?
Is there any payment?
What you're getting
is far more precious than money.
Must be diamonds.
I'm not sharing it with you.
- A ceremonial shawl.
- Huh?!
Say what?!
Why did your face fall
when I said ceremonial shawl?
Don't you remember?
Didn't we honour you
with a ceremonial shawl
at the last community wedding?
One more thing, Paappan...
I've put your name down
for a ₹500 donation for the event.
I'll collect the cash later.
At least pay for the 50-rupee
shawl yourself, you cheapskates!
This is the classic Paappan humour!
That's Paappan's pressure point!
Now get out of here.
I'll pay up.
See you at the event!
Man, these guys deserve
to be the ministers here.
By the way, when did actor Mammootty
offer to buy our van?
When did he say that?
Weren't you the one
blabbering about it back there?
Some higher power makes
me say those things, Paappan!
Then tell your "higher power"
to tone it down a little.
Shajiyett!
Paappan!
Oi!
Today is our appointment with the
astrologer, Raman Panicker. Let's go.
Fine, sorcerer or whatever.
Let's go.
Is our luck really
that bad, Paappan?
Trust me,
the worst is yet to come!
Come.
If this involves a lot of hiking,
count me out.
It's not far, dude. We just have
get past this hill to find him.
Does anything he says
ever work?
Clearly! Why else would we be
"working" our way up this hill?
Look, I see someone
who looks human over there.
Obviously.
Did you think this was a zoo?
Why is that fellow
sitting like that?
He's meditating.
Oh, then he must be a Christian.
Shut up, Paappan!
How do we let him know we're here?
What's with all these chickens?
Is this some barbecue joint?
- I'm hungry.
- Yeah.
He has made fried chickens fly.
So did he tie them up now
so they wouldn't fly away?
Ugh!
He actually did it!
Panicker...
Has he departed?
Panicker! Oi!
Keep your voice down, Captain!
See, he has opened his eyes.
The one burdened with sorrow,
step forward.
- I'm ready.
- Move, man.
Make way, boys.
The elder of the group,
step forward and be seated.
Believe it or not,
you look like a senior citizen.
- He meant you, Shajiyettan.
- Huh!?
Go ahead, Shajiyettan.
He thought it was
a walking stick.
Sit in the bare state.
- Oh, do I have to strip bare now?
- What are you doing?!
Hey!
Just take off
your sandals and sit!
Oh, is that how you say that?
Can't you at least
get a couple of chairs on EMI?
Oh boy...
Don't sit like you're about
to take a dump. Sit properly.
Even while burdened
with so many troubles,
you still don't truly
believe in this, do you?
Our Old Testament warns that
the Lord will destroy the superstitious.
And yet, fate has brought you
before me.
So now, sit in silence.
- Sit silently.
- Captain!
Silence!
[chanting]
Look at him laying out
those Skibidis.
It's Kavadi (Cowrie shells).
Oh, that's
what they're called?
[continues chanting]
I've made my move.
It's your turn now, Sorcerer.
Huh!
Hey!
- This is your problem!
- Oh, did I move it to the wrong spot?
You're too impulsive!
Yeah, I knew that!
You must be more
careful when you play.
- You just lost a pawn!
- Stop it!
The path of the religious man
is the best!
Huh? What language is this?
It's Greek.
- How are we supposed to follow this?
- You will follow soon enough.
Look at him.
Lord Ayyappa! I'll offer you
genuine golden plates!
Shaji Paappan!
What is it?
You will ride
into battle on horseback,
like a king.
With his sprained back?
- Ruined it!
- Paappan has always been our King.
He'll arrive on horseback.
Sometimes he'll even arrive on a donkey.
Haven't you witnessed
such visions before?
I have.
A great battle
is about to unfold.
Your companions will perish
in the middle of that battle.
- Huh?
- Huh!
From then on,
you will have to fight
all by yourself, Paappan.
Do you not see
the cosmos aligning?
Gateways to unknown realms
are about to open.
The time for you
to fight is drawing near.
The very survival of this world
rests upon your victory.
You need not pay me.
You may leave.
But remember...
Victory...
must be inevitable
for you in every lifetime.
Mother Goddess!
There she is!
Cassandra!
How far did the Captain say?
Almost a hundred marine miles.
Hmm.
One more day.
What's happening?
- They have not finished eating yet.
- Is that so?
Mr. Padmanabhan...
The very thought
that came to your mind
would surely have
come to mine as well,
because I am brilliant.
Such is the way of things.
Great minds truly do think alike.
Indeed. Therefore,
we must begin our exodus today.
Let's flee!
Flee?
What in heaven's name
are you saying?
Since the East India Company
stands as our ally,
we can fight Azam Khan together.
That's what I meant!
Fight him?
You mean... war?
No!
Forget the fact that we do not
possess even one tenth of his forces.
He has cannons.
Let that pass as well.
He has got something even
bigger in his arsenal.
A big one!
What might that be?
That's called
the bloody Mysore Rocket.
Not even the East India Company
possesses such a weapon.
The orders are clear:
we are to hold our ground.
That means... fight to death!
To go up
in gunpowder smoke!
- Huh!
- Oh no!
I refuse to do that.
- I'm out of here today!
- So are we!
I, however,
shall remain and fight.
Poor!
Good luck, mate.
Good luck.
Until now, I had heard
only stories of exoduses.
By Your Majesty's grace, I now have
the fortune to witness one for myself.
My companion,
my pride!
Fire the cannon!
The Sultan's secret weapon!
My own invention.
The Mysore Rocket!
Fire!
Within two days, Padmanabhan's kingdom
shall be under my command.
♪ Lion of Mysore, brave and grand,
Your fame resounds through every land ♪
♪ By our motherland we vow to thee,
We shall lay down our lives most gladly ♪
♪ Lion of Mysore, brave and grand,
Your fame resounds through every land ♪
♪ By our motherland we vow to thee,
We shall lay down our lives most gladly ♪
♪ Lion of Mysore, brave and grand,
Your fame resounds through every land ♪
♪ By our motherland we vow to thee,
We shall lay down our lives most gladly ♪
♪ We shall lay down
our lives most gladly ♪
♪ O, Love Divine! ♪
♪ The Sultan who marches
to conquer the earth ♪
♪ A lone stag in this duel,
gleaming like gold in its worth ♪
♪ O, Love Divine! ♪
♪ The Sultan who marches
to conquer the earth ♪
♪ A lone stag in this duel,
gleaming like gold in its worth ♪
♪ My Sultan!
Lion-king Sultan! ♪
♪ Star of stars Sultan!
Valiant warrior Sultan! ♪
♪ The victor of Mysore,
mighty in renown ♪
♪ A hero the Huzoor
proudly calls his own ♪
♪ My Sultan!
Lion-king Sultan! ♪
♪ Star of stars Sultan!
Valiant warrior Sultan! ♪
The injury is in the fourteenth
vertebra of the spinal cord.
I fear this back pain will plague you
for many lifetimes to come.
Many lifetimes?!
♪ O, Love Divine! ♪
♪ Lion of Mysore, brave and grand,
Your fame resounds through every land ♪
♪ By our motherland we vow to thee,
We shall lay down our lives most gladly ♪
Wow!
At the sight of our arsenal
and our valiant soldiers,
I feel an urge
to march to battle tomorrow.
- What say you, Kurup?
- Indeed, Your Majesty.
Must we lead these thirty-seven men
to their deaths tomorrow itself?
Hey! Don't jinx it!
Follow me.
You have bound all the weapons in silk
threads for their safekeeping?
- Huh!
- Good job!
Brush away those cobwebs
and show them to His Majesty.
Has the sword
turned into a knife over time?
♪ As the Supreme Ruler Badshah
ascends the throne ♪
♪ My longing gaze
seeks you alone ♪
♪ Drenched in blood,
the monarch's blade ♪
♪ On its hilt where
the royal hand is laid ♪
♪ You are the priceless gem
set in that blade ♪
When that coward Azam Khan
arrives, inform him
that this District Court Magistrate
Lieutenant Colonel Walter Joseph
has no intention of speaking
with anyone except Tipu Sultan.
♪ An empire growing mightier day by day,
Are you the emperor who holds its sway? ♪
♪ The Sultan who marches
to conquer the earth ♪
♪ A lone stag in this duel,
gleaming like gold in its worth ♪
♪ The Sultan who marches
to conquer the earth ♪
♪ A lone stag in this duel,
gleaming like gold in its worth ♪
♪ My Sultan!
Lion-king Sultan! ♪
♪ Star of stars Sultan!
Valiant warrior Sultan! ♪
♪ O, Love Divine! ♪
♪ Lion of Mysore, brave and grand,
Your fame resounds through every land ♪
♪ By our motherland we vow to thee,
We shall lay down our lives most gladly ♪
♪ Lion of Mysore, brave and grand,
Your fame resounds through every land ♪
♪ By our motherland we vow to thee,
We shall lay down our lives most gladly ♪
♪ Lion of Mysore, brave and grand,
Your fame resounds through every land ♪
♪ By our motherland we vow to thee,
We shall lay down our lives most gladly ♪
What happened here?
Where is everyone?
Azam Khan coming.
Big army.
He kill all.
We all escaping, Madam.
Are these Azam Khan and boys
going to be a problem for us?
No. It's a blessing in disguise.
But we need to find Walter first.
- Thank you.
In my mind...
a most brilliant battle strategy
is taking shape.
The Nagathan bridge is now being
constructed across this river.
For their vast army
to cross this river,
a bridge is essential.
Boats alone will never suffice.
Thus,
let's destroy this bridge.
When desperation forces them
to cross the river
in small boats,
we can kill them one by one
by raining arrows from this vantage point.
What are your thoughts?
What can we say?
What do you think of
my genius, Narayanan?
Well...
My brilliance has rendered
you speechless, hasn't it?
Not quite.
Would it not be wiser to cross the
bridge and flee while we still can?
Hey, Narayanan!
Do not speak such nonsense!
But, my Lord...
Majority of our soldiers
fled the moment they heard
of Azam Khan's arrival,
and have not been seen since.
The word is they ran
without stopping,
crossed beyond the kingdom's borders,
and fled for good.
Cowards!
Where is Commander-in-Chief Kurup?
Summon him!
♪ Commander of the Legion,
a hero of might ♪
Your Highness...
Splendid!
To lift my spirits
in this time of crisis,
you have arrived to perform
some art form, I suppose?
Summon the royal dancers as well.
- Let the performance begin.
- Which dancers?
They must have fled and reached
the end of the earth by now.
This is no time for performances, my Lord.
It is time to flee.
Since this morning,
we all have become Muslims.
Thus I am no longer Kurup,
but Abu Salah.
Abu Salah.
This here is Salaam.
Salaam.
And this one…
who were you again?
Saifullah Hidhayath Al Anthruvan.
- Huh?
- Just "Anthru" will do.
The word is that General Khan
does not slay
his Muslim brethren.
Truly?
Your Majesty!
Kurup! How could you--
Is it not better to lose
a little skin from the body
than to have one's head
severed from the neck?
Your Majesty,
we shall be safe here from now on.
But as for you...
Your Majesty, a message
has come from King Elayidathu.
They have already
begun their exodus.
It would be wise
to take the Royal Family
and seek refuge in the woods.
Your Majesty...
We do not bid farewell at night.
- Assalamu Alaikum.
- Salaam.
♪ Commander of the Legion,
a hero of might ♪
Don't look back,
or he'll summon us again!
And the Commander-in-Chief has
made his exit too!
What about you?
Do you want to exit too?
Never.
I'll betray you to Azam Khan
and remain here as his loyal servant.
You are carrying
the jest a little too far.
Who knows whether we shall have
the chance to jest ever again.
But in all seriousness,
Your Majesty...
Why are you so determined
to remain here?
We need not abandon the land
like the others.
Could we not remain hidden
for a few days?
Once that wretched Khan
returns to Mysore, we may return!
Nair...
Years ago, even when
the Portuguese Gama came,
my ancestors never
abandoned this land.
They never even attempted to.
They stood guard
over this palace and its riches.
And now this Azam Khan...
has not come
to this humble village
without reason.
What could his motive be, Highness?
What do we possess
that holds such great value?
Oh no! Oh no!
My Lord!
These men are from
the King's guard.
We seized them as they were fleeing.
They strayed from their path
and walked straight into our hands.
Yet they hold only the most
basic knowledge of the palace.
- Yes!
- True, Lord!
We know absolutely nothing, Lord!
Excellent! In reward for
telling me nothing of worth,
have their heads severed
and mounted on spears outside the tent!
- As you command, Lord.
- Oh no!
Oh no, Lord!
Not merely basic information,
we know remarkable secrets!
Hey! Tell him!
I have eight children, man!
Lord... it is but hearsay.
[whispers a secret]
So the tale I heard is true.
In a matter of days,
all of it shall be mine!
To celebrate this news, rip out the tongues
of the men who revealed it!
- Oh no!
- Lord!
Oh no!
- Your Majesty!
- You've lost your balance.
Mind the stairs.
I'm doing fine now.
Follow me.
I'm right behind you.
What brings you here
at this hour, Mappila?
I only came to show my face.
What else would you show
His Highness but your face?!
Do not utter such nonsense
at this twilight hour!
Okay.
Look at him!
Our engineer has laid aside
his official robes,
and has come prepared
to defend the kingdom.
Vareeth, only the brave
get the honour of...
a glorious death in battle.
Death?
- So, are we not leaving?
- We are.
What's all the whispering about?
It's nothing, Your Majesty.
They say Tipu's forces will arrive
in two days.
The villagers have already
begun to flee.
Cowards!
There is little point continuing
the bridge work now, is there?
So my men and I
were thinking of making
a strategic retreat to Travancore.
Why?
There, the mighty and powerful
Lord Padmanabhan will protect us.
Why? Do you doubt my strength?
I do not doubt it.
But my men remain unconvinced.
Hey Mappila...
The King had planned to raise
your status to the heavens.
I am in no haste to reach
the heavens just yet, Nair.
I'll go to Travancore
and work my way up gradually.
So I thought I would pay
my final respects before leaving.
I need your blessings.
We don't bid farewell at night.
So are we not leaving tonight?
Come on.
Vareeth Mappila, wait.
Nagathan bridge's construction
must be completed within two days.
- Huh?!
- On a war footing.
Why, Lord?
Won't they destroy the bridge?
Then would not all our efforts
be in vain?
They will not destroy the bridge.
Everyone needs the bridge, do they not?
Go and gather workers at once.
Tell them they will be paid
four or five times the wages.
I shall send Narayanan
with a formal letter...
and the required funds.
You may leave, Vareeth.
- You come with me.
- Okay.
What if we toss the letter
in the river and flee with the money?
- Ugh!
- Bad idea?
What if we discard the letter
and run off with the money?
Huh?
Here you go.
A threat over our heads!
The bridge called Nagathan!
Chief...
This protest is going
to be headache for us.
What headache?
No chance!
There are barely
seven people out there.
We are not going
to demolish a bridge for them.
Oh no! That won't do.
The bridge must be demolished.
If not, I'll have to resign
and join the frontline of that protest!
Fine, go ahead and resign then.
- That's better.
- Huh!
At least I will finally
have some peace in this office!
CM, if we demolish the old bridge,
we can build a new one.
Building a new bridge will be viewed
as an administrative reform.
Doesn't my department deserve
a chance to transform?
Ugh, you are becoming unbearable!
Fine, do whatever you want.
Damn it!
- Hey Shashi...
- Yes.
Is this going to create
more trouble later?
Why are you talking like that, Chief?
Clinging to this rusty old bridge,
what trouble could come
other than me?
Let me go!
Please let me go!
Michael...
I will repeat myself
one final time.
You stole a page from an ancient book
that everybody thought was a fairy tale.
Where is it?
Lady, I swear...
I'll call the police.
Police?
Go ahead.
Scream.
For every sound you make,
you will lose one finger.
Come on.
Scream.
Who are you people?
Michael...
I am associating with
some very serious people
and they don't like delays.
We had been to the
State Archive Directorate at Trivandrum.
We know you stole the page.
So, tell me...
Where is it?
Where is the location?
I don't know.
Wrong answer!
Please! No!
Get his phone.
I need that bloody location.
The deadline for submitting tenders
to demolish the Nagathan Bridge
via controlled implosion ended yesterday.
A press conference regarding the awarding
of the contract is currently underway.
On to it.
Thirteen companies have
submitted quotations
to demolish the Nagathan Bridge
through controlled implosion.
The company that submitted
the lowest quotation,
Xavier and Dawood Associates
from Mumbai,
will demolish the bridge.
- What's going on?
- I have no clue!
Has he gone completely nuts, Soman?
- Here.
- I don't need it.
Is this contagious?
Hey, wait!
Look, Paappan, your scrap business
idea is all well and good.
Those iron rods and wheels
you mentioned are indeed old.
But they are on Kerala
State Electricity Board property!
Without issuing a tender,
we cannot simply hand them to you.
Can we get this trend...
I mean, that thing, without anyone knowing?
Sure, if you manage
to become
the Chief Minister of Kerala.
Won't that take a lot of time?!
My dear Paappan, stop wasting my time
and find something that will actually work.
- Convey my regards to Rachel!
- Genzy!
Hey! You can make this happen! Hey!
Her name is Gen Z!
Yet she is as outdated
as Paappan himself!
Stop blabbering! Come.
He was talking to you.
You two are listed
as the Kerala proprietors for
Xavier & Dawood Associates.
Yeah, yeah.
I see you have experience
handling several explosions
across the country.
Yes, we do.
Even so, I must say...
You will be held fully responsible
for this explosion.
- Absolutely.
- Here you go.
- Sir...
- Yes.
Not just this explosion...
from now on, for every explosion in India
we will be responsible.
Yeah, fine. Whatever!
Safety during the explosion,
and clearing the debris
afterward.
All of that will be your responsibility.
And if there is any casualty
during the explosion,
you will be the first ones
charged with manslaughter.
- Got it?
- What was that mansl...?
Murder charge!
Fine, carry on.
Get lost!
- Good thing you're with me.
- I'm not coming.
Let's just forget about
this scrap business.
But that's how guys like
Ambani and Tata made it big.
Who on earth are they?
- What happened, Paappan?
- Hey!
Doesn't he look like
that loser we know?
Battery Simon.
- It's definitely that loser.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Chill. I won't shoot a video.
Pauper!
I mean, Paappan!
- So, you're a lawyer now?
- Yeah. At the bar of debt.
You're looking pretty sharp.
- Like a corpse in a coffin!
- Thanks.
By the way,
I've been looking for you.
Oh...
You tried to kidnap my
sister Rachel, did you not?
See!
Didn't I tell you
Paappan would ask that?
We weren't trying to kidnap her.
We were just mollycoddling her!
- Oh no!
- What is this?
Yes. Proceed, Your Honour.
- I am ready.
- It's in English.
- What is this?
- This is a cover.
- Isn't that what I said?
So there's a new player on board?
Hmm.
Let's play along then.
Hey! Isn't this for me to spit into?
Anyone can spit in it,
can't they?
Why are we in the cellar?
Did you bring me here to do chores?
Move this mat aside.
Do not stand there like a pole.
Bring that torch!
You're the first person I've ever
brought in here besides me.
What is that?
I dropped the spittoon.
The spittoon? Now?
Come this way.
This is a treasure passed down
through generations, Narayanan.
I know that.
After all, you haven't even done something
worth a proverb on your own!
Hey!
No king in these parts
possesses such wealth.
Everyone saw my hard times
and believed this rare treasure
was only a legend.
And I never went about
speaking of it.
Except you,
this palace holds many
priceless things.
- Isn't it?
- Narayanan!
Not another word from you!
- I'll do the talking.
- Sure.
Azam Khan did not come here...
for this priceless treasure alone.
Then?
Come with me.
This rare gemstone.
It emerged from an unknown realm
beyond the heavens.
Such is the legend
bestowed upon us by our ancestors.
It is believed to wield a force
unknown to mankind.
We call it Star Dust.
Under no circumstances,
must it fall into
another's hands.
What shall we do with it,
Your Majesty?
At first I thought of taking it
with me when I flee.
But if I am captured,
I will lose my life
and the stone with it.
True.
So follow my instructions...
exactly, and in complete secrecy.
Go...
and tell the guards to be ready.
Okay.
And do not go spreading the word
about what you saw here.
Never!
Comrades!
According to our readings,
the Stardust has become active
once again after centuries.
From now on,
critical events will unfold
across multiple timelines!
The King himself sent this...
so the bridge would not weaken.
Amulets blessed
with sacred chants.
Jesus, protect us!
Everything has been done
as you commanded.
- Subhadra, come.
- Shall we begin our escape?
We shall.
For one last time,
let me behold my entire realm.
What if I never return?
Scrap agreement.
First Party: Shaji Paappan
of Pannimattom.
Second Party: For Xavier
and Dawood Associates,
Soman Pachilakkunnil
and Simon Batteryparambil.
The agreement seems fine.
Since Rachel paid
the ₹10,000 on time,
we managed to secure the deal.
Abu...
I have a feeling...
once we get the scrap
from this bridge,
we're going to make it big!
Yes.
Like finding an egg
from a chicken biryani!
Yeah, right!
This will be yet another chapter
in Paappan's book of blunders.
- Stop it!
- What?
Take them away soon,
and let me stay here, Jesus!
Hey, Sulaiman!
Sulaiman!
Napping at work?
Moron!
Wake up!
Hey, you!
Haven't I told you a thousand times
not to daydream during work hours?
You have, boss.
Get up, you lazy bum!
If I catch you resting
one more time...
Rest in peace!
Move it!
Get back to work!
Moron!
Even the donkey got lazy
after hanging around this idiot!
There's no way out, Antony.
Just keep pulling.
Are you seeing this, DK?
Maruthunayagam's kicks
turned poor Dude's spine
to jelly.
Are you going to run away
like the other guy?
Look, Paily…
I'm not going
anywhere without Dude.
Dude is my god.
My own god.
Good for you.
We are all going to die getting
beaten up in this bandit's copra yard.
Hey! Get back to work!
On it!
With the old boss, all we had to do
was make parottas.
If we burn down his hotel
and try to run away,
- do you think he'll spare us?
- Exactly!
I won't spare you guys.
My uncle sold you to me
so I could make you work like slaves.
I won't let you go
until I recover the loss you caused him
with interest.
And you won't finish paying it
in this lifetime.
- Sulaiman!
- Yes?
Don't even dream of
escaping from my clutches.
Maruthu sir, at least add
some salt to this gruel.
I won't go anywhere.
Hey! Just shut up and eat
what you're given, you idiot!
Boss!
Listen here, you rascal!
You have to wake up early
and go break rocks.
Breaking rocks?!
Oh, my god!
Dude sir...
I'm sick of this life!
I couldn't even make it
to Hong Kong.
Forget that.
My Kerala...
I just want to see my Kerala
at least once.
Not Hong Kong, you baboon!
It was Bangkok!
We're already screwed
and I've got zero patience left.
So don't get me started.
I'm literally dying
to see Kerala again.
Dude sir...
Let's somehow escape from here.
It's not that I don't want to, Paily.
But I can't leave
without my Antony.
They treat people like trash here,
and he's worried about a donkey!
Antony!
Hey Antony...
You know what?
I have to work
at the quarry tomorrow.
You've got the day off.
Good night!
Oh, boy...
Antony...
Antony!
- Xavier sir...
- Yes!
The order to demolish the bridge...
You were too drunk
to read it yesterday.
Now that you're sober,
why don't you read it?
What for? Isn't it written
exactly the way I said?
Sir, that's true.
But once you read it,
you'll be so pleased
you'll pour yourself two extra drinks.
Have a look.
Nice, very nice!
We get to demolish the bridge ourselves.
Sir, that's not the only highlight.
There's more!
Take a look at this too.
Yeah.
Wow! This is another highlight.
Under the terms of this Agreement,
all the remaining scrap
from the Nagathan Bridge
being demolished
by Xavier & Dawood Company...
namely the rebar, bricks,
iron, rust, soil and stone,
including all debris
from the bridge site...
shall be acquired by the First Party,
Shaji Paappan of Pannimattom,
for a sum of ₹10,000,
without leaving anything behind.
It is hereby agreed.
Happy?
What on earth is this?
Signed on behalf of Dawood & Co.
by Soman and Simon.
You just wanted
the bridge demolished, right?
What do we need
all that rust and scrap for?
It would've cost us 10 lakhs
just to clear the debris.
Yes.
We ripped those guys off
for peanuts.
The rest is pure profit
for you, sir!
And that's not all, sir.
To make sure they wouldn't
change their minds later,
we called the officials there
and signed it right in front of them.
Now tell me...
aren't you going to celebrate
with two extra drinks?
- What?
- I asked...
if you're going to celebrate
with two more drinks.
Yeah.
- You...!
- Yikes!
You stupid Battery!
Sir, have mercy on him!
I'm the innocent one!
You're not innocent.
You're a walking disaster!
- Stop there!
- Yes, if you say so!
- I'll burn you alive today!
- Oh no!
What are you watching?
Some guy's wedding night vlog.
Wait... is the whole thing there?
Part two comes out
only next week.
I'll wait then.
- [Abu burps]
- Ugh!
Will you fill up the empty cylinder
with your gas?
Shajiyett...
Look, the full history of that bridge
is printed in the newspaper.
It was built during the British era.
- Built during the British era?
- Yeah.
Then there should be
iron rods and rings inside it.
Right.
- Paappoy!
- Ah, the virus arrives. What is it now?
We shouldn't stoop to
this miserable scrap business.
You already look like you came
straight out of a junkyard, Paappan.
This line of work
is far below our status.
Won't people call you "Scrap Paappan"
when they see you?
What do they call him now?
- "Pauper Paappan."
- Like that's much better!
Shut up, Captain!
This swing isn't strong enough
for all of you to cling to it.
I wish I had been born
a white man in America.
Yeah, then you'd be Sahib Paappan!
Paappan, look!
It's Satan Xavier.
- Who's that?
- Underworld, underworld!
♪ High Range,
Highly Danger ♪
You sneaky Paappan!
♪ High Range,
Highly Danger ♪
♪ Satan Xavier ♪
- Stand up, old hag!
- You bloody!
♪ Paappan ♪
♪ The High Range's highly dangerous
underworld kingpin renowned ♪
Satan...
Satan Xavier!
Paappan...
Shaji Paappan.
Well, well!
These are my boys.
They made a small slip-up
yesterday morning.
That scrap agreement has to be
written the other way around.
The other way? If you write it backwards,
will anyone even understand it?
- Like we understood it earlier!
- Shut up!
Before you decide anything,
hear me out first.
Abu, uncle is about to tell a story.
Pay attention.
Back in the mid-1700s,
it was my great-great-grandfather,
Walter Sahib,
who built that bridge.
Oh!
Just a day before
the bridge's inauguration,
he passed away.
- How sad!
- Very good!
He loved this land so much that
they didn't take his body
back to London.
Instead, they placed his ashes
inside the bridge itself.
Huh?
Hoping to see those ashes
just once,
his beloved wife,
Dolores Aunty,
still waits,
her tears never drying.
He's not talking about your mom!
Dollar grandma!
Wait, if she's still waiting,
that Dollar Aunty must be
at least 300 years old now, right?
That's right!
Huh!
Not the aunty herself, Uncle!
- Aunty's aunt's brother's--
- Look, Xavier sir...
We need a moment
to think this over.
- Right?
- Yes.
You don't have to think.
You bought it for ₹10,000, right?
Yes.
- I'll give you ₹20,000.
- That's fair.
Isn't that enough?
Actually,
make it thirty.
Fine, let's make it fifty!
- Agree for fifty, Uncle!
- Fi... Fif... Fifty? No, sir.
It won't take long to count.
One lakh!
Shajiyetta, just stay quiet
for two minutes
and the price will keep rising.
Hmm?
- Two!
- Wow!
- Two lakhs!
- Told you!
Three lakhs!
Four lakhs!
- Five lakhs!
- Huh!
Six lakhs!
- Seven lakhs!
- Who the hell is that?
I'll throw this at you!
Eight lakhs!
- Nine lakhs!
- Huh?!
Ten lakhs!
- Eleven lakhs!
- Huh?!
Oh, that's the game?
Fine!
- Take this--
- Enough!!!
25 lakhs!
Twenty-five lakhs!
Err...
Even if you offer a fortune
in gold, we won't give it, sir.
We… we dreamt of a vulture.
That's why!
- You mean, 'Venture'.
- Yeah, that stuff.
You dogs! You're using
my grandfather's ashes
- to build your vulture dreams?
- Culture!
Shut up!
Hey!
- Shajiyetta!
- You better return my agreement!
Idiots!
- Oh no!
- Abu!
- Shajiyettan!
- I'm leaving this world!
My Shajiyettan...!
- You must pay the van's EMI.
- The bullet didn't hit you, Shajiyettan!
The shot came from over there.
Look, it's Sarbath!
♪ If valour ever claimed a name,
If the fight for truth ignites a flame ♪
If you create a scene
on the public road,
I'll shoot all of you
and smoke you away!
Go home!
- Paappan...
- What the hell is it?
I'm going to get that agreement
back from you.
- Even if I have to kill you for it!
- Dream on!
- Just wait and see!
- Stop making me laugh. Get going.
If you don't want to get shot
by the police, disperse!
Shameer, we'll deal with you later!
Sir... did you see
that Xavier's attitude, sir?
You should go there, grab his gun,
and smack him across the face!
- Hey Dhanaya...
- Yes?
Every time we see him,
you keep egging me on for no reason.
Last time when our cars crashed,
only I went flying.
You didn't fly.
Switch on the siren!
Let the locals gather.
Let's embarrass them!
Shajiyetta, you should've
finished him right here.
Would a lion waste its time
fighting a rabbit?
So what if you're
the rabbit, Paappan?
Don't you have your
own unique strengths?
I'm the... lion...
Hey, hey, hey!
If our Chief steps out,
all hell will break loose!
- We know.
- What is he, a chimpanzee?
Let's go.
Good thing
that Sarbath guy stepped in.
Otherwise that Satan
would've shot us down!
Wouldn't it be wiser
to just return the agreement?
We can move on
to the next scrap deal.
No, man.
Something valuable
is hidden inside that bridge.
- Really?
- I'm certain.
Otherwise, he wouldn't turn up
all worked up and rattled like this.
Oh!
What do you think is actually
inside that bridge, Paappan?
You wouldn't understand
even if I explained it.
Inside it,
there's something that will change
my life, your life,
and his life.
My army and I battled Azam Khan
for three long days.
Three days!
You got it?
- When was that?
- At the end of a fierce battle,
only when no other way remained,
did we decide to flee.
And that too because
that stupid King Padmanabhan fled first.
Full stop.
Perfect.
Excuse me, Water sir...
Could you tell the Viceroy
about us as well, Water sir?
Just like the story you told now.
Feel free to make it up.
Why not!
- Then write down these two lines.
- Write.
Hype us up!
Who's that?
Did you hear something?
Azam Khan!
Hide!
Oh, my god!
Let's run with Sahib.
Come on!
Huh!
What a beautiful maiden!
- Is she not?
- Indeed.
A white madam!
A foreigner is here
without letting me know?
For what reason?
And that too a young lady!
Young or old, sir,
you shouldn't let anyone through.
- She shall not pass through!
- That's the spirit.
- I will not let her through!
- Go!
- Get my coat!
- Okay. Let's go!
Go.
♪ Riding wild on destiny ♪
♪ Charging to the end of time ♪
♪ Hark, she comes, she comes ♪
♪ Just as our seers divined ♪
Easy.
We come in peace.
Approach with caution, lady.
I only wish to speak with
Mr. Walter Joseph.
I am Walter Joseph.
Not Mister.
Lord Walter Joseph!
Well, well, well.
Look!
Who is here in Lord Walter's territory
without intimating him beforehand?
I had sent a letter
seeking your permission.
I regret you didn't receive it.
I don't care!
I care about protocols!
Without my prior permission,
without considering my convenience...
and with a group of armed men,
how dare you trespass here
just to disturb this Walter...
at a place where I simply
came for a picnic?
Are you that naive?
Answer me!
Water sir is rocking it!
Or you think your beauty is going
to save you from my wrath, huh?
- No, sir. I only--
- Shut up!
Who said, "Hands down"?
Hands in the air, lady!
Good, baby girl!
Mr. Walter...
I really hate guns
being pointed at my face.
- Boys!
- Yes?
You heard that?
We heard nothing, sir.
Ask her to say it louder.
It seems the lady does not fancy
guns pointed at her!
Is it? Then strike her
with the handle, sir.
♪ District Magistrate... ♪
Oh no!
Walter...
Tell me about King Padmanabhan.
It is certain
Padmanabhan will lose his kingdom.
He may either hide in the woods
or flee the province.
What becomes of him
no longer concerns the Company.
For the Company has
already forsaken even me.
I swear!
Pinky promise.
Please do not hurt
our Sahib any further, Madam.
He is all we have.
Oh! Is that so?
Madam...
Wh... wh... Why do you care
about Padmanabhan?
Nothing.
Just a friend in Portugal had asked
that I convey his regards
to Padmanabhan.
Right?
That's all.
♪ Riding wild on destiny ♪
♪ Charging to the end of time ♪
♪ Hark, she comes, she comes ♪
♪ Just as our seers divined ♪
♪ We wait, we watch as stars conspire ♪
♪ We pray, we bow to the cosmic choir ♪
♪ Lo! She's here, she's here ♪
♪ To reap death and desire ♪
♪ Riding wild on destiny ♪
♪ Charging to the end of time ♪
♪ Hark, she comes, she comes ♪
♪ Just as our seers divined ♪
♪ We wait, we watch as stars conspire ♪
♪ We pray, we bow to the cosmic choir ♪
♪ Lo! She's here, she's here ♪
There's nothing here.
He moved it.
What now?
We have to find him
before someone else does.
Cassandra...
The informer says...
Azam Khan has started his march.
Let's go.
Our new base of operations
shall be in Mysore.
We shall build
our future bridges there.
Then what about our trip
to Travancore?
Why should the whole lot
rush there?
Good morning!
Well done, my subjects.
I am delighted you have built
a new bridge for my arrival.
Ordinarily, when such works
are finished,
kings reward us
with silk and gold.
This is the first time I'm receiving
a golden necklace with a medallion.
I shall never forget
this gift in my lifetime!
As a token of gratitude for building
this magnificent bridge and aiding me,
hurl this idiot Mappila
into the river!
Why?
I do not know how to swim, Khan!
I do not know how to swim!
- Twice the joy. Splendid!
- Oh no!
- Dragon!
- My Lord!
I'm afraid of water snakes!
Oh no!
I shall never build a bridge
in any lifetime again!
I'm scared of water snakes!
Oh no!
♪ Ko.. Ko.. Ko...
Koran... Koran... ♪
Oh my!
They seem to be good folk.
♪ Commander of the Legion,
a hero of might ♪
Peace be upon you.
And upon you be peace
and the mercy of Allah...
Err... the mercy of Allah...
And His blessings.
Ah... and His blessings.
What is your name?
Abu Salah.
Have you heard of telescopes?
No, no! We are not
that sort of people, Lord.
[in Kannada] Very nice.
♪ Commander of the Legion,
a hero of might ♪
Oh no!
Allah!
That will not help now, Commander!
O Goddess!
Oh no!
Did I not warn you
not to pull hair from the horse's tail
and stick it on our beards?
- It's itching as well!
- Oh no!
A royal massage!
A royal 'message'!!
Your Majesty,
I have fulfilled your command.
The arch in the heart
of the forest marks the spot.
Proceed with caution.
As I said before,
I shall proceed
from here on my own.
Do not follow me
and put yourselves
in danger as well.
You remember my instructions?
Go to the secret hideout.
If I fail to return,
head straight
to the Chudala hills.
You need not wait for my return.
♪ Grandmaster of the duel,
sovereign of the land ♪
♪ War-dance titan
none may ever withstand ♪
Look at him go.
There's nothing on his head.
- True.
- Huh?
I meant he isn't
wearing his crown.
Oh, that's what I meant too.
♪ O fearless guardian,
protector of the order ♪
[In Kannada] My dear subjects,
lend me your ears.
Is that Sanskrit?
My war is with kings,
not with the people.
Whoever reveals
where the King hides
may claim this reward.
Come right here!
Those gold coins are mine!
Hold this.
I'm going to tell him.
Do not tell him.
It is a trap.
He will never give the coins.
This is not your
pauper King Pappanabhan
who cheats men
without paying them.
This is Azam Khan!
My Lord!
I know it, Lord.
Bravo!
I am pleased
someone has chosen to cooperate.
Tell me then.
Where does he hide?
Where exactly?
Here... I mean... No!
Over there... I'm certain.
Clever fellow.
Very clever.
Are you not pleased
to have become a rich man?
He is done for!
- Who goes there!
- Yes, Lord!
Prepare the horses!
I would like a white one
and a red one.
Oh no!
Oh my God!
Relax!
It is only that fool Koma Kurup
and his men.
Where are you rushing
in such haste, Koma Kurup?
Where is Padmanabhan?
I am going in search of
King Padmanabhan, Walter Sahib.
After we allowed the King to flee,
some of us attempted
to battle Azam Khan ourselves.
- Oh, is it?
- But the whipping was unbearable.
What?! Whips in a war?
Err...
Not a whip.
It was a whip-sword!
And... did the army march
past Padmanabhan's kingdom?
- The army has--
- The army shall go nowhere, Sahib,
Not until they seize
King Padmanabhan's secret treasure.
Oh!?
We are going after him.
All right.
Hurry!
Walter sir,
could this be the reason
behind that white lady's arrival?
Cassandra...
Azam Khan...
Now all the dots are connected.
You lying King...
Your time is up!
Guys!
Let's go for a treasure hunt!
Yeah!
Antony...
Did you know?
I've been seeing my aunty lately.
Not in my dreams,
but in real life.
She actually talks to me.
And I talk back to her.
You probably think
I've gone crazy, right?
I'm not crazy, you donkey.
Sorry, buddy!
This is...
extrasensory perception.
Oh God!
I can see you laughing at me.
How could you possibly
believe any of this?
After all, you're all rationalists, right?
Oh, my Dude sir!
Antony...
I can see Soman, the venomous snake
that once wrapped around my neck,
standing right behind me.
Dude sir!
I can see you sitting here
as well. Clearly.
So did you attain
extrasensory perception too?
Of course!
I've got the "sensory" gear too! Ugh!
Dude sir... what the hell
are you even talking about?
What is it?
- Hey, Soman!
- Yeah!
- How did you get here?
- Me?
Didn't I slog across
the desert just to meet you, sir?
- Is that so?
- Yeah!
Listen!
I've brought a huge deal.
- Huh?
- Oh, yeah...
It's a mega jackpot!
[In Tamil] Does this face
look like someone who wins jackpots?
Yes, it does.
"Dude!"
I've left
that life behind, Soman.
Dilman died long ago
in another life.
When?
All that remains now
is Sulaiman.
I'm perfectly content
with my life now.
But I'm not!
- You know why?
- Why?
Because I killed my ambition.
My god!
You killed Nambeeshan?
If you don't come, Paappan is going
to grab the jackpot!
Paappan?
- That bloody village bumpkin?
- Yes.
That village bumpkin who never lets us
succeed, no matter what!
That bloody Paappan!
Boss, if you set me free,
with a few resources,
we'll rake in
crores, boss, crores!
Fifty percent will be yours, Boss!
Huh!
- Dude!
- Oh no!
- Hey, Sulaiman...
- Yes, Boss!
You don't know the rules of our gang.
You are my property.
I will be the owner
of everything you get!
The entire 100% will be mine!
That's the deal.
Do you understand, sir?
I have heard this somewhere before!
Boss, I agree to this deal!
Thank you, Boss!
Thank you!
You scoundrel!
The minute I step out of here,
I'll vanish.
You won't find a single trace of me,
however hard you try.
Hey, Azhaku!
Call Pulikesi.
- Nice undies!
- Of course!
Superb!
I don't wear local undies, Boss.
I prefer Armani.
This isn't Armani.
Then?
It's "Harm"ani.
Way more deadly!
Really?
Yes, it is.
You're right.
It's making a buzzing sound!
Those undies carry
an electric current, Sulaiman.
That's the noise you're hearing.
Don't stress yourself out.
There are holes for
number one and two.
Why do his undies
need a power supply?
For this!
Boss!
If you talk too much
or cross your limits,
you'll get a shock, just like this.
Even if the thought
of removing them crosses your mind,
the GPS will trigger a blast
and you'll be finished.
- Pulikesi...
- Yes, Boss!
Pulikesi will come with you.
Okay?
If you even think
of escaping from him...
I'll press the button immediately!
You'll be reduced to dust!
What, Sulaiman?
Is this deal okay?
Why even bother asking him?
He is ready for everything.
- Aren't you?
- Yes.
Don't be upset.
I'm going to take you
away from here.
I won't let you suffer
here for long.
And that boss of ours?
I'll finish him!
I blew up his uncle's shop
with a bomb!
You don't know me well enough.
What the hell is this, Paily?
Okay, my bro!
- This is 'The Donkey Life'!
- Huh!
Don't be sad.
- He is like this now.
- I'll see you soon.
Sitting on ticking time bombs
and playing "Mission Impossible"
is nothing new to me.
- Let's go, boys.
- Sir...
Don't forget me
once you get what you want.
At least this time,
I have to make it big!
Of course, Soman.
Announce it to the whole world...
Once again,
Dude is on the way!
- Yeah!
- Yes!
Dear fellow citizens,
this sturdy Nagathan Bridge,
which has served us for centuries,
is being demolished
via controlled implosion
for no particular reason.
King Padmanabha, who ruled
these highlands in the 1800s,
completed the construction
of this bridge
in collaboration with Walter Joseph
of the British East India Company.
At that time, the construction
of this bridge was spearheaded
by the eminent engineer,
Vareeth Mappila.
You have to give credit to Mappila,
that engineer who built this bridge!
Look at it, standing firm
for over three hundred years!
But didn't Aashaan say
that it was shaking?
Shut up!
[media reports]
- Paappan...
- Yes?
- Satan Xavier!
- Don't look at him.
That's the opposition's allegation.
Minister P.P. Shashi took to social media
to state that wise administrators
prioritise public safety
by pre-emptively eliminating
potential hazards.
What are you doing,
you frog-face?
It's your first scrap deal, right?
Let's shoot a reel.
I'll break that thing
and throw it in the water!
You've been at it
for quite a while now!
Making a reel
while the bridge blows up!
Paappan, you're giving off
major "Dad vibes" right now.
Yes. My "Dad vibe" is better than
your "Dad-less vibe"!
Sigh!
Emotional damage!
Quit grinning and make sure
you grab everything once it explodes.
What if the bridge collapses on my head
and I die, Shajiyetta?
Wouldn't that be a heroic death?
We must rush there
as soon as the bridge collapses.
Let them take the stones, iron,
cement, or gravel.
There will be boxes hidden there.
We must take those.
Sir... one doubt.
What if Sarbath shoots us in the butt
while we're running there?
- Shut up!
- Yes.
Precisely because of that danger,
only you two are going.
Just us?
The countdown will begin shortly.
Welcome to the bridge
demolition festival...
- It's procedure!
- Errr...
Everyone is welcome
to witness the procedure.
This explosion will give me
plenty of Satan's stones.
Will you really get
Satan's stones, Aashaan?
Why are you glued to me?
Stand back and listen to the countdown.
- Damn you!
- Thousands of residents across
the neighbouring areas
of the Nagathan Bridge,
including Muthiyanmala,
Pothumukku, and Marayikkonam
are set to face severe travel hardships
following the bridge's demolition.
And... as soon as
the bridge collapses,
those rascals Paappan and Xavier
will start tearing into each other.
We must reach the spot
before anyone else.
They should step in
only under our control.
Okay.
Are you ready, sir?
Yes, ready.
Countdown begins.
Ten...
Nine...
Eight...
Seven...
Six...
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One!
Run, Soman!
The explosion has just happened.
The historic bridge...
- There's a helicopter above the bridge.
- Look, a helicopter!
Huh! Who's that?
What on earth is that?
A vulture?
♪ He is the DUDE ♪
Who the hell is that?!
No, Shajiyetta!
That's the gunman!
Is he dead and going to heaven?
♪ He is the DUDE ♪
He's not going
to heaven, Paappan.
He's making off with our stuff!
There's something
in those boxes, Shajiyetta!
Otherwise, he wouldn't have hired
a helicopter to get here, Paappan.
Do you recognise him, sir?
That scoundrel in the suit!
- He is the "Dude"!
- Yay!
Oh no!
This is that other fellow!
- Dude sir!
- Huh!
- Yeah, the boxes!
- ♪ DUDE ♪
Hasta la vista, skibidis!
Turn it around!
Go! Fly away!
Go fast, man!
♪ DUDE ♪
Don't go!
Please don't go!
A helicopter is flying away
from the bridge after the explosion.
Listen to your police uncle!
Drop the boxes!
It's gone!
That's gone!
The bridge was demolished
very well, Aashaan.
You...!
I saw the whole thing.
I want those boxes you just
waved goodbye to, right now.
No, Aashaan!
I wasn't waving goodbye!
- I was saying "don't go, don't go."
- Shut up!
Are you all ganging up to trick me?
If you don't bring the goods…
The red snappers and ribbonfish
in my dam are starving.
I'll serve them
a chilled Soda Sarbath
brewed from your blood!
- No, Aashaan! No!
- I need my blood.
You'll get your boxes
in no time, Aashaan!
I need your blessings, Aashaan.
Go find those boxes, you dog!
- Start the jeep!
- Sir!
♪ He is the DUDE ♪
- Yeah!
- Come up!
Thank you, boys!
Yaay, yaay, yaay!
♪ Paappan, Paappan ♪
♪ The elder Paappan ♪
- Throw the net, Thankappan!
- ♪ Thomas Paappan ♪
♪ Paappan, Paappan ♪
♪ The elder Paappan ♪
- Hey! Psst!
- ♪ Thomas Paappan ♪
You bloody old village bumpkins!
You again?!
Hey, I warned you long ago
not to come to the High Range hills
and mess with my boys.
He'll tell you the rest.
♪ Even Haji Mastan would salute the man,
The brave and mighty Shaji Paappan ♪
Is that...
the bloody village bumpkin?
♪ Even Haji Mastan would salute the man,
The brave and mighty Shaji Paappan ♪
Bloody nemesis!
My archenemy!
- Martin!
- Yes, Paappan!
Step on it!
I've got a scarecrow to roast.
- That was awesome, brother!
- You bet!
Hey there, Mr. Gunman!
What did you think?
That I wouldn't expect you?
Every time the Lord
blesses me with something,
why do you always come after me
in that filthy jacket to mess it up?
Any time, guys!
You bloody village bumpkin!
I will--
Listen up, you moron!
You better watch your back!
If you come after me again,
I'll shove a bomb down your throat
and blow you to bits!
Oh no!
- Oh no! A bomb!
- Oh God!
Bomb!
Oh no! The boxes!
What the hell just happened?
Hey Shaji...
You kept bragging
about planting bombs…
And you planted one
under our own butts? You moron!
This wasn't my bomb, Chettayi!
Don't you know
our bombs never explode?
This was planted by someone
who knows their job.
Whoever it is, don't come back
until you take him down.
Let me reach the shore first
before I get taken down.
Where is the shore now?
Andre, fetch our things.
Yeah!
You know what to do
in situations like this, right?
Yeah!
Okay.
I understand.
Thanks.
Listen up, guys.
Change of plans.
We're going to go to--
♪ Shameer... Shameer...
O Sarbath Shameer! ♪
No.
Don't shoot the police.
It will only cause trouble.
Bloody bombers!
Did that rascal reach that shore?
So now even foreigners
are messing with my job!
- Officer, we were just trying to--
- Where are the boxes?
The boxes are in that vehicle.
Well, sir... didn't we hear that
the British helped build this bridge?
What if they're taking the boxes
they left behind while building it?
Then it's "lost and found,"
right, sir?
Explain our laws to them, sir.
- Alright. I'll explain it in English.
- Got the key!
Madam, listen carefully.
This box...
Bridge broke.
One dog take the box.
Aashaan waiting.
And you come take, I no--
[In Malayalam]
You're a special kind of fool, officer!
- A fool?
- Huh! No need subtitles!
Dhanaya, she knows Malayalam!
Hands up, woman!
Officer, I hate guns
being pointed at my face.
Hmph!
What did she just say?
She says she hates guns
being pointed at her face.
Oh, really?
What will she--
- Sir!
- It's true!
She really hates it!
Sir!
Hello...
Run for your lives!
♪ The burning fire ♪
There's room for only one foreigner
around here!
You heard that?
Useless buffalo!
♪ Go home, little girl ♪
♪ Striking like high-voltage
lightning crashing to the ground ♪
Shit!
Come out! Come out!
Bullshit!
Where are the boxes, Shajiyetta?
I couldn't search for it
in the chaos after the blast.
Sigh!
I'm really curious!
My dear Dude sir,
when will you learn to handle
a box properly?
Mr. Dragon...
I'll be asking the questions.
Where is my chopper?
The chopper?
When you fell into the water,
it dropped us
at a nearby school ground.
Then the chopper driver
flew off with it.
I waved goodbye and thanked him.
What else could we do?
Then we spotted a vehicle, hijacked it,
and came straight here.
Happy?
- Very good.
- Oh no!
You lost the chopper just when
a high-speed chase
was about to start? Stupid!
Idiots!
Bad Idiots!
♪ He is the DUDE ♪
Even a dog wouldn't want
a Paappan who lost the boxes.
Just jump back into the water.
I'll smash that
useless head of yours—
- You bloody village bumpkin!!!
- I didn't die because... Huh!
What, you beggar?
This isn't over yet!
I'll incinerate you
and that ride of yours.
And your village...
I'll burn it to the ground!
Then come here and burn it!
I'll write 'village'
on a piece of paper.
Take it and go burn that.
But you don't know
how to write 'village, ' Paappan!
He doesn't know
that I don't know it!
Get lost, you dog!
- He's crying sadly.
- No.
- He's making faces at us.
- Like this?
- Yeah, that's what he's doing.
- Oh yeah?
Wow, such a perfect monkey!
Don't give up, Dude sir!
Keep up, Abu!
Forget it.
He's better at making faces.
- We might lose.
- Shajiyetta!
Don't give up, Dude sir!
Damn! A phone call
right now!
Mr. Village Bumpkin!
What?
The chopper pilot told me
which way the boxes went.
Have a good day!
He said "Have a good day."
What do we do, Shajiyetta?
Shajiyetta...
Look, your brother is calling.
Chettayi, someone took the boxes.
It wasn't just anyone.
It was Satan Xavier!
He's heading for the border.
Hurry up!
Come on, boys!
- I won't let him get away!
- Start the van, Paappan!
♪ Stardust falling down ♪
♪ Oh baby who gonna catch it ♪
♪ The treasure's flyin off ♪
♪ Paappan's running for it ♪
♪ Crazy like the Aries
Cool with the shades on ♪
♪ Moving in a hurry
Gotta get the star back ♪
♪ Paappan's in a hurry,
Paappan's in a hurry ♪
♪ Move aside, boy ♪
♪ No time to play around ♪
♪ The dude is on the front ♪
♪ If you wanna win the chase,
you better run ♪
♪ You better run ♪
From here, we head directly
to Madurai this evening.
A container must be ready there
to head to Dubai port.
I need no mistakes!
We're all going together, right?
- No.
- Oh.
I'm going to Portugal.
You're going to Pollachi.
Ugh!
- Dude was better than this guy.
- Who?
Brief me, Jack.
Lara...
The organisation is not happy.
I have covered this one for you,
but do not mess up.
Thanks, Jack.
I owe you one.
Please send a party to intercept.
Already did.
It's almost time
and we need Star Dust.
Do not fail.
I won't.
What happened was just a small delay.
Well, no more delays then.
Shit!
Boys, your lifetime settlement
is waiting in this
dashboard box.
Vehicle spotted.
Near the valley.
800 meters and closing.
We never expected this
when we joined you.
At least you remembered
to pay us our worth.
Don't talk about worth.
We won't get a penny.
Take the shot now.
Oh no!
My God!
This is not over yet.
Sweet dreams, little boy.
Grab the boxes.
Check the other one.
It's empty.
What!
It's empty!
Where the hell is the Star Dust?
Shift to the right and stomp...
Bend down and rise up...
Shift to the left...
Why has the training ceased, Vikraman?
A guest awaits you, my Lord.
What troubles you, elder brother?
Why does your face show no joy
even at the sight of your younger brother?
You renounced the kingdom
and its rule.
Are you displeased because I keep
coming here and troubling you?
Hey! Why do you stand there
like stone?
Speak. What is the reason?
I shall tell you the reason!
Walter Sahib?
So this is where
you fled to, Sahib?
Shut up!
Those grand titles held weight
only until Azam Khan arrived.
Where is my treasure?
Huh? Who is that?
Treasure... treasure...
the treasure!
Treasure?
Which treasure?
Are you deceiving me again?
I will grant you
exactly one moment.
Where is my treasure?
- Water Sahib!
- Yes?
If we kill him,
how shall we obtain the treasure?
That is true.
Change of target!
Padmanabhan...
I shall count to three.
One!
- Two!
- Four!
Don't!
- I'll tell you.
- Don't!
Even if we lose our lives,
do not tell them where it is!
Oh, really?
Say three, sir.
Fine. Three!
O Goddess!
Oh no!
That white lady is coming
to wallop us again, Sahib!
Oh no!
- Fire!
- Oh no!
Please don't shoot me, Madam!
Oh no! She shot me!
- Hey, Vikraman!
- Yes.
Stop practising your moves in hiding.
Stand forth and fight!
Come forward, younger brother!
Shit!
Oh no! My rear!
Don't stop.
Keep running!
Hey, Padmanabhan!
Oh God! Mother!
Oh God!
- My little brother! Padmanabhan!
- Big brother!
- Here I go, brother.
- Going where?
The bullet didn't even hit you,
you fool!
It struck your armour!
Now rise!
So the bullet did not pierce me?
Silence! Up, now!
Get up and run!
- Come here!
- Kill her, Sahib!
Oh no!
Your horse awaits
at the end of this tunnel.
Gather your men and
ride to Eraniel Palace at once.
The Emperor of Travancore will protect you!
O Guardian Deity!
May your journey be safe.
- Where is the bomb?
- What?
The country bomb!
Oh no! I forgot to bring it!
You stupid!
- Where is the bomb?
- Oh no!
Hey, soldier! Give me the bomb!
Please bomb me!
Throw! Throw!
- Throwing!
- Hey, give the bomb to Sahib!
Not this way!
Oh no!!!
Oh God!
No matter how much
herbal remedy I apply,
this pain from the whipping
just won't go away.
- Huh!
- Look, it's the King!
Shankaran! Achyuthan!
Look! His Majesty is alive!
My eyes and heart never tire
of seeing you, Your Majesty!
You said you don't bid farewell
after dark and left, Abu Salah!
So why are you back here
covered in cow dung?
Answer me.
Before we even realised it,
we have become warriors again,
Your Highness.
Along with that,
our patriotism has also grown.
For what?
Just forget all that, my Lord.
How did you come here?
- Kurup...
- Yes.
You must realise something
at least now.
It is not only
Azam Khan pursuing us.
There is that traitor Walter Sahib
and other foreign powers as well.
So Kurup, we must go
and meet His Highness of Travancore
at once.
We shall obtain
weapons from there--
Where did that come from?
Azam Khan!
I used to be a real terror once!
And now? Stranded in the middle
of a tea estate with a flat tire!
Bad!
- It's too bad!
- Hey!
This isn't a tea estate, man.
It's a pineapple estate.
Can't you see that?
Tea, pineapple, who gives a damn!
Mr. Dragon...
Back in Bangkok,
I wasn't giving massages.
I was a gangster.
A monster.
I've stormed through downtown Bangkok
in epic chases,
smashing through police cruisers
and the armed trucks of rival gangs.
That's Son of Damodaran Unni,
Dilman Edakochi for you!
Now look at me!
I've ended up like a soggy,
burnt onion fritter!
Dude's Bangkok slap!
Very nice.
Oh God, time is running out.
Paappan!
Where are we racing off to?
Now that it's on the news,
they'll try
to slip into Tamil Nadu.
We can grab them in Madurai.
Right.
Then step on
the accelerator, Paappan!
Do you think I'm stepping on
your father's chest here?
We're lucky it even has
four decent tires.
We have to find out
what's in those boxes.
Let's take this route.
This field used to be
my outdoor toilet.
You can do that even now,
but there won't be any water.
No screw-ups this time, boys.
I am optimistic.
As they say,
third time's a charm.
Correct!
This is your last chance.
There won't be a fourth chance.
I don't need four.
I'll take the fifth.
No way.
Mr. Pulikesi...
Don't try to act tough with me just because
of that transformer in my underwear.
The shock it gives today
may not be there tomorrow.
Because--
Ow! Oh no!
Stop pressing it!
He'll die!
We can't even grab him!
Hey, nutcase...
How are you still dropping punchlines
after getting your butt electrocuted?
If the boss doesn't get the box,
it's my butt that
will get electrocuted!
The helicopter rent
was too expensive.
Dude!
- Vehicle is ready!
- Yes.
- Chase!
- Okay!
- Start the vehicle!
- ♪ He is the DUDE! ♪
Paappan, I want to leave this gang.
Give me a transfer certificate.
And I want to join
that gunman's gang instead!
- Fantastic!
- I want to be a don like him!
Why are you silent, Paappan?
I don't respond to such crap!
Paappan, look over there!
Huh!
♪ Within a mind shattered
by broken dreams... ♪
♪ Upon the steps stained
by the weight of a curse... ♪
♪ I stood in prayer
as the twilight deepened... ♪
♪ O, beauty of my soul,
who drifts away into the distance... ♪
♪ Dissolve into my life-breath ♪
Look!
♪ And do it swiftly ♪
Who's that?
He is a distant relative,
named Paappan.
Ah, alright.
You know, I was thinking...
I was having the same thought.
We missed the wedding biryani.
- Right?
- Will you shut up?
- Hey, Pookie boy!
- Yes?
What do you call it
when people go back in time?
That's time travel, Paappan.
Right.
If I could do that,
I'd go back
and stop his parents' wedding!
Then I wouldn't have had
to deal with him.
Now I'm stuck with no choice.
Take that wreath off the vehicle
and put it on him.
Are you talking about the wreath
on top of our vehicle, Paappan?
Don't take it to heart, Shajiyettan.
She's never going to have
a happy marriage.
Did you see
the way that groom stood?
He's a total dud.
Just like you, Shajiyettan.
Damn right!
I am a dud.
No wonder I keep dragging you all around
like a lottery ticket that never wins!
Abu, what kind of talk is that?
He looks like a civet.
And you call him a dud?
Your father is the civet!
Trying to swing from a doomed
man's rope, you low-life?
- Drop it, Paappan.
- Drop it?!
I should drop you
guys off a cliff first!
My mother warned me
never to let you guys into the house.
Because of you guys,
now even I got kicked out!
- Paappan! Jeep! Jeep!
- Jeep!
Turn the Jeep!
Turn it around!
Oh my God!
Sir...
The vehicles of that Dude
who took the boxes and Paappan
have crashed in front of our station!
If the tug-of-war guy and
the gunman are together,
one thing is certain.
Those rascals definitely know
where the loot is.
Pounce on them, Paappi!
What are you saying, sir?
I'm all alone here, sir.
In that case,
just keep a close eye on them.
Of course, I will!
Hear me, King!
Today, you shall meet your end!
Your Majesty!
It is time to end this.
Azam Khan!
The timeline crossing process
is about to begin.
Let's hope for a good outcome.
If you truly have the mettle,
face me one-on-one!
A wise choice, Your Majesty.
Better to die
with a blade to the chest
than to die with an arrow in the back
while fleeing like a coward.
Paappan has nothing
left to lose now!
Flip, and it's Malappuram.
Turn, and it's Thiruvananthapuram!
You wretch!
Paappan won't rest
until you're done and dusted!
Flip Malappuram,
turn Thiruvananthapuram,
or do whatever the hell you want!
Bangkok is behind me...
and Miami is waiting ahead!
Come to Daddy!
Look at his arrogance!
- Yeah.
- He'll meet his end today!
Crush him, Shajiyetta!
No sentiments, no compromise!
You lunatic!
The box is all that matters.
- Do we really need a fight right now?
- This guy is getting on my nerves!
It is necessary!
Because we won't get another chance.
This is our last ride.
♪ He is the DUDE ♪
I'm coming for you.
Toofaan!
Charge!
Kill him, my Lord.
Bhairava!
Finish him off, Your Majesty!
♪ Valiant heroes,
Sound the battle cry! ♪
♪ Blazing wrath on fire,
Strike and charge on high! ♪
♪ Valiant heroes,
Sound the battle cry! ♪
♪ Blood-red war arises,
Strike and charge on high! ♪
Shajiyetta!!!
What was that tremor?
My Lord!
Your Majesty! Huh!
Was that lightning?
Where has our king gone?
Did the king just
vanish into thin air?
- What?
He disappeared!
- Huh! Dude sir!
- Where is that nutcase?
Sir...
Lightning struck them both
and they just vanished!
Huh?!
Struck by lightning and vanished?
What are they, Minnal Murali?
Tell the truth, you rascal!
Hey, where did Paappan go?
Hey, that gunman is missing too!
He pressed that switch
and made our Dude Sir vanish.
Hey, why are you hitting me?
Both the box and that nutcase
have vanished!
If I go back and tell this,
the boss will chop me into pieces!
It is during times of crisis like these
that true heroes are forged.
It is!
- Oh! Abu, don't run!
- He ran away!
Abu ran.
Shouldn't we run too?
Man, you guys are so stupid!
- Paappan already told us before he left.
- He told us?
Didn't he say he'd go back
and stop my parents' wedding?
- In some Tempo traveller, right?
- Time travel.
Ah, time traveller.
Let him do his thing
and come back.
If it's sesame oil pressing,
Antony and I can handle it.
Just Antony and I are enough.
But for copra work,
I need an assistant.
I need a donkey.
Antony!
What the hell happened?
Where am I?
Where on earth am I?
♪ He is the DUDE ♪
♪ Your neatly combed feathery hair...
how were they ruffled, my lass? ♪
♪ How were they ruffled, my lass? ♪
♪ To the thorny wild I went for a lily,
the brambles snagged them loose ♪
Seriously, which is this place?
♪ That mark of sandal upon your brow,
how did it vanish, my lass? ♪
♪ Whither did it fade? ♪
♪ Under the scorching sun
on the long, winding paths ♪
Somebody should be there.
♪ The salt of my sweat
washed it clean, my lad... ♪
♪ The golden ring that graced your nose,
how was it lost, my lass? ♪
♪ How was it lost? ♪
Gentleman, one Martini Gold.
Sharp and elegant.
Make it dry. Please.
I cannot quite understand
what drink you desire, local foreigner.
♪ The golden bangles that clasped
your arms, how did they vanish, my lass? ♪
Oh! It's a vintage theme here, is it?
Then give me a glass of
your finest wine.
Very well, sir.
♪ They snapped
and shattered apart, my lad... ♪
♪ I knew not of these wiles and clever
tricks, my bird of five-coloured plumes! ♪
Stop it, you mongrels!
♪ Vareeth ♪
No song or dance
shall calm my rage!
I could have gone to Mysore
and built so many new bridges!
Instead, he threw me off
my own bridge into the river!
That lying scoundrel, Azam Khan!
Azam Khan.
Dirty fellow.
Even after I told him I could not swim
and was terrified of snakes,
he would not heed me!
Even my coat, gifted to me
by Father Victor in London,
was ripped apart by alligators!
So sad!
Had those fishermen not
cast their nets in time,
think what would have
become of me!
I will kill him!
I need no guns or swords
to kill him.
My spanner is all I need!
A spanner!
I shall unscrew
every nut and bolt of his...
every single nut...
his...
nut...
Very emotional story.
Please continue.
Oh no!
Azam Khan!
Everybody run!
Did you think I would not recognise
you in that coat, you scoundrel?
- Oh no! My clothes!
- Don't look there, you scoundrel!
Jump!
What kind of crazy,
messy mix-up is this?
Has everyone left?
Who is this Azam Khan?
Where is he now?
That fellow who just ran off
looked exactly like the Sarbath-maker!
But why did he run away?
Shouldn't I be the one running?
Dragon!
I don't see a single scoundrel here.
All the ones I saw have run away.
Something is fishy.
Dear people,
after a magnificent procession,
our "Heritage 2025"
now reaches its closing ceremony.
All those who have preserved
our land's heritage
are here with us on
this stage today.
Except for one person.
The king of tug-of-war,
Shaji Paappan!
He will be arriving shortly.
If he says he'll show up,
he'll definitely show up!
O Goddess!!!
♪ Grandmaster of the duel,
sovereign of the land ♪
♪ War-dance titan none may ever withstand ♪
He... Huh?
♪ Lord of the realm,
great master of valour ♪
♪ O fearless guardian,
protector of the order ♪
♪ The Infinite One,
Scion of the royal bloodstream ♪
♪ Despot of Empires,
Autocrat Supreme ♪
♪ Monarch of the blade,
king of every crown ♪
♪ Behold the mighty Padmanabha,
great king of renown ♪
Don't just stand there staring,
say something on the mic!
No one needs to be afraid.
Shaji Paappan has lost his mind!
Everyone, please come back.
What kingdom is this?
Rohini!
O Goddess!
My back!
I'm going to kill him today!
Release my hand!
Who are you people?
- Shaji!
- Huh?
Drowning yourself in cheap liquor
and dressing like a clown,
are you trying to disgrace me in front
of all these people, you son of a gun?
- Who are you, lady?
- Your worst nightmare!
Shaji Paappan, cut out
this nonsense!
How did you grow
such a thick beard so quickly, man?
Lift him up
and prop him up on that stage.
- Prop me up?
- Yeah, lift him!
- Lift him, lift him.
- Hey, stop!
I am the King.
We all feel like kings
after a couple of drinks.
You grab him. Lift!
What are you doing?
Hey, do not touch me there!
Let's honour him royally today!
My back is grievously hurt!
The whole world
knows that, Paappan.
What is this?
Are you trying to devour me?
Stop making lame jokes, Paappan!
I am not Paappan.
I am Padmanabhan!
♪ Grandmaster of the duel,
sovereign of the land ♪
♪ War-dance titan
none may ever withstand ♪
♪ Lord of the realm,
great master of valour ♪
♪ O fearless guardian,
protector of the order ♪
What happens now, Baba?
Chaos, confusion.
And in every timeline,
war awaits!
Paappan!
♪ Paappan, Paappan ♪
♪ O Paappan, Paappan ♪
♪ Even Haji Mastan would salute the man,
The brave and mighty Shaji Paappan ♪
♪ Even an atom bomb would surely fizzle,
Before Shaji Paappan's lethal sizzle ♪
♪ Even Haji Mastan would salute the man,
The brave and mighty Shaji Paappan ♪
♪ Even an atom bomb would surely fizzle,
Before Shaji Paappan's lethal sizzle ♪
♪ O precious Paappan,
O priceless Paappan ♪
♪ The festival bursts with joy in the air,
Cheers and euphoria everywhere ♪
♪ Rope in hand for the tug-of-war,
Here comes the little army with a roar ♪
♪ Drums roll loud, storm-clouds proclaim,
Sirens and war-cries hail their fame ♪
♪ The world shall bow
to their blazing palms ♪
♪ Like pearls that fall
from shattered dreams ♪
♪ Like lightning racing for the sky,
Their daring hearts find paths to try ♪
♪ Where firework rebels gather bold,
Defy the sun that burns the road ♪
♪ O fearless legends brave and free,
Swimming across the roaring, raging sea ♪
♪ To the clash where lion warriors fight,
Come forth, O heroes of might ♪
♪ All brave hearts gather as one,
Make the raging battle begun ♪
♪ They swing on a rogue elephant's tusk,
Daredevils bold, fierce and brusque ♪
♪ Who dares to stand against their flame,
And halt their blazing charge to fame? ♪
♪ The festival bursts with joy in the air,
Cheers and euphoria everywhere ♪
♪ Rope in hand for the tug-of-war,
Here comes the little army with a roar ♪
♪ Drums roll loud, storm-clouds proclaim,
Sirens and war-cries hail their fame ♪
♪ The world shall bow
to their blazing palms ♪
♪ Like pearls that fall
from shattered dreams ♪
♪ Like lightning racing for the sky,
Their daring hearts find paths to try ♪
♪ Where firework rebels gather bold,
Defy the sun that burns the road ♪
♪ O fearless legends brave and free,
Swimming across the roaring, raging sea ♪
♪ With burning embers in their veins,
With fiery wings that break their chains ♪
♪ War-drums roar across the land,
The world now trembles at their stand ♪
♪ Crouching panthers shiver in dread,
Their pride bows down its head ♪
♪ All who stand before their might,
Soon call it quits and quit the fight ♪