My Queen,
what are you two ladies doing?
I...
I'm keeping Her Majesty company
while she bathes.
Your Majesty,
what is going on?
Is this what you wanted me to see?
Your Majesty,
I did hear from
a maid from Her Majesty's palace who said
that Her Majesty was having an affair.
So I wanted you to see it for yourself.
A maid
said the Empress committed adultery,
and you just foolishly believed it?
Qinxiang, tell His Majesty.
You saw Her Majesty
meeting someone secretly in the palace
with your own eyes, didn't you?
I didn't.
I never said that.
Liar!
You clearly told me yourself
that Her Majesty was committing adultery.
I even gave you a hundred taels of silver.
And now you go back on your word?
Your Majesty.
[REBIRTH]
[Episode 16]
Your Majesty,
don't you remember
what day it is today?
Not to mention that I would
never be disloyal to you.
Even if I were to do something
so unforgivable,
why would I choose today of all days?
Wouldn't I fear being struck by lightning?
Guards.
Drag Beauty Hu and this maid out
and beat them to death.
Your Majesty!
I know I was wrong!
Spare me, Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, please show mercy!
Drag them out!
Your Majesty!
Spare me, Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, I was wrong!
Your Majesty!
-Spare me, Your Majesty!
-Your Majesty!
You know my secret.
I could kill you.
Spare me, Your Majesty.
I haven't seen Chu Qiao
go to hell with my own eyes yet.
I can't die.
Do you think this
will spare your life?
I did hear
the conversation
between you and Lord Zhan.
But what I said
is also my long-cherished wish.
Back then, on my wedding day,
she and Yan Xun
rebelled in Zhenhuangcheng
and ruined my life's happiness.
Now that I am married
to the Prince of Luo,
because she resembles Princess Fu,
he repeatedly comes to her aid.
Your Majesty, do you remember
what you said
when you agreed to my marriage
to the Prince of Luo?
I said I would become
your right-hand woman.
I know where Chu Qiao is now.
Where is she?
She's gone to Lincheng.
Among the prisoners exchanged
between Yan Xun and Great Yong
is her Deputy Commander, He Xiao.
I'm afraid right now,
her hiding in Biantang as Princess Fu
is already known to Yan Xun.
A few days ago,
on the streets of Tangjing,
I even saw a few Great Yan spies
holding her portrait,
looking for her everywhere.
You mean
Chu Qiao went to Lincheng
while the Crown Prince
was in Qiongzhou
to rescue her former deputy general?
Yes.
I was just joking.
The palace is so cold.
Such a kind and lovely beauty as you.
If I killed you,
where could I find another?
Your Majesty.
So,
the Crown Prince's visit
to Qiongzhou was just a diversion.
Covering for Chu Qiao
to save the Xiuli Army
was his real purpose.
Where do you think
Princess Fu and Young Master Zhuge
have gone?
Why haven't they come back for dinner?
-None of your business.
I won't eat.
Why did you bring me here?
Did you release
all those lanterns?
The paper on those lanterns
is special madder-dyed rice paper
from Qingshan Manor.
Even in strong winds,
they won't easily lose
their center of gravity.
So they can fly higher and farther
than ordinary sky lanterns.
Today isn't a festival.
Why did you release so many sky lanterns?
Zhuge Yue,
what are you up to?
These sky lanterns
are not ordinary ones for blessings.
They're a signal I agreed upon
with the Moon Guard of Qingshan Manor.
When they see these signals,
they will know I'm still alive.
When we reach
the next stronghold tomorrow,
they will be waiting there
to meet me.
You're going to contact
the Moon Guard of Qingshan Manor?
Don't worry.
Those who can recognize this signal
are all my closest confidants.
Qingshan Manor has strongholds
in various countries and cities.
A very small number of spies
in these strongholds
are my people.
I didn't contact them before
because I didn't want the Zhuge family
and the Great Yong court
to know I am alive,
nor did I want to implicate them.
But now, asking them
to help me find
a few members of the Xiuli Army
shouldn't be a problem.
Zhuge Yue.
-Greetings, Young Master Yue.
-Greetings, Chief of Qingshan Manor.
Rise.
I am no longer
the Chief of Qingshan Manor.
You don't need to bow to me.
Young Master Yue,
we thought at Mount Ximin, you were...
When we saw the sky lanterns,
we couldn't believe it was true,
let alone that we could see you again.
Since I was away,
has everything been alright?
Yes.
We are Moon Guard stationed
at secret outposts.
Since we are far from Qingshan Manor,
we are fine.
But we can't say for sure
about the other brothers
from Qingshan Manor.
Young Master Yue,
when will you return to Qingshan Manor?
Once you return,
the brothers in Qingshan Manor
won't be bullied by the young masters
of the third and fourth households.
I won't return to Qingshan Manor.
Why, Young Master Yue?
The Zhuge family and the imperial court
still don't know that I am still alive.
I also hope you won't reveal
that you have seen me.
I came this time
because I need your help
with an important matter.
Help me find the remnants
of the Xiuli Army.
Young Master Yue,
we will do our best.
Who sent you?
The Crown Prince.
The Crown Prince sent me.
Who are you?
This is the Crown Prince's Mansion.
Who dares to cause trouble here?
Your Highness.
Zhan Ziyu has surrounded
the outside with his men
and says he wants to see King Ximeng.
Lord Zhan, what brings you here?
King Ximeng.
By Her Majesty's order,
the Crown Prince conspired
with Ximeng to assassinate His Majesty
and stole Biantang's secret compendium.
The Queen of Lingyue
and the fake King Ximeng
are to be arrested immediately!
Wait.
This is the assassin
who attacked His Majesty yesterday?
Yes.
Lord Zuo ordered us
to dispose of the body immediately
without delay.
[Liu's Mansion]
I felt at that time
that the location of the scar
on the assassin's body was very strange.
It seemed to be deliberately
hiding something.
So I took a closer look
and found that at the edge of the outline,
it was originally a tattoo.
The last time I saw a tattoo
on the back of someone's neck
was 15 years ago
when I led troops
to wipe out the Nanxi Tribe.
Fifteen years ago,
Biantang exterminated the Nanxi people.
Even if someone
was lucky enough to escape,
how could they work for the Crown Prince?
Someone must be framing the Crown Prince!
Please say something!
The Crown Prince is the heir of Biantang
and His Majesty's
only legitimate bloodline.
Why would he collude with Ximeng
to commit patricide and regicide?
And that assassin.
Without any preparation,
he infiltrated the palace
late at night to assassinate the Emperor.
He confessed at once
to acting on the Crown Prince's orders,
then killed himself immediately.
This series of actions
is full of suspicious points.
Do you think no one in the court
can see through it?
You mean...
This is a messy business,
and the Emperor's own family affair.
None of us—you, the officials, or I—
may intervene.
Go back and write a leave request now,
saying you are sick.
Stay quietly in your mansion.
Don't come out and meddle.
And don't come to me.
I will continue to be sick.
Go back quickly.
Your Majesty,
His Majesty's injuries are not serious.
They are just superficial wounds.
He will recover in a few days.
But it's been so many days.
Why is His Majesty still unconscious
and delirious?
Well...
Your Majesty.
His Majesty has old ailments.
He has overworked himself daily,
exhausting too much energy.
Coupled with excessive eating
and drinking,
this has caused extreme anxiety
and an irregular pulse.
I'm afraid...
Afraid of what?
I'm afraid even with good care,
it will be hard to recover to how it was.
[Crown Prince Maocheng]
You are finally here.
You've hidden your true self
and endured for all these years.
It's been hard on you.
What you've always coveted
is the throne I sit upon, right?
Stop deceiving yourself.
You and the Prince of Chang
are from the same mother,
the legitimate flesh and blood of Mother.
While I am,
in your eyes,
just an illegitimate son
born to a lady
of low status.
If I hadn't fought my way
into Xuri Palace today,
it wouldn't have been long
before you got rid of me,
just like how you got rid of
your so-called brothers!
Murdering your brother
to seize the throne,
you will be cursed by heaven!
Why haven't I
seen you in the mansion?
Although you haven't seen me,
Your Highness,
I have long admired you.
Each time you visited
the Crown Prince's Mansion
to discuss affairs,
I would secretly watch you
from the festooned gate
in the west courtyard,
as you walked from the palace gate
to the Crown Prince's study.
I just never thought
I would see your heroic bearing
in such a way.
Do you think by saying this,
I will spare you?
No! No!
Let go!
Your Highness,
starting today,
you are the Crown Prince of Biantang.
I am willing to serve by your side.
Your Highness!
I am willing to give up any status
to serve by your side.
I can let you continue to be a concubine
and be the most honorable woman
in Biantang!
[Yuelai Inn]
-General Chu!
I'm Li Ben,
First-Class Scout of the Xiuli Army,
reporting to you, General Chu!
I'm Xia Qingjiang,
Outpost of the Xiuli Army,
reporting to you, General Chu!
I'm a Corporal of the Infantry Battalion
of the Xiuli Army,
reporting to you, General Chu!
I'm He Shao, Archer of the Xiuli Army,
I'm Lang Li, Deputy Commander
of Xiuli Army's Infantry Battalion,
reporting to you, General Chu!
I'm He Xiao,
Deputy Commander of the Xiuli Army,
reporting to you, General Chu!
Good.
You are all alive.
That's great.
We are alive.
Young Master Zhuge sent people to find us.
Back then, I couldn't save you in time
and made you suffer.
How could we blame you?
It was Cheng Yuan who deceived us.
-Yes!
He Xiao told me.
Out of 5,000 brothers,
only you guys are left.
I am a general of the Xiuli Army.
5,200 soldiers of the Xiuli Army
shall be brought home,
whether alive or dead.
There are 5,200 soldiers
in the Xiuli Army in total.
Most of them
died on the battlefield.
Among the thousands
who were not buried in Great Yan,
excluding those who returned home,
[The Loyal Martyrs of the Xiuli Army]
the rest are all here.
Many of the fallen
could not be found.
I collected their belongings
and buried them together in this cenotaph.
Wang Jin.
Wang Jin was from Bizhou,
whose family grew peaches.
When we were in the army,
whenever he missed home,
he wanted to eat the yellow peaches
from Bizhou.
Brother,
I'll put the yellow peaches
from your hometown here for you.
If you want to eat them,
just tell me in my dream,
and I'll bring them to you.
Chen Yuan.
Chen Yuan was an opera fan.
He didn't finish reading
the ending of this chapbook.
I'm afraid
he won't be able to rest in peace.
Brother,
I'll burn this for you.
I hope you can be happy
in the world beyond.
Brothers!
They died for our country.
They risked their lives,
which is admirable.
See off the soldiers!
-See off the soldiers!
♪ Wind sighs bleakly ♪
♪ Yi River cold ♪
♪ A warrior goes ♪
Brothers,
may you rest in peace!
♪ Never to return ♪
♪ Flames of war arise ♪
♪ Golden spears and steeds ♪
♪ Swords flash, and shadows dance ♪
♪ Blood dyes the yellow sand ♪
♪ Through woe and weal ♪
♪ We shared adversity ♪
♪ Heart to heart and soul to soul ♪
♪ Loyalty beyond all price ♪
♪ Loyal souls forever dwell ♪
♪ Heaven and earth mourn together ♪
♪ A tragic epic ♪
♪ Shall stand through all ages ♪
♪ Loyal souls forever dwell ♪
♪ Heaven and earth mourn together ♪
♪ A tragic epic ♪
♪ Shall stand through all ages ♪
There's no one here now.
Cry if you want.
No one will see you.
Who wants to cry?
Zhuge Yue,
thank you.
Ahead is the border of Biantang.
Lady Chu and Young Master Zhuge ordered
us to split up.
I'll take the Xiuli Army north.
You follow Lady Chu east
back to Tangjing.
Have you arranged a place to stay?
Our young master has arranged it.
When he was carrying out
a mission in his early years,
he bought a villa
in the territory of Biantang.
I will take Lord He and the Xiuli Army
to settle down first.
That place is not far from Tangjing.
If necessary,
we can assist at any time.
Why are you here?
Something happened in Tangjing.
The Crown Prince was accused
of assassinating the Emperor
and colluding with King Ximeng.
He was put into prison by the Empress.
Our restaurant was also sealed up.
The Princess has set off.
The Ximeng mission
has all been arrested and put into prison.
The Queen of Lingyue
and the fake King Ximeng were not caught.
However,
the Queen of Lingyue's personal guards
have all confessed.
The ones who helped them
get the compendium
are the Crown Prince and Chu Qiao.
These witnesses and physical evidence
are enough to prove
the Crown Prince's collusion with Ximeng.
Sir, your water is ready.
Thank you.
We are taking the fastest route
to Tangjing.
We have to go through
the mountains all the way.
The horses definitely can't bear it.
But I have arranged for the Moon Guard
to wait in the town ahead.
As long as we go down the mountain,
we can change to new horses.
We will travel day and night,
cross the mountain from Liu River,
and arrive earlier than
Minglu's team.
You really are the military counselor
of Great Yong.
You are so familiar
with the terrain of Biantang.
Yes.
So if Li Ce takes you away,
I will definitely not spare Biantang.
Let's go.
[Li Qi, General of Cavalry of Biantang]
General Li was assassinated
the night before last.
He survived,
but the assassin cut off one of his hands.
We received this box the next day,
along with this letter.
Present the letter to me.
Your Majesty, this letter...
Yan Xun sent his men to deliver this.
He already knows
that Chu Qiao is in Biantang.
He wants us to hand over
the Queen of Great Yan to him.
Otherwise...
Otherwise what?
Otherwise, his Black Eagle Army
will break through
Biantang's northern defense line.
[Qifeng Palace]
Yan Xun is so audacious.
Our two Generals of Cavalry in Biantang
are Sun Di and Li Qi.
He actually, so quietly,
cut off one of his hands.
He also cut off one of Biantang's arms!
Your Majesty.
That Chu Qiao
has always been a great threat to us.
Why don't we take this opportunity
to issue a warrant for her arrest
and return her to Great Yan,
to eliminate future troubles?
Fool!
If we hand over Chu Qiao now,
it means we admit to harboring
the Queen of Great Yan.
If Yan Xun wants to use this as an excuse
to attack our northern defenses,
at that time,
Biantang will be in the wrong,
and we won't know how to conduct ourselves
among other nations!
I am foolish.
Please forgive me, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
What is it?
The Princess Consort of Luo is outside.
She says she has news
about the new King of Great Yan
and wants to discuss it with you.
What did you say?
I said,
Biantang and Great Yan
should form a marriage alliance
by marrying off Princess Fu.
Right now,
Yan Xun has known
that Chu Qiao is in Biantang.
If you don't hand her over,
given his character,
he definitely won't let it go.
If he uses this to attack Biantang,
even if Biantang's military strength
is not inferior to Great Yan's,
it would still be an unprovoked disaster.
But if you hand her over,
it will amount to admitting
that Biantang harbored
the Queen of Great Yan.
Even if Yan Xun
is willing not to pursue it,
Biantang will not only be humiliated
but also lose General Li Qi for nothing.
How could you let it go?
But under the pretense of
marrying Princess Fu to form an alliance,
we can confirm her identity
as the Princess
and send Chu Qiao away.
We can also ask Great Yan
for a generous betrothal gift,
such as horses, gold, silver,
or even cities in Great Yan.
Yan Xun will give
whatever you want.
But where Chu Qiao is right now
is still unknown.
The news of the Crown Prince's
imprisonment has spread.
She must be on her way back to Tangjing.
This was your idea?
Are you willing
to let Yan Xun marry Princess Fu
to be the Queen of Great Yan?
Since I'm already
the Princess Consort of Luo of Biantang,
I naturally only
have the Prince of Luo in my heart.
But I dare not deceive you, Your Majesty.
I grew up with Yan Xun from childhood,
and we do have some childhood friendship.
I am willing to use this friendship
to facilitate this marriage alliance
for you.
His Majesty is coming back.
Prepare everything in advance.
All the desks and screens
must be wiped clean one by one.
Keep the tea warm.
And...
My Lady,
I was just in the court...
I was just in the court
and heard the elders discussing.
They say
His Majesty has gone to Biantang
and might not return for a while.
Why has His Majesty gone to Biantang?
I heard...
that Chu Qiao is in Biantang.
Prince of Luo Li Yan, legitimate son
of the late Prince of Chang,
is loyal, filial, and well-mannered,
possessing extraordinary literary talent.
He is hereby appointed Minister of Rites
and granted a mansion of 500 qing
and 100 jade belts.
He's ordered to negotiate peace
and marriage with the King of Great Yan.
Your Highness,
you should properly thank
the Princess Consort of Luo
for securing this position for you.
From now on,
you are no longer an idle prince,
but the Minister of Rites.
Perfect timing.
Help me see which hairpin looks better.
Chun'er.
You've been going to the palace
a lot lately,
getting so close to Her Majesty.
Then Her Majesty suddenly rewarded me
and put me in charge of
some political marriage.
What exactly did you do?
Strange.
I've done so much for you.
Why are you thanking me in such a tone?
Tell me,
what exactly did you do?
Me?
I did many great things for you.
First, I told
the spy Yan Xun sent to find Chu Qiao
that Princess Fu
is the Queen of Great Yan
they are looking for.
Then I told Her Majesty
that Chu Qiao is not in Tangjing,
but went to Lincheng
to find her old subordinates.
Tell me,
now that Her Majesty knows this,
how could she not be burning with anxiety?
But this is not enough.
The greatest merit I achieved
is to think of a foolproof plan
for Her Majesty.
I told her to marry Chu Qiao off
to Great Yan,
using Princess Fu's name
for the political marriage.
Her Majesty was so happy
that she appointed you
as the envoy for this marriage.
You want me to negotiate
with the King of Great Yan
for the marriage of Princess Fu?
Why did you do this?
Chun'er, Chun'er,
don't do this!
You ask me why?
Because I'm not like you.
You only swallow insults
and wait for death.
You dare not fight for anything.
You only use high-sounding reasons
to deceive yourself and others,
saying you don't want it
and staying away from disputes.
It's just because you don't dare!
Chun'er,
is that how you see me?
Yes!
In my eyes, you are just that cowardly.
You like me and married me,
but don't even dare to touch me.
And you say
you'll wait until the day I'm willing.
Let me tell you,
that day will never come.
I will never willingly
love a cowardly and incompetent person!
I'm not!
According to Her Majesty's decree,
Princess Fu
is virtuous, elegant,
gentle, and wise.
To show Her Majesty's favor and regard,
she is specially granted
to marry into Great Yan
to form a good relationship
between the two countries.
This dowry is a gift from Her Majesty.
Interesting.
The envoy sent by Biantang even brought
his female family members.
Greetings, King of Great Yan,
My Lord.
The Prince of Luo said
our Princess Consort
is an old acquaintance of yours,
so there's no need for formalities.
Please move
to the itinerant court,
prepared for you, to talk.
Your Princess Consort
is an old acquaintance of mine?
Your Majesty,
congratulations.
Why is it you?
Prince of Luo Li Yan
is the Empress-appointed Marriage Envoy.
He is here to welcome
the King of Great Yan.
I am Li Yan's Princess Consort,
and I also came with him
by Her Majesty's order.
It is hoped that you
can abandon past prejudices
and facilitate the marriage
and our good relations.
Do you not want it?
Marrying Princess Fu
is the most important matter in Great Yan.
Since you've let it go,
how could I keep it in mind?
Then, please move to the itinerant court
to discuss the marriage alliance with us.
I just want to see you
suffer with my own eyes,
watching you lose everything,
including everyone you care about!
I'll make every single one
of them
live a life worse than death.
It's just that besides him,
there is another group of people.
-Marriage alliance?
It's just that I am the Princess's guard,
and I also have
some personal relationship with her,
so it is inconvenient to leave easily.