Mr. Ye?
What brings you here?
Was it you
or Fu Hailian?
I have no idea what you're saying.
I think it's Fu Hailian.
He hates the military nobles so much.
He'd love to blow
Great Yan's military nobles
to bits.
Sure, he's thought about it.
But that's all it is.
So I think
it's you.
After all, I've crossed you
more than once.
And you get back at people
over the smallest slight.
You mean
His Majesty removing you
as the Crown Prince's study companion?
So it really was you.
Yes.
It was my duty.
I just made
a suggestion to His Majesty.
It wasn't revenge.
How dare you still deny it?
You call me
someone who holds a grudge.
Taking away a Crown Prince's study companion
is nothing.
Then why did you do it?
Because His Highness
may have loyal men
or sycophants,
but never
someone like you.
What kind of person am I?
A
desperate one.
Sir.
A desperate one, huh.
Do you know
why Chen Yanyun said that?
I don't.
But I know
he's up to no good.
Because he's scared.
He's scared
I'll win the Crown Prince over.
That actually reminds me.
I may not be
the Crown Prince's study companion.
But I'm not letting
the time I spent on him
go to waste.
Sir,
if I may.
His Majesty just ordered a probe
into the attack on the Crown Prince,
and you removed Mr. Ye from his post.
Isn't that
a bit obvious?
Doesn't matter.
Since the late Prince Chengqing's rebellion,
His Majesty has been wary of military nobles.
Now the attack on the Crown Prince
has dragged in the late Prince Chengqing
and Prince Glorian.
I expect
His Majesty will start
cracking down on military nobles soon.
So removing Ye Xian from his post
is nothing but good
for him.
You're trying to
protect Lord Changxing?
Civil officials
and military nobles may be at odds,
but the country
always needs its warriors.
Lord Changxing made real contributions
and can actually fight.
I'll protect him whenever I can.
Understood.
Mr. Ye's always thinking of you.
He knew you were bored in the palace,
so he went out of his way to find
all these fun little things for you.
Too bad he can't
come play with me in the palace anymore.
He has a heart condition.
I can't
force him to stay.
There'll be other chances.
Hold onto this for me.
Show it to me secretly tonight.
Yes.
Ye Xian really gets me.
All my other study companions
treat me like their master now.
So boring.
Ye Xian is the only one
who treats me like a friend!
Ye Xian does so much for me.
I feel bad taking his gifts for nothing.
I should give him something in return.
Mr. Ye,
His Highness specially
grants you this token.
With it,
you may enter and leave the East Palace
anytime without permission.
I'm deeply moved
by His Highness's kindness.
I only hope to recover soon
and continue to serve him.
Uncle.
What brings you here?
What do you need?
A classmate just sent word.
The court has appointed
Mr. Chang Tinglan as chief examiner
for this year's metropolitan exam.
You foresaw this
and told me to seek Mr. Chang's guidance?
Guidance is one thing.
How much you actually learn
depends on your own ability.
Thank you, Uncle.
Go on.
I
have one more thing to ask.
Could you
not
arrange a match for me just yet?
Wait until after the metropolitan exam.
Why?
You have
someone else in mind?
No.
It's just...
I don't want to rush things.
You don't need to go to the academy today.
Come with me somewhere.
Yes.
I know
I shouldn't go against my uncle.
He must have thought long and hard
before arranging a match with the Yu family.
Xuanqing.
But I've followed
his lead my whole life.
This once, even if I'm wrong,
even if it costs me,
I have to take the chance.
Or
I'll regret it for the rest of my life.
Exactly.
I support you.
This is a lifetime decision.
This...
This is the cenotaph
of your birth father, Lin Zhengwei.
Are you wondering
why it's a cenotaph?
Because
your father committed
an unpardonable crime.
He was sentenced to immediate execution.
Back then,
I was too low in rank
to retrieve his body.
But...
But didn't you tell me my father...
my birth father
died protecting you
from river pirates?
That was a lie.
The truth is,
Lin Zhengwei
colluded with the river pirates
and tipped them off about the ship's route.
The ship went down, and people died.
Over a hundred soldiers and officers
drowned.
Now, only two people
know about this.
One is me.
The other is Yu Kaiji,
the former chief of the Jiaodong section
of the canal transport office.
Your future father-in-law.
Then
why did you still take me in?
Because your birth father
did save my life.
And your mother
hanged herself the night your father
was executed.
You were the only one
left in the family.
I didn't realize your mother
hid it from you so well.
You really had no idea.
But you have great literary flair.
Completely different from your father.
I felt sorry for you,
so I brought you home
and adopted you into the Fifth Branch.
I see.
You want me to marry Miss Yu
because her father
will help keep this secret.
Yes.
I expect
you'll pass the metropolitan exam.
But once you do,
you'll draw attention.
Especially from those
who seek a marriage alliance with us.
They'll dig into your background.
And then
this past
will be hard to hide.
Luckily, Kaiji thinks highly of you.
And his daughter, Wanxue,
has feelings for you.
So we agreed
to arrange the match
before the metropolitan exam.
Now you know
everything.
Marry Miss Yu
and keep this secret
as best you can?
Or call off the match
and face whatever comes
after you pass the exam?
You decide.
Miss,
a kite bears your feelings.
Isn't giving it to Mr. Chen Xuanqing
too forward?
I want to be straightforward.
Let him know how I feel.
Then I'll know how he feels too.
After all, I'm a girl.
I can't keep meeting him in secret.
And I don't want to spend my days
guessing and second guessing.
I'd rather just
ask him once and be done with it.
But
I do think he
has feelings for me.
Why else
would he ask me out?
Are you sure she's going to
see Chen Xuanqing?
Most likely.
Even if she isn't,
why are you panicking?
Just wait and see.
It's flying!
Miss!
So high!
It really is Chen Xuanqing.
Let's follow them.
Go over there.
That place is small.
Don't let them spot us.
Okay, let's go.
Miss Gu came early.
She's flying a kite.
A kite?
Look.
A kite.
Miss Gu is...
Xuanqing.
Xuanqing?
You go alone.
I'm not going.
When you get there,
tell her
something came up
and I really can't make it.
Give this
to her for me.
But...
Why?
Miss Gu has been waiting for you.
Besides,
we're the ones who asked her to come.
I know.
But
I can't see her right now.
It's not the right time.
Are you sure about this?
Thank you for the birthday gift.
I hope one day
I can be as brave
and free
as you.
See?
I wasn't lying.
Told you Jinzhao and Chen Xuanqing
were secretly seeing each other.
Now you have something on her.
She won't be able to bully you anymore.
Jinzhao really is something.
Her reputation is already this bad,
and she still acts so carelessly.
If this ever gets out...
This must never get out!
Swear
you won't tell anyone
what you saw today.
You never saw
Jinzhao
or Chen Xuanqing.
None of it ever happened.
Have you lost your mind?
What's wrong with you?
You said it yourself,
Jinzhao's reputation is already bad.
If we add secret meetings
to that,
how could that end well?
She's our older sister.
If her reputation is ruined,
it hurts both you and me.
Since when are you so protective of her?
She's family,
not a stranger.
Then tell Father and Mother.
Not them either.
If Father finds out,
your mother will know too.
I know what your mother
and Nanny Zhou did
to Jinzhao's marriage prospects.
That was all a misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding or not,
I don't trust Father
and I don't trust your mother.
Don't worry.
I know this has nothing to do with you.
To me,
you're you. They're them.
Just promise me.
Don't tell anyone
what you saw today.
Come on!
Fine!
You're so annoying.
Don't you forget it!
What time is it now?
Why isn't he here yet?
Miss, be patient.
We arrived early.
Miss, he's here.
Miss Gu.
Miss Qingpu.
Where is your master?
He had things to do
at the academy today
and couldn't get away,
so he can't make it.
I'm really sorry.
He asked me
to give you this.
We had an agreement.
Why did he suddenly not come?
Qingpu,
stop.
I understand what your master
means.
Miss.
He's just playing with you.
What is Mr. Chen
thinking anyway?
Whatever he's thinking.
I did my best.
Him not showing up
is on him.
I just need to know I tried
and I have no regrets.
Miss.
The Madam
sent over some new jewelry
for you to use during the New Year.
That's thoughtful of her.
Open it.
Let me see.
This color suits you.
Put them on
and let me see.
Miss,
I don't need them.
Come on.
This color is plain.
Can't pair them
with gold or gems.
Just a
simple bracelet then.
This one works.
Miss.
Put it on.
So pretty.
Qingpu.
I wish we could go back
to Tongzhou for the New Year.
I want to be
with Grandmother,
watching Iron Fireworks with my brother.
When did you get here?
I've been here for a while.
Saw you were lost in thought,
so I didn't want to disturb you.
You
are always so formal.
I asked you here
for your advice.
Tongzhou's autumn tax this year
is 50% higher than last year's.
This is all thanks to
the land equalization.
I've been wondering
how to spread the word
about this success.
Help me come up with something.
Let the court
and common people
see the benefits
of land surveying
and the new tax laws.
But we can't spend too much money.
Can't just blow everything
we've just earned.
I actually do have an idea.
Go on.
In recent years,
because the court has no money,
we haven't seen
the Aoshan Lantern display.
So I think
you should propose
that the Ministry of Revenue
fund them
and set them up again this year.
Then
bring in
the best folk performances
from
across the country,
like street shows,
dragon
and lion dances,
and Qinqiang opera.
Especially the Iron Fireworks.
They're lively and lucky.
I
haven't seen them in years.
Let the people of the capital
have a real celebration.
And on top of that,
set up more porridge kitchens
to help the refugees.
Let everyone
have a proper New Year.
Good.
Great idea.
Build up the momentum
and make the people happy.
Good.
Excellent!
But one thing.
The grace should come from above.
Instead of in Revenue's name,
do it
in His Majesty's name.
Understood.
That's wise of you.
Take it easy.
Why are you coughing again?
I thought
you were getting better.
I wasn't coughing at all a few days ago.
Don't know why
it's back.
Have some tea.
Okay.
This is the end of the year.
Don't just stand there.
Sit down.
Sit.
Rong.
There's
too much rich food in your bowl.
It causes internal heartiness.
Eat some vegetables.
Thank you, Mother.
Father.
Thank you, Father.
Have some vegetables.
Thank you, Mother.
Have some more.
Grandmother.
I want some meatballs.
Here.
Move the meatballs closer.
Jinzhao
loves meatballs.
Here.
Let me get you some.
Yao.
Let me give you one too.
Is it good?
Yes.
Here.
Your grandmother says
you love meatballs.
Try it
and see if it tastes the same
as the one
in Tongzhou.
Delicious.
Have some more.
You've wasted away.
Your clothes look so loose on you.
I feel like
you've been
a bit down lately.
Firecrackers!
I want to go to the temple fair.
I want to go too!
Go on.
Let's go.
Be careful.
Got it!
You should go too.
Out with the old, in with the new.
Don't carry
the bad luck and unhappiness
into the new year.
Miss,
time to drink your medicine.
When will I be done with this medicine?
I was perfectly fine.
Why am I coughing again?
Coughs come and go.
It's been
dry
and dusty lately.
That can easily trigger a cough.
Just keep warm.
Maybe
you'll be better in a few days.
I hope so.
What's wrong?
I'll go get a physician!
Wait.
It's the New Year.
Where are you going to find a physician?
But Miss...
Don't say anything yet.
Listen to me.
But...
This is
Jinzhao's first New Year
at home.
If I tell them this,
the kids
won't have fun.
Don't ruin the mood.
Let's wait till after the New Year.
The Madam's coughing so loud
we can hear it across the courtyard.
Did you call a physician?
No.
It seems the Madam
had the Master keep the New Year's vigil.
He's staying in the front courtyard.
No need to go to the Madam's courtyard.
Why did it suddenly get so bad?
She was fine just a few days ago.
Liuxiang, you can go now.
I want to talk to Nanny Zhou alone.
I added rhubarb
to the Madam's medicine.
What?
Keep your voice down.
How could you put that in her...
Nanny Zhou.
I really had no choice.
Don't you see?
Only if she's really sick
will the Master let you run the household.
Still, we can't do that.
Think about Lan's coming-of-age ceremony
and her future dowry.
I did all of this.
Just pretend I never told you.
But we can't...
The Master is here!
Well, if it isn't Mr. Chen.
Happy New Year.
I wish you well.
Mr. Su, happy New Year to you too.
I rented
a two-room suite up ahead.
Would you care
to come upstairs and take a look?
Better than getting jostled around
down here with the crowd.
I'll go see the Aoshan Lantern display.
I'll come to you
in a bit.
Alright.
It's a deal.
Rong, wait for me!
I've seen plenty of dragon dances.
But a fire-breathing dragon is rare.
Watch out.
I'm fine.
Let's go somewhere else for a look.
I was telling people
that the New Year in the capital
isn't as lively as in Tongzhou.
Seems
I was talking big.
I think you were right.
Sure, the capital is busier,
but they don't have Iron Fireworks.
So Tongzhou is still better.
Walking over bridges cures all illnesses.
Let's go do that.
Rong.
Where did he go?
Let's go.
Sir, it's just us now.
Gentlemen,
take care.
Let's go.
Okay.
Come again tomorrow.
Alright.
Sir.
Mr. Gu!
You're not resting during the New Year?
If no one else is resting,
why should I?
Alright, alright.
Right this way.
After you.
Why are there so many people?
This was your stupid idea.
Sir,
you asked me
where the ladies of the capital
go for New Year outings.
I was just asking casually.
You took it too seriously.
Miss Gu?
Mr. Ye.
Sir,
is Miss Gu
still mad at you?
No one
is asking you to speak.
Miss.
He's the heir of Lord Changxing.
Wouldn't it be rude
if we just run off like this?
If I stay,
I'll only be even ruder!
I'm doing this for his own good.
Miss,
didn't you say the capital
doesn't have Iron Fireworks?
Let's go up ahead and see!
Okay.
Sir, look over there.
Let's go that way!
So
this is Iron Fireworks.
You've never seen it before?
I'm an idiot.
I forgot you've been
in central Sichuan all these years.
I thought I wouldn't
get to see Iron Fireworks this year.
But here they are.
So for every loss,
there's a gain.
Since that's the case,
I shouldn't go looking for trouble.
I can't believe the capital
has Iron Fireworks.
I wonder if Jinzhao
saw it.
She's always loved watching this.
Grandmother even brought
a Shanxi troupe
to Tongzhou just for her.
You should be thanking me.
If I hadn't dragged you along,
you'd have missed this grand spectacle.
Long live the Great Yan!
Mr. Chen Yanyun?
Someone fell in the water!
Help!
- Chen Yi.
- Sir.
Hurry and save her!
Someone fell in the water!
Sir,
I think someone fell in.
Help!
Let's go check it out.
Someone fell in over there!
He got her out.
She's safe.
Are you alright?
It's you.
Thank you, Mr. Chen.
Miss! Miss!
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Sir,
isn't that
Mr. Chen Yanyun's guard?
Could it be...
It is him.
Don't catch a cold.
Thanks.
Miss,
Lord Guan saved you.
No.
It was Mr. Chen Yanyun.
You mean the person
who saved you at the back mountain
in Tongzhou
wasn't Mr. Chen Xuanqing,
but Mr. Chen Yanyun?
In the water,
when he was pulling me to shore,
it all came back to me.
Miss,
so
Mr. Chen Yanyun
has saved you three times now.
Yeah.
How am I ever going to
repay such a favor?
Why does my drawing
look so much like...
Jinzhao?
Sir,
the ginger soup is ready.
Leave it over there.
Yes.
Chen Yi.
Sir.
Go
invite Miss Gu over.
Yes.
Sir,
what is this about?
Just go invite her.
Yes.
I spoke out of turn.
Wait. Come back.
Never mind.
You can go now.
Yes.