(Watch on www.kisskh.be Support Admin)
So, do you like him or what?
Not to the point of liking him yet. I
just want to get to know him better.
Do you think Fah knows it's you?
If it were the real Typhoon, he
wouldn't even be able to talk to P'Fah.
You're afraid of losing P'Fah.
But aren't you afraid P'Fah
might fall for someone else?
Of course I am.
What's wrong with you, Fah? You usually
accept things from anyone, don't you?
Because there's already
someone in his heart now.
How could he casually
accept things from others?
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
- Good morning, Doctor Fah.
- Good morning.
Here you go.
Here you are.
Happy birthday.
You must have received
plenty of birthday wishes already.
But please allow me to be one
more person praying for you.
Whether it's your studies,
or your work,
you're already amazing.
I hope you get some time to rest as well.
And be very happy.
Because your smile is one
of the wonders of this world.
I bought a Polaroid camera
as your birthday present.
If it's not too much trouble,
I'd like to invite you to
take photos together.
So we can share photos
from our everyday lives.
But if it's inconvenient, that's totally fine.
Just accepting it
already makes me very happy.
So, how was it?
Mm.
I think it's the same person.
I think I've found the
person from the letters.
No.
He came to me himself.
Don't you recognize his handwriting?
Phoon's handwriting didn't look like this before. Or
did he change it on purpose so I wouldn't recognize it?
But after writing for a while,
he must've gotten used to it.
So when he wrote the
birthday card, he slipped up.
What do you think about him?
I used to think of Phoon as
nothing more than a younger brother.
A kid next door I wanted
to take the best care of.
But you know he's never
seen you as just a brother.
I know.
And I'm sure Phoon knows it too.
But after all this happened,
it feels like I've gotten to
know another side of Phoon.
A side that's not just the
little brother he's always been.
So how do you feel about him now?
I like the person from the letters.
If that person is Phoon,
then I guess I like Phoon.
That's really all there is to it.
Aren't you mad at him?
For not being honest with you?
I
I'm actually happy.
That it's Phoon.
So what are you going to do now?
Are you just going to stay the
same and wait for him to confess?
I
I used to think I was
patient enough to wait.
But now I'm not so sure anymore.
Why is P'Fah so kind?
He even remembered.
That I'm afraid of the dark.
Are you sure you can still tutor
like this? You're really not okay.
I honestly don't know how I should act.
Just act normal.
Smile, stay calm, and be normal.
Nothing should happen. You can do it.
Stay strong. You'll get
through this. Trust me.
- Easter.
- Yes.
Shall we go now?
Yes, let's go.
What about Phoon?
Are you coming with us?
Oh, you guys go ahead. I need
to take care of something first.
Phoon, where's the pen
you borrowed from me?
The pen I borrowed? Oh, I'll find it.
- Found it.
- Okay.
See you. Bye.
- Want this too?
- Just take it.
Let's go.
Aren't we fighting over food now?
P'Gib, here you go.
Okay.
Hey, don't go yet.
Doctor Fah asked me to make
cocoa for someone special.
Wait a moment. I'll make it for you.
Oh, okay.
So?
How's your relationship going?
- It's good.
- That's good.
I've seen you two exchanging
letters for quite a while.
There's bound to be some progress.
Yes.
It's ready. Cocoa for someone special.
Someone special?
Well, Typhoon is a
special customer of my cafe.
I just came to pick something up.
- Did he bring it today yet?
- Oh, yeah. He already did.
You're here at an unusual time today, Fah.
I usually see you in the morning.
I just happened to be free.
And…
Have you treated him to cocoa yet?
Uh...
Of course I have. I wouldn't forget.
Phoon's tutoring with friends
at the café today, right?
Oh, yes.
Go with me then.
Okay.
Let's go.
Phoon.
Yes?
How have you been?
I've been well.
What about you, P'Fah?
I'm doing well too.
If there's anything at all,
you can always tell me.
I didn't pass the medical school exam.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
I mean, you worked so hard tutoring me.
Are you okay?
At first, I was a little disappointed.
But now I think maybe
this outcome is for the best.
Why is that?
I think I'll take the entrance
exam for a faculty I actually like.
I just made an important decision in my
life, even though I can't say what it is.
But thinking about you
gave me more courage.
That's amazing.
Thank you.
Thank you for stepping
in to help yesterday.
You already thanked me yesterday.
P'Fah…
You even remembered.
That I'm afraid of thunder.
And afraid of the dark.
Of course I remembered.
When the power went out,
the first thing I thought
was, “What about Phoon?”
"Where is Phoon?"
When I realized you'd gone to the restroom,
I went looking for you right away.
P'Fah…
Over the past year,
I've grown up so much.
I know.
You've done really well.
Aren't you going to ask me?
About why, back then, I…
Do you want to tell me?
If not, you don't have to.
I believe that
you must have had your reasons.
Whenever you're ready,
you can tell me then.
I'm
I'm afraid that you're still angry.
I'm not angry at you.
Don't overthink it.
The shirt is really nice, but
it's too loose. I can't wear it.
What is it?
I was just thinking…
You really are tiny.
With P'Fah, it's probably…
- Back to how it used to be.
- Like before?
I mean, yesterday, P'Fah…
Patted my head and said,
“You're really tiny.”
Wait, isn't “tiny” just a
polite way of saying “short”?
North, why are you killing the mood?
He meant it affectionately, idiot.
Seriously.
Anyway, let's focus on the “head pat” part.
What about it?
Hey.
Why are you making that face?
I lied to P'Fah about Fun.
If he finds out, he'll definitely be mad.
So you're going to tell him.
About P'Fun?
I just don't want to lie anymore.
I think that's good.
When you go talk to him,
you can apologize to him again.
I think it'll be fine.
You're sincere, after all.
I guess that's what I'll do.
Hey, guys.
Today,
let's go reading.
Dao, come with us.
No, I've got work to do.
- I was broke too, and I'm not even taking jobs like that.
- Not working? You used to.
Sure. You just happened to
meet P'Jo. Lucky you, that's all.
Yeah, yeah. It's your head
that's messed up right now.
Here.
I'm still choosing.
What does that have to do with you?
Hey, let me see too.
North, don't push. Move.
Let me see. Why are you so stingy?
Whoa.
Is that a picture of the sun?
This is...
Isn't this Phoon's sky?
- North, stop. You're going overboard.
- Why are you stopping me?
Look at how you're acting.
- Let's hurry up and eat before P'Fah sees.
- Yeah, hurry up.
Eat fast. P'Fah's coming.
More? Here, take it.
Finish everything.
All of it.
- You started it.
- I'm not a dog.
- Bye, P'Gib! Bye!
- Bye!
I'll come get a new coupon tomorrow.
My cafe's coupons are almost gone.
Fah.
You've been coming in the
evening for two days now.
Were you waiting on purpose?
No.
I wanted him to leave first.
So we wouldn't run into each other.
Okay, wait a moment.
Okay.
Here you go.
Why didn't you come in
the morning like usual?
I was going to pick someone up on the way.
It's nothing. I'll go now.
Pick someone up?
Want some?
P'Hill, do you want some?
Hey, Fah. What should we eat this evening?
No idea.
You guys aren't helping at all.
Go ask your wife.
I just saw him wandering around here.
He went to the bathroom.
North probably spoils Ter.
Me?
Ugh.
I don't want to fight with North.
Then sushi is fine.
- Which place?
- The one in front of the campus?
It just opened. The
reviews say it's really good.
Sounds good. Let's go.
You guys go ahead. I'll wait for North.
Phoon, come with us.
You can go with me.
Then I'll go with P'Fah.
Sure. See you at the restaurant.
Hurry up.
Let's go. See you.
- I'll carry it for you.
- See you at the restaurant.
Oh, thank you.
Just go.
- Want some?
- No.
Thank you.
Phoon, could you grab
the blue paper bag for me?
Uh…
Could you take the stuff inside out?
What's inside?
Photos.
A letter and some snacks.
What kind of photos?
Flowers.
Could you read the letter to me?
Uh… is that okay?
Yes.
I want to know what
it says, but I'm driving.
Could you read it for me?
The flowers I've been taking care
of for months have finally bloomed.
They're really beautiful.
I couldn't help but take
photos to share with you.
If you're interested in growing some,
I'd be happy to recommend how.
Final exams are coming up,
so you must be studying hard.
I am too.
Hang in there.
Let's get through finals together.
Is that all?
Uh, P'Fah.
Weren't we supposed to
eat sushi with the others?
This place is good.
I wanted you to try it.
Oh.
Okay.
Here.
P'Fah.
Yes?
If I start over as a first-year student,
would it be a waste of time?
No.
If it means getting to
know yourself better,
and knowing what you truly want to study.
What do you like.
No matter what it is, I think it's worth it.
So then
what faculty are you
planning to transfer to?
Have you decided yet?
I want to study photography.
That's good.
You like it, after all.
By the way
that faculty
doesn't it require
Arts-Language Program scores?
Have you been preparing for a long time?
Well
I just started studying.
But
I'm afraid I won't
remember everything in time.
Phoon…
Do you want me to tutor you?
Would that really be okay?
Of course.
But this time
I'm not letting you run away anywhere.
In that case
I'll be in your care, then.
Sure.
Thank you.
About
the letters
yes?
You can ask. Why?
Whose are they?
I don't know.
You've been talking, but you
don't even know who he is?
That's right.
I barely know anything about him.
He didn't tell you anything about himself?
No.
I asked, but he wouldn't say.
That's too bad.
But it's okay, really.
If he's comfortable
I'm okay with everything.
And
how long have you been talking?
About
two months now.
Well
that's quite a while.
Actually,
I want to keep talking longer.
That's nice.
Hmm?
What's nice?
Oh
I mean
the person who
writes the letters.
He's kind of cute.
But
these days, not many people
write letters to talk anymore.
Mm.
But it does have its downsides.
When you want to meet
you can't.
When you want to hear his voice
And another thing
if one day he disappears...
I
wouldn't know what to do.
If he really disappeared
he'd be pretty heartless, wouldn't he?
Heartless?
Of course.
After making someone like him this much,
and then just disappearing.
If that's not heartless
what would you call it?
People should learn to take
responsibility for other feelings.
Right?
Fun.
I'm really happy to have today.
I once thought my life would
have no meaning anymore
when Fun wasn't by my side.
But in the end
I got to meet everyone.
I learned so many things.
And that's how I realized that being alive
is already the best thing.
I once thought the rain would never stop.
But when it finally did
the sky was truly beautiful.
It was worth the wait.
Waiting for a brighter sky.
The point is—you know P'Fah likes him,
but the guy from the
letters doesn't know yet.
So what are you gonna do?
Keep sending letters like this?
I think that's the only way, yeah.
We've come this far already.
And P'Fah even told
you he likes him already.
I'm so happy the letter
plan worked out for Maew.
Worked out?
Me, really?
Maew, we're already this far—have
some confidence in yourself.
- You're basically about to ask him to be your boyfriend already. Hey, why'd you hit me?
- He's shy.
Wow, you're really blushing hard.
Caught you.
But seriously, P'Fah is no joke.
He's pretty clear about it too.
Hey, guys.
I've got something to tell you.
Hmm?
- I'm going to drop out.
- What? You've got kidney stones?
Drop out.
Seriously, you're never
serious at the right time.
I thought you said kidney stones.
You're really dropping out?
Yeah.
I already applied for the photography exam.
So it'll just be me and Foam left together.
If it's just you two, don't fight, okay?
- Yeah.
- But I'm kinda sad.
I won't be with you guys anymore.
Come on, you're being dramatic.
We'll still see each other anyway, right?
- Yeah.
- True.
We're really happy for you, Maew.
That you finally chose your own path.
Won't your dad say anything about it?
Especially now that you're
talking to p"Fah again.
Whatever happens, happens.
Well…
If my dad won't pay for
me to study photography,
I'll just do freelance
photography or something.
I never wanted to rely
on him forever anyway.
It's okay. You've got us.
Don't pressure yourself too much.
You're already amazing
for deciding this much.
Yeah, I think I'm pretty amazing too.
Both for being born
and for everything about Fun.
For every time my dad blamed
me, even when I did nothing wrong.
I used to think that if one
day I lost my mom and Fun,
I wouldn't want to lose my dad too.
Until I started losing myself.
Damn, that's handsome.
Hey.
Daotok, wanna go eat?
Nah, I'm going back to my room to work.
Look at him.
Wow.
Always ditching his friends.
Do you know how lonely we are?
- For real.
- I see you two eating with your boyfriends every day.
When do you even have time to be lonely?
Wow, you really can talk.
I know it—you secretly went to eat together,
just the two of you and P'Fah, right?
Yeah.
That day I ordered tons of sushi. So
what, you made me to eat everything.
True. He must paid for that.
So now that Typhoon
and P'Fah are good again,
how's the situation with the letter person?
- Answer me.
- It's going okay.
Caught you.
What does “going okay” mean?
Are you really not going to tell P'Fah?
I'm scared that if I tell him,
P'Fah will be disappointed.
Hey.
No way.
You never know though, right?
I don't think P'Fah would be disappointed.
P'Fah really seems to like
the person in the letters, Phoon.
Yeah.
I think so too.
Thanks. I feel better now. I trust Dao.
Hey, I said the same thing.
- Why don't you trust me?
- Huh?
What the hell, let's go.
You never believe anything I say.
What are you even saying?
Would it be possible if I
wanted to see you just once?
Do you think Phoon will come see you?
He will.
Why are you so confident about that?
What kind of plan do you have?
About the letters…
Actually, I have something
I'm not sure about too.
What is it?
I'm not sure if that person
really likes me or not.
If they didn't like you, why
would they write you letters?
I don't know.
- Maybe they're writing to several people.
- No way.
How do you know, Phoon?
Just a guess.
Then that means they like me, right?
Yeah.
Only me, right?
So that means he'll love only me, right?
What do you say?
Yes. I'm sure he'll love
P'Fah and only P'Fah.
Oh.
Was it fun teasing him?
He was kind of cute getting teased.
Look at your friend.
But when you really think about it,
North and Ter aren't bad at all.
They've totally got their friend's back.
Even if it's not very smooth.
So what do you think we should do?
I think Ter will already go
along with Phoon anyway.
He'll probably talk him into it.
But as for North,
he'll likely be the one
pushing him to come.
I think that's exactly why I'm confident
Phoon will come—because of North.
Hey, you should thank me.
My wife's doing this
much for you, you know.
- Ok.
- Your boyfriend does something nice and you take all the credit.
Of course I do.
What are you guys talking about?
You're loud as hell.
And what's wrong with
you? Why do you look like Jo?
How does he looks like me?
You always smirk when
you've got some evil plan, like
like “damn, I'm handsome” or something.
Which
you actually are handsome, Jo.
I mean,
in this whole world, you're the
only one I'll admit I'm second to.
Everyone else, I think I'm better-looking.
Nice save.
Isn't it sticking out a bit?
You look like a teenage mom.
Tuck your stomach in a little.
This right here is the ultimate level.
Seriously, what are you guys doing?
Disguised him
I know it's a disguise, but
what are you doing it for?
Just talk to him directly.
Maew doesn't dare face him directly, North.
So you're really going to
disguise yourselves like this?
- Yeah.
- You think P'Fah won't notice?
Hey, look at this.
This.
What do you think?
If you ran into him on the street,
you wouldn't recognize him.
You wouldn't recognize
him? Idiot. Just look at him.
Damn it, North. If you can't recognize
him, don't act like you're so smart.
You're not helping, and now
you're getting in the way. Seriously.
Alright, alright. Don't fight. Stop it.
So, does this outfit pass?
Mm, it passes.
I think it passes too.
But I think you should take it off. It's hot.
Yeah.
Okay?
You'll pass out on the actual day.
Ow, ow.
I think I can handle it.
You're already panting
just standing in the room.
But P'Fah recognizes Maew's voice. So
does that mean you guys can't talk at all?
Then what if
I write it in a notebook?
Sure.
I don't think he'd mind that much.
So have you written back
yet, about agreeing to meet?
Not yet.
I don't know what to say.
Just say you'll meet
him, but with conditions.
But right now,
I think P'Fah is already
head over heels for you.
Whatever you ask, he'll
probably agree to it all.
Caught you.
North.
Me again.
Thank you for wanting to meet me.
I want to meet you too.
It might seem a bit complicated,
but I have a few conditions.
Is it this place?
Hey, why are you so tense?
Let's go.
One.
I'll be wearing something
rather unusual when I meet you.
Please don't mind it.
Two.
I don't want you to
try to find out who I am.
Thank you for coming to meet me.
Three. If you happen to find out
who I am,
please pretend you don't know.
I have so many things I want to tell you.
I really feel at ease.
You're my safe zone.
Is that okay?
Can you be my safe zone?
I can be anything.
That's so sweet.
Why are you being this kind to me?
Because you're important to me.
I really wanted to hear you say that.
You're important to me.
You're not ready yet, are you?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
For now,
this is enough.
Has anyone ever told you
that you're really cute?
Where have you been all this time?
There's something I want to ask you.
Yes?
I once wrote in my letter that
the name Tonfah comes from
my father wanting me to be the sky,
and my mother wanting me to be a tree.
What about you?
What do you want me to be?
Love.
Why did you want to meet me?
I just wanted to know
how I'd feel if I met you.
And then I realized
it feels really good.
I want to see you often.
What about you?
Why did you decide to come meet me?
Because you said you wanted to see me.
Why?
Even though you chose to
hide your identity this much.
I don't really know. You just
said you wanted to meet me,
so I wanted to come see you.
May I hold your hand?
You're love to me too.
What's wrong?
You don't like it? I'm sorry.
Do you want to wipe your tears
first? I'll close my eyes, okay?
Have you stopped crying?
It's okay.
Wait.
I really like your soft lips
when I kiss you.
Anyway, your first time meeting...
Don't say it.
It's been so long since we last met, P'Fah.
Didn't we just see each other yesterday?
Are you free tonight?
I'll tutor you.
The chance is here. Go for it.
P'Fah is kind to everyone.
He might really like the
person from the letters.
You might be wondering why I kissed you.
The answer is...