=No Doubt In Us=
(Adapted from the Manman comic No Doubt in Us)
=Episode 2=
The Empress Dowager has arrived.
Mother.
Xu Yu,
how dare you!
This is regicide!
Regicide warrants
the execution of your entire clan.
Aunt,
the Empress has always run wild
because of her powerful family.
- How insolent!
- You're the insolent one!
Thanks to His Majesty's
abundant blessings,
he didn't fall
for the Xu family's schemes.
What?
Your Xu family
has always been ambitious.
Now they're not even
bothering to hide it?
(Mother knows right from wrong.)
(Why condemn Xu Yu
without hearing the facts?)
(And Qiluo too.)
(She's merely a consort.)
(How dare she disrespect the Empress?)
His Majesty has arrived.
Your Majesty,
what brings you here?
Your Majesty.
Empress Dowager.
Empress Dowager,
my fall into the water
wasn't the Empress's fault.
I've been unfilial and caused you worry.
Your Majesty,
Her Majesty bullied me.
Qiluo.
Your Majesty.
This is indecent.
Empress Dowager, don't worry.
I'll handle the Empress.
Return to your palace.
Qiluo,
accompany her.
Your Majesty.
What should we do, Your Majesty?
Don't twist my waist.
Then what do you propose?
Go find him.
(Star-Gazing Pavilion)
(Seven-day retreat. Do not disturb)
The Grand Preceptor is in retreat.
Who'll help us switch back?
Why would the Grand Preceptor
retreat now?
He has reasons for retreating.
Let's try solving this ourselves first.
(External force caused our body swap.)
(Let's try the same method.)
Your Majesty.
Are you ready?
Come on.
Three, two, one!
Xu Yu,
you deceived me.
Your Majesty.
No.
We must abandon this method.
Otherwise, before swapping back,
we'll be exhausted.
I recall when we fell into the water,
I heard thunder.
There was indeed thunder.
My body felt a tingling pain.
What now?
Their Majesties jumped into water again.
It's time.
Where are you going?
To hold court.
Come back soon.
You're holding court.
I'm holding court?
(Taiji Hall)
Your Majesty,
the imperial bloodline is fragile.
The crown prince position
remains vacant.
Without an heir soon,
ministers will grow restless,
and the realm cannot be pacified.
In my humble opinion,
concubine selection should be tomorrow.
(Maintain imperial dignity in court.)
Posture straight, gaze steady,
and never reveal joy or anger.
(My father fights at the frontier.)
(My brother postpones
marriage for the war.)
(You old fools)
(scramble to find
Xiao Jinyun concubines.)
(Treating me like decoration?)
With war raging, the treasury is empty.
This year's concubine selection
can be skipped.
Securing the imperial lineage
is the foundation of the state.
Provisions and supplies will be handled
by the Ministry of Revenue.
(How is this helping the Emperor?
It's clearly to sideline the Emperor.)
What do you mean?
Now our soldiers
are protecting the country,
fighting on the front lines.
Instead, I'll hold
a concubine selection.
Won't that make me
a pleasure-seeking tyrant?
Cancel the selection.
That's all.
Dismissed.
- Your Majesty is wise!
- We respectfully see Your Majesty off.
How dare you quibble!
Wasn't it you who pushed
His Majesty yesterday?
Don't think you can hide it from me
because His Majesty favors you.
His Majesty has been
buried in memorials.
His body is exhausted.
He slipped and accidentally
fell into the lake.
I jumped into the water to save him.
Why did His Majesty fall into the water
as soon as he went to see you?
Did you push him in
and then pretend to rescue him
to vie for favor?
I disdain such actions.
Nor would I be foolish enough
to use such a risky move
to implicate my entire family.
I've heard
your family's recent border victories
are overshadowing the throne.
Who knows if you have ulterior motives?
Heard?
Then tell me, Consort Zhao.
Where did you hear that?
You reside in the palace,
yet you speak confidently
about the Xu family's affairs.
Could it be that Chancellor Zhao
informed you of court matters,
using the harem to interfere in politics
and frame the Xu family?
No.
Aunt.
I'm exhausted.
Is the Empress in Fengyi Palace?
A-A palace maid said
Her Majesty went to Ci'an Palace
to pay respects,
and it's been some time.
(No. Could something have happened?)
Your Majesty,
Prince Xiaoyao requests an audience.
(Jinming, Prince Xiaoyao?)
(It's said that Prince Xiaoyao
is of noble character)
(and favored by the Emperor
and Empress Dowager.)
(He is elegant and handsome,)
(with a face like the autumn moon
and a glow like spring blossoms.)
So handsome.
This is Prince Xiaoyao? So handsome.
(Xiaoyao)
(Xiao Jinming)
Jinyun.
Jinyun, lend me some money.
I've been cheated.
Prince Ning cheated.
Jinyun, you almost
wouldn't have seen me.
Jinyun.
Brother!
You must avenge me.
I'll issue an edict for you
to seize Prince Ning's assets.
- Alright?
- Sure.
No, it's too severe.
Why go big for something small?
Please, Jinyun, just lend me some money.
Lending you money is possible,
unless you agree to one condition.
What condition?
Go to Ci'an Palace
and bring my wife back.
Rest assured,
I will not fail the mission.
But, Jinyun,
you're quite concerned about her.
Nonsense.
(I'm not concerned about him.)
(I'm worried that if I don't
rescue Xiao Jinyun,)
(when we switch bodies back later,)
(with his pettiness,
he will retaliate tenfold.)
What are you waiting for?
Go and bring her to Fengyi Palace.
With me, Prince Xiaoyao,
stepping in, how could it not succeed?
Jinyun.
Remember to prepare the money.
♪Parting clouds
to pluck the waxing moon♪
♪Brewing a pot of bygone years♪
♪Chill flame, window shade,
console my grieving soul♪
♪Drunk through lifetimes
with no dreams returned♪
♪If not for letting go, how could I
bear to shatter this dream♪
♪Returning to drift
through the mortal world♪
♪Like her, like me, like you♪
♪Hairpins carved
with endless sighs and regrets♪
♪Fate laid bare my deepest thoughts♪
♪Like vows, like remorse, like love♪
♪Loving, hurting,
and regretting our late meeting♪
♪Tell me, after all this entanglement,
who regrets it more♪