In the previous episode...
Team Nankatsu made it
to the finals
of the single elimination
tournament in Shizuoka.
Despite not being
able to count on
their goalkeeper
Genzo Wakabayashi,
they overcame that
and defeated team Shimada.
A team known for
their strong
defensive lineup.
It was a difficult
battle for Team Nankatsu...
Not only did they
have to deal with
Shimada's
defensive prowess,
but their endurance
and effectiveness
was put to the test
due to the rain.
During the second half,
Tsubasa had
the determination
not to let any of that
stop him.
And thanks to
his teammate's passes,
he beat Shimada
to the punch
and scored
the game winning goal.
It was also then that
goalkeeper Yuzo Morisaki
was able to show off
his skill and worth
on the playing field.
Stopping a shot
could've cost
Nankatsu the game.
On the other hand,
team Meiwa also made it
to the finals...
lead by the tiger himself,
Kojiro Hyuga.
[opening theme]
Episode 12:
Crushing Wakabayashi.
Shimizu will win it all!
Shimizu will never fall!
-Go team! Go team!
-You're the one!
-Shimizu knows that
-they are done!
-Go team! Go team!
-There it is...
-You're the one!
-Each team's crowd
is going wild cheering.
Finally, the moment has
come to decide which team
will represent
the Shizuoka prefecture.
Which team will win
to compete at
the national tournament?
Will it be team Nankatsu,
mostly composed of team members from Shutetsu?
NATIONAL JUVENILE SOCCER TOURNAMENT SHIZUOKA TOURNAMENT NANKATSU SC
Or will it be team Shimizu?
Whom have won perfect games
NATIONAL JUVENILE SOCCER TOURNAMENT SHIZUOKA TOURNAMENT NANKATSU SC
in all of their matches thus far.
Listen, the time has come, everyone.
Hey, how's your leg doing, by the way?
I feel like it's brand new.
I wouldn't let you guys
play this match without me.
Thanks again, Yuzo.
You defended the goal
for us.
-Job well done.
-Mhm.
Now I'll be the one
protecting our team's goal
with everything I've got.
SHIMIZU FC LOCKER ROOM
Remember,
our strategy is to cover
that kid Tsubasa Ozora
at all costs.
It doesn't matter
if he has the ball or not.
I don't want you to let him
move freely whatsoever,
you all got that?
-Yes!
I'll say this once.
Keep your eyes on him.
-Yes.
-We'll do that, Captain.
Mhm.
Both teams
have put forth
their best effort
to be here.
It's the moment of truth.
Now we'll finally see
Nankatsu and Shimizu
face off.
The team that wins
will represent
Shizuoka prefecture.
This sucks.
I'm on the bench again?
You can do it, Tsubasa!
You are the best!
Hey, Sanae,
you're too intense.
The match
hasn't even started.
Can you tone it down a tad?
Who are you calling intense?
Don't you know
how important this match is?
Now more than ever,
we have to--
Come on, Tsubasa,
score on them!
What? What?
I thought I heard someone
yelling out Tsubasa's name.
You thought you were
his only fan?
There's tons of girls
that cheer him.
Listen carefully,
I'm the only one who can
really cheer Tsubasa on.
Both teams
are waiting on
the ref's signal to begin.
Nankatsu maintains
their 4-3-3 formation,
lead by Tsubasa Ozora,
and Genzo Wakabayashi.
Tsubasa scored a hat trick
in his last match,
while Genzo was out
because of an injury.
But today, he's ready to
jump out into the field.
Nankatsu's roster
is complete.
Team Shimizu
prefers to use
a defensive formation
favorable to
his team leader
Morimichi Kawakami,
their prodigy.
With a 4-4-2 formation,
they're a well-rounded team
who doesn't fall short
to Nankatsu.
Their players
are very strong.
Both teams have
practically scored
the same amount of goals
in their matches.
Which makes it hard
to predict the winner
of this nail-biting
encounter.
If we win this, we'll go to
the national tournament.
Hey, Tsubasa,
It's time to win.
Yeah.
And the official whistle
sparks up the hearts
of these young men.
Taro Misaki dribbles
the ball with determination.
I won't let you go through.
Here, Hajime!
Taro Misaki
quickly changes the pace
and passes to
Hajime Taki.
Tsubasa!
Tsubasa
makes a run for it,
looking for a pass
from Hajime.
-Oh!
But Tsubasa finds himself
totally covered
by two other players.
Huh?!
Be careful, Hajime!
That ball's mine.
And team Shimizu
-just stole the ball.
-Run, Ichiro, move it!
Now, the yellow team starts
their counterattack.
Pass it, I'm open.
Ichiro Kanda
is asking for the ball.
Everyone, run back!
Ichiro!
Suzuki to Ichiro Kanda.
I won't let you score.
Ichiro Kanda
avoids that sliding tackle
from Nankatsu.
There's no doubt that
Shizimu's players
are very capable.
But are they good enough
to get through
-Shingo Takasugi?
-Don't dream of it.
Watch carefully
as Obayashi
and Koji Murakami
get close to
the penalty area.
-Don't let them shoot.
-We have to block them.
Ichiro Kanda
kicks a pass to Obayashi.
Take this!
Obayashi
shoots towards the goal...
Captain!
Look out, Genzo!
The goalkeeper
launches himself
towards the ball.
Genzo Wakabayashi embraces
the impact of the shot.
-No!
-Good job, Captain!
It's mine.
Now it's our turn.
Tsubasa!
Genzo Wakabayashi
sends the ball flying to
the other side of the field
to Nankatsu's forward
Tsubasa Ozora.
However,
there's a lot to overcome:
two players from Shimizu.
The three of
them jump at the same time,
but the Nankatsu's
shining star
gets the height needed to
keep possession of the ball.
Taro Misaki receives it
and passes
without thinking twice,
back to Tsubasa whom
runs towards the goal.
Tsubasa, you can do it!
And there it is.
Nankatsu's number ten's
shot is a fierce one.
But the ball
hits the goal post
with a direct impact.
Oh! Hey, that should've
gone in.
-That was too close.
-Too close for comfort.
That wasn't enough guys.
We need one more
to cover him.
Aww, that shot should've
made it in.
That's not fair.
-It's okay, Tsubasa.
-Huh?
Don't worry about it.
You'll get to score a goal
next time.
Who does she think
she is?
Huh?
Hey, Sanae, wait up!
-Tsubasa!
-Huh?
Did you forget about me?
It's me! Yayoi!
I came to cheer you on.
Uh...
Hey, just wait a second!
Oh! Huh?
What's with you and Tsubasa?
Who are you?
Hello and who might you be?
I'm the leader of
Nankatsu's cheering squad.
And I also protect
Tsubasa from harpies.
I can see that.
Tsubasa and I used to
go to the same school.
My name is Yayoi Aoba.
Nice to meet you.
Hey, cutie, how are you?
I'm also a--
You shut up, Koji.
Don't be a bootlicker.
Tsubasa is incredible
when he plays, isn't he?
He's got so much energy.
Ah... Huh?
I remember him
playing with his soccer ball
at school all day long.
He was never without it.
While watching him play
in the field,
I can tell that
his heart really...
belongs to the field.
He looks so much happier.
Back then, everyone thought
that he was weird...
because he spent his days
playing soccer.
Doesn't he ever get tired
of playing with the ball?
But I was fascinated with
Tsubasa's passion
for soccer.
He never got tired.
Yayoi, we want to
leave already.
It was sad.
I never could tell him
how I felt for him.
By the time I realized,
he had already left.
Aren't you going to
cheer for him?
Tsubasa has the ball now
and he's running.
What?!
The ball lands directly
on Tsubasa's chest.
-Huh?
-But now there are
three Shimizu players
covering him.
Now, there's three players?
You want three on him?
Yes, exactly.
But if we were to do that,
wouldn't our goal
be totally defenseless,
Captain?
You're overreacting.
Even if he dares to shoot...
I know that I can stop
his shot easily.
That's my job here.
He's the only scorer
Nankatsu's got.
Which means if we cover
Tsubasa the whole time...
there's no way they can
score on us.
This is the first time
Tsubasa's being covered
by three players at a time.
How will he overcome
this strategy
by Team Shimizu?
There are
no teammates near him.
What will you do, Tsubasa?
The more they know you,
the more pressure
the opposing team
will put on you.
-Tsubasa! Pass it here!
-Huh?
-Here!
-No!
If you keep covering
Tsubasa like that,
you're giving us all
the freedom in the world.
Teppei!
I got it!
The Nankatsu Team
passes the ball freely.
Teppei Kisugi exploits
the weak defense
and manages to make
his way to the penalty area.
He sets up
his shot and...
Morimichi Kawakami
stops it!
-What?
-What a nice catch, Captain!
What a great catch
made by the star player
of Shimizu.
Nankatsu might have
Genzo on their side,
but Team Shimizu has me
in covering their goal.
Morimichi is
a very good goalkeeper.
Tsubasa!
Have it your way, groupie.
We'll settle this once
the match is over.
Everyone, go forward!
This is
going to be a fierce battle.
They are very even.
It looks like
neither team
wants to give up ground
on the pitch.
Uh... Here it goes!
Team Shimizu
fires up a shot
towards Nankatsu's goal.
But the genius goalkeeper
Genzo Wakabayashi
easily stops that shot.
Looks like
Nankatsu's goalkeeper
is in perfect condition
to defend the team's goal.
No injuries here.
The referee whistles
the end of the first half.
We'll go on break
with both teams tied up
on the scoreboard.
While I'm standing here,
there'll be no goals
for Shimizu.
Don't get too cocky now.
Or you'll end up
regretting it, Genzo.
We'll be back with
Captain Tsubasa!
AFFILIATION: SHIMIZU FC BIRTHDAY: MAY 9 HEIGHT: 156 CM WEIGHT: 47 KG BLOOD TYPE: O
And we're back!
NANKATSU SC
LOCKER ROOM
Those guys
from Shimizu are strong.
That's true. I had no idea
they were that good.
Winning this match
won't be easy.
We know that.
Everybody, calm down!
-Huh?
-Listen up!
All we have to do
during this match
is to score one goal.
But keep this in mind...
they'll be covering Tsubasa
all the time.
So don't forget to play
as a team
throughout this match.
-Yes!
We didn't come here to lose.
We came to defeat Shimizu.
-Exactly.
We will go to
the national tournament.
Yeah!
Let's win this, team!
-Yes!
Hey, guys, I'm going to
score that goal for you.
Huh?
Tsubasa...
In that case,
we will be counting on you.
Yes!
SHIMIZU FC
LOCKER ROOM
During the second half,
I want you to cover
Tsubasa better.
We need to win by a goal
or we won't go to
the national tournament.
So from this point onward,
our strategy
will go as follows.
We'll destroy their goalie,
Genzo Wakabayashi!
If we stop
Tsubasa's offensive plays,
and we neutralize
Genzo's defensive skills,
victory will
fall on our laps
without a doubt, Coach.
I have a feeling that
their goalkeepers' injury
isn't fully healed
quite yet.
Listen up, guys,
we'll be the ones playing
at the national tournament.
-Yeah!
-That was a good game.
I've been thinking it over.
I'm going to
talk to that girl
right this instant.
She's an angel that
fell from the heavens...
a flower that beautifies
anyone's--
-I heard you say that!
-Ugh... Why me?
Koji, I'll go talk to her.
She's not there.
Where did she go?
I don't see her.
She was there
just a moment ago.
NATIONAL JUVENILE SOCCER TOURNAMENT SHIZUOKA TOURNAMENT, FINAL NANKATSU SC SHIMIZU FC
And the second half
has officially begun.
The first half finished
with a nothing-nothing tie.
Which of the two teams
will be able to score first?
-Shimizu will win it all!
-Shimizu will never fall!
-Go team! Go team!
-You're the one!
-Shimizu knows that
-they are done!
Team Shimizu is focused on
passing the ball
with precise short passes
during the first half.
Now, it looks like
their strategy
is to move forward
running faster plays.
Of course,
just as expected,
Tsubasa has three players
covering him.
Wow, are they just
going to keep that up?
Takeshi,
-open up a bit more!
-Huh?
Uh-huh.
You're good there!
Stop!
Nankatsu's goalkeeper
is giving out
desperate orders
to his team's defense.
Yeah, now it's our turn.
Be careful.
Team Shimizu is starting
to counterattack
with a long pass.
The whole team
is running towards
the goal.
The ball is landing
inside the penalty area.
I got it.
Shingo, it's mine.
The goalkeeper
waits for the ball.
Here comes
Team Shimizu.
Genzo Wakabayashi
goes for the ball.
What an incredible jump.
Be careful.
The players from Shimizu
aren't stopping.
What's happening?
They went straight for
the goalkeeper.
No!
Genzo!
And the referee
calls out the foul.
That was totally on purpose.
They didn't even care about
injuring the goalkeeper.
You idiots...
That was your intention
from the beginning,
wasn't it?
Don't take it personally.
We just wanted to
secure our victory
so we can go to
the national tournament.
Hey, Genzo, are you okay?
Yes, of course I am.
They'll need more than
a weak hit to stop me.
That's the spirit, Genzo.
Don't you forget it.
You have to score a goal.
-Yeah!
Phew, I thought this
would really worsen
Genzo's leg injury.
And we're back
with a goal kick
from Nankatsu.
We can do it!
Oh, no, Genzo!
What's happening?
Nankatsu's goalkeeper
hit the floor
and he can't
get himself up.
Genzo's really hurt.
He can't stand up.
This is our opportunity.
Yeah, we have to
attack them now.
Don't you dare stop.
Get the ball back, guys.
Don't let them get
any closer.
No...
-Ichiro!
-Shimizu is
attacking
from the right wing.
No, this can't be.
Now we'll finally
get to score.
Ichiro Kanda
makes a cross pass
-to the penalty area.
-He's all yours.
I won't allow you
to score.
Genzo
Wakabayashi launches himself
towards the ball.
But the injury
doesn't let him.
Obayashi from Shimizu
stares at a completely
unguarded goal.
And Taro Misaki
has miraculously
cleared the ball!
What a great save, Taro.
But unfortunately,
the ball bounces towards
Kazumasa Kato from Shimizu.
This is our opportunity.
Here it goes!
Nankatsu's
goalkeeper can't even move.
No! Captain!
He's useless now.
Looks like
the first goal
will go to Shimizu.
Not as long as my name is
Genzo Wakabayashi.
I'll never back down!
Incredible.
The goalkeeper
Genzo Wakabayashi
manages to stop the ball
despite being injured.
I'm counting on you,
Tsubasa!
Even though
he's injured,
Genzo kicks off the ball
to the midfield.
Soccer is played
with both feet,
and you only managed
to hurt one of them.
And the ball
goes directly to Tsubasa.
Genzo put his trust on me.
I won't let him down.
Don't let them gain ground.
-Tsubasa!
-Cover him already!
No matter how many players,
I'm confident you can
run past them.
I believe in you, Tsubasa.
You were able to outrun
my whole team
at one point...
Three players from Shimizu
won't even compare.
Nankatsu's number 10
easily out-dribbles
Shimizu.
Genzo...
I'm going to score the goal
I promised you.
I won't disappoint you.
Tsubasa, you promised me!
Score!
Tsubasa kicks a volley!
And there you have it.
Team Nankatsu
scores their first goal.
Yeah! Goal!
Justice
-was served.
-Well done!
-Tsubasa's effort,
-Great, Tsubasa!
-Genzo's and
-Good job, Tsubasa!
-everyone else's in Nankatsu
-I knew it, you can do it!
has finally reflected
in the scoreboard.
Thank you very much,
Tsubasa.
You did it.
I'll defend our advantage.
Huh?
I hate that guy.
-Shimizu will win it all!
-Shimizu will never fall!
-Go team! Go team!
-You're the one!
-Shimizu knows that
-they are done!
Team, let's go score
another one.
We won't let you guys
beat us.
Huh?
Teppei
Kisugi passes the ball
to his teammate.
Now, Nankatsu has
possession of the ball.
Tsubasa, here!
Taro Misaki
now makes a very smart pass
towards the penalty area.
What a goal!
Team Nankatsu is now
up by two goals to nothing.
After the first goal,
Team Nankatsu's been
revitalized.
Tsubasa's incredible.
Tell me, don't you think
he's fantastic?
Yeah.
I'm happy we came
all the way to Shizuoka
to see him.
MUSASHINO ELEMENTARY SCHOOL - TOKYO
Yeah, you can do it!
-Over here! Over here!
-Pass it, pass it!
Hey, let's move already!
Ugh, what a waste of time.
He isn't here.
Hey, Kojiro, tell me,
who did we come see
at this school?
I wanted to come see
two players...
just before we played
our next match.
One of them is
Genzo Wakabayashi,
from Nankatsu.
And the other player is...
Jun Misugi from Musashi FC,
a high profile player.
But neither of them is here
right now.
I don't know Jun Misugi.
You serious, Takeshi?
They call him
the Prince of the Pitch.
A very talented
young player.
You can do it!
And the ball
is in the clutches of
Nankatsu's goalkeeper,
Genzo Wakabayashi.
Despite his injury,
Genzo is risking
everything
to defend his goal.
Nankatsu
can taste victory
at the tip of
their tongue.
There's only one minute
on the clock.
Listen up, I want you
to give me another goal.
Tsubasa!
Genzo
passes the ball to Tsubasa,
the star striker
of Nankatsu.
Stop him.
Don't let him shoot.
I know where
I need to shoot.
Great goal!
Tsubasa gets a hat trick!
The referee signals
the end of the match.
Team Nankatsu is
the champion of Shizuoka!
Yeah, that's right!
The team
that is going to represent
our prefecture at
the national tournament
-will be
-I'm so happy right now!
-the Nankatsu squad.
-Me too.
Until now,
Tsubasa has made
three goals
in every single match.
He's a talent
we've never seen before.
Incredible.
You really are incredible.
Job well done, Tsubasa.
-Good job out there, guys!
-Great work, team!
What a pity, they beat us.
We couldn't defeat Tsubasa
or Genzo Wakabayashi.
They're better.
Yeah, tell us about it.
We couldn't compete
on their level.
They won fair and square.
It was a good match, guys.
Oh! Tsubasa!
Huh?
Go to the national
tournament...
and you win it for
all of us, you got that?
Thank you, Morimichi.
Yeah!
They really did it.
Everything ended well.
Yes.
-Hey, Tsubasa!
-Congratulations on--
-Congratulations on winning!
It's that brat again!
You were great!
I hope I see you at
the national tournament.
I got transferred too,
you know?
And now, I'm with
Team Musashi from Tokyo.
I hope I see you very soon.
Uh...
I think I know that player.
You know him, Coach?
Tell us who he is.
His name's Jun Misugi.
One of most talented
young players
in the league right now.
He's an exceptional player.
Jun Misugi...
You take care, Tsubasa.
Who the hell does
she think she is?
I guess I'll just
have to become
the team's representative.
-I'll be the manager.
-Huh?
That way,
I'll be able to go to
the national tournament
right next to
-my handsome Tsubasa.
-Ugh...
NATIONAL JUVENILE SOCCER TOURNAMENT SHIZUOKA REPRESENTATIVE NANKATSU SC CONGRATULATIONS!
And so,
the single elimination
tournament
to choose Shizuoka
prefecture's team concluded.
Leaving Nankatsu
as the centerpiece
of all the matches.
In the meantime,
the Wangan stadium,
where the national
tournament matches
will be held,
anxiously awaits
the arrival of
the new young players.
You did it, Tsubasa.
Yeah!
The next step is
the national tournament.
From now on, you'll have to
play seriously.
Yeah.
That's how it'll be.
I'll win
the national tournament,
and I'll go with Roberto
to Brazil
to be a professional player.
[ending theme]