You...
will all be buried with me.
This is the antidote for Ricin.
I'll give you a choice.
An assassin just broke in
and triggered the Bird Alarm Bell.
The assassin is now dead.
Stand down!
Wait!
Leave the assassin's body here
for His Majesty to verify his identity!
Xing?
Xing,
it's me.
Zhuge Yue...
[REBIRTH]
[Episode 26]
Pass on my order!
Everyone retreat outside the inner palace.
Any trespassers will be killed!
All guards!
His Majesty is unwell.
All guards are ordered to retreat
out of the inner palace courtyard!
No trespassing!
Yes!
Hurry up and check how she is.
No vital organs were hit.
She is just exhausted.
I will go get some medicine to save her.
Alright.
We can only force-feed her the medicine
for now.
If it works,
she will wake up in a couple of days.
You go rest first.
The poison in your body...
I am fine.
Xing!
Just lie down and don't move around.
Don't die
before General Chu actually dies.
I wouldn't know how to explain it to her
when she wakes up.
What is this?
If I'm not mistaken,
this is the antidote to Blood on Snow.
When I was looking for medicine
for General Chu,
I found it by accident.
This smell...
It's wolf vine?
Exactly. It's wolf vine from Ximeng.
It is highly toxic,
but it counteracts Blood on Snow.
So it can be used
to fight poison with poison,
and force Blood on Snow
out of your heart completely.
It's just that...
It's just that wolf vine is highly toxic.
It could be an antidote
or a deadly poison.
Not only that,
besides wolf vine,
there are other herbs in it
whose origin I don't know.
But given the toxicity of wolf vine,
you'll likely fall into a coma
for 7 days after taking it,
with a continuous fever
during the whole time.
If the fever subsides on its own,
you will wake up within 7 days.
If it doesn't...
If it doesn't, you can have my corpse
for your research.
I...
Well...
Really?
What about Xing?
How is she?
She's fine.
I checked her injuries.
There's nothing serious.
She is just exhausted.
She will wake up in a couple of days
after taking medicine.
I've already asked Meng En
to bring Minglu and Wang Shi'er
over here.
Minglu is looking after her now.
I'll go see her.
What about the medicine?
I'll take it after Xing wakes up.
Xing,
since you left Qingshan Manor,
we have had many misunderstandings
and almost been separated
by life and death.
I can't remember how long it has been
since I looked at you this closely.
I always thought
there was no danger in the world
that could not be resolved.
Now, being with you like this,
I am afraid.
I'm afraid I can't make it
until you wake up.
I'm afraid that this time,
death will truly separate us.
My Lord.
My Lord?
Miss Chu's breathing has been steady
these past few days.
She is out of danger.
My Lord, please drink this medicine first.
This smell...
It smells bad,
but it's my newly developed decoction.
It can temporarily suppress
the Blood on Snow in your body.
Rest assured, Young Master.
Miss Chu will certainly be fine.
Why did she pass out so quickly?
Did I use too much medicine?
You sneaky rat!
You don't even make a sound when you walk?
It's just a habit
I've developed from work.
Loud noises might wake the dead.
Well...
Lord Zhuge has had a fever for 3 days.
Aren't you afraid he won't wake up?
He will surely die without the medicine.
Taking it gives him a ray of hope.
I am a miracle doctor
with noble medical ethics,
almost like the reincarnation
of the divine physician Hua Tuo.
How could I leave him to die?
Right.
You are the reincarnation
of legendary doctors.
But just in case—
if he doesn't wake up,
how will you explain it to Lady Chu?
Then I can only hope
that either they both wake up,
or...
neither of them wakes up.
What are you muttering about?
Reaching the same end
by different means...
isn't a bad thing!
Bad news!
Something...
Something terrible happened to Miss Chu!
Miss Chu?
Miss Chu... Miss Chu...
Tell us!
She woke up!
She woke up?
How did it happen so fast?
You didn't tell her
about Young Master Zhuge, did you?
Lady Chu...
Xiao Ran.
Hurry up and check his pulse.
His pulse doesn't seem right.
Minglu,
fetch me a basin of colder water.
What are you waiting for?
♪ The dust in the world ♪
♪ Is blown away easily by the wind ♪
♪ Who can stay calm ♪
♪ And not be scared? ♪
♪ A slight ripple ♪
♪ Floating life hangs by a thread ♪
♪ The more pulled, the softer it gets ♪
♪ Who dares to say forever? ♪
♪ Let it be ♪
♪ Grudges and grace
were never meant to be ♪
♪ Why must you take and demand so much? ♪
♪ Go weaving ♪
♪ Grand and glorious excuses ♪
♪ We once beheld ♪
♪ A mirage on earth ♪
♪ Beauty never ♪
♪ Lasts for long ♪
♪ No matter how a jade is carved ♪
♪ It's just a stone ♪
♪ It will eventually disappear ♪
How is he?
It's been 7 days.
His pulse is chaotic, and the high fever
still hasn't gone down.
It should be caused
by the heat poison of Blood on Snow.
The heat poison is fierce.
If it can't be released,
it will coagulate inside his body.
Then it will be even harder for him
to wake up.
Is there any way?
The fastest way to cool him down
is to soak his whole body in ice water.
Miss Chu,
everything is ready.
Tell them to leave.
Yes.
♪ On the water ♪
♪ Countless ♪
♪ Ripples rise ♪
♪ Through the mortal world ♪
♪ With meetings and goodbyes ♪
♪ How unfair fate is ♪
♪ It gave all the memories back to you ♪
♪ Yet left me ♪
♪ Stuck right here ♪
Xing,
you are...
♪ Rain falls down ♪
an invincible... general.
♪ Lingering thoughts ♪
♪ Awake once more ♪
You can definitely...
♪ Let the wind shape ♪
♪ Another me ♪
take me away.
I know you are still alive,
♪ How can I escape ♪
and I know it was you
who sent the Huotu water.
♪ All the reflections that hold you? ♪
Zhuge Yue,
you've been alive all along.
♪ Behind the illusions
of the moon in water ♪
Why have you been hiding from me?
♪ I wait to sink deep ♪
Since you chose this path yourself,
♪ May fortune smile on all below ♪
even if it leads through
a mountain of corpses and a sea of blood,
you will walk it alone.
But if one day,
♪ Just to hear when you'll come home ♪
you find you can no longer
take a step forward,
you know the way...
♪ Braving schemes alone ♪
♪ Treading through thorns ♪
back to Qingshan Manor.
♪ Searching for your name ♪
♪ Till storms rise again ♪
You've always been protecting me.
♪ Not a single regret remains ♪
Now,
it's my turn to protect you.
♪ Melt the ice ♪
♪ That fate has wrought ♪
Zhuge Yue,
you told me
♪ Let the night ♪
that if one day I regret it,
you would be right behind me,
waiting for me to return.
You can't die.
♪ Forever glow ♪
You must always be here.
I promise you.
I want you to stay by my side forever too.
To the ends of the earth,
we live and die together.
♪ May fortune smile on all below ♪
♪ Just to hear when you'll come home ♪
♪ Braving schemes alone ♪
♪ Treading through thorns ♪
♪ Searching for your name ♪
♪ Till storms rise again ♪
They're the Sun-Moon Twin Swords.
♪ Not a single regret remains ♪
They represent
that we will be together forever.
♪ Melt the ice ♪
♪ That fate has wrought ♪
♪ Let the night ♪
♪ Forever glow ♪
[Capital of Great Yan]
Keep going.
We are almost home.
Keep going. Be good.
Let's go.
Helian, are you alright?
Take me to see His Majesty.
General Cheng, thank you
for sending people to search for me
during the turbulent times in Great Yan.
This is His Majesty's order.
I was just following it.
Thanks for your trouble, General Cheng.
Your Majesty!
What is it?
Your Majesty,
Consort Helian has returned.
I see.
I'm glad she's back safely.
Tell her to go back and rest.
You may leave too.
Yes.
Your Majesty!
Your Highness!
No need to pay respects.
I'm glad you're back safely.
I rushed back to the Capital of Great Yan
day and night
because I have something to report to you.
Sister Huan!
Sister Huan, there's a letter for you!
There's a letter for you!
Sister Huan. Sister Huan.
There's a letter for you.
Thank you.
Buy yourself some fruits.
I want it too! I want it too!
Go on. Buy yourselves some fruits.
Let's go buy some fruits.
Okay, let's go!
Let's go!
Take care.
As a token of gratitude
for the donkey.
[I will repay your kindness
for lending me the donkey.]
It's you?
Jing,
take the troops away.
Don't disturb the villagers.
Yes!
Your Majesty, please rest early.
We will camp here tonight.
Yes.
Do you remember it?
This is Mountain Snow.
This...
is Mountain Snow?
This was my father's favorite horse.
Once, I secretly rode it out.
It got spooked,
broke off its reins, and ran away.
Afraid of my father's punishment,
I didn't dare to return to the palace.
It was you
who looked for it with me
all night in Mount Hei.
We found it by the Li River in the end.
What exactly are you trying to say?
You once told me
that making mistakes doesn't matter.
As long as you make amends in time,
it's never too late.
Huan Huan,
I lost Great Yan.
Can you help me get it back?
You must have already known the reason
I invited you elders here today.
You'll be deciding
where the future of Great Yan lies.
We will follow the old rules.
Each of you has an eagle feather arrow.
Putting it in the upper censer
means you agree
that the 13 tribes
will secede from Great Yan,
govern themselves, and form an alliance.
Otherwise,
it means you veto it.
Except for the Yan family,
the elders of the 12 tribes are all here.
Please,
after careful consideration,
cast your vote.
This horse is not Mountain Snow at all.
Four years ago, I rode it on a hunt.
To protect me,
it was killed by ferocious wildcats.
What are you trying to say?
Even the horses in Great Yan
know how to repay a favor.
I won't give you a chance
to kill me again.
Elders, what are your decisions?
Great Yan is already beset
by internal and external troubles.
The new King of Great Yan
is not up to the task.
If you cannot see the stakes here,
you can only wait for your doom.
Is the Snowy Region Tribe still
going to sit back and do nothing?
Boy,
do you remember how your sister
was killed?
Our Snowy Region Tribe
made an alliance with the Yan family
to protect Great Yan forever,
and protect the King of Great Yan.
I cannot break my father's promise.
What your father
promised the old King of Great Yan
was to protect Great Yan,
not Yan Xun's family!
Only by making the right choice
for your tribe
are you truly
keeping your father's promise!
An Luo.
General Huan?
General Huan is not dead?
Sister?
General Huan?
Sister!
I thought you...
Your Majesty?
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty.
Well done.
You are the pride
of our Snowy Region Tribe.
General Huan.
You have been away from Great Yan
for a long time.
You have no idea
what Great Yan has gone through
during this time.
I'm afraid you can't vote
on behalf of the Snowy Region Tribe now.
Besides,
don't you think you should tell us
where you have been these days
and what happened?
Elder Huo Sang.
Back then,
Great Yan had just opened up trade.
A Great Yong supply caravan
was plundered in the Baichuan Tribe.
The Emperor of Great Yong was furious
and sent troops to demand an explanation.
If it wasn't the old King of Great Yan
who mediated the matter...
As someone who experienced it back then,
Elder Huo Sang,
you must still remember it vividly.
Elder Pale.
Do you know how,
during those extremely cold years,
when you were forced to migrate south
with no food or clothing,
you eventually found
this fertile land?
Oh, right.
Elder Tubu.
Do you still remember
who overcame all objections
to dig a canal
from the other side of Mount Huihui
to bring fresh water
to the Hongchuan Tribe?
Everything you mentioned
was done by the old King of Great Yan.
The old King of Great Yan
was indeed kind to us,
but we have also served him loyally
all our lives.
Now Great Yan is torn apart
and can't withstand any more storms.
Are you
asking us, for this so-called loyalty,
to completely ignore
the fate of Great Yan?
Now, surrounded by tigers and wolves,
the winter of Great Yan is approaching.
If the 13 tribes fall apart,
Great Yan will no longer exist!
This arrow
was made by my father
with his own hands back then.
I've been keeping it with me
all these years
and never let it leave my side.
My previous actions
have failed Great Yan
and failed my father.
But I believe,
if he were here today,
he wouldn't want to see Great Yan
fall apart.
So I'm casting this vote
for my father.
Huan Huan,
the winter of Great Yan is approaching.
The 13 tribes will survive
if we stay together.
If we fall apart,
Great Yan will no longer exist.
I once thought
the Snowy Region Tribe and Great Yan
would share the same fate.
I am your subject and relative,
and I should be loyal to you.
But after facing death once,
I understand now.
I won't be blindly loyal to you anymore.
I will return to Great Yan.
That is my home.
However,
I want 5,000 Black Eagle Army soldiers.
They must be under my command completely.
In today's Ximeng,
all people are equal!
Long live the King!
Long live the Queen!
I am no longer a noble young master
of the Zhuge family.
I can only cling to you and marry into
the Chu family as your matrilocal husband.
By order of His Majesty!
The Seventh Prince
mobilized troops without permission.
He is suspected
of colluding with the enemy to rebel.
The Painting of the Subjugated Queen!
Today,
I will trample on
Yan Xun's dignity.