Ji.
I can see now. I can see now.
Ji Ling.
Changsheng. Have you seen Ji Ling?
BRING HEALTH…
GATHER THE ESSENCE OF THE UNIVERSE
TO SHIELD ALL MAGICAL HARM
"A dragon scale
banishes all curses
and misfortunes…"
"…shields the spirit,
and restores life from death.
However, it settles only upon
the one it deems worthy."
Wu.
To kill Jiu Ying, you must die.
But the dragon scale
can bring you back to life.
However, not everyone can bear its power.
But you've been through
countless rewinds with Lonescale's power,
creating a tie with the dragon scale.
Maybe that's what it means
to be the fated one.
Your heart was once occupied
by Jiu Ying's spirit fragment.
From now on,
let my dragon scale reside in your heart
and stay with you forever.
Don't be sad.
Don't cry.
I'll always be with you.
Whatever you want, I'll bring it to you.
You'll offer your heart if I want it?
Yes.
You like Ji Ling. I like him, too.
I've always liked my past self.
So even if there is no future,
there's nothing to regret.
But you are different.
You hate your past.
You never enjoyed a moment of happiness.
So, Wu,
you deserve
a bright future more than I do.
Ji.
He's dead.
Finally, he's free.
I have to go now.
Who are you?
I told you.
I am you.
You are me.
We are Yuan Wuhuo's
unfortunate obsessions.
I've always wanted to be
your older brother and protect you.
But many times,
I thought
you were supposed to be
a carefree little fox.
I hoped you could be freed from
the shackles of the Dragon Deity's throne.
I got you trapped here.
What gives me the right
to be your brother?
I haven't achieved
anything I wanted
to achieve in my life.
Before Yuan Wuhuo died,
he had only two obsessions.
One was to protect his brother forever.
The other was to free
Ji Ling from the lies.
The good and evil twin
six-eyed butterfly demons
devoured Yuan Wuhuo's physical form
and absorbed his two obsessions.
Two completely different beings
of good and evil split apart.
That is, you and me.
Li Jie and the butterfly demon Yuan Wuhuo.
I tried everything to kill him
and free him from his endless pain.
You tried your best
to protect the Dragon Deity.
We are nothing
but the obsessions of a dying man.
No.
I may have come to Ji Ling
because of the obsession.
But all these years,
I've witnessed his glory, pain,
mercy, and loneliness.
All this has nothing to do
with you or the obsession.
I did my best to serve the Shilin Sect
out of my own will.
Very good.
But the person
you want to protect has died.
Now, who are you going to live for?
Figure out the answer yourself.
My obsession has already been fulfilled.
He's dead.
He's free.
Now I have to go.
The person I want to protect
is waiting for me across the river.
Father. Mother.
-Father. Mother.
-Brother.
-You're back.
-I missed you.
Xizai, you've grown so tall.
Brother. Have some. It's still warm.
Give Xizai one.
Come on.
-I've eaten.
-What?
Mother's dumplings. Try it.
You've lost weight. Try it.
Come on. Eat more.
Gain some weight. Be like me.
Look at me.
So this is the Formless Moon.
What celestial air.
Breathe it in,
and I'll live 500 more years.
But why does it feel so cold?
Traitor to the Formless Moon.
How dare you bring someone here?
-Why are you here?
-To destroy the Oracle Stone.
Destroy the Oracle Stone?
Wu Wangyan. Are you crazy?
The Sacred Spring doesn't lie.
Memories don't lie.
I came back to tell you the entire truth.
Jiu Ying's spirit fragment
has been hiding in the Oracle Stone.
Jiu Ying has integrated his spirit
with the Oracle Stone.
The stone's power is everlasting,
which sustains Jiu Ying's spirit.
To kill Jiu Ying,
we must destroy the Oracle Stone.
THE OLD DRAGON FALLS
THE NEW DRAGON RISES
HEAVEN AND EARTH TREMBLE
CHAOS FILLS THE WORLD
AN OLD SOUL RETURNS AGAINST TIME
A NEW MOON RESHAPES THE WORLD
This is the new prophecy.
"The old dragon falls.
The new dragon rises.
Heaven and earth tremble.
Chaos fills the world.
An old soul returns against time.
A new moon reshapes the world."
But nobody knows what it means.
What's wrong?
We're finally destroying this stone.
Isn't that a good thing?
Why do you guys look unhappy?
-It's nothing.
More and more like a married couple.
Finally,
Jiu Ying is taken down.
Master Dragon Deity would be happy, right?
For so many years,
he's been absorbing the dark power
from those possessed
by Jiu Ying's spirit fragments
to shoulder the pain for those people.
I want to see my grandson again.
Despicable Dragon Deity.
So what if you wipe me out?
I am Jiu Ying.
I am immortal.
Too bad he won't be able to see this.
These fancy garments
have always been the worst curse.
People burdened with longing
carry an empty tomb in their hearts.
Inside the tomb,
no bones, just the clothes.
This is life…
You silly fox.
Didn't you spend a lifetime
wearing someone else's garments?
Some people are destined
to be like two mountains,
gazing across vast grasslands,
across canyons,
across a distance
that can never be closed,
watching over each other.
What are they waiting for?
They're waiting for the snow.
All it takes is a snow
for them to be both crowned in white,
as if they had grown old together.
Hey.
We've grown old together.
Thank you, Master.
Bless us, Master Dragon Deity.
I didn't expect that the story
started here and ended here too.
I wanted to kill the dragon.
But now,
I've become the dragon.
Master Dragon Deity.
Thank you for blessing me.
These are all for you.
Now you're obligated.
It seems that you have
to protect the commoners
for the rest of your life.
Thank you, Master Dragon Deity.
Do you think he is the Dragon Deity?
Look.
Even the demon hunter commander
is standing behind him.
He must be the Dragon Deity.
He will bless everyone.
-Yeah.
-Right.
Thank you, Master Dragon Deity.
Humans are better than demons in one way.
When a human dies,
people set a tombstone
and honor their memory.
But when a demon dies,
they are gone without a trace.
If…
I mean,
if I can have a tombstone after I die,
I would wish for the name on my tombstone
to change my surname from "Ji"
meaning a vessel,
to a common family surname "Ji".
I want to be remembered.
I want to be mourned.
I don't want to be
nothing more than a spirit vessel.
Rest assured.
I'll protect you.
I won't let you die.
Master Ji Ling sacrificed himself.
We shall inherit his legacy
and guard the world.
Master Ji Ling.
I'll always remember
the day you helped Luo'an City
dispel the Fox-Allure Spell.
The sky looked amazing.
Master Ji Ling.
Are you free now?
I'm happy for you.
-Master Ji Ling.
To me, you will always
be the Dragon Deity.
Ji Ling.
You will never be forgotten.
Every time I came to this room,
I took a new puppet.
We only had to put
this heart stone in its chest
to get a brand new Ji Ling.
Again and again.
I should already be used
to your death by now.
But now,
you're gone for real.
You said you wanted a tombstone.
So, I'll bury this heart stone with you
and make you a tombstone
engraved with Ji Ling's name.
"Spirit Memorial."
Dragon Deity's Power.
Master Chi Wen.
This is the last strand
of Dragon Deity's Power I left behind.
This heart stone contains
all the memories of Ji Ling.
I'll take it to the Dragon Abyss,
bathe it in the Sun and Moon
to absorb the universe's essence.
Maybe after thousands of years,
this heart stone can form
a shape through cultivation.
Thousands of years?
I can't wait that long.
From now on, there are dragons once more.
Jiu Ying has fallen.
The mortal world regained peace.
To the former Dragon Deity,
my brother, Chi Wen.
The former Dragon Deity was Ji Ling.
Don't blame him.
How could I blame him?
Without Ji Ling, there would be no peace.
Ji Ling.
You are the real Dragon Deity
to the people.
Let's drink to the former Dragon Deity,
Ji Ling.
To Master Bai Ze.
To Si Feng.
To all those who died to save the world.
And to the hardships we shared
and to Wu Shiguang for becoming a dragon.
And to…
To… To our precious friendship.
You sure know how to cozy up
to people, you little weasel.
Hold on tight to the Shilin Sect token,
or you'll be shattered.
Wuyi.
Wu Shiguang, Li Jie, and the others
are drinking and celebrating
under the golden-scale wood.
Celebrating?
What I mean is,
it's not just about celebrating
the death of Jiu Ying.
On top of that,
more importantly,
they are commemorating Ji Ling.
The golden-scale wood
is full of ribbons for Ji Ling
from demon hunters and common people.
Don't you want to check it out?
No.
Wuyi.
I thought I gave you my heart.
But your true heart
was Jiu Ying's spirit fragment.
The last head of Jiu Ying was destroyed.
And all the fragments faded away.
You would have died.
But Ji Ling kept you alive
with his dragon scale.
He surely wishes for you
to live on, happy and well.
I don't know what else I can do for you.
But are you going to stay here forever?
If Ji Ling could see you right now,
he would never want you to be like this.
Come back to the Formless Moon with me.
I'll keep you company.
Wangyan.
Disturbing, huh?
Painful, huh?
Jiu Ying.
You're still alive.
As long as you're alive, I'll survive.
What I put in your heart
wasn't just my spirit fragment.
There's also the Oracle Stone.
I wasted half of my sacred power
to cut out a small piece
of the indestructible Oracle Stone.
As long as the stone endures,
I shall not die.
Guess why I wrapped Wu Wangyan's heart
around my spirit fragment I left in you.
Because it's my biggest secret.
This secret must remain
undetectable to anyone.
Now Ji Ling is dead.
Wu Shiguang has become
the new Dragon Deity.
No one in this world
will remember and honor Ji Ling
except for you.
And this longing
will be your eternal shackles,
torturing you forever.
Why don't we set you free now?
Hand over your physical form.
Let your heart fly to the one
you love and stay with him.
Come with me.
He's not gone.
He's in my heart,
keeping me company all along.
You can wear human skin to look like him.
But you'll never have his loving eyes.
He loves me and the people.
So,
I won't let you ruin
the world he has been guarding.
We need to talk.
Wait for me to come back.
What's wrong with you?
You're too busy to even
talk to your brother?
What are you talking about?
You're the Dragon Deity now.
Everyone listens to you.
What about me? What do I do?
-What do you mean?
-You dog…
When you're riding high,
don't ditch your pack.
You won't even let me stay
in the Cosmic Pouch.
I have nowhere to go here
with terrifying formations everywhere.
What am I doing here?
We ran into danger
several times out there.
Have you forgotten?
It's for your own good.
You're not a weasel.
You're an ungrateful brat.
I'm not afraid of danger. I'm afraid of…
Enough. You're obviously still drunk.
We'll talk later.
What's wrong?
The last Dragon Deity's Power from Chi Wen
took Ji Ling's heart stone
to the Dragon Abyss.
He said that the heart stone
contains all the memories of Ji Ling.
Maybe thousands of years later,
it can cultivate into human form.
That's great.
Humans are mortal.
I can't wait that long.
But you can.
If you see him,
tell him
that I've figured out who I am.
Look. So sparkling.
Doesn't it look like our former home?
I remember that I liked
waiting for you by the water
in the illusion.
This time,
let me wait for you by the water.
I'll be back in just a few days.
That's long enough.
This is…
I added my dragon scale to it.
Impressive craftsmanship.
You once said
that two people
are like two rivers.
They converge
and change each other's course.
But it seems our fates
are headed in directions
that will never let us
grow old together like normal people.
It's fine, as long
as I can stay with you forever.
Wangyan.
Marry me.
Sisters.
We carried out many tasks
assigned by Jiu Ying,
causing a lot of tragedy
beyond redemption.
Wangyan. Let's go.
I want to give it my all
to redeem the errors I once made.
But it's just my choice.
You've dedicated everything
to the Formless Moon.
It's time to start your own lives
and pursue true freedom.
But I don't know what I want, either.
I think I'm used to this lifestyle.
I'm used to carrying out missions.
Instead of searching aimlessly,
why don't we make amends with you?
That's right.
We are sisters
who share honor and disgrace.
We should stand by each other.
Wangyan.
Formless Moon, submit to me.