[Fated Hearts]
[Episode 6]
Xueying.
It's okay.
-You're back.
-You're finally back.
Will you dare to run off like that again?
So disobedient.
Yixiao.
-Master!
Master.
You're finally back.
Her Ladyship has been worried sick.
How are you?
You're not hurt, are you?
Master.
What are you crying for?
I'm perfectly fine, aren't I?
It's not like I died or anything.
Stop crying.
Did you practice today?
Yes.
Then let me see
if you've made any progress.
Since these kids
arrived,
the mansion has never been this lively.
His Highness's never liked crowds.
I wonder why
he didn't lose his temper this time.
Indeed.
Alright, that's enough.
You left and never came back.
They've been crying the whole time,
saying they'll never be naughty
or make you angry again.
Alright, Eleven,
take them back to rest.
Get some water
and wash their faces and bodies properly.
Go back now.
If you dare run off again,
you'll be punished.
Got it.
Let's go back and wash up, shall we?
Let's go, Shunzi.
Bath time.
Bath time, Nine.
Let's go.
Who exactly kidnapped Fang?
Some people from Jinxiu.
Do you know them?
They claimed to be my comrades.
What kind of person
would treat their own comrades like this?
From what I see,
there aren't many decent ones
among you Jinxiu people either.
Yixiao,
you must be careful.
I originally thought
Feng Suige was
a cold-blooded killer,
but now I see
that people from Jinxiu
can't be trusted either.
You're now deep in the heart of danger,
with nowhere to turn.
It's just about
surviving in desperate situations
and seeking victory in danger.
I'm just worried about the kids.
Don't worry.
There must be a solution.
[Murong Residence] [Tea House] [Market]
Your Highness.
Those Jinxiu undercover guards
who fell into the river have been found.
None of them survived.
But most importantly,
their faces are completely disfigured,
unrecognizable from
what they once were.
Should I have the coroner's artist
try to reconstruct them,
see if we can restore their appearance?
No need to probe further,
nor concern yourself
with their real identities.
As long as they're from Jinxiu.
Hang their bodies from the city gate.
At dawn, when the gates open,
I'll let everyone know
that Jinxiu sent assassins against me.
Understood.
But about that shipment of oil...
Any news?
No.
The person in charge of oil
at the Armaments Bureau has gone missing.
Seems they've been silenced.
Indeed.
I've been thinking about that too.
Are you saying
someone actually coordinated with Jinxiu
to take your life?
Even Prime Minister Zhuang
wouldn't dare
be so blatant.
This is happening right here
in Yujing City,
under the Emperor's nose.
So...
Should I continue investigating?
No need.
This lead is already dead.
Your Majesty, Her Highness is here.
I pay my respects to you, Mother.
I heard you couldn't sleep last night,
so I had some calming tea prepared
and found some century-old ginseng
from Mount Ling,
hoping it will help you
sleep better, Mother.
Among all these children,
you're the sweetest.
All the care I've given you
hasn't been in vain.
Xiyang,
do you know why
I summoned you here today?
You all may leave.
Yes.
I'm guessing,
Mother, you summoned me here
for the matter of the marriage alliance.
You're always so clever,
just as I like.
That clever mind of yours
really seems to take after me.
You're just like my own daughter.
You've always
treated me as your own.
I remember when we kids were little,
Chengyang would always complain
that you were biased in my favor.
You've grown up now
and reached the age for marriage,
yet I'm so reluctant to let you go.
I know you care for me.
About this marriage alliance,
since you already know,
I'd like to hear
your thoughts on it.
Don't worry,
if you're unwilling,
no one can force you.
But will Father agree?
I'll decide for you.
Even if your father gets angry,
he can only
blame me.
I'd rather face his anger
than let you suffer.
Mother, you've taught me since childhood
that as a princess of Susha,
I must contribute to our kingdom,
and I've always remembered that.
Now
is the time for me
to serve Susha.
So you mean...
I'm willing to go through with
the marriage alliance.
You've truly grown up now.
Even when it comes to important matters
like marriage,
you have your own thoughts.
It really puts my mind at ease.
Why did you mysteriously call me out
so early in the morning?
What's going on?
I'm not planning to
stay at Feng Suige's residence any longer.
I can't eat or sleep well there.
I'm planning to purchase
a house in Yujing.
Didn't we agree
that you'd take the three kids
back to Zhengnian Villa?
Those three kids
have their hearts set on you.
We may have fooled them once,
but can we fool them a second time?
Besides,
leaving Susha might not be safe either.
I've thought it all through.
Once you've finished your business,
we can leave together.
I'll handle my own affairs
by myself.
Don't worry.
Actually, all these matters
have nothing to do with you.
You don't have to stay in Yujing.
That won't do.
You're someone I rescued,
which makes you one of our own.
Of course I need to protect you.
Why are you so nice to me?
Because you saved me.
We share a life-and-death bond.
I'm an only child,
and I've always envied
others who have sisters.
Eleven is like a little sister to me.
I've always wished
I can have an older sister.
Why don't you be my older sister?
How about we become sworn sisters?
What do you think?
Would you like that?
Would you?
Alright,
I'll do as you say.
Then it's settled.
From now on, we'll share our blessings
and face hardships together.
You're my older sister now.
Sister.
Call me too. Come on.
From now on, I'll have an older sister!
[Real Estate Agency]
Here we are.
I want the best house you have.
-Honored guests, lease come in.
-I'm buying it today.
So you're the young mistress
of Zhengnian Villa.
The house has been tidied up.
This way, please.
I'll need to sign
and put it on the account.
Is that really doable?
Of course.
You're our most honored guest.
Money is negotiable
I'm putting it on your emperor,
Feng Pingcheng's account, though.
No problem. No problem.
How do you two feel about
this house? Are you satisfied?
I'm quite satisfied.
Thank you for your trouble.
Then I shall take my leave
and not disturb you further.
Charging it to Feng Pingcheng's account?
You're really something.
That's actually doing Feng Pingcheng
a favor, alright?
Whether it's Emperor of Jinxiu
or Feng Pingcheng,
they both want to earn favors
with my Zhengnian Villa.
Now that I've brought it to him myself,
Feng Pingcheng will certainly accept.
By the way,
Sister,
once I bring Fang here,
this place will be
our home in Yujing City.
We have a home now!
Come take a look.
This will serve as a clinic,
specifically for treating patients.
And this area will be the pharmacy.
Sister, there's also a garden in the back.
I'll go take a look.
We have a home now,
a place to call our own here.
Now, I can leave
Feng Suige's residence whenever I want.
But
why don't I feel happy about it?
Grandfather.
I've been
diligently practicing
my calligraphy lately.
Please take a look.
[A good man has built a hut in the valley
by the stream, so much at his ease.]
[Alone he sleeps and speaks when awake,
and will surely not forget.]
Have I made progress?
[A good man has built a hut at the bend
of the mound, an air of indifference.]
[Alone he sleeps and sings when awake,
and will never pass from the spot.]
[A good man has built a hut
on the level height, so self-collected.]
[Alone he sleeps, wakes and sleeps again,
and swears he will never tell.]
Have you shown it to your father?
Not yet.
I was thinking
of getting your guidance first,
Grandfather.
After I make improvements,
I'll show it to my father.
Have you forgotten what I taught you?
You said before
that all of my writings
must be reviewed by my father first.
You must always keep in mind the proper
principles between ruler and subject.
You are a prince of Susha.
Apart from your tutors,
only your father
has the right to evaluate your work.
Yes.
Grandfather,
I'm going to study now.
I take my leave.
Your handwriting is gentle and dignified,
but lacks decisiveness and sharpness.
Your father
won't like it.
Thank you, Grandfather,
I shall take my leave.
Father.
Empress.
You must be feeling more at ease
now that you've talked to Xiyang, right?
Indeed.
You're truly prescient, Father.
But how did you know
that Xiyang would certainly agree?
Compared to Feng Suige,
Chengyang's character
is truly too gentle.
He's not suited to be a ruler.
But whether he is or isn't
doesn't really matter.
The one who will inherit the throne
can only be Chengyang.
Chengyang's future
depends entirely on you, Father.
It's the future of the entire Zhuang clan.
By the way,
I heard that early this morning,
Feng Suige hung the bodies of
a few undercover guards from Jinxiu
at the city gate,
claiming he was assassinated.
Do you think he'll
ruin our plans?
Since you already know
the princess's thoughts,
why should you worry?
Father, you mean that
no matter how Feng Suige
interferes,
His Majesty's final decision
will depend on
whether she's willing to go through with
the marriage alliance or not?
If she's not willing,
once she marries into Jinxiu,
she will
become a hidden threat.
His Majesty surely understands this.
[I, Fang Chengyu, Governor of Yuzhou,
kneel to submit this memorial]
[Memorial]
What did you just say
you came here for today?
I ask you to uphold justice
for me, Father.
You've never
asked me to intervene
in anything since childhood.
Today's matter is different.
I encountered
an assassination attempt
by Jinxiu's undercover guards
and nearly lost my life.
However, as it concerns Jinxiu
and political affairs
between the two kingdoms,
I dare not make decisions on my own.
You hung those bodies at the city gate.
You seem quite decisive to me.
It doesn't seem that
you dare not make decisions on your own.
Please understand, Father.
It's only because the assassins' bodies
were disfigured
that I ordered them hung at the gate,
only to
help Jinxiu identify them
and retrieve them promptly.
How thoughtful of you.
This is what I should do.
Since it was Jinxiu
who proposed the marriage alliance,
though they speak sweetly but harbor evil,
seeking peace on the surface
while attacking in secret,
I must still consider the dignity
of our kingdom
and everyone's reputation,
and cannot openly
tear our relations apart.
Fortunately, I was lucky
to survive this time.
Even if Jinxiu
continues to
send assassins after me,
as the First Prince of Susha,
I must prioritize the bigger picture
and practice restraint.
All decisions
are yours to make, Father.
If the assassins' faces
are unrecognizable,
how can you be certain
that they were from Jinxiu?
Support Admin Watch on
dramacool.club or kissasia.be
Translate by =Qari= @Team Vik
I have a witness.
You haven't told me
how I should repay this favor.
It's simple.
You just need to tell the truth.
I need you to testify
that those people
are Jinxiu's undercover guards.
That's it?
Is it really that simple?
Actually, it's not that simple.
You need to consider that
agreeing to help me
is equivalent to
betraying your former comrades.
Otherwise, I'll kill him!
They wanted to kill Fang.
What kind of comrades are they?
I'll help you.
This is my witness's testimony,
sufficient to prove
the identity of those assassins.
Your witness
is that woman named Fu Yixiao,
a female general from Jinxiu, right?
She has lost her memory
and her background is unknown.
Using her as a witness
won't convince anyone.
Then I request Your Majesty
to reject Jinxiu's
marriage alliance proposal.
This way, I can openly
investigate the assassins' identities
and offer you evidence
that will convince everyone, Father.
It's too late.
Xia Jingshi
will soon arrive in Yujing.
I've already sent a reply to Jinxiu.
The marriage alliance
between the two kingdoms
has been decided.
Please, Father,
revoke that order.
A ruler's word cannot be taken back.
How can I revoke it?
Whether to marry or not
is just a matter of your word, Father.
This matter is settled.
There's nothing more to discuss.
If that's the case,
then I
have one more unreasonable request!
Since Jinxiu wants me dead,
and since you, Father,
don't care whether I live or die,
then I beg you to issue the order
that on the day Xia Jingshi
marries Xiyang,
grant me death.
Consider it as adding some excitement
to this marriage alliance!
You think
I don't have the heart to kill you?
Of course you do!
For the sake of
peace and self-preservation,
you even have the heart
to send your only daughter
into hell!
Of course you have no remorse
about losing another son!
If this marriage alliance
is to go through,
it'll only be over my dead body.
Please forgive me, Father.
I heard everything from outside
and didn't have the time
to request an audience properly.
Xiyang?
Xiyang.
Now that you're here,
tell him yourself.
Brother.
I'm willing to accept
the marriage alliance.
Have you lost your mind?
Brother.
-Xiyang.
-I've always wanted to tell you that...
You don't have to compromise
and agree to this marriage alliance.
I was about to win just now.
I've been deliberately
pressing the issue of the Jinxiu assassin,
making sure all of
Yujing knows about it,
just to force Father
to turn against Jinxiu.
I provoked Father to sentence me to death
to make him understand that
If he insists on this marriage alliance,
I, Feng Suige, will fight
to the death to prevent it.
I know you can't
see the situation clearly now,
but you only need to know that
no one can force you
to marry Xia Jingshi.
Not even Father.
Father has now
painted himself into a corner.
Be a little more patient,
I will continue to find ways
to pressure Father.
Today, I'll definitely
force him to revoke his order.
Brother.
Why have you never asked me
whether I'm willing to marry Xia Jingshi?
What did you say?
Father sent someone
to ask about my wishes,
and so did Mother.
I've been waiting
for you to ask me.
What do you want me to ask you?
Ask me
if I'm willing
to marry Xia Jingshi.
Fine.
I'm asking you.
What is your wish?
Actually, I...
Feng Xiyang!
You'd better think carefully
before you answer me.
I'm willing to marry Xia Jingshi.
Why?
I like him.
You've met him?
A chance encounter,
just once.
He probably doesn't even remember me.
You've only met him once,
and you dare say you like him?
Brother,
when you meet the right person,
once is enough.
You're aware that he is my enemy.
You've only met him once,
but I'm your brother,
Feng Xiyang!
We are flesh and blood.
Brother!
Please grant my wish.
I will not grant it.
Brother.
What have I done wrong?
I just want to marry the man I admire,
and this marriage alliance
will bring peace.
What wrong have I done?
Because Xia Jingshi
will always be Susha's enemy!
No one knows him better than I do.
I know his hypocrisy,
his pretense,
and his forbearance.
Xia Jingshi's hands
are stained with the blood of
our Susha warriors,
and my sword is also soaked with
the blood of his Jinxiu soldiers!
Between me and Xia Jingshi,
there can never be peace!
Do you understand?
That's because
he hasn't met me before.
Brother.
Trust me,
I will change Xia Jingshi.
Why are you so naive?
Would you dare say
that you would never fall in love with
a woman from an enemy kingdom?
Never.
I, Feng Suige, absolutely would not.
Do you dare to swear
that if you fall in love
with a woman from an enemy kingdom,
you'll be struck by lightning?
I, Feng Suige, swear to heaven,
if I fall in love with a female general
from an enemy kingdom, I...
Brother!
Brother, I was wrong.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have forced you to swear.
If someone must be struck by lightning,
it should be me who bears it.
I was wrong.
It was my fault.
Since you truly wish to marry him,
I shouldn't stand in your way.
I'll support your decision.
[Wutong Mansion]
Stop them!
My Lady.
Miss Ling.
Are you going to leave just like that?
I'm not a prisoner in your mansion.
You've repeatedly tried to
stop me from leaving.
Who gave you such audacity?
Right.
You're from Zhengnian Villa,
and you're free to come and go
as you please.
But this child Fang
was rescued by His Highness.
Without His Highness's permission,
there's no way I could let him go.
If your prince wants to
hold someone accountable,
tell him to come find me.
This is the First Prince's Residence!
Not a place where you can come
and go as you please.
I say we can leave, so we will.
But...
♪ The rain drifts endlessly ♪
♪ The old dream burns the heart ♪
♪ Dreams sink into ruin ♪
♪ Missing the warmth of your palm ♪
[Wutong Mansion]
Your Highness.
They insist on moving out.
♪ Awaiting dusk ♪
♪ Shadows take root in the mountain pass ♪
♪ In just a moment, tears stained ♪
♪ Amid the bustling sound
of wind and rain ♪
♪ Who laughs at me,
heart cold as the desert ♪
♪ Dreams turn through a lifetime ♪
You're leaving?
♪ Who sighs for me, enduring separations ♪
Yes.
♪ Love is a trial, harsh and cold ♪
♪ Who crushes the lingering pain for me? ♪
♪ Clouds vanish, rain ceases, seek me ♪
Okay.
Let's go.
Get in.
♪ The world is vast and far ♪
[Wutong Mansion]
Come on.
♪ Time is unbearable to endure ♪
Get in.
♪ Lost in the wilderness ♪
Sister, get in the carriage.
♪ I've been looking for you ♪
You go ahead.
I'll come find you later.
[Wutong Mansion]
♪ Even if devastation fills my eyes ♪
♪ The shadows continue to sway ♪
♪ The phoenix going against light ♪
♪ Has been looking for a thousand miles ♪
♪ As years pass, dust stirs,
stirring deep longing ♪
♪ All I ask is to be together  forever ♪
♪ In the dark night, I look back ♪
♪ Amid despair ♪
♪ A grain of incense, a tear,
an inch of ash ♪
♪ Gathered and parted, all for you ♪
That area is a forbidden place
in the residence.
No one can enter except His Highness.
♪ You and I silently recite ♪
Haven't you noticed something's off
with His Highness today?
♪ This love will never perish ♪
I-Is there?
Isn't there?
♪ I search for you, yet cannot find you ♪
Even if I told you,
you wouldn't understand.
Just pretend you didn't see me.
Mother.
If your spirit is watching from heaven,
[In Memory of Late Mother Qingyu]
please don't blame Xiyang
for being disobedient.
This is all my fault.
Ever since we were little,
I've only focused on doing everything
to protect Xiyang.
I never thought
that because of this,
she never truly experienced
the treachery of human nature,
which is why she's so naive.
[In Memory of Late Mother Qingyu]
This is all my fault.
[Virtuous and Serene, Honored in Peace]
Weren't you leaving?
Why did you follow me here?
I'm confused.
You didn't ask where I was going.
If you wanted to tell me,
you would have done so.
What's wrong with you?
Don't be like this. It's quite scary.
Why did you go to the palace
and come back like
a completely different person?
The more unusual you act,
the more I feel
you're hiding some kind of
scheme or plot.
Come give me a hand.
Come on.
Such a big box.
What's hidden in there?
Could it be
deadly weapons or magical armor?
Who would bury magical armor
in the dirt?
Then it must be gold.
It's actually wine!
I never expected
you had such a hobby.
This is the Daughter's Red
my mother left behind years ago.
She told me
it could not be opened
until my sister's wedding day.
Is your mother
Empress Zhuang of Susha Kingdom?
Her? Come on.
Help me
drink all this wine.
The wine my mother left behind
shouldn't go to waste.
You've fought on battlefields
as the Red-Clad General,
so you should be able to
hold your liquor, right?
So you won't wait
until your sister's wedding day?
Xia Jingshi doesn't deserve it.
I won't leave him even a single drop.
I never thought
the mighty First Prince of Susha
could be so childish.
Who's childish?
Well then.
Today,
I'll be childish this once.
[Wutong Mansion]
[Daughter's Red]
Your mother's wine
isn't very strong.
Looks like you really can
hold your liquor.
I don't remember anything anyway,
and I don't know
what I'm good at
or if I can handle alcohol well.
Having it tested today
actually brought me a pleasant surprise.
Sometimes,
I really envy you.
Losing all your memories
also means
you've forgotten all your worries.
That's not difficult at all.
Although Xueying can't
♪ The rain drifts endlessly ♪
cure my amnesia,
if you need it,
♪ The old dream burns the heart ♪
she can write you a prescription
and help you forget everything as well.
♪ Dreams sink into ruin ♪
Given Xueying's medical skills,
that won't be hard.
♪ Missing the warmth of your palm ♪
So, what do you say?
Want to give it a try?
One pill to cure all your sorrows.
♪ Awaiting dusk ♪
That won't be necessary.
♪ Shadows take root in the mountain pass ♪
Let's not trouble Miss Ling.
♪ In just a moment, tears stained ♪
But I'm actually quite curious.
♪ Amid the bustling sound
of wind and rain ♪
What is it like
♪ Who laughs at me,
heart cold as the desert ♪
to lose all your memories?
You open your eyes with no memory at all.
You don't remember your history
and your past,
and you don't remember
who you once hated.
Nor do you remember
who you once loved.
What's even more ridiculous is that
everyone around you
knows who you are.
They all know you're Fu Yixiao,
but you yourself have no idea.
That's not so bad.
Not bad at all.
By the way,
was I famous
in Susha in the past as well?
You Three Heroes of Jinxiu
are all Xia Jingshi's
most prized subordinates.
Ning Fei the fierce general,
Xiao Weiran the strategist,
and you, Fu Yixiao,
Jinxiu's number one archer.
In our Susha army,
killing Ning Fei and Xiao Weiran
earns the rank of battalion commander,
and killing you, Fu Yixiao,
earns company commander.
So every soldier in Susha
wants to claim your heads.
That's outrageous!
It's normal for soldiers
to seek military merit.
No need to take it personally.
Why does killing them
earn battalion commander,
while killing me only earns
company commander?
Which bastard
set this rule?
I did.
You?
Alright, when I get back to camp,
I'll change the rule immediately.
Killing you
will also earn battalion commander.
How's that?
That's more like it.
Do you
look down on women a lot?
Do you not believe women
can also fight on the battlefield?
Then let me ask you,
when you were shot by
the woman you despised the most
with a single arrow,
failing when victory was within reach
and losing everything,
how did it feel?
How could you bring up one's painful past
to their face?
Don't you get it?
Tearing open wounds
right to someone's face
is the most satisfying.
I've helped you
drink so much wine.
Now tell me.
How did it feel...
Nothing special.
Victory and defeat are common in war.
Didn't you
want to cut me down with one stroke?
Not only that.
I wish I could
cut you into pieces,
tear you limb from limb,
have you drawn and quartered,
and grind your bones to dust.
Alright.
Once we find out the truth,
my life is yours to do with as you please.
But you're already quite lucky.
At least you know
who your enemy is.
What about me?
Xueying said
I was shot dead within five steps
by the person closest to me.
Until now,
I still don't know who that person was.
Compared to me,
you're not feeling
quite so bad now, are you?
Then it seems
I should help you find
your killer as soon as possible.
Good wine!
[Sentry Station,
Border Pass of Susha Kingdom]
Stop!
This is Susha's territory.
Who are you?
[Pass]
Please take me to your commander.
Follow me.
[Susha Border]
[Susha]
Following Your Highness
to fight against Susha
for so many years,
I've dreamed every night
of marching with Your Highness
to conquer Susha
and storm Yujing.
I never expected that
the first time
[Susha Border]
I see Susha's boundary marker in my life,
I'd have to hold back
from smashing that darn thing.
[Susha Border]
Your Highness,
are you really going to marry
Susha's princess?
We could simply rescue Yixiao
and leave.
[Susha Border]
Let them pass!
Your Highness, we can proceed now.
From here to Yujing
is still over 400 miles.
We've been traveling day and night
these days.
Even if we can endure it,
the horses can't.
There's a post station not far ahead.
Do you think we should...
Then let's rest at the post station
for the night
and head to Yujing City tomorrow.
Yes.
Why does a hero not wield the Wu sword,
seizing the 50 prefectures
of mountain passes?
At Red Cliff's cape,
the eternal waves roar.
On the Copper Dyke road,
the midnight moon shines.
Draw the carved bow, aim at Sirius.
In the cold frost and dawn moon,
with steel and horse, crush Susha!
So you still remember
your poem in the Jinxiu Army.
Come on,
recite with me!
Saddle in the snow,
sword at my waist.
I won't return until Jinxiu is conquered!
Saddle in the snow,
sword at my waist.
Sword...
Give me your sword.
♪ Arrows skim through fleeting light ♪
♪ In the blink of an eye ♪
♪ Scattering among clouds and mist ♪
You're drunk.
♪ I fall off a cliff ♪
Who are you?
♪ My wings, in an instant ♪
You know me?
♪ Shatter into sand ♪
What are you to me?
Before today, we were enemies.
♪ Who once laughed at frost ♪
♪ Riding across the world with ease ♪
From today...
That's not right.
♪ And who was swept away toward ♪
Who am I?
♪ That muted darkness ♪
I don't remember who I am.
♪ Who once ♪
♪ Melted me with a gaze like a river ♪
Will everyone in this world
forget who I am?
Not remembering who you are?
♪ You're the answer in my heart ♪
You wish.
You're Fu Yixiao.
I'd recognize you
even if you turned to ashes.
Good that you remember.
That's good.
♪ I have resolved ♪
♪ To ignite a body of sparks ♪
You're drunk.
I'll take you back to rest.
Thank you.
You're a good person,
♪ Like arrows, falling like rain ♪
and good people
♪ Reaching with burning intensity ♪
will be rewarded.
I brought you into the enemy kingdom
♪ Who laughed at frost ♪
and put you in mortal danger.
♪ Riding across the world with ease ♪
How could I possibly be a good person?
♪ And who was swept away toward ♪
♪ That muted darkness ♪
What a beautiful, full moon.
♪ Who once ♪
♪ Melted me with a gaze like a river ♪
What moon are you talking about?
♪ You're the answer in my heart ♪
Why is the moon so close to me?
♪ I have resolved ♪
♪ To ignite a body of sparks ♪
So the moon
feels like this.
Soft and bouncy.
♪ Like arrows, falling like rain ♪
And it's warm.
♪ Reaching with burning intensity ♪
♪ Through clouds and mist I wander ♪
♪ Watching the stars scatter their light ♪