EPISODE 10
RECIPIENT: HAN SEO-YUL
[camera shutter clicks]
STAFF JU HYUN-SU
[elevator bell dings]
Geez, this careless punk.
I told him not to get stuff
delivered here.
[door lock beeps]
Seol-ah, what are you doing here?
I could ask you the same thing.
The man that you just saw…
Is Ju Hyun-su.
He killed my sister.
Why were you chasing him too?
I wasn't chasing after him.
I came to find Chair Kim's
property under a pseudonym.
So, he was in Chair Kim's building?
Could there be some kind of
connection between the two?
For now, it's just speculation.
Let's go somewhere else.
- We shouldn't be talking about this...
- But I…
I have nothing more to say.
Everything I know ends here.
Are you feeling okay?
You've been
taking care of yourself, right?
Listen, Woo-seok.
You stay safe, all right?
[sighs]
The man that you just saw is Ju Hyun-su.
He killed my sister.
Ju Hyun-su in Chair Kim's building?
Could there be some kind of
connection between the two?
[Woo-hee] I didn't lie like the others.
Ugh, quit worrying.
I told them straight up that
I was going on a trip with my boyfriend.
So, you should trust me too, brother.
Wow, when did you grow up so much?
You always treat me like a child.
At this rate, I'll get married before you.
Ms. Cha Woo-hee, easy, all right?
Getting married, already?
Over there. Just drop me off there.
Call me when you get to Busan.
Hey, you can eat that.
Be careful, okay?
Okay.
[chuckles]
[phone buzzing]
Hey, Woo-hee.
Mr. Cha Woo-seok, right?
Hello. I'm Woo-hee's boyfriend.
Ms. Cha, who was seated
in the passenger seat,
was not wearing a seat belt.
PHOTOS FOR COURT SUBMISSION
A sleep-inducing agent was
detected in her bloodstream.
At the recommendation…
PROSECUTION
…of the defendant, Ju Hyun-su,
she had taken out
a $210,000 life insurance policy.
POLICYHOLDER: CHA WOO-HEE
BENEFICIARY: JU HYUN-SU
There are circumstances that
raise suspicion about the accident…
JUDGE
…but there's no objective evidence
to conclude that it was intentional.
Only the charge of
causing the victim's death
through negligence is sustained.
The defendant, Ju Hyun-su,
is hereby sentenced to one year in prison.
[gavel bangs]
[breathes shakily]
That's evidence of having
transported some kind of artwork.
But why Ju Hyun-su?
You said that you saw Han Seol-ah
coming down from the rooftop
on the day Kim Yun-ji died.
But yet you're the only one
without an alibi for the time of her fall.
Aren't you trying to frame Han Seol-ah
when you're the one who killed her?
You even made the tip-off call
with your voice altered.
No! No!
I did not kill anyone.
Well, listen,
it looks like you don't even understand
what charges you're sitting here for.
I only followed Han Seol-ah
to see what she was up to.
- [door closes]
- [car door closes]
[sighs]
I thought it was suspicious
when I saw them sneaking out.
I was determined to find out that time…
[sighs] …but I lost them again.
"Again"?
That's right. [Breathes deeply]
The day Ms. Kim died,
I was the one who took that video.
[Seol-ah] What are you trying to say?
[Ms. Kim] I wonder…
If your secret came out
for the whole world to see,
would you still be this graceful?
[scoffs]
And why did you keep following
Han Seol-ah around?
You're asking me why?
Because the police
couldn't even catch her!
Because you're not doing your jobs.
Even now, you're holding me here
when I've done nothing wrong!
Why are…
Why are you people doing this to me?
What did I even do wrong?
[breathing shakily]
I didn't kill anyone.
[cries]
[sighs]
So, you're saying you didn't
supply champagne that day?
Uh, no.
It was a VIP event, so Chair Kim
said she'd handle it herself.
Chair Kim from the auction house?
Yeah.
The champagne Mr. Paek drank
and collapsed from, it wasn't ours.
Then why did you attend the event?
I didn't sneak in. I got in the proper way
with Seol-ah's invitation, you know.
No, why you went.
What was your purpose
in attending the event?
[sighs]
I thought, if I met a decent guy,
[sighs] I might try to get
something going with him.
Honestly, I love parties.
In Korea, there aren't many
opportunities to wear dresses.
But you weren't even on
the guest list the day Kim Yun-ji died.
Did you go just to wear a dress?
[sighs] I really didn't do anything crazy.
You did something.
No, I did not.
I just thought that girl, Kim Yun-ji,
was so strange…
Ms. Han only drinks decaf coffee, right?
Okay.
Here's your coffee.
Thank you.
DECAF
Here you go.
How are things?
[gasps]
What's wrong with you?
What's your deal?
Are you a stalker?
Are you jealous of Seol-ah?
If you so much as follow her around
or harass her, you will regret it.
[chuckles]
All I wanted to do was scare her.
I never thought that would happen.
Then, where were you at
the time of Kim Yun-ji's fall?
I was at the party!
I was shocked too, so I stayed
with the others to see what was going on.
[sighs]
I honestly thought I was going to die.
[sighs] How the hell did
Seol-ah stick it out in there?
Oh, geez.
Oh, wow. This is the first time
a consignor's died on me.
I thought this year
was already bad enough.
So what do we need to check legally?
The consignment contract clearly
states that Royal Auction
is responsible for securely storing the
painting until the owner comes forward.
So, you're saying we can keep the painting
until the owner shows up. Is that right?
Yes, ma'am.
It's highly likely that the case will go
to court, so it'll probably take a while.
Hmm.
Oh, ma'am, you need to see this.
Ms. Han had this in her possession.
Hmm.
LIST OF CHAIR KIM'S PROPERTIES
REGISTERED UNDER BORROWED NAMES
Looks like
you've got nothing better to do.
I gave you everything
and you're still digging into this?
If you can't replace the Stiller piece,
then you'll end up in Busan too.
[stammers] Ma'am, but…
Sure.
[sighs]
RECIPIENT: HAN SEO-YUL
This looks like their base.
Han Seo-yul, who caused the accident,
might be living with Ju Hyun-su.
[exclaims] I knew it.
Mr. Cha, you've got such good instinct!
I mean, you noticed the
same pattern as your sister's accident.
Ha! These bastards were
totally in on it together! [Clicks tongue]
What about the paintings?
There were signs that the paintings
were moved to an empty store space.
They must've been moved to
a more discreet location.
[sighs]
Thank God we held the
Stiller piece before it disappeared.
What's going to happen with that?
The owner is dead.
They'll go through
the inheritance process.
I checked with the client's lawyer,
and a designated recipient had already
been named in the event of his death.
There's no way Han Seol-ah's
tangled up in this too, right?
Oh, no way.
CERTIFICATE OF TESTAMENTARY GIFT
OF ARTWORK
ARTICLE 1
(TESTATOR AND BENEFICIARY INFORMATION)
TESTATOR: PAEK JUN-BEOM
BENEFICIARY: HAN SEOL-AH
Why do you hate Han Seol-ah so much?
When I was little, I used to like her.
Ever since I was six,
my brother meant everything to me.
[both panting]
[yelps]
- [young Eun-hye] No! [Whimpers]
- [grunts, groans]
Get up, Do Eun-hyuk.
[breathes shakily]
Get up.
[groans]
- Eun-hye.
- Yes.
Please go tell your brother
to come eat with us.
Okay!
The woman Do Eun-hyuk had his eyes
on his whole life was Han Seol-ah.
I was fine with him loving her
more than me, his own sister,
as long as he was happy with her.
[scoffs] But…
It made me angry to
watch him get nothing in return
and just be used over and over again,
like an idiot.
So I thought if I
exposed who she really was,
my brother would finally give up on her.
That she wasn't just cursed with bad luck,
but a witch who kills people.
So, Han Seol-ah is a witch?
And yet your brother would still do
anything and everything for her, right?
Eun-hye.
[sighs] Brother.
Get up. Let's go.
[sighs]
Why aren't you saying anything?
Huh?
Why aren't you
getting angry or scolding me?
Let's go eat.
What would you like?
Shouldn't I be getting a nice meal
after that?
And why is that?
All you did was get
questioned as a witness.
Well, I just never want to
come back to the police station.
I did nothing wrong, but it's still scary…
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for everything.
Then buy me a steak.
Not pork, good beef. The best kind.
Let's go.
Those addresses…
You actually checked them all?
Chair Kim's properties.
I'm looking into them one by one.
How's Eun-hye doing?
I heard she bawled her eyes
out at the police.
I was so nervous I started shaking,
so imagine how scared she was.
It's all my fault.
She looks like an adult on the outside,
but inside she's still a kid.
I should've been more caring.
Maybe don't be too harsh on Eun-hye.
She was just looking out for her brother.
That's right. When you love someone,
you want to protect them.
I lashed out at Kim Yun-ji
the day she died.
You did?
It looked like she was
giving you a hard time at work.
I'd been planning to give her a piece of
my mind and waiting for the right moment.
Sorry I stuck my nose in.
I kept thinking I should tell you,
but I just couldn't open my mouth, so…
Yeah, but you shouldn't have
gotten involved.
[sighing] I know…
Thank you.
It feels good knowing
that someone's always got my back.
You know, when we were kids,
you two always stood up for me.
When kids bad-mouthed me or picked on me,
Eun-hyuk would beat them up,
and you would humiliate them.
Sorry, and thank you.
Even if it's too late.
Hey, why are you
suddenly acting like this?
Now, I feel even worse.
[chuckles]
[sniffles]
Don't cry. You'll ruin your makeup.
I only did it
because I wanted to protect you.
You know how I feel, right?
- [chuckles]
- [sniffles]
[phone buzzing]
CHA WOO-SEOK
[line ringing]
[phone buzzing continues]
[line rings, stops]
[voicemail] Your call cannot be connected.
- You will be directed to voicemail…
- [phone beeps]
[sighs]
[Eun-hyuk] Did you really mean it?
When you told me
I should stop focusing on you.
When we were kids,
I thought we'd go to college together,
and then end up being
something special to each other.
But then I watched as you always
made sure to keep your distance from me,
and I realized the furthest
you'd ever let me in, was as a friend.
If my past was a burden even to you,
then who in this world
could I ever be with?
But, it's not like that.
Do you know why I dated Su-ho?
He had even less than I did.
He needed me
enough that even someone like me
could feel pity for him,
so I couldn't just turn away.
So, that means you chose Lee Su-ho
instead of me?
I didn't want to lose you.
It was also easier
to be with someone who liked me.
I was a coward.
[inhales deeply]
What about the other guys?
Did you date them
just 'cause they liked you?
I hated being alone,
and I wanted to start a family.
I thought I was a very strong person,
but I guess I was wrong.
You don't have to be so strong.
Just be yourself
and live your life.
Lee Su-ho legally died twice
because of me.
I guess your decision of not becoming
involved with me was the right one.
No, Seol-ah, that's…
[sighs]
GANGHA POLICE STATION
Chair Kim of Royal Auction
prepared the champagne herself?
What's her relationship with Han Seol-ah?
Is she only just her boss?
Paek Jun-beom was a VIP client,
so Chair Kim had Han Seol-ah
assigned to manage him.
Check if there's an insurance
policy involved in this case.
Let's see if it follows the same pattern.
I still have suspicions about Do Eun-hyuk.
But we checked all of
his alibis last time.
Woo-seok's accident happened while
Do Eun-hyuk was being questioned here,
but that was actually instigated
by Lee Su-ho,
so it has nothing to do with Do Eun-hyuk.
While interrogating Do Eun-hye,
I got the sense that he would do
anything Han Seol-ah asked him to do.
[sighs]
Let's start by tracing his movements
on the day Lee Su-ho died.
You're still working?
Wow, how do you take photos like this?
Do you have to dive in with the model?
There's an underwater studio.
Sometimes I shoot at a free diving center,
and other times I go out to the ocean.
It's very cool, but isn't it dangerous?
You'd have to be good at scuba diving,
I guess.
No major accidents so far.
But, what brings you here?
On the day Paek Jun-beom died, you were
working at that Royal Auction event?
I was.
Did you see Paek Jun-beom…
I mean Lee Su-ho collapsing?
Everyone saw it.
Where did you go after the event that day?
I went to Cheongun.
I have my personal studio there.
Didn't you say you usually
go there on the weekends?
So, why go all the way there
on a weekday at such a late hour?
I had a project
that needed to be finished.
Can you prove that you were in Cheongun
the night of the murder?
How would you like me to prove it?
With your dashcam footage.
Should be more than enough.
There's a camera in front of my studio.
Do you want me to check that too?
Well, it'd be great
if you could submit both.
Sure, no problem.
Phone bid, $70,000.
Current highest is 70,000.
Do I have a bid of 73,500?
$73,500, confirmed.
That's the highest bid
on the floor right now.
Do I hear $77,000? 77,000...
I'm withdrawing my bid.
I've had a change of heart.
What?
The flow's been broken.
Dozens of people are
waiting for you to captivate them.
What are you gonna do?
An auctioneer isn't just
someone who calls out bids.
They convince people of
the value of the artwork.
No matter how much the crowd wavers,
you have to stay grounded.
- [sighs]
- You have to trust yourself.
Yes, the withdrawal of
the on-floor bid has been confirmed.
The current highest is 70,000
from a phone bidder.
Now confirming $73,500.
No more bids?
I will call it three times and then
I will proceed to close the bidding.
73,500.73,500.73,500.
Any more bids?
And sold for 70,000.
[melancholy music playing]
[phone buzzing]
Hello?
[secretary] Ms. Han, I'm calling from
the secretary's office at Your Home.
How can I help you?
I need to discuss an inheritance matter
with you.
YOUR HOME LEGAL TEAM
ATTORNEY KIM JUN-SEONG
I am the attorney handling the execution
of the late Paek Jun-beom's will.
Mr. Paek left something for you,
Ms. Han Seol-ah.
He left it for me?
You have inherited a painting.
One painted by Emil Stiller.
He insured it prior to the auction
and designated you,
Ms. Han Seol-ah, as the beneficiary
in the event of his death.
I haven't heard anything about this
and I never agreed to it.
A bequest doesn't require
the beneficiary's approval.
I guess he wanted to keep it a secret.
[secretary] Mr. Paek had been experiencing
complications from the Syria incident,
so he made preparations
in case anything happened.
So is this really
Ms. Han's last auction here?
They're transferring her to Busan,
but it means they're pushing her out.
Oh, that's what it means.
Honestly, does this make any sense to you,
Tae-seok?
- No, it doesn't!
- [sighs] Sang-mi on the main stage?
[sighs] We're at the same level now
but soon she'll be my supervisor.
I show off all the skills,
and someone else gets promoted!
Hmm, skills?
I don't remember seeing her show off any.
[Na-hee] What?
[elevator dings]
[sighs]
Are you still seeing Han Seol-ah?
Looks like she's about to get fired.
I'm here for work.
[scoffs] Nice excuse.
Any progress in the case?
What? You're not going to tell me?
I don't think
you're telling me everything either.
Let's talk later then.
Why?
[sighs]
[footsteps approaching]
Sorry for coming unannounced.
I tried calling, but…
Do you want me to take a guess
why you're here?
The Stiller painting.
[sighs]
Ask away.
Aren't you here
because you wanted to ask me something?
Why Su-ho left such an expensive painting
to me, whether I already knew everything,
or whether I caused him to do it.
It's unlikely to become yours though,
it depends on how they see it.
If it's a bequest from Paek Jun-beom,
or if it's from Lee Su-ho.
You came here just to say that?
To tell me the Stiller painting
can't be mine?
I wanted to see you…
Because I was worried.
It's a special clause in the will.
The police aren't aware of it yet.
We can't stall much,
but we can buy some time
until the real culprit is revealed...
No need for that.
Just give the police
all the information they want.
Then Han Seol-ah becomes
the prime suspect again.
Maybe that's just what
Su-ho wanted exactly.
I don't believe he left me the painting
because he actually wanted me to have it.
- [sighs]
- I'll say this again.
You're in danger too, Woo-seok.
The culprit has never once targeted me,
but the man by my side.
Then protect me.
Don't push me away because you're scared,
and please don't run.
Stay right by my side…
And keep me safe.
[sighs]
[lock clicks]
[line rings]
I need to see you.
[line clicks]
LIST OF CHAIR KIM'S PROPERTIES
REGISTERED UNDER BORROWED NAMES
I was actually about to head over to you.
TERRACE DE VILLA
While going through
Chair Kim's properties,
and looking for a suitable place
to hide Taemyung's paintings…
HYUN-SU'S FRUIT
Ju Hyun-su, Chair Kim's henchman.
I've seen him going in and out
of Chair Kim's office here,
and I thought I should let you know.
So, we've been after the same person?
If we find Taemyung's paintings,
we'll uncover everything
that Chair Kim and Ju Hyun-su did,
and finally you'll be able to reveal the
truth about what happened to your sister.
There was evidence
that the paintings were moved here.
I think the space was used
when the paintings were swapped.
Chair Kim deals with
risky business elsewhere,
and once it's finally safe,
she moves it to the secret vault.
Then the paintings are…
Among the warehouses
that the company rents,
there's one that
the employees can't access.
That warehouse has been reserved
for Chair Kim's personal use.
The storage unit
where that accident happened.
Where Paek Jun-beom was?
Why call me
to such an expensive place, huh?
I was hoping for some food
cooked by you, ma'am.
An insurance investigator is on the case,
and Ms. Han is working with him,
and she's determined to screw me over.
[sighs]
What are you doing
about the Taemyung piece?
There's no need to worry.
What can they really do about it?
There's no hard evidence anywhere.
And if they manage to find the paintings?
Don't you realize when that happens,
it will all be over?
They're safely stored,
so don't worry, okay?
Hmm.
It's too risky where they are.
Move them to my vault now.
Okay.
[engine starts]
The art storage has just become available,
so you can go ahead
and set up a new contract with us.
Are you saying there were paintings
stored here until now?
[receptionist] Yes,
someone canceled their contract.
Are there any other
art-specific storage units here on site?
This is the only space
designed specifically for art.
Was there an issue with the storage unit?
From what I understand,
the owner retrieved them
due to personal reasons.
The paintings that were here
definitely belong to the Taemyung Group.
[sighs] The truck we saw earlier
[sighs] we should've checked it.
That leaves us with just one possibility.
How much time do we have
until your auction?
One week.
That's all the time we have to get in.
They're in Chair Kim's vault.
[sighs]
[door opening]
I heard they've been pressuring you
to resign.
From Chair Kim's perspective, I get it.
What boss would want an employee
constantly at the police station?
Keeping your feelings hidden
right beside your enemy…
That couldn't have been easy.
There were…
Times I wavered too…
Because I couldn't accept
hating the person I was supposed to hate.
[sighs]
I saw that a lot while investigating.
Parents who blind their own
children just to collect insurance money
and kids who protect their parents
even though they're monsters.
I guess what you feel towards Chair Kim
is something like that.
Woo-seok, how do you know all of that?
Because I was a survivor too.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[grunts] What took you so long?
I'm seriously starving.
I couldn't eat anything
since this isn't my place.
Wow. This two-shot.
Very nice.
Your visuals match really well together.
Here we go.
This is a subcontractor that worked
with the Royal Auction architect.
Companies like this usually have
pretty low security.
The Royal Auction building
was completed on July 15, 2017.
2016-2017
These look like the blueprint files
exchanged from 2016 to 2017.
Oh…
INDIVIDUAL HALL
PROFESSIONAL BLDG
ROYAL AUCTION
ROYAL AUCTION_13F (CHAIRMAN'S SUITE).PDF
Found it.
Just as I thought.
It's this empty space behind
the kitchen wall in Chair Kim's office.
The space is pretty big.
Could there really be a secret vault?
It's close by, easy to manage, and there
are no security cameras on that floor.
Wait, don't tell me
we're going to sneak in there.
CORNERSTONE
HERE BEGINS A NEW ERA OF ART
BUILDING NAME: ROYAL AUCTION BUILDING
[Seol-ah] Chair Kim has a password
she always uses.
One, seven, zero, seven, one, five.
[gasps]
Congrats, Ms. Han!
Oh, my. Oh, oh. Hey, hey, hey.
So…
Mr. Paek left behind a gift for you, huh?
I heard that the Stiller piece
is yours now.
I have no intention of accepting it.
Are you crazy?
The guy who died
isn't the real Paek Jun-beom.
He was impersonating him.
It's not even his, so how could he
have the right to leave it to me?
Don't worry. I already checked everything
with a law firm.
And legally, there's a very high chance
you'll get it.
And if it doesn't work out,
we'll file a lawsuit.
I'll cover all the costs.
Aren't you investing too much
on an employee you're about to let go?
When did I say that?
I only told you to go take it easy
at the Busan office.
I never said you were out.
Besides, now that we're here, you don't
even have to go to Busan anymore.
Your father can finally
rest easy now, huh?
Looks like his daughter's
about to land on her feet.
We haven't decided on the main piece
for the upcoming auction yet.
Did you happen to see
the list I submitted?
Song Hwan-ju's posthumous piece.
It's his last work, never released before.
When the world sees this,
it'll cause a huge stir, huh?
This… How did you…
This is a stand-in for the Stiller piece,
so it needs to make an impact.
And it's the biggest card
I've been hiding under my sleeve.
This is great.
It will certainly generate
about as much buzz as the Stiller.
It's quite the send-off
for my last auction.
I'm offering you an opportunity,
and you're still saying
this is your last one?
COMMERCIAL INSURANCE COVERAGE
FOR MUSEUMS AND CULTURAL INSTITUTIONS
INSURANCE POLICY
NAME: PAEK JUN-BEOM
GROUNDS FOR RESCISSION OF THE POLICY
CONSIGNOR: PAEK JUN-BEOM
BENEFICIARY: HAN SEOL-AH
A bequest?
It's a special clause
stating that if Paek Jun-beom dies,
Han Seol-ah inherits
the Emil Stiller painting,
and the insurance payout
goes to her as well.
What? I heard it's gonna sell
for over $10 million.
Does that mean
we're suspecting Han Seol-ah?
That's a strong motive for murder.
If Han Seol-ah is behind it,
she may have changed her pattern.
When all those men died, she failed to
collect the insurance payouts.
But now with the painting in the bequest,
it's different.
She can make sure she gets the money.
And the stakes are even higher now.
Wait, but Paek Jun-beom was actually
Lee Su-ho, right?
Can she still inherit it?
I actually looked into it,
and it's a bit complicated.
He lived under the identity of
Paek Jun-beom,
but the painting could also be considered
Lee Su-ho's asset.
There's room for a legal dispute.
They'll have a lawsuit then.
BENEFICIARY: HAN SEOL-AH
I already put the tracker
on Chair Kim's car.
Dr. Shin will be watching.
Are you sure you'll be okay though?
Why don't I just do it...
In the worst case, one of us will
stay behind and proceed with Plan B.
If I get caught,
I can just say I'm leaving
the company anyway.
But if you get caught, our plan fails.
[sighs]
Just take pictures and get out right away.
[device beeps]
LIVE CAM
CANCEL / CONNECT
CONNECTING…
Chair Kim's on her way home right now.
Be ready in case security shows up,
and mark the entrance clearly.
I'm in front of the door.
[Seol-ah] One, seven, zero,
seven, one, five.
[lock clicks]
[Seol-ah] I'm going in.
Be careful.
[lock clicks]
[gasps, sighs]
I made it in.
[static]
[static continues]
- Woo-seok?
- Seol-ah.
Seol-ah?
UNSTABLE CONNECTION, CHECK NETWORK
TRY AGAIN
[phone buzzes]
ACCESS GRANTED
DOOR SECURED
Is this an error? What is this?
[Seol-ah] Vanished Sensation
by Fabien Leclerc
is sold to Chairman Park Min-cheol
of the Taemyung Group.
FIRE BREAKS OUT ON A TRUCK TRANSPORTING
TAEMYUNG CULTURAL FOUNDATION ART
Turn the car around.
[tires screech]
[Dr. Shin] What's this?
She's turning around.
Why? What's going on?
Chair Kim's car is heading back
to the office.
The auctioneer needs to get out fast.
[no audible dialogue]
It's weird. I still can't get the eyes
to look like Mom's.
[inhales sharply]
Well, let me see a second.
[sighs]
It's not that they don't look like hers.
Your mother's eyes are complicated.
Look at them closely.
They hold a story of everything
she's been through her whole entire life.
But what does that mean?
Daddy's complimenting you.
My daughter's finally trying
to see the person, not just the drawing.
I want to draw as good as you, Dad.
Skill improves quickly once you learn.
But, hmm, putting your heart into it…
Not everyone can do that.
My dear Seol-ah has that passion in her.
That's what makes Daddy very proud.
- Really?
- Of course, who's your dad?
Oh, my goodness,
you really are two peas in a pod.
[sighs] Looks like we're going to have
another painter in the family.
And what's wrong with that? [Chuckles]
[clicks tongue]
Seol-ah, don't become a painter.
Be a doctor. A doctor.
Our dear Seol-ah will become
a very famous artist.
- Right?
- Mm-hmm.
[chuckling]
[chuckles]
[Chair Kim] If this ends up
being a posthumous work,
- I'll make sure it sells for a high price.
- [sobs] No! Please, I'm begging you.
[wails]
No!
- Just let me keep it! No! Please!
- [cries]
[coughing, groans]
Whoa, I see her car.
What should we do? Should I crash into it?
She's coming. What do we do? Huh?
I'm going in.
Hurry! She's pulling in!
Come on, seriously!
[device buzzes]
[metal clanks]
- Hmm. You're getting off work late.
- I have a shoot tomorrow.
So I wanted to get ready.
[alarm blaring]
[Seol-ah] The exit code is different.
[blaring continues]
[device buzzes]
[buzzes]
[Chair Kim] First, take care
of that bastard quietly.
It may not be enough,
but the culprit will show up soon.
No. I don't want to use you as bait.
I'm the only one who can get close
without raising any suspicion.
Get her. Don't touch anything.
Han Seol-ah!
[Seol-ah] Until we catch the killer,
nothing is really over.
[Woo-seok] It's been a while.
Your neck will be the one on the line.
- It's all your fault.
- [exclaims]
Well, we'll just have to wait
and see whose neck is on the line.