CBFC
There is another world too
other than ours.
Genies live in there.
Innumerable miracles
happen in their lives.
And their king is Karkimuki.
All the genies in his kingdom
were happy.
But he was very sad.
One thing troubled him a lot.
There is no successor to him.
Public wanted the king
to have a successor.
One who would take over
the kingdom after him.
Public offered prayers.
And a beautiful son was born to him.
King's happiness knew no bounds.
He got his successor.
King raised his son Chinchiniya by
providing him everything.
He showered his entire love
and happiness unto his son.
His son became his world.
When Chinchiniya turned 10,
he expressed a wish to his father.
That he wanted to go to a world,
where sages perform austerities.
Karkimuki didn't ignore his wish,
and took him to that world.
Chinchiniya became mad with
happiness after entering that world.
He was playing hide-and-seek
with his father.
While playing Chinchiniya went
and hid in such a place,
where a sage was offering penance
for thousands of years.
His penance was interrupted
due to Chinchiniya.
Sage became furious in anger.
and started curing Chinchiniya.
Karkimuki started pleading
with the sage,
and begged with him
to forgive Chinchiniya.
But the sage was
not willing to forgive Chinchiniya.
Because Chinchiniya has broken
the penance of thousands of years.
Karkimuki begged in front
of the sage,
to punish him instead of his son.
Karkimuki turned him into a statue,
instead of his son by cursing him.
Sage said,
48 days after settling
himself free,
from the statue, he will
go back to his world.
Only the human who frees you,
from the statue recites the
mantra written on the statue.
Otherwise you'll turn into ashes
in the air forever.
Father and son started crying
after hearing it.
The sage threw him on earth
after turning him into a statue.
"It's a no moon day
and the moon is missing"
"tire India is crazy
for the leader"
"Nagini..."
Thiru!
Yes!
Getting late for school.
Turn off the TV and
get ready quickly.
I'm ready, mother.
"My leader is going great"
Ghee rotis for lunch,
finish them, okay. - Hmm.
Anything else other than this?
Paratha?
Ba... Ba... Ba...
Paneer makhani, right?
Not that?
Ba... Ba... Ba...
One minute, I'll be back soon.
Yay! See what I brought.
Break, papaya, banana, biscuits,
and almond milk.
Do you want?
What do you say?
Mother is right, isn't it?
Mother, I was going to say bye.
Oh!
Sorry, son. Sorry!
I'm so sorry,
mother couldn't understand.
Bus has come, go fast.
Quick!
Bye!
- Bye!
How does a hen make sound?
(Laughing)
His face looks exactly like a hen.
What are you watching?
If someone makes fun of us and
we too make fun of them in return,
then what is the difference between
them and us? My uncle says so.
So what should I do?
- Learn to be happy my friend.
Getting angry is
not good for health.
You're giving a big lecture.
Leave!
That stammering boy has left!
His friend is here.
Let's tease her.
Leave me, leave!
Good morning, madam!
- Good morning students!
Please sit down.
Take out your English
text book please.
Turn to page 88.
Don't tell. Unit number 9.
Rishita, please read dear.
There are lots of things.
They won't let me do.
I am not...
- (Boy stammering)
Next.
So I patiently wait till,
I'm all grown up,
and I'll show them all one day.
Next please.
I could show them now
if they give me a,
I could show them now...
things I could do if I try.
Next.
Bu... but...
But... nobody...
nobody knows...
that...
Students! Silence!
Who told you to read?
Sit.
Madam, I can.... read.
If you read then
the school will get closed.
Sit down.
Silence!
'Shree Shankh Baba'
Swamiji, he stammers a little bit.
Go... Go... God bless!
Ma.... Mamma... Papa...
Thiru!
- Ah?
Tell the answer.
(Boy stammering)
Rishita.
- Present.
Present, madam!
- Present, madam! - Pa...
Thiru!
Son...
Need to give them
at Kishore's house.
Take them.
Ka... Ka...
Ka...
Ka ka...
Where is the Principle room, child?
Leave it, it'll get late.
What... What did you do?
Oh! Blood!
Doctor, he's injured.
Mad!
Not blood, it's paint.
Sorry.
It also became like me.
Working slowly.
Uncle...
- Tell fast.
Pe... Pe...
What are you trying to say?
I told you many times to
write on paper the things you want.
Go and get it written by
your mother, go.
What are you staring at?
Go!
DREAM
Why does this word refers
to APJ Abdul Kamal sir?
Because he said
something about dream.
What are you saying, madam?
It is 4 pm by the time
we reach home from school.
And then English tuition at 4 pm.
Maths tuition at 6 pm.
7 pm to 8 pm science tuition.
Once the tuition gets over,
I play a game.
No time to sleep,
so where is the time to dream.
Silence! Silence!
Listen,
we're not taking about the dreams
we get in sleep.
Dreams are those which
don't let us to sleep, sit down.
Which dream we get without sleeping?
Okay, now you tell me about your
dreams in life.
Madam...
- Yes.
My dream is to become
a teacher like you.
Superb, Riya.
Madam, I want to become a boxer
like Mary Kom. -Wow!
Miss...
- Yes?
I want to become a cricketer
like MS. Dhoni.
Great!
Madam, my dream is to
do a government job.
Good. Government job, super!
Why do you want to do
a government job?
Because government employee,
reaches office after 11 am.
and comes home before 5 pm.
And they have lot of side income.
They come home and watch TV
by eating popcorn.
By watching popcorn?
Where did you learn all this from?
My mummy, father and
all neighbours do the same.
Because I stay in government colony.
Silence!
Listen, bring your father
to school tomorrow. Sit.
My father doesn't
go anywhere without bribe.
How much are you giving?
Silence!
Sit down!
May I come in, madam.
- Please come.
On 15th?
- Yes, madam.
Thank you.
- Okay.
Okay, so on coming 15th July,
Kamraj sir's birthday
celebration is there.
There will be inter school
competition on this occasion.
First is speech competition.
Who all want to participate?
Raise your hands fast.
Madam!
- Super!
Good!
Madam!
Excellent!
- I can, madam.
Very good!
- I can, madam!
Super!
What's the matter?
Why are you so sad, friend?
I want to... participate
in speech competition.
Don't participate
Participate in Essay writing.
You watch...
I'll do practice...
and...
come first...
in competition.
You wait here, I'll go
and get snacks for us.
Sir is participating
in speech competition.
What will the stammering boy
do in speech competition?
He might get something
for stammering.
Will come first in stammering.
(Boys teasing)
Hey!
Leave!
What are you doing?
- Leave!
Mummy!
Mummy! It's paining!
Ouch!
- Move! Move!
What happened?
He's bleeding!
- Ouch!
He's bleeding on head!
Hospital...
take him to the hospital.
Quick!
Who did this?
Thiru!
Madam...
Shut up!
(Stammering)
I said shut up!
Your child is becoming
naughty every day.
He broke one student's head
in the class.
What will we tell his parents?
The class teacher has
complained to me many times.
Teacher, you tell him.
What should I tell?
He fights with someone
or the other every day.
Tell him anything,
it doesn't matter to him.
I've not seen a more worthless boy
than him in my career.
I'm really sorry, madam.
I'll talk to him,
he'll not do it again.
Don't say sorry.
You write an apology letter
saying he won't repeat it.
If he does,
then you find another school.
Why did you do it, son?
Thiru is a good boy, right?
You should have said sorry
when you committed a mistake, right?
Why didn't you say?
Mother, I didn't... push Arun.
Indra pushed me,
and I fell on Arun.
Teacher punished me...
without asking.
Didn't allow me to say anything.
I too want to talk...
like others.
I...
Whenever I say something...
everyone makes fun of me.
Mother, why do I stammer?
You'll become fine soon, Thiru.
My loving son will speak fast.
Calm down, good boys
don't cry like this.
Come to me, calm down.
Open your mouth, child.
Open more.
More.
Lift your head.
Is it paining here?
Here?
Open your mouth again.
Say one, two, three.
One, two, three,
four, five...
si...
Six.
- Six.
Se... sev...
- Okay, relax.
His jaw muscles are flexible now.
Nothing to fear.
Doctor, Thiru will
become fine, isn't it?
He'll become fine very soon.
I'll tell some exercises,
make him do them.
We'll start the next treat
after the improvement, okay.
Thank you, doctor.
'Silent please'
Coming for picnic?
I... don't like.
Come, I'm too going.
You go...
I'm not coming.
Silly boy!
You don't like anyone.
Why are you searching me?
Come, children!
Come!
Make it fast, come fast.
- Wait! Wait! Stand here.
Make a line.
Come in line!
Come here! -Siddharth,
you come and stand here.
Children! Boys and girls
on different sides.
Stand together and
don't leave each others' hand.
Tanya, come this side.
Raju, come to the left.
Is everyone wearing ID card?
Yes, madam!
Very good!
We all will go together in group.
Nobody should go alone,
and don't touch anything.
Take permission from us
if you want to go anywhere. Okay?
Okay, madam!
Madam...
- What Thiru?
Cannot control.
Came just now
and you want to go immediately.
Okay, go and do it fast.
Go.
Mummy!
Help! Help!
Help!
Someone help me!
Help! Help!
[Chant]
Devil! Devil!
I can see!
I can speak!
I can hear too!
I'm free?
I'm free!
"I'm free! I'm free!"
Where is the one freed me?
Boss! Where are you?
Ghost! Run!
Run!
So tiny!
Run! Ghost!
Small kid is my master?
Mummy!
Mummy! Save me from this devil!
Gone...
Gone.
Where did he go?
Where are you lost?
Your slave is here.
De... De...
Devil!
Save me!
Help!
Devil!
- Tired?
Shall I give you massage?
Devil!
Don't run, boss.
No fun!
You'll fall down.
Smart boy!
- Devil!
Help! Help!
Stop my boss!
This is not a soft sofa,
it is my hand.
I'm telling the truth.
Why are you getting tired
by running?
Oh-oh!
He's down.
I feel as if he got scared
after seeing me.
My boss!
I think the boss is doing yoga.
What shall I do?
What shall I do now?
Hmm.
[Chant]
There is water in stone.
Thank you rock stone.
My boss.
Don't fear.
[Chant]
Run! Run!
Help!
He's frightened of me
like a goat after seeing tiger.
I think I look more like a
band music player than a genie.
I'll make him my friend.
I swear on my genie world.
And then we both friends
will have tea and toast.
Where did you go?
We all became worried
by searching for you.
You'll never mend your ways
even now, go inside.
Are you hungry?
- No, madam.
See there!
Hey slow!
Boss, you were searching
for me, right? - Hmm.
What happened? Why are you shouting?
Look here.
What happened? There is
nobody next to you.
Nobody can see me other than you.
(Sobbing)
This is my younger sister's
wedding card.
Sit down.
Come home one month
before the wedding.
You make all the arrangements.
You go back to your house
after one month of wedding.
Okay, brother.
She was so small,
and now she's getting married.
Girls grow up very fast,
like Vande Bharat.
Look, who has come.
Say hi to uncle.
- Hi dear Thiru.
Didn't recognize the
moustache uncle?
Mummy...
Devil!
Hey!
He's your uncle, talk nicely.
He is not uncle...
he's devil.
Is he saying so
because of my moustache?
Look how he is
twirling his moustache.
No, Thiru. Keep quiet.
Don't say like that.
It is not his mistake.
There are lice
inside the moustache.
Look... devil is laughing.
He's pulling me.
Okay, sister, you come on
the wedding day itself, that's fine.
Brother, eat and go.
- No, no, my stomach is full.
Look, dear. Don't watch
scary cartoons.
Bye!
Don't come again.
I get scared by watching you.
So leave from here.
- Keep quiet.
Sorry, brother, he's just a kid.
Don't feel bad, please.
What to do? My face is scary.
- Bye.
Kids find my moustache to be funny.
I'll shave the moustache.
Look, devil is escaping.
- Thiru!
Shut your mouth!
My boss, is everything fine?
Shall I remove shoes?
It's me.
Mamma!
What happened, son?
Mother, de... de...
Feeling hungry?
No, mother.
De... de... -Laddoos?
Okay, I'll bring right now.
By the way, who are you?
Why are you following me?
I feel scared
by seeing you. - Oh!
That's why I don't see
myself in the mirror.
What if I change my get up?
How do I look?
Fatty!
How am I?
Thin!
How is it now?
I love you. (Bengali)
I love you.
I...
How is it now?
Ninja!
Yay!
(Boy laughing)
How is it now?
Bhim!
Bhim! Bhim! Bhim!
Chhota Bhim!
How is it now?
Uniform like mine.
Who are you?
Do you work in circus?
I'm Karkimuki, king of Genie world.
3000 years back a sage has cured me
and turned me into a statue.
And you freed me.
That's why I'm here to serve you.
I'll do whatever you say.
You're speaking pure Hindi.
I didn't understand anything.
Talk Mumbai Hindi.
Mumbai Hindi...
Mix of Urdu, Hindi,
Marathi and Punjabi.
Actually the thing is,
3000 years back a sage has
cursed me.
And you made me free of it.
So I came to repay the favour.
I'm your friend...
I mean bestie.
Yes!
Yes?
Why did you.... hit him?
Whoever troubles my boss,
I'll burn him into ashes.
I mean he will be dead.
Do you understand?
3 Idiots! I'm coming!
I'm too coming!
My boss!
Give the ball to me!
- Give me! - Pass it!
Why is he walking like that?
Injured his leg?
We'll break him leg too now.
What are you watching?
You all have....troubled me a lot.
Sorry to me.
I'll not say.
What will you do?
It'll be bad...
if you don't say.
Stop your overacting.
Leave quietly from here. Okay.
Are you... saying sorry or not?
Stammering boy!
I'll not say, leave!
I'll let you play if you say sorry.
Hey, take the ball from him.
Hey, pull it.
Come on!
I'll catch it now.
What are you doing?
Catch it. - Catch it if you can.
Hey!
You troubled me a lot, right?
Thiru will take revenge
for everything.
Run! Run!
Come on, catch.
I'm tired!
Got it!
Move I say!
I'll get crushed.
Hey!
Why is the hall flying?
I'll fall down!
Are you hurt?
- Come, come.
At your service.
It's paining.
What do you say?
I got it, right?
Ouch!
His shorts came down.
Yours too!
Mine too!
Run! Run!
Save yourself by running away!
No water.
What happened?
- Shower isn't working.
Wow! See the water.
Oh!
No!
Will you eat egg?
No? I'll eat.
What is this?
Run! Run! Run!
There is a rat!
Niranjan, take homework book
from everyone.
Everybody out!
"There is fun with you"
Hey little fellow.
What do you want?
You got it in writing, right?
Give it.
Want chocolate.
I've come.
[Chant]
PERK.
Ah!
DIARY MILK.
Ah?
Ah!
What do you want?
Speak up!
Pe... Pe... Pe...
I want pen.
You want pen?
Don't bring paper next time.
Tell whatever you want.
I'm giving the shop on rent.
Hi!
Genie...
- Yes?
Thanks.
Thanks my friend.
Why boss?
Whatever... I say, you listen to it.
And you... fulfil my wish.
Do you know my father was
also the same?
Once I was going on bike
with my father.
Suddenly,
a truck has hit us.
And my father died.
Since then I started stammering.
My mother says so.
Now....I've
only one wish left.
What is it?
Tell me, my boss.
I'll fulfil it.
Boss... How is it?
Wonderful!
What's there in hand?
Ball.
In our Genie world.
Alia Genie was getting
married to Kalia Genie.
Top dances from Hollywood
were called for dancing.
Baba...
what are you doing?
Didn't sleep at night?
I'm turning you into a statue
and sending you to earth.;
Whoever frees you from the statue.
he should recite the same mantra
on the 48th day.
The one written on the murti.
And then you'll be able
to go back to your world.
Otherwise you'll get
destroyed in the air.
And tell about the mantra,
only when he asks you.
Need to tell.
But how.
What if I tell?
No, no.
Welcome to all of you.
Thank you very much!
And now the next contestant
in Speech Competition is,
Thiruvaran from
AWLM Higher Secondary School.
You there!
No goal is bigger, whoever
doesn't give their best only loses.
My humble greetings to all mothers,
teachers and everyone.
It is normal to
feel let down due to problems,
but whoever fights will win.
But listen carefully.
Failure is the first step
towards success.
And you'll come across
innumerable problems on this path,
but you shouldn't stop.
Make yourself strong enough,
that God himself asks the person
about his wish.
A great person said,
victory and defeat are part of life,
but life is never ending.
Walk towards a new destination,
this is just the beginning,
entire journey is left to traverse.
No, no, sky is the limit.
Superb!
- Yay!
Yay!
Thanks to all of you
from the bottom of my heart.
Great! Saw any dream?
Day dreams come true.
Really?
- Yes.
They become true!
- Thiru!
Happy birthday!
Tell me what you want,
your mother will get it.
Tell me fast.
Pasta... noodles...
milkshake...
My dear son, I'll get
everything you want today. Done!
Done!
Happy birthday!
I'll get everything
my son wants today.
Come on.
Thiru, today is
my happy birthday too.
Is it? So tell...
what you want?
If you recite the mantra
then I can go to the Genie world.
I will.
Boss, today is my happy birthday.
Come on... come on...
Come on...
- Today is my birthday too.
Leave it.
Mother...
Come to school.
There is a surprise.
What surprise, son?
How will it be a surprise
if I reveal it?
Come to the school and
watch yourself, you'll be shocked.
Shendi! [Pony tail]
I'm late for school.
Do something and take me soon.
[Chant]
Welcome!
Hey... arrived at school?
See here.
House is here.
School... house... school.
Quick! Quick! Quick!
Follow me!
- Yes.
Bro, bro...
- What do you want, bro?
Crocodile.
- Why are you joking?
Okay, let's play again.
Bro, bro...
- What do you want, bro?
Tell me, bro.
- I'll tell, bro.
Bro, bro.
Why are you repeating the
same line?
Play properly.
- Let's play again, bro.
What do you want, bro?
I want fruit, bro.
Which bro?
- Big one, bro.
How big, bro?
- Biggest of all, bro.
Tell the name.
- Jackfruit, bro. - Boss...
Come here.
- What happened, bro?
Let's play again, bro.
Did you see this?
What do you want, bro?
Flower.
- Which colour, bro?
Black colour, bro.
For whom?
Bro, bro...
What do you want, bro?
I'm your bro.
Tell me, bro.
Neither I like these people,
nor their songs.
Oh!
How should I tell him my feelings?
What is your name?
Jyeshta.
- Okay, okay.
I want my name to be in that list.
[Chant]
AWLM Higher Secondary School's,
Brainwaves festival
welcomes you all.
Along with our school,
other schools' students
too have participated
in this festival.
During the 7 days festival, students
will show a new talent each day.
So let's this festival
with Speech Competition.
All the best, children!
Go.
So our first participant is Razia
from Swami Vivekananda High school.
Kiddo!
Mother India!
I'll sit here.
Has it started.
- Yes, just now.
The power of knowledge
is more powerful than a weapon.
I love my school, my teachers,
and my friends.
Thank you very much.
So our next participant
in Speech Competition is.
Master Thiruvaran,
from AWLM Higher Secondary School.
[Chant]
My humble greetings teachers
and my classmates.
A boat never sails past...
fearing the waves.
Those who keep trying...
never...
never fail.
What happened?
Those... those who keep trying...
never...
- Don't cry.
Never fail.
Calm down.
Don't cry. No.
Please don't cry.
Why did you come?
Leave from here.
Leave.
Are you so angry with me?
Forgive me.
I trusted you and participated
in the Speech Competition.
But you cheated me.
If you helped me then
I would have spoken well.
I cannot stop your stammering.
But why?
We too have certain rules.
Dead people cannot be
brought back to life.
Time cannot be brought back.
I can heal the wounds on your body.
I cannot cure your mental disease.
Forgive me, Boss.
You can do.
Will you stop my stammering or not?
Give a final reply.
What are you saying?
I cannot help you in any way in it.
So you're not my friend.
Our friendship is over from today.
Don't come behind me,
and don't talk to me.
Leave!
- Listen to me!
Please stop.
Don't cry, son.
Everything will be fine.
Children who stammer
often faces this problem.
You must be feeling very bad
for being a mother.
I've solved many case like this.
You don't take stress.
But Thiru is very upset, doctor.
I don't know what to do.
Let him rest for two days.
He'll be fine.
Good morning!
Hot chocolate!
Forgive me.
I'm sorry, I beg you.
Please don't cry.
Please don't...
There is cavity in your teeth.
What are you doing?
Please I say!
No!
Forgive me.
Forgive me!
No!
Hello. Who is it speaking?
I'll call later, I'm getting late.
Where is the church road?
Want to go to the church?
Go straight and take right.
Go little ahead and...
Hey, what are you doing?
Leave! - Remove!
What are you doing?
- Remove it!
Hey!
No! No!
Start!
Start the bike!
Leave!
- Leave my hand!
The mood seems to be good today.
I'll tell my feelings,
so that I can go back to my world.
Shendi!
- Yes, boss.
I'll not talk hereafter.
Why my dear?
Everyone would laugh when
I used to speak.
Now the time is so bad,
that they laugh
immediately after seeing me.
That's why I...will not
talk to anyone.
Don't say like that my dear.
Wait, I'll make you provoke you.
(Screaming)
Mother...
Let him rest for two days.
He'll be fine.
Thiru...
- Hmm.
From today don't do any work,
without asking mother.
- Hmm.
Promise?
Promise!
Bye.
- Bye.
Shendi!
Come with me to school.
Okay!
Good morning, everyone.
Welcome to AWLM
Higher Secondary School.
Today is the final day of Brainwave
2021 Intercultural Festival.
In this cultural fest, we saw
numerous talents of many kids.
The judge for this intercultural
festival is a multilinguist,
Mr. Irai Anbu.
He is an IAS officer.
He loves children!
He is a great human being
who encourages
the talents of the children.
It is a great honour for us
and for our school to welcome him.
Thank you so much for coming.
Please!
Thank you so much!
Shendi!
why... why did you bring me here?
Run!
Welcome back!
Come back!
He's back again.
Run!
Come back!
Oh dear!
Milka Singh didn't run so fast.
I am scared to look at this place.
Come, let's go.
We should not run away
from problems, master.
We should face it with courage.
Participate in the competition.
Isn't it enough
that I have already been insulted?
Should I get insulted
again and again?
If you run saying they are laughing,
you should keep running
throughout your life.
Just stand and think
once with patience.
Whoever turns his minus into plus,
this world will only look at him.
Wherever we were insulted,
we should stand and win there.
Go and participate
in the competition.
Go.
What do you want me to do now?
Abracadabra...
Can I perform like this?
You can do, master.
You talk what you think confidently.
If you wonder what will people say
then what will they think?
Ignore them and move on.
- Find your destiny moving forward.
If you find the river,
search for the sea.
Did you hear me?
The sage himself said.
Isn't it?
Go!
Next participant is Indhu
from AWLM Higher Secondary School.
Hi, everyone.
I am Mary Kom,
very happy to meet you all today.
I will make my country
famous in the whole world.
Thank you.
Next contestant is Lakshith Sai
from AKI school.
What are you going to do?
I will say, ma'am.
As soon as you enter the stage,
you should say without fear, okay?
Lord Balaji came personally.
Ask what you want.
Hey, the hen has come again.
Bring a bucket of water.
It will urinate again on the stage.
Go.
Hey, where are you going?
To participate in
the competition, madam.
You have already damaged
the school's integrity.
I will perform correctly
this time, madam.
Do something, go now.
Next participant, is Thirunavukarasu
from AWLM Higher Secondary School.
Sir, the child stammers.
He is performing so well.
My child!
'I bless you
with speech this moment.'
You can give a speech.
Write a poem and read it.
And also spend your life
as a great poet.
You can show the world
how much power education has.
I bless you!
Mother,
Dad!
mother,
father,
I am able to talk,
Goddess, I can talk,
He is performing really well.
You answered my prayers.
I can speak.
I can speak. - Great!
Goddess,
Goddess...
He is speaking.
I am blessed!
Mom!
You rendered them speechless.
Goddess!
- Give him a reward.
He performed the best.
- I can speak!
I can speak!
Sir, give him the prize,
give him the prize.
Goddess.
Thank you!
I am blessed!
Ladies and gentlemen,
accept my greetings.
And love to the children.
Today, the children
in the fancy dress competition,
they displayed
their imaginative skills
and I saw the excellent
performance with my eyes.
If we have to give prizes,
we need to give prizes
to each and every student.
But when one student
entered the stage,
you all mocked and laughed at him.
That student is one who cannot
talk well because of his stammer.
But still that student
got on the stage boldly
and participated in the competition.
He changed his defeat to victory
making his weakness his strength.
I have decided to give
the main prize to him.
Cheer up!
I am pleading one thing with the
teachers and the parents who are here.
Never make fun
of another man's weakness.
God created all of us.
Even if someone has
some small disorder,
don't make it big and mock at them.
In fact, encourage the child.
There's only one reason for me
to give this award.
Hey, super!
Super!
Thiru, sorry.
We are friends?
Friends.
Me too.
I have participated in a competition
for the first time and won a cup.
I feel like telling it to everyone.
But when I think of mom,
I am scared.
She won't believe that I can win.
You should tell everyone,
that's it, right, master?
Hmm.
Let's go!
Where?
Hold on!
Let's go!
Master,
say now.
What?
You said you wanted
to tell everyone, right?
Tell now.
I have won.
I have won a cup.
He has won.
- I have won.
Okay.
Good... morning, ma'am.
Good morning,
how are you today?
Good, ma'am.
- Good,
go to class, have a nice day.
So sweet.
Good morning, ma'am.
- Good morning, ma'am.
Good morning,
students, please sit down.
Good morning, ma'am.
- Everybody, clap for Thiru.
Very good, Thiru.
Very, very good.
Everybody, take out
your English text book, please.
Today, we are going to study page
no. 23,
unit three, little by little.
Little by little, an acorn said. As
it slowly sank in its mossy bed.
Bhushan, next.
Downward it sent out
a thread-like root.
Up in the air sprang a tiny shoot.
Ask my Thiru to read.
- Day by day and year by year,
Little by little... the leaves -Ask
him to sit. Ask my Thiru to read.
appear.
Thiru,
- What?
read it.
Yes!
Little by little, an acorn said.
As it slowly sank in mossy bed.
I am improving every day.
Hidden
deep in the earth away.
Little by little, each
day it grow, Little by
little, it sipped the dew.
Very good,
everyone, clap for Thiru.
Hey! He read it!
He read it!
Very good.
Very, very good.
Hey, do you know
that Thiru knows magic?
We have already become friends. Why
are you giving so much of buildup?
Hey Thiru really knows magic,
you know?
Even for me, he did magic
and got a big ice cream, you know?
Even if you want something, tell him.
He will do magic and get it for you.
Is that so?
Then, ask him to get
a ball for us to play.
Yes.
Abracadabra...
Huh?
Hey, he would have already
kept it in his pocket.
Ask him something else very big.
Come on, get a bat, let's see.
Yes.
Abracadabra...
Wow!
Hey, he really knows magic.
Hey, yes.
How did you get to
know all this magic?
I will tell you one thing.
You should not tell it to anyone.
Promise?
- For what?
I have a friend by name Jinni
His name is Shendi.
It only does these magics.
I go to the washroom at midnight.
Are you lying to me about ghosts?
If you see my friend, Jinni
you will pee in your pants.
Shendi!
Shendi, come here.
Come.
Jenni has arrived.
Run! Run!
Don't be scared.
If you are friends to Thiru,
you are my friends too
Lollipop!
Friends!
Ah!
Wow!
Friends!
Great!
Hey look there,
the moon is at work.
Yes.
Come, let's have some refreshment.
What are you doing, granny?
Can't you see?
I am selling vadas.
Then feed one for free.
Hmm.
The spider has made cobwebs here.
I baked this 'vada' a decade ago.
Hence, Spiderman made a home in it.
He is Jinni.
Here is your snack.
Yours and yours.
Here. This is yours.
And you. You.
I want one.
It's super tasty.
My granny states
she had dinner at Moonlight.
But we had our dinner on the moon.
Hey, we are having
lunch, not dinner.
Right?
What to do that he ask me?
I really don't know what to do.
How to make him say what I want?
I am very happy now
only because of you.
Yes!
Those who insulted me
have become my friends.
Teachers are talking well.
That's why,
this is all because of you.
Yes.
Okay, then,
you ask whatever you want.
I will do it.
Why are you looking like that?
You ask me what you want.
I should see
my Chinchinya.
Chinchinya?
Who is it?
He's not an animal
but my son, master.
I was childless for years.
I got him as a boon.
After he was born
and kept on my hand,
there was no boundary
to the joy within my heart, master.
The first time he smiled at me,
I found a reason to live for.
All the babies
first utter the word mom.
But the first word of my son was
Dad!
He said it all the time.
Time just flew with him.
I experienced
no creature in all the worlds
would have been so happy like me.
I don't know who cast their eyes.
He was determined to go
the world of sages and saints,
I had no option.
I took him there.
His face was lit
with so much of happiness.
He was playing a game with me,
and he hide inside a snakepit.
I kept searching for him
and I went inside that pit too.
The penance of a sage
who was inside was disturbed.
The sage got furious on me.
And cursed
turning me into a statue.
I was helpless.
And couldn't do anything.
I saw tears in my
Chinchinya's eyes.
The face which knew only to smile,
I saw tears for the first time.
His crying face is still
in front of my eyes.
I am not sad that I got this curse.
Well, I am sad that
I got separated from him.
Now for the past 3000 years.
I want to meet my son.
Once.
Let me meet my son once.
Please!
Then, why were you with me?
You can go to your world, right?
I cannot go to my world
just like that, master.
Within 48 days of my freedom,
the mantra which is inside
my statue, only if you recite it,
I can go to
our world.
If that doesn't happen,
I will vanish in thin air
and die.
No! No!
That is not possible!
whatever mantra it is,
I will tell that.
Tell me what mantra it is,
I will say that.
I won't let you die.
I will read it.
Abracadabra...
(chant)
I will read... wait.
Tell me what is next?
What happened,
What? What? Shendi!
The time has come for me
to vanish in thin air.
Coming Shivrathri
will be my last day,
as I said, my 48th day.
I will memorize the chant.
I won't let you go!
I will read the mantra. I will.
Master!
What is in your mouth?
Oh!
If I do like this, I won't stammer,
I saw in YouTube, that's why.
I am trying the trick.
No, master.
It will hurt you.
This pain is nothing
compared to the pain
which people inflicted on me.
I will Chinchinya has his father.
I, I know how painful
it is to miss a father.
Chinchinya must be
missing you, right?
I will definitely...
tell the mantra.
You can go to your world.
(chant)
Thiru.
What mom?
What are you doing?
Nothing.
But I heard you reading.
I...
I am reading and
writing a homework, mom.
No,
you were reading something else.
No, nothing, mom.
- Show me.
Mom, leave it, mom.
Mom, it is nothing.
Show me, hey.
- Mom.
Thiru.
Why are you dull?
Nothing.
Nowadays,
there are changes in his activities.
Is it?
- Yes.
He is alone.
He is avoiding me.
He mutters while sleeping.
He is hiding something from me.
I don't know what to do.
I feel very confused.
You don't worry.
Everything will be all right.
Right.
- I will go.
Hi, Thiruna's mom. How are you?
- Hi!
I am fine, ma'am. How are you?
I am fine.
Hasn't Thiruna come?
No, he has gone for tuition's.
Sorry, don't mistake me.
For what?
That's because I misunderstood
Thiruna all these days.
He won the fancy competition and
the whole school is in awe of him.
And I found out
Thiru is a talented boy,
I feel so guilty for it.
I am so sorry,
Really sorry!
By heart, I am telling you, Our school
is so proud only because of Thiru.
Okay, madam, I will leave. Bye. Bye.
Bye.
'He won the fancy competition and
the whole school is in awe of him.'
'Hereafter, whatever work you do,'
'you shouldn't do
without telling me.'
'Okay?'
Uh!
What is this?
What happened, master?
I am unable to memorize that mantra.
If someone else would
free you instead of me,
he would read the mantra easily.
You could have gone to your world
and meet Chinchinya.
I am sorry!
I cannot read the mantra.
I'm sorry.
I am sorry. Sorry.
Thiru, come here.
Where did you go?
I went to play, mom.
Where did you go and play?
Thiru,
you are hiding something from me.
Better tell me the truth.
I...
I am telling the truth, mom.
You are telling the truth, right?
What is this?
Is this your truth?
I know that you participated
in the competition.
You are hiding something from me.
Better tell me the truth.
I want to know what's
happening with you.
I am asking you, tell me.
Why are you not talking
when I am asking?
Who... is it, who?
Mom! Ghost, he's Jenni.
My friend.
No! No! He is a ghost?
He's a ghost!
Stay away from him. - Mom!
It's a good ghost, mom.
But a Jin.
It helped me a lot.
Whatever help it did, I don't care.
You first ask it to leave.
Listen! Listen!
Whom do you want?
Your mother or the Jin.
Mom! Please, mom.
Oh, God!
Is mom important
or the ghost important?
Mom...
Why did you do that?
Why? Tell me.
You lied to me.
Ask it to go.
Why did you do it to me?
You are a liar.
- Mom! Mom!
Ask him to leave.
- I am leaving.
You don't understand my words.
Don't beat my master, mam.
I am leaving.
Jini!
Thiru, leave him.
- No! No!
No!
Leave him! Come here.
Don't go!
- Come to me!
Thiru, leave.
- No!
Leave my son,
go away, go away.
Please go!
Mom...
- Thiru.
No!
- No! No!
Don't cry.
Leave him.
Jini!
Let him go!
Stop it!
Shendi!
Operation?
Don't be scared.
It's a small operation.
Admit in the morning
and after operation,
you can leave in the evening.
If you do the operation,
stammering will be cured.
And it is not expensive.
I'll do it in 5 lakh.
When will you do the operation, doctor?
Eat, dear.
You are getting operated tomorrow.
You shouldn't sleep
with empty stomach.
Listen to my words. Eat.
Thiru.
Whatever mom does,
she will do only for your good.
Eat a little, dear.
Hey, are you really a doctor?
I brought my daughter
for treatment believing you, right?
Don't get angry.
Talk a little patiently.
I want to kill you.
You made his life hell.
Though she stammered,
my daughter used to talk well.
After operation, she's mute.
Are you a doctor?
Listen, I will...
How can I talk calmly, man?
Here.
Whatever happened has happened.
I have given five lakhs
more than what you spent.
Leave this matter here
without making it big, please.
Please!
Sir. It's him, sir.
Arrest him.
Madam! Who are you, madam?
He is my son, sir.
You seem to look educated.
Won't you enquire about the doctor
who does the treatment and
the genuineness of the hospital?
If we had been a little late, your
son's would lose his life.
I made a big mistake, Deepa.
Stop overthinking.
Stop worrying.
All is well!
I did this so that Thiru talks well.
But now I don't understand
what to do.
I know a doctor.
Go to him.
Okay.
First of all,
for those
who have this stammering problem,
it is impossible to cure them
with medicine or operation.
You may go abroad
for the treatment.
It is a total waste to spend money
and time for this.
To treat this illness,
you need to get rid of his fear.
What we need to do
is first allow him to talk.
Stop making his feel
he's has a flaw?
When we are not
paying attention to them,
it affects them immensely.
So, we need to pay attention.
If you ensure him
whatever he says is right,
it will build his confidence.
You can do his treatment
for that a doctor is not needed.
'Today is the 48th day.'
'This is my last day.'
Sorry dear.
Hereafter, whatever you
want to talk, talk to me boldly.
I will listen to it. Okay?
Say something.
No, mom.
You won't listen.
Thiru!
whatever your mom does,
she will do for your good, dear.
You didn't want others
to mock at me,
but when did you listen to my words?
Whenever I talk,
you give 10 options.
'There is bread, there is papaya,
there is banana, there is biscuit.'
And almond milk.
'Tell me. What do you want?'
But Shendi allowed me to talk.
and listened patiently
and completely to whatever I spoke.
I lost in a competition just once,
as you always broke my confidence.
But Shendi
encouraged me always.
That's why, I won.
Only because of that confidence,
I won where I lost, mom.
I won for the first time in my life, mom.
Those who made fun of me,
it made them my friends.
It brought me good name
from the teachers.
It did a lot more good things
for me, mom.
On that day, Jini saved you
from those thieves, mom.
You never took me seriously.
I never suffered
till that ghost was with me, mom.
He took care of me.
Loved me.
You separated me from it, mom.
I won't talk to you.
Thiru,
Hey... hey wait!
Thiru, wait!
Thiru! Wait!
Shendi! Shendi!
Shendi!
Go home.
I will read the mantra.
I will read it.
(chant)
No!
Thiru!
Thiru, you stopped stammering.
Master.
Hey!
Shendi!
Mom!
Get up, mom.
Mom, what is wrong?
Mom...
Mom. Get up, mom.
Mom, what is it?
Mom...
Get up, mom.
'Ghosts have certain rules.'
'We should not bring
back dead people alive,'
'stop time,'
'solve problems that
are related to the heart.'
'If we go against these rules,'
'we will be punished for
Brahma dosha and I will die.'
Mom.
Please get up!
Mom! Mom!
Get up!
Mom...
Thiru!
Thiru, I cannot see you sad.
I want to see you happy.
Shendi!
Thiru!
The young poet of this state
wants to present you some poems.
Please listen to him carefully.
Hope. Hopelessness. Desire.
Language. Drama. Passion.
Apiration. Intoxication. Origin.
Sweet. A wave. Wisdom.
Brilliant. Radiant. Beautiful!
Kavita. Babita. Sarita.
Shakila. Jamela. Pathela.
Rihana. Sultana. Ruksana.
Julie. Tulip. Mona. Sona.
Food. Eat. Drink.
Sit. Get up. Lie down.
Reena. Tina.
Sweat. Bath.
Wash. Cry.
Youth. Mosquito net.
Story. Grandma.
One rupee. Two rupees.
Four rupees. Come forward
and go behind.
Come if you wish or don't.
Eat. Treasure. Banana.
Rizwana. Farzana. Come tomorrow.
Lovely. Adorable. Fascinating.
Fish. Lizard. Brocolli. Peanuts.
Road. Path. Way. Swing.
Did you hear
neither from East nor from West.
Nor from North or from South.
I spoke it through my mouth.