ظآزShrugging off past burdensظآز
ظآزBeneath the mask, who am I?ظآز
ظآزRelease and find wider shoresظآز
ظآزLove's a riddle, and rain pours heavyظآز
ظآزCrossed paths, now downward fallظآز
ظآزFrom dust arises starlight's sparkظآز
ظآزTearing through
the night's dense blockadeظآز
ظآزHeart's flame illuminates all solitudeظآز
ظآزLet time's sails drift endlesslyظآز
ظآزThrough wandering exileظآز
ظآزBreaking free from the cocoon,
I start anewظآز
ظآزMoon as song, life as flameظآز
ظآزNameless heart clings fiercelyظآز
ظآزLet meظآز
ظآزCharge toward the next raging riverظآز
ظآزMoon darts, snow fallsظآز
ظآزWe tread rugged paths to reuniteظآز
ظآزHands held tightظآز
ظآزWe forever live for love's sakeظآز
ظآزShadow's spear burns fiercelyظآز
=Legend of The Female General=
=Episode 17=
Let's go.
Look at this.
So beautiful!
Truly lovely.
Where are
Mr. Cheng and Miss Song?
They must've seen something
delicious or entertaining.
Leave them alone.
- Great!
What's this?
Well...
Impressive!
It's called Plucking Spring.
Plucking Spring?
The Water God Festival
is a festival for lovers.
Besides worshiping the Water God,
we prepare programs
for couples.
The Plucking Spring
is one of the traditions.
Look, on that tall bridge
hangs a wooden ball
containing the first cluster
of winter jasmine
that bloomed in spring.
Whoever retrieves it
the fastest
wins the Plucking Spring.
I see.
Good.
The winner
gets a grand prize.
What kind of prizes
are there?
All sorts of treasures
you can imagine.
Looks like you are
interested.
Let's check it out.
Okay.
- Great!
Good.
That's Mr. Qiao.
What kind of whip
is this?
You've got a good eye!
This is Ziyu Whip, the biggest prize
for the Plucking Spring.
Seems you
really like this whip.
It's quite a unique whip.
Since you like it,
I'll get it for you.
Let her husband
win it for his wife instead.
Honey.
Don't even think about it.
I'm already thinking.
If I don't have to pretend
to be elegant and delicate,
I'd compete to get it myself.
You really want that?
Hmm.
Fine weapons are rare.
Missing this chance
would be a pity.
I'll compete.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Anyway I can't
let my wife down.
- Great!
Honey.
Be careful.
Don't worry, Honey.
- Awesome!
Look out!
Amazing!
- Great!
(Enjoy the beauty and harmony of spring)
That's my nephew.
This is the Ziyu Whip.
Here you go.
Thank you.
My pleasure.
As long as you're happy.
I'm genuinely happy.
How come
Mr. Cui and the ladies
disappeared?
Probably they wanted us
to have privacy.
It's quite weird
to hear you
say something like that
in a cold tone.
Let's go.
Make one for her.
No need.
Make one.
Alright.
If we buy this,
we can't take it when we leave.
Why waste money?
Don't you like it?
If you do, then get one.
If you don't pursue something
you fear to lose,
that'd be rather dull.
Today,
you can
do everything you wish to do
without worries.
Just be your true self
as you've always been.
Whatever you like
and dislike,
just say it outright.
Don't hold it back.
Can I truly
do whatever I want?
Do as you please.
Alright.
Do as I please.
Miss, your dough figurine is ready.
Thank you.
My pleasure.
Have a look.
Does it look like me?
It's better than you.
Turns out I do
look like a woman.
You are a woman.
We followed the faintest clues
to trace Chai Anxi.
But when I reached his hideout,
I was still late.
I'm sorry.
Please punish me.
Keep looking.
Yes.
Perhaps we should go back.
We're Qiao Huanqing
and Wen Yuyan.
We must keep acting.
Is Chai Anxi a cockroach?
He's so good at hiding.
No worries.
He can't escape Jiyang.
I will search everywhere
for him.
Look!
A snake.
Throw it back!
I hate snakes!
Throw it away!
Come on.
Coward.
Taotao.
No more pranks.
You're so gullible.
You wear it all day.
Huanqing.
Yuyan.
Uncle.
What a coincidence!
Huanqing and Yuyan
stumbled onto Lovers' Bridge.
As a couple,
you should
cross this bridge.
During the Festival,
lovers crossing this bridge
will stay together forever.
Did you hear that?
Stay together forever.
What a dreadful curse.
True.
Look!
This is the Lovers' Bridge.
Only genuine lovers
can cross it together.
They can't match me.
I've crossed it four times.
You're quite romantic.
If I were him,
I'd cross just once in my life,
with one person only.
What a rare opportunity!
Huanqing.
Yuyan.
Go give it a try!
Exactly.
Go ahead.
Give it a try.
Crossing the bridge
is about the courage and love
to move forward together.
Love
brings you courage.
Courage born from love
makes you invincible.
Moreover,
the princess favors
lovers with unbreakable bonds.
If you two cross this bridge,
it'll make it easier
for you
to visit the princess.
Okay.
What?
Nothing.
You make great sacrifices
to meet Princess Mengji.
Be careful.
Hold onto me.
This bridge looks unstable.
Crossing it together
might compromise your reputation, no?
If you can't handle it,
then...
Never mind.
To meet the princess earlier,
let's get it over with
quickly now.
Made it
sound like we're going to die.
You made it sound
like I'm going
to live and die with you.
We can live together,
not die together.
Commander.
Should we use Qinggong?
Or we pretend we're stuck,
falling down?
Someone will help us.
Grab my collar.
Quickly.
Hold tight.
It's so shaky.
Will they fall?
No.
They're not like us.
What do you mean?
Are you implying
we'd fall?
They know martial arts.
But we don't.
Let's watch.
How about making a bet?
Let's cross that bridge too.
I bet we won't fall.
Should I then bet
that we'll fall?
That's madness!
Are you going or not?
Sure.
Go.
Sorry.
(This is worse than daily drills)
(at the training field.)
Almost there.
ظآزBefore fate is confirmedظآز
ظآزMy love rests between your fingersظآز
ظآزFarewell tears blurred my sightظآز
ظآزIndescribable yearningsظآز
ظآزAwaiting the spread of moonlightظآز
Sir, keep moving!
Go.
Oh.
Well done,
my nephew indeed, Huanqing.
Did it on the first try.
I feared
that if you failed,
you might never try again.
Surprisingly,
you easily crossed the Lovers' Bridge.
That's good.
Since you crossed the Lovers' Bridge,
in this life,
the two of you
will never part.
Indeed.
They will never part.
Where are
Mr. Cheng and Miss Song?
They are
crossing the Lovers' Bridge now.
Careful!
As one
of the Capital's Four Young Masters,
I'm reduced to doing this.
It's utterly undignified.
Maybe we should quit.
Cheng Lisu!
If you retreat now,
I'll beat you up.
Infuriating!
Crossing the bridge or not?
Let's do it!
What a surprise!
They bicker all the time.
They are actually a couple.
Exactly.
Right,
back then,
I used to tug the braids
of the girl next door.
That feeling...
Great!
We're already halfway done.
Victory is within reach.
We absolutely cannot give up.
Hmm.
- Good!
- One more!
Look at that one up ahead.
- It's beautiful.
- More!
- Great!
Another one!
Mr. Cui.
What a coincidence!
Miss Yan, Miss Ling.
Why haven't I seen
your parents around?
Our parents are on the boat.
Min'er and I
came out with servants
for a stroll.
We'll see the ceremony
and bring back some offerings.
- Great!
Why are they
wearing masks?
Each mask
represents an identity.
These are related to legends
about the Water God.
During the ceremony,
everyone sings and dances together
to spread the legends
about the Water God.
It's fascinating.
If you're interested,
you can dance with them
and play a character.
After it concludes,
an elder will dip willow branches
in blessed water
and sprinkle the water on everyone.
The blessed water
will bring you good fortune.
Why let her join?
Min'er and I also
want to dance on stage.
If Mrs. Qiao
joins us,
it'll be better.
Alright!
But I don't usually dance.
You won't laugh at me, right?
Of course not.
We'll teach you.
What's this?
If she doesn't participate,
how can we make a fool of her?
We'll go get masks then.
Go ahead.
Good.
You know they have ill intentions.
Why not refuse?
I'll play it by ear.
Besides,
even if I decline, they will try again.
I want to see what tricks
they're going to play.
You really never stop thinking of
becoming a general.
Absolutely.
Come on.
They're waving at me now.
I'll go over.
Hmm.
How interesting!
- Great!
Look!
Mr. Cui.
Is something wrong?
A minor issue.
Enjoy yourselves
and have fun.
- Great!
(Looks like something big happened.)
Mrs. Qiao.
There are many people
at today's ritual ceremony.
The ceremony master mentioned
that these masks
must be assigned by lottery.
Why don't you draw a lot too?
What's different about these masks?
Different masks
represent different roles.
In the myths
of the Water God,
there are villains and buffoons.
Who knows
which unlucky soul will draw them?
I believe you won't
draw any of them.
Alright!
(Liar Fox)
Liar Fox.
It's actually Liar Fox?
How unfortunate!
What's wrong with this role?
He's a vicious liar
who did evils near water sources.
He swindled people's fortunes,
even targeting elders and children.
The most shameless things
were all done by him.
The deities could
no longer tolerate this.
They sent a man of the Water God,
an immortal, to subdue him.
Then?
The deceiver
could tell countless lies to others,
but under the immortal's magic,
he could only speak truths.
He confessed ten secrets
about himself.
Finally, he was imprisoned
in an underwater dungeon,
never to set foot on land again.
Oh.
How tragic!
It is tragic indeed.
However,
since you've drawn that role,
you must play Liar Fox.
If you accept to join the ritual
but later withdraw,
you'll be punished
by the Water God.
Fine.
I can be a buffoon.
Someone
has to play it, right?
As you said,
Liar Fox must tell secrets
to the immortal, right?
Correct.
The secrets
must be genuine.
So, Mrs. Qiao,
you have to reveal ten secrets of yours.
The so-called immortal
is just a madman
who snoops into others' secrets.
That's the immortal's mask.
Let me play the immortal.
Why?
We already have someone
play that role.
My wife's secrets
shouldn't be heard by others.
Put it on.
Let me help.
Haven't you worn masks before?
It's not that hard.
You've worn many?
Perhaps I wear masks in my dreams.
How should we dance?
I have no idea.
Miss Ling mentioned
that Liar Fox must tell the immortal
ten secrets.
Now that we're here,
let me tell you
my ten secrets.
Go ahead.
I'm listening.
I will
start dancing.
I used to handle alcohol well,
but now I can't.
I've memorized Wuzi's Art of War.
I'm the number one in Yezhou Garrison.
My favorite dish
is mushroom and chicken stew.
I gave Lisu's jade pendant
to the courtesans
of Wanhua Pavilion.
How impressive!
In my eyes,
Commander is a good man.
I'm deeply grateful to him.
What a smooth talker.
Every time Commander misunderstands me,
it breaks my heart.
Go on.
Commander and I met
in a former life.
I was once a general.
I thought
you'd say "I will be."
The last secret.
I love the moon.
Yet the moon doesn't know.
That's all.
ظآزCrimson threads entwine like rings,
binding our first vowظآز
ظآزTime lingers as you and I share
overlapping palm linesظآز
ظآزZither and harp
accompany our dancing dreamsظآز
ظآزThe brocade moon writes our vow,
keeping this promiseظآز
Jiyang has many famous views.
But only the fireflies
at the Firefly Spring
are truly renowned.
It really is beautiful.
Commander.
Why are you being so kind
to me today?
Isn't today your birthday?
How did you know?
You are
not a good liar.
Sometimes,
your lies are flawed.
you speak truths or tell lies.
It's hard to tell.
Frankly,
we're the same sort.
On your birthday,
don't you make a wish?
Go ahead.
Finish your birthday.
I have no wishes.
Making a wish
is just self-deception.
Whatever I desire,
I'll get it myself.
That's it?
I thought you would
wish for promotions and honors
or military achievements.
Commander.
Haven't you noticed
that since we met,
I've always pretended
to be someone else?
For example, Cheng Lisu
and Wen Yuyan.
Who knows
who I'll pretend to be next?
Do you feel wronged?
Not exactly.
But I'm afraid
after pretending
to be someone else for too long,
I might forget who I really am.
ظآزI've seen the mountainsظآز
ظآزAnd trodden through iceظآز
ظآزDay after day, I venture aloneظآز
I hope
there's someone in this world
who comes for me.
ظآزA restless yearning in my soulظآز
ظآزGazing through the mireظآز
(Not for He Rufei.)
(Not for General Feihong.)
(Just for me.)
(Coming for me.)
ظآزSoaring across the world's expanseظآز
ظآزThere must always be a longingظآز
ظآزDisregard the wounds to seek the lightظآز
ظآزLight shines upon my heartظآز
ظآزUnveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstreamظآز
ظآزThe resonance of courage
rings loud and clearظآز
ظآزIt's the boldness
that defines existenceظآز
ظآزLight shines upon my heartظآز
Commander.
You must remember my name.
I am...
He Yan.
I'll remember.
ظآزLight shines upon my heartظآز
ظآزUnveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstreamظآز
ظآزThe resonance of courage
rings loud and clearظآز
ظآزIt's the boldness
that defines existenceظآز
ظآزI've seen the mountainsظآز
ظآزAnd trodden through iceظآز
ظآزDay after day, I venture aloneظآز
ظآزDestiny is my creedظآز
ظآزIdeals surge beneath the surfaceظآز
ظآزIgniting the flame against the windsظآز
ظآزA restless yearning in my soulظآز
ظآزGazing through the mireظآز
ظآزWho cares about this boundless voidظآز
ظآزCharge ahead with blazing fervorظآز
ظآزStubbornly fighting with my lifeظآز
ظآزSoaring across the world's expanseظآز
ظآزThere must always be a longingظآز
ظآزDisregard the wounds to seek the lightظآز
ظآزLight shines upon my heartظآز
ظآزUnveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstreamظآز
ظآزThe resonance of courage
rings loud and clearظآز
ظآزIt's the boldness
that defines existenceظآز
ظآزChasing the light within my heartظآز
ظآزBurying frailty,
embracing life through deathظآز
ظآزYou'll meet gazes where storms brewظآز
ظآزWith our unwavering true love,
brave the world with meظآز
ظآزSoaring across the world's expanseظآز
ظآزThere must always be a longingظآز
ظآزDisregard the wounds to seek the lightظآز
ظآزLight shines upon my heartظآز
ظآزUnveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstreamظآز
ظآزThe resonance of courage
rings loud and clearظآز
ظآزIt's the boldness
that defines existenceظآز
ظآزChasing the light within my heartظآز
ظآزBurying frailty,
embracing life through deathظآز
ظآزYou'll meet gazes where storms brewظآز
ظآزWith our unwavering true love,
brave the world with meظآز