I…We decided to be drum majors.
What do they teach here?
Here, have a look.
It costs 30,000 baht per
person for private class?
It offers good friends and good connection.
I just met you not long ago and
now you showed up here at POPA.
1..2... 3...
Super drunk! Super fun!
Bambi. You study here, too?
Hey guys, watch this.
Look at her!
That is soooo good!
Lukjan, you're so goddamn gorgeous!
I know.
You seemed so close to Name.
I thought you didn't like him.
It's nothing. He asked me
to join his MV, just for fun.
Why? I Nothing.
You think I'm that stupid.
You think I don't know you?
You don't actually look
like a smart person anyway.
Guys! Look at this!
What a freak in guy!
He woke up, posted a clip and hundreds
of thousands people liked his clip already.
Wow! I Look at that!
Cocky! I Switch!
I didn't do it by myself.
Unlike you, edited it and
everything. I Stop mocking me.
Let's search about Bambi.
Right.
Here she comes!
Just Princess of Trash.
Nobody looks at you, waste of society.
Let's skip.
Sustainable is real messed up.
You're the trash girl!
No! I mean it in a good way. I like it.
Let's go back to our lesson,
you're having too much fun.
Okay, so…
We're going back to 14.
Bambi.
You're not going to the party?
I can't, I'll have a meeting after this.
What're you doing?
It's so refreshing.
See? I flicked it open and I inhaled it.
Wow! Free acting for me?
Wanna try? I Sure.
It's freezing. I Right?
Nice smell too.
You like it?
You can have it.
What're you gonna use after?
I can get a new one.
Think of it as
a welcoming gift for joining our class.
Thank you.
How is it? Feeling any better
after getting to know them?
They're fine but
when they looked up your names
you all have good stories up there.
But when they looked up my
name, I was Princess of Trash.
It was funny in the beginning
but when I heard it a lot
it was really annoying.
If you don't like it, then you
should do something else.
It can wipe away.
It is that easy?
The problem is that I
don't know what to do.
Why don't you start
from something you like?
What do you like to do?
I like
listening to music.
See? Then you should sing.
Anyone can launch their singles.
I have a friend and he's super ordinary.
He came up with a fun idea to make music
he made good song with good beats.
Now he becomes famous.
You should try.
You can think of something?
Wow! I really missed it.
You want to make music? I Yep.
Sure. No problem.
I haven't had it for such a long time.
Let it cool down first.
How is it?
The familiar taste.
Even though hip-hop is originated
from the west side of the world,
it has found its way into Thailand
and flourished to the highest
level in the past 10 years.
A boy named Mhong is another person
who was influenced by this culture.
Mhong!
Go to the front of the class.
You can't trust human's heart.
It's too deep to understand.
Even the most twisted of vines
seems benign compared to the soul.
Still, he has never had a dream before.
Hey,
what's your IG account?
I'll tag you in your rap video.
You're Mhong, right? I'm Bambi.
Until A$AP Rocky met his Rihanna,
an ordinary boy like Mhong
started to be interested in his talent.
Why does he need to stop growing?
To be a professional rapper
has become a boy's
dream before he knows it.
I'm here to ask about
music.
What should I do to start?
Start it? I Mhong!
Table five wants noodles with no veggies.
Got it.
I think you should start with
asking yourself what
kind of music you like.
Music that I like?
I can listen to anything, like pop music.
Like Sabrina or AESPA?
I love Sabrina. I Yeah?
You serious? Me too.
Starting with grouping your ideas.
Like Sabrina mostly
tells stories about her life.
If you can think of anything,
just send them to me.
I can handle the rest.
Don't worrying about recording
studio, we can do that at my company.
No worries.
You think I can use it?
I'm not a trainee like you.
I need to help out my friends
in a studio this Friday.
I can ask them about it.
Can I come?
Maybe I can them myself and.
I want to see how they make music.
But if it's not okay, then I'm cool.
For you, anything.
Thanks. I No problem.
What are you fucking shooting?
Why didn't you do something? Aloha?
Green, what the! What are you playing at?
What? Have you ever
fucking played this game?
This is crazy, oh my!
Damn it! I Diesel, can you keep it down?
Your dad asked
if you still feel guilty
about that car accident?
Sure.
That's so cool, bro. I Of course.
But I want some ad-libs that
could balance my song to make it better.
Sure you can.
Hey, can you moan for my song?
Moan it like when you
sleep with your boyfriend.
Can you try?
I want the sound that
you're about to finish.
You should try it could
go well with the song.
Can you try?
I don't think she can.
Why's that?
She has never sung in the studio before.
But she wanted to
record a song, didn't she?
Why's that? I It could ruin her reputation
if she moans. I What reputation?
No one knows it was you.
Why? You're here already.
Fine.
I don't want to force you or anything.
Let's go find something to eat.
See you.
I can try.
That's more like it. Make it hot.
Okay?
(Singing)
Let's do this.
You want me to record it?
But.
Can I be in this room with only Mhong?
I can't do it around too many people.
Sure thing.
Mhong, can you do it?
Hey,
are you sure about this?
If you don't want to, you don't have to.
I just think that if I help him out,
he could help me out in the future.
Please guide me.
I trust you.
Wait! No!
Let's do this one more time, you could try
to close your eyes and
breathe out slowly, okay?
You want me to turn off the lights?
You could feel better
without anyone looking at you
and it could help you with that, okay?
Wait a minute. I Thank you.
Okay?
Let's try again.
Let's go, Bambi.
What do you think?
Well…Um…I think it's fine.
Good. Well done.
Won't you turn on the lights?
Right. Sure.
Okay.
This serum is the starter item for someone
who wants to take care of themselves,
Garnier Bright Complete
Overnight Booster Serum.
Just a few drops on your
palm and tap them to your face.
It's easy to use.
I can guarantee you that ladies
will fall in love with your bright skin.
Hello, Gunner.
Mhong, they like how you mixed the song.
They are thinking of your
debut in showcase next month.
So dope!
No shit! You serious?
This is too much!
But they need to hear
your demo first, okay?
If it's not that good, they won't
let you on stage, you hear me?
Just try it. I Whoa!
Don't worry. I'll give
you my best shot, bro.
About recording studio for Bambi,
if nobody is scheduled to
use it, then you can book it.
Okay? I You guys are too kind.
This is so cool. You're so good at this.
You're gonna be famous.
I can go this far
because of you.
You crazy? It's a team effort.
I didn't do anything.
Well, it's true.
I'm thinking about writing a new song.
How's your new song going? Need any help?
I'm about to show it to you.
I wrote a little of it but…
It's okay. Let me see.
I'm not sure if it's good enough.
I know! Why don't we go up to my room?
We can sing it out loud
and I could add some beats.
Let's go.
Mhong, don't forget to
close the shop for me.
Make yourself at home, dear.
I'm about to head home.
You are? I Yeah, I
should go. It's getting late.
See you.
See you later.
Okay. I Bye.
Bye.
When you paint with watercolor,
don't forget to clean your brush first
so colors won't mix.
Here.
It's messed up.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You can get closer if you want.
CUT!
Good, let's move on to the next scene.
Thank you.
What is it? Your brows are twisting.
I mean…
Honestly, I don't know.
I..I think I didn't really
into this scene that much.
I'm not sure.
You think viewers would feel that scene?
I think it's fine.
I looked at you so much and
I started to feel something.
Yeah? I Yeah.
Don't stress out.
Thank you. I Thank you.
Tang. I What?
What is it?
I think…
Can you talk to the director for me?
I want to try it again.
I understand you.
And I know that viewers can
feel how hard you work on this.
The director has his reasons.
It's okay. I No, I feel.
I think.. I They know what they're doing.
If you want it to be better,
you need to work harder before shooting.
Work harder and better in a limited time
you know?
It's really fine. I Yeah.
Don't dwell on it.
Mheng! That table, over there.
Take it to that table, go.
It's late. What're you doing? I Sleeping.
I'm helping out at the shop.
Noodles to go. I Sure. Just a sec.
You want to come here?
What type of beef? I Tender one.
Tender.
I just ate it. You want me to
eat your noodles every day?
You said you like it, I
want you to have it again.
Get it to this table.
Can you boost me up?
Sure, it's here.
What type of beef?
You get my whole support,
can you think of a song?
Nope. Because I'm busy thinking of you.
Just kidding.
The small type of noodles.
You're not working? You
sent texts back so fast.
Eureka!
I can think of something.
You do? That's so great.
Wait, is it your song or my song?
What's wrong with you? You
haven't showed up here quite often.
Can I get your Discord account so
we can play at the same time easily?
Yo! Aloha!
We've been playing together for such a long time,
why did we just exchange our Discord accounts?
What is it with your username?
How to pronounce it? So hard.
Kwamfhundanupha.
My name is Dream.
Hello?
You're a girl?
Why are you playing this type of game?
I rarely see women playing this game.
What's wrong with a woman
playing shooting game?
Why can't we play it?
I play it better than you.
I don't know, it's just weird.
I don't fucking know.
We're not in Stone Age,
stop judging already.
The world is not developing
enough because of people like you.
You're a smarty-pants, aren't you?
Can you try to educate me?
Why women like you play this game?
Hello?
The world is a shitty place. I
just want to blow off steam here.
You can do anything in a
game, everyone is equal.
That's true.
You can be whoever you
want, do whatever you want here.
You can be anyone.
Except a good gamer, you amateur.
And you dare to judge people?
Such a smart mouth.
I want to see how someone
with such a smart mouth look like.
Show me your IG.
I don't normally use IG. I gotta
go. Bye. I I don't believe you.
You're done with work?
You're coming to the protest?
You go ahead, I'll go after.
This is a work of art!
Their fans must have loved you for this.
You think?
I'll give you more works.
Okay? I Sure.
Pour me with more works. I can do them all.
I gotta go. See you.
Be safe, bye. I Bye.
Hello, mom.
Where are you?
Are you going to the protest?
I'm at home.
See? I'm really at home.
You know that I'm worried about you, right?
I just don't want you to face what I faced.
Do you have enough money?
I can help you out.
Dream,
I really want you to go home.
You know what?
Your dad didn't want it to end up like this.
He didn't have a choice.
You should forgive him.
Cut him some slack.
What do you mean he didn't have a choice?
You got that ankle bracelet
because of him, you forgot already?
I can't pretend like nothing happened.
I should go.
I need to tell you that our
party concerned about this.
We received more complaints
from younger generations
who wanted to revise the bills
and the party concerned about it.
We're working on it.
We'll submit the draft to the parliament
next month so it can be some changes.
We focus on Prisoners of Conscience
and they need to be released.
In the future… I Liar!
Prisoners of Conscience can't
be punished because of this.
What do you think?
Well, I'm not good at this.
But aren't you supposed to like each other?
I watched it and I don't feel like you did.
It's not like you're not good at acting.
Actually, I thought
this could be better than this.
I miss being on stage in the play.
I could feel
the taste of freedom back then.
I was so happy.
You didn't really like
what you're doing right now?
I thought you enjoy doing it.
Actually,
I really love acting.
When they asked me to join the series,
I said yes immediately.
When I tried it, I just
acted as they told me to.
They said that
people are already happy when
they see me with Namkhang.
People are happy.
But are you happy?
My mom likes to say
if you want something, you
need to give something first.
I need to trade it.
To make people happy,
then people will make me happy in return.
Thank you for telling me this.
But why did you tell me?
I have no idea.
I just feel like you would
want to listen to me,
to understand me.
Do you remember what you once told me?
Do whatever you want.
You want to be in a play,
then you should ask them to be in one.
This could boost you up.
I'm coming all the way
here to listen to your song.
I know. I feel really confident about
it. That's why I told you to come.
Let's go up to my room.
Huh?
If I save it, then I can't revise it later.
Come on, let's go to my room.
Something like this.
That's so good.
Yeah? I It's cute.
But I think it should add something.
Which one do you think I should add?
What about that one on top? I Which one?
This one?
Not that one! I Which one?
Right, this one?
Hey,
what perfume did you use?
It smells so good.
You still can smell it?
It should be faded already.
Excuse me.
Nope, I still can smell it.
If you said so.
Tell me if you want more sounds.
Right, Bambi.
Honestly,
since we were apart,
I always wanted to meet you.
I tried to say hi to you.
But I didn't know what to say.
I didn't know how to start talking to you
until I met you at POPA.
I think it's destiny.
Bambi…
I…
Can I kiss you?
If you want something, you
need to give something first.
I need to trade it.
I really like the song
you just played for me.
Can I have this song?
Sure, you can.
Let's go recording this song.
Wow! So cute. Now I have
enough energy to record a song.
It's done!
You're the best. I'm ready to shoot an MV.
Let's get something to eat at Siam.
I'll finish class late, rain check?
Yay! Thank you so much. I really like it.
Do you like me?
I'll have a sweet dream tonight.
I Super cute, you little Bambi.
When will this song end? I've
been listening to it for 9 hours.
I followed from TikTok, Pure and
Namkhang's dance challenge is so cute.
Hello, everyone. I'm Bambi
I'd like to thank everyone for
using my song DM.
Please join dance challenge. See you later.
Are you okay? Why didn't you text me back?
Can I talk to you after the showcase?
You produced a song for a girl.
If you can't finish your
song, forget about the show.
Can you serve the noodles?
Mhong!
Look at this!
He asked a girl to be his
girlfriend. I Look at this.
In the middle of party. I Super cute.
I want a boyfriend like this. I I know.
I'd do anything.
It's hard to say no. Many
people are cheering them on.
So cute, look at that.
What're you looking at?
Where's Mhong?
Let's go. I don't want to be late.
What kind of song is this? I don't get it.
Let's go listening to the song in a car.
Can't. No more condoms.
I have.
Sure but can you stop bringing up Name?
Okay?
I don't really care about him. Let's go.
Alright everyone, for the next song,
I have a surprise for you.
His name isn't on the list, but
everyone knows him.
Please give it up for Mhongmuangthai.
Hello, everyone. I'm Mhongmuangthai.
I'm not here as an artist
but I'm here to express my feeling
to someone.
Without further ado, I'd like to ask
the singer of a song called DM to get up.
Get up!
Can you be my girlfriend?
Be his girlfriend!
You're my baby, my Bambi.
Can you be my girlfriend?
It's okay. It's alright, bro.
It's okay.
Bambi, hey!
What's going on?
What's wrong with you?
It's my fault.
I should have told you sooner.
Hey!
If you're not ready,
it's really okay.
We don't have to be official.
It's not about that.
Well, it's my fault to put
you in a spotlight like that.
But I really have deep feeling about you.
And I feel like you'd feel the same way
with signals you gave me.
What is it that you feel about me?
I don't feel that way with you.
I'm sorry for giving you mixed signals.
What do you mean?
I don't like you like that.
You don't?
If you don't like me,
then why did you did that?
I did everything for you, I
produced a song for you.
Say something!
Say something! Why did you did that?
Just tell me, what was it between us?
I'm sorry.
Can you please tell
me that you didn't do it
because you wanted a song?
Did you have any feeling for me?
Tell me! Say something!
Tell me that you have the same feeling.
I'm sorry.
I'm hurt.
Bambi.
Are you okay?
Stop crying.
I kissed Mhong because.
I just wanted his song.
If I want something, I need to
give something in return, right?
I didn't know that it'd feel shitty like this.
It's okay.
Let yourself feel this way.
Now you know how it feels.
So you won't repeat it again.
You're back?
How's the concert? I Let
me know if you need me
I was waiting for so
long. I I'm here with you.
You got flowers?
Did you film your performance?
I want to see it.
I want to know how your debut was.
Many people cheered you on?
I didn't film anything.
You can go to bed, I'll wash the dishes.
Well, I was waiting to see it.
Close up the shop after
you're done cleaning.
Got it.
I still want to be your friend.
If you want something, you
need to give something first.
To make people happy,
then people will make me happy in return.
You're free tonight?
I'm taking you somewhere.
Huh?
Do you think Tokyo act weirdly lately?
Right, he's in love right now.
Can I ask you something? You do know that
I really like you, right?
Bambi, you're too stiff.
Can you relax your face? Can I
get a smile without an actual smile?
Where's the picture?
Hey, Ms.Duangtawan is here.
Who is Ms.Duangtawan?