(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
HONG MIN-BEOM
Hello?
Yeah, I'll be there in ten minutes.
Director Hong, don't hang up the phone.
Just flip it over
and leave it on the table,
so I can listen in.
- You get what I'm saying, right?
Let me cut to the chase.
What are you doing?
Stop being a little bitch and sit still.
GANG-YONG
You there?
I'm right here, asshole.
What the hell are you trying to do?
Do you have a death wish?
You're making a big fucking mistake
right now, you stupid fucking asshole.
You might want to tell him to shut up.
Dude! Stop!
You're going to rot in a cell
for the rest of your life.
You motherfucker!
Fuck! Shut the hell up,
you fucking son of a bitch!
Jackass.
Have you calmed down?
I can't hear you.
Tell me what you want.
There's a report that came into
the Yeongmoonpo Police Department.
In a parking lot,
a guy on a motorcycle slashed a man's neck
and then got away.
Write this.
Seoul, Gangdong, A 6438.
No need to look it up.
It's a fake license plate.
Find out where
the guy on this motorcycle is hiding.
- Do you know how hard it is--
- I know it takes a long time.
That's why you'll do it.
It's 10:00 right now.
I'll give you five hours.
If you can't find him…
…your cousin's little striptease
will be online.
Try to pull something on me,
and it'll also find its way online.
If you don't want to see
lil Group's stock prices tank,
I suggest you do well.
Good luck.
What is it?
735629.
See you soon.
Fuck you!
BLOODHOUNDS
Hello, sir.
- Whoa, salute!
- Salute!
Soju's on me. I'm buying.
- This way, sir.
- Right, thank you.
- Sir.
- Hello.
They boil the bodies for days
until the bones get soft.
They grind them up
and pour them into the ocean.
It costs 15 million to do all that.
You couldn't find a bone.
Turning people into stew. Sick fucks.
Who told you that?
I visited Seung-deok in prison.
How does that punk know this
when he's locked up?
Prison is the best source
for information like this.
You guys all right back there?
- Yes, sir.
- Yes. We're all right, sir.
Seeing all that couldn't have been easy.
By the way, what will happen
when they open the casino?
What will happen?
Kim Myeong-gil will make lots of money.
- Oh.
- Gun-woo.
Sir.
Gambling and drug addicts
take out a lot of private loans.
Kim Myeong-gil connects the casino
with moneylending.
The more people visit his casino,
the more people will take out loans.
He'll just rake in easy money day by day.
But I thought
only foreigners could go to casinos.
Do you think
Kim Myeong-gil cares about the law?
He'll let all the big spenders in
through the back door.
They're not going to make any money
operating legally.
Once he's made enough money,
Kim Myeong-gil will buy a building
with a loan.
Then he'll use that building as collateral
for another loan to buy a bigger building.
Man.
That asshole's a real piece of work.
He'll go even harder running the casino
to pay back that loan.
And Smile Capital will squeeze
even more people dry.
It'll be the opening
of Kim Myeong-gil's personal kingdom.
The money Myeong-gil stole from me
back then was worth over 20 billion won
at the time.
Once we get it back,
how would you feel
about taking a trip around the world
with Gun-woo and Woo-jin, huh?
We have enough money as it is.
That's true.
And we can't travel because of COVID
True.
Why don't we go to Rome together?
Why Rome?
When I was 20,
I watched a film called Roman Holiday.
Back then, I vowed to go one day
when I made a lot of money,
but I haven't had the chance yet.
I thought it might be nice
to go with you all,
the three of you, you know?
If we go,
I'll buy you guys anything you want.
Grandpa, Italy is way too expensive.
It's the land of luxury.
Look, kid, I'm Choi Tae-ho, all right?
I'll show you how to really spend money.
Grandpa, that's called "flexing," okay?
Yeah, well, I'll show you flexing.
I'll do some big flexing.
Not big flexing. You just say "flex."
Flex.
So when this is over,
we'll all go together, okay?
Hello, sir.
That sounds good, sir.
Yes.
Hm. Mr. Choi invited us
for drinks at his place.
I guess he's in a pretty good mood.
Hey, you guys drink?
You know it!
Can we speed it up a little?
There's double
and quadruple-speed playback. Which one?
- Let's make it double.
- Got it.
If I was Kim Myeong-gil,
I would've thought to move the hard drive
to a safer location by now,
just in case
Im Jang-do revealed my weaknesses.
Do you think he can afford that?
We've boxed him into a corner.
He has no one left to help him now
except for that Mr. Jung guy.
Besides,
I don't think that
Kim Myeong-gil would trust just anyone.
He doesn't have to move it far.
He could hide it in the trunk of a car,
and we wouldn't find it.
- Hm.
- Kim Myeong-gil knows that.
You're right.
The tides would turn in our favor
if we manage to recruit an enemy of his
over to our side.
But to do that, we need the hard drive.
It should contain everything
about Myeong-gil's blackmail victims.
Those people share our motivations.
And there will be many powerful people,
like the heir of the Iil Group
mixed in with the bunch.
The longer this fight drags on,
the less likely we'll come out on top.
I'm sure Myeong-gil has made
a vast network of connections by now.
Every cop, prosecutor, and politician
that could be bought
is probably in his pocket by now.
We can't ever let our guard down,
or else we're finished.
Yeah.
But it's true we've taken down
three of his thugs, right?
It makes sense that we get anxious
when looking at the big picture,
but the way I see it,
I think we're doing pretty well.
I mean, no one's gotten hurt so far.
That's true.
Let's take things one at a time.
We can take Kim Myeong-gil down
and then his company.
Besides, now that Im Jang-do
and Kim Jun-min's out of the picture,
Kim Myeong-gil must be feeling
the noose tighten.
I guess she does have a point.
Mm…
Ah, yes, um,
Mr. Choi, sirs.
I would like to propose a toast
for everyone's safety and our shared goal.
When I say, "Find that hard drive
we will do,"
then you say,
"Kim Myeong-gil, you are through."
I'd appreciate it if you said it loud.
Let's get started. Raise your glasses.
Find that hard drive, yes we do.
- Kim Myeong-gil.
- You are through!
I'm on my way over
to Joongang Police Station.
Those assholes moved
from Dongpa-gu to Joongang-gu.
Can you find them by 3:00?
I'll find them soon
if they stopped in Joongang-gu,
but if they crossed over,
I'll have to keep looking, I guess.
Please, bro.
Don't worry about it.
We'll do what the bastard wants for now.
Once we make it past this,
I'll think of a way to fuck this guy up.
Thank you. Seriously.
Min-beom,
you think I'd just let some asshole
mess with my family like this?
It'll be fine.
Okay?
You're all I have right now.
Don't drink too much, okay?
Mm.
Jeez.
Why did he drink so much
if he's such a lightweight?
I guess
he was in a pretty good mood today.
I'm going to bed. What about you?
I'm going to head back downstairs.
- Aren't you tired?
- Not really.
Good work today.
Yeah.
Gun-woo.
Gun-woo?
You're not asleep?
No, why are you awake?
Oh, everyone is downstairs having a drink.
You're drinking too?
Mm-mm. Not me.
Good.
I guess I'll make hangover soup
in the morning.
Great. Get some sleep.
I'll close the door.
Okay, sleep tight.
Good night, Mom.
God, it's been so long
since we drank together.
Mm.
Is it a woman?
Who would call you this late at night?
Tell me.
Hey…
I'm going to be a dad.
When?
In two months. It's a girl.
We've been together for three years now.
Hey, man, if you had family,
you should've told me, you idiot.
Then you would've told me not to come.
Go home now. I'll wrap things up here.
It's been so long
since we had a drink together.
I want to stay.
I said go home.
Oh, don't be mad.
Here.
No, I'm good.
It's not for you. Get your wife some meat.
She needs iron right now. Come on.
It's too much.
Aren't you coming downstairs?
Yeah, I'm coming.
- I'll go on ahead.
- Sure.
Call a cab.
I'll have another smoke
until it gets here.
Hey.
Thank you.
Don't make it weird.
You're the best, you know?
I'm going to get some hanwoo
on my way back.
Oh.
Hyeon-ju says she's going to bed early.
Hm.
Are you all right?
Yes.
You seem really worried right now, sir.
I'm the one who taught Myeong-gil.
He's my responsibility.
But when my body… broke down,
I couldn't fight him.
The only thing
that I could manage
was taking care of Hyeon-ju.
Who are you?
Oh, I--
I'm a friend
of your father's.
Oh no. Don't cry. Don't cry.
Hey.
Papa!
CONDOLENCES
Sorry for your loss.
Get the best condolence flowers you can,
then fill up the room with them.
Yes, sir.
Have ten men guard the place
until they're done moving the coffin
to the grave site.
- Should we arm them?
- Uh, no.
It's for the child.
She's doing the wake alone.
And let's get her some food.
Yes, sir.
Sir, I think you left your scarf inside.
Oh, don't worry about it.
Why on earth did he kill himself?
He delivered papers in the morning,
made parts at a factory,
and worked as a chauffeur at night.
He got just three hours of sleep every day
for two years working graveyard shifts
to save his daughter.
Then his child gets better,
and he kills himself?
I just don't get it.
I told him
that I didn't need any interest.
He just had to pay back the principal,
and I'd give him an extension
if he ever needed more time.
Um, I'll look into it.
I just don't understand.
Here.
Third floor.
Excuse me.
Jesus.
Are you, by chance, on your way
to Mr. Cha Sang-ho's funeral?
Yes.
Two years ago, when I got surgery
and couldn't lift things,
Hyeon-ju's dad would take out the trash
for me for three months.
God, he was the nicest,
hardest-working person around.
I felt so bad for Hyeon-ju.
That poor little thing sick
without a mother around.
I used to feed her
and fill up their fridge,
so they didn't run out things to eat.
Why would he kill himself
now that Hyeon-ju has gotten better?
It's because of the loan shark bastards!
They used to come over
whenever they pleased,
grabbing him by the neck
and beating him. God--
What did they look like?
Uh, well,
one was almost the size of a brown bear.
The other one was tall, incredibly tall.
One month later,
another person I had lent money to
killed themselves.
It was also someone
I had given an interest-free loan
because of a sick family member.
I'm going home too soon.
Watch the stairs.
Ah, my brother.
I'll go now.
- Get home safe.
- Okay.
Good night.
Yang-jung found out later
that the people
that I had given those loans
for their family's medical expenses
had been visited by Myeong-gil.
He was going around taking several million
in loan extension fees from them
every month,
telling them
that he was following my orders.
My mom fell for the same trick.
He hid a clause in the fine print
within the contract.
Oh.
I'm so sorry.
A lot of people got hurt because of me.
That's not true.
You don't need to feel sorry
for what happened to us, Mr. Choi.
I think you have a strong sense
of responsibility,
which is why you feel so much guilt.
Those who are truly shameless
feel no guilt whatsoever.
They always blame others
and prey on people weaker than them.
But I think the only reason
why we're all gathered here today
is because of the goodwill you've spread
throughout the years.
I don't think Hyeon-ju knows
that you bought the orphanage for her,
but I'm sure
she will always believe in you
with all her heart.
We'll work together
and bring Kim Myeong-gil down
no matter what.
So please stop blaming yourself,
and please take care of your health, sir.
When we're done, I'll set you up
with your own private boxing gym.
That should help you focus
on your training
until you eventually become a champion.
And I'll build a nice big café
for your mom on the ground floor.
No rent until the day I die.
Wow.
What, you don't know what to say
all of a sudden?
No.
A thank you would do.
Oh.
Thank you so much, Mr. Choi.
No.
I'm the one that should be thanking you.
You're teaching me
what youth is all about.
This is…
flex!
Right?
Yes.
- Let's take a look over there.
- Here?
- No, no. Next to it.
- Oh, all right.
- How about up there? That part.
- All right. Thank you.
- Okay.
Good job.
GANG-YONG
- Yes.
- Onyu-ro 88.
Will that do?
Thank you very much.
- Let's go.
- Yes, sir!
Look.
President Choi is on crutches.
Hm.
They tortured him.
Did he rat us out?
I'm not sure, sir.
Hm.
It's much safer for us to assume he did.
Let's get President Choi.
Then Jang-do.
Yes, sir.
Um, sir.
LEE DU-YEONG
Make sure you don't kill the guy.
I need information.
Yes, sir.
- And take off that thing.
- Oh.
Mm.
Honey.
Someone's at the door.
Who is it?
Uh, I'm from downstairs.
I'm here because there's water leaking
from our ceiling.
Would you mind
if I came in to check your bathroom?
I promise this won't take long.
It's just
that our house is flooded right now.
Our kids haven't gotten any sleep
because of this.
I would really appreciate it.
Right now?
Yes, it won't take long.
I'll just check your bathroom.
- Honey?
- Hm?
- Who is it?
- He says water is leaking downstairs.
- Move over, honey.
- Huh?
Move over.
Shh.
Huh?
- Just a second.
- Okay.
Listen to me.
Call the cops now and report a burglary.
- Why?
- I'll explain later.
You trust me, right?
Yes.
And also,
no matter what,
do not open the door, you hear me?
Okay.
Mm-hm.
It's all right, honey.
Nothing's going to happen. It's all right.
Okay.
Dongjak-gu, Samjin-dong.
Please, please!
Hurry. My husband's in danger.
- Come on, come on. Let's go.
- Get in there. Go.
Where is he?
Whoa! Shit.
Go, go, go! Go!
Hm.
Tell me where to find Hwang Yang-jung,
and I'll let your girl live.
I always keep my promises
with no exceptions.
Trust me.
- Did you sleep well, Mr. Choi?
- I did.
Did you sleep well?
- Like a baby.
- Me too.
Hey, sit down.
Hey, so this is a first for us.
Yes, we should do this more.
Dude, get up now. Hm.
Let's eat.
- Oh, wow. Thank you.
- Oh, of course.
- Mm. Yeah.
- Here.
- He's not coming?
- He won't get up.
God, you should've told him to eat
and then sleep.
He got his fill last night, didn't he?
Yes.
All that big talk
about being a good drinker.
- Then let's eat.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for this meal.
- Please enjoy.
Whoa!
- Mm. Um, Gun-woo.
- Yes, sir?
When are you taking your mother
to the orphanage?
I can do it.
Let me borrow your car, Grandpa.
It's been outside for a while.
Someone might've seen it, so be careful.
- I'll be okay.
- All right.
Do you wanna go after we eat?
This time of day,
we should make it there in an hour.
Mom, that work for you?
Uh, to be honest,
I think I… I would feel a lot better
if I just stayed here
and kept preparing meals for everyone.
Mrs. Yoon.
Uh, I don't mean to impose,
but would you mind helping out
at our orphanage?
It's just that
your cooking skills are really impressive…
I think the children would love it.
Mrs. Yoon, this food is just amazing.
Mom, I also think
that would be for the best.
- Well, okay if it helps you in any way.
- That's great. Thank you so much.
Yes.
So you're not going to be skipping meals,
you promise?
Mm-hm.
Please stay safe, sweetie.
Don't worry so much, okay?
Mm.
I won't. I believe in my son.
HWANGSUSA
SECURITY DISABLED
Min-dong.
How did you find me?
Well,
Lee Du-yeong told me.
Did you do something to his girl?
Whoa, whoa.
You kill them?
Let's go.
Come on. Go.
Mr. Choi!
Kim Myeong-gil's thugs are outside.
What are you talking about?
Let's go to the basement.
There's a gun down there.
I'll stay behind.
Hurry up and go get the gun.
- Go!
- No, Woo-jin!
- Damn it!
- Woo-jin, get out of there.
Woo-jin!
Get in there.
No!
Go fuck him up!
Woo-jin!
Go, go, go!
You're dead, motherfucker!
Let's get him.
Get in there!
Out of the way!
Woo-jin! Woo-jin!
Woo-jin!
Sir.
- Where is he?
- This way, sir.
Get pouring, you two.
- Yes, sir.
groaning
Blood, ugh.
Well done.
You are actually…
someone I'm grateful for.
Hey, over here.
You see,
you gave me a dream.
You…
That's why…
…I'm going to make this painless.
Oh, it's all right.
It'll be over quick. It's all right.
You won't feel anything.
Yeah, there.
It's all right. Ah, it's all right.
Mm.
Gun-woo.
- Try the back door.
- Okay.
Woo-jin!
No!
Hyeon-ju!
Jesus, Hyeon-ju!
Just hold on.
Grandpa.
Grandpa! Grandpa!
Oh God, Grandpa.
Grandpa!
Get up, please. You're not dead.
Oh God! No, no! Gun-woo!
Gun-woo, come! Gun-woo!
Grandpa, please get up.
Please, please help. Please, please.
Grandpa.
- We need to get out, Hyeon-ju.
- No!
- We have to get out! Hurry!
- No, no. We can't! Let go!
If you stay here, you'll die too!
Grandpa! Grandpa!
Let go of me!
Scalpel.
Suction! Some more gauze, please.
- What's the patient's status?
- BP's 80/50!
Starting blood transfusion!
We're short on blood because of COVID.
We'll need to get it elsewhere.
Get us as much as you can somehow.
Clip!
- Then what do we do?
- His other legal guardian--
What is it?
They're saying
they don't have enough blood for Woo-jin.
- Oh, God.
- What's your blood type?
- It's Type A.
- Come with me.
I promise I'll save Woo-jin
no matter what, so don't worry. Okay?
Okay.
He's losing a lot of blood.
Please, we need more blood now!
We need more gauze.
I need it now. Please hurry.
All done.
Is this enough to save Hong Woo-jin?
No, I think we'll need a couple more bags.
Oh.
Okay, then let me
just fill up another one please.
We've already gotten too much.
More would put you at risk.
Oh, don't worry about it. I'm a boxer.
It'll take more than this to kill me.
- It's fine.
- I'm sorry. I can't
Listen to me.
I really, really have to save him. Please.
Please just let me fill up another one.
- Please, I'm begging you.
- I really can't.
This won't kill me, really.
Please,
I have to save Woo-jin.
I have to save him.
I really won't die.
Please, I'm begging you.
I'm begging you. Please, please.
I can't see due to the blood.
- Suction!
- Applying suction.
I can't control the bleeding.
Please prepare the Surgicel.
Surgicel ready.
Keep it coming.
I'll be needing more.
Blood pressure dropping.
Please hurry. Hurry!