=Eight Hundred=
(Months ago)
Chen Hui,
several people have told me before
that this stuff
tastes a bit like plastic.
There won't be any problems, right?
How could it taste like plastic?
I don't know either.
It's the taste of this water.
From now on, before we ship out,
wash the goods with clean water first.
Got it.
=Episode 11=
(Happy Birthday)
(Efficient and Pragmatic,
Fair and Honest)
Here.
This isn't right.
What is this?
Even the thickness is different.
I heard there's been a major discovery.
Director Tong, hurry.
Hongbing,
is all of this evidence
you brought back?
Yes.
We found it
in the old coal washing plant.
But we don't know
what this foam
was used for.
How did you track it
to the coal washing plant?
Director Tong,
that day,
when I saw the rainbow glow
on the cough syrup bottle,
I felt like I'd seen it
somewhere before.
Then, I remembered,
it was at the old coal washing plant.
In the past, the old plant
always used
polyacrylamide
as a flocculant.
Gao Ying's father
developed a skin disease
from long-term exposure to it.
Later, the plant's technology
was upgraded,
new equipment was brought in,
and that's why the old plant
was abandoned.
I see.
Have all the drugs
at the scene been counted?
They have.
The quantity is massive.
It gave me a shock.
How many?
Five hundred bottles.
Five hundred bottles?
So many?
Have people been assigned
to stake out the scene?
After the discovery,
I told our big guy to stake it out.
Lin just headed over too,
he should be there by now.
We'll do three shifts a day.
Tomorrow, I'm going to the city
to give a special report
to the municipal PSB leadership
about the situation here.
Director Tong,
this is our only lead right now.
We can only follow this line
and see where it leads.
Indeed.
Director Chen, it's pieced together.
What was this used to hold?
Tomorrow, send everyone
from the station out.
All of us, go and investigate.
We must find out
what this thing
was actually for.
Boss, have you seen
packaging like this in the photo?
Do we have this product
in this type of packaging in our store?
Never seen it.
This packaging wouldn't be for medicine.
Go to the electronics shop next door
and ask Wang.
Electronics?
(Xiaojian Home Appliances)
Right? See how the picture looks?
Isn't it much better
than that black-and-white one?
I just got it in.
(High-End Customization)
(Raojiang Radio Company
Welcomes All Customers)
This looks about the same
as this one, right?
This should be
an imported VCD player.
They were quite popular
in Jin'gang a couple of years ago.
I don't have any in stock now.
Could you give me
a copy of this manual?
Sure.
Great, thanks.
(Jiangbin Municipal People's Hospital)
Wang Dayu, come in.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Sorry, I didn't hurt you, did I?
No.
(Danshen Injection)
Officer Liu.
Songge?
Thank you.
Are you all right, Officer Liu?
I'm fine.
Are you here for dialysis?
I just finished my session.
I'll stay with you for a while.
All right.
Hui
didn't come with you?
He went back to town today
to hand over the roller skating rink.
Officer Liu,
I want to ask you a question.
Go ahead.
About what you said last time,
viewing life and death
with indifference...
How did you find
such great courage?
Songge,
let me ask you.
Do you love Hui?
Of course.
To protect him,
would you be afraid of dying?
No.
Actually, I'm just like you.
Choosing to face all this alone
is also to protect
the people I love.
But you've distanced yourself from them.
When they find out the truth later,
won't they be even more heartbroken?
Perhaps.
Or maybe by then,
they will have already forgotten me.
Officer Liu,
is there anything
I can do for you?
For me?
In my current state,
I might also have to face
the same situation as you someday.
I think
we are people
who can understand each other.
Now, I just want every day
to be fulfilling
and happy.
To have new experiences every day.
I like your open-mindedness.
Only then do I feel
that I'm truly alive.
(Yingxiong Roller Skating Rink)
Rental contract,
business license,
(Party B Signature)
and fire safety permit are all here.
Thank you, Hui.
I'll transfer the final payment
to you tomorrow.
- Dad.
- Mr. Chen.
Hello.
You brat, you didn't even say
you were coming back.
I could've had your mom
cook something nice
and had dinner at home.
Dad, I have to go back
as soon as I'm done here.
There's so much to do
for the internet cafe's opening.
Isn't it Mom's birthday tomorrow?
Songge and I will be back then.
Your mother really misses you.
- I know.
- Boss, where should I put this?
Just put it here. Be careful.
You're putting a VCD player here?
I plan to make this place
look like a small bar.
People can watch TV or something
when they're free.
This looks like
an imported VCD player.
They were quite popular
in Jin'gang a couple of years ago.
But I
don't have any in stock now.
Hui,
where did you buy
this VCD player?
A friend in Jin'gang gave it to me.
It must have been expensive, right?
It's second-hand.
A JVC 717.
A brand-new one cost over
ten thousand back then.
It's outdated now.
It's not worth much.
In all of Fengyang,
there probably isn't a second one.
You still remember, right?
We both discussed this.
When it's your mother's birthday,
we would give her a VCD player.
You haven't forgotten, have you?
I remember.
I think this is pretty good.
Such an expensive item,
and your mother and I
haven't even enjoyed it yet.
It's fine, Hui.
If your parents like it,
just take it with you.
Thank you.
It's nothing, Mr. Chen.
Then, according to our accounts,
just give me two thousand less.
Fine.
Where is the packaging box?
Let's pack it up.
It's just a short walk.
Why do you need a packaging box?
If it's packed nicely,
it'll give your mother a fresh feeling.
Won't she be happy?
It's second-hand, Dad.
Who knows where
the packaging went long ago?
Alright, go look for it. Hurry up.
No need, trust me.
You won't find it.
The junk collector
keeps an eye on me every day.
Plastic bottles,
beer bottles, cardboard boxes...
He collects them every day.
Look at you, Hui.
How about this, Mr. Chen?
I'll help you find an empty box
so it's easier for you
to take home. Okay?
We have empty boxes. I'll go find one.
- Thank you.
- I'm going to look now.
Thank you.
(People's Public Security)
(Evidence Box)
Director Chen,
is this the one you're looking for?
This is it.
May I use it for a bit?
Sure.
Just sign here,
and you can take it.
(Chen Hongbing)
What is it for?
JVC 717.
In all of Fengyang,
there probably isn't a second one.
Hui, hurry up.
You sell tube popsicles here too?
Thirty yuan?
Mine are only one-fifty each.
This bag is so dirty,
yet you're still carrying it.
Why is there blood on it?
- Dad.
- Why are you here?
I came to find you.
Director Chen.
It's me.
(Lu Yuan)
I always feel that these people
are always one step ahead of us.
The day of your accident,
what did Huo Kaiming
say to you?
(Fengyang Town Police Station
Manpower Distribution Map)
I just hope
that our family
can be harmonious and happy.
Son,
I have no choice.
I'm a policeman.
Do you hate me?
For you,
I would do anything.
I want you
to be happy
for your whole lives.
(Third Police District)
(Efficient and Pragmatic,
Fair and Honest)
You're here so early.
Director Tong.
What's wrong?
Why do you look so pale?
I
didn't go home last night.
You were here
all night?
Why?
What happened?
It's the VCD player.
You found it?
Where was it found?
At
Hui's roller skating rink.
Director Tong,
this way,
the suspicion against Hui
cannot be ruled out.
Now, I can only
apply for recusal.
Wait a minute.
Even if that foam
belongs to Hui,
it can't be considered
direct evidence, right?
When anyone buys an appliance,
don't they just throw
the plastic wrap away?
Our station's situation
is unique.
You know this.
We're too short-staffed,
and the area we cover is so complicated.
Regarding this case,
besides you,
I really can't find
the right person to investigate
in such a short time.
Then, find a newcomer.
Hongbing,
find a newcomer?
It's not that easy.
In our Fengyang,
it's only an 800-meter radius area.
If they argue in the east,
they'll hear it in the west.
If a new face shows up,
everyone in the town will know.
How would you investigate?
Director Tong, then what
do you want me to do?
How about this?
Come with me to the city again.
We'll report to the Bureau leadership
and see what they think.
Sound good?
It's settled. Let's go.
No.
Director Tong,
I...
I have one more request.
Go ahead.
This machine,
can I take it back?
Why?
Today is Ding Yue's birthday.
I told my son
that this was a gift for his mother.
I'm afraid that when Hui gets back
and doesn't see this thing,
it'll be trouble
if he gets any other ideas.
We'll do as you say.
Thank you.
Hongbing.
Dude.
Tell me
what I should do.
(People's Public Security)
Leaders,
(Jiangbin Public Security)
that's exactly how
everything happened.
Mr. Chen Hongbing,
please wait outside for a moment.
(Pinglin West Street)
Mr. Chen Hongbing
is a veteran police officer.
In his 20-plus years of service,
he has always worked very hard.
His ability and achievements
are obvious to everyone.
But in this case,
the subject of the investigation involves
his son.
We can't be arbitrary,
nor can we be sentimental.
Therefore, I believe
we need to discuss this further.
We've arrived at the city bus station.
For Fengyang or Ping County,
get off here.
(There is no way out for violations.
Reform through hard work for a new life)
Hongbing,
how come you're here?
Why am I here?
Because I missed you.
I should have come to see you sooner.
At the station and at home,
there's just too much going on.
I couldn't get away.
I brought you two cartons of cigarettes.
What's wrong with you?
Are you sick?
It's nothing. Just when I was out
working a few days ago,
I worked up a sweat
and caught a chill in the wind.
I've just got a bit of a cold.
Did you take medicine?
I did.
I'll be fine in a couple of days.
Hongbing,
you don't look very well.
Did something happen?
What could happen to me?
Nothing's wrong. I just missed you,
so I came to see you.
Right,
there's a question
I've been wanting to ask you.
Ask away.
Do you hate me?
Why would I hate you?
Why don't you hate me?
Let me put it this way.
I'm the one who made a mistake.
It's not like you
framed me to get me in here.
Tell me.
If one day,
I meet a friend,
and our relationship
is just like ours,
if he does something illegal,
and I arrest him
and process him,
will he think the same way you do?
Will he?
That's hard to say.
First,
he has to be someone
who sees things clearly.
If he's a muddled person,
he'll only hate you even more.
See things clearly...
Dad.
Hongbing.
What is it?
Even though you don't say it,
I know in my heart
that something must have happened.
We grew up together.
I know what kind of person
you are very well.
You're good to your family
and loyal to your friends.
No one would think ill of you.
Take me for example.
My lawyer told me
that if I hadn't turned myself in
and hadn't gone with you
to catch Ma Heping,
I'd be facing
at least seven or eight years.
So, for this,
I should actually thank you.
Grandpa.
You're back?
I'm back.
- You're back.
- Mom.
Where's Songge?
She's getting dialysis.
The hospital is busy today,
so she'll probably be back quite late.
But she didn't forget
to prepare a birthday gift for you.
Let me see what it is.
This has our contact information.
It's even a refrigerator magnet.
Look, Mom.
This way, you can reach us
anytime, anywhere.
This is really convenient.
Songge is so thoughtful.
I'm almost done here.
Go wash your hands.
Songge is more than just thoughtful.
The cake is sugar-free.
She spent two days looking for it.
It's because she was worried
that Dad and Grandpa couldn't have sugar.
Songge has been attentive
since she was a child.
When you two live in the city together,
take good care of each other.
If you need anything,
just take it from home.
Mom, if you're worried about us,
just come visit us more often.
Now,
I finally understand.
Since ancient times,
parents haven't been able
to control their children's affairs.
As long as you think it's right,
just keep moving forward.
Mom,
don't worry.
We'll make something of ourselves.
Of course, you will.
You're my son, after all.
Get me two plates.
Okay.
Alright, that's about it.
Your dad will be home soon.
Go tell Grandpa it's time to eat.
Grandpa?
Grandpa.
Time to eat.
Hearing aid?
I'll go find it for you.
Director Tong,
I'm back.
Just arrived in Fengyang.
It's Ding Yue's birthday today.
Hui is back too.
With everything that's happened lately,
I'm very worried about this kid.
So I'm thinking of feeling him out
later while we're eating.
Do you think that's appropriate?
Grandpa,
your hearing aid.
Mom?
Dad didn't set up
the VCD player for you?
Can I ever count on him for anything?
He brought it back
and just left it by the door.
The amplifier and the VCD player
were brought back in two separate trips.
I just stuffed them
under your grandpa's bed.
Since you're home today,
can you help me set it up?
Sure.
Where's the VCD player?
It's not under the bed.
Maybe it's in the storage room?
Go check it out.
Several people have told me before
that this stuff tastes
a bit like plastic.
There won't be any problems, right?
It's just the taste of the water.
Where's the packaging box?
Let's wrap it up.
It's second-hand, Dad.
The packaging is long gone.
Director Tong, you heard
what I said clearly, right?
Where's Hui? Where did he go?
I don't know.
He just said he'd help me
with the VCD player,
then he ran out without a word.
You didn't even change your shoes.
Where are you going?
Hongbing, the food is ready.
Come and eat.
Where are you going?
I'll be back in a bit.
Let me make a call.
Big guy,
it's Chen Hongbing.
My phone died.
Listen carefully. Bring a few people
to the washing pool
at the coal washing plant.
Yes, right now.
(Golden Peony)
(Heyi Coal Washing Plant, Fengyang Town)
Dad,
let's not wait anymore.
I'll get you some soup.
Ding Yue,
I...
I want to wish you
a happy birthday first.
Thanks, Dad.
For over 20 years,
this family
only felt like a home
because of you.
In the days ahead,
I'll still have to rely on you.
Don't let this family
fall apart.
Dad,
don't you worry.
Let's eat.
Hurry and drink your soup.
Otherwise, it'll get cold.
Okay.
Good.