(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 32=
(Three days later)
You're not what you used to be.
Fine.
I'll give you some more days to recover.
He Simu,
you'll never get the truth
you've been seeking.
Why didn't you tell me
before you returned this time?
I would have welcomed you.
You are well-informed.
You came when I just arrived.
Simu,
when you're back this time,
you look different.
Very good.
It's been centuries.
Congratulations on getting your beloved.
Simu,
the mist in your eyes is gone.
Since when did I have that?
Every spirit
has a specific obsession.
He knows why he lives
and why he disappears.
Even though those are not
very decent obsessions.
But Simu,
you're born a spirit.
There was always a mist in your eyes.
Now,
your heart is finally settled.
I'm really happy for you.
Yan Ke must not know this.
He has feelings for you.
What if his love grows into hate?
He might hurt your man. Be careful.
But it's all right.
Recently,
he's been terribly busy.
He travels between the two worlds.
No time for jealousy.
Why does he go to the Mortal World?
We don't know why,
but for a few months,
no spirits came from Shuozhou.
We thought some spirits
wanted to linger there.
So we sent Spirit Officials.
But they didn't find anything unusual.
After that, Yan Ke went many times
to Shuozhou to investigate.
Shuozhou.
(Sovereign's Hall)
When did Her Grace come back?
Who knows?
Her Grace loved excitement.
But now she has returned
so quietly.
Anything abnormal often means trouble.
We must be careful.
Greetings, Your Grace.
You may rise.
In the Mortal World,
I executed a sinner
who was on the run for years.
It's the Lord of Jiling Temple,
Song Xingyu.
Song Xingyu?
He manipulated mortals,
interfered with mortal affairs,
and violated our decrees.
I executed him on the spot
and annihilated him.
I hope all of you
will take this as a warning.
How wise you are, Your Grace.
Yan Ke,
you're in charge of the North Abyss.
How is everything?
Sorry for my poor supervision.
Three days ago, it was hit
by an undersea earthquake.
There was a partial collapse.
Some spirits have been trapped.
- Now...
- It collapsed?
We are still searching for them.
Why didn't you report this
until I asked you?
Don't be angry, Your Grace.
Not many spirits are missing.
And I'm sparing no effort
in searching for them.
Punish me as you wish.
Yan Ke,
I gave you the right
to supervise the Void,
but you did a poor job,
causing some spirits to suffer.
This is your first sin.
Second,
you showed no respect
and decided without my permission.
Acting on your own
is the sin of usurpation.
You'll be flogged 50 times
and grounded ten days.
Immediately.
Your Grace,
thank you for the punishment.
It's just a little problem.
Isn't the punishment too harsh?
Her Grace decides
who to punish or whether to punish him.
Simu,
I've prepared new entertainment for you.
You'll love it.
I'd like to see
how much you care about that mortal.
(Shuozhou)
(Chongxing Store)
So that's it.
(Liang)
Xu,
I sneaked into Youzhou and scouted.
The Chong's deployments vary
in the morning, noon, and evening.
I sketched three versions
of their deployments.
The one in the evening
is the same as what you saw last time.
But it varies greatly
in the other two periods.
Very good.
All we need is Xia Qingsheng's backup.
When will he be back?
News came this morning.
Commandant Xia
recruited troops smoothly in Shenzhou.
Now, he's on his way back.
I guess soon,
he will join us.
Where's Han Lingqiu?
General Tang of the uprising army
needs backup in Jingzhou.
Captain Han has gone there
to meet with him.
He left a few days ago.
You two just missed each other.
I was just wondering
why you were so happy these days.
So you're free from his supervision.
You can slack off
instead of practicing.
I'm not slacking off.
I've brought you something urgent.
Let me handle it.
What's this heavy thing?
Luoxian
had it delivered urgently.
It's said to be a present
for Xu.
Xu,
she said the remaining 13 prefectures
were all on this map.
With Luozhou as a foothold,
spy centers were set up
and named Ziwei.
This map is created
based on the intelligence
from all the centers
in 17 Prefectures.
- Great.
- Nice.
It's...
Impressive.
(Enjoy the Beauty)
General Duan,
you're a hero to Shuozhou.
Mr. Lin is away on business,
but he ordered us
to clean out his residence
where you can live.
To welcome you, our prefect
prepared some excellent wine
and had it delivered to your troops.
Please accept it.
According to our prefect,
if you aren't satisfied
with today's wine,
he'll have new wine delivered tomorrow.
He'll continue
until you're satisfied.
Bring my thanks to him.
I'll have a good taste
of the wine he's sent.
I'll take my leave.
I was ordered to serve you, General.
Then why are you lowering your head?
I can't even see
what you look like.
I...
Let me serve you, General.
Do you know who I am?
General Duan.
My name, I mean.
My name is Duan Xu.
Duan Shunxi.
Stop it.
Simu.
How come you can always recognize me?
I see that look
when you wish to be recognized.
I was passing by,
so I came to see you.
I made you an amulet.
Take it with you.
All right.
Let me put it on you.
The war may be dangerous,
but you needn't have come
in person.
General Duan,
hidden dangers are harder to avoid.
There are problems
you mortals can't solve.
If you're in serious trouble,
remember to summon me.
Guards!
No need.
They can no longer
hear you.
Mu'ertu,
do you hate to see me this much?
You're merely an ousted Young Priest.
What do you want?
I came here
to tell you one thing.
Seventeen, you've been yearning for...
He's back.
Now he's the general of the Liang Army,
Duan Xu.
He's from Great Liang?
Duan Xu ruined my father and me.
Just like you,
I want him dead.
Let's work together.
The All-Knowing...
They were here.
Who was here?
Any word of Han Lingqiu?
A message came yesterday.
He joined General Tang in Jingzhou.
What a wonderful trap to catch him!
I think General Tang
has been corrupted by the Chong Army.
He pretended to need backup.
When we reached Jingzhou,
he'd work with our enemy
to annihilate us.
But Captain Han is in Jingzhou.
With only a few soldiers.
Han Lingqiu may have been detained.
Meng Wan,
ride to the Tabai Army
and tell them
not to trust Han Lingqiu's orders.
Without my command,
no troops can enter Jingzhou.
Yes.
Commandant Wu.
Lead 50,000 soldiers.
You leave right now.
Within three days,
take four cities southwest of Jingzhou.
Don't worry, General.
Count on me.
Nothing will go wrong.
I'll teach them a good lesson.
Qingsheng,
lead 10,000 elite soldiers.
Within three days,
take two eastern cities.
These cities are all occupied
by the Chong Army.
Once you take them,
you'll cut the connection
between Jingzhou and Chong.
I won't let you down.
What about Han?
Trapped in the enemy camp,
he will definitely be used
as a hostage.
We'll save him, right?
Of course we will.
But we won't use our troops.
You focus on the war.
I'll rescue him.
But...
- Yes.
Han Lingqiu.
Wake up.
Leave with me.
It's you.
Why didn't you kill me back then?
Why did you save me instead?
Why did you erase my memories?
Why?
And why did I
get back my memories?
Your memories are back?
Han Lingqiu,
think clearly.
Open your eyes and look at me.
I'm Duan Xu.
You're Han Lingqiu.
We're comrades who fight together
instead of the All-Knowing assassins.
I have no time to argue now.
Just go with me.
Duan Xu.
Han Lingqiu.
Mentor,
how have you been?
Congratulations.
You've finally caught me.
You saved him once.
Why did you come to save him again?
Why?
Maybe for the same reason
that I didn't kill you back then.
That's the compassion
you've always despised.
I taught you everything,
the martial arts,
and the techniques.
And I killed all the people
you asked me to kill!
Some are noble while some are humble.
How could you betray me
for humble ones?
Mentor,
there isn't an answer
to everything in this world.
But I can tell you this.
Seventeen, your once favorite disciple...
His obedience,
attachment,
fervor, and devotion were all fake!
Always fake.
I hate everything about the All-Knowing.
And I never think it's an honor
to be Seventeen.
The truth is,
I've never believed
in a single god.
I was the one
who pulled myself
out of all that misery.
The god's power only exists
when I believe in him.
So the god's power...
Is actually my power.
Cangshen won't forgive
such sacrilegious words!
Didn't you hear?
Leave with me now.
Or will you stay and be a slave?
You should have been Seventeen!
He's a traitor
with sinister motives.
He wasn't even qualified for the Trial.
He ruined your life,
led you down the wrong path,
and made you serve your enemy!
You should
hate him most!
Then why didn't you kill me back then?
Why did you save me?
Why?
Catch him!
Kill!
(Oh no.)
Kill him.
Simu.
I'm taking you away.
Han Lingqiu.
Take him away.
You were just in time, Your Grace.
If I hadn't sensed
the amulet's abnormality,
you would
have been killed.
Are you so worried about me?
Don't act pitiful to fool me.
Let me ask you.
What's wrong with your body?
What does that mean?
Your senses
have been fading.
Don't overthink it, Simu.
Mortals grow old.
All the senses
fade as well.
That's normal.
If you're tired of me now,
what happens when I'm old?
Will you really argue with a sick man?
Your health...
Is it really all right?
Don't worry.
By the way...
Simu,
did you kill some mortals?
I kind of saw you do it.
Foxy,
you saw it wrong.
Sleep now.
When you wake up, see a doctor.
Take your medicine.
Promise me.
Even when you're on the battlefield,
you can't charge forward,
regardless of safety.
You must treasure your life.
Understand?
Simu.
What's wrong?
I should go.
Foxy,
wait until I return.
Jiang Ai.
Simu, what happened?
It has
Bai Sanxing's aura.
Yes.
I refined his soul candle
into this.
When you hold it,
he'll take your orders.
Simu,
what do you want me to do
with this thing?
It's not what I want you to do,
but what you truly want to do.
Lady Jiang Ai,
you must be cautious from now on.
Greetings, Your Grace.
For what reason have you summoned us
so urgently?
According to our decrees,
how should a spirit be punished
for interfering with mortals
and killing mortals?
According to Article 1, Section 1
of 32 Golden-wall Decrees,
he deserves the harshest punishment,
regardless of the extent of his power.
I killed mortals in the Mortal World.
- What...
- By law...
Punish me according to our decrees.
Don't do that, Your Grace.
If you're punished for violation,
our world will fall into chaos!
I uphold the decrees for my father.
If I weren't punished,
our world would be in chaos.
But...
Yan Ke, what do you think
I should do?
Considering your power,
it's easy for you to kill spirits.
But it's hard to make them
obey you.
If you defend the Golden-wall Decrees
and uphold your father's justice,
I beg you to set an example
and take your punishment
by our decrees.
His Lordship...
Didn't he...?
Why did he say that?
I interfered with mortal affairs
and killed mortals.
By the Golden-wall Decrees,
I shall relinquish the Book of Spirits,
stop using the Lantern,
and take the harshest punishment.
Unexpectedly, Her Grace
was harsh on others,
and harsher on herself.
Spirits are born free.
Her Grace is the Sovereign.
She sacrifices herself
just for these decrees.
Is it worth it?
♪Falling down like snow♪
♪Joys and sorrows of the mortal world♪
♪Swept along by the daylight♪
♪The forms and hues of the mortal realm♪
♪Lingering for a fleeting moment♪
♪Was once touched by laughing tears♪
♪If I could live a simple life♪
♪For once♪
♪I'd be a guest in a sweet dream♪
♪Dawn and dusk rise and set♪
♪Longing to meet, yet parted by destiny♪
♪Let me wander through♪
♪Light and dark, without turning back♪
♪Wander to the other shore
with the lantern♪
♪Accompanied by eternity♪
♪As all things turn and flow♪
♪Whether I stay or go, I'm all alone♪
♪As stars shift and change places♪
♪A century is like a dream♪
♪Let me journey across them all♪
♪Without reincarnations♪
♪A lone lamp shines on the other shore♪
♪Accompanied by the abyss♪
♪Moments may last♪
♪Love and hate will fade away♪
During your recuperation,
I am willing
to help you manage
all the affairs of the Void.
Don't bother.
During my recuperation,
all the affairs here
will be handled by Jiang Ai.
We shall obey, Your Grace.
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪