[Team Leader Baek Su Jeong]
[Moon Ga Young]
[Director Ban Ju Yeon]
[Choi Hyeon Wook]
[Yongsung's successor. [The new chaebol director?]
[Im Se Mi]
[Kwak Shi Yang]
[My Dearest Enemy]
[This series is fictional.]
[Characters and settings are fictional.]
What's this...
like this?
This...
I gave it to my first love to confess my love.
It has no other meaning.
I didn't want to forget the wound I sustained back then.
That's why I hid it.
Or...
why are you asking...
You're the Black Dragon, aren't you?
Strawberry?
Didn't you know it was me?
I guess you didn't know.
That's why we're in this mess.
Go. I can't talk right now.
[Chapter 9]
What if they find out who the other person is?
I'm sure that would be a huge shock.
Since they haven't found it yet, maybe they'll never know.
And Ju Yeon finally...
He looks genuinely happy.
Oh.
Ha Jin, are you busy at work?
Shall I come and help you?
You know I'm not busy.
Ha Jin, should I come and entertain you then?
Instead, you should rest.
You must be tired of following my schedule.
I'm not tired at all.
Being at home is more tiring.
I have no energy because I can't see you.
I actually want to talk about something.
What?
Black Dragon and Su Jeong.
What about them?
Hey! Hey, beggar!
Hey!
Hey, how can a beggar ignore me?
This is your fault!
Yong Jun.
Are you alright? Oh, no...
Did you two have a fight?
Don't you see he's injured? [Administrative Office]
What will you do if there's a scar on your precious leg?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Do you think an apology is enough?
You need to raise your child well.
I heard that Su Jeong's mother is in the hospital.
I'm sorry about that too.
It must be difficult alone.
But still.
You shouldn't completely neglect your child.
Sir?
He is often reported to not bring materials and to disrupt classes.
I heard he couldn't pay for his lunch on time either.
Did you know that she didn't bring any food to the picnic and forced everyone to share?
Lady.
Other mothers complain that she spoils the classroom atmosphere.
And it created problems like that.
I am sorry.
Let's go, Yong Jun.
Baba.
Yes.
Ben...
I didn't.
Yes.
I should pay more attention to you.
No.
I am good.
I decided to be strong on my own.
Darling!
No...
I decided to check out Baek Su Bin as well.
Because the father doesn't have the power to do it, and the mother...
He's gone now.
Perhaps that's why I was even angrier.
You were the first person I wanted to trust.
But in the end, I couldn't trust you either.
And I have to be alone.
I heard that this place is famous for its bagel sandwiches.
We are here because they wanted to join our store.
Does it taste bad?
No, it's fine.
Did something happen last night?
You look tired.
You don't seem to have any appetite either.
Was there a problem with the room you stayed in?
I didn't sleep very well.
I had a nightmare.
It was about things that shouldn't have happened.
I still feel very alive, as if it were real.
Safe.
It must be a terrible nightmare.
[My Princess]
One moment, please.
I don't like these kinds of fashion styles.
I don't even want to be near it.
So what now?
I don't care.
Because I love you.
The character in the game isn't real.
Actually, you're such a pathetic person.
Stop pretending like that and stay sealed forever, you little cow!
If the same person hurts me and also makes me smile, what should I do?
Hey, are you sick or something?
- Sister. - Yes.
Nothing. I'll wait for you to start.
What did you want to say?
What?
Thing...
Your director.
Do you still get along well with him/her?
Why are you asking?
Well...
Y-So, the director...
Is the director Black Dragon?
What? How—how did you know?
Since when?
Since last night.
Did you really have to drag me out as soon as you got back from your business trip?
Prepare yourself and listen.
Now we're going to my girlfriend's shop.
Why would I go there?
The name of the place is 'Sulo.'
Is the owner of that place your girlfriend?
Yes. When we get there, your first love will be there.
Su Jeong?
Damn it.
You knew?
H-Since when?
Since last night.
Hey, are you okay?
Shouldn't we go? Huh?
How long have you known?
I saw you two together on the day you brought the director.
Yes, it should have happened then.
I've thought about this a lot too.
I thought you'd be even more surprised to learn more later.
That's why I wanted to say it today.
Are you okay, Su Jeong?
I am not ok.
I'm not feeling well at all.
You dated Black Dragon, right?
This is the downside.
How can the Black Dragon and I be together...?
Oh dear, why didn't I understand?
You should have told me sooner.
I wanted it.
But I didn't want it to affect his work.
And I really didn't know you were going to leave.
Yes.
It's not your fault at all.
It's all my fault. My fault.
When I learned...
Black Dragon was an immature middle school student.
More than being fooled by a child...
...what bothered me was that I wasn't sure what I loved about him.
The person I loved and trusted was fake, you know.
This time I thought I knew him well.
If the Black Dragon is the one who deceived me, then who exactly did I fall in love with?
What are you going to do now?
I want to avoid him for now, but...
Hello.
Thing...
I don't know what to say.
But I thought I needed to see you.
I wanted to see you. That's why I came.
So, you met by chance in the shop and in the game...
...you learned that we are Black Dragon and Strawberry, who met.
While they try to separate us
Did you get together?
We also met by chance.
We didn't come together while you were trying to separate us.
That's not the important thing here.
That means the manager knows everything about my past.
C-Not much. D-I've learned a little.
A little.
- I'm leaving. - Su Jeong!
Wait, calm down a bit.
Can you sit down for a minute?
Shall we sit down?
E-If you don't mind, may I say something?
Since this has happened, I want all four of us to come to an agreement.
Let's leave the past in the past.
And this happened when I was little.
You two will continue to see each other, right?
- Yes. - No.
Safe.
I need to start preparing for today.
Oh dear, I should help him too.
Let's talk outside.
- Wait- - Su Jeong-
- Ju Yeon- - Kara Ejder-
Sence...
Can you continue to love me?
What do you want to say?
You've found out who I am.
Can you still love me?
Sence...
Can't you do it?
I think it will be difficult.
I don't think I can.
Can you make this decision so easily?
It's not easy. Obviously.
No matter how much I thought about it, my answer would be the same.
- Mrs. Baek - Well, let's finish now.
Now to finish...
It would be best for both of us.
What do you think happened to them?
Ju Yeon wants to keep seeing him, but Su Jeong doesn't.
Perhaps they've been hurt more by the past than we think.
Rather, if you keep bumping into a wall, the wall...
...you're good at breaking things, but you know the wall very well.
This can amplify your fear.
Su Jeong often found himself alone, hitting many different walls.
They might not want to deal with a particular wall.
I don't think he wants to bring the pain up again.
[Su Jeong]
So let's finish now.
Now to finish...
It would be best for both of us.
It was easy for him.
Team Leader Baek.
Come to my office immediately.
Please...
Sit and wait.
Team Leader Baek.
Yes.
The next branch to be renovated should be the Daejeon branch.
The audit results also look good.
I will prepare it in a way that will not affect the program.
I haven't told you to leave yet.
Wait.
Our conversation isn't over.
Director, why are you making me sit here all day?
I told you. I need to talk to you.
Then speak now.
Just because we broke up—that's your opinion.
I can't leave.
Why should we break up?
Do you have to ask?
Have you forgotten what first love meant to us?
A bad memory.
We don't want to be reminded. How can we continue the conversation?
Because I still love you.
You told me to keep loving what I love.
That's you.
How can I stand?
You said you loved me too.
That was a time when I didn't know who he was.
In that case...
I won't tell you my age...
I am sorry.
It was my fault.
Please...
Please forgive me.
Forget everything...
And think about Ban Ju Yeon now.
From where...
You haven't changed at all?
You were like that back then too.
You said you loved me.
But you left me behind, as if it was all a lie.
Have you seen?
You haven't forgotten that I hurt you.
As you said,
I wish my love for you was a complete lie and a joke.
I wouldn't be hurt, and I wouldn't say things that would hurt a child.
I could have comforted you by saying we could meet again when we're older.
I truly loved you.
I trusted you this much.
I was happy to have someone I could trust.
But you were just a child.
How can I ever love you again now?
I made it very spicy.
How did it happen?
I can't say if it's painful or not.
How strange. It can't be.
I broke up with him.
You don't open up easily.
You must have loved him very much.
I know.
I think I was very lonely.
After meeting with the Black Dragon...
During the offline meeting, I realized that...
I was truly alone.
I was desperate.
I needed someone so much...
I didn't realize he was a child.
I think that's why I was deceived.
Like an idiot.
I hate this so much.
You don't just hate the Black Dragon.
You hate yourself too.
From the person he was then.
Elder brother,
Have you ever experienced a breakup?
What?
You've experienced it many times because you've gone out so much.
How could you relive so much heartbreak?
Ju Yeon, I think you're drunk.
When dating, both people need to agree.
But why?
Why in the end, one person,
Does it end when you say 'it's over'?
I disagree with this.
Ben, Ban Ju Yeon, bu...
I will fight against the brutal system of segregation.
No.
Actually, I can't.
Because I don't have the right.
What do you mean by "right"?
I thought I was the only one suffering...
Because I was the only one being sincere.
How disappointed she was in me...
And I didn't know how hurt she was, thinking she had been deceived.
I was a truly ignorant child.
I'm the one who hurts her the most.
Ju-Yeon.
Git.
The person I truly hate...
It wasn't you.
It was me.
[Is Yongsung's heir, Ban Ju Yeon, getting married?]
An employee?
That's what a team leader says, according to a rumor.
[Is she dating a subordinate, not a chaebol?]
- Look. - Seriously...
Behind.
Team Leader, did you see this by chance?
[Is Yongsung's heir, Ban Ju Yeon, getting married?]
What's this?
I also saw the original photo.
I believe this woman is Baek Su Jeong from the Strategy Team.
There was an article on an office workers' website this morning.
I think that's where it started. [I saw a chaebol]
You were recently announced as the heir and some...
...even the employees recognized Team Leader Baek in the photo.
Even before the PR team could handle it, it had already spread across various social media platforms and websites.
During this process, the rumor grew.
I understand.
Why did you meet Team Leader Baek's family?
I met them.
And to be polite, I bought them a meal.
I understand.
I thought so too.
You're in a difficult situation for no reason.
I know.
How unfair to Mrs. Baek.
Get it done as soon as possible.
Team Leader Baek, I heard you're marrying the director.
- Is that true? - Excuse me?
I heard your wedding will be at the Yongsung Hotel.
The hotel staff know everything.
But why would the director date Team Leader Baek?
And should she even marry him?
Why not? It's beautiful.
Yes.
Being beautiful is the best.
Oh, I wish I were beautiful too.
Excuse me, team leaders,
I thought Yongsung Store was number one in the industry.
That's why I was proud to work here.
I did my best too.
But the team leaders at store number 1 are responding to an unconfirmed rumor...
...he believes and judges a female colleague's appearance.
I'm disappointed.
We were complimenting you.
Let's begin the meeting.
Ve...
Let's only talk about work in the office.
I know what you're thinking, but the director and I aren't.
Yes. Of course you're not.
Sir?
Na Na, what's wrong? Is something wrong?
That's not true.
No, just...
I thought you might find this very unfair.
- Excuse me? - That makes no sense.
Why you...?
So you're going to jump into hell even with the director?
Really. They know nothing.
Absolutely impossible.
But people are speaking very badly.
Because they couldn't see how much they hated each other.
They were terrifying on the roof.
You should be upset about all this nonsense.
I am good.
- Don't cry, Na Na. - Team Leader...
I know. To entertain themselves...
...they believe whatever they want to believe. Do you understand?
They know how to fabricate sensational things.
They have no idea what the Team Leader is like.
How much longer will this go on?
I don't know.
It's a false rumor. They'll stop talking within a month.
Yes. They should be.
I'm going to report them.
I removed all the articles.
We decided not to address it formally.
The PR team is analyzing public opinion in online communities.
They say it's a baseless rumor.
Many didn't believe it, thinking the heirs and employees couldn't get out.
I think everything will calm down in time.
You wanted to see me, Madam President.
Yes.
I'm not interested in your game, but knowing about family activities is enough.
Why are you creating noise by not recognizing the hierarchy?
You're giving people the wrong impression.
- Extremism always creates problems. - I'm sorry.
Because you are known as the heir, wherever you go and whoever you are with...
...if you meet up, do so, but don't forget that investors are watching you.
If you want to grow the company, meet the right people in the right places.
Yes, I'll keep that in mind.
Alright...
Are you just going to leave it like this?
They started talking even though there was nothing there.
Do you think this won't happen again?
Next time, they'll make a fuss over even smaller things.
Baek Su Jeong...
Find the right moment and fire him before people notice.
You need to pull the weed out from the very beginning.
I think this will be difficult.
Will it be difficult?
Team Leader Baek...
This is a very important piece of staff for the renovation project.
Dismissing him because of a false rumor is a significant...
...it would be our loss if we were faced with that project.
It would be difficult to replace him.
Okay.
Then leave him.
If he comes back on my radar, I'll take action myself.
You can go.
Their...
You knew how to bring them together, didn't you, Manager Kwon?
Yes, I knew it.
Or...
You have also dealt with the families of employees in the past.
I didn't think this would be a problem.
That's why I didn't tell you.
I am sorry.
If you're upset, you need to take responsibility, Manager Kwon.
Are you ok?
Everyone's talking about the two of you all day.
Why shouldn't I be okay?
It's not true anyway.
I didn't see...
He's been in the Director's office for a while now.
He was probably summoned by the president.
He'll be fine.
He's good at figuring everything out.
You don't need to worry.
I'm not worried.
I think he's worried.
I'm going to do something for all businesses whose sales record is below 10%.
- All of them? - Yes.
We will either cancel the contract or come up with a plan.
I plan to do things quickly.
The renovation project is also ongoing.
I don't know how it will turn out in the long term, but...
...fixing a few large stores won't be enough.
To double sales and maybe even more...
...for this reason, all branches need to improve their sales.
We'll be busy.
We need to be even busier.
That sounds good.
We need to be very careful right now.
Director.
What's wrong?
Thing...
This doesn't cause any problems with the lady president, does it?
I don't think this concerns you.
I'm directly involved. How can I not be worried?
If he misunderstood, I'll explain myself.
I'll say nothing happened—No. There's no need for that.
Like you said, there's nothing.
This won't be a problem.
Then I felt relieved.
Yes like that.
So, let's not get involved personally from now on.
Okay.
Finally...
Everything seems to have returned to normal.
Relaxing.
The song is innocent.
Start loving him again, together with me.
Payment has been processed.
Lady?
Oh, yes.
Thank you. Have a good day.
I don't need to ask to do that, do I?
Are you home, my daughter?
Oh dear, why is it raining so much?
Su Jeong.
Baba.
What's wrong, Su Jeong?
Su Jeong, what is this?
What's happening?
I'm sorry, Dad.
I guess I wasn't such a strong person after all.
I thought I was strong.
What's wrong...
Sister, is it because of that jerk?
Why? He wanted to keep it a secret.
Is he blaming you for the rumor now?
I'm going to kill that dog.
No, that's not it. That's not it.
How is that not the case?
Ben...
I suggested they leave.
I left him, Dad.
We decided to end it.
When monitoring businesses with low sales,
I noticed one of them stood out.
Are you talking about the clothing brand 'Bukayo'?
Yes.
It's one of the bestsellers at another branch.
The discrepancy was extreme.
I'll just prepare a report about him.
Send it this morning.
Don't force me to ask you next time.
Okay, I'll be more careful.
Team Leader.
I think the rumor will disappear very soon.
You seem more distant than before.
The rumors didn't make things any stranger, did they?
- No. - Right?
That's good then.
This is great.
We don't seem close.
[Grace]
[Curved]
Ok.
Come on, I told you to sit down.
You make me feel bad.
No problem.
I'd rather be like this, close to you, than sit down.
Thank you.
How is the Black Dragon?
He's only focused on work.
I think he's exaggerating, but that's just the way he is.
I can't say whether it's worse or better.
But I'm worried.
Su Jeong too.
He has always been focused on his work.
Rumors spread when things were already complicated.
They can't make progress overnight.
It should disturb them.
Even if they can't show it.
Aren't you going home, Team Leader?
I have to go.
I'll be leaving soon. Don't worry and go now.
Okay. See you tomorrow then.
- Have a safe trip home. - Thank you.
Team Leader.
Director.
Are you really relieved to be back to normal?
Has anyone seen the director today?
No, I haven't seen it.
Isn't he in his office?
He went home very late last night.
I left after 10 o'clock, but he was still there.
Really?
One minute.
He always keeps the messaging app open.
Closed.
At the meeting?
How strange. It always keeps it on.
[Director Ban Ju Yeon - Offline]
Are you ok?
[Director Ban Ju Yeon]
I need to get approval today.
Manager.
Is the director working remotely?
He couldn't come today because he's sick.
Is he/she very ill?
I'm not sure. I also received a brief report.
If he could have come, he would have.
Since he's at home, he must be very ill.
I'm worried. How sick is he/she?
He had been skipping meals lately.
He was working day and night.
How can it be good?
The president will be upset if she finds out.
Will she be upset because he's sick?
Health problems within the homeowner's family pose risks.
Then, if you'll excuse me.
Wake up. Why should you be the one worrying?
But as a human being, I can worry about another human being.
He's an adult. He'll figure it out himself.
I'm sure it's fine.
Will you be alright?
Our relationship could be revealed at any moment, and that...
Becoming Yongsung's successor could be a problem for your dream.
I think I'll be alright...
As long as I have you.
As long as you love me.
Medicine... Give me everything.
He's not eating. He fainted from overwork.
Give me everything I can to save him.
[Pharmacy]
Yes, Madam President.
Director.
My god.
Director, are you alright?
Did she try to go to work in that condition?
I am sorry.
I was sad then, and I'm sad now.
I only thought about my own pain.
I've forgotten the pain I caused.
But it's the same this time too.
What if I hurt him again?
I want to be...
I was going to be your biggest and coolest secret.
Don't go.
Ben...
I thought I wanted someone to love me.
Even if I don't work for it or try very hard for it.
Or...
You gave me such love.
In that case...
And now.
So, don't feel bad about it.
Don't hate yourself either.
You already...
You're my biggest and coolest secret.
Because you are my first love.
I love you.
I love you too.
[Director Ban Ju Yeon]
[Notice of Termination]
[Strategy Team Director Ban Ju Yeon]
[My Dearest Enemy]
Mrs. Baek was seen going in and out of the director's house...
Was the director fired?
Then you are unemployed.
Unemployed?
I'm bad at being bad at things.
Things you do alone...
Do it with me from now on.
Team Leader Baek Su Jeong...
Take care of her secretly.
What is this, Team Leader?
This makes no sense.
Can you leave it up to the director for now?
I will also have a choice to make.