There's something I'd like to confirm.
The rumor
that one of our teachers is acting unusually,
is true.
My name is Solar.
I'm the homeroom teacher of Grade 2, Class 1.
But on the day of the parents' meeting,
I'll be Sun.
Actually, my concern is
not only Teacher Solar,
but also Teacher Pobmek.
I apologize to all the parents
for not having a teaching license yet.
I'll allow this for one year only.
I hope the teachers with issues
will be able to sort themselves out.
Thank you, Ms. Pang.
Let me hug you.
So nice.
I feel twice as encouraged now.
C.
A minor.
D minor, then G.
This is weird, man.
You used to be able to do this.
Why did you suddenly quit?
No reason.
School just got intense,
so I stopped playing.
It's alright.
Just keep practicing,
and it'll come back to you.
Hello, Mom.
What?
You're at my condo?
Oh? You're not home?
But I keep hearing some noises.
Something's not right.
I'm scared it might be a thief.
It's not a thief, Mom.
Oh, ma'am.
Hello.
Oh.
So you're the maintenance guy?
Pobmek!
I've got everything set just right.
Can you not mess with it?
Gosh, Jee!
Can you stop obsessing over this
for a second?
I'm freaking stressed right now!
Huh? Why are you so stressed?
I haven't told my mom...
that I'm dating a guy.
Well...
Don't worry.
Please continue working.
Well...
I'm not a maintenance guy.
So you're with condo management.
Don't mind me.
I'm just here to surprise my son
and his partner today.
He's worked really hard
and was able to afford a nice condo,
so I just wanted to come visit him.
And I want to meet his partner.
I want to see if she's pretty.
My mom is super strict.
She never accepts anything easily.
Is that a girl or a boy?
Mom!
Kids these days are weird.
That's why I take good care of my son.
I made sure he's in a good environment
and chose the right faculty for him.
You're studying accounting, right?
Do you like it?
Well, I...
Of course, he likes it.
Good university, good environment.
I even put him in the on-campus dorm.
Who knows what he'd face
if I let him live elsewhere on his own?
Is it really that bad?
Yeah.
Not to mention, she used to
call me every day when I was in school.
If it was out of concern,
I wouldn't mind at all.
But it felt more like
she was trying to find fault with me.
But from what I've seen of your mom
since I was a kid,
I don't think she's that strict.
My mom?
How do you see her?
She seems pretty modern,
lives in the present,
and knows a lot about new things.
That's not my mom.
But damn, I have no idea...
if she'll be okay with me dating Solar.
That's right.
I'm Pobmek's boyfriend. My name is Solar.
Oh!
We finally met!
This is just like a BL series!
You two are so cute!
Thank you. Would you like something to drink?
Yeah, sure.
Here you go.
Want some, Solar?
Not right now. Thank you.
If I didn't have a son,
I'd be sipping beer by the pool,
not worrying about anyone by now.
Oh?
Why don't you try that?
You're right.
But I gave up a lot of things I liked
when I had Pobmek.
By the way,
Pobmek loves steamed crab with herbs.
- You know that?
- Yes.
I love making it for him when he comes home.
But he hasn't been home in a long time.
I guess he's busy with work.
Why are you smiling?
You're so sweet and kind to Pobmek.
I just thought you two would be very close,
but why...
This guitar...
It's mine!
Hello.
Hi, Jee!
What are you doing here?
Oh, I was just out running some errands
with Pobmek.
It's so nice that
you're still friends with my son.
And we're lucky we work at the same place.
Really?
You both work as auditors
at the same company?
You two are really impressive.
You're too kind.
How have you been, Jee?
How's working as an auditor? Good?
I enjoy it.
That's great.
You know,
a good job gives you stability in life.
Do you still play guitar as a hobby?
Solar, this reminds me of
when Pobmek was in high school.
He used to play music, you know?
Yeah.
And now, our final band
in the Hot Woof Music Awards competition.
Let's give it up for them!
Art Attack!
[Mom]
But he wasn't very good.
It's for the best
that he didn't waste time forcing it.
He got his act together,
focused on his studies instead,
and got into accounting.
- Otherwise...
- Mom.
Let's stop talking about this.
Aunt, would you like some dessert?
- I can order something for you.
- Yeah, that'd be great.
Here.
Oh.
Let me try this.
Oh, wow!
- It's good, right?
- Yummy.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm trying to be.
I'm just scared of what'll happen
if Mom finds out you can switch with Sun,
and that I'm an elementary school teacher.
But your mom seems kind.
Aren't you overthinking it?
My mom is the reason I feel this way now.
Hey, I'm heading out.
I need to check the kids' homework.
Oh, I mean,
I need to check the interns' accounting work.
I'm gonna go.
Mom.
What time are you leaving?
I'll drop you off.
I think I'll stay for a couple of days.
I can sleep on the sofa. No need to worry.
You two usually eat here, right?
Let me show off my cooking skills tomorrow.
[Sponge Bath Service]
[Jak-Ka-Jee]
Is it that bad, man?
[Principal Sodchuen]
What? What's going on?
Tell me how to hide from my mom
the fact that I'm a teacher.
Lately, I've been waking up late.
If Mom wakes up and sees Sun, I'm screwed.
[Principal Sodchuen]
Then get him out of the apartment ASAP.
Hey, she's probably asleep.
I think...
Damn it!
If I wake him up right now, he'll be Sun.
[Sponge Bath Service]
Mission accomplished.
Thanks for the advice.
- Uncle.
- Whoa!
Why did you bring me here?
Well, I brought you here to do something fun.
Don't tell me you're up to something again.
Pobmek!
[Pobmek Ekrakrak]
[Auditor]
What a coincidence.
Where are you going? Do you need a ride?
I'm going to see Pobmek at the office.
Please hop in.
Nice.
The seat's set at 100 degrees,
and the distance from the front
is just right.
Just what I'd expect from your car, Jee.
You're the only one who gets me this well.
But unfortunately,
I'm not going to the office today.
Oh? Why didn't you say so?
It's alright.
You're already in, and I'm free anyway.
Why don't we go to the market
and get Pobmek something delicious to eat?
That's actually a good idea.
Let's go.
Oh.
How's it going? All good?
At first, it was pretty tough,
but now it's better.
He's calmed down.
You're good.
You've got Sun under control now.
Actually, no.
Sun dug out all the snacks you hid.
Oh! My secret stash got trashed.
May I submit the form for the talent stage?
Please leave it on the desk, Four.
To be honest,
would it be okay
if Sun stayed with you for a while?
I don't mind him staying with me.
It's just that he might get fussy.
He's not used to my place.
We'll just have to deal with it,
even if it means crying
or losing sleep for a couple of days.
Otherwise, there'll be trouble.
♫ Take it off, take it, take it off ♫
♫ Don't hide no more, don't hide no more ♫
Sun,
I don't think I can give you the title of
Sigma Boy anymore,
because you're about to
get eliminated by Teacher Pobmek.
Huh?
What are you guys talking about?
Four overheard that
you're going to stay with Principal Sodchuen!
Yeah. You probably won't be
a cool boy anymore,
because you're going to
stay with that auntie!
Please! Why would you believe Four and King?
Don't listen to them, Sun.
Yeah, don't listen to them, Sun.
You can put it here.
It's you again.
You really get me.
Thank you so much for asking them
to pack it nicely in this box.
[Ploysai Seafood]
Of course.
We can't leave strong-smelling food in the car
for too long.
Leave it in the car for too long?
I get you, Jee.
Now it's your turn to get me.
Please take me to see Pobmek at the office.
Oh, the office is kind of complicated.
There are a lot of people,
you have to take the elevator up
several floors,
and you even need an employee badge.
Can I take you there another day?
Jee, I'm begging you.
Ever since Pobmek started university,
he's been distant from me.
I know less about him every day.
I'm scared that one day,
I won't know anything about my son at all.
Alright.
I'll take you there.
Thank you so much.
Let's go.
[Stop - Visitor Registration]
What can I help you with?
Oh, are you new?
Why don't you recognize me?
I'm one of the auditors.
Can I just drive in and out in 10 minutes?
I'll be quick.
Their security system is great, isn't it?
They keep checking over and over.
You can tap your employee badge here.
I forgot my badge.
What should I do?
It's okay.
This is my son's business card.
He works here.
This looks like it's not...
Jee!
What have you done?
You drove into the barrier?
Are you out of your mind?
I'm sorry.
I didn't know what to do and freaked out.
Fine.
Just do whatever you can
to keep her from causing any more trouble.
And don't let our secret get out,
no matter what.
- Got it?
- Yeah.
I'll be right there.
You see, Sun?
The truth is out.
He really wants to get rid of you.
Jee, I figured it out.
You're a teacher,
but you didn't tell your family, did you?
Wait, how do you know?
[School Vehicle Access Card]
And you want
to hide it from your parents, right?
I bet you're afraid they'll be disappointed.
I think I get it.
You're a grown-up.
It's normal to have secrets.
How about this?
I won't make a big deal out of it, okay?
Is it going to be a big deal?
How could it not be?
I hate it so much when adults keep secrets.
It's bad, bad, bad.
Oh! Hey!
Where are you going?
I'll tell you later.
Take care of Sun for me.
What's going on?
Why is Uncle doing this to me?
Why does he want me
to stay with someone else?
Looks like you'll have to do
what fairytale princesses do.
Huh? What's he supposed to do?
Run away, of course.
What are you waiting for, Sun?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
But your mom already left.
She said she didn't want
the crab meat she bought to go bad.
What's all this?
Pobmek, tell me honestly.
How much longer are you going to
keep lying to your mom?
When she found out I was just a teacher,
she didn't seem to mind.
- Hello?
- Hey! We have a problem!
Sun ran away from school!
- What?
- What is it?
I already asked the kids.
They said Sun's heading back to the condo.
Damn! What the hell?
Hey, what's going on?
My mom is about to meet Sun!
Shit!
Oh, you're back.
Yeah.
Hey. What are you looking for?
Oh, nothing.
Uncle!
You can't just ship me off to some auntie!
And who's this auntie?
Are you going to steal my bed?
So you're telling me that after the accident,
Solar has been like this?
It might sound hard to believe,
but as you can see,
my friends and I are trying to
help Solar recover.
So...
please don't be mad at him.
Is this why...
you've been avoiding me all this time?
Well...
I was just afraid... you wouldn't understand.
We're family.
You're not the only one who's grown up.
Things I couldn't accept before,
I understand better now.
We haven't gotten to know each other yet.
My name is Pafun.
And you?
What's your name?
It's Sun.
Sun is very mature for his age.
Just a little naughty.
I'm not naughty!
Actually, I'm a very good kid,
and I work hard at school.
Right, Uncle?
Yeah. If you say so.
But it'd be great if you spoke more politely.
But I think the good thing about being a kid
is being able to speak directly,
not beating around the bush like adults.
Besides, I don't think you're stubborn,
right?
That's right.
The stubborn one is the one teaching.
Look, Auntie!
He's a teacher, but he's even
more stubborn than his students.
Pobmek.
You...
You're...
You're not... an auditor?
I was.
And?
Now you're a teacher?
Teaching elementary students?
Yes.
Go quit your job right now.
Mom.
- Calm down.
- Come with me!
You're going to quit right now!
I said right now! You hear me?
Do you hear me?
Pobmek, look at me!
I said you need to quit right now!
I won't allow this!
You're coming with me!
I'm not quitting!
Stop forcing me already, will you?
I'm not forcing you.
You are.
Fine! I'm forcing you!
Am I so wrong for wanting my son
to have a good future?
What's wrong with my life right now?
How is being a teacher a bad thing?
Jee is a teacher just like me.
We even teach at the same school.
Why aren't you scolding Jee,
but you're scolding me?
How are Jee and I any different?
In the end...
you're kind to everyone,
except your own son.
Uncle, where are you taking me?
Uncle, where are we going?
Uncle.
Uncle, I'm scared.
♫ Let our story be written in our hearts ♫
♫ 'Cause this love is meant just for us ♫
♫ I will never let your hand go ♫
♫ I will paint
and fill the storyline with you ♫
♫ No matter if the sky turns dark and blue ♫
♫ I will remain right here beside you,
always ♫
Pobmek!
Didn't you have an interview today?
Why didn't you go?
You gave it up for music? Seriously?
Wanna do it now?
Come on! No more.
We've been at it all day.
No!
I mean, when are you
going to pack your stuff?
We have to move out tomorrow.
Yeah, I know.
We still have time tomorrow.
[Whose boyfriend is this?]
What are you up to?
Nothing.
I just wanted to show off my boyfriend.
Hey!
What are you doing?
I give up! I get it!
I get it!
Don't be so naughty, okay?
No! Stop!
Stop!
- Hey.
- Yeah?
There's one thing I still don't understand.
Why did you stop playing guitar?
I just didn't want to play anymore.
Really?
That's a shame.
Look.
When you're with a guitar, you look happy.
Hey!
What's wrong?
Wow!
You're such a sigma boy, Uncle!
Sun, I can play the guitar now!
I can do it now!
Yay!
I can do it now! Yay!
Uncle, watch out!
[Pobmek]
Hello?
Yes, he's my son.
What?
He's in the hospital?
Pobmek.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
I never realized...
that I'd been hurting you your whole life.
Oh?
But they said you were in the hospital.
I just came to get my finger treated.
I was sitting on the side of the road
when a car grazed me.
But I'm fine.
What didn't survive was the guitar.
It got completely crushed.
So...
you're still playing guitar?
I actually just got back into it.
I have to, especially now.
Because it's the only way
that can help Solar recover.
Mom.
Could you please be a little kinder to me?
Both about the guitar...
and about me being a teacher.
It might not be what you want,
but it's what I truly chose for myself.
I'm sorry.
I was really wrong.
From now on,
I won't stop you from doing anything.
I promise.
That's not how you make a promise.
Then how do you make one?
You have to pinky promise.
Alright, come on.
Let's pinky promise.
No. I changed my mind.
Let's hug!
You'll see what Pobmek is like as a teacher.
He might not be perfect,
but he's pretty good.
- Okay.
- 8 times 12?
- 96!
- Good job!
Give yourselves a big hand!
Next, let's do the 9 times table.
I've already taught you this.
I know you all can do it.
- 9 times 1?
- 9!
- 9 times 2?
- Still good!
- 9 times 3?
- Our brains are on fire!
Heh!
Oh.
Guys, this is my mom.
- Say hello.
- Hello, ma'am!
Thank you.
Here, I have something for you.
Wow!
Teacher, can you play a song for us?
Play a song!
Alright.
I'll play one song, but you have to
get back to studying after that, okay?
Yay!
Hey.
What if Solar doesn't recover?
Do you two really think you'll be okay?
Mom!
You're ruining the mood.
Hey, I'm really not judging.
I'm just worried about you.
If that's the case,
I'll help take care of him.
Thank you so much, Aunt.
Honestly, it's because of Pobmek
that I want to do everything I can
to get better.
Hey, Pobmek.
Why don't you play that special song for me?
The one you said could make Sun
fall asleep right away.
I want to hear it.
I still can't really remember that one,
but I do remember
it's a song I wrote when I was in a band.
It's okay. Just play whatever you can.
Mom!
No filming! I'm shy!
Don't be shy. Keep playing.
This is your moment.
Solar, I'll send you the clip later.
Thank you.
Cute.
[Solar: Mom, I have something to show you!]
I'm glad you and your mom made up.
[Atsara & Little Lion]
You seem totally different now.
Really?
Since I met you,
it's felt like
you've always been carrying something.
But today, right now,
you've finally put it down.
That's probably true.
Mom and I are just starting to understand...
and learn more about each other.
I guess that's life.
There's so much more to learn.
Wow. Well said.
I'm so lucky to have you as my boyfriend.
Let me kiss your cheek.
I'm just as lucky
to have you as my boyfriend.
Why do you want Sun to sleep so much?
Because I'm tired of him.
Sodchuen, has anyone seen Sun?
Today, we're on a secret mission
to take Sun to his mom!
What?
What now?
Sun! Sun.
Hey!
Aunt, what is this?
I'm just wondering
if all of this is my fault.
But you still have me.