[Fated Hearts]
[Episode 24]
Your Highness, please halt.
No one may trespass in the Inner Palace without permission.
Come here, come here.
[Ning'an Hall]
What an impressive show of force,
Your Highness!
You actually stormed into the palace
with your men.
Are you staging a rebellion?
What rebellion?
These are merely guards from my household.
How could such a small number
stage a rebellion?
What a joke.
Since when are household guards allowed
into the imperial palace?
I know perfectly well what you're up to.
Don't think
you can control
His Majesty's life and death.
I'm still here.
You're slandering me.
There's no need
for this back-and-forth bickering.
It's just a waste of time.
Heaven will judge
whether you're loyal or treacherous.
As long as I'm here,
you can't harm His Majesty
in the slightest.
You can't stop what I intend to do.
Stop him!
Today, by the order of my ancestors,
I am here to protect His Majesty.
Anyone who dares to stop me
will be killed without mercy!
-Yes, sir!
T-Terrible news! Terrible news!
Terrible news!
His Majesty...
His Majesty has disappeared!
Where is His Majesty?
That's what I should be asking you.
I just entered the palace.
You've guarded His Majesty
in the palace the entire time.
Where did you send His Majesty?
With the Jinwu Guards present,
no one can take His Majesty away.
Since the Jinwu Guards are also gone,
it can only mean
His Majesty woke up and left on his own.
If someone
had forcibly abducted His Majesty,
there would be signs of a fight here.
Even Eunuch Ma
and Lord Ling are gone.
This can only mean His Majesty himself
wanted to leave.
But why would His Majesty
leave?
[Zichen Hall]
Don't you dare step forward!
If you are truly
as loyal as you claim
and have been guarding
His Majesty all along in the palace,
why didn't he inform you when he awoke?
From my understanding of His Majesty,
he would never leave the palace
unless he sensed grave danger within.
How could there be any danger
in the palace?
You're just spouting nonsense.
You just said
I can't stop you from doing what you want.
You've been colluding with Murong Yao,
having him
secretly conspire with Xia Jingshi—
what is your real scheme?
Murong Yao is your friend.
He's been colluding with Xia Jingshi,
and you want to kill him.
But what does that have to do with me?
I don't care what plot you have,
but if you dare
threaten His Majesty's safety,
I won't let you off.
Since His Majesty has awakened,
when he returns,
you will pay
for what you did today.
[Zichen Hall]
Let's go.
Get them!
[Zichen Hall]
Your Highness.
The Imperial Guards' duty is
to protect the royal family.
Today, you're going to
stop me for the sake of
a treacherous official?
Your Highness,
please don't make things difficult for us.
Come here.
Come closer.
Prime Minister,
the First Prince has not committed
any act of rebellion.
As for his crime
of trespassing in the palace,
only His Majesty himself can
pass judgment.
We dare not stop him.
His Majesty left the palace,
and you were completely unaware.
How fitting
for Susha's Imperial Guards!
If you can't find His Majesty,
end your lives and atone for your failure!
Yes.
Your Highness,
behind Rongyang Palace is
the rear gate of the imperial palace.
I left from there,
and no one stopped me.
Today, I wandered the streets for a while,
shook off those tailing me,
and found out who they really are.
Good.
Have we made contact
with Wang Encheng?
His grandfather followed the late emperor
on campaign
and earned battle honors.
He was granted a hereditary post and,
with his grandfather arranging it,
married the niece
of the Marquis of Bao'an.
From then on, his official career was
smooth sailing.
But now...
his wife
has been favored by Xia Jingyan.
The affair has caused quite a stir.
The whole city knows about it.
He can only swallow his anger.
Now he's full of grievances,
and everyone avoids him.
There's also
the Vice Minister of Works... Dai Quan?
Yes.
Xia Jingyan's been supervising work
on the Empress Dowager's mausoleum,
and Dai Quan has been
at the construction site on Mount Gu.
I haven't reached him yet.
But I have made contact
with the others.
When you went to find those people,
did anyone see you?
I found Wang Encheng
at a restaurant.
There must have been people who saw us.
Any word from Bai Shouzhuo?
He said he's found a couple of
the men you're looking for.
They are all placed in key positions.
He also said that
if Your Highness has further instructions,
you can leave messages in the Library.
How about
I go to the Library again?
No need.
You should just focus on those officials
and stay out of palace affairs.
I had the maids
brew some flower tea.
My Prince, if you like it,
please try it first.
When Your Highness the Princess left
Rongyang Palace today,
did anyone follow you?
A guard followed me,
but seeing
I was just out to pick flowers,
he kept watch from outside the hall
at a distance.
What's wrong?
Your Highness,
how about we...
Is there anything I can do?
I know you don't want to
be under house arrest here.
If there's anything I can do,
just say it.
What are you worried about, My Prince?
Right now,
we're in the same boat.
Besides, I don't want to
be trapped here either.
[Murong Residence]
Go to the palace.
Yes.
[Murong Residence]
I put the Imperial Guards
under your command.
How could you have no clue
when His Majesty left the palace?
If His Majesty didn't want anyone to know,
he had plenty of ways.
What I'm worried about now is
why he left.
Has he
already noticed
what I'm planning to do?
You mean he's been awake this whole time,
just pretending to fool us?
Feng Pingcheng cannot be underestimated.
Without such methods,
how could it
have been his turn
to become emperor back then?
Then, with one imperial edict,
he could have us both destroyed.
Why leave the palace at all?
If it's really as you say—
that Feng Pingcheng knows everything—
once he returns to the palace,
it will be our death.
We must find him quickly
and kill him.
I don't want to implicate my father.
I don't want my father to die
because of me.
Even now,
you're still thinking
only about your father?
Everything I'm doing
is for my father
and for our Murong family!
Then help me kill Feng Suige.
As long as he dies,
Chengyang will be the sole heir
of Susha.
Feng Pingcheng waking up
won't change a thing.
After Chengyang ascends the throne,
you'll become
the only prince
of a different lineage in Susha.
Once you're enfeoffed as king
with your own fiefs,
only then can you take back
what your family deserves.
Only in this way
can you bring peace
to your father's spirit in heaven.
What nonsense are you talking about?
What "spirit in heaven"?
You're insane.
What makes you think
you can stand against Feng Suige?
If the Feng Battalion marches rapidly,
they'll reach the city gates within a day!
How do you know I have no backup plan?
This is the stronghold
my son established years ago.
Following Jingheng's plan,
I've been secretly training
my own soldiers.
We still have a chance
to turn things around.
General,
the household has sent word:
they've found
the Elder Marquis's whereabouts.
Once I make sure my father is safe,
I'll help you.
[Library]
Your Highness just needs to
place the item
on the bottom shelf of the last bookshelf
in the library.
Someone
will come for it in time.
Remember:
don't let anyone find out about this.
[Taiping Holy Prescriptions
for Universal Relief]
[Library]
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Why are you here, Your Majesty?
Shouldn't I be asking you that?
I have nothing to do,
so I thought I'd find some books to read.
I'm curious
what kinds of books you are looking for.
This one?
[Rhapsody on the Ethical Order]
Or the ones below?
[Grand View of Materia Medica]
[Xunzi]
These books?
Your Majesty needn't look any further!
[Xunzi]
I'll tell you.
Ever since I arrived in Shengjing,
My Prince has been distant toward me.
I had no choice
but to come here to find books...
on the art of marital harmony.
Marital harmony?
That sounds very profound and mysterious.
Why don't you explain it to me
and teach me?
What are you really doing here?
Your Majesty, please don't humiliate me.
Your Majesty,
please conduct yourself properly.
You're overthinking.
How am I humiliating you?
Princess, don't be angry.
I was just joking.
If you truly
want to please Xia Jingshi,
find him some books
on the art of war.
He has always liked
such impractical things since childhood.
Did Your Highness's trip to the Library
go smoothly?
Everything went smoothly.
I heard
the Emperor also went to the Library.
He didn't give you a hard time, did he?
We must have missed each other.
I didn't see him.
My Prince must be hungry by now.
I'll go speed things up in the kitchen.
Just as we were talking, here it is.
Dried fish flakes,
Crystal Dragon Phoenix Cake,
preserved cherries...
These are all Susha's specialties.
My Prince, you had them
specially prepare these dishes for me?
It wasn't me.
It wasn't me either.
My Prince.
Try this Crystal Dragon Phoenix Cake.
It's not sweet.
Back in Susha,
I often made it for my father
and brother.
Everyone.
This servant was sent here
by His Majesty's order
to deliver a message
to Your Highness the Princess.
Go ahead, Chief Eunuch Bai.
"I deeply understand that you,
Princess of Zhennan,
must feel homesick
residing in Shengjing.
Today, I've specially ordered
the Imperial Kitchen
to prepare some Susha delicacies
to help ease your homesickness.
Please enjoy them, Princess."
I thank His Majesty
for his great kindness.
His Majesty said
there's no need for courtesy.
He also said
today's encounter at the Library
brought him great pleasure.
Hound has led the Qiongqi Unit
to seal off the imperial palace.
The moment Zhuang Shen leaves the palace,
we'll be notified.
Yun Fang. Yun Qing.
-Yes.
Return to the Feng Battalion immediately
and gather all the elites.
By tomorrow noon,
assemble 10 li outside Yujing City.
-Yes.
Then I'll go find His Majesty now.
That won't be necessary!
Your father is also looking for you.
Come with me.
He's waiting for you.
Your old man woke up three days ago
but was too weak to move.
He told me to keep it a secret
while he pretended to be unconscious.
Today, he suddenly said
he wanted to leave the palace
to come here.
He regained consciousness
without telling anyone,
and now
he's left the palace in secret—
what exactly happened?
I'm not entirely clear either.
You'd better
ask your old man yourself in a moment.
Oh, and
he's witnessed
too much treachery these past few days.
He's in a bad mood.
Don't provoke him.
Your Highness,
His Majesty is waiting for you.
Since my mother passed away,
he's never set foot here again.
I thought he'd forgotten
my mother even had a residence here.
Go ahead.
I'll wait for you outside.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
How is Your Majesty's health?
I heard
you barged into the palace with your men.
For what purpose?
To protect Your Majesty.
Why wasn't it to stage a palace coup
and seize the throne?
That throne of mine
doesn't tempt you at all?
You were unconscious for many days,
so you probably don't know
what's happened in the palace.
What could possibly be new?
Treacherous ministers
controlling the court,
officials taking sides,
rebels revealing their ambitions,
and sycophants clinging to
whoever has power—
the same old story.
I raised an army at 28,
founded the nation,
and became emperor at 33.
To this day, I've reigned for 25 years.
There's no court intrigue
or palace turmoil
I haven't already seen.
You're suffering from a terminal illness
and didn't tell me.
You woke up three days ago
and still didn't tell me.
What?
Do I have to report everything to you?
Are you blaming me
for forcing my way into the palace today?
Zhuang Shen is plotting treason,
and the palace is full of danger.
I brought men to the palace
because I didn't want you to die...
If I died,
wouldn't that be
your heaven-sent opportunity?
I've waited all these days,
yet you've shown
no intention whatsoever
of rebelling to seize the throne.
I've painstakingly groomed you for years,
yet you don't even have
a spark of ambition to become emperor!
You've disappointed me greatly.
By your logic,
I was wrong not to
rebel and usurp the throne
while you lay dying?
Yes.
Of course you were wrong!
You are utterly wrong!
You are my son.
You should've coveted the throne.
You should've wished me dead!
You should've schemed day and night
to take this empire for yourself!
That is what you,
as the First Prince of Susha,
ought to do.
Do you think the throne
will automatically be yours once I die?
If you don't fight for the throne,
it'll
fall into someone else's hands!
I have no interest in your throne.
That is exactly
what I despise most about you.
Sit.
How is your arm now?
Let me see.
Everyone says you're a miracle worker.
Well, I've nearly fully recovered.
Now, when I draw the bow,
it doesn't feel
as strenuous as it used to.
Here, grip my wrist.
Good, good.
You've recovered well.
You've recovered really well.
I'm telling you,
you'd better take good care of that arm.
I'll be
boasting about treating your arm—
don't make me look bad.
Don't worry.
Something big is going to happen
in Yujing City.
If you have no pressing matters,
come stay at my Zhengnian Villa
for a while.
I appreciate your kindness,
but...
I can't leave yet.
You're right.
This family has
far too many tangled problems.
You think I'll simply wait to be killed?
The realm I conquered with my blood—
you think I'd just hand it to others?
I must personally choose an heir
while I'm still alive.
Are you telling me this
just to say
you've chosen me?
What else?
Other than you,
I have no choice.
Of course you do.
Xiyang, Chengyang,
they're your children too.
Nonsense.
Xiyang is a woman.
So what?
If she becomes empress,
I'll personally go
chop off the heads of
those who oppose her.
Child,
you think you can
stand against the whole world?
Fine.
If you dare not choose a woman to rule,
you still have Chengyang.
I will never let
someone with the Zhuang bloodline
inherit my throne!
This one won't do,
and that one you refuse—
why so many concerns?
You clearly still
-cling to your imperial ambition.
-That's because you're not cruel enough—
not enough to shatter my obsession.
When I fell gravely ill,
you didn't seize the opportunity
to expand your power
or take my throne.
You actually stayed at my bedside
playing the dutiful son...
What I do is my business.
No, no, no.
I, Feng Pingcheng,
don't need a filial son!
What I want is
an heir with ambition and spine,
with courage and cunning—
one who would betray the world
if necessary
to become a mighty ruler!
Then listen up!
Being your son
is my misfortune.
I never agreed
to be your heir.
What you've pursued your entire life
means nothing to me!
I don't care
for your empire at all.
Stop!
After Feng Pingcheng awoke,
he could no longer feel his legs.
He probably won't be able to
stand up again.
I'm not sure
how much longer he can live.
Let him be.
What happened to your legs?
Go.
Why look back?
The way you look now
is exactly
like your mother.
Since you're sick,
I won't hold your coming here
against you.
But how dare you mention my mother?
Do you know
how this unfinished chess game came to be?
This was the last game
your mother and I played.
In this game,
she clearly could have let me off,
but she left me no escape.
She was always like this—
fiercely competitive,
refusing to let me win.
Don't you dare mention her.
I often racked my brains wondering
how to turn the tables
and defeat her.
She wanted to win—
as if I didn't.
Haven't you always wanted to know
how your mother
really died?
-You're finally willing to tell me.
-That's because after all these years
of painstaking planning,
I'm finally about to win.
Many people have speculated
about the real cause
of your mother's death.
Some think
it was because she controlled
the Storm Alliance
and refused to submit to me.
Others think
it was because she was a Jinxiu spy,
and I was suspicious of her.
A mere Storm Alliance—
why would I fear it?
I don't even
take Jinxiu seriously,
so why would I care about
claims she was their spy?
I remember everything
that happened
on the day my mother died.
If you dare speak even half a lie,
I will never let you off.
In your mother's heart,
there were always things
more important than me.
Though she accompanied me
in conquering the world,
she never treated me
as emperor.
[16 years ago]
She never saw me
as her entire world.
She never belonged to me,
never let me truly possess her,
and never submitted to me docilely.
Mom, I caught crabs!
As the First Prince,
Suige should be the Crown Prince.
You promised that
when he grew up,
inheriting the throne
would be entirely his decision.
You can't interfere now.
So, catching crabs in the countryside
isn't interfering with him,
but me naming him
Crown Prince is?
Officail Website : kissasian.be
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
"Naming"?
I told you before:
in this small courtyard,
you're not allowed to
act like an emperor with me.
Mom!
A crab is crawling out!
Chop it!
I'll chop anyone who dares act arrogantly
before me.
I couldn't control her.
I knew that one day
she'd leave me,
as if I'd never owned
her at all.
Why should she have belonged to you?
Just because she refused to submit,
you let Zhuang Shen
and Zhuang Jingyuan kill her?
Because she tried to take you...
from me!
Come on, sit here.
Is it comfortable?
Then stay in the palace
and rule from here.
From now on,
you'll sit in this chair,
okay?
No.
I promised Mom that
when I grow up,
I'll roam the world with her.
You listen to your mother
but not your father?
If Father wanted to make you emperor
in the future,
you wouldn't want that either?
Mom said
that ever since you became Emperor,
you've become a different person.
She said becoming emperor
turns people bad.
I wanted you to inherit the throne.
I wanted to raise you to be
an even greater ruler,
destined to leave a more glorious legacy!
But she undermined my plans
and crossed my final line.
I would never allow it.
So you killed her?
Was it you who killed her?
All these years,
I've asked you again and again
whether you wanted to be Crown Prince.
You never appreciated it,
insisting you wanted to be a general
who protects the nation
and guards the land.
That's when
I knew
you'd never forgotten
what your mother said.
She's been dead all these years,
yet her words still hold sway over you.
You tell me,
did she deserve to die?
Enough!
She had no great ambitions
and was short-sighted,
just like a common peasant woman!
She wasn't worthy of being your mother,
let alone worthy of being my Empress!
Shut up...
Suige,
you cannot be like her.
I gave her
every honor,
yet she showed no gratitude.
Who did she think
she was?
She pretended to be so aloof.
She pretended to be a hermit.
She even pretended to be
so pure and untainted!
Through and through, she was nothing
but a peasant woman!
Shut your mouth!
I'll kill you!
Come on!
Kill me!
Suige,
just saying it won't do.
Don't you hate me?
Do it!
Kill me!
I simply don't think you hate me enough!
Your mother
died because of you!
Shut up!
I'll ask you one last time:
how did my mother die?
Back then, before she died,
she pointed a sword at me
just like this.
[Changchun Palace]
Greetings, Your Majesty the Empress.
Your Majesty the Empress,
the Jinxiu spy we caught
has confessed
that you're also an accomplice.
Your personal maid
has also testified
that you secretly met with Jinxiu people.
In your bedchamber,
we found
secret correspondence
between you and Jinxiu people.
Feng Pingcheng,
just based on
this petty frame-up,
you want to arrest me and interrogate me?
As long as you remain in the palace,
trust me—
I'll find out the truth for you
and clear your name.
Stay for how long?
You just want to
trap me in the palace.
Why the excuse?
We are husband and wife.
I can choose not to pursue
the suspicion that you're a Jinxiu spy.
If you insist on leaving,
I won't have anyone
stop you.
But...
I won't allow you
to take Suige and Xiyang with you.
They are my children.
Why can't I take them?
I'm not discussing this with you.
Feng Pingcheng,
look in the mirror
and see
what you've become!
You've been blinded by your lust
for power.
This imperial palace
has become your cage.
I will never
let my children
follow your path.
Listen up,
from now on,
those two children
have nothing to do with you whatsoever.
Try taking them and see what happens.
Sister, it's in your nature
to resist staying in the palace for long.
Because of that, His Majesty
has lost his temper many times
over the years.
Now that things have come to this point,
Sister, please don't
provoke His Majesty further.
The children are better off raised here
in the palace
than suffering hardships outside.
In the future, I'll take care of
those two children for you.
Please rest assured.
Who do you think you are?
I'm talking to Feng Pingcheng.
You have no place to speak!
Your Majesty the Empress,
you bear the title
yet refuse to share His Majesty's burdens—
you disgrace the position.
I've long
since tired of being this Empress.
Wei Qingyu.
Do you know what you're saying?
Listen up, Feng Pingcheng,
I will never let Suige
follow your path,
trapped by power as you are.
His path forward
will be his own choice.
Stop, all of you!
Suige must stay.
This is
not up to you.
Protect His Majesty!
I warned you long ago—
I'll cut down anyone who dares to
act arrogantly before me!
You are no exception.
Your Majesty!
Since the moment she died,
these past 15 years,
I've devoted myself to one thing—
molding you, through relentless effort,
into exactly the person
I envisioned.
When you were a child,
you were just like your mother—
the kindness and compassion in your bones
made me sick.
You are my son.
You're in the royal family.
You are the heir I've chosen!
You must be even more cold-blooded
and ruthless than I am!
Xiyang and I had only one mother.
I don't want her to raise us.
From now on,
she...
is your mother.
So you did all of that on purpose.
On the day my mother died,
the first thing you said to me
was to make me
accept someone else as my mother.
From that moment on,
you meant to make me hate you.
Without soul-deep hatred,
how else could I have
rid you of the weakness inside you?
All these years,
you've clawed your way forward
on your own.
My painstaking efforts were not in vain.
You've gone mad.
Only through madness can one win.
You only care about victory
and yourself!
My mother died because of you!
-You never deserved her!
-I deserved her!
I gave her
all the beautiful things,
but she refused them.
What she rejected, I give to you.
Am I wrong?
I want to hand you the realm I conquered
with my own blood! Am I wrong?
Am I...
Go on, keep shouting and cursing!
Why have you stopped?
I'm holding the sword.
You know your son
won't kill you.
But I will!
I won't show you any mercy!
When my son and I are talking,
it's not your place to interrupt.
Your son?
In what way do you resemble a father?
Although I have no parents
or kin,
I know
real families
are not like this.
I've never seen a father
hurt his son like this
or force his son like this!
The "son" you speak of
is nothing but a tool
to carry on your ambition!
What kind of father are you?
This is the investiture edict.
I've already named you Crown Prince.
All these years,
I've kept Zhuang Shen alive
only to use him
as a means to hone you!
I'm handing you the thing
I've treasured most
in my life!
Go!
Storm the palace,
seize the imperial seal,
and stamp this edict.
Then you will be the Crown Prince.
Kill me! After I die,
you'll be the emperor of Susha!
I'm entrusting the nation to you!
You must make this country even stronger!
That's just your wishful thinking!
That's not what Feng Suige truly wants!
You need say no more!
You don't love him at all.
You just have no other choice.
Have you ever protected him?
Where were you
when he needed you?
You keep saying
you are his father,
but have you ever done
one thing a father should do?
Look at
what you've become now.
Abandoned by all, family shattered,
wife dead, and children estranged.
You treat your son
like an enemy,
yet still pretend to be
a loving father.
Aren't you ashamed of such hypocrisy?
And now
you're taking refuge here.
This was his mother's place.
Do you even deserve to be here?
I am a wise ruler.
You don't understand
my painstaking efforts
or my duty to family and country!
Do you understand?
As it's said,
family comes before country!
You don't even care for your own family—
how can you speak of duty
to family and country!