Characters, actions, places, occupations,
(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
and events in this series are fictional and
created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge
or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
You mustered the courage
to break up with your boyfriend.
Why don’t you try something new?
Trust me. You can do it.
There’s a chance
that we will get back together.
We had a brief kiss.
You’re okay with it, right?
Didn’t you say I’m not your type?
You can be my type for one night.
Bambi.
You get the wrong person.
We shouldn’t have kissed that night.
Now, it’s hard to see you
as just a sister.
I’m sorry.
I didn’t know that she would come back.
Are you still interested
in being more than a one-night stand?
Thank you, everyone,
for showing your support for Fiona and me.
All the promotional videos for the brand.
Don’t you think they look great?
Yes.
Please give a round of applause
to Prim Pariyakorn Rungruengsuk,
the director of these videos
and my girlfriend.
What genres of music
are you into right now?
Didn’t you say
you knew everything about me?
You can’t even remember
the music that I like.
Time passes, people change.
Do you still listen to the same music
as in high school?
Yes.
See?
You are attached to the past.
You keep going back to the same memories
and the same people.
You always find a way
to talk about yourself.
Why don’t you try to listen
to disco music?
I don’t like dancing.
What about metal music?
It’s too heavy.
What about sexy music?
Can you stop joking around?
Or…
do you want to listen to…
my style?
Knock it off.
I didn’t let you tag along to joke around.
I’m not joking around.
I’m just thinking about
when we were in college.
When I waited for you
to buy vinyl records at a thrift store.
You told me
you wanted to make a lot of money.
So you could buy as many vinyl records
as you wanted.
You finally achieved your goal.
Not really. I still need to be careful
when spending money.
I have to take care of my mom and sister.
Unlike you, I can’t just point
and buy whatever, and I have to work.
Who said I don’t work?
I do.
I’m helping my mom manage her brand.
You know what?
My goal is to be so successful
that I’m on the list of
Asia’s most influential people under 30.
I hope you achieve it.
You already have everything you need.
I can do it
if I have you by my side as my girlfriend.
I am not your girlfriend yet.
I only give you a chance
to prove yourself.
Don’t get too excited.
You are unpredictable.
I never know
which version of you will show up.
There’s only one version of me.
I’m pretty.
I’m rich.
I’m cute.
I’m good at pampering you.
I’m still that darling
you have fallen in love with
since college.
I was in love with you.
At least, you once loved me.
Shasha.
Do you have a new toothbrush?
Yes, it’s under the wash basin.
Can you find it for me?
I can’t find it. This is not my condo.
Don’t you have a regular toothbrush?
No.
An electric toothbrush
can clean teeth better.
Don’t worry.
I get a new brush head for you.
I never share my toothbrush with anyone.
Thank you.
You can keep it.
So you can use it next time you come here.
There won’t be next time.
You can throw it away after I use it.
Are you sure?
How many times have you come here?
Is it the third time?
If my friend didn’t bail on me last night,
I wouldn’t come here.
Fine.
If it makes you feel better,
you can use whatever excuse you want
to deny that you have a thing for me.
It’s fine by me.
It’s not easy to be a model.
You can only eat healthy food.
You can’t have sweets.
It’s okay.
I can have something else
instead of sweets.
My appetite was fulfilled last night.
Can you stop saying this stuff?
It’s so lame.
What do you want me to say?
I still don’t know
how you want me to treat you.
You said you wanted us
to be friends with benefits.
But right now,
we are doing only half of it.
You’re doing it again.
We slept together. So we got the benefits.
But we are not friends.
Okay.
My name is Gorya.
I’m 24.
My family opens a diner.
I’m an only child.
My parents wanted me to be a doctor.
But I chose to study fashion.
My favorite is red.
I like listening to rock music
and ghost stories,
but I’m scared of ghosts.
My longest relationship is one year long.
We broke up because she cheated on me.
I wasn’t sad for long
because I’d rather focus on work.
I don’t care because I’m pretty.
My biggest goal is to start
my own clothing brand named Gorya.
That’s all.
Now you know me.
Your turn.
My name is Shasha.
I’m 25.
I’m the only child.
My mom took me to auditions since I was 8.
My nanny was my friend.
My closest friend is my manager.
My favorite color is black.
I like classical music.
I’ve had only one girlfriend.
Then I realized that
I don’t want to be in a relationship.
I don’t like taking responsibility
for other people’s feelings.
I just want to do whatever I want
and go wherever I want.
I don’t dream of tomorrow.
I just enjoy today.
What?
Are you the kid
in the Crocodile toothbrush ad?
You played a tooth worm.
Be careful, tooth worms are dangerous.
Stop it.
It’s been ages.
How can you still remember it?
I think we can be friends.
You are not a bad person.
I told you I’m a nice person.
Don’t get ahead of yourself.
Even as friends,
we need to get to know each other first.
I’ll get tissue for you.
Do you want a blueberry?
You can catch a taxi home.
I’m going to meet Min at the gallery.
Can I come with you?
I’m free today.
Didn’t you say you are working now?
You should focus on your work.
I have my own priority.
You know that
I always put love before work.
-Go home.
-No.
Bambi.
When did you get back?
Why didn’t you visit Zee?
I’m sorry. Do I know you?
Bambi, don’t you remember me?
I’m Pae, Zee’s friend.
Zee? Who?
I don’t know anyone by that name.
Zee is…
I think you got the wrong person.
I don’t know you.
You may have seen me on social media.
If you’re my fan,
this is my personal time.
Bambi.
Ouch.
Bambi, are you okay?
Why are you running away?
I’m scared of a stalker like her.
Ouch.
I think you should have
a doctor take a look.
Maybe the injury is serious.
It’s okay. It’s not that serious.
Why risk it?
The injury could get worse.
I’ll take you to the hospital.
Come on.
Her ankle is just sprained.
There is no broken bone.
In the meantime, you should refrain
from walking too much and wearing heels.
What?
I don’t like wearing flats.
Bambi.
Your ankle is injured. It’s not the time
to worry about your looks.
It’s okay, Doctor.
I’ll take care of it.
Thank you.
Why did you run away?
Why didn’t you ask for my help?
I was afraid of a creep like her.
She didn’t look like a creep.
It looked like she knew you.
She might be one of my mom’s fans.
Or she might be a stalker
who wanted to get close to me.
This kind of thing could happen
to a pretty girl like me.
Can you stop joking around?
Do you really not know her
and the person named Zee
that she talked about?
No, I don’t know them.
Let’s forget about it.
Will I be able to walk?
Wait here.
Come here.
Easy.
Will I ever find
an amazing girlfriend like you?
You will never find one.
I’m the type that if you lose me once,
you lose me forever.
I’m helping you
because I feel bad for you.
Hold them.
But I’m injured.
I’m a patient.
Hold them, Miss Bambi.
You are so mean.
Here we go.
Be gentle.
Ouch.
I mean it.
You’re at a hospital?
Alright. It’s okay.
I hope her injury is not serious.
Alright.
How is Prim?
I heard you said she’s at a hospital.
Prim is fine.
Bambi fell and sprained her ankle.
So they end up getting back together.
They have a love-hate relationship.
What about us?
You kissed me.
Aren’t you going to give me your answer?
Don’t act all innocent.
You set me up for it.
But you also played along with it,
didn’t you?
I get it.
These feelings are new to you.
I don’t mean to pressure you.
But I want you to know
that I really like you.
I know.
But don’t rush me.
Give me some time.
I want to be sure
that I’m not doing this
because I feel lonely
or I have a moment of weakness.
I understand you.
I don’t want to pressure you.
If I cross the line,
you can always tell me.
But I can’t really tell.
The line is very blurred to me.
If you want me to see you as a friend,
I don’t think I can do it.
You understand me, right?
Then…
we should take things slowly.
You need to give
a newbie like me some time.
I’ll see you as a senior in this.
One day,
I’ll cross this line of senior-junior.
Do you really need
to dig through this pile of clothes?
This is the life of
a hard-working stylist.
If you want to be my friend,
then you need to get used to
this kind of life.
These used clothes,
if we know how to mix and match them,
we can sell them.
Some of them are in terrible conditions.
That’s why we need to hand-pick them.
Since you’re here,
you should make yourself useful.
Sit down.
Pick those that look pretty and cool.
How will I know which ones you like?
Just do it.
I trust your taste.
Do you want this one?
Here.
Do you want to take a break?
It feels better to have you
take care of me.
Hold it yourself.
I don’t think you can do it.
Don’t be so quick to judge.
I’m still a newbie.
Give me some time.
This is the only time I took you here.
I’m afraid that your delicate skin
might get rashes, miss princess.
These are what I picked and will buy.
What? They are in the pile.
I want them too.
If you picked them, then
you should have put them by your side.
I only turned to talk to my friend
for a few seconds.
They are what I picked.
I don’t care.
I like them too.
Miss, what are you going to do
with these clothes?
I’m going to sell them.
I’ll buy them.
How much are they?
250 baht.
If you take all three,
the total will be 750.
Okay. I’ll buy them.
I’ll buy only the ones my friend wants.
Sure. You’ll take all three, right?
I’m so lucky.
I don’t have to sell them somewhere else.
I’ll go buy a drink and be right back.
If you want them, you should hold them.
Anyone has the right to take them.
Shasha.
Look. It’s only 20 baht per item.
You are spending money recklessly.
If it’s what you want, you will have it.
How about this one?
Do you really think it looks good?
Yes. Don’t you like it?
Do you think it looks good
if you have to wear it?
Put it here.
I’ll ask my dad
to carry them upstairs later.
I can help you carry them upstairs.
No.
Only my close friends
are allowed to go upstairs.
I’ve helped you all day,
but I’m still not your close friend?
Not even close.
I feel discouraged.
A girl like you…
it seems like you never struggle in life.
Why?
Do you think it’s easy to be a model?
I’m not saying it’s easy.
But it’s not as tough as my job.
I want to be one too.
Do I do it right?
How am I doing?
Do I have the potential to be a model?
Do you know,
before I got where I am,
what kind of pain I had to endure?
Hey.
I know this is a scene from Notting Hill.
It’s my favorite movie.
We have the same favorite movie.
I want to tell you this.
My life is not easy.
My mom was very controlling
about how I looked.
She always corrected my posture.
I’ve never had a friend.
All I did was go to auditions.
Try to live like that for ten years.
Then you will understand me.
Fine. I’m sorry.
It’s okay.
I get it.
Those who don’t know me
will think my life is perfect.
I’m leaving.
Today, I’m your friend,
but I haven’t gotten any benefits.
Shasha.
Stop it. I’m not in the mood.
You should leave.
Okay. Bye.
She still doesn’t answer your calls?
It’s been three days.
No.
I still don’t understand
why she had to run away.
Did she ever tell you what happened
while she was abroad?
No.
She only told me she went to study abroad.
She was not in the mood
and wanted to get back at her mom.
So she contacted no one in Thailand.
That’s all.
If you’re curious, you need to dig up.
Social media is for snooping on people.
I REALLY MISS YOU.
Does your ankle still hurt?
Did you go to the doctor’s appointment?
It doesn’t hurt anymore.
I’m just wearing the bandage
to get your sympathy.
Why did you turn off your phone
and not reply to my texts?
I wanted to have an introverted moment.
I went off the grid to make you miss me.
I have something to give you.
Ouch.
Stop, Bambi.
What do you want? I’ll get it for you.
The vinyl records over there.
Take all of them.
Wow, Bambi.
They are all rare records.
Yes.
They are…
yours.
I can’t take them.
Your dad really treasured them.
He is dead. He wouldn’t mind.
You can take them.
I can’t take them.
It’s worth thousands of baht.
You should take them.
My mom and I won’t play them anyway.
I’m sure
you will take better care of them.
Thank you.
I don’t have to buy records for a while.
Don’t forget to listen to them every day.
This one is so cool, Bambi.
Bambi.
Yes.
If you have a problem,
you can always tell me.
No matter what our relationship is,
I’ll always care about you.
Why are you saying
these sweet words to me?
I like staying like this.
Thank you.
Can you look at the camera?
Please smile at the camera.
One, two, three. Beautiful.
One, two, three, Great.
Congratulations, Bambi.
Thank you.
Did you find out what happened
when she was abroad?
I haven’t talked to her.
I’m waiting until she’s ready to talk.
If she wants to tell me, she will.
She looks really pretty today.
You think so?
She always looks pretty like this.
Min. Prim.
Praew.
You work for this event? I didn’t know it.
I’m shooting behind-the-scenes pictures.
Min helped me get this job.
Why didn’t you tell me?
I just helped her get a job.
I don’t need to tell you about it.
Excuse me.
I’ll go and give her the flower.
Fine.
You bought it for her.
It’s the flower from our company.
I already asked for an invoice for it.
Min.
Thank you for this job.
It saves my life.
It’s not a big deal.
When you become famous,
your fee will be high.
So I’d better hire you now.
If it is your job, I won’t take any pay.
I want…
What? What do you want?
Didn’t you tell me
you wouldn’t cross the line?
You are so pretty today.
I can’t help it.
You need to be patient.
If you want good stuff,
it will take some time.
It’s done, Shasha.
You can change your outfit over there.
Thank you.
Sha.
Claire.
It’s been a while since we last met.
I’m busy.
I miss you.
Yeah.
I think that night…
it was really fun.
Why didn’t you contact me?
Did I do something wrong?
No, you didn’t.
It just…
We were just having fun, right?
I know.
But…
I want to go to your condo again.
I promise that this time,
it will be unforgettable.
Mod.
Why is the model not putting the dress on?
The show is about to begin.
Gorya, the model…
She what?
Do your job, Mod.
We are here to work.
We don’t have time to fool around.
Wow.
You remember my favorite flower.
Can you give it to me later?
The flower is from Lady Bird.
Stop making excuses.
Pony.
-Hello.
-Hi, sis.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
Pony.
Prim, this is Pony.
She owns a women’s clothes business.
She’s launching a new collection.
She’s looking for a production team
for her promotional video.
Hello, Pony. I’m Prim.
Hello.
Bambi told me
that you produced the Fiona ad.
She said you are talented.
I’m looking for a production team
that understands what I want.
So we can work together for a long time.
Can I have your contact info?
I’ll have my employee contact you.
Sure.
Here.
Thank you.
See you.
See you. Thank you.
Let’s take pictures.
Stop it, Bambi.
You don’t need to get this close.
We need to create buzz.
What buzz?
You’ll see.
Thank you, everyone,
for showing your support for Fiona and me.
My mom made Yanin a legendary brand
a long time ago.
The legend is still alive.
But now we are starting a new chapter.
Things that are so old and outdated
that we thought
they would never have a comeback.
If we work hard,
I believe
it can regain its top spot one day.
Hold on.
There’s another important person.
All the promotional videos for the brand.
Don’t you think they look great?
Yes.
Please give a round of applause
to Prim Pariyakorn Rungruengsuk,
the director of these videos
and my girlfriend.
Why didn’t you tell me?
Can you step closer?
-Please smile.
-Can you look at the camera?
Nice.
Can I have one more picture?
You are leaving?
Aren’t you going to the afterparty?
No.
I’ve gone through random bullshit today.
Are you upset about Prim and Bambi?
Don’t tell me…
you are still not over her?
It’s none of your business.
I’m not the type
who can get over quickly like you.
What do you mean?
Are you jealous to see me with Claire?
Why would I be jealous?
I slept with her once.
She likes me,
but I don’t feel the same way.
I don’t want to know.
Let me go.
I want to go home.
Do you want to go to my condo?
Let me go.
Gorya.
Are you okay?
It’s nothing. I’m leaving.
Congratulations, Prim.
You and Bambi officially became a couple.
Those who have a crush on you
will go home and cry.
You don’t need to congratulate me.
Bambi just wanted to create buzz.
Gorya.
Aren’t you going to the afterparty?
No.
I have nothing to celebrate today.
Congratulations.
Are you going to keep them both?
Won’t you give me a chance?
What are you talking about?
Bambi, can you take a picture with me?
Ready?
Thank you.
Why did you do that?
I haven’t agreed to it.
Calm down.
I’ve thought it through.
This will benefit you.
How?
People are paying attention
to this nonsense.
The buzz will put you in the spotlight.
You win.
I win.
People pay attention to my brand.
You have new connections from this event.
I don’t want to get new jobs this way.
I work hard to get where I am
without help from you or your mom.
But that’s not enough, Prim.
These connections can help you
achieve your dream.
An international award, don’t you want it?
Yes, but not like this.
I can do it myself.
I don’t need help from anyone.
Anyone?
I’m just anyone to you?
I did all this for you.
You’ve never done anything for me, Bambi.
You did everything for your own benefit.
Like always.
Sure.
I’ll go get it.
Under the counter, right?
Sure. Bye.
Praew. Where are you going?
Min.
I need to go to Blossom
to get something for Ant.
Isn’t the bar closed today?
She gave me the keys.
Do you need a ride?
I’m going that way.
Are you going that way?
Or do you want me to ride with you?
Stop flirting with me. Get in.
I can’t give you an inch.
I never saw the bar when it was empty.
The bar closes once a week.
You need to let her have a day off.
Where is it?
I found it.
I’ll let her know.
Do you want a drink?
I can make it for you.
No.
We can’t take her drink behind her back.
She trusts you.
She won’t mind.
We can have it.
She was the one
who taught me how to make drinks.
Let’s have a drink.
There are only us in this bar tonight.
Is it a good idea?
If it’s not good,
I won’t ask you to do it.
Hey.
Do you know what?
I wanted to be a bartender.
But when I thought about it,
I didn’t think I could do it.
I’m a lightweight.
I can tell.
Your cheeks are all red.
Is it that obvious?
Can I ask you for real?
Why do you like me?
Can I tell you the truth?
You are pretty.
There are many pretty girls out there.
Why don’t you like them?
Why are you pushing me away?
I like you.
Why are you telling me
to like someone else?
I’m not pushing you away.
I just want to know if I’m worth enough
for someone to fall for me.
That jerk not only hurt your feelings,
but he also ruined your self-confidence.
Min.
I want you to know…
you are so cool.
Do you know that?
You are super cool.
Even though I started to like you because
you are pretty, talented, and kind,
I’ll always find new reasons
to fall for you.
Even in the end,
we may not end up together.
You will be the last straight girl
that I fall for.
What if I’m not straight anymore?
I’m here to pick up the records
I ordered the other day.
How is your girlfriend?
I saw her fall the other day.
She is now okay.
Is it all done?
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Can I ask you something?
You came to talk to Bambi the other day.
Do you remember?
Yes.
You were with her.
Do you know Bambi?
Yes.
Her ex is my friend.
I didn’t get why she pretended
that she didn’t know me.
But now I get it.
I guess she can’t deal with what happened.
What happened?
I’m sorry.
What is your relationship with Bambi?
I’m her girlfriend.
Zee broke up with her girlfriend
to date Bambi.
They were dating for around six months.
They keep their relationship private.
They didn’t go public.
Zee told me that it was Bambi’s rule.
She wanted to be sure about
their relationship before telling anyone.
So Zee agreed
to keep their relationship a secret.
Why did they break up?
Zee told me
that Bambi still couldn’t get over her ex.
They had a big fight.
It led to an accident.
What accident?
Gorya.
Wake up, sweetie.
Why are you still sleeping when you have
an appointment with your friend?
Wake up.
Get up.
An appointment with whom?
I don’t have an appointment.
Today is my day off.
I’m going to sleep until noon.
Do you remember it wrong?
She’s been waiting for you for a while.
Come on.
Get up.
Who is she?
It’s on the tip of my tongue.
Shashasha.
That’s her name.
Shashasha?
Yes.
Don’t keep her waiting. Get up.
Mom.
Her name is Shasha.
It’s the same.
Come on. Get up.
Get up now.
It’s not good to keep her waiting.
Enjoy your food.
Thank you.
What are you doing here?
I want to get more sleep.
Minced pork and basil stir-fry with water,
with low salt and spicy level,
and served with a soft-boiled egg.
What do you want?
This is another thing
you need to learn about me.
What games are you playing?
There’s no need for us
to get to know each other anymore.
Let’s call it quits.
I won’t go to your condo again.
It’s okay.
I don’t want that from you anyway.
I just want to be your friend.
Is it that hard for you to find a friend?
You’re not afraid to point out
when I do something wrong or lame.
I want to have someone honest in my life.
Fine.
Miss high-maintenance…
…model.
Where are you taking me today?
Hello, Bambi.
Are you not mad at me anymore?
Are you free?
Can you come out to meet me?
No, I don’t want to go.
I have something important to tell you.
Please come to see me.
I’ll send my location to you.
I said I won’t go.
Prim.
What time is it, Min?
11 o’clock.
I was sleeping so comfortably
that I lost track of time.
How do you feel?
I’ve never woken up this late.
I guess we had a great time last night.
We cuddled and lost track of time.
In the end,
the person who told me
not to cross the line
broke the rule herself.
It’s just a physical thing.
Emotionally, I’m still the same.
We are still friends.
What we did last night,
friends don’t do that.
The friend zone ended
when your lips touched mine.
Min, stop hesitating.
Cross the line and be on my side.
Don’t rush me.
I’m still learning it.
What we did last night,
it doesn’t seem like
you need to learn anymore.
You are so good at it,
like you’re an expert.
I don’t want to wake up.
Being friends,
we don’t need to be this close.
We aren’t following the rules of friends.
We are following the rules of shooting.
We need to hit the target.
So I have to get close to teach you.
Be careful.
If you aren’t careful,
you might become the target yourself.
I won’t be an easy target.
I’ll wait and see.
When I set my sights on something,
I’ve never missed.
Prim.
Stop filming me.
I don’t look good right now.
It’s not true.
You’ve never left your house
if you don’t feel pretty.
No matter how sad you are,
you never let anyone see you unkempt
except me.
Just say what you want to tell me.
I’m sorry about the other day.
I didn’t mean to say what I said.
You always have a way to surprise me.
I was just taken aback.
Then what?
I know that you mean well.
You are the one
who knows everything about me.
You are the only one I’m not afraid to cry
when watching a scene where a dog dies.
You are the only one
who is in the memory space
of my computer
and my head.
You are the only one…
who I can share my stupid dream with
because you never look down on it.
This place.
It was where I asked you to be
my girlfriend when we were in college.
It will also be the place…
where I ask you to be my girlfriend again.
I miss you so much.
All the bad things in the past,
it’s just the past.
Let’s leave them behind.
Let’s have a fresh start.
I still want to share
my happiness with you.
(Bambi still couldn’t get over her ex.)
They had a big fight.
It led to an accident.
What accident?
They were arguing
while they were in the car.
They had an accident.
Zee…
She died.
I think Bambi still can’t deal with it.
That’s why she pretended
that she didn’t know me.
I’m sorry.
I want you to understand
that I did everything
because I want to see you happy.
That’s all.
I get it now.
Don’t disappear from my life again.
Can you do that?
Don’t leave me, Bambi.
I’m here now.
Don't cry.
If I knew getting back together
would be this good,
I would have done it a long time ago.
A straight girl like you enjoys playing
with the hearts of lesbians.
You keep messing with me like this.
Is it because you feel insecure
that Prim might be swayed?
I’m not messing with you.
I just want to be your friend.
You called me your girlfriend.
Then you’ll be my girlfriend for tonight.
It’s not easy to be my girlfriend.
You are picky.
You should go back
and enjoy the night with her.
Are you jealous because of Kris?
We had a great time back then.
But I’m going to make today even better.