KING THE LAND
I love you, Sa-rang.
I love you too.
I don't want to go back to Korea.
I just want to stay here
for the rest of my life.
- I love Bangkok.
- Is it good?
What about Cho-rong?
She's probably eagerly waiting for you.
You're right, I had a daughter.
I almost forgot.
Cho-rong's mom, what's wrong with you?
Come to your senses.
Okay.
It is pretty sad to leave.
It all feels like a dream.
We can always do this again.
Somewhere even better next time.
Don't forget what you just said.
Okay, I definitely won't, ma'am.
What's the point of traveling together
when everyone just splits up?
Why did I even bother planning this trip,
Mr. No?
He's right.
You crossed the line and upset Mr. Yoo.
You're the best.
So…
that is why
I prepared a final present.
What is it?
It's a secret.
That means there's nothing.
You're right.
Okay. Let's go.
We go hard!
- We go hard!
We are…
- One!
These are our seats?
We all have business-class seats.
This is unreal.
Well of course.
King Group's VIP employees
should sit in VIP seats.
- Do you like it?
- Yes.
Totally. I love it.
Watch your head.
I've always just served
the passengers who sit here.
I never imagined
that I'd get to sit here myself.
I know, right? What is all of this?
I have so much space.
Mr. Yoo, thank you so much.
We'll make sure to increase sales.
Enjoy it to the fullest.
You all deserve it.
You're the best!
This trip was perfect
from start to finish.
Thank you.
I should be thanking you.
I had fun thanks to you.
Am I allowed to be this happy?
I'll make you even happier in the future.
EPISODE 11
The 100th-anniversary event is important
as it can only be held once a century.
No mistakes are allowed.
The banquet will consist of ten courses.
We'll mainly be in charge of
greeting the important guests
and serving the VVIP tables.
Since we'll be serving VVIPs,
let's provide the best service
under King the Land's name.
- Okay. We'll do our best.
Once we receive the guest list,
can you check their information
and make sure we don't miss anything
that needs to be prepared, Ha-na?
Yes, I'll make sure to do that.
I'll tell you if there are any changes.
That's it for today's meeting.
Also, Ms. Best Employee,
did you have a fun trip?
Yes, I enjoyed my time thanks to you.
They chose one employee per subsidiary.
I'm glad the hotel's best employee
was someone from King the Land.
I'm proud.
Let's work hard
so that the next best employee
gets chosen from King the Land.
- Yes, ma'am.
Ms. Jeon,
this isn't much, but…
- What is this?
- It's a bath bomb.
I heard you take a bubble bath
every night after work.
I picked one with a nice scent.
It's so touching to hear
that you thought of me while traveling.
Thank you. I'll use it well.
All right.
Look at her currying favor.
She only brought something for Ms. Jeon.
This is for you, Du-ri.
This is yours, Se-ho.
This is for you, Da-seok,
and Ne-mo.
This is yours, Ha-na.
You didn't have to buy stuff for us too.
It's really nothing much.
I just thought of you all while shopping.
Also, we're a team.
Thank you. I'll use it well.
- Thank you.
- Thanks so much for this.
This is the hotel's plaque
prepared as a gift for the VIP guests
who will be attending the event.
WE APPRECIATE YOUR SUPPORT
It looks better than I expected.
Good work.
I'm glad to hear that you like it.
I planned and prepared it myself.
All right. But is this real gold?
Yes. Following the limits
of the anti-graft law,
I prepared 3 don of pure gold,
which is 11.25 g.
Let's prepare gifts for the employees too.
- For every single one?
- Of course.
Will the hotel be able to afford it?
If it's that burdensome,
we can take out your gift.
It's not burdensome at all.
I love your idea.
If it's for everyone,
I'd recommend
a hotel voucher or a buffet ticket.
Let's put our convenience aside.
Survey what the employees actually want,
and prepare it that way.
Yes, sir.
I'll listen to their opinions
and prepare a gift
that will satisfy their wishes.
Good. Thank you.
Mr. Gu?
- Mr. Gu!
- Yes?
Hey.
I called you multiple times,
but you wouldn't respond, sir.
Sorry. I was a little busy with this.
Then what do you think
of working in your office?
No, it's okay.
You're probably busy.
You can go back to work.
I'm asking you because
I can't work properly with you here.
This is not an office.
You shouldn't be acting like this here.
Can't I work here a little?
Of course not.
What?
Who's the boss here?
Get me the boss.
I just want to see your face.
It's hard to make time
in the midst of all my work.
It's nice to be in the same space as you,
even for a short while.
Is it just me?
No.
I feel the same way.
Would you like something to drink, sir?
I'll take anything, please.
Since you usually drink tea
rather than coffee in the afternoon,
what do you think of Earl Grey tea?
But how do you know so much about me?
Are you interested in me?
It's my job as a King the Land employee
to remember our guests' preferences.
If that's the only reason,
then it's slightly upsetting.
Look who's talking.
You didn't even respond when I called you.
You sure can hold a grudge.
I'm pretty sure I already said sorry.
You said you were upset,
so I just mentioned something as well.
If you're that upset,
why don't we leave together later?
How do we do that
with all these people watching?
There are one, two, three,
four, five, six… Not that many.
That's not a lot.
Did we commit a crime?
Is love a crime?
I just don't want to be
the center of their gossip.
We can leave separately,
then meet up later.
Mr. Gu.
I looked everywhere for you.
Ms. Gu is looking for you.
Rather urgently, if I may add.
The guest list for the
100th-anniversary event isn't finalized.
Yes, it is.
I just need to make a final decision.
What's the difference?
You don't have time to take it easy.
Even the chairman's secretary's office
is asking for the guest list.
I'm not taking it easy.
I'm just trying to be careful.
Then carefully make a quick decision.
And take a look at this.
This is the list of the VIPs
invited to major King Group events
over the past five years.
For your information,
Ms. Gu has mainly invited politicians
such as members of
the National Assembly and the LITC.
So?
We should do the same?
No.
As the people
who will be leading King Group,
we should go with a young,
future-oriented, and global image.
That's why I was thinking…
Let's invite popular K-pop idols.
I'll obviously be in charge
of inviting them.
I told you to prepare for the event,
not satisfy your own interests.
I'll take care of the rest.
You can just focus on the rehearsal.
Got it?
I'm counting on you.
"I'm counting on you."
You're cool.
Gosh. "I'm counting on you."
Invite the people on that list.
I asked Assemblyman Park
to give a congratulatory address,
so arrange a section
after the chairman's speech.
I'm in charge of the event.
Just accept my help while it lasts.
It's my responsibility,
so I'll do whatever I want.
When you're in charge,
you can do whatever you want.
You should know when to quit acting up.
The 100th-anniversary event is not a joke.
We'll be presenting
who we'll be working with
for the next 100 years.
We need dignified people to be there.
Politicians, high-ranking officials
from the Ministry of Finance…
I guess you want to
create a future with these people.
They are valuable people
for all of King Group's subsidiaries.
I don't want to create anything
with these people.
Success attained by mooching off
of those with power
will crumble in front of power
no matter what.
You know that.
Then what kind of future
will you make with whom?
There's a saying that the moment
you forget about the people
who helped you along the way
is the moment of your fall.
That means the next 100 years
should be created with the people
who helped build up this hotel.
It must be fun playing the hero.
You even gave the employees
business-class seats kept for executives
and tried so hard to win their favor.
Do you think you'll become something
if you have them on your side?
I wasn't trying to win their favor.
I just did the obvious.
Whether an executive or an employee,
anyone who works hard for the company
will receive the same treatment.
- Who are you to do that?
- Me?
Someone with a conscience.
At the very least,
the company shouldn't be stabbing
its employees in the back.
Don't you think?
Do you really think
all people are the same?
Even though all balloons look the same,
some float up and some fall down.
What differentiates them
is their blood.
They may look the same, but they're not.
Because they have different genes.
Just like you and me.
How am I different?
Just live without knowing.
That's your fate.
ALANGA SALES TARGET
This is our new target.
Calculate the sales on a daily basis
and give me a report
when you clock out every day.
The target amount is too high.
So you can't do it?
No, we can't.
Our original goal of a 10% increase
compared to last month is already so high.
All right.
Then I'll report to headquarters
about a personnel reduction here.
Sorry? A personnel reduction?
Sales may be increasing,
but so are the rent
and incidental expenses.
Alanga is in the red.
With the current sales,
we can't keep everyone.
So after this month…
MIN YU-BIN
…fire the junior member.
All of a sudden?
That's why I gave you a solution.
But you rejected it.
Well, then.
Wait. I'll do it.
We can do it.
You should've said that earlier.
How peaceful and nice is it now?
I'm an advocate of peace.
By the way,
you should treat the rest of us
to an expensive meal.
Why?
It was thanks to me
that you went to Bangkok.
Did you forget?
It wasn't thanks to you, Ms. Do.
It was a result of my own efforts.
Who gave you the motivation?
Thanks to me,
who encouraged you to work harder,
you achieved record-high sales
and got chosen as the best employee.
I heard omakase dining
is the trend these days.
Make a reservation for next week.
Then,
I'll be leaving to work offsite.
It is a Mediterranean appetizer dish
made with natural oysters
from the west coast.
I used fennel to give it a fresh flavor.
It's fresh. It'd make a good appetizer.
For the main course,
we prepared prime beef tenderloin
with a marbling score of nine
from free-range, organic cows
from an animal welfare farm.
Great.
Overall, everything looks excellent.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you, sir.
Starting three months ago,
head chefs from each restaurant
have worked together
using the best ingredients.
There will be some elderly guests.
I'd like to add some dishes
that are easy to digest.
Also, what do you think of preparing
a separate full-course meal
for people who prefer Korean food,
so that they can choose?
Understood.
I'll discuss it with the others
and have it prepared.
All right. Thank you.
I'll take the steak. Thank you.
So you failed to get promoted again.
Mind your own business.
What's the point of working your ass off?
Learn from Mi-na.
She buys presents for her boss
and even helps her family make kimchi.
Who wouldn't adore her?
Let's go for a consolation drink.
- No thanks.
- All right then.
Suit yourself.
Ms. Yoo.
Yes?
Why don't we go somewhere nice
and have some drinks
to celebrate Mi-na's promotion?
That sounds great.
Then will it be on you?
I will pay for your drink, Ms. Yoo.
Okay, let's go. You all heard him, right?
Yes, I'd love to go.
I'm sorry,
but I don't think I can join you all.
What?
Ro-un, we have to listen to
whatever the captain says.
I have plans.
All of us had plans as well.
No, it's okay.
We can't make things mandatory these days.
It's okay, right?
Well of course.
Go ahead. Get out of here.
I'm a flexible person, you know.
You're the best, Mr. No.
All right. Then please excuse me.
Let's go, Pyeong-hwa.
What?
What are you doing, Ro-un?
I had plans with Pyeong-hwa.
Then we'll be leaving first.
Let's go.
I'll get going then.
I hope you have a fun time.
Then I'll also leave if that's okay.
I was pretty tired.
Thank you for your consideration.
I can't believe this.
Did we have plans tonight?
Yes.
I was planning on coming here with you.
Our time in Bangkok was too short.
Isn't it nice here?
If the captain says so,
we all have to attend no matter what.
Aren't you even worried about tomorrow?
Tomorrow will take care of itself.
Today, I just like being here with you.
By any chance…
do you like me?
Yes.
I like you.
I'm sorry,
but I don't think
I can accept your feelings.
It's okay.
I just answered your question
because you asked.
You can do whatever you want.
I'll do what my heart tells me to do.
You can go around this way
to go to the main building.
- Goodbye.
- All right. Thank you.
- Sir.
- Mr. Gu.
Do you have a few minutes?
I'm sorry,
but an important guest
will be arriving soon,
so I can't leave.
It won't take long.
I'm sorry, Mr. Gu.
I have to greet this guest myself.
Then I'll be waiting at King the Land.
- Yes, sir. I'll be with you shortly.
- Okay.
Welcome. I was waiting for you.
How have you been?
I've been doing well thanks to you.
Right this way.
I'm sorry for making you wait.
No, I'm the one
who made the sudden request.
- Please sit.
- Okay.
What would you like to drink?
May I have a hot cup of tea?
Yes, sir.
I'll take the same thing.
All right.
You've been working here
for over seven years, right?
Both then and now,
you have a pretty smile.
How do you know how long I've worked here?
Because I'm the doorkeeper of this hotel.
You're right.
It's a pleasure to see you here, sir.
I'll get the tea prepared right away.
Who was the lady from earlier?
She visits the hotel once a month
around this hour
to eat a bowl of beef bone soup.
She used to come with her husband.
After he passed, she still comes alone.
I thought she would feel less lonely
if I waited for her in his stead.
The more I get to know the hotel staff,
the more I come to respect you all.
I think you're truly amazing.
No, I'm not.
I do this because I enjoy it.
I hear you have worked here
the longest among all the staff.
You've stayed with us for a long time,
so I wanted to meet you
and have a conversation with you.
I don't know if I'll be of any help.
Is there a guest
that you remember the most?
There is a large tree
by the main entrance of the hotel.
It was donated by someone
who was a charter member.
He also helped the hotel a lot
when it was in crisis.
After he passed away,
his son made frequent visits to the hotel,
but I haven't seen him recently.
If I get the chance,
I'd like to greet him as a guest again.
So there was someone like that.
I had no idea.
Was it always your dream
to work at a hotel?
No.
I just chased happiness
and ended up here.
So…
did you find happiness?
Thank you for your time.
Take care.
Why did you bow so politely?
- I was shocked.
- The rehearsal.
- Is everything ready?
- Yes, sir.
Shall we?
Keep the plates straight.
Don't let them tilt.
Check your entrance and exit routes
so that the food can be served smoothly.
We must not exceed our allotted time.
They're so cool.
Are the rehearsals
usually performed to this extent?
All the banquets held at King Hotel
are rehearsed the day before the event.
Since this particular event
involves serving VVIP guests,
we are rehearsing in greater detail.
Everyone is doing a lot more
than I expected.
Please keep it up until the end.
Yes, sir.
We will serve each guest
with our utmost sincerity.
Thank you.
Wait! Hold on.
- It's me.
- You scared me.
Are you okay?
- Do I look okay?
- My goodness.
How are you so strong?
My stomach.
Why did you suddenly hug me from behind?
You startled me.
I was trying to surprise you.
Though I didn't know
you'd be so excited to see me.
I'm sorry. Are you okay?
I won't have to worry about you
walking alone at night.
Did you take boxing lessons as a kid?
This sound isn't coming from my mouth.
It's coming from my punches.
Are you having fun?
I never lost to anyone
ever since I was little.
I bet.
Is it that painful?
Oh no.
Are you okay?
Goodness.
Oh no.
It hurts.
Do you need to go to the hospital?
Should we go?
It hurts.
This feels nice.
You can't do this here.
I need to recharge.
Today was so exhausting.
I'm running out of energy.
Can you plug in a charger here?
I need to recharge.
There.
I'm afraid someone might see us.
I'm at 1% now.
Just 1%?
Yes, please charge me.
Please.
I'm at 5%. Now 10%.
That's far from enough.
Charge, please.
I'm at 15, 25, 30%.
100%. I'm fully charged.
Gosh, you're so silly.
Oh my god.
- Oh my goodness.
- What?
- Hide.
- Why?
What's wrong with you?
Oh no.
They're King Hotel employees.
- Get up.
- But where?
- Hold on. Where?
- The bus.
- Hurry.
- That gave me a fright.
- You're employees, yes?
"Employees"?
Hello, Mr. Gu!
- Hello, Mr. Gu!
Hello, Mr. Gu.
KING HOTEL SHUTTLE BUS
Mr. Gu,
this is the shuttle bus that helps
King Hotel employees commute
to and from work.
The hotel has three shifts,
so the bus operates
six different times throughout the day.
We enjoy a lot of employee perks,
but I believe this shuttle bus
is what the employees need most.
Thank you very much.
Thank you!
- Thank you!
- Say goodbye now.
Smile and wave goodbye.
I'm very thankful as well.
- Please keep up the good work.
- We love you!
Okay.
Get home safely.
Mr. Gu will now get off.
Goodbye.
- Thank you.
Mr. Gu, you're the best!
- Thank you!
You're the best!
- That was so funny.
- Jeez.
We went out of the frying pan
into the fryer.
How did you come up with that on the spot?
My mind went completely blank.
I don't know either.
I had to ride it out somehow.
No secrets are forever.
We should still be careful.
Why?
Because I'm the chairman's son?
If I were worried about that,
I wouldn't have dated you
in the first place.
But how did you find this place?
Well,
you seemed to like the moon in Bangkok,
so I ran a search.
Apparently, this river has the most moons.
It's beautiful.
Is it?
Should we go down and walk?
By the way,
why did you meet the doorman earlier?
It was for the event.
I heard he was with the hotel the longest,
so I wanted to talk to him.
I heard he worked here for over 30 years.
He's living proof of King Hotel's history.
Yes, that's what I heard too.
By any chance…
did you ask him?
About what?
About your mom.
I'm sure he'd know.
Why bother?
"Why bother?"
There's no point in asking him.
The answer is obvious.
Where's my mom?
She wasn't here yesterday,
and she's not here today.
Please get up.
The chairman is waiting.
Whenever I asked something,
everyone kept their mouth shut
and hid the truth from me even more.
It felt as if the traces
that I'd just barely found
were all being erased.
But still,
he could be the one to tell you.
It's okay.
It was a matter
that I had to solve on my own anyway.
Also,
I decided
to put an end to my quest.
You're home.
Hurry up and sit.
What's all this?
All right.
It's good.
The sauce tastes just right.
Hey Sa-rang,
did Mr. No
do it yet?
- Do what?
- What do you think?
Ask you out.
No, we don't like each other.
Why not? What's wrong with Mr. No?
I'd say he's a pretty decent man.
It's nothing like that.
If not, why did you two
run away in Thailand
and make Mr. Yoo upset?
I think I need to wash up first.
You guys go ahead.
Gosh, it's so hot.
I can't eat because it's so hot.
Why does she feel hot all of a sudden?
So I'm suggesting that we co-host
the 100th-anniversary event
as staff representatives.
I thought you didn't like me.
That's correct.
But I have to put personal feelings aside.
You did a great job
during the inaugural ceremony.
It's only natural for me
to host the big event
as a staff representative,
but not with you.
I'm out of your league.
What a shame.
It would be nice if you were kind-hearted.
Why do you care
whether I'm kind-hearted or not?
I just think it's a pity.
You're exceptionally beautiful
and competent enough
to have become the youngest manager.
I just don't understand why you would
keep making a mockery of yourself.
- Is that an insult or a compliment?
- An insult.
Well, I'm not too keen on your offer,
but since you're begging me,
I'll lend you a helping hand
as King Hotel's most competent employee.
Yes, please help me.
I hope we get along.
I must be insane.
Why would I fall for a guy like him?
Why are you…
Does it hurt a lot?
Well of course it does.
You hit me with steel.
Goodness.
You shouldn't have snuck in
like a thief without telling me.
I just…
I came to give you these gifts.
And last time,
I noticed the water pressure was low,
so I was trying to fix the sink
while I was waiting.
Then you should've told me.
You didn't give me a chance to.
Hold on.
Come to think of it,
you and your granddaughter are so similar.
Your fist moves before your mouth.
Of course. She's my baby.
Do you know why she's so pretty?
It's because she takes after me.
But what is all of that?
These?
You know how Sa-rang went to Thailand
after being chosen as the best employee?
Thailand is known for its silk.
And this was made from its finest.
I don't have anywhere to wear this.
Why did you spend your money
on something like this?
Do you have money to burn?
From now on, you can travel a lot.
I'll take you to many places.
Let's see.
If you'll excuse me.
What do you think? Isn't it pretty?
- Oh, I don't know…
- Here.
Yes, it is pretty.
Well, I guess I do look good
no matter what I wear.
It's thanks to my good fashion sense.
Hold on a second.
This is a magical cream
that smooths out all the wrinkles
on your face.
And…
this is called Tiger Balm.
It's good for any aches or pains.
It also soothes headaches.
What?
Then is it a cure-all?
Yes, it's the best remedy for the elderly.
I see.
How much did you buy?
You could run a store with all of that.
Goodness.
You can share these
with your market friends.
I…
just bought a little.
I can't believe
you thought of my friends too.
How sweet of you.
Last time, your friends gave me
vegetable juice and yogurt drinks.
Hey,
just be a good son to your father.
Did you buy a gift for your father?
No.
Good grief.
What's the point of having kids?
Jeez.
Give this to your father.
All right.
Did you eat?
Not yet.
- Ms. Cha.
- Yes?
Here's the ginseng chicken soup.
Goodness. Just in time.
Sa-rang told me
that you raised her all by yourself
ever since she was little.
I didn't do much.
She grew well on her own.
She never once threw a tantrum
even though she lived apart from her mom.
She kept everything bottled up,
and when she acted
like a baby for the first time,
saying she wanted to live with her,
her mom got into an accident.
I think that's why
she's never asked me
to do anything for her.
From now on,
I'll stay by her side
and let her throw tantrums
and act like a baby.
You can always rely on me
to protect both you and Sa-rang.
I'm okay.
Just treat Sa-rang well, okay?
I'll treat you both well.
Thank you
for raising Sa-rang
to be such a beautiful person.
Here. I cooked it for a while
to make it tender.
- Try it.
- Thank you.
Let's see how it tastes.
- Here.
- Yes.
- Take it.
- Thank you.
Sure. Eat up.
Thank you.
Sir.
Hello.
I know this is sudden,
but may I ask you something?
Yes, go ahead.
I was wondering
if you knew someone
who used to work here long ago.
Do you know a person
by the name of Han Mi-so?
I do.
Then do you know her contact information
or where she may be right now?
I know who she is,
but that's about it.
I see.
Thank you for your time.
But I have a friend
who might remember more than I do.
Hello.
May I ask if you're Ms. Kim Ok-ja,
the room inspector?
What are you doing?
How dare you step into the room
with your shoes on?
Get out.
I'm sorry.
Hotel rooms are products
prepared for the guests.
How dare a concierge
step on a guest's product?
You don't know the basics.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to ask you something.
Whatever it is, I don't want to talk
to someone who lacks common sense.
Goodbye.
I apologize for the discourtesy.
I'll visit you again at another time.
Are you going to leave Won be?
He finally set his mind to something.
I should let him.
It's an important event.
When you first launched Alanga,
all the executives were against it.
But do you know why I let you?
I was giving you a chance.
Won should also be given
a chance for it to be fair.
Alanga's success was guaranteed.
What Won is doing
will obviously lead to failure.
If he fails,
I'll hold him responsible then.
Now is not the time to intervene.
Won acts
so much like his mom.
Don't you agree?
I'm worried about how much you'll suffer
if you have to abandon him
just like you abandoned his mom.
You're all grown up.
You're even worrying about me now.
You're home.
Yes.
Get some rest.
What is it?
Do you have something to say?
No.
Are my opinions not important
in planning for the big event?
There was something I wanted to ask.
And what is that?
Is the King Hotel of today
the hotel that you wanted it to be?
It was my dream
for everyone who came to King Hotel
to be happy.
Everyone including the guests
and the employees.
However,
a dream is just a dream.
Did you ever try to make it come true?
My employees' lives
and the lives of their families
depend on my decisions.
I believe the hotel has lasted 100 years
because I never made
any reckless attempts.
I have no regrets.
I was able to protect King Hotel
in exchange for my dream,
and I also built King Air
and King Distribution.
That's good to hear.
I…
was worried that you never had a dream.
I know what it is that you want to do.
I know what you desire too.
But
don't do it.
I'm being serious. This is a warning.
Do you understand?
- Father--
- If it's hard,
ask your sister for help.
Asking for help is a skill.
It's Tiger Balm.
Apply it to alleviate any type of pain.
Today is finally here.
It's going to be the best party ever,
so don't be nervous.
There's no need to be.
We've done well so far,
and everything will continue to go well.
No need to be nervous.
We've rehearsed enough.
It's going to be the best party
without a hitch.
So don't worry.
You can just count on me.
Why are you trembling?
Me?
What are you talking about?
I'm not the type to get nervous.
You know that.
I wasn't trembling.
I don't think so.
You're so nervous.
No, I'm not.
Why are you sweating?
I'm sweating?
Don't be nervous.
- It's a party.
- Yes.
- Have fun.
- Okay.
Drink some water.
- And breathe.
- Yes, sir.
You're super nervous.
Good luck!
2023 KING HOTEL
100TH-ANNIVERSARY CELEBRATION
100TH-ANNIVERSARY EVENT PROGRAM
WORDS OF WELCOME AND ENCOURAGEMENT
HEAD MANAGER GU WON
Goodness.
Thank you.
I thought we were doing
something important.
- This is it?
- What do you mean?
We're greeting the guests
of our hotel's 100th birthday party.
This is the most important role.
Something like this
may be important to you,
but it isn't for me.
The host is the first person
to greet the guests.
At least for today,
we are the hosts of this party.
Just wipe your sweat.
You acted so cool,
but you're a nervous wreck.
I don't get nervous. Where's the sweat?
Oh, there it is.
Do you like me?
KING GROUP
CHAIRMAN GU IL-HUN
ASSEMBLYMAN PARK DU-SIK
KING HOTEL
MANAGING DIRECTOR GU HWA-RAN
Happy 100th anniversary to King Hotel.
Hello,
I am King Hotel's head manager, Gu Won.
I would like to sincerely thank
all of the honored guests
for attending King Hotel's
100th-anniversary event.
In addition,
I'd like to express
my bottomless gratitude
to all the employees
who are working diligently
behind the scenes even now
in order to make this event shine.
Then,
we will start the ceremony
with Chairman Gu Il-hun's
congratulatory address.
Hello,
I am Gu Il-hun.
In preparation
for my congratulatory address,
I contacted a speech expert.
I told the expert that I wanted to deliver
a historic speech
for the hotel's 100th-anniversary event,
and I sought an expert's advice.
I was given an unequivocal answer.
"Just make it short."
What? Did someone arrive?
I wonder what's so funny.
We never get to watch the event.
We're always just running around.
But this time,
I feel like we're the stars of the event.
It feels like I'm serving guests
for a party at my house.
You're right.
This only happens once every 100 years.
Let's finish strong
on behalf of King the Land.
- Yes, ma'am.
Sa-rang, you're up next, right?
Yes. I'll be right back.
- Good luck.
I hope the past 100 years
will be able to shape
the next 100 years of the hotel.
Also,
for the 200th-anniversary event,
I will try to prepare
an even shorter message.
Thank you.
- I liked your speech.
- Thanks.
Thank you.
Next up, we have a special guest
who will deliver a congratulatory address.
It's your turn, Mr. Park.
- You'll do great.
- Of course.
It was not easy to invite this person.
I would like to thank you
on behalf of the hotel's executives.
Mr. Choi Yeong-su,
could you please come forward?
What is this?
Thank you for coming.
I hope I'm not disrupting the event.
You're the guest of honor.
Please.
Hello,
my name is Choi Yeong-su.
I own a small pizza shop in Daejeon.
To be honest,
I'm not exactly sure
why I was invited to this event.
I think it may be
because of my father.
My father was a charter member
of King Hotel's membership club.
I believe my father was the one
who planted the tree
in front of the hotel.
When I was little,
I came here a lot with my father.
To me, King Hotel was the best playground.
I remember the CEO of the hotel
being very loving.
But once my father's business
started to decline,
I never got to come back here.
Since I've been busy making ends meet,
I noticed that I've started to lose hope
and that I give up more easily.
However,
coming back here makes me dream.
Next Christmas,
I plan on visiting King Hotel
with my family.
Until then, I'm going to work really hard.
Also, I would like to sincerely thank
Head Manager Gu Won
for coming all the way to Daejeon
to invite a nobody like me to this event.
And…
How should I end this?
Well…
May King Hotel prosper!
Thank you.
- You may go this way.
- Hey, so you're Yeong-su.
Right? Mr. Choi Jang-su's eldest son.
Do you remember me?
How could I forget you?
I received so much help from your father.
I owe him a lot.
I'm sorry that I was unaware.
You're always welcome.
The rooms and restaurants
will always be reserved for you.
Make sure you come with your family. Okay?
Have a seat.
He's Choi Jang-su's son.
Can you believe it?
It is said
that flowers don't forget
about the person who watered them.
While planning for this event,
I continued to keep that saying in mind.
The people who helped create
the first 100 years of King Hotel
and the people who will be creating
the next 100 years are all here together.
I would now like to introduce you all
to the VIP of VIPs.
I'm sorry for the confusion.
I look forward to your speech.
The deep-rooted tree of King Hotel.
I now introduce you to Mr. Kim Bong-sik.
Hello.
I am
King Hotel's doorman, Kim Bong-sik.
You were a salesman
for a pharmaceutical company?
That's right.
I usually treated my clients
at King Hotel's bar.
At times, I would have to drink
three times a day
during lunch, dinner,
and even late at night.
But one day,
I got so drunk
that I fell asleep
on a sofa in the hotel lobby,
and when I woke up in the morning,
I witnessed
a completely different world.
All of the employees were working
with smiles on their faces.
It made me wonder
why everyone looked so happy.
That's when I started to dream.
I thought I would be able to live
with a smile on my face if I worked here.
So I started working here.
Do you think you could repeat
what you just said during our event?
What event, sir?
The 100th-anniversary event.
That's absurd.
That's not a place for me.
Please, sir.
Why are you doing this?
You're the doorkeeper of our hotel.
You looked after King Hotel for 30 years.
Please grace the occasion
with your presence.
Are you being serious?
Please share your dream
with me as well.
Coming to King Hotel,
I achieved my dream.
Most of my time at work
is spent outside of the hotel,
but I am the proud doorkeeper
of King Hotel,
Kim Bong-sik.
HOTEL LOWER LEVEL 1
Hello.
Are those the lights that were used
in our hotel 20 years ago?
Yes, that's right.
They're the first lights that I replaced
after I started working here.
But what brings you here, Mr. Gu?
I came here to ask you for a favor.
I've only been cutting meat for ten years.
A VIP?
Please. How am I a VIP?
People don't even know
there's a butcher like me
who works in the hotel.
That's why I want to show them.
That there are people
who work for the hotel
even though they've never worn a uniform.
I appreciate your intentions,
but I'm worried.
I have a low rank,
but I've worked at the hotel for longer,
so I'll be upfront.
Do you know what
the best kind of hotel is?
What?
A hotel where people like me
don't run into the guests.
That is why we always try our best
to avoid the guests.
But you're asking me
to stand on the podium?
If you put a spotlight on people like us,
you'll be criticized, Mr. Gu.
Do you know what I consider
to be the best hotel?
One that's profitable?
That's right.
The best hotel
is a highly profitable one
with high sales figures.
That is why people like you
are the most valuable.
It is you who are on the front lines
who make the best hotel.
If I had been planning on
using you for the event,
I would've just ordered HR to do this.
But you all are the most important guests,
so I came here myself.
It's King Hotel's 100th-anniversary event.
I don't want it to be held
without the guests of honor.
I have been working
in the room inspection team for 27 years,
and my name is Kim Ok-ja.
Although I don't meet the guests…
Mr. Park.
Ms. Gu.
You made a big mistake today.
You'll pay for this.
…so that the guests may feel welcomed.
That is how I've been shaping
King Hotel from my position.
Your speech was incredible.
It is an honor
to be able to serve my seniors.
Thank you.
I'm sorry about the other day.
I learned a lot.
Don't be.
I didn't consider the fact
that you don't work in the rooms.
I wanted to apologize
for getting so worked up.
Not at all.
Come again next time.
I promise I'll be more calm.
Okay. Thank you.
I'll make sure to stop by.
That's my son.
PROPOSAL FOR KING HOTEL'S
MISSION AND BUSINESS GOALS
STRATEGIC PLANNING TEAM, HAN MI-SO
"A hotel where everyone is happy"?
Do you really think that's possible?
You're more than capable
of making such a hotel.
I'll help you by your side.
Father.
What are you doing?
Are you reminiscing
when the event's been ruined?
Let's talk later.
Won and his sentimentality
cost us the most essential figure
for our group, Assemblyman Park.
The duty-free license expires next year,
so it needs to be renewed.
We also need to expand air routes.
- Aren't you aware?
- That's right.
There were so many things to do
that I lost sight of what was valuable.
Don't make me distrust you too.
King Group
is not yours alone.
- Enjoy your time.
- Sure.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
You were amazing today.
I'm always amazing.
Do you want to
come to my house this Sunday?
Pyeong-hwa won't be home
because of a flight.
Yes, I do.
I'll be there no matter what.
Make it delicious.
Thank you for inviting me.
Welcome.
They're so beautiful.
You made all of this yourself?
It's not a lot,
but I prepared it with care and love.
"It's not a lot"? This is a feast.
I just
wanted to make you a home-cooked meal.
Thank you.
MR. NO
Aren't you going to pick up?
No, I don't want to be interrupted.
I wonder what will taste the best.
- I know everything will taste good.
- Yes.
But I'll have the rolled omelet.
How does it taste? Is it okay?
It's not just okay.
It's remarkable.
You could be the sous-chef of our hotel.
Well if you hire me, I'd be happy to.
- Try this too.
- Okay.
This is so touching, babe.
"Babe"?
You should try it too, babe.
Here.
How is it?
It's so good, babe.
- You think it's good too, babe?
- Yes.
Thank you.
I don't know if I deserve to receive
such a marvelous dinner.
I'll cook for you again next time.
I'd love that.
This is nice.
It is.
The music is so nice too.
- I drank it all.
- Me too.
- I'll bring more.
- No, I'll do it.
This is my place. Let me.
- You made me food. Let me.
- No.
I'll do it.
- Me.
- Just stay still.
- I want to do it.
- Let me.
- No, I will.
- I will.
I will.
- I'll go.
- Then let's go together.
Wait.
Okay. Shall we go together?
Sure.
Are you going to drink more beer?
What if I say no?
KING THE LAND
I want to go somewhere.
Let's go.
You won't ask where it is?
Bring me reports on what you'll do
for the future of King Group.
Both of you.
The war has finally begun.
You only have me.
Make sure you report
everything related to Mr. Gu to me.
In that case,
how high can I go by helping you?
How come your employees aren't trained?
I can't leave you alone
if you're this endearing.
It's your fault.
Subtitle translation by: Stephanie Jung