ALL FIGURES, INCIDENTS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, AND OTHERS ARE FICTITIOUS
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS WERE FILMED
SAFELY IN ACCORDANCE WITH GUIDELINES
EPISODE 2
He suddenly started
talking nonsense like a madman.
He tumbled down and bumped his head.
Then, he sprawled on the floor
and blacked out--
Oh, I-rang. Are you okay?
Do you recognize me? Who am I?
Yes, what is it?
Bong-su.
I'm okay, so tell them to drop us off.
No, you're not okay.
You asked for an ambulance earlier.
That was because I felt
too ashamed to stay there.
Goodbye.
I-rang, wait for me.
I really don't get it, though.
You're all good after tumbling that hard?
- Then, was it all an act?
- An act?
You suddenly swore in dialect,
pointed your finger at the defendant,
and even tried to attack him.
I did that?
Yes, you did.
You should be nominated for an Oscar.
It wasn't an act! I blacked out for real.
Wait. Where are you going in that state?
- My office.
- What?
I can't go on like this.
I need to put an end to it.
An end?
Hello, Father. This is Shin I-rang.
I'm sorry, but could you
come over to my office?
Yes, this is an emergency.
What…
Hello, Mother.
Did you arrive?
Which hospital is it?
Oh, the thing is…
He went to his office just fine.
I don't think you should worry.
Where is his office?
That,
I don't know.
Which hospital is it?
COURTROOMS,
CIVIL MEDIATION CENTER, ANNEX
- He went to his office.
- He did?
That means he's not injured much.
What a relief.
Did I-rang give you his business card?
What?
No, he said he didn't have any yet.
Oh, excuse me.
I'm Attorney Shin I-rang's family.
Do you perhaps know where his office is?
I do.
Here you go.
Thank you.
PRINCIPAL ATTORNEY SHIN I-RANG
Okcheon Building?
Shin I-rang is a total nutcase.
We might win easily thanks to him.
Prosecutor Kim?
Long time no see, Na-hyun.
What brings you to a civil trial,
Prosecutor Kim?
I decided to stop by
because I was curious.
What?
A search and seizure?
Okay. I'll be there soon.
Are you raiding Cheongil Hospital?
There's no reason to do so.
A man died.
An investigation will determine
whether there's a reason or not.
See you again, Na-hyun.
That darn prosecutor is
just as annoying as ever.
I better try
persuading the plaintiff again.
She shouldn't act recklessly
at least for her sick daughter.
Is what I asked for ready?
Yes, sir.
GANGSTER PATIENT WHO ASSAULTED
MEDICAL STAFF FALSELY CLAIMS MALPRACTICE
Let's seal the deal
while we have the upper hand.
Send this to the reporters
and plant it among YouTubers.
Yes, sir.
I should've burned these from the start.
This happened because I was such a softie.
I know it's not my business,
but what about the case?
I'll continue on my own.
I'd like you to pray for him
so that he can rest in peace at least.
Why don't we wait until he comes
for the sake of your time together?
I might be swayed if I see him.
Are you sure about this?
Let me do it myself.
GANGSTER PATIENT WHO ASSAULTED
MEDICAL STAFF FALSELY CLAIMS MALPRACTICE
WHAT WOULD YOU EXPECT
FROM A GANGSTER? LOL
JI-WOO
What the…
Ji-woo!
What's going on? What's wrong?
SCUM IS BETTER OFF DEAD,
JUSTICE SERVED, NICE!
Darn it.
Leave the rest to me…
and rest in peace.
No! Not now!
Mr. Shin?
You anchovy head.
Stop right this instant.
You know nothing!
Who are you to meddle with it?
I need to go to my daughter.
Don't try to get in the way,
or I'll make you pay.
How could you do this to the priest!
Did you just hit me, lady?
What? "Lady"?
I worked my butt off
to raise and educate you,
and you dare call me "lady"?
Say that again.
Say that again, brat.
Run away.
This man isn't your son.
What?
Shin I-rang!
What…
What is going on?
Ji-woo.
Ji-woo…
So, are you saying
that this talisman summoned a ghost,
my son happened to see that ghost
after opening his law office here,
and that very ghost is
the victim of the earlier trial,
Lee Gang-pung?
That's right.
Will I-rang come back
if we burn this talisman to ashes?
Not now.
He's possessed at the moment,
so we don't know
what will happen if we do.
LEE GANG-PUNG
What happened?
Help me, Mr. Attorney.
I don't want to.
I get that you're a ghost,
but have some shame.
After all that you did,
you want my help again?
This will be the last time.
Go away.
You just wouldn't listen
when I talk to you nicely.
Ji-woo is sick!
She read that article about my past.
It must've shocked her.
She clutched her stomach in pain
and passed out.
Why did you save it until now?
You should've told me right away!
Geez.
Darn it.
Can you take me to Sadang-dong?
- Sure, get in.
- Okay.
- Taking off.
There! The right one.
- Zero-five-two-five and star.
- Zero-five-two-five, star.
There. In her room.
Ji-woo.
Ji-woo! Wake up.
What… Where did he go?
What's going on?
Did you see a taxi here?
Did you perhaps drive here?
Get the doors, please.
Patient, can you hear me?
Ji-woo.
She had acute stomach cramps.
She's okay now.
Mom's here.
I'm sorry.
I had no idea his past would be an issue.
Now, the defense will keep
pouncing on Mr. Lee's character.
To deal with them,
I need to know about him.
I mean, everything about him
including his past.
The first time I met him was 20 years ago.
Where do I hang it?
Over here, please.
- Here?
- Yes.
I went to Cheongju Prison
with my church people
to hold a Christmas service there.
Gang-pung helped me make a Christmas tree.
He made foolish decisions
and became a gangster,
but he reflected on his wrongdoings,
turned himself in, and went to prison.
VICTIM OF MALPRACTICE IN LEGAL BATTLE
WAS ONCE A GANGSTER
I think that's enough.
Let's go.
You should be with Ji-woo for now.
I'll do what I can
to prepare for the trial.
Okay.
- Attorney Shin.
- Yes?
How did you enter my house, though?
And how did you know that Ji-woo was sick?
Oh, that…
I went there
to get your signature on something
and found Ji-woo unconscious.
The door…
The door was open.
I wonder why the door was open.
Then,
why did you suddenly speak in a dialect
during the trial?
I'm also from the same darn region.
I speak in my hometown dialect
when I get worked up.
Ji-woo shouldn't be alone.
Hurry inside now.
Okay, I will.
- Sure, sure thing.
- Bye.
Look.
Thank you.
It wasn't for you.
Stay here and join me later
when Ji-woo gets better.
Let's work on our next plan.
Okay.
Attorney Han.
Attorney Han?
Hello.
You didn't leave.
How is the girl?
She still has a fever,
but she's stable now.
You look a little pale.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Is she not feeling well?
Mom, I'm back.
W-What is it this time? You're scaring me.
Shin I-rang.
Look me straight in the eye.
It's scary every time you call me
by my full name.
Did I do something wrong again?
Goodness.
Mom.
This is a bit awkward.
Can't you be on my case as usual?
No way.
I can't possibly mistreat my precious son.
But we should be precise
with calculations.
Let's see.
COMMERCIAL LEASE AGREEMENT
You found out?
It was too easy.
You opened a law office under your name.
It was obvious where you got the money.
Mom, the thing is--
It's okay.
Now that it turned out this way,
I'll consider it an investment.
Stamp your fingerprint here.
What…
HALF OF SHIN I-RANG LAW OFFICE
BELONGS TO MOM
Half?
Sure we're immediate family,
but this isn't fair.
Should I own it all, then?
Fine.
I don't have an ink pad, though.
MOM: PARK GYEONG-HWA
SON: SHIN I-RANG
There you go.
It's nearby, so have your meals here.
You can drive…
There's a car?
SHIN I-RANG LAW OFFICE
Here you go.
Its oil needs to be changed.
PITTER-PATTER BUTCHER-STYLE BBQ
- Geez, that startled me!
- Oh, my goodness!
Can't you just show up in an ordinary way?
I freaked out even more.
Want me to knock or something?
To open the door and put the seat belt on?
Keep your cool, I-rang.
You're not dealing with a human.
Anyway,
shouldn't we find Nurse Oh Jin-suk?
No one will believe us without her.
- I found her.
- What?
I got a call from the detective agency.
Ms. Oh is a divorced mom
raising her child alone.
She was so poor that when Lee Jeong-seok
offered money to silence her,
she couldn't turn it down.
Nurse Oh Jin-suk?
A mom can do anything…
for her child.
But is that really
for your child?
Hi, guys.
Why? What is it?
What's going on?
What is it?
FOLLOW YOUR DAD TO PRISON
YOUR DAD IS A LIAR
LEAVE OUR SCHOOL!
DID A GHOST TAKE YOUR DAD?
I-RANG'S DAD IS A CRIMINAL!
I know it all too well
how devastating it is for a child…
CORRUPT PROSECUTOR
…when they realize the dirty truth
behind the privileges they've had.
That's not the case for Jun-seo.
He's too young
to know anything.
All right.
Let's say you'll manage
to keep him in the dark somehow.
- But have you been at ease?
- It's too late now.
Once you die, you're dead for good.
It's all over.
It's not over.
There's another person dying.
What do you mean?
Mr. Lee Gang-pung's daughter.
You've seen her at the hospital.
Make it quick and come back out, okay?
I have an exam tomorrow.
Take it easy with your exams.
Stop joking around.
Okay, my kiddo.
My surgery will be over in a jiffy.
Good luck.
Don't worry.
- See you.
- See you later.
Since her dad died,
she cooped herself in her room
and barely ate anything.
She ended up passing out
and got sent to the ER.
Her healthy dad died overnight.
It'd be odd
if she were okay.
Now that you know,
please testify.
You're the only one
who can tell the truth.
So, please…
reveal the truth.
I can't do it.
That man is going to make us pay.
What else haven't you told me
other than Oh Jin-suk?
I'm asking if the search and seizure
may find anything against us.
An EMR, for example.
EMR…
What's that?
Electronic Medical Record.
It's the mainframe
of a hospital's computer room.
All surgical records are stored in it.
Anesthesia doctor?
Does it mean it has a record
of my heart rate during the surgery?
That's right.
Only if we find that hard disk,
we can perfectly prove
against the doctor's claim
that you died of a heart attack.
You should be called Attorney Romantic.
Did you graduate from med school too?
What a playlist.
- What?
I didn't know until today.
Mr. Attorney.
They submitted
a fabricated record to court.
Search through the EMR.
The original should be
in the operating room's computer.
Ms. Oh Jin-suk told me.
Oh, I see.
Anyway, it'll be game over
with that, right?
But where is it?
That's the question.
When I asked the hospital for it,
they said they recently got a new one.
They got a new one?
What about the old one, then?
They sold it.
Sold it?
So, I made an anonymous report.
The prosecution should've
started investigating by now.
I'll check the surveillance footage
around the hospital.
I need you to collect information
by the prosecutor in charge.
Okay.
From what I heard,
the prosecution got an anonymous report
about the EMR.
That's why they started investigating.
We're about to get busted
thanks to some idiot.
What did you say, woman?
Watch what you say, Attorney Han.
I can't chime in with improbable lies.
Are you kidding me?
- Han Na-hyun.
- Yes?
You're dismissed.
I'm in charge of this case.
You heard me.
TAEBAEK LAW FIRM
Gosh, I'm lost for words.
What's with her?
Geez.
What…
What's wrong?
I understand.
You killed a man.
No wonder you're losing your mind.
Kill…
Kill him? Who do you mean?
I did speak to you kindly with honorifics,
but we're not friends.
Wait.
I offered that nurse money as you advised.
I handed over the EMR to you
because you said you'd take care of it.
I…
even recorded our conversations,
sir…
So what?
Who's going to listen to it?
The judges?
Will you let them know
that you messed up and killed a man,
and that your attorney helped you
get away with it?
- No, that's not it.
- Hey!
When someone cleans up after your mess,
you should be grateful
if you ever see reason, okay?
Consider yourself blessed
to have Attorney Han defend you.
Han Na-hyun would even risk her life
to win a trial.
CONTACTS
PROSECUTOR KIM HYEON-U
A hospital computer?
We don't service such computers.
Then, could there be a place
that services used hospital computers?
Probably.
An informant?
I know you tried
to find this anonymous informant.
If they're going to testify,
we have the right to know who it is.
I don't know who it is.
The person used a public phone,
and no CCTV cameras were nearby.
Based on the report,
it's highly likely to be an insider.
Don't you have anyone in mind?
Or maybe the doctor said something.
No.
Hospitals are where
random people come and go.
He said he couldn't specify anyone.
INVESTIGATOR LEE
I THINK WE FOUND IT
Just a moment.
Let me go to the bathroom.
Sure.
What's wrong?
I dropped it in the bathroom.
I have to make an urgent call.
Can I use your phone?
Of course.
"Saenara Used Appliances."
MR. YANG DO-GYEONG
Hello, Attorney Yang.
Did you take care of the computer?
It will cross the sea
to meet its new owner tonight.
Did you get rid of the hard disk?
Of course, I burned it and threw it out.
The prosecution is sniffing around.
Be careful.
Okay, goodbye.
CHEONGIL HOSPITAL
I'd be crazy
if I got rid of this nice safety net.
Let's go to the warehouse.
Where did you find it?
We received pictures from our source.
They were taken last night.
I asked the hospital,
and they said it was their device.
Where's the location?
Incheon, and the owner is Cho Gi-cheol.
Incheon.
Should we request a search warrant?
It'll be too late if we wait for it.
Let's head there now.
Mr. Attorney.
Saenara Used Appliances has the computer.
- Saenara Used Appliances?
- I saw them talking.
KANG HA-NA
SUPREME PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
KIM HAE-YEONG
Attached is the info
on Saenara Used Appliances and its owner.
CRIMINAL RECORDS CHECK REPORT
BUSINESS LICENSE
Great work today! Thank you!
You didn't have to come
all the way here, I-rang.
You know I played a surgeon role
in the SBS weekend drama,
Doctors, a year ago.
I didn't have any lines, but I got
quite a lot of blood on my hands.
Oh, you did.
I was in a rush.
Anyway, we need to find
a computer mainframe
a bit bigger than a normal computer
with a blue sticker on it.
I see. Don't you worry.
You can count on me.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Off we go.
SAENARA USED APPLIANCES
We're here.
Excuse me…
What are you going to do with that?
I doubt any workers are still here.
- Then?
- I'll just sneak in and get the computer.
Can you keep watch on that side?
Okay.
Hey…
This makes me feel uneasy.
Look.
I think you should be careful.
I know the owner here.
You know him?
He used to be my boss
back when I was young and stupid.
Are you saying he's a gangster?
He was vicious.
He beat up whoever displeased him
to a pulp.
Every time, he sang the same song.
A gangster exports used appliances
for a living?
Maybe he turned over a new leaf.
Even a dog passing by would laugh.
He started trafficking drugs 20 years ago.
What? Drugs?
Does that mean
this place isn't a warehouse,
but the den of a drug syndicate?
Sure seems like it with those guys around.
- What's going on?
- Who the heck is it?
You should've told me that sooner!
Please don't save important information!
I'd been meaning to tell you.
I-rang!
These guys seem very angry!
Get them!
What's going on?
Move over.
Two people aren't enough.
- Just a moment.
- What?
Where are you going, I-rang!
Help out!
I'm sorry!
I-rang, I'm doing what I can!
I didn't mean you.
Bong-su, over here.
I-rang, hold this position.
I'll go find the computer, okay?
But…
Me too!
So what if you find it?
We have no way out of here!
You got brains in those heads of yours?
There are windows on the side!
- Yes, sir!
- The windows!
Get the windows.
Damn morons.
What are you waiting for?
They're about to come in!
Oh, here are the computers.
Hold on. A bit bigger. A blue sticker.
A bit bigger. A blue sticker.
Outta my way.
Gosh. A bit bigger. A blue sticker. A bit…
A blue sticker.
I found it!
I-rang, I found the computer,
but the hard disk is missing!
It doesn't matter!
Find a hole in the wall or something!
I found it!
I found it here.
Really?
Where's the computer?
Computer? No, I found a dog hole.
W-What?
You told me
not to save important information.
The "what" you found
is the important part!
You darn dog-hole ghost!
Darn dog hole?
I mean a dog hole.
Where are they?
Let's go. Hurry.
I'm from the Prosecutors' Office.
That woman…
I hear you're keeping important evidence.
KANG HA-NA
SUPREME PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
Did you buy that online or what?
Boys, she claims herself
to be a prosecutor.
Cho Gi-cheol.
You were born on February 11, 1979.
Your hometown is
Sasaeng-dong, Chungcheongnam-do.
Your mother is dead,
and your father is missing.
You have seven assault convictions
and two fraud convictions.
You are beyond saving.
What's your deal?
What are you saying?
What you did just now is
assault and obstruction of justice.
Add concealing crucial evidence to that,
and you'll be in the slammer for a while.
I'm going to pile on
the punishment, you see.
Fine, I'll let you check.
Boys, open it up.
Attorney Han is here to find
what the doctor hid?
Isn't she on his side?
I know. This is strange.
Wow.
It's the 1991 Grandeur box-type.
Wow, it's even got authentic interior.
This is Cho Gi-cheol's car.
There's a secret space under the seat.
A secret space?
What? What did you say?
I-rang! What are you doing?
I-rang, don't do that.
Oh, geez.
This is not good.
What are you doing?
I found it.
What on earth?
How did you know where it was?
It's a business secret.
What? You're scaring me.
Anyway, let's get out of here.
Hold on.
Actual drugs.
Oh, dear. We got caught. What should I do?
Get her.
The prosecution knows
that I'm here.
I don't care if she's a prosecutor.
Get her.
What the heck?
Isn't that my car?
Attorney Han, are you okay?
I'm screwed.
Attorney?
Not a prosecutor?
Are you or are you not?
I-rang!
What?
What is this cute trick
you're pulling all together?
Boys!
Get them all.
I-rang.
Wait.
Wait a minute!
Whoever is up there,
I know you're watching!
Please help me out once more!
Give me strength just this one last time!
Why didn't you just set this place on fire
instead of smashing it all?
You're really
making things exhausting!
Darn.
Turn the music on.
Yes, sir.
Put that thing down before you regret it.
I don't want to.
Which one should I beat up first?
Make a guess
or not!
Okay,
the first target is
the girl who fooled me.
Are you okay?
This is unfair.
I came here first,
so I should also take
the beating first, no?
Is that your wish?
Punk, your wish is
going to come true today.
Turn up the volume!
How disappointing of you!
I hear you're good and kind!
Why are you sitting back
and watching, huh?
Oh, come on!
This song…
It's a happy moment. Happy days.
Smile. Smile, you punks.
It's a happy day!
When they're faced with someone they hate
or something that causes rage,
the possibility of possession increases.
Oh, your cheeks are burning.
Are you done swinging?
Is it my turn now?
What's this strange sense of déjà vu?
- Who are you?
- Me?
I'm gangster attorney, Lee Gang-pung!
What the heck are you saying?
Stop joking around.
They're gangsters,
and they even have drugs.
Don't worry, my dear.
I'll save you soon.
Okay?
"My dear"?
We might need a whole hospital
to accommodate you all.
Or a funeral hall can be another option.
Why you damn nutjob…
Trying to catch a fly?
Where do you think you're going?
Go on! Attack him!
What in the world?
I-rang!
Wait.
Don't leave us!
Oh, no!
No, that's enough!
You're dead meat!
What the…
Push!
Darn.
Attack him. Get in there!
Spare me!
I don't want to.
SAENARA USED APPLIANCES
I-rang!
What… Can you stay with him?
I'll go bring people.
Mr. Shin.
Attorney Shin, can you hear me?
Attorney Shin!
CHEONGIL HOSPITAL
Attorney Han, are you okay?
Are you okay?
This is unfair.
I came here first,
so I should also take
the beating first, no?
- Let's go inside.
- Yes, sir.
Get the nearby surveillance footage first.
Yes, sir.
The man who was recently criticized
for playing the victim
turns out to have been murdered
by the doctor in charge.
The police have proved the doctor's murder
based on the hospital computer's hard disk
and the testimony
of the nurse who witnessed it.
Meanwhile, they're--
HAN SO-HYUN
COURT OF KOREA
EFFORT ALWAYS PAYS OFF
ATTORNEY SEO IN-GYU DUBBED "KING"
A LAWYER THAT PEOPLE WANT TO EMPLOY!
A LAWYER THAT PEOPLE BELIEVE IN!
I WANT TO BE A LAWYER
THAT ALWAYS WINS!
I MUST WIN EVERY TIME!
WON
WON, WON, WON,
WON, WON, WON
LOST
- Mr. Attorney.
- Hello.
How is Ji-woo?
Hi, Ji-woo.
I'm Attorney Shin I-rang.
We met briefly at the hospital, remember?
Is it still…
too hard for you?
Ji-woo.
Your dad…
didn't die because of you.
It's not your fault.
So, don't blame yourself too much.
What do you know, mister?
I…
can tell.
What? You don't like it?
Why are you picking at the food?
It's nothing.
No way. I can tell there's something.
Come on and tell me.
I couldn't sleep
because you snored too loudly.
That's not good.
My kiddo will have trouble getting tall
and studying if she can't sleep.
This won't do.
I'll go see a doctor right away.
It's all my fault.
I heard snoring wasn't good
for your health,
and I knew my dad
would do anything for me.
If I just didn't say that,
he wouldn't have died.
No, Ji-woo.
My death…
is absolutely not your fault.
The hospital and the doctor are to blame.
Those in the wrong were all punished.
So…
So Ji-woo, please…
go back
to your usual bright self.
Live happily…
with your mom for me, okay?
Okay, kiddo?
Dad?
Mom.
I heard Dad's voice.
What?
I guess your dad is
always keeping by our side.
Let's be brave
and live happily, okay?
Wait.
Must we burn this talisman?
He can just stay with us.
He'll get to watch Ji-woo grow
and be of support to Min-ju.
Attorney Shin.
Why must he go?
I should.
I don't belong here.
Thank you so much for everything.
The pleasure is mine.
Thank you.
It was only for a short time,
but I was happy.
I guarantee
you'll go to a good place.
Farewell.
OKCHEON BUILDING
- Is it all over?
- Yes.
Your son is inside. Go on ahead.
Father.
Yes?
Thank you so much.
Don't mention it.
Goodbye.
JOB APPLICATION
NAME: SHIN I-RANG
Are you busy?
What brings you here, Mom?
I'm here to feed my attorney son
who's working late hours.
Mom,
about Dad…
What about him?
Never mind.
What is it?
You know,
when we arrived at the hospital,
he was already dead.
I'm wondering
if he wanted to tell us anything.
If he did,
he might show up to us at least once.
Nonsense.
Well,
I guess it wouldn't be so bad
if he did show up.
I have tons of questions for him too.
Eat up before it gets cold.
Don't be home too late.
See you.
You're leaving already?
That's right.
Let's say the worst is behind us now
and make a fresh start.
This should be enough
to ward off even the oldest ghosts.
LEGAL CONSULTATION, LEGAL ADVICE
SHIN I-RANG LAW OFFICE
How may I help you, girl?
What brings you here?
Mister,
you can see me?
What?
Not again.
Why does it keep happening to me?
You looked so cool
when you were dancing earlier.
A trainee committed suicide
and the fans are going wild.
Let me look into it.
- Loanne was…
- Hey!
Stop causing harm to others
and just go home.
The girls found it hard to deal with her.
Her phone disappeared from the scene.
You think she was murdered?
Let's go catch the culprit.
Do you know who Loanne is?
- Who are you?
- Who are you? A reporter?
How did you get in? Let's go.
I heard a phone ring.
I never heard that ringtone before.
Subtitle translation by: Eunjin Erica Kim