[suspenseful music]
Milkit!
Where are you?
Can you hear me?
Milkit!
I'll find you.
[SATILS]
Milkit.
Come now.
Rise and shine.
Oh, no, but how?
Oh, my, someone's
learned some new tricks.
That reaction you gave
me just now almost
seemed genuinely human.
You've done well.
I'm proud of you.
Stop.
I want my master.
Well, that's too bad.
I had this playroom specially
made in a secret location.
Nobody's coming to save you.
Foolish girl, you're
never going to see
that master of yours again.
All that's left for you
to do is writhe in pain
as I carve you up.
You'll be even
uglier than before.
Now, be a good girl
and entertain me
with your sheer agony.
I'd do anything for my
master, but that's not you.
[whip cracks]
Insolent slave!
How dare you speak back to me?
You have no right
to choose your owner.
Hey, Flum.
Welcy?
Did you settle things with
the church's newest lapdog?
How'd you know?
Dein came in here.
And not long after, so did you.
The most logical
inference is that you
might have been following him.
OK.
What about you?
Why are you here?
I heard that this
mansion recently had
a secret chamber installed.
I'm here to investigate.
A secret chamber?
Where is it?
I need you to take me there.
It's urgent!
Ink and Milkit could be
in grave danger as we speak.
Sure,
I'll help, no problem.
This way.
It won't be long
now, Milkit and Ink.
Please wait.
I'm coming.
[SATILS]
That other girl you call master
is a hopeless idiot,
wasting her time trying
to fix your worthless face.
[GASP] Ink's here?
Only for me to ruin it again.
Let's pull off
those bandages,
so I can get
a better look at it.
Hey, what?
Demonstrating how loyal
you are to your master?
How precious.
Look below.
Take even one step back
and you'll fall off.
Behold the fate you'll
suffer if that should happen.
And if you're stubborn
enough to survive that--
[growling]
--your new friends
there will be waiting
patiently to eat you alive.
Go on, make your choice.
Whoa, it looks like
you're about to slip,
or maybe those chains will
come loose from the wall
and decide for you.
Whatever will you do?
You'd sacrifice
your body just to keep
hiding that precious face?
I'm shocked you value a promise
with her more than your life.
It's so sweet, I could cry.
Master, please come save me.
[SATILS] Wow, praying for
your new master to rescue you?
You're a slave, remember?
You can be louder than that.
Scream and cry for me.
Oh, so defiant.
The old you never reacted
to anything-- your only flaw,
but an annoying one.
Very good.
I'm liking your new
impertinent spirit.
Crushing it will be a treat.
[scream]
[FLUM]
Why can't you get angry at me
for not showing up
to protect you sooner?
Let me have it.
We're not slave and master.
You're Milkit, and I'm Flum.
That's all there is.
[NARRATOR]
In that moment--
Better start moving.
You won't like it when my knife
pokes through your body over
and over again.
[NARRATOR] --she decided
to believe in her master
until the bitter end
and go down fighting.
Such a look in your eye.
Fine then, have it your way.
Resist and have
your body shredded up
and scarred from head to toe.
[evil laugh]
[explosion]
Huh?
You witch, leave
my Milkit alone!
Who the hell are you?
Now you'll pay.
You'll pay!
You deserve to suffer for this.
[MILKIT]
My master.
I'm so sorry, my Milkit.
I should have been here sooner.
My dear Milkit.
My dear master.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Ink.
Truly, I said
such awful things.
I feel terrible.
And I'm--
[INK] Flum, why are
you apologizing?
[FLUM] Because you're
a very dear friend to me.
And yet I was so mean to you.
And even after all that,
you stopped those eyeballs.
You protected me when
I fought with Dein.
Flum.
Thank you, Ink.
Oh, what's this?
[screaming]
[thud]
[groaning]
No, don't!
You monsters!
Get away from me!
[screams]
There, master, that's
the one who kidnapped me.
Girl, I just did what
Satils asked me to.
Sadly, both she
and that Dein guy
turned out to be
good for nothings.
Just pathetic.
[FLUM]
I see.
So you were the one who made
Ink believe she was a burden.
It's true.
Why shouldn't she believe it?
[MOTHER]
Nekt.
Greetings, ladies.
Please call me "Mother."
You must be the renowned
Flum Apricot.
[FLUM]
You're Mother.
My, what chilly reception.
Anyhow, I hear you've
been looking after Ink.
I owe you my gratitude.
Thank you, dear.
Shut the hell up.
You're no Mother, not after
everything you've done to Ink.
Whatever do you mean?
Could you be referring to the
core Ink's heart once was?
It's the same
for the other ones too.
All my children have had their
hearts replaced with cores.
But unlike the rest of us,
she's a useless failure.
Flum and the others I've
met since I ran away never
hurt me or call me names.
They treat me well
and say I'm their friend.
Oh, Ink.
You tell them.
Have you made some
friends during your
unapproved escapades?
Well, that's fine, but you
know that family comes first.
Come, it's time we go home.
[FLUM]
Don't do it, Ink!
You and the rest,
you're not my family.
[MOTHER]
Of course we are.
I figured it
out after I left.
The life I was forced to endure
and your world was all wrong
because I met Flum and my
friends that made me truly
laugh for the first time.
And that's how I even
learned what laughing was.
That's why I want
to always be with them.
They're my friends
who care about me.
And they're much more
important than your family.
[MOTHER] You can't be
stupid enough to believe you
could live together
with humans, can you?
Did your time out
there cause you
to forget you're a creepy,
eyeball-spitting monster?
How will you survive
without your medicine?
[FLUM] You don't care
about Ink's feelings.
You're nothing
but a narcissistic monster!
[INK] I'm happy here,
so I'm staying with them.
[MOTHER] Very well, I guess
your siblings were right.
You're not needed.
When you eventually
realize I was right,
you'll come to regret
this decision,
you ungrateful, good
for nothing brat.
Are you OK?
Enough!
And you dare call
yourself a "mother?"
That's my mother, and you
can't speak to her like that.
You're making me upset.
Let's not get carried away.
I haven't decided whether
we should kill this girl
or make use of
the abilities she possesses.
And she was able
to destroy a core, right?
I'm rather intrigued
by this power of yours
as research material,
I should say.
Well, till next time.
It's been fun.
You won't get away!
[INK]
It's all right, Flum.
Thank you.
But they-- they're the ones
who messed up your body.
But you let me
be your friend.
That was more
than enough for me.
I'm happy.
But we should end things.
End?
Mm-hmm.
It's time.
I'll embrace
a human life and death.
Hold on.
Why are you
talking about death?
It's my fault, isn't it?
Sara and Eterna are gone.
If we continue living
together like we did before,
I could attack you
or Milkit without meaning to.
You might get hurt, or worse--
I don't want to make any more
of my precious friends suffer.
That's why I should die.
Please, Flum, you're
the only one with the ability
to break the core
that's been placed
where my heart should be.
You can, right?
Please do it.
If you'll do this
favor for me,
I'll get to die as a normal
girl who had friends.
No, I can't.
I can't do it.
[MILKIT] And is that
really what you want?
I think not.
Not long ago, I felt
just the same as you.
I was stuck in a dark
place I couldn't escape,
ready to die, with no hope
that help was coming.
But then I met my master,
and I started to change.
Isn't that why you
stayed with us?
Aren't you trying to change
your life for the better?
I am.
I want to keep eating, bathing,
and relaxing with you all.
Life just started getting fun.
I want you to have
more of that.
So then, what do we do?
That's right.
Eterna would know.
But I still don't
know if she's alive.
[footsteps]
Over here.
You holding up
all right, Flum?
Gadhio!
[GADHIO] It's good
to see you're still well.
I'm glad you're all OK.
Same goes for you.
How are you unscathed?
You think eyeballs
could stop me?
Eterna,
I'm sorry for everything.
You've done nothing
that requires an apology.
Infuriating.
I knew Jean was
on a power trip,
but I never imagined he'd
go so far behind our backs.
I don't want to sound
like I'm thankful to him,
but in a strange way,
he led me to Milkit.
Anyway, what'd I miss before
you caught up to us down there,
Gadhio?
You fought Nekt, right?
I take it that one went right?
Unfortunately,
the kid got away,
vanished as soon as
it was clear I won.
That was when Eterna
showed her face.
Oh, right.
I saw that Nekt had a bruise.
And what's happened to you
since the last time we met up,
Eterna?
[ETERNA] Milkit and I ran into
Dein when we went out shopping.
I used water magic
to protect her
and fled from
the swarm of eyeballs.
But apparently,
those eyeballs
didn't give chase for long.
She was making her
way back to you
when we ran into each other.
Ink must have
subconsciously kept you safe.
So after that, the two of you
went to come help us out?
[GADHIO] I was doing everything
I could to track you down.
And along the way,
I met that Welcy girl.
[FLUM] And Sara,
you said she's alive.
How did you find that out?
[GADHIO]
She was in the demon realm.
Right before she was
attacked by eyeballs,
Neigass appeared
and came to her aid.
[FLUM]
Neigass saved her?
Sara must have
left an impression.
Great.
Did you happen to see Ed
and Jonny in the demon realm?
I'm not familiar.
So that means only
Sara made it out alive.
That explains why
the girl was so distressed,
even though she was safe.
[SARA]
I'm begging you.
I promise I'll pay you
back to save my friends.
I've lost far too
many people I love.
Please, no more.
Even if this girl is
an illusion you've made,
your primary goal is still
to break up the heroes party,
is it not?
Explain.
What can I say
to earn your trust?
Telling me all the demons
know about Origin
would be an excellent start.
After that, she told me
our party's true purpose.
Is it not to kill
all the demons?
[GADHIO]
Nope.
It's to undo
the seal on Origin.
In the beginning,
Origin was a man-made machine
designed as an infinite
source of energy.
It brought humanity
great prosperity.
Of course, that era
of peace did not last long.
Their minds corrupted by power
and the promise of wealth.
Humanity fought in a
bloody war till none remained.
As if rejecting that outcome,
the world gave birth
to a new kind of humanity.
Among them, some were
blessed with immense power.
They were called "Heroes."
Thanks to the first Hero,
Origin was sealed,
and with it,
the root cause of all evil.
[GADHIO] But the difference
between sealed and destroyed
is a seal can be undone.
That's why the church summoned
us to subjugate the Demon Lord.
They're merely using
the Hero's Party as a means
to bring back Origin.
The seal is at
the Demon Lord's castle.
It's kept safe.
They have been
defending it for eons now.
Wait, Dein claimed his
power came from Origin.
And he seemed strong
enough to back it up.
Does that mean something
happened to the seal?
Yeah, it seems
Origin's influence
is beginning to leak out.
That's why Neigass came
to our kingdom to investigate
the cause of the leak.
Oh, so that's why
she was in Anichidey.
[GADHIO] You ask me,
from what the demon said,
I think one
of them is a traitor.
When the demon attacks occurred
ten and eight years ago,
they weren't
the ones in charge.
The church was.
Someone on the demon side
must have colluded with them.
You know that
Sara girl you met?
She survived one.
What a coincidence.
She's not the only
one we know of.
[FLUM]
Maria, right?
After the attacks,
five pregnant women were
abducted who each gave birth.
Those kids are now
called the Spiral Children.
And they were given
to the church for research.
[FLUM] Are you saying
those kids were--
[GADHIO]
Yeah, most likely.
They treated children
just like monsters.
[GADHIO] Does that mean
you saw their monsters?
Yeah, I fought
one some time ago.
I did too, alongside my wife.
Wait, you're married?
I was up until that
Chimera killed her.
[GASP]
[GADHIO] After that,
I joined the Hero's Party
to find answers
on what happened
and get revenge on
the ones who killed my wife.
Awful.
Do they care so little for the
lives of their fellow humans?
[ETERNA]
Not just the church.
This entire kingdom couldn't
care less whether those
who call it home, live or die.
Eterna.
[GADHIO] You sound like
you know something.
Because I'm basically
the same as Ink.
But somehow I've
made it this far.
So I'm sure Ink will be fine.
[NARRATOR] After that, Ink
received a heart transplant.
Flum destroyed the Core.
And Eterna used her magic
to take Dein's heart
and ensure Ink took to it.
[JEAN]
You think you know me.
Explain yourself.
I know that you are
in search of power.
And as a devout
member of the clergy,
I will guide the lost lambs.
Oh, you've
caught my interest.
I'll give you that much credit.
[MARIA] I gave one of these to
Cyrill, and now it's your turn.
Did you now?
Intriguing.
Flare meteorite!
Ha!
Take my blue flame!
Tricky move.
Wait, this isn't fire.
It is both fire
and ice at once.
My power has finally ascended
past that of any mortal man.
Well, that seems new.
What could Jean be
up to this time?
The lord's work.
Wonder if I made
her mad there.
You used it.
Flum, tell me,
what should I do?
He used some strange
magic I'd never seen before.
What do you think
the odds are that they
obtained Origin's power too?
Impossible.
How could they?
We have the text
of the seal's formula.
And it's kept
under lock and key.
Only I know where it is
and, of course, Dhiza.
Good.
You've returned to me.
All that I do is
for you, after all.
I was successful in tracking
down their hideout.
The church has a research team
that we were not aware of.
The children,
Necromancy and Chimera's.
That's enough.
Please save your strength.
How's it going?
Not good.
Too little, too late.
[NARRATOR]
Welcy uncovered
a great deal of evidence
in Satils' mansion,
leading her to the
church's research facility.
But by then, they had already
cleared the place out.
So they knew we were coming.
I suppose that means
I need to keep any information
I find close to the chest.
According to Origin, in order
to build his resistance
to the power of reversal,
we must absorb Flum Apricot
without killing her?
That's awfully easy
for papa to say.
Desperate times, the clock
is still ticking down on us.
I suspect one of your kin
of committing treason.
Preposterous.
We have our duty.
Jonny.
What's wrong, dear?
It's all my fault.
They're gone forever.
You had a nightmare,
didn't you?
I've got you now.
It's all right.
Wow, check it out!
It's chow time.
I want to dig in.
It looks almost too
beautiful to mess up.
I hope there's something
to each of your liking.
These recipes were new to me.
Give yourself some
credit, just for once.
Your cooking's
always delicious.
[ETERNA] Milkit, take what
Flum says with a grain of salt.
You're her rock,
so she's biased.
[GADHIO]
But, you know,
compared to when
she was traveling with us,
I'd say Milkit is good for her.
Aww,
you're joining her, Gadhio?
If I'm master's rock,
then she's mine as well.
Honestly, I don't know if
I could go on without her.
Really?
Who knows what
tomorrow will bring?
But for now,
I'm with my family.
Hey, Milkit, I love you.
And I love you.
I'll live my life with them.
[NARRATOR]
After a few days passed,
the town felt
unusually peaceful.
Another quiet morning.
Oh.
If it isn't
my favorite adventurer.
Have any new jobs come in?
Wha-- Hold on.
Seriously?
Am I really your favorite?
I was just joking.
You want work?
Well, then,
how about this one?