[If you don't turn yourself in,
your limbs will rot and you'll die]
[All characters and events are fictional,
and any resemblance is coincidental]
[Scenes with children and animals were filmed
safely under professional supervision]
Start with this.
What does '12+2' even mean?
How have you been?
You got married, right? Have kids too?
I'm alone.
Goodness, what have you been
doing all this time?
Back when we were young,
I thought maybe you and Ji Won
would end up getting married.
Ji Won always liked you
more than me, you know?
I don't want to talk about Ji Won.
You even tried to kill Ji Won too.
No, you've got it wrong.
Once I realized it was Ji Won,
I was just going to leave.
But then she happened to take a photo,
and while I was trying to take it from her...
How's Ji Won doing?
- Who knows?
- Oh.
So you don't keep in touch with her?
Don't tell me the friend you lost was Ji Won?
Now,
talk about this first.
[Murder: 12+2, Rape: 19, Attempted: 15]
Well, three of these you'd recognize.
But the really interesting part...
It's over here.
Tae Joo, you probably
couldn't even imagine it.
[Episode 8]
Oh, are you coming around now?
Where am I?
Wait, you don't remember?
Earlier, at the funeral home.
There's nothing seriously wrong.
Just exhaustion.
No, wait. You should
at least finish the IV drip.
[Examination Room]
Wait, Mr. Kang!
Hey, Tae Joo! Are you okay?
What did the doctor say?
You didn't have to push yourself
to come here.
My mother would've appreciated it.
There you go grinning again.
You did the same thing earlier.
- What did you say?
- Before your mother's memorial portrait.
I was gonna let it slide
since you're in mourning.
But you're seriously unbelievable.
- Hey!
- What are you doing now?
The illegal detention of Lee Ki Beom!
I'm arresting you for ordering assault
and unlawful confinement. Let's go!
Just hit me, Tae Joo!
Get over here, you punk!
The chief mourner...
the chief mourner is being arrested.
What kind of nonsense is this?
Some crazy punk put handcuffs
on Prosecutor Cha.
What?
- What are you doing, you punk!
- You punk!
- Let go!
- Get over here, you punk!
Stop!
- Sir, stop it!
- Let go! Stop!
- Let go, you punk!
- Get a grip, you punk!
Let go of me!
- Let go!
- Snap out of it!
- Get a hold of yourself!
- Let go, you punk!
That punk really handcuffed him.
Hey, you punk!
Hey, get him out of here now!
- Let's go.
- I said let go, you punk!
Come on, Tae Joo.
Just stop.
Let go, you punk!
Why would you go that far?
You went too far back there, sir.
I did it to survive.
So...
I could stay alive.
If I just sat there and did nothing,
I felt like I was gonna explode inside first.
I felt like I was gonna die.
Like I was the one dying.
Don't like the alcohol?
Want me to bring something else?
Darn it, it would've been a perfect funeral.
It really could've been a perfect funeral.
I had just caught a serial killer.
It was exactly when I needed
all the attention on me.
But then, that punk Lee Ki Beom
dropped dead and nearly ruined everything.
And right then, my mother passed away.
All the big names from politics and business
showed up to pay their respects to me.
I was making connections
and strengthening my network.
It was like a final gift from my mother.
And then it all went up in smoke.
Because of Kang Tae Joo...
Oh, this...
How am I supposed to
repay this favor, Sang Beom?
What should I do so I can feel
less sorry toward my mother?
Should I turn that punk
into chum in the Pacific?
Just say the word!
I told you, you're not allowed in!
Move, you punk! I need to see Mr. Cha!
Sir!
Please save me!
They said the audit team is going to
investigate me over Lee Ki Beom's death.
Everyone, get out.
In that case, you should
cooperate with the investigation.
Who do you think caused this whole mess?
Excuse me?
I did nothing but faithfully
carry out the tasks you ordered me to do.
What exactly are you implying?
It sounds like you're saying I ordered you
to beat Lee Ki Beom to death, huh?
Did I actually say that?
N-No, that's not what I meant, sir.
I mean, it's...
Listen, Mr. Do Hyeong Gu.
I brought real shame upon myself
in front of my mother today.
I've become a disgraced son.
I'm feeling really shaken up today.
Handle your own problems yourself.
Try denying it to the very end if you want.
Anyway, the victim's dead,
who would know who hit him?
But
about Lee Ki Beom,
was it because of you
that it turned out that way?
Pardon?
I mean, you didn't interrogate him alone.
Right?
Detective Kang Tae Joo
worked hard on it too, right?
Detective Do, did you see anything?
Yes.
I admit to the illegal detention, but,
that's all.
So you're saying there's someone else
who mistreated Lee Ki Beom?
I saw it with my own eyes.
Sergeant Kang Tae Joo was beating
Lee Ki Beom to a pulp.
So I informed the prosecutor,
had the suspect transferred immediately,
and banned all visitation.
Ask Detective Jang Myeong Do
if you don't believe me.
Yes, that's all true.
[Sergeant Kang Tae Joo:
3-month pay suspension]
[and reassignment for suspect abuse]
Mr. Park, what on earth is going on?
This is driving me crazy.
Can they really hand down disciplinary action
without even questioning the accused?
They say they witnessed
you beating Lee Ki Beom.
Who said that?
Jang Myeong Do, Do Hyeong Gu, those punks.
That punk Si Young pulled a nasty stunt.
He must've been really pissed off.
I'm going to file an objection.
You know it's perjury too, don't you, Chief?
Tae Joo.
This audit team was dispatched
from National Police Headquarters.
The commissioner and my father
are practically lifelong buddies.
I really
don't have the authority to handle this.
And Cha Si Young wasn't the only one
who got pissed off because of you that day.
My father too, and everyone else
who was there.
A petty Sergeant,
just a lowly Sergeant!
You actually put handcuffs on a prosecutor,
and during his bereavement at that.
Wow, people like that kind of punk
need to be gently stepped on first.
So they're just
being that low,
pinning this kind of false charge on me?
Just
accept it.
Take some time away from Kangseng.
I'll call you again when the time comes.
I can't do that.
You think I'm asking you right now?
Why is my article not up?
Don't you get it? It got cut.
Why was it cut? It was even
in yesterday's edited version.
The higher-ups cut your article.
And it was on the publisher's orders.
Why would the publisher do that?
Because Prosecutor Cha Si Young,
who ordered that illegal arrest,
is the publisher's future son-in-law.
What?
Ji Won, Ji Won, have you heard the news?
Watch how you address me!
No, that's not important right now.
Well, Tae Joo...
He is the one who caused the suspect's death.
Then the police officer
who killed that suspect is him?
Yes.
There was
actually a request to cover up this incident,
but I refused, so he seems
to be holding a grudge.
Unbelievable, how little must he think
of a prosecutor to go this far?
Who's going to lock this punk up?
I'll do it, sir.
It's an internal police matter.
Do we really need to step in?
It's just a waste of manpower.
Seriously, you...
You're so soft. That's why people
like that crawl all over you.
I'm ashamed, sir.
You handle it.
Yes, understood, sir!
Jeez...
Hey!
How dare you frame me with that accusation?
Are you still human?
You were the one who came at me first.
And at my mother's funeral, of all places.
That crossed the line.
Who's the one who killed a man
and ended up hiding at his mother's funeral?
Do you see it now?
How different you and I are?
Me beating a suspect
like Lee Ki Beom isn't a crime.
But
when you insult me, it is.
That's what we call hierarchy, Tae Joo.
I've told you countless times.
You can't beat me.
We're different from the start.
Twenty-five!
Twenty-six!
Twenty-seven!
So close!
You were just three away.
Seok Man, fighting!
Back to the start!
I... I can't do this anymore.
So, Seok Man,
just tell me now.
You killed Lee Joo Hee, didn't you?
No, I didn't!
I tried being nice, but that won't work.
Hey, start over!
Please... please spare me.
You punk!
Sit!
One.
Two.
Three...
You haven't heard anything weird, have you?
What do you mean?
If not, never mind.
Have you had dinner?
Not in the mood.
Who eats depending on mood?
You eat when it's time to eat.
Just wait a bit, it'll be ready soon.
Sun Young!
Tae Joo, you really need to start living
on your own now, you know?
Try cooking for yourself once in a while.
Stop just filling up
on jjajangmyeon every day.
Are you going somewhere?
I'm getting married, you know.
Has my belly gotten big?
Will it show in the dress?
[Dae Ho Chinese Restaurant]
[A suspect died from police brutality,]
[but the officer who exposed the truth
is being framed as the perpetrator]
No, this article can't run.
Why not?
The illegally arrested suspect
died from torture.
And the detective who reported it
is being framed as the perpetrator.
Your paper should be able to run it.
It's still a major newspaper in Seoul.
Do you even know
who Prosecutor Cha Si Young's father is?
It's retired General Cha Mu Jin.
He's a close friend with the president.
And he's running in the upcoming by-election.
Darn it, on one side, it's the father-in-law,
and on the other, it's the father?
Anyway,
Cha Mu Jin is a dangerous man.
A reporter who investigated
his corruption even got forced out.
Seems like they were seriously tortured.
I'd help if I could,
but you guys should just give it up.
How can we give up?
One person is dead,
and the other is falsely accused.
Ji Won! Let's stop this.
- What?
- I don't want to lose my job.
There's nothing else I can do.
Stop talking nonsense and go get the car!
Why are you taking it out on me?
Jeez, nothing's going right.
Ouch...
Ji Won!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
What was that?
Are you sleeping well?
I think I wake up quite often in my sleep.
And I feel spaced out sometimes.
I seem to have a slight headache as well.
How's your mood?
My mood...
I'm not sure.
It's short-term memory loss.
Pardon?
It means she can't remember
specific events or information.
It seems
she couldn't accept her fiancé's death
and erased it from her memory.
So her memory will come back, right?
Of course.
When will that be?
That's uncertain.
It could come back as soon as tomorrow,
or it could take years.
Oh, right. And don't try
to force her memory back.
If she becomes confused,
she might harm herself.
[Bang Kyung Moon Clinic]
My purse! I must've left it in the exam room.
Tae Joo, go wait in the car.
I'll be right back.
Be careful.
Yeah.
[Bang Kyung Moon Clinic]
Ugh, shut up.
I'm telling you,
it's clearly attempted murder.
Stop overreacting.
Hey!
What do you mean?
Attempted murder?
What are you doing here?
You first. What is that supposed to mean?
Oh, it's nothing. He's just overreacting.
Ji Won was trying to clear your name,
but she nearly got killed because of it.
Hey, stop it! Darn it.
Stop this right now.
Don't be ridiculous. It's my article.
They're the ones framing me
just because I put handcuffs on a prosecutor!
You think you'll be safe?
I didn't become a journalist
just to live safely.
Let's find the evidence.
They said the place Ki Beom was held
was a bathhouse, right?
If we can just find that bathhouse...
Neutralizing evidence and bribing witnesses?
That's nothing for those guys.
This isn't something we can win.
Don't you get it?
Those bastards and us,
we're different from the very beginning.
Are you really the Kang Tae Joo I knew?
How could you say something like that?
If we back down now, what about
Ki Beom who died unjustly?
Still, we're like
his older brother and sister.
If we do nothing,
it'd be too cruel to Ki Beom.
What does a dead man even know?
You really...
Ugh, seriously...
What's wrong?
Something bothering you?
They said the baby's healthy, right?
I'm just a bit tired.
It's normal to feel tired.
Don't go out for a while. Just stay home.
If you need anything, just tell me.
Tae Joo.
Yeah.
You'll be a good uncle to my baby, right?
Of course. Do you even have to ask?
Then can you buy me that castella
from the Italian bakery?
The baby wants it.
Now?
It's too far, right?
Not really, it's just an hour round trip.
Don't worry. You wait at home.
I'll buy it and be right back.
Ki Beom.
Ki Beom, Ki Beom, wake up.
Ki Beom!
Ki Beom, you're home.
Ki Beom...
Ki Beom isn't waking up.
Lee Ki Beom.
Wake up!
Ki Beom...
Ki Beom!
Is that really true?
[Family motto, diligence and integrity]
I'm telling you, it is.
My cousin is a patrol officer
at Kangseng Station.
Unbelievable...
How could something like that happen?
What is all this commotion about?
Mother isn't feeling well.
Honey, the police officer
who caused Ki Beom's death apparently...
They say it's Tae Joo.
There could be a misunderstanding.
What misunderstanding?
They say he received disciplinary action
for the Ki Beom case as well.
That can't be true.
You're coming here?
Yes, I'll be there to pick you up
today, Si Young.
Let's have dinner together.
No, I could go myself.
You need days like this too.
I'm leaving home now, so come out
to the main gate by 30 minutes.
Alright.
Sun Young!
I bought the castella.
Hey, Sun Young!
Sun Young!
What's this? Blood?
Sun Young... this...
If she becomes confused,
she might harm herself.
Sun Young...
Sun Young!
Kang Sun Young!
Oh, there's Tae Joo!
Ki Hwan, calm down
and ask what happened first.
There must be some misunderstanding.
I know that.
Kang Sun Young!
Oh.
Hey!
Have you guys seen Sun Young? Have you...
Ki Hwan, have you seen Sun Young?
Ki Hwan! Ki Hwan!
Is that really what you should
be saying right now?
Do you know how I feel
coming to you like this?
Calm down!
Later. I'll explain everything later.
There is no "later." Answer me now.
Was it really you?
Did Ki Beom die because of you?
Yeah.
It's because of me. There, happy now?
Now let go!
I said let go, you punk!
Hey, you punk!
How could you!
How could you do that?
You!
Do you know what Ki Beom meant to me?
Bring my brother back, you punk!
Bring my brother back!
My brother...
Ki Hwan, I...
Ki Hwan, please.
Help me out.
I know I shouldn't be asking you this.
Please... save Sun Young.
Please save Sun Young!
What do you mean, Tae Joo?
I think Sun Young is trying to kill herself!
I...
Darn it...
Ma'am! Have you seen Sun Young? Sun Young?
I haven't seen Sun Young. Is something wrong?
I'll tell you later.
If you see her, please let me know!
Sun Young!
- Sun Young!
- Excuse me, have you seen Sun Young?
Sun Young!
Kang Sun Young!
Come down!
Tae Joo!
Tae Joo...
What's wrong, Tae Joo?
Sun Young, Sun Young...
- Sun Young?
- Sun Young...
Sun Young...
Tae Joo, that's not Sun Young.
That's not her.
Look, that isn't Sun Young, right?
I told you not to go to
dangerous places, didn't I?
I told you, didn't I?
Tae Joo!
We found Sun Young!
We found Sun Young.
What are you doing here?
Sun Young, why did you do this!
[Punish murderer Cha Si Young]
Don't you know you can't do this here?
Go away!
I said go!
Let go of me!
Hey, hold her properly!
I told you to go! Jeez...
Let go of me!
Hold her properly!
- Jeez...
- Okay, enough.
It's okay, I'll calm her down.
- Please take this away.
- Yes, sir.
Will you be alright?
It's okay.
[Muwon District Court]
Sun Young,
I think there's been a misunderstanding...
I understand you're deeply hurt.
Shut your mouth!
But...
- Hee Jin!
- What are you?
Who do you think you are to touch my man?
Calm down!
- Don't do this!
- Do you even know who I am?
Please stop!
Si Young!
- You crazy...
- It's okay.
What?
- What?
- I'm okay, really.
You're getting this worked up
over something like this?
Hold it in!
Your man only got a few slaps,
but mine lost his life.
Because of this murderer!
It's okay.
When did your memory come back?
At the hospital.
I heard you and Ji Won talking.
Then you should've told me.
You should've blamed me instead.
I killed Ki Beom.
What?
I told Ki Beom.
Not to confess under any circumstances.
To fight it to the end.
To hold out no matter what.
That's why he ended up dead.
He just kept holding out
and fighting like that.
I ended up killing Ki Beom.
Sun Young.
I should've just told him to go to prison.
10 years, no...
I could've waited even decades if I had to.
I should've told him just not to get hurt.
I should've told him
I'd wait with the baby.
I should've just told him
all he had to do was come back.
What should I do?
Oh my goodness, what should I do?
What if it leaves a scar?
Si Young!
- Yes?
- Who is that woman?
What is going on between you two?
No, it's really not like that!
Anyway, I'm sorry. It's all because of me.
I...
I will never, ever forgive her for this.
I'll make her rot in prison for life!
Aggravated assault? Adultery?
Anyway, there are charges
with heavy sentences, right?
You'll do that for me, right, Si Young?
What on earth is going on?
Hee Jin was assaulted?
- Father!
- Oh, my dear.
Are you badly hurt?
But where?
Oh, it's a bit scratched here.
But the psychological shock
seems more severe.
Who dares lay a hand on my daughter-in-law?
Where is that woman?
They say she's in the holding cell now.
No settlement, no forgiveness,
absolutely none of that!
Make sure she pays for it!
Yes, Father.
Oh dear.
Jeez.
Don't worry.
[Kangseng Bookstore]
We're closed.
Tae Joo.
What's with the bookstore?
We decided to leave Kangseng.
If this is because of me...
It's because we can't imagine
living here without Ki Beom.
Then where are you going?
Near my in-laws' place.
It's not completely unfamiliar,
and I think that would be better.
Sun Young
is okay, right?
Thanks for yesterday.
Ki Beom ended up like that because of me.
I couldn't protect him.
I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry.
Ki Hwan, I promise you.
I'll make sure those who did this to Ki Beom
get punished.
No matter how long it takes, I...
I will, no matter what.
I'm here just to tell you this.
I should go now.
Tae... Tae Joo!
Let's
never see each other again.
Never again.
Ki Hwan!
Seok Man.
What brings you here?
Seok Man, did you really kill them?
I mean, those women.
No!
Ki Hwan, it really wasn't me.
I really
didn't do anything.
Then how did Ki Beom's handkerchief
end up with you?
That... Ki Beom must have left it behind.
Please ask Ki Beom about it.
Seok Man.
Ki Beom is dead.
What?
Why did Ki Beom...
Wasn't he released?
Hasn't anyone told you
why Ki Beom died?
Ki Beom was beaten to death by the police.
If only you had been caught in time,
that wouldn't have happened.
Ki Hwan, it really wasn't me.
Please believe me.
Seok Man.
If you keep this up,
you'll end up like Ki Beom.
If you feel sorry for Ki Beom,
repent and take your punishment.
I really don't know
how that handkerchief ended up with me.
By any chance,
has my younger brother been here?
No, he hasn't even shown his face lately.
Tell Ki Beom to come visit.
My daughters are looking for him.
They're asking when the handsome guy
is coming. They're going crazy.
Okay.
Then I'll get going.
Alright, take care.
Please take good care of my mother, Uncle.
Don't worry and just focus on moving.
Okay.
I'll come pick you up once the move is done.
I'll be going now.
Drive safely!
Stay still.
It'll be over soon.
Are you dozing off now?
Are you, you punk?
Shh.
Just five minutes.
Just five minutes, please...
Then just say one thing.
Say you killed Lee Joo Hee.
Then I'll let you sleep as much as you want.
You punk!
Snap out of it, wake up!
Im Seok Man!
You punk!
Sleepy? You sleepy?
Want me to put you to sleep? You punk!
Confess, and you'll only do
five years and get out.
At this rate, you'll really end up
with the death penalty!
Open your eyes, you punk! Answer me!
Open your eyes, you punk!
I... I...
You killed them, right?
You killed them. Answer me, Seok Man.
I...
I killed them.
That's it, you punk!
That's the answer I want, you punk!
Good job, Seok Man.
Oh, good boy!
Well done.
What did you just say?
- You confessed?
- Oh gosh...
What on earth were you thinking?
I...
I don't even know myself.
By the way, what day is it today?
How long have I been here
since I was arrested?
Why do you ask?
Why haven't my father and sister
come to see me?
Sir.
Did you really reach out to my family?
What is it?
Did something happen?
Well,
they said they can't come because
they're afraid of what people might think.
- What?
- If they come here,
they'll be labeled
as the family of a serial killer.
And they're afraid
they might even lose their jobs.
And they said they want to
cut ties with you too.
But I'm not the killer.
- Why...
- What are you going to do then?
Everyone's going around
saying you're a murderer.
I...
Shut up! Shut up, you punk!
Why are you crying, you darn murderer!
Darn it!
Jeez.
Please help cover up my sister's case.
Then I'll quietly leave Kangseng.
Are you admitting you hit Lee Ki Beom then?
No,
I'm saying I accept the disciplinary action.
And someday,
I'll prove the punishment was unfair.
What?
It's my fight.
I won't let anyone else take it on.
If someone's going to break, it'll be me.
You're still going to fight to the end?
Even when it's obvious you'll lose?
If I fight to the end, then even if I lose,
it won't really be losing.
It's like throwing an egg at a rock.
I'm going to go for it anyway.
Even if it breaks,
it'll leave the stench of rot behind.
It can't stay a rock forever.
If it keeps getting worn down,
there'll come a day he becomes just a pebble.
Now, I understand
why that punk felt so inferior to you.
You two were born the same,
but you have something he doesn't.
What do you mean "born the same"?
Oh!
My stepmother, that punk's mother,
used to work at a bar.
Just like your mother.
My father met her there too.
Why didn't you tell me?
That your mom works as a hostess?
Do you want me to spill
[Kang Tae Joo, son of a bar hostess]
who you really are?
Everyone should know what they need to know.
- They're here.
- Please give us a statement.
Hey, snap out of it
and follow what we practiced, got it?
Answer me, you punk!
Alright, please step aside.
Alright, please step aside!
We'll begin the reenactment.
Ask questions after it's over.
- It's him!
- How did you do it?
Please move aside!
- Hey!
- Can you answer a few questions?
Move!
So, we'll start the crime scene
reenactment now.
Alright, how did you get into
the house from here?
How did you get in, you punk!
- I climbed over the wall...
- Climb over, quickly.
That's it!
That's how it happened.
Get over it, quickly!
Is that how you got over?
Hey!
- Hey, you punk!
- How is he supposed to climb like that?
Get your head together!
This punk...
You punk, you really wanna die?
Just do it like we practiced at the station!
- Quickly, quickly!
- You punk!
Get over it quickly, you punk!
Alright, he's climbing over.
Okay, come on over!
That's it!
Alright, snap out of it, you punk!
- Please clear the way for a second!
- Just a moment.
Jeez, this punk, seriously.
What are you doing now?
What? Oh, you're here.
What is this, are we filming a comedy?
Well, maybe this punk hasn't eaten.
So what, you're just going to watch?
- Pardon?
- Help him out! Prop something up at least.
Oh, okay.
Step aside. Move.
Alright, what are you doing?
Alright, step on this and get over quick!
One, two!
Is the suspect unable
to climb the wall by himself?
He does have a bit of a leg issue.
Maybe he is nervous.
Looks like he lost some strength.
It's not a big issue.
It's done.
Grab him, grab him!
Grab him, hurry!
Alright, you're up.
Did you get over this?
You must have gotten over, right?
Yeah, alright. You got over, you got over.
Okay, you got over.
Then what did you do next?
What did you do?
Hey, you said you covered her mouth first!
Yeah...
Think calmly.
Seeing how they work, it's really...
How come there's not a single guy
who works as well as Kang Tae Joo?
You punk, hurry.
You pressed down on her neck, right?
Seriously, Tae Joo, you could've done better.
You pressed hard, didn't you? Come on.
- They're out!
- Can you give us a statement?
- Just a few questions.
- Why did you do it?
Huh?
What is he saying?
Sir! Congratulations.
The reenactment went well today.
Is this really something to celebrate?
We regret the delay in arresting the suspect
and the suffering of the bereaved families.
Why did you start doing the reenactment
from the 7th case?
Unlike the others, the 7th case
took place inside a house,
and we wanted to proceed
while the scene was less disturbed.
Yes, that's why we did it. Please wrap it up.
I heard Kang Tae Joo is leaving Kangseng.
He's moving to Muwon.
So this is really the end now.
You've worked hard.
What rock?
You're just a pebble.
What on earth was he saying?
I'm definitely going to smash you!
You little pebble punk!
You waited long, didn't you?
I'm sorry.
I'll come more often from now on.
I miss you, Ki Beom.
Ki Beom.
Sun Young looks really distressed.
I'm thinking of sending her to join you.
What do you think?
So you won't be lonely.
Oh, Ms. Kang!
Hye Jin! Are you on your way home?
Yes! Ms. Kang.
Can I visit your house this Sunday?
Of course!
What do you want to eat?
Ice cream?
Then shall we eat ice cream
together that day?
You are that happy?
You really won't go?
It's not that I don't blame you, Tae Joo.
I know, it's not your fault.
I understand it in my head,
but my heart doesn't feel that way.
- Sun Young.
- Please.
Let's not see each other for a while.
Ms. Kang!
You're Hye Jin's mother, right?
Has Hye Jin come here by any chance?
No, is something wrong?
Hye Jin didn't come home yesterday.
What?
[Thank you for your support,
Cha Mu Jin, Liberty Republic Party]
[I'll be a worker for Kangseng.
[Thank you, Cha Mu Jin]
Your Honor,
for the defendant who cruelly took
the lives of seven innocent people,
I request the maximum penalty
of the court, death.
- What?
- What? No!
Death?
Defendant, please be seated.
[1988 Model Civil Servant Awards Ceremony]
We'll now begin the Model Civil Servant
Awards Ceremony.
The awards will be presented
by Minister of Home Affairs Mun Hyo Seok.
Please welcome him with applause!
Alright, those called, please come forward.
Superintendent Cha Jun Young,
Sergeant Jang Myeong Do,
Sergeant Do Hyeong Gu,
Corporal Park Dae Ho,
and lastly, Prosecutor Cha Si Young,
please step forward.
Certificate of Commendation.
Prosecutor Cha Si Young of the Muwon District
Prosecutors' Office, Kangseng Branch.
Sir, are you sure you really saw it?
Yes, I'm telling you, I saw it.
It was just lying right here!
Hey, Detective Kang, anything there?
Yeah, there is something!
There is? What is it?
Vomit. That guy's vomit.
What?
You must've been pretty drunk yesterday, huh?
Yeah, right. This is the spot.
I threw up and looked to the side, and...
Well, there was a woman's body right there.
But why isn't it here now?
Oh dear, if you drink too much,
you start seeing things.
There it goes again, jeez.
Alright, everyone, dismissed!
- Let's go!
- Yes, sir!
Lay off the booze! Don't make people
dig around for nothing, seriously.
Jeez, let's go!
Sir!
The body you said you saw,
what did it look like?
She was naked!
I thought it was a mannequin.
The hands and feet? Were they tied up?
Well, I don't remember clearly.
Everyone, please give a round of applause!
Any idea what these two could be?
You specifically separated those two cases,
so that must have been
very memorable for you too, right?
Of course, I can't forget either of them.
Oh dear.
If I reveal this,
the whole country will go crazy.
Police and prosecutors
will all be in trouble.
So what,
should I not confess?
Hey, Tae Joo, should you ask,
I can keep quiet.
What do you think?
Come on, what are friends for?
- I'm asking you.
- Yeah, sure.
Just tell me everything truthfully.
I want to know the truth about this case.
Every single detail.
Are you serious?
You'll regret it, though.
I'm begging you.
[Murder: 12+2]
One of them
was a child.
A very young girl.
The killings are not over yet.
It's him, the Kangseng Serial Killer!
So, you mean someone who has seen the body
could go commit a copycat murder?
The prosecutor is now trying to
frame the witness as a criminal.
They're hiding something.
Were there any suspicious incidents?
- But it's a child. An eight-year-old girl.
- Ms. Kang.
You punk! Why are you making trouble here?
- What did he say that got you worked up?
- Hey, stop.
And now what? A serial killer, you say?
Kang Tae Joo, do you even know
what I went through for this?