If I'm going to date a kid,
it definitely can't be Jun.
Why not?
Because he's Tai's little brother.
So what's Tai got to do with this?
You're just a friend of his brother.
Tai treats Jun like he's the most precious thing. They've
known each other since they were kids—super close.
You know what? Tai once told
me he wanted his mom to adopt Jun.
I can't even imagine... if I ever broke up
with Jun, how would I face my friend? v.
But they're not real siblings,
are they? If you like him, go for it.
I just don't want to
mess things up with Tai. v.
I...
Shut up, Sorn. And listen to me. All the plans you're
making for the future—go ahead. I'm not stopping you.
Because those are
things that bring stability.
But this—this is about your heart.
I want you to think about
today, not just the future.
You always make things
harder than they need to be.
Let me ask you
seriously—what are you afraid of?
Are you really happy saying
things that go against your heart?
Even I can tell you like him—and
I'm just watching from afar.
Did Jun pay you to say all this?
Nope. I just feel sorry for you.
You're such an idiot.
A kid confesses they like
you and all you say is 'thanks'?
What, you thanking your dad?
Isn't your dad the same as mine, you idiot?
And another thing—was he eavesdropping?
When he said he liked me?
Nosy little shit.
And he was drunk at the time.
You can't take everything a
drunk person says seriously.
He was drunk?
Yeah, right. You're just making excuses.
I saw everything.
And I know Jom is close to Jun too.
But... I don't really know that name.
Is he one of your crew?
You know Jom too?
Did Jun tell you about him?
No, he just happened to
call when I was with Jun.
'Hia Jom this, Hia Jom that.
' Sounds like they're
planning a trip together too.
So how far have you and
Jom gotten in your chats?
You two seem real close, huh?
And what's wrong with that?
We just know each other.
But you're not like this with Win.
Or Tai. Or Champ.
You don't spam texts
or call them this much.
I just talk to Hia Jom
about random stuff, that's all.
And with Hia Champ,
I've talked to him forever
even during the two years you disappeared,
I kept in touch.
I told you already—I don't like Jom.
What did Hia Jom even
do for you to dislike him?
Ask yourself what's going on with you.
You chase away everyone I talk to—Piangrak,
now Jom.
Why is that?
What if I said I was jealous?
Don't say it.
I told you before—if you don't
feel anything, don't say anything.
But what if I really am jealous, Jun?
Could you handle it?
You've hated me for years.
You won't even call me 'Hia.
' Even if you say you like me more now,
it doesn't mean you can
ignore everything else, right?
But I already confessed that I like you.
Do you understand what that means?
And you replied… 'Thanks.'
So how am I supposed to
believe you're really jealous?
You remember that?
I think I've been clear
enough about how I feel.
What you do with that—it's up to you.
Do you really like me? For real?
Get out. Don't come near me.
Tell me.
Tell me now, while you're sober.
. Otherwise I won't count what
you said when you were drunk.
What the hell, P'...
Sounds like someone just woke up...
Just leave.
I'm sleepy. I want to sleep.
You're not going to
let me take care of you?
Go take a shower, P'.
I'm seriously tired.
What if I said I was jealous?
Your eyes look swollen. Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Are you sick or something?
I'll take you to the doctor.
I don't want Tai blaming me
for bringing you home sick.
You okay? You've got to tell
me if something's wrong, Jun.
Man, I'm just happy you and Hia
Sorn are finally cool with each other.
Now we can actually go on
trips without all the death stares.
Jun.
Hey, Hia Champ. Hello. v.
So, how was the trip?
It was fun, Hia.
Then how come you didn't
come with Sorn today?
Hey Jun.
Hi Hia.
Where's my souvenir?
Oops, I forgot, Hia.
But I did buy something.
I went down south, so I
brought back some salted eggs.
Ah… hmm. (Feels like “Oh, I see.”)
Were the eggs very salty?
Yeah, they were salty.
James,
were the salted eggs salty?
Yeah… they were salty.
You mean, like, actual eggs?
Salted eggs are like… this, right?
Ugh.
That's not it?
Nope.
Sorn,
go check the order upstairs.
I think there's a mistake.
Okay.
Even more than pomelos.
Four of them. Four eggs.
Where did you go this morning?
Why didn't you leave with me?
I had some errands to run.
What errands?
Why didn't you tell me?
We could've gone together.
Didn't want to bother you.
Bother me with what?
Or did you plan to meet that asshole Jom?
No, I didn't.
And what if I did meet with Jom?
What's it got to do with you?
It has everything to do with me!
Because.
I'm the one Tai asked to look after you.
If you're going somewhere,
shouldn't you at least tell me first?
Let's go eat. I'm starving… come on.
I'm not hungry.
Then what do you want to eat?
Just tell me and I'll buy it.
We can eat together.
But I'm still...
If you say you're not
hungry one more time, Jun,
I swear I'll kiss you right here.
Aren't you afraid people
will think you like me?
Or did you forget you told me you didn't?
Jun…
Sorn,
come outside with me.
What's up?
Just ask.
Why'd you bring Jun to the house?
No reason.
He was free, so I invited him.
And? Looks like you
two get along pretty well.
I told you to open your heart to Jun.
He's just a normal kid.
That cheeky attitude—it's
just one part of who he is.
Yeah, real cheeky.
First day he shows up, he's already
drinking bootleg liquor with Nu.
Excuse me, here's your food.
Oh, let me get a menu too, please.
Sure.
I'll have… this one,
and this one… oh,
and this one too.
Why you ordering so much?
Feeding the whole company or what?
It's for your precious little brother, isn't it?
You sure take care of my brother well.
Didn't you ask me to look after him?
Yeah, and that's good.
Just don't forget—Jun's
like our little brother.
Yeah.
Where are you rushing off to?
Uh…
You've got plans every damn day. You
never wait to go home with me anymore.
Ever since you got back from the
South, you've been avoiding me.
What's going on with you?
If you keep shutting me out like this,
how am I supposed to know what's wrong?
Fine. I'll go shower and get
dressed. Let's head to work together.
Do you even get what I'm saying?
Yeah.
Food delivery.
P'Jom.
Hello. Is Khun Korn around?
Oh, Korn went to the café.
Okay, could you give this to him for me?
Sure, I'll take it for him.
Thank you.
Is Jun here?
Umm...
Praew, give this to Jun
for me. He's working for me.
Okay.
It's fine. Just let Jun know
I brought him some snacks.
Sure.
Thanks.
You seriously couldn't go get it yourself?
Jom bought that for you. Isn't it
rude if you don't go out to get it?
I already told Praew to grab it for me.
P'Sorn, can you help me? I'm
not really sure how to do this.
Same here, P'. I've been stuck for a while.
Why aren't my calculations matching up?
Since Jun's into fitness, I
got him something healthy.
Really?
What's going on between you and Jom?!
What the hell, P'?
Jom looks like he's trying to hit on you.
So what if he is?
You just met him. You don't
even know if he's a good person.
And how would you know if he is or
not? I haven't even tried dating him.
So you're gonna date him after
you just told me you liked me?
Isn't that none of your business?
Jun!!!
At least Jom never said...
He doesn't like younger guys.
You don't know a damn
thing, so stop talking.
Then if you don't know,
shut the hell up too.
Whatever's going on between
me and Jom... that's my business.
Hey, what's up?
Hey.
You been here long?
Yeah, a while. Are you drunk?
What? No way. Come on, let's have a drink.
Cheers!
Hold up. This is Hia Jom.
Hello.
Hey there.
And this is Win, my friend.
I'll be right back, bye!
You're such a drunk, man.
Hia.
Do you think someone like me
should even have a girlfriend?
Why do you ask that, Jun?
I used to date girls, y'know…
but it never worked out.
So I started liking guys instead.
You're not surprised I like guys?
A little. But honestly, it's
not far from what I expected.
Wait… do I come off that obvious?
But the guy I like… he
doesn't like me back.
So are you gonna go after him, or move on?
I don't know.
Hia. I think… I should probably let go.
Just haven't found someone to heal me yet.
Then take your time, Jun.
And if you're not ready, you
can lean on my shoulder for now.
Thanks, Hia.
That's enough, Jun.
Come on, Hia, just a little more.
That's too much already, Jun. Enough.
Hey, Sorn! Easy! Don't start
something here, calm down!
Jun, we're going home!
Hia Sorn.
I'm going home!
I said I'm not going back!
Hia Sorn? Why are you even here?
No one invited you.
Oh! Hi P'Franz, want a drink?
Just one more, yeah?
Let Jun go. If he wants to
drink, let him. I'll look after him.
Mind your own business.
Let's go home!
You! Come with me!
Jun.
Hey! Let him go! This is family business!
You're hurting him!
Look at what you did, Jun!
Why the hell would you
act like that at the club?
What if Tai asks me...
Hia Tai!
Hia Tai! Hia Tai.
Hia Tai that! It's always about Hia Tai!
Let me ask you straight.
Have you ever cared about
me by yourself? Just once?
All you do is use Hia Tai as an excuse.
Stop yelling at me, Jun!
No. Let go!
What the hell do you want from me,
Jun? You've been saying crap all day!
Then what do you want from me?
If you don't like me, just leave me alone!
Or is this how you care for
me—as Tai's precious little brother?
Don't bother next time.
I don't need it.
And dragging me out of
the club like some stray dog.
Did Tai tell you to do that too?
Huh?
Don't forget—you're just the
guy who taught me about sex.
You have no right to act like that.
Jun.
And another thing...
Every time we sleep together,
it's because you wanted it!!
And I was just the idiot
who let you fool me.
From now on.
You and I—we're done. I
don't care what it's about.
You won't have to deal
with a kid like me ever again.
And just so you know.
I hate you.
Shit! P'Sorn!
Hey, where'd you go last night?
I told you, didn't I? Don't drive drunk.
I wasn't drunk, bro. I went out with Jun.
Try to keep that kid in check. He'll
go off the rails when he grows up.
Bro…
Hmm?
It's just…
Nah.
What?
I don't know how to start.
That serious, huh?
Looks like Hia Sorn and
that Jun guy are about to...
Sorn, what the hell's wrong with you?
You sent the wrong order. If I sent this to
the client, what then? Pay attention, man.
Did Tai call you?
Yeah, he did.
What about Jun?
Why should I tell you?
Why didn't he show up for work?
I called him so many
times, he wouldn't answer.
He probably had something to do.
Let me borrow your phone, I'll call him.
Damn, what the hell's with
you today? You're so annoying.
Just let me borrow it.
Fine.
Hello, Champ.
Why aren't you answering my calls?
Are you ignoring me now?
Sorn, I gotta go.
Don't hang up on me, Jun! How are we supposed
to fix this if you keep running away?
I know you're mad, but I want to talk, I want to clear
things up. If you keep avoiding me, how can we fix it?
Let's talk later.
Jun.
I'll come pick you up this
evening. You're at Tai's place, right?
Want me to bring you something to eat?
Up to you.
See you.
Champ.
What's wrong with Sorn lately?
Did he fight with his girlfriend?
No idea, maybe he's on his period.
Oh, his period?
Just like me, mine just started too.
I'll go buy pads then, maybe get
some for Sorn too. The winged ones.
Size 20. Byeee.
Hey, what are you eating? Having
a celebration without telling me?
Why are you here?
Where is he?
Who?
Don't play dumb. I know you know
everything. I want to talk to him first.
Where are you going?
If you won't help, then
shut up. I'll go look for him.
If I do shut up, will you calm down?
Or will you finally be clearer than Jun is?
You led the kid on for months, dragged me into
it until you started lying to yourself too.
And when the kid actually fell for
you, you turned out to be a coward.
Have you even asked yourself
whether you really like him?
Sorn, are you and Jun dating?
Dating?, Damn!!!
He doesn't even know
if he really likes Jun.
Then how can I admit I like
him? He's your little brother.
I had to hold myself back.
Because if you get mad…
So how many times have you two done it? Did
you ever think that he's my little brother?
If you don't really like
him, then let him go.
Don't let him fall deeper
than he already has.
Guys, calm down!
Where's Jun? Let's just
call him and talk this out.
Jun's not here.
Tai.
I want to talk to Jun.
Then why didn't you talk to him before?
Think hard—what did you say to him
that made him not want to face you?
Let me tell you something. First thing you
need to do is admit your own damn feelings.
You idiot!!!
Fine… I like him.
I like them… so much it hurts.
I don't usually go for
younger people, you know...
But I like them. I really do.
So no one thought to tell me anything?
It's Sorn business, not yours.
Fine… I get it.
Sorn? You're here late. Is something
wrong? Did something happen to Jun?
Oh, no. I just happened to be nearby. Jun asked me to bring something
he forgot, but he messaged me saying I don't need to anymore.
Well then, I'll get going.
Okay, take care getting home.
Why do I feel like I'm helping someone
run off with someone else's wife?
You're still not answering Sorn's
calls? He's called you so many times.
Screw it. Just ignore it.
Shit, he's calling my house now.
Just pick up. But don't tell him I'm with you.
And if he asks where I am, don't say anything.
Hello, bro. I can't say, Tai orders.
That's all for now, my dad asked
me to run an errand. Yes, sir.
Jun, what are you gonna
do if he actually finds you?
I don't know.
Then… let me ask you this instead.
If he tells you he likes
you… would you be with him?
What would you like to
order today, P'James?
Espresso, thanks.
Morning, P'Sorn! You're here early today.
Good morning, P'Sorn.
Mmm... Jun's not coming in to work today?
Looks like… he's not coming.
Why does Sorn look so stressed today?
Yeah, I'm kinda scared now too.
You can't avoid me forever, Jun.
I will find you.
Get ready to meet me.
Hey, have you and Jun talked it out yet?
He's avoiding me. Thinks he
can just take leave and disappear.
So what are you gonna do?
He can't stay off work for long.
If he's gone too much, he
won't pass his internship.
Look… about yesterday, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to go off on you like that.
But you were right. It's
not really my business.
Who says that?
Everything's your business too…
But why… I don't feel like that.
What even are we? I don't even know.
Forget it…
Hey, it's not like that…
If you don't really feel
anything, then don't act like this.
Yo Win, doing stock check?
Yeah… so much stuff.
Hey, let's grab something
to eat tonight. I'm starving.
Pad Thai with omelette sound good?
You got it, man.
You made a deal. No backing out.
Deal!
See you, back to work.
Bye. Work hard, man.
Okay.
Still mad at me?
What… Who's mad at you?
Can we not be like this?
I really hate this feeling.
You don't need to feel anything.
It's always left hanging anyway.
Champ...
It's just...
It's fine. It's not even my business.
Champ, talk nicely to me, please?
Alright then, truce.
You look kinda cute in glasses, y'know.
Don't even.
Still mad? Huh?
Dunno.
Do you even shower, dude?
Mmm…
In the meantime, you should
really think about your feelings.
Mmm…
Maybe Jun needs time too.
He's been gone for a whole week. Still
not enough time to think things through?
Damn, shave that thing already!
Dude, I legit thought
you were a jungle bandit.
What are we celebrating?
Celebrate my ass. I came to
comfort someone heartbroken.
Who?
You, idiot.
I'm not heartbroken.
I just…
Got dumped?
I asked Korn where Jun is—he didn't know.
Asked Tai—he wouldn't say a word.
But that guy Jom, the one who
went clubbing with Jun? He knows.
Oh hey.
Whose rhino plushie is that?
It's Jun's.
So tiny and squishy.
Here, here—take this.
Let's toast.
Come on, Tai. Just tell me where Jun is.
Hia, I'm not trusting a
guy like Sorn. No way.
No way... Hia Sorn?
I caught you. Did you ever even miss me?
Obviously not.
Even if you didn't… I missed you.