(Lee Je Hoon)
(Jang Hyuk Jin, Bae Yoo Ram, Kim Eui Sung, Pyo Ye Jin)
(Taxi Driver 3)
(This drama is a work of fiction)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(Children and animals were filmed under guidelines.)
(2002)
Next team, stand by.
Showtime in 20. Let's move it!
Okay. Hey, let's go!
Hey, get up there. Go.
Get up there. Just get on stage.
- Come on. - Manager.
- What? What's wrong? - My leg still really hurts.
Don't start that before the show. Everyone here is in pain.
You're not the only one hurting. Let's go.
But it really hurts.
Stop with the excuses and let's just go.
No mistakes with the choreography today.
- We're moving. Please hurry. - Right.
I said, let's go!
Let's do this!
Don't be nervous. Go kill it out there.
That's it.
I'm so sorry. The stage isn't quite ready yet.
Just a moment. Hey! Kill the lights!
Close the curtain!
Hold on. Just a second. Do it again, hurry!
I'm really sorry. You're the Britel team, right?
Again, I'm so sorry. Just one moment.
Hey! Who on earth was that?
Are you with us?
The surgery was a success.
About your leg...
Tissue necrosis had set in, so we had to perform an amputation.
If the pain gets too severe, just call a nurse.
- Did you check her VAS? - Yes, I did.
If she's in too much pain, give her a shot.
Doctor.
What am I going to do? Doctor.
What am I going to do?
I heard she fell off the stage during her debut performance.
That's just awful.
Excuse me.
- Could you help me with this? - Sure.
What can I help you with?
Why are you looking at me like that?
I'm sorry?
Because you pity me?
No, that's not it.
Goodness.
Why on earth are you staring at me like that?
(Taxi Driver 3)
All right! I'm in the building's network.
Starting now.
Something tells me this is an adult entertainment club.
Which means the CCTV...
They've got CCTV, but they've kept it off the network.
Chief Park, open the electrical box in the hallway corner, please.
I'll patch you in right now.
You're connected. Take a look.
Connection established.
Kang Ju Ri is in one of the rooms,
and she's drinking with some guy?
What about the member who left the dorm?
Still nothing.
Then shouldn't you postpone their debut?
- Their debut is too soon to delay. - Isn't that a waste?
We should just focus on the girls we still have.
Rushing things and losing Ro Mi was a big enough mistake.
CEO Kang, you're really passionate about creating idols.
I must've debuted over 100 groups back in my broadcasting days,
but you never see them around anymore.
So is this about some unfulfilled dream of yours?
What was the group's name again?
Elements. Look out for them, will you?
And if I do,
what's in it for me, CEO Kang?
I'm sure I'll make it worth your while.
I'm sure you know...
I'm an asset, not a liability, to you, Producer Lee.
Gosh. A gold card.
You've got a point there.
Is someone else here?
Come on.
Hurry. Get out!
No, the manager said they were closed today.
Hang on, I'll go check.
I think they're onto us. You need to hide now!
Someone must be here.
Who's there?
Driver Kim Do Gi! Gosh! What do we do?
Hey, the lights are coming on over here too.
What?
Darn it. Wait.
Darn it.
Must be a faulty sensor. This is why I hate electronics.
Whatever, let's just go back and finish our drinks.
Man, my heart hasn't pounded like that in a while.
I think this is the place where Ro Mi was photographed.
- Yeon Min, you must start strong. - Okay.
Ji An, you're too slow.
Ji An, what's with that look on your face?
I'm sorry. I lost control of my breathing.
Wrong.
You should already be smiling before anyone has to ask.
Your smile doesn't have to be real. Otherwise,
the camera will pick up on how you're really feeling each time.
Yes, I'm sorry.
- I won't let it show next time. - That's more like it.
Huddle up, everyone.
Yeon Min, be decisive in the center.
- Cut that out. - Okay.
A Ra, when you belt, just go for it. And Soo Jung, you must smile more.
- It's your secret weapon. Got it? - Yes.
If you perform like that tomorrow, you'll be fine.
Now go out there and blow them all away.
- Okay. - Okay.
But, CEO Kang, aren't you coming with us?
My job was to get you to your debut.
Now, the rest is up to you.
From tomorrow, you can pay me back for a change, okay?
- Okay. - Now go get some rest, hurry.
- Okay. - Thank you.
- That's enough. Get inside, quick. - Thank you.
- No messing around. Go to bed. - Okay.
What are you doing?
Good work today, ma'am.
(If you're weak-willed enough to sneak out your phone, )
(then give up on being an idol right now.)
The person you called is unavailable You'll be sent to voicemail...
Ro Mi. We're debuting tomorrow.
I'm so sorry we're debuting without you.
It would've been so much better if you were with us.
The CEO said she's keeping your spot open.
Please come back to us, whenever you're ready.
I miss you, Ro Mi.
You're not going to write back this time either?
No, I'm not.
The members are probably hurt that you've never replied.
The four of them need to be seen as a complete group.
If I remind them there used to be five of us,
they'll just be constantly reminded of the empty spot.
And they'll already be so nervous on their debut day.
I see your point.
I hadn't even thought of that.
I really hope our Elements have a great debut tomorrow.
And that they really get to shine.
You'll be wishing for them too, right?
Remember? Kang Ju Ri was where we tailed the general director to.
And that's where Ro Mi's video was filmed.
So the director and Kang Ju Ri are working together?
But seeing her work so hard with the producer for their debut,
doesn't it seem like Kang Ju Ri is out of the loop?
So is this all the general director's doing?
So we're sure about the director, but not if Kang Ju Ri is with him.
Right. We just can't be sure.
I think we need to dig a little deeper..
What their real goal is.
Then you'll have to stick close to Kang Ju Ri tomorrow too.
That might be a problem tomorrow.
- It's the day of Elements' debut. - Right!
- You sound like their manager. - I am their manager.
The element that makes the world a happier place,
the manager of Elements.
What's this new side of you?
Ro Mi was also desperately hoping for the group's successful debut.
I know.
I'll have to work harder tomorrow.
As their manager.
Did you see him?
- He's so hot, right? - Yes!
- How may I help you? - Oh, my gosh!
(Manager of Elements)
We're here for Elements' debut today!
Great. You chose the same return day as all the A-listers.
Thanks to you, everyone here knows you're here for your debut.
What was the name? Elephant, was it?
That's the animal!
We'll give our official greeting. Two, three.
- Hello. - Hello.
- We're the element that makes... - We're the element that makes...
- the world a happier place, - the world a happier place,
- Elements! - Elements!
- Elements? As in, the elements? - Yes.
- Okay, I'm looking forward to it. - We'll do our best!
Gosh. Shall we head inside?
- Where are you now? - I'll be there in ten.
- Hello, sir. - Hey.
- One, two, three. Hello! - Hello!
Soo Jung.
Yeon Min.
A Ra.
Ji An.
- Are you okay? - I have a bit of a headache.
We must map all the camera blocking during rehearsal,
so do it all exactly as prepared, right down to the ending pose.
If anything changes for the take, we can't shoot it.
We're starting right away, so please get ready now.
- Okay. - Okay.
I just need to use the restroom real quick.
- Ji An! - Ji An!
- Ji An! Are you okay? - Ji An.
- Ji An. - She's fine.
She can hear you.
Move. Get out of the way.
Gosh. What's wrong with her, right before the taping?
- Hey, give me a hand. - Yes.
Unbelievable.
Gosh, darn it.
I'm taking Ji An to the hospital. You, go postpone the rehearsal.
Ji An!
- Darn it. - Ji An will be okay, right?
Shouldn't we all go with her to the hospital?
- Get the next act ready. - I'll get Elements on standby.
Goodness.
- Elements, you're next. Let's go. - Oh, no, what do we do?
What do you mean? Is there a problem?
Well...
One of the members just had to go to the hospital.
What? I told you, you can't be short a single member.
She'll be back right away. Please, push our spot back a little.
Don't be ridiculous!
What's taking so long to set up the next team?
One of the members is running a little late.
What? If someone's missing, how can we get the blocking right?
Is this show a joke? Just cut them and move on.
What are we going to do? They're going to cut us.
What are we going to do?
- But the girls practiced so hard. - I know.
- Oh, no, this can't be happening. - You heard him.
No, please. We have to perform today.
Please, I'm begging you.
I'm sorry, but Elements will not be performing due to a missing member.
Oh, no.
It's over. Everything's ruined.
We're completely done for.
Wait!
Elements that make the world a happier place.
- They're debuting today. - What? I thought we were one short.
We're all here.
You're sure you have everyone?
If not, you're in big trouble. Seriously.
We do!
- There's someone else? - Who?
- Could it be you, Go Eun? - What?
Hey, hurry and get ready.
But I'm not ready for this.
- What was it again? Seriously. - Just go out there. You'll be fine.
Go on, give it a shot.
Okay, let's start the rehearsal. Elements, 30 seconds to stage.
The members are on standby, right?
- Yes, they are... - Oh, gosh, my heart is pounding.
- I'm so nervous. - Oh, no.
They say they're ready, so we're heading in now.
- They're all on standby now. - Okay.
Let's roll.
- Lights! Okay, let's go. Go on. - Do we go on now?
Going in.
(Elements' Ji An)
Wait, is that right?
Okay, ready. And three, two...
Action.
Camera 3, a tight shot on each member. Camera 3.
Okay.
Who is that?
A member went to the hospital,
so the manager is covering for her for the rehearsal.
What? But that guy...
He's good.
Square! Come forward. Spread out. And then the finger thing.
Again from the top. Okay! Get down.
Okay. Shush. Now, back.
Driver Kim, you're killing it.
Forward. Hold your spot. Ji An's spot, hold still.
- To the back. Yes. - Go Eun would be even better.
Back. You're making it hard for me to concentrate.
Ji An's blocking. Okay.
Who's that? A Ra, Soo Jung... A Ra?
Wait, how does he know the choreography so well?
Even if he was watching them from the sidelines the whole time,
actually doing it himself is a whole other story.
You have to hand it to Driver Kim. I'd believe he was one of them.
He's really good.
Guess he doesn't need my help after all.
Is this a co-ed group or what?
- Thank you. - Soo Jung.
- Thank you. - A Ra.
- Thank you. - Yeon Min.
- Thank you. - Manager Kim. Wait, about this...
This is the ending, right? Pull out from Ji An to a full shot.
Ending shot!
Gosh. What's with the wink and the heart?
Goodness.
I'm exhausted just watching him.
It does look exhausting.
That's a wrap on their rehearsal. See you at the taping. Great job.
(One Selected)
Chief Choi, what are you doing?
I'm saving it to watch whenever I'm feeling down.
- Watch what? Give it here. - Hey, send me a copy of that too.
- Yes, sure. - What? A copy? Come on. Stop it.
- Come on, let's watch it together. - No way! I own the copyright!
Come on.
- Go, Elements! - Go, Elements!
I swear I was about to starve to death.
What is all this?
Gosh, your accent...
What did I just say?
I guess I was so hungry, I wasn't thinking straight.
I was so worried about what we'd do if you couldn't make it.
Before you got here, I must've said "What do we do?" 300 times.
That's right. Our manager...
was a lifesaver. He covered for you perfectly during rehearsal.
I'm really sorry for making you all worry.
Thank you, Manager Kim.
From what I saw today,
Ji An, even though you were sick, you were tougher than anyone.
A Ra, you did a great job fighting off your hunger.
Yeon Min, you did an amazing job overcoming your anxiety,
and our Soo Jung,
your smile was the brightest of them all.
It was a truly perfect debut performance.
- We did it. - We did it.
And you, Manager Kim, were a picture-perfect...
ending fairy.
- Wasn't it this? No, this one. - Right. This one.
- This. - This one, right here.
- That's it. - Come on, let's eat.
- Let's eat. - Thank you for the food.
What do you think about Manager Kim as a replacement for Manager Song?
I'm not so sure.
He seems to be getting too close with the members.
When Manager Song gets back, shouldn't we just get rid of him?
He's a handful, Ju Ri. It's like talking to a brick wall.
Go get Assistant Manager Kim.
Okay.
All right.
Our very own Elements. Look at my little treasures.
Goodness.
Hey, you all worked hard today. Hey, Ji An. You were so light.
Don't go collapsing again. Eat up. Don't worry about it.
Just keep it under 500 calories.
You need to replenish your energy, so let's all eat up.
- Hey! - Okay!
Hey! Zip it, okay?
Hurry up and get out. She's looking for you.
You were looking for me, ma'am?
Thanks to you, their debut went perfectly.
- Good work. - Congratulations, ma'am!
Congratulations for what?
Elements just had their debut. And you're not happy about it?
So they've debuted.
So what changes now?
Do they suddenly become stars?
Do we make a ton of money?
What do you think, Assistant Manager Kim?
Looks like she's testing Driver Kim Do Gi, doesn't it?
Gosh.
No matter what,
you just can't get emotionally invested.
- Just like you said. - Then,
are you saying I'm being sincere with those girls?
Do you know why I hired you?
I'm not sure.
I like your raw spirit. And you've got drive.
Most of all, you're so by-the-book.
You do whatever you're told, no questions asked.
I've learned that in life,
you have to get on the boss's good side
for everything to go well.
- Your money, your career. - Really?
If I told you to, could you even hit a woman?
Chief Park, it's go time! Go!
- Hurry! Go! - Me?
If you tell me to, I'll do anything.
Ji An will do.
Go on. Hit her.
This is no joke. The line...
Her poor self-control almost ruined the debut for the others.
What's wrong?
Did you get attached already? You can't bring yourself to do it?
I've already made myself clear.
If you give the order,
I will do it.
You're the punk who hit me last time.
Payback time!
- Sir, what are you doing? - Why did you get in my way?
Sir?
- What a complete psycho. - You can't do this in here, sir.
The boss is watching.
That's enough, everyone. Let's go.
Gyeong Su. Take care of this.
- Yes, of course. - But I haven't done what you asked.
Forget it.
Surprise!
Thanks for the cameo.
You should get that checked out.
- I'll bring the car around. - Okay, but wait a second.
The pen.
I guess you won't be needing this anymore.
Yes, ma'am.
Driver Kim, you're officially on the inside now.
You're back.
I've been thinking.
- Something's weird. - Come on. What is?
Why is it only me getting beaten up by Driver Kim?
Jin Eon.
This is when you need to reframe your thinking.
Reframe my thinking?
Don't think, "Why is it always me?"
Think, "Why am I the one he trusts?"
What?
I think he's onto something too.
Think about it. Whenever Driver Kim is in a tough spot,
the first person he seeks out...
is you, Chief Park.
- So that's it. - Yes.
So that's a good thing, then.
- Of course it is. - It's a great thing.
Here. Eat up. I got you a hamburger.
You did really great.
Gyeong Gu. This hamburger has no flavor.
- You take the wrapper off first. - Gosh.
I found this on the passenger seat.
- Sorry to trouble you. - It's no trouble, ma'am!
Spare me the details.
Box up the entire second row for me.
Let me see the purple one from the top row.
I'll have the rest boxed up for you.
Thank you.
I should get them a gift to celebrate their debut.
I'm sure the members will love their gifts.
No.
They're not for them. They're a gift to myself.
One pair for each of them.
When I was little, everyone used to tell me...
that I was destined to be a star.
But after my accident,
they all started looking at me with such pity.
Like I was the only person it had ever happened to.
Everyone has a downfall.
Anyone can fall from grace.
What's so darn entertaining that they have to keep staring?
It's irritating.
How pretty.
That was a great performance. Next up is a new girl group's debut.
Elements, with "Fly With Me."
- Let's check it out! - It's on!
- It's us. - It's finally us!
- Oh, my gosh. - My goodness.
I'm so nervous.
(Music Stage, Elements)
I should've eaten something. Don't I look like I'm starving?
You always look like that.
It'd have been better with Ro Mi.
Right?
- I know. - Tell me about it.
Hey, Soo Jung, you're on screen!
Time to settle up.
We'll start with Soo Jung.
Okay.
Do Gi.
Start the car.
You're such a good dancer! We're total idols!
- I know. - We're not bad, right?
Guys, we're so good.
- We're so pretty. - Look, the camera loves us.
- Goodness! - We're actually good.
- We're good. - We're singers now.
(Music Stage, Elements)
- We're so pretty. - Just gorgeous.
Pay attention. The real training starts now.
Watch and learn.
Oh, okay.
Oh, my, Manager Kang!
- Oh, my. - You're laying it on a bit thick.
Our Kang Star is here! I had to run out to greet you.
All our VIPs only ask for Kang Star. What am I supposed to do?
Come on. That's a given. Of course.
It's not every day you get to meet a celebrity who just debuted.
The other managers keep asking me for my secret.
They say they can't get anyone, no matter how good the offer is.
And even if I told them my secret, could they pull it off?
They must start as trainees.
Give my place special treatment.
They've been waiting. Hurry up and come in.
Do Gi, stand by. You wait right here.
Hello.
Hello!
Sir, good to see you. It's been a while.
Geez, I'm pretty sure I'm younger, but he always calls me "sir."
Hey, pass me the chopsticks.
Yes, sir.
I've got to know my place. You'll always be "sir" to me.
Shut it.
I was told you wanted to see me?
I'm not very exciting company, you know.
Come on. The madam told me everything.
She said to meet that new idol, you're the one I need to impress.
You can't force romance, you know.
Impressive.
Ju Ri, I already put in a good word for you.
What was the name of that group that just debuted again?
It's Elements.
Elements. Here, take a look.
The brand-new, hot-off-the-presses girl group, Elements.
It really is her.
What is this?
This was the plan all along.
From the very beginning...
There she is!
Hey, she's gorgeous, right?
After you showed me that photo,
I told you I had to meet her! You remember, right?
Look, I'm not normally this pushy,
but I'm kind of in a hurry today.
Is there any way I could meet her today?
No.
Okay, then. How about tomorrow?
If you're that desperate, you can just call an escort.
That's why our Kang Star here is giving you this sneak peek.
Crushing a dream that hasn't yet tasted despair...
takes more effort than you'd think.
I don't know what she means.
So when can I meet her?
I'll arrange a meeting no later than the end of the week.
She needs time to open up on her own terms.
That's a new one. How do you open up your heart?
- How do you do that? - Very carefully.
You idiot.
To ruin a dream they worked so hard for...
is the last thing those girls want.
Hey, CEO Kang, I just came in.
Look who it is.
Oh, right!
You're the "heart" guy.
Hey, you're a pretty good dancer.
Your form is like ballet.
CEO Kang.
Assistant Manager Kim.
- That's Assistant Manager Kim? - Yes.
He's a good dancer.
- The footage looked good. - Time to pay up.
It's their debut and final stage all in one. It has to look good.
The girls did great. They're good singers and dancers.
They'll just wash out soon after their debut anyway.
I guess so.
How many idol groups debut monthly? A ton, right?
Rather than walk away with nothing,
isn't getting tips at least better?
CEO Kang.
You should cut me in on the action later on, okay?
To give the girls who get sold off the second they debut...
one live performance, I have to grease a lot of palms.
This is nothing. This is just my pocket money.
Kang Ju Ri never intended to give them a proper debut.
Not from the moment she recruited the trainees.
So their training wasn't to prepare for a debut as idols,
but to make them "entertain" clients? Can you believe that?
By sabotaging the "debuted" idols, Kang Ju Ri...
was making up for her own failures.
By cruelly destroying others' dreams like this?
She used their desperation to save the dream they'd worked so hard for,
and set a perfect trap, leaving them with no other choice.
All by creating a fake agency called Yellowstar.
Go teach them a lesson right now.
That's right. We can't let those jerks escape.
Okay. Now that the truth is out, it's time for the next step, right?
Do Gi, I want you to go meet Ro Mi.
Because it's the client's choice, not ours.
The girls did great. They're good singers and dancers.
They'll just wash out soon after their debut anyway.
I guess so.
How many idol groups debut monthly? A ton, right?
Rather than walk away with nothing,
isn't getting tips at least better?
How could our CEO do this to us?
(Deluxe Taxi, Don't die. Get revenge.)
(Private)
(103 Taxi Driver)
(Accepts one-dollar bills only)
Hello.
First, thank you for choosing Rainbow Deluxe Taxi.
For your safety and convenience, we'll review a few instructions.
To request the services of the Deluxe Taxi,
press the blue button on the left of the screen.
If not, please press the red button on the right.
Now, please make your choice!
- Ro Mi, are you asleep? - No.
Ro Mi, no matter what happens, let's make sure we debut together.
Yes. We definitely will.
- Elements has to debut together! - What? You guys are still awake?
We have to debut together!
Hey, me too! I want in.
Me too. Stop it.
- Me too! - Hey, me too!
Let's go.
(Bang Bang Pow Pow Special Effects Team)
(Deluxe Taxi)
Vehicle 5283 is now in service.
So, what should we wreck first, Mr. Manager?
Whatever we start with,
- we must repay them a hundredfold. - A hundredfold! I love it!
I love it too!
A hundredfold sounds great.
(Bang Bang Pow Pow Special Effects Team)
(Girl Group's Shocking Antics)
(What is she doing at a bar before her debut?)
Have you lost your mind?
Why should all their work be wasted just because of you?
But, CEO Kang, I really don't remember.
Does your memory matter now, Soo Jung?
You're an idol now.
But if you're already caught up in a scandal,
it won't just affect you. Elements will be disbanded.
Can you afford the penalty for breach of contract?
What do I do, CEO Kang?
Fortunately for you, the guy wants to meet with you.
You need to meet with him...
and say you'll do anything he wants if he doesn't release the video.
If he wants to be your boyfriend, you let him.
- CEO Kang. - There's nothing to be afraid of.
You already know exactly what to do.
Just do what you were taught.
What I was taught?
Don't let it get to you. Just smile.
You don't have to mean it.
Because no matter where you go, anyone you meet is a fan.
You're not selling your body, Soo Jung.
You're making your dream come true.
And you're helping your friends achieve their dreams too.
Stop crying like a child and give me an answer.
Stop this, we survive together.
If not, we die together because of you.
You have such beautiful eyes. You'll do just fine.
Yes, I'll be there in 10 minutes,
so get Soo Jung ready and send her down.
And...
Darn it, she hung up on me again.
CEO Kang really gets things done. She's just a nasty piece of work.
A textbook sociopath.
Soo Jung. I'm on your side.
Darn it! What is that?
Soo Jung, the company is on your side.
Why won't it stop?
Why isn't this working?
Stop! Hey, stop!
Stop!
My hips kept swaying on me during my swing earlier.
I was so annoyed, I wanted to tear them right off.
- You were on fire today, though. - Yes, I'm running late today.
Was that your wife?
Relax, okay?
She's my girl, so be gentle. Like she's made of cotton candy.
But the booking was just for you. Is it cool that we all came?
Don't be so dense. Darn it.
- Hey! - What?
We'll just pay more! What, are you broke or something?
Well, I don't have as much as you do!
Plus, she's an idol, so she can't just run her mouth.
- Let's go party. - Let's do it!
Soo Jung, we are here!
Gosh, you startled me!
Well, look what we have here. Not just one guy, but a whole crew.
- Who are you? - Who do you think? It's Soo Jung.
You're the ones who asked for me.
What are you waiting for? Pour the drinks.
Let's party hard tonight!
- Gosh, you startled me again. - Darn, I forgot to shave my legs.
And what are you supposed to be?
Me? Park Soo Jung.
You called us. Where are you going?
Do you have any idea who I am? One call and you jerks are done.
- Kim Soo Jung is here too. - You jerk! Do you know who I am?
I'll tell my dad, and you'll all...
Wait! Time-out!
Gosh.
Come on. We'll take care of things here.
Driver Kim, you should go now. The live broadcast starts soon.
- Go on. - Okay.
- I mean... - Gosh, it's so hot.
Final check for the live broadcast!
- Yes, control room cameras are set. - Okay.
Mic tone checked. Return monitor is clear.
Okay.
- Standby on stage. - Okay.
- Go Eun is good to go! - Okay! What?
- Hey, who was that? Who's ready? - Starting countdown.
Five, four, three, two, one.
And action!
- Hello, everyone. - Hello, everyone.
Welcome back to Music Stage.
- I'm your host for today, MC Hyuk. - And I'm Yoon.
- That's right, everyone. - The madam told me everything.
She said to meet that new idol,
- you're the one I need to impress. - Gosh.
- If you're that desperate, - What?
- you can just call an escort. - What is this?
Turn it off, quick!
Crushing a dream that hasn't yet tasted despair...
takes more effort than you'd think.
Time to pay up.
The footage looked good.
Hey! Are you trying to ruin the live show? I said, turn it off!
It's their debut and final stage all in one. It has to look good.
The girls did great. They're good singers and dancers.
Hey, why won't the audio cut out? Why won't it cut out?
- They'll just wash out soon... - Who is it?
- after their debut anyway. - Who played that?
How many idol groups debut monthly? A ton, right?
- Who on earth is it? Turn it off! - Rather than walk away...
with nothing, isn't getting tips at least better?
- And action! - This can't be happening. No!
You should cut me in...
- on the action later on, okay? - Do you know...
- what it took me to get here? - To give the girls who get...
- Do you know what it took me? - sold off the second they debut...
one live performance, I have to grease a lot of palms.
- Where's that sound coming from? - This is nothing.
- This is just my pocket money. - Why won't it turn off?
They'll just wash out soon after their debut anyway.
Rather than walk away with nothing, isn't getting tips at least better?
Hey!
- Just one comment, please! - Say something!
Please make a statement!
Out of the way! Let her through!
Ms. Kang Ju Ri! Please give us a comment!
- Ms. Kang Ju Ri! - Stop filming.
- One comment, please! - Stop filming!
- Get out of my way! - Everyone, make way!
- Let go of me! - Please make a statement!
Everyone, clear a path.
- Let go of me! - Ms. Kang!
Everybody, stop filming! Don't follow her!
Get her!
- Ms. Kang Ju Ri! - There she is! Ms. Kang Ju Ri!
- Ms. Kang Ju Ri! - Ms. Kang Ju Ri!
Ms. Kang, a comment!
- Stop the car! - Get out of the way!
CEO Kang, give us your comment!
Don't you have anything to say?
Ms. Kang Ju Ri!
It's confirmed that CEO Kang Ju Ri of Yellowstar...
illegally filmed her agency's idols...
and used the videos to blackmail them for sexual favors.
The scandal with illegal contracts and unpaid wages for idols...
was also masterminded by CEO Kang...
- There she is! - She's out!
Ms. Kang Ju Ri! Are the rumors true?
Ms. Kang Ju Ri! Did you blackmail them yourself?
Ms. Kang, is it true you filmed your idols...
and blackmailed them?
The person you called is unavailable You'll be sent to voicemail...
This is driving me crazy.
Ms. Kang Ju Ri, wait!
Ms. Kang, using sponsors as bait,
did you extort money from the wealthy?
- Hey! - Ms. Kang Ju Ri!
Did you profit by forcing your idols...
- to work in adult entertainment? - Ms. Kang.
- Give us one comment, Ms. Kang! - Open the door!
- Come on. - Ms. Kang!
The way down!
(Stairwell)
Ms. Kang Ju Ri, give us your comment!
- Darn it! - Ms. Kang!
Assistant Manager Kim.
Come and get me. I can't get down from here,
and I have nowhere to go.
I'm on the rooftop. Come get me.
But I'm already at the top.
So, how does it feel to have your big debut?
Assistant Manager Kim?
To make you a star,
I've decided to become your new manager.
What?
You did all of this?
But why would you do this?
Why?
Don't tell me...
you're frowning.
You're supposed to be smiling.
As if how you really feel matters at all.
Or am I wrong?
Or does it not matter, since you'll be forgotten anyway?
You scum.
Hey!
Everyone starts out with pure passion.
And anyone can fail.
But that doesn't mean it's a downfall.
Even if you stumble today,
you can get back on your feet tomorrow.
Don't make me laugh.
You're the one...
who's been spiraling after just one failure.
Those girls...
Do you really think they'll ever make it?
Who's even going to remember them?
At least I'm helping them make some money.
So what's the problem?
What's your problem?
Hey.
How long do you think their shelf life is?
What are you doing?
Are you filming me right now?
Hey!
Hey. Stay back.
Stop filming.
Stay away.
No!
I can't move. No!
Stop filming! No.
Hold on tight.
Don't you ever...
give up.
No.
(Deluxe Taxi)
I can't thank you enough.
It's not over yet.
How to push forward with the members waiting for their leader...
That's where it starts now.
Right.
They must be waiting for you. You should go.
Okay.
(Deluxe Taxi)
Thank you so much! Thank you!
- Are you sure? - I don't know.
What are we going to do now?
We have to stick together. We just debuted.
- What else? - Seriously...
We have to keep going.
What are we going to do?
Ro Mi.
- Ro Mi, where have you been? - Ro Mi!
- Ro Mi. - Ro Mi. Where have you been?
- I'm so sorry. - We were so...
- I'm so glad you're back. - It's okay.
- We're glad you're back. - We missed you.
Thank goodness.
You made the right choice.
- It's so good to see you. - We missed you so much.
Now we're all back together.
(Ibiga Jjamppong Restaurant)
This looks delicious.
What? How can we not drink with all this great food before us?
Go Eun, you're not drinking?
- No, I'm not. - Why not?
She doesn't have a glass.
Were you going to drink all by yourself?
Of course. You have to have a drink with a good meal.
I'll have one too, then.
- Looks like all the food is here. - Yes, sir.
- Mr. Jang, would you like a drink? - Of course. I've got to have one.
- All right. A toast. - To a job well done.
- Great job. - Cheers.
- Let's dig in. - Let's dig in.
Enjoy, everyone.
The foundation of Chinese cuisine is jjamppong. It has to be good.
Gosh, it's so chewy and addictive. This is a must-order.
- How is it, Driver Kim? - It's really good.
It's got a nice kick.
The more I drink this broth, the more I want.
Music Stage has been incredible! But everyone, it's not over yet!
Next, the hottest rookie idol group out there right now.
- I know who you're talking about. - You do?
They're all over online,
- and they're brought back... - Here they come.
By popular demand. You're talking about them, right?
The element that makes the world a happier place, Elements.
- Please welcome them! - Please welcome them!
(Music Stage, Elements)
They're gorgeous.
I never get tired of this song.
- I already joined their fan club. - I already did too.
- What? - So did I.
Seriously?
(Music Stage, Elements)
(Deluxe Taxi)
(24M 5283)
Vehicle 5283...
is now in service.
(Special thanks to our guest stars, Jang Na Ra and Kang Na Eon)
(Taxi Driver 3)
Hello, Mr. Hero.
Can you just tell me exactly where and who you bought it from?
- Looking to buy a bicycle. - ID, Fishing King.
All of the posts posted by that jerk's ID...
I went through and reported them all.
Then he contacted me.
Apologies for the late introduction.
Your delivery's here.
- Eat your noodles. - Give me my money, you wench.
As for my instruction, I'll replace it with what will happen from now.
He's using a burner phone and a ghost account.
- It's all fake. - But one thing is real.
The police? They can't catch me.
His voice.
Where is he right now?