(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
YUMI'S CELLS 3
EPISODE 16
THE PRETTY OLDER GIRL WHO BUYS MEALS
THE BRAIN SCIENCE OF LOVE
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN FALLING IN LOVE
MS. KIM, PLEASE CALL ME WHEN YOU WAKE UP
It's nine already?
Oh, Ms. Kim.
Hello, Na-hee.
Oh no. Did I wake you up?
No, I was already up.
- Already?
- Yeah, why?
I was wondering when's a good time
for our meeting next week.
Shin PD was asking.
He could've just asked me directly.
He said he didn't want to
disturb your writing.
I'm making good progress
so I'll finish episode 15 today.
Let's have the meeting tomorrow.
Episode 15 is already done?
Yeah, I've picked up some speed.
That's amazing!
But Ms. Kim, did you pull an all-nighter?
No, I got some sleep.
Can I help you with anything?
No, it's the weekend, so just rest.
I'll let you know if I need you.
Okay, I understand.
You got this, Ms. Kim!
Let's go!
Why is she making progress
so quickly all of a sudden?
It's strange.
What's not to like?
This is how it should be.
The village is so peaceful.
I'm almost grateful to Soon-rok
for drawing the boundary.
When I think about how we wasted
all those weeks for nothing...
it really makes my blood boil.
What's that?
Hey, what is it?
Hey! What's going on?
Today is Sunday.
It's Soon-rok's blind date.
So what?
What do we do?
Who pushed for it?
Why is she fussing
when she's the one who set it up?
It's your fault.
You, Pride!
Was I supposed to just stand by
while Soon-rok was drawing the line?
You could've just said you'd look into it.
Why did you have to actually set it up?
That's how I protected Yu-mi's pride
because I actually set it up.
Thanks to my judgment
Yu-mi was able to save face.
Now, don't forget, everyone.
If you say you don't like me
then I don't like you either!
Just shut up!
Why don't you shut up?
There are only a few hours left.
My chest is churning.
Like something's about to explode.
That kind of simmering feeling?
What's wrong with her?
Love is acting weird.
I think she's about to explode!
Hey, don't come over here!
What a sight.
I knew you guys would end up like this.
Why did she follow him to Busan
when her deadline is so close?
What did she gain from going there?
Did she go all that way
just to set up a blind date?
No.
All energy can be
converted into another form.
Love, come here.
Follow me.
We can use this anxious heart for writing.
Now, pour it all out.
No, not here.
That's right.
I've got it. It's all coming to me.
The emotions are just gushing out.
This is brilliant.
This is good.
Am I a genius?
Yu-mi, guess where I am.
This looks like my neighborhood.
THIS LOOKS LIKE MY NEIGHBORHOOD
That's right.
I came to your neighborhood.
I'm supposed to meet Shin Soon-rok here.
Why did you come all the way here?
You could have met in Seoul.
I had work in Ilsan this morning
so I said it's more convenient here.
I'll have a good time and report back.
You don't have to report back.
No need to report. Have a good...
He's here.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO REPORT BACK.
HAVE A GOOD TIME
He's even more handsome in person.
I'll contact you later.
They met.
They finally met.
Ignore it.
I was at my peak concentration.
Let's keep going.
But aren't you hungry?
Hey, Hunger Cell, you're hungry, right?
How about we eat something first?
I'm not hungry.
I ate snacks all night.
You must be craving sugar.
I had juice, so I'm not craving it.
Why not?
You crave it all the time
so why not now!
I'm craving sugar.
Let's eat something.
First floor.
First floor. Cancel.
Second basement floor.
What? Aren't we going to
the convenience store?
How far are you going to go for a snack?
I'm suddenly craving
strawberry custard bungeoppang.
Hey, what?
You're going home
to buy bungeoppang?
Oh, this is crazy.
You didn't even bring the car keys...
Who brought the car keys?
It's only a ten-minute drive away.
Let's get some fresh air too.
I've been pushing myself too hard.
Oh, my. Wait!
Isn't that them over there?
I knew it.
They really met.
Of course they met.
Stop stating the obvious.
Jennie dressed up nicely today.
She put a lot of effort
into her makeup too.
Her curls look great too.
They look good together.
Let's go.
You said you'd finish it today.
That's right, Yu-mi.
You might get a parking ticket.
- What was that?
- What do we do? She saw us.
Yu-mi.
Yu-mi!
What is this? This can't be happening.
Besides, do you know
Yu-mi didn't even wash her face?
And her clothes are a mess!
Let's just go. Let's bolt.
Everyone, calm down.
Yu-mi isn't just Kim Yu-mi anymore.
She's the star writer, Kim Yu-mi.
We have to protect our writer's pride.
So what are we supposed to do?
There's only one thing
Yu-mi can do now.
- Jennie.
- Yu-mi!
- Hello.
- Ms. Kim.
I was just passing by
and remembered
the photo you sent, so I peeked.
To see how it was going.
But you caught me.
I thought you were in your studio.
I came to buy some bungeoppang
since I only eat from this one place.
Are you eating something good?
Yes, pasta.
- What about you? Did you have lunch?
- Of course I did.
- I'll let you two get back to it.
- Wait!
Stay a little longer.
Hey, I can take a hint.
But you both look so cool today.
You don't look like the people I know.
I always look like this, don't I?
Oh, yes. You're right.
Well, have a great time.
Shin PD, see you at the meeting.
Oh, okay.
I'll contact you later.
I sent her a picture
of this place earlier.
I guess she saw it passing by.
I see.
Just a moment.
Ms. Kim.
- Why would you...
- I already paid.
No, why did you pay for this?
Well, the matchmaker can treat you.
I'm the older one.
That's the only path
for Yu-mi to take now.
Being the pretty older girl
who buys meals.
PRETTY OLDER GIRL
Have a great time.
Wait...
She paid?
Yes.
I shouldn't have sent the picture.
I made her worry.
I think she came all this way
just to buy us a meal.
Thanks for the meal.
She's a really good person.
She's great to work with, right?
Yes.
Right, I'm glad I treated them.
Since we met anyway.
Good job.
The pretty older girl
who buys meals?
THE PRETTY OLDER GIRL WHO BUYS MEALS
So now Yu-mi is the
"pretty older girl who buys food"?
It was an unavoidable situation.
Still, it was handled well
without making it awkward.
I didn't wake up just to become
a "pretty older girl who buys food."
It's not so bad being the
"pretty older girl who buys food."
She might just be an
"older girl who buys food."
PPANGEO PPANGEO
- Hello.
- Oh, hello.
Ten strawberry custard bungeoppang please.
Okay.
But it will be about five minutes.
- Oh, that's fine.
- Okay.
I'll pay first.
Okay, here you go.
By the way...
Are you sick?
Me, sick?
- I'm not.
- Well...
You look a little tired today.
I see.
Oh, it shows.
- I've been swamped with work lately.
- I see.
I told you we should've put on makeup.
"Tired" is just a nice way of saying
she looks like a mess.
Thank you for the meal.
Thank you so much!
For a handsome man
and a delicious lunch. Hehe.
You're the best!
As you age
you need more excuses
to protect your pride.
Maybe that's why there are so many
"pretty older girls who buy meals."
EPISODE 17
THE CHARM OF THE GAME
It's Jennie.
Jennie.
Are you really reporting back?
Don't answer it!
I'll call her after I finish.
Hey!
How can you not answer?
Hey, Jennie.
Are you in your studio?
Yeah, in my studio.
Did it go well...
I'm nearby right now.
Can I come up for a bit?
- Here?
- I have something to give you.
- Sure.
- What was the unit number again?
It's 1505.
Okay, see you soon.
Okay.
She's coming up right away?
- Yu-mi.
- Jennie, come in.
You've been busy lately, right?
Soon-rok said you'd be very busy
since your deadline is tomorrow.
Soon-rok?
They're on a first name basis already?
Isn't that better
than calling each other by nicknames?
I am busy...
but I have a deadline every week
so I'm fine.
Well...
I just wanted to give you this.
What's this?
They're cookies.
For a sugar boost
when you're stuck with work.
Gosh, you shouldn't have.
Sit down. Want some tea?
Can I?
Of course, you can.
I feel this every time I come here
but the view here is really amazing.
Right?
I can't move because of the view.
So, how did it go?
The date?
Yeah.
How was it?
Can I be honest?
I guess it was a bust.
Of course.
- So you didn't like him?
- I like him.
You like him?
He's totally my type.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
At first, I thought he seemed a bit cold
but the way
he smiled sometimes was so cute.
I know. I know what you mean.
And he was surprisingly funny.
He's a bit quirky,
like he's in his own little world.
I told you
I know what you mean.
I'm glad you liked him.
But I'm not sure
what Soon-rok thinks of me.
- Why?
- We said bye on a good note
but I feel he won't contact me.
I'm not sure.
You should do it.
Yu-mi.
Can't you ask him for me?
- Me?
- Yes.
Can't you just casually ask him
what he thinks of me?
I set you up and bought you a meal.
Isn't that enough?
Do I have to provide
after-sales service too?
And whose fault is this?
Who came up with the "pretty older girl
who buys meals" concept?
Fine.
- I'll ask him later...
- Now.
Can you ask him right now?
- Now?
- Yes.
I'm dying to know.
MS. KIM
Yes, Ms. Kim.
Shin PD, is this a good time to talk?
Yes.
Oh, have you sent the manuscript?
I haven't been able to check my email yet.
No, it's not about that.
How was it?
Sorry?
The date today...
Oh, the date.
I was just curious.
Well, we met and it went well.
She seemed like a nice person.
Right?
Jennie is so cute, right?
She's so cheerful and a great person.
She's a total mood-maker.
Yes. I think so.
So...
Well...
you're going to
see her again, right?
Oh, yes.
- Really?
- Yes.
I should contact her.
Oh, yes. Right.
That's great.
Okay, I'll let you know
when I send the manuscript.
Okay.
Shin PD said
he had a lot of fun too.
He said it was fun.
Really?
I bet he'll contact you soon.
Yu-mi, thank you so much.
I was so lonely.
I'm way lonelier.
- What?
- Nothing.
Wait.
Something's wrong.
Hello? Hey, Love Cell,
something is a bit strange.
Did you make a misdiagnosis?
Writer Yu-mi doesn't seem
interested at all.
Hey, has my diagnosis ever been wrong?
I'm the authority in this field!
Look, she set him up
on a blind date right away
bought him a meal
and even called him to wish him well.
What if he drew the line for no reason?
It's not for no reason.
He drew a line, she lost interest.
Is that it?
Well, isn't that a relief anyway?
We have to work together
so it's a relief.
It is a relief...
Is it really a relief?
Then why do I feel bad?
Me?
I don't feel bad.
Right? I don't, right?
I'm just tired.
Right, it's because you're tired.
PRIME LOVE CELL
Hello.
You're here.
I thought you were coming with Jang PD.
- I'm coming from another meeting.
- I see.
Would you like some coffee?
Could I have an iced Americano?
- Of course.
- Thank you.
The script was interesting.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
This episode's emotional scenes
were especially good.
That's a relief.
If you say it's good,
then it must be really good.
You're not the type to say things
just to make a writer feel good.
Is that the image I have?
It's not an image.
You're that kind of person.
Aren't you?
Oh, I see.
So that's the kind of person I am.
There are a few minor things
but I'll mention them at the meeting.
Okay.
Yu-mi.
You said you have a meeting today, right?
Did Soon-rok get there?
I'm just curious.
I haven't heard from him yet.
By the way...
Did you contact...
Jennie?
Oh, right.
Not yet.
Okay.
Do I...
really have to?
Oh, no.
Of course not.
Okay.
I'll contact her soon.
What was that?
Why the grim face?
Don't jump to conclusions.
It's the same as usual.
- Ms. Kim, I'm here.
- You're here.
You two came together?
- Hello.
- We ran into each other on the way.
Shin PD, hello.
- Shin PD, you're here already?
- Hello.
JENNIE
Yu-mi, I heard from Soon-rok.
We're meeting on Friday. Yay!
That's great.
I'll do my best. Let's go!
Right, I feel relieved.
I've done all I can.
Let's just forget about it.
You guys handle it yourselves.
Just stop already, please.
What should I make?
Player Seo Hyeong-jun has come out.
He has one win, one loss, four holds.
An ERA of 2.33 and a HIP of 1.93.
Player Seo Hyeong-jun's
curveball was really good
but in the end,
KT's offense didn't explode
- so he was pulled with no decision.
- Yes.
Jang Jin-hyeok comes in
as the center fielder
and Player Kwon Dong-jin
comes in as the shortstop.
It looks like the first tag
touched the ground first.
- To the side.
- It touched and then grazed past.
- So it happened in two motions.
- Yes.
Not in a single motion.
Sliding to the side...
The wall, the wall, it's over.
He catches it there
and creates a deflected hit.
LOHAS is coming alive like this.
First score, KT Wiz.
Both left and right-handed
batters are swinging
but he's weaker from the right...
But something's off.
Since his batting is improving
he's hitting homers from the right.
In this game, his son pitched,
and he's coming to bat now....
- Heave, ho, heave, ho.
It's strange.
I'm home, but why don't I feel
like I'm recharging?
I'm going to sleep more.
- Hello?
- Hey, you did something useless.
That stupid moderation surgery.
I shouldn't have brought up
the blind date.
I drew a line to avoid complications
but now it's even more complicated.
I came home, but I can't recharge.
My head is a mess.
No, if you're too tired
you might not be able to recharge.
No! It's because the surgery went wrong.
What are you going to do now?
This is LOHAS showing us.
- Leaving behind good results.
- Yes.
Kia is taking the lead.
WRITER BAEK NA-HEE
Hello?
Shin PD, are you free to talk?
Yes.
Since our male lead likes games
Ms. Kim ordered a game console
to try it out herself.
It arrived a little while ago.
Oh, really?
I thought the installation
would be simple, so I said I'd do it
but I just can't seem to do it.
You said you have the same one
at home, right?
Yes, that's right.
Just leave it.
I'll set it up next time I go.
Okay, so I'm giving up and going home now.
I'll just put it aside for now.
Shouldn't Ms. Kim...
try it out soon?
Well, I was waiting
- until Friday...
- Should I go now?
What?
Leave it and tell me the studio code.
I'll go set it up and come back.
But it's late.
I don't have anything better to do.
You just got home
and you're going out again?
I'm not charging anyway.
Though I don't know why.
I'd rather tire myself out physically
so I can sleep.
Starting navigation.
It's done.
Ms. Kim.
Wait, what's going on?
Why'd Writer Yu-mi suddenly show up?
What do we do?
It's about to run out of battery.
- Soon-rok, get a grip.
- Get a grip!
- Why are you here at this hour?
- Why are you...
I came to set this up.
Na-hee contacted me
and said she couldn't do it.
Gosh.
You didn't have to rush over to do that.
I didn't have much else to do.
But Ms. Kim, why are you...
Oh, me?
I couldn't sleep
and didn't want to waste time
so I thought I'd write
a bit of episode 16.
But you really startled me.
I'm almost done.
If you give me ten minutes...
Don't worry about it.
I don't have to write right now.
I'll be done soon.
I brought some
strawberry custard bungeoppang.
Would you like some?
Yes, I'll have some.
Something to drink?
I have milk
or cola.
I'll have milk.
You have good taste, right?
Milk is a must with the bungeoppang.
I was a bit taken aback
when you offered cola for a second.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Would you like to...
sit here for a moment?
Me?
Have you ever used one of these?
Oh, no. I'm terrible at games.
I'll give you a quick tutorial.
Have a seat.
Oh, okay.
You have to control everything with this.
I've seen this a lot.
It'll be a bit confusing
for the first few days.
First, place your hands like this.
Thumbs too.
Yes, like this.
See the X and O buttons here?
Yes.
O is the back button
and X is the start button.
Okay.
Want to give it a try?
Start.
- No, you have to press X.
- Oh, right. X.
Yes.
SELECT CHAPTER
SELECT CHARACTER
See? It's starting, right?
- Oh, so this is how it starts.
- You did great.
Okay, now let's learn
how to move forward and jump.
Push the left stick up
while pressing X twice
with your right hand
then square once, quickly.
Can you try that?
- No, not like that...
- Oh, wait...
Like this.
Oh, okay.
No, that's not it.
Hold on.
Push the stick up with your left hand
and press X twice.
Square button
and then it does this.
Like this. See?
Do you get how to control it?
You get it, right? How it works?
Yes, I think I get it...
but I think I need to practice a bit.
Yes.
It'll take a few days to get used to it.
- Okay. I'll try it by myself.
- Okay.
Is that not it?
- What's wrong with it?
- No, slowly.
Oh, slowly?
Oh, I got it.
Or not?
- Why is it doing this?
- No, while moving forward.
Yes, like this?
Hold on.
Oh, gosh.
Like... like this.
Oh, okay, okay.
I totally get it now. It's like this.
How do I... I'll try it myself.
Oh, okay.
Oh, I got it.
Gosh, this is simple.
You're good at this.
Do you want to try another game?
- Right now?
- Yes.
Which one is fun?
One moment.
Oh, this one is fun.
This one's super popular.
It's a game even a complete
beginner can play.
I recommend it.
Another one?
Oh, this one is a game with a story
so I'm sure you'll like it, Ms. Kim.
This one is really good.
It's...
But, Shin PD...
It's late. Shouldn't you be going?
It's already past twelve o'clock.
Is it...
You're right.
I'll try it by myself.
I'll get the hang of it if I keep playing.
Okay. Take your time.
Thanks for coming so late.
It's nothing.
Then I'll be going now.
Okay.
- I'll just clean this up then.
- Oh, no, please.
I'll clean it up.
Then I'll just take the box out.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
Call me anytime
if you have trouble.
I have to try it myself.
I won't bother you.
It's not a bother.
Okay. If I really can't do it
I'll call you.
Okay.
- Bye.
- Going down.
Take care.
Door closing.
It's so late.
I'm already tired
and I couldn't even charge...
What's this?
This isn't my house,
so why are the lights so bright?
EPISODE 18 VINTAGE WINE
Where are you going?
I'm going to a meeting.
- A meeting with Yu-mi's team?
- Yes.
- Why?
- If you go now, when will it end?
I don't know.
- In two or three hours?
- You'll have dinner too?
Well, it'll probably end before that.
- But why...
- It's nothing.
Do well. Good luck.
Soon-rok, are you busy?
Where are we meeting today?
Oh, no. He forgot to make a reservation
at the restaurant.
Soon-rok said he'd do it.
RESTAURANTS
It's Friday evening.
We might not be able to get a reservation.
I'll get going now.
Yoo PD, I'll be leaving now.
Yes, goodbye.
What if we change the username?
I think the username
makes it more obvious.
But will that make it plausible?
I don't think the viewers
will know the difference.
Wouldn't it be better to have them
change the security company?
The security company?
If they change the company
everything will change anyway.
And the male lead was on a
business trip, so he didn't know.
That sounds good.
But I don't know what all changes
when you change security companies.
- Oh, I'll look it up.
- Should I look into it?
I have a friend who works
at a security company.
Oh, that would be great.
I don't know anything about that.
I'll look into it.
Thank you.
Then it seems everything is settled.
Should we wrap up the meeting here?
- Yes, great work everyone.
- Yes.
What should we do for dinner?
- Should we grab a bite before we go?
- Yes, sounds good.
Oh, I have plans.
That's right.
You have plans.
- Let's just the two of us go eat.
- Okay.
Shin PD, where are you going?
Great work today.
Meeting twice means
we've fulfilled all the manners.
Let's wrap it up today.
Yeah, I just arrived.
What floor is it?
The 15th floor. Okay.
What? It's Writer Ju-ho.
Why is he here?
Well, the meeting will end early anyway.
Who is that?
Who is it?
Yes, hello. This is Writer Kim Ju-ho.
- Ms. Kim.
- Who is it?
He says he's Writer Kim Ju-ho.
- Kim Ju-ho?
- Yes.
- He's downstairs?
What should I do?
Wait, what?
Let him in for now.
- Hello.
- Oh, yes.
Come in.
Ms. Kim, he's here.
Hello, Ms. Kim.
Hello.
Am I interrupting something?
Or may I come in for a moment?
- Yes, of course. Come in.
- Thank you.
Your studio is really nice.
This studio
is just like you.
You were surprised that I came
so suddenly, weren't you?
Of course, I was surprised.
You came without any notice.
I had some business in Ilsan
and I remembered hearing
that your studio was nearby.
I asked Dae-yong
and since you had a meeting today
I thought you'd be here.
Oh, I see.
Oh, and...
I also came to give you this.
Is this wine?
Yes, I just got back
from a short trip to Europe.
I bought some nice vintage wine
and you came to mind, Ms. Kim.
Oh, thank you.
By any chance
do you like vintage wine?
I don't know much about wine.
I see.
It's a 1997 vintage.
A 1997 vintage?
I bet your assistant
wasn't born then, right?
Right, I was born in 1999.
Ms. Kim, do you happen to remember?
- In 1997, we...
- I don't remember
what I did in 1997 at all.
I was too young.
I'm not from your generation
so don't ask me.
But...
this seems very expensive.
Why give it to me?
Well...
It's a peace offering.
I felt I was a bit rude in Busan
so I wanted to apologize.
If you put it that way
then I should apologize too.
I lost my temper that day too.
So are we even now?
Well...
it's not something
we need to be even about.
It was just an incident.
I knew it.
Ms. Kim, you live up to your name.
But Dae-yong kept pushing me
to come and apologize.
So you were pressured into coming.
No wonder.
Well, anyway...
let's at least shake hands to make up.
I'm sorry.
Well, I'm not sure if this calls
for a handshake...
But, sure.
Shouldn't we take a photo as proof?
So the Chief Editor can see it.
This is why I like you, Ms. Kim.
- Have a seat.
- Oh, yes.
Would you like some coffee?
You're offering coffee too?
Of course. What would you like?
Okay, then...
I'll have an iced latte, please.
- Okay.
- Just a moment.
I don't see Shin PD.
I heard there was a meeting,
so I thought he would be here too.
He had an appointment, so he left early.
You don't think he heard
I was coming and bailed, do you?
I don't think so.
Soon-rok is upset with me.
The rumor is that you're the one
who's upset, Mr. Kim.
Gosh, no way.
But I feel more comfortable
without him.
He kept acting like your bodyguard.
What?
Your meeting is over, right?
Would you like to have dinner together?
I just got here.
I'm here now too.
Yes, Shin PD.
Are you still at the studio?
No, we left.
Is everything okay?
What do you mean?
Has Writer Kim Ju-ho left?
How did you know he came by?
- I saw him when I was leaving.
- I see.
We're having dinner with Writer Kim now.
- Dinner?
- Yes.
Mr. Kim brought some vintage wine
and he suggested we open it together
so we came to Roti Vino.
And it's really delicious.
Mr. Kim explained the wine so well.
Okay, I get it.
- Enjoy your dinner.
- Okay.
Bye.
Let me give you our menu.
- Thank you.
- Is this for takeout?
No, I'll order when my party arrives.
Here is the wine you ordered.
What is this?
The gentleman there ordered it.
This is already the third bottle.
Would you like to taste it?
No, actually.
Please fill this glass all the way.
- And just a little for us, please.
- Of course.
Let me clear the glasses.
Na-hee.
We'll leave after this dessert.
What?
Go pay before he orders more.
Oh, okay.
That guy just doesn't know when to stop.
Gosh, he always crosses the line.
I shouldn't have made up with him.
Yu-mi, I think I got stood up.
What are you talking about?
Soon-rok canceled on me.
Right before we were supposed to meet.
What? Why all of a sudden?
It's Luce Vino.
No, the restaurant's name is Luce Vino.
Oh, it's next to Kim Yu-mi's studio.
You know the one, right?
Yes, that place.
Anyway, I'm here.
Yeah, just come here for now.
He canceled right before?
Yeah.
I'm eating by myself right now.
What the heck?
What was his reason?
Isn't that Shin PD over there?
Why is he here?
I don't know.
He just said he was sorry.
Why is he here?
Okay.
Okay, I got it.
Hello, Mr. Kim.
What is this?
Why are you out here?
How did you get here?
I heard you left early
because you had plans.
It got canceled.
I talked to Na-hee
and she said you were all here, so...
So I came to see you
and I also hadn't eaten dinner yet.
I can still order, right?
I'm hungry.
Hey.
You.
Are you spying on me?
Looks like you came to spy on me again.
The way you suddenly ran here.
You're seriously driving me crazy.
What are they talking about?
I think Mr. Kim is angry.
I think so too.
Hey.
What am I supposed to do with you?
You've been getting on my nerves
ever since Busan, you jerk.
Hey, why are you doing this to me?
Vintage wine.
Soon-rok, stop.
What? Vintage wine?
- What about it?
- The vintage wine...
has that meaning for you.
- What does it mean?
- You use vintage wine to woo someone.
To seduce a woman from work
you always use the vintage wine.
Well...
I think I've seen you do it
to at least five people.
The last was a baseball team employee
you met during a report, right?
And the translator.
Oh, also.
There was also the Chief Editor
from the Japanese publishing house.
You always gift them vintage wine
asking to share memories of that era.
And it always ended badly.
You've even pushed me
to clean up your messes.
Hey, are you really going to
run your mouth like this?
Yes, stop running your mouth, Soon-rok.
Chief Editor Ahn doesn't know
about this stuff, does he?
Because I didn't report it.
But if he knew about this
he probably wouldn't try
to set you up with Ms. Kim
I'm in charge of Ms. Kim right now
and from the moment you brought
that damn vintage wine
I'm in a position
where I can't help but worry.
Should I go out there?
Okay.
Actually, never mind. I'll go.
Hey, you just hit me?
This guy actually hits people.
This son of a bitch. Hey!
You want to come at me?
Hey, my glasses!
I can't believe this. You.
Hey!
Let go! Hey, let go!
What's with them?
Hey, let go! Let go!
What are they doing?
You really...
Hurry, let's go.
They must be crazy.
It looks like a fight broke out.
I told you to stop, Mr. Kim.
No, let me go!
No, really, because...
Let go! It wasn't me, it was him!
Let go! Just let go, you jerk!
- No, I'm telling you it was him.
- What are you doing?
Jeez, seriously.
Let go. I'll talk to him. I won't hit him.
Just let go.
Jeez.
- You punk!
- Stop, stop, stop.
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Stop.
That's enough.
Damn it, let go of me.
Ms. Kim, please go inside.
You don't have to worry about it.
I'll handle everything.
I mean, what was that?
I have no idea what just happened.
I know... right?
But how did you get here?
I called Ju-ho.
I told him he should come see you.
I thought it would be okay
if we all had a meal together...
- It's all my fault. I'm sorry.
- Jeez.
You didn't know it would
turn out like this.
Go on inside.
I'll contact you later.
Gosh, I was so surprised.
I thought I was watching a play.
The two rushed onto the stage,
then rushed off.
And they kicked...
You think this is funny right now?
I'm sorry.
Unbelievable.
We're screwed, Soon-rok.
We're completely screwed.
I said we're completely screwed.
What are you going to do now?
CHIEF EDITOR AHN DAE-YONG
Hello?
Hey, you brat, are you crazy?
Gosh, this punk.
I even changed your team,
and you're causing trouble again.
Hey, who do you think you are,
fighting with a senior writer?
I...
didn't do anything.
Mr. Kim caused this.
Shut it. Come apologize right now
or resign.
I'm at his studio right now,
so get over here immediately.
I'm sorry.
But I...
Don't argue who's right or wrong.
Settle it later. Apologize first.
Get over here now.
Yes, Chief Editor Ahn.
Yes, yes.
Then what about Shin PD?
I told him to come and apologize.
He'll be here soon.
I have to make them reconcile
today, no matter what.
But why on earth did they fight?
I don't know.
He won't tell me either.
Okay.
I'll call you back.
- Okay, sure.
- Bye.
Who is it?
Shin PD.
I thought you went to see Mr. Kim.
Why are you here?
I felt like I had to see you first.
Why?
Why did you come here?
I don't know.
What do you mean, you don't know?
I'm not sure either...
Why did you break your plans
with Jennie and come here?
I don't know.
You don't know that either?
I shouldn't have done that.
I know. You shouldn't have.
So, did you come here
to apologize to me for that?
It's fine, I'm okay.
- Just go to...
- I didn't come here to apologize.
Then why?
I think...
I like you.
PRETTY OLDER GIRL WHO BUYS MEALS
YUMI'S CELLS 3
Why is Soon-rok acting
like that right now?
Everyone, it's a real emergency!
- I'll take care of it!
- Get him!
Yu-mi set it up without knowing.
We already ended things cleanly.
I'm going to Soon-rok.
Heart Fever Time!
Shin PD, come this way.
Run, Soon-rok!
Shin PD? What are you doing here?
It's just like yesterday.