(Uilhan Brewery)
(1. Malting, 2. Malt milling, 3. Mash tun, 4. Hopping)
(Kim Se Jeong)
(Highly passionate, highly sensitive)
(Lee Jong Won)
(Shin Do Hyun)
(Baek Sung Chul)
(Uilhan Brewery)
(Naro Beer)
(Brewing Love)
(This is a work of fiction.)
(Scenes with child actors and animals were filmed...)
(under production guidelines along with experts.)
This...
Do you have any idea...
how many times I prayed for a chance to meet you?
Saving a life isn't that big of a deal for me.
I only did what I should've done.
How is this not a big deal when we got to meet again like this?
Your emotions. Why...
What's wrong?
What a surprise.
Who would've guessed?
Our fates must be entwined in a mysterious way.
Right.
I had no idea it was you.
I mean, you were nothing like the woman who saved me.
Find everything that poses a risk to you,
and protect yourself first.
That's how you can be kind to yourself.
Be kind to myself...
Isn't that for people who don't have to face struggles in life?
Is that so?
Well, people change throughout their lives.
Shall we head back inside? Let's not keep Mr. Yoon waiting.
What was that?
Why didn't you tell me...
you were in contact with Ms. Chae?
I had no idea.
Did you even ask?
That day...
Goodness.
Wasn't it an incident you didn't want to talk about?
I didn't mention her for your sake.
All is well since he now knows.
Of course.
You're right.
Little guy. How's the pink teddy bear?
The pink teddy bear?
Min Ho, a big boy like you...
shouldn't be playing with stuffed animals.
What...
It's all right.
I'm 32, and I still like pink teddy bears.
Who cares?
What...
Sir, I won that pink teddy bear for him,
so it's upsetting to hear you say that.
Goodness. Were you the sniper?
Yes.
My gosh.
As said, our fates must be entwined.
Hold on. Yong Ju, wait.
Can't you stay so that we can talk?
The situation has been bothering me.
Until next time, sniper lady.
Sure. I'll win you another stuffed animal.
I love you, sniper lady.
Drive home safely.
Take a break if you feel like dozing off...
and get back on the road when you're not sleepy.
That reminds me.
Don't forget your promise.
The stuffed animal.
Got it.
I'll get going then.
What? But...
Hold on.
But...
She's definitely hiding something.
(Brewing Love)
Is she still not back?
My gosh.
Goodness...
My goodness.
What? Grandma, why aren't you asleep?
I was jolted out of my slumber.
Are you just getting back? It's late.
- Should I turn on the light? - No, don't.
It'll be blinding. Go to bed already.
Why is the night light off?
I told you to keep it on to prevent getting hurt in the dark.
I heard you, okay? Did you come home to nag me?
- I'm going to bed, so leave. - So temperamental.
Good night.
Why? Do you have something to say?
No. Sleep tight.
Grandma put this up here again.
Why would she do this when I don't need it?
As said, our fates must be entwined.
Protect yourself first.
Grandma?
Grandma, what's wrong?
Welcome.
- Do you have a reservation? - Yes.
Why am I always the first to arrive?
I told you I was busy on weekends.
Besides, aren't you too old...
to celebrate your birthday with your parents?
If you had to have us here, why not book a fancier place...
rather than this casual restaurant for kids?
Kids would come to places like this...
to celebrate birthdays with their families.
I never got to, and it ate away at me.
Unbelievable. The price dropped again.
I'm getting married.
A year later. No matter what.
I was wondering when you'd say that again.
Kids these days opt to stay unmarried...
and lead incredible lives.
Why are you so desperate to get married?
You're a weird one.
My dream is to be a good mom.
Sure. I hope you have a daughter like you.
That's right. I'll have a daughter like me...
and be the mother that you never were.
What didn't I do right by you?
I fed you nice things, bought you nice clothes,
and sent you to nice schools.
You were offered a premium childhood.
Do you have any idea how rough it was for me...
to live in poverty?
You should count your blessings.
Did I say otherwise?
I know I had it lucky and am grateful for it.
But you should at least know the truth.
All you did was give me money.
Of course, ma'am. I'm almost there. Just wait a little while longer.
Absolutely. You're the only one I'm relaying this information to.
Yes, of course. Sure thing.
Ah Reum, those corvinas are expensive.
Have that rather than cake.
What's the time? Gosh, I'm off.
Anyway, Ah Reum, happy birthday!
- Weren't I right? - You were.
Why is he here?
I seem to see him everywhere.
- Do you have a reservation? - Yes, under Oh Chan Hwi.
Did they have to seat him here?
- Did you see that? - No way.
- What are you doing? - Come on.
What a joke.
- Over here. - Here.
- What should we have? - Let's hurry up and order.
- I'm hungry. - Me too. What about this?
- Sounds good. I want that. - Me too.
- This one. - Why did I hide?
Baby brother, choose what you want.
I want alcohol.
- What? No way. - I want a drink.
- That's a no. - Guys.
- It's Mom and Dad. - Mom and Dad?
- Son! - Mom, Dad.
- Mom! - Hey.
I can't believe you guys.
- You went on a trip overseas... - Sorry.
Sorry.
and left me to celebrate our baby brother's birthday.
Being the eldest brother of a Korean family is a challenge.
Anyway, stay safe and have fun.
- I love you. - I love you.
I love you, Mom.
- They must be having fun. - It'll be fun for them.
A family expressing their love for one another?
Ah Reum, I have a meeting and must leave early.
Take your time with your meal.
That's right. I should get going too.
Drop me off on the way.
What? Is there anything you can do by yourself?
Do you still want a husband after seeing that? I'm off.
I'll pay for the meal on my way out.
See you later. Bye.
- Lucky you, baby brother. - I'm the best, right?
Hold on.
- How about a photo? - Sounds good.
- We'll send it to Mom. - Nice.
Seriously?
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, dear baby brother
- Happy birthday! - Happy birthday!
Happy birthday to you
- Happy birthday to you - Happy birthday, Ah Reum
Happy birthday, dear Ah Reum
Happy birthday to you
Make a wish and blow out the candles.
Ms. Beautiful Bang?
It really is you.
Seeing you on the weekend is a nice treat.
Right. Fancy running into you here.
She's Ms. Beautiful Bang whom I work with. Say hi.
- Hi. - Hi.
They're my siblings.
Bit Na, U Ri, Wi Ha, and Man Se.
You have four siblings?
I've never seen anyone of our age with that many siblings.
Right. It's not Ms. Beautiful Bang, but just Bang Ah Reum.
- Happy birthday. - Thank you.
We share a birthday.
Really? No way.
Ms. Beautiful Bang, I'd love to have coffee with you,
but I have to drop them off.
- Who said anything? - Right?
Just in case you're bummed out. I'll see you around.
Why would I be bummed out?
- Guys, let's go. - It was nice to meet you.
- Take care. - Bye.
It's picture-perfect.
This was the only place I could come to.
I already ate, but I'm hungrier for some reason.
It was the same back in the countryside.
Why do you keep caring?
Others usually spend money on me.
You're mistaken. I spent money on you too.
This box of chocolate sandwich cookies...
cost 5.8 dollars.
- I see. - Make a wish...
and blow out the candles.
"I want Oh Chan Hwi as my boyfriend."
- What was that? - I didn't say anything.
Happy birthday.
(A very early morning a few days later)
Photo, my eyes open easily in the morning these days.
What a delicious morning it is.
Photo.
Why did Yong Ju leave in a hurry?
She's obviously hiding something from me.
Should I call her?
No, right?
I should wait, right? Yes.
Hey, Photo.
What a beautiful sunny day, right?
But what's the point?
I don't even know how Yong Ju feels.
Ms. Chae, is something the matter?
Yes, you seem a little down today.
No, everything's fine.
We're getting the first batch of the new product sample today,
so I guess I'm a little nervous.
This actually helps refresh your mood.
Thank you.
It's good.
Thanks again.
What about me? I need a little pick-me-up too.
Here, take the whole thing.
(Jisang Liquor)
The elders...
You're here.
Well, I prepared these. They're nothing special.
When will they be here?
- I'm telling you. - Come on.
Hello, everyone.
- Chae Yong Ju, right? - Chae Yong Ju, again?
- Chae Yong Ju is here. - What's the matter?
- Well... - Say it.
Why did you do it?
Why did you do that?
Why did you wreck the town?
Why did you have to do that?
What? Me?
Yirgacheffe.
Boss, you're here.
I guess we should go and do some work now.
- Yes. - Gosh, we took a long break.
My goodness.
Did I tell you ladies?
You know, Ms. Chae Yong Ju was the one who saved my life.
Here you are, going on about Chae Yong Ju again.
Seriously...
I mean, you've been doing this for days.
At this rate, I might see Chae Yong Ju in my dreams.
But I think there's something she's hiding from me,
and I really can't figure out what it might be.
What could it be?
You can either like her or be depressed.
Make up your mind, will you?
You're driving us nuts, seriously.
(Uilhan Pub)
Why are you buying flowers every day for this place? It's a pub.
Aren't they so pretty?
These flowers looked so pretty that I just had to buy them.
Chief, I went to visit my father, and Ms. Chae was there.
When I saw her, I felt my heart drop.
- Oh, no! - What?
My ear is bleeding.
- What? - Am I dying?
Can I hang out here for a bit?
It's not like you'll leave if I say no.
Exactly.
Well, Ms. Chae isn't saying anything.
But I should still wait, you know. I am curious.
All you talk about is...
Chae Yong Ju.
How much longer are you going to talk about her?
Come on. Don't be so mean.
- Jjuan, let me explain... - My gosh.
I am blocking you. You have been blocked.
Boss, keep your mouth shut.
I tried to hide it,
but I guess Mr. Yoon felt it too.
But I must say, I've never seen him so chatty.
- I know. - Yes.
All day long, he's like, "Yong Ju." He can't stop talking about you.
Oh, boy.
I mean, how did he even live...
- before he met Chae Yong Ju? - Right?
Exactly.
I thought my love,
Jjuan, and I were the only ones in this town...
who were brought together by fate.
- What are you doing? - You startled us.
We're not even curious about you two.
Grandma, the man I saved is living a pretty happy life.
It's great, isn't it? Aren't you glad?
So, you're okay too. Right, Grandma?
I don't need to regret what happened.
Right?
(Grandma)
Grandma, I'm sorry I came so late.
But...
why do I feel so uneasy?
What's wrong?
What? Shall we go inside?
I hope the sample turned out nicely.
What's the matter now?
(Uilhan Brewery)
Oh, nice.
(1st sample)
(Beer name, brewer, volume, pairing, suggested price)
I focused on the aroma while making the first sample.
Beers from big brands...
all smell similar.
The aroma is either weak,
or it's just like any other grainy scent.
It is very aromatic, indeed.
You must've used premium-quality hops.
Of course, it'll smell and taste good if you use good ingredients,
but it also means the unit cost will be high.
I have to drive on our way back,
so I can't taste it.
There's a bitter aftertaste, although it's subtle.
You have sensitive taste buds.
I'm a supertaster.
The quality is certainly there,
but the aroma isn't enough...
for us to nail down the concept.
Shall we check out the second sample now?
How about we use locally grown hops, rice, and barley...
and emphasize that it only contains locally grown ingredients?
There are many beers like that already.
I've tried so many beers while traveling across the country.
Then how about we try cold-temperature aging?
Then it'll taste smoother.
Just from the sounds of it, I can tell the costs will go up.
Like the lemon beer and the grapefruit beer,
how about we add a new fruit flavor?
If it's not done well, it's likely to fail...
because of the artificial taste.
(Mashing: Crushed, malted grains are soaked...)
(in hot water to extract sugars from malt.)
(Filtering: After mashing, grain bits are filtered out.)
(Hopping: Boil the wort and add hops.)
(Chilling: Chill wort to below 20°C.)
(Yeast and Airlock: Yeast is added...)
(to aid fermentation, and an airlock...)
(is installed to monitor the fermentation process.)
(Hydrometer: A hydrometer is used...)
(to check the condition of the yeast and the alcohol percentage.)
(Check Additional Ingredients)
(Storage in Beer Aging Cellar)
We've done everything we humans could do on our end.
Now, we shall wait, hoping the beer will turn out nicely.
But you two were in different groups in the special forces.
How did you two become friends?
Right, I was curious too.
That's a very important and sensitive issue.
So, we can't really tell you guys.
Well, it's like a state secret.
(1 year earlier)
My gosh! Unit 767, the strongest of all.
You're working hard to protect our country.
Come on. I'm getting used to selling booze now.
That's right. Let me know when you're on leave.
I'll buy you all kinds of delicious food.
Yes. Solidarity.
"Unit 767, the strongest of all?"
I am not cool with this.
How dare she use UDF's nickname?
"How dare she?"
I'm Oh Chan Hwi.
I'm Chae Yong Ju.
- I used all my might. - That was our youth.
Goodness. What's with you two?
Sure, keep calling it a state secret.
It's so childish that I refuse to hear the rest.
It's hot. Do you guys want coffee?
We have to go downtown to get coffee, right?
- You should go since you said it. - What?
No! I will go.
Because I'm...
a cool guy.
(Cool Guy)
Hey, I cherish that bike. I never let anyone else use it.
I'll use it in secret since you cherish it so much.
What? You're definitely not using it in secret now.
I found the helmet on my own.
I want to ride that too.
You've been on that bike.
Me?
Ms. Beautiful Bang, why are you still sitting down?
You have to come with me.
- Me? Why? - Are you saying I should go alone?
How many... One, two, three, four, five.
I need to get five cups of coffee.
I only have two hands.
Okay, I'll come with you.
I noticed that you had such a happy family.
All families are happy. Am I wrong?
Some families aren't.
So, do you live with the Five Eagles?
No.
I live on my own.
The truth is,
I've run away from home.
I told you I had a lot of secrets.
I guess...
I might want to know those secrets.
My gosh. Hey, I heard that!
You seem quite interested in me these days.
Once you fall for my charms, there's...
There's no way out.
Had I not crossed paths with Yoon Min Ju at that moment,
would Grandma's situation have changed?
(Grandma)
I missed her call.
Grandma!
Grandma, I'm sorry I came so late.
No. What's the point of thinking about this now?
It's all in the past now anyway.
What are you doing here alone?
I just wanted to get some air.
Why are you avoiding me?
What do you mean? I wasn't avoiding you.
I could sense it when I saw you at my dad's place.
I thought, "There's something she can't tell me."
If you want me to wait until you're ready to talk, I'll wait.
So...
don't avoid me.
If you avoid me, I will be sad.
I feel like you can read my mind even if I try to hide stuff,
so I'll just tell you honestly.
I have a lot on my mind now.
But it has nothing to do with you. It's about me.
I just...
Once I sort my thoughts, I will tell you everything.
I won't avoid you, either.
Okay.
Yong Ju!
Rao has to go back to Seoul now.
What?
What is it? What's wrong?
I just heard that my dad collapsed.
I should go and see him to find out what's going on.
But I have to drive. What should I do?
Wait, you drank earlier.
Let's take my car.
- Okay. - I'll come with you too.
(Central Surgery Center)
Mom.
Rao!
What happened?
- Your dad... - Yes.
What happened? Tell me.
What should we do?
We've confirmed that it's an ischemic stroke.
He will have to undergo emergency surgery now.
Please read this surgery consent form...
and sign it right away.
Mom.
Wait.
(Authorized Personnel Only)
(Pontine hemorrhage, intracerebral hemorrhage)
(Respiratory paralysis could occur.)
(Signature)
You have to sign the form, Rao.
You are his guardian now.
Rao.
Shim Rao.
Okay.
(Signature)
Thank you.
- Rao. - Yes.
Listen to me carefully, all right?
There comes a moment in life...
when you suddenly have to become an adult overnight.
It's when your parents who you thought would protect you forever...
suddenly collapse.
From now on, you should protect your parents.
But what can I do? I am not ready for this at all.
Even now, I have no idea what to do. What should I do?
Can you calm down first?
You should not be crying now.
Come with me.
It's your dad, so you should get extra large diapers.
If you only use regular diapers like these, it'll get expensive.
If you use these...
with separate liners, it'll be much more cost-effective.
You're his son,
but it'll be embarrassing for him to have you change his diapers for him.
Keep that in mind and try to be extra sweet to him...
so he won't be too embarrassed.
You see, bedsores can be very scary.
Clean his body often to check for new ones.
- I'll wait outside. - Okay.
This way.
Hospital bills, care expenses, and more.
You'll have to pay a lot of bills from now on.
Consider using caregivers on weekends.
If not, you should be here.
Take that into account too.
If you stay here as a caregiver all day,
you'll collapse first.
Care is like running a marathon.
- You should be in good condition... - But how do you know...
all of this so well?
Yeah. How do I know all of this?
Mr. Yoon?
Why are you here, Mr. Yoon?
- Gosh... - Mr. Shim Cheol Nam!
We received all the payments for your bills.
What? He is my father.
Have you bought everything already?
CEO Yoon, I truly appreciate that,
but I'll handle it myself.
It's rather uncomfortable.
Honestly, I've no idea when I'll be able to pay you back.
And...
That's how it is. I can handle it.
That's exactly how I felt too.
"Why would other people help me this much?"
"Just leave me alone." This kind of thought, I mean.
But those meddlesome people...
made me who I am now.
When you're forced into a corner,
you lose control of yourself,
not knowing if you need help now.
People just need...
to stretch their arms and say, "I need help."
But they end up harming themselves.
Don't make that mistake...
and accept the person offering to help.
Then, you'll be able to help someone later, Rao.
This is actually nothing.
There will be a lot more you have to go through.
So,
cheer up.
Yes.
This is just the beginning. Take a firm stand.
- We can do it. - Yes.
I'll gather myself up and take a firm stand.
Honestly, I'm not confident...
Can I call you if there's something unclear?
- No. - Sorry?
Kidding. Ask whatever.
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
It's raining.
I'll take you home.
That's okay. I can take a taxi.
- Please, allow me to do that. - If you want...
Okay.
Wear my jacket until we get in the car...
What are you waiting for?
I bet she never watches soap operas.
I'm coming!
Wait for me.
Wherever you go, if possible.
Are you okay?
What would make me worried?
I'm just worried about him.
Giving useful tips to Rao means...
you've already gone through all of those.
You've gone through a lot.
Thanks for the ride.
It must be tough to go back right away.
Hey, the guy!
Please come in!
To our house?
One second.
Why did you invite him? He is a busy man.
Just get some water for him.
Water? Okay.
You're the guy!
It's nice to meet you.
"The guy?"
Yes, you're the guy.
I've heard a lot about you from her.
Did she talk a lot about me?
When did I? Please!
You haven't had dinner yet, right?
- Yong Ju, set the table. - Dinner?
This is so sudden. I'm not sure if we have anything...
Please, let me. I'll help her set it.
Okay.
So,
what did she mention about me?
You need some water?
Please, zip it!
- Here. - Thanks.
Well,
she usually doesn't drink at home.
- One day... - Stop!
It wasn't anything.
It's not funny at all!
Let me help you.
It's okay. I'm used to doing it alone.
Then, let me dry the dishes, at least.
Would you?
Come on!
What did I say?
One day, I had a 38-degree fever.
So, I was wondering if I should go for a part-time job.
I will do it.
I hope...
you get along well with her.
I mean, you two spending ordinary days like today.
I've told this...
to no one yet.
I like her a lot.
That's why...
I'll be more friendly with her.
I see.
Thanks.
What the heck? When did I go to sleep?
Oh, my!
I hope he went back well.
The phone is turned off.
Transferring to voicemail.
I'm sorry. Because of me...
(Last night)
Her room is so empty.
It's very contrary to what she usually says.
What on earth happened to her?
- That. - Yes?
Over there.
The real sad thing about poverty is...
that it doesn't give you time to look for the things you like.
It prevents Yong Ju from living up to her name.
When did this happen?
Six years ago after I collapsed.
Hey!
Hey! What?
You can't lose consciousness. Hold on.
(Grandma)
Hey.
You're okay.
Everything will be okay.
Is this 911?
I don't know what made you decide to do this.
Find everything that poses a risk to you,
and protect yourself first.
That's how you can be kind to yourself.
I don't know how to thank you for this.
Well, if you don't mind,
would you give me your bank account number?
No. I just did what I was supposed to do.
(1 missed call)
What? She called me.
Grandma.
Grandma!
Grandma, what's wrong? Wake up, Grandma!
Grandma, what's wrong with you? Oh, no. Grandma.
Grandma, please wake up! What's wrong?
Grandma! Can you not hear me?
Grandma!
(911 Emergency Medical Services)
I was late.
Grandma, I'm sorry I came so late.
Grandma...
(Operating Room)
(Hwikyeong General Hospital)
For cerebral hemorrhages,
it's crucial to treat patients within the golden hour,
but she was brought here rather late.
She's bleeding more as we speak.
As you can read in the form, she may experience hemiplegia...
or speech impairment after the surgery.
(Signature)
She blames herself...
for what happened to me.
I told her countless times not to do that.
She came home late...
because she was busy saving someone's life.
I need to pay for the surgery and rehabilitation.
Right, I'll need a caregiver too.
How much does it cost to hire a caregiver?
It's quite pricey. So the monthly expenses...
My paycheck won't even be enough to cover everything.
For communications security. Sergeant Kim.
Wait. Should I call you by your name now?
Well, I just wanted to ask you...
about military discharges.
Gosh, no.
I'm just thinking about it for now.
I just had a few questions.
Then can I text you some questions I have?
Thank you. Okay.
You told me to protect myself.
I'll do...
whatever it takes to protect myself.
(Off to Germany for his studies, Discharged from the military)
So let's meet again one day.
("Everything I Love Will Make Me Cry")
(Chae Yong Ju's Memory Album)
(This must have been my go-to outfit even as a kid.)
What's so desperate this time around?
Why do you keep saying you're all right?
But you're trying way too hard.
If you keep suppressing them, it will become a habit.
Good job, doing that all on your own.
("Your Name, Youth" by Movning)
It was me who made you give up...
on living your life.
- Grandma. - Yes?
I don't...
regret my decision back then.
I feel awful for saying this to you.
But...
I decided not to regret it.
That's right.
Who cares about what happened in the past?
The past is the past.
If the past keeps dragging you down,
just grab it and kick it aside.
Why are you acting so timid? That's not very like you.
- I'll be off. - Don't be afraid.
You bet. I'm your granddaughter.
Why are they all standing outside?
Gosh, what do we do?
- I can't believe this happened. - My goodness.
- Right. - Seriously. Did someone go up?
- What? Oh, my. - No way. Why would anyone do that?
- Why would anyone go up there... - My goodness.
- so early in the morning? - Right.
- Hello. - My goodness.
- Hey. - What's going on?
They received a report...
regarding a distress situation from the mountain.
It rained so much last night.
And there must've been a landslide from the downpour.
Someone clueless must've gone up and gotten into an accident.
- My gosh. - Oh, my.
- There it goes. Good grief. - Really?
- Two ambulances? - There are two ambulances?
- Two? - I hope it's nothing serious.
One, two. This is the village chief.
I got a call from the fire department.
They received a report about a distress situation...
from the mountain.
It was a man's voice.
His phone got turned off in the middle of a call.
Everyone should check if their family is all right.
- A man's voice? - That's all.
- So his phone isn't working. - What?
- Everyone, check on your family. - What about Mr. Yoon?
Mr. Yoon? Oh, my.
Come to think of it, we didn't see him today.
No way.
He's probably sleeping.
I'm sure he's home.
- Has anyone seen him? - He must be home.
The phone is turned off.
- His phone is turned off. - Transferring to voicemail.
- No way. - There's no way.
- Right. - No way.
- My gosh. - He didn't answer his phone.
- Goodness. - Who would go to the mountain?
My gosh.
- Where's Mr. Yoon? - What?
- He's not here. - Where did he go?
He said he needed to sort out some things,
so he grabbed some camping tools and went out.
- He asked me to feed Photo. - Camping tools?
It can't be.
My gosh.
What?
Mr. Yoon!
Mr. Yoon Min Ju!
Darn it.
Where on earth is he?
What?
Is he...
Were you really camping here?
Hey.
"Hey?"
Did you know I looked everywhere for you?
The cut...
You're hurt.
How could you just disappear...
after leaving a note saying you're sorry?
I came here to see you, but there was a distress situation.
And you were nowhere to be seen.
All kinds of thoughts crossed my mind. Seriously.
Remember what I told you?
It wasn't about you. This was about me.
If I were to go back in time...
and relive the same situation all over again,
I would still save you.
I would save you, Mr. Yoon.
So don't avoid me.
Don't disappear like this.
I'm sorry for making you worry.
But...
I didn't disappear.
I needed time to think too.
I kept feeling responsible...
for what happened to your grandmother too.
But I needed time to think.
To figure out a way to be with you despite what happened...
instead of avoiding it.
Then you should have told me so.
You turned off your phone. And you only left a note...
I'm sorry about that too.
But how did you hurt your forehead? Are you okay?
I'm not okay! I'm not...
I'm not okay at all.
You see,
no one had ever asked me if I was okay.
And that had never been a problem for me.
But ever since I met you, you kept asking me if I was okay.
You made me question if I was really okay...
or not.
"I see. I'm not okay right now."
"I'm hurting right now."
I have these thoughts now.
Look what I've become because of you.
I will...
never leave you.
(Brewing Love)
You're giving the villagers the wrong idea.
- You said you would wait. - Yes, I'm waiting.
This is confusing. I'm shutting you out!
It's been a while, my dear ex-boyfriend.
"Ex-boyfriend?"
She looks especially beautiful today.
- What's your favorite dish? - Toasts.
I'd rather see the new product fail...
than see the Marketing Team succeed.
To make up for the time you spent not being yourself,
I'm going to find everything you like.