CHAPTER 32:
A VARIABLE CALLED NA DEUL-I
-How have you been?
-Good.
You seem to be doing well too.
I'm happy for you.
To tell the truth,
I was surprised to hear from you.
Pleased too.
You could have gotten in touch yourself.
Are you doing better now?
Yeah.
When I heard you had a surgery,
I was really worried.
And I couldn't get hold of you.
I'm sorry I didn't say anything.
I was in shock.
And I was really upset too.
I can't believe you majored in Education
and became a teacher.
It was so unexpected.
I was sure you'd stick with research.
Eui-ju?
What are you doing here?
EPISODE 10
Sir.
Oh, I was just doing some studying,
but it's time to go home.
Eui-ju.
Have you finally decided
to put some effort into your studies?
Yes.
What brought you here, Mr. Ha?
Is that Mr. Ga?
What do we have here?
My dear Mr. Ga, the standoffish robot,
is enjoying coffee with someone.
With a lady friend, no less.
Hang on a second.
By any chance…
You're Professor Na Deul-i, right?
Yes, that's me.
I knew it. I saw you on the news.
I was touched by the interview you gave
after winning the Fields Medal.
Oh, thank you.
Where are my manners?
It's nice to meet you.
I'm a colleague of Mr. Ga's.
My name is Ha E-den. It's such a pleasure.
Anyhow, how do you know Mr. Ga?
We're friends.
Friends. I see.
When a man and woman
meet in a cafe on the weekend,
it's a date 99% of the time, no?
Shall we get going?
-Yes.
-Okay.
You two look great together.
You make a great couple.
See you again soon.
-Oh, sure.
-Take care.
As for you, study hard!
If you want to become
as great as Professor Na.
Get home safely.
Hop on.
Thank you.
Hello.
My name is Yeo Eui-ju.
Mr. Ga is my homeroom teacher.
I see. Hello.
Wow, that's amazing.
I can't believe
you have a student of your own.
Were you at college with Mr. Ga?
No, we've been friends
since middle school.
I see. Middle school?
That's a long time.
You'd best get going.
About that thing I suggested.
You'll give it some thought?
I'm not sure.
Are you playing hard to get or what?
Get going already.
All right.
Until next time, Eui-ju.
Okay, goodbye.
Drive safe.
Mr. Ga, your friend
seems really nice.
She's pretty, and she seems really kind.
And she even won the Fields Medal.
That's so cool.
I wish I had a friend like that.
I bet she's super popular.
She must have a boyfriend, right?
Would it be difficult to find someone
when you're as perfect as her?
When you're good at everything,
people would always compare
your partner to you,
making them feel insecure.
What are you trying to say?
It's just
I was wondering what kind of guy
someone so amazing would date.
Why?
If you don't get more than 50 points
in the upcoming math exam,
I'm telling your parents about your novel
at our parent-teacher meeting.
Sorry?
Come on, that's not fair.
Sir, you won't really, will you?
Please tell me you won't. Come on.
Sir!
I'll try my best,
but 50 points in math is a tall order.
Sir, that thing your friend
was talking about just now.
What did she want you to think over?
It's not really any of your business.
Would it kill you to be nicer?
Don't forget my coke.
Just a moment, sir.
I'll be right back.
Hold up.
Don't go.
Wait for me, okay?
Got it.
Don't forget the factors
associated with constipation.
I hope you won't end up back in the ER.
It's not for me.
It's for my little brother.
You're a great sister.
What, getting blackmailed
into doing his bidding?
What does he have on you?
Only two people found out about my secret.
As usual, I was engrossed
in writing my novel…
and talking to others online.
Hey, I've got a random question.
What do you have our group chat saved as?
Beautiful Life. BL.
Real Estate Chat for me.
Because sometimes,
my hubby looks at my phone.
This is a rough draft
of something I'm working on.
The characters
are a young master and his servant.
Let me know what you think.
That's such a great character dynamic.
I don't get why your stuff
isn't more popular, Imuk.
It's such a shame.
Just imagine the beautiful young master
being heartbroken over the aloof servant.
That just shot chills down my spine.
I think
there's someone behind me.
Can it be a ghost?
It'd be better if it were.
If it's your parents, I'll pray for you.
Did you see anything?
Still, at least it wasn't my parents.
But I do have to keep buying him coke
whenever he wants it.
Why do you like it so much?
I'm not sure.
People like what they like.
I guess that's why you kept writing
despite bombing every time.
I always thought I'd hit it big
if I just kept on writing.
That's unfounded confidence.
If there were a basis for it,
that'd be a prophecy, not confidence.
I'll keep at it,
and I will get better.
Sir.
You know,
back when EBC's crew came by to shoot,
you didn't finish your answer
to my questions.
I'm curious why you decided
to become a teacher.
How was hanging out with your friend?
Good.
She's back for the first time in years
and being feted
for winning the Fields Medal.
And yet, she took the time
to come to Jeonju to see you.
Why would she do that?
This wasn't exactly a reunion
with your old Olympiad team.
She came to see just you.
No one else but you.
Why is that?
Did you share a warm and precious memory
from when you were both young?
Did they use to date?
That's the only explanation.
When it comes to men and women,
it's all about the chemistry.
There needs to be that spark
for you to want to see that person again
after years have passed.
-You know what I'm saying?
-True that.
Mind your own business.
Looks like you're right.
Dude!
I thought all you ever did was study.
My guess is that
Woo-su and this girl Deul-i
hit it off at the Olympiad,
started dating, and then broke up.
-No way.
-Hear me out.
That must be why he dropped out.
The thought of seeing his ex-girlfriend
pained his heart too much.
-Been there.
-Just the thought
upset him so much
that he couldn't face it.
Even our cold-hearted Woo-su
once felt the flicker of true love.
Or something like that.
I'm so proud of him.
Still, he wouldn't just quit.
Of course, he would.
Why? Because they were rivals.
Woo-su would have said,
"I'll pull out
so you can reach for the stars."
Or some such.
Only one of them could win.
You're saying Woo-su
gave up on math for a girl?
Well, there was another reason as well.
What?
That thing.
His phobia of being filmed.
He feared finishing first.
"Wow, that's amazing."
"I can't believe
you have a student of your own."
What's so amazing about that?
Is it really so amazing
for a teacher to have students?
Until next time, Eui-ju.
"Next time"?
Sure.
Maybe we will meet again.
WE WERE FRIENDS, EPISODE 7
Who are you?
Me?
I'm the Chairwoman's secretary, Na Ran-i.
As long as she pays me,
I take care of all her dirty work.
She wants me to get you away from Si-on.
As much as I appreciate your pretty face…
This is it for you.
No. Don't do it!
Yoon!
How did you find me?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
SI-ON LOWERED HIMSELF TO MEET YOON'S EYES
Let's get out of here.
SO CLOSE AND SO INTENSE,
HIS GAZE MADE YOON'S HEART RACE
JUST THEN, RAN-I CALLED OUT
How amusing.
Let's see how long you can keep this up.
RAN-I'S COMMENT
PROVOKED YOON'S WILDER NATURE
Just a moment.
I refuse to be in anyone's debt.
No!
-Don't!
-Let it…
YOON BID HER FAREWELL
IT WAS FOR SI-ON, OF ALL PEOPLE
CHAPTER 33:
SOMETHING UTTERLY USELESS
-Eun Ha-su.
-Here.
-Oh A-rin.
-Choi Yu-mi.
-Here.
-Yeo Eui-ju.
-Choi Go-ya.
-Here.
Choi Ji-a.
-Hong Su-min.
-Here.
-Jeon Chae-won.
-Im Su-yeon.
-Here.
-Lee Eun-ji.
-Choi Hye-jeong.
-Here.
I hope you're all ready for class.
-I smell alcohol.
-What on earth?
-It's definitely alcohol.
-What's this?
Quiet.
Who's on cleaning duty today?
Me, sir.
-Eui-ju.
-Yes, sir?
-Clean up again.
-Yes, sir.
-Let's air out the room. Open the windows.
-But it's cold.
Ji-a, go to the nurse's office.
Morning to you too.
Hey!
Mr. Ga.
She's in your class, right?
Are you aware she's come to school drunk?
Goodness me.
How can a student come to school
reeking of alcohol?
You're the one who wasn't in her uniform
when the EBC crew was here filming.
Are you taking school seriously?
Ms. Kim, let me get back to you
after hearing Ji-a's side of the story.
Mr. Ga.
This student is drunk.
What is there to understand?
Step out for a moment.
I don't want to butt heads
with you over nothing.
I finally got rid of that knot yesterday,
and I'm starting to tense up again.
Ji-a's background differs somewhat
from that of other students.
She has no parental support.
She's staying at a youth shelter
and must earn a living herself.
Despite that,
she still has a strong desire to learn.
Really?
That's great.
Then, she'll surely do well
at another school.
She might seem tough,
but she's still just a child.
As her homeroom teacher,
I'd like to personally make sure
she turns her life around.
Please allow me that opportunity.
Mr. Ga.
Do you recall our school motto?
It's "Aim for the Elite."
I can't seem to imagine her career choices
or her life goals of any kind
being anywhere near that ideal.
In other words,
she's not a good fit for this school.
You may leave.
Does he think he's a crusader for justice?
Of all the students to stick up for,
he chose the one who showed up drunk.
How obnoxious.
Would you believe
he's friends with Na Deul-i?
Who is Na Deul-i?
Don't you know, Aunt Young-hee?
She's the Fields Medal winner.
Apparently, they're friends.
What?
You're unbelievable.
Why are you only mentioning this now?
When else did I have the chance?
Ji-a.
Why did you do it?
It's wrong for a student
to come to school drunk.
Anyone can make a mistake.
It's what's next that's important.
Write an essay stating what you did wrong
and what you're going to do about it.
I will show it to the principal.
Yes, sir.
I'll get you a lighter punishment,
so be sure to wear your uniform
and don't skip class
or get into any trouble.
Yes, sir.
-That's for sure.
-I can't take it.
Eui-ju, over here!
Eui-ju, quickly!
-I don't know.
-This is so good.
-Try it. It's incredible.
-Let's see.
Where are you off to, Go-ya?
Can I sit here?
Sit down, Eui-ju.
Okay.
The food is so good today!
Eat up. It's delish.
Can I have a minute, Go-ya?
Go-ya, where are you going?
-I have huge news.
-What is it?
Young-hee wanted to expel Ji-a,
but Mr. Ga stopped her.
-Really?
-That's amazing.
Seems like it's on hold.
Gosh. How did he manage that?
He must have some kind of leverage.
When are you going to make up with Go-ya?
I have to say everything twice.
It sucks.
Is Go-ya still refusing to talk to you?
Yeah.
What did you guys argue about, anyway?
Argue?
We didn't argue.
-What is it?
-Oh, please.
Just tell us.
I have a research idea
I'd like to work on with you.
You were always
the most interesting person to talk to.
I don't know how long it will take,
but I really want to work with you
on the topology
of algebraic curves and surfaces.
Why that topic?
I'm not sure. It just drew me in.
I was looking
for something utterly useless.
Remember that Hardy quote?
"No discovery of mine has made,
or is likely to make,
directly or indirectly,
for good or ill,
the least difference
to the amenity of the world."
"I have
-never done anything useful."
-"…never done anything useful."
That's my next goal.
Accomplishing something utterly useless.
Where are you going?
For a walk.
I'll go with you.
I need to walk off my dinner.
Are you still getting bad headaches?
Sometimes.
Shouldn't you see a doctor?
It's not that bad.
Just go anyway.
There's no harm in getting checked out.
Fine. I'll go.
No empty promises, all right?
Make sure you go.
Okay.
Get me a coke on your way home.
I'm already home.
I'm in my room.
Can I get it tomorrow instead?
Mom!
I have something to tell you.
Hey, Eui-do!
Okay, Eui-do. I get it, all right?
I'll go now.
About that proposal
from your friend Deul-i.
What do you think?
Be honest.
I don't know. I'm not interested.
Liar.
You answered too quickly
like you'd rehearsed it.
I wish you'd do what you really want to.
So seize this opportunity
and go to the US.
Go do the research you want to do
before it's too late.
Are you going to the US?
It's late. Go home.
I don't want to.
To tell the truth, I…
I told you
I never wanted to see you again.
What am I going to do now?
How come you're here?
Sir! What do we do?
Why isn't she answering?
Why isn't she even checking?
-Hurry up and leave.
-Sir!
I see you still haven't figured me out.
"You're going down for real then."
So cool.
He's so cool.
Tell him how you feel.
To show him how serious you are,
look him in the eye.
-I…
-For at least three seconds.
Look him in the eye for three seconds.
Subtitle: Paul Carver