Is it okay if I spend the night here?
Are you picking me up?
I really came here to see you.
We didn’t know you’re here.
I’m Amethyst, by the way. I don’t think we’ve met yet.
Kalix.
Do you still think about our first night together?
What am I to you, Kalix?
Luna. It means moon.
You’ll remember me everytime you look at the moon.
Like a curse.
More like a tattoo in my brain.
The resthouse in Tagaytay.
That’s right, Architect Valeria.
I’m not here as your Legal Counsel, but as your client.
Yes, Architect Valeria.
We have other great architects in the firm.
Maybe Architect Ynares can handle–
Luna, I suggest you review the project first,
before you make a decision.
And I want you to discuss the details with Attorney Martinez.
As far as I’m concerned, this project is very profitable.
I’m free tomorrow at 5 PM.
What do you think, Luna?
I’ll bring my Real Estate Lawyer to the meeting.
We’re not gonna be alone together if that’s what you’re hesitating about.
No, that’s not the problem.
I have a meeting tomorrow until 6 PM so I can’t, I’m sorry.
Okay, let’s set a meeting at a later date.
My schedule for this month is a bit tight.
But we have other architects that can–
How about 7 PM tomorrow?
After your last meeting.
Are you gonna be free by that time, Architect?
Yes–
I’ll be available at 7 PM.
Great!
Great, great.
So, everything’s settled then?
- Thank you, sir. - All right, thank you!
Thank you, Architect!
I’ll see you tomorrow then.
I’m sorry, I’m late.
And so is your lawyer.
My time is valuable, Attorney Martinez.
I’m sorry.
It’s not gonna happen again.
I’ll follow up on him.
He’s here.
He’s just parking.
Okay.
So Luna–
I mean, uh– Architect Valeria.
About the project,
as you know this is the family property of–
Attorney Martinez,
I think it would be better if we wait for your lawyer
so that we won’t have to discuss it again.
Where is he, by the way?
I thought he’s just parking?
If we’re going to work together, punctuality and honesty are important.
Especially in our line of work.
I know.
I’m sorry, again.
Architect!
Adonis, wh-what are you doing here?
Long time no see, Architect.
How are you?
Architect Valeria,
he’s my Real Estate Lawyer.
Attorney Figueroa, at your service.
You?
Are you kidding me?
First, you got a job in our firm out of all the firms in Manila.
Then, you proposed a project to my dad.
And, you want to hire me, as your architect?
What are you doing, Kalix?
I can’t do this.
- I shouldn’t be doing this. - Architect, wait.
Architect, please let me explain.
Explain what?
That we really want to hire you for this project.
And you even brought Adonis?
Am I a joke to you?
No. I don’t–
What are you up to, Kalix? What’s this? What are you doing?
This isn’t some joke. It’s a job offer.
I really want you as my architect.
Seriously,
why do you want me to be your architect?
Because you’re the most competent and innovative architect to get this job done.
I’ve seen your past works.
And I think your designs match my preferences.
And with that being said–
I’m giving you full creative freedom.
And if you look at page 6, a generous fee as well.
So?
Thirty percent?
Financing won’t be a problem.
We just have to iron out some details but–
I think we’re good after that.
What do you think?
I’ll just refer you to our other architects.
It just won’t work out with the both of us.
For this big of a project,
the client and the architect must be on the same page.
I think the two of us–
we won’t get along.
Not like that, Kalix.
Like this, see? Clink! There you go!
One, two, three, clink!
Cute!
So cute.
You really get along, huh?
Lucky for you, he agreed to do that couple challenge video.
Oh jeez,
I had to force him but I’m glad he agreed.
Damn, you guys are so cringey.
You’re too much, Luna.
Come on.
You deserve this happiness, lovebirds.
Kalix, you better watch out if you make Luna cry.
Oh, don’t you dare.
I will not hurt Luna.
I promise.
These two are too sweet.
He’s head over heels for me.
So are you.
Hey, enough about you! Let’s move on.
Let’s talk about halloween break. What are your plans?
‘Cause we’re going to our hometown.
I don’t know yet. How about you, Via?
Well, I have no plans yet,
maybe just stay home and study or maybe visit the cemetery.
I'm not sure.
How about you, Yanna?
Me?
I don't know.
Wherever the hotties are, I’ll be there!
You’re crazy.
Luna, Kalix, what about you guys?
- We’re going to– - We’re going to–
- Oh! - Wow!
They’re in sync.
They are really a match.
Go, tell them.
We’re going to Boracay.
What?
Boracay?
Show-off!
Are you two going alone?
Yes.
Our first couple trip.
But seriously,
if you two get married five to ten years from now,
I promise we’d be the sexiest and prettiest bridesmaids ever!
Right?
- So true, I agree. - Right!
No pressure at all.
You know what Ke, I kinda feel pressured.
I’m confident that Kalix and I
are ready for our first trip together.
The itinerary is prepared,
I’ve listed the restaurants we’re gonna eat at as well
but I don’t know, I'm worried.
I also feel nervous.
It can’t be helped when you’re in love, right?
There’s a ton of emotions like nervousness, fear, doubts.
But it all goes away when they make you feel loved.
I do feel that assurance from Kalix.
But what if we have something we don’t like about each other?
- What if– - What if you stop overthinking?
What if you just let your love flow its own way?
Let your relationship fly and grow naturally.
Damn, I’m so smart!
Just know that there is a reason why the universe brought you two together.
Girl, is that you?
You’re giving such good advice,
I think you’re ready to have a boyfriend.
Just enjoy your Boracay trip.
I know you’ll manage ‘cause you’re such a flirt.
You bitch!
Would you look at this?
Don’t you have anything better?
Don’t you have something that reveals more skin?
Well, do you?
I won’t really need more of that, you know.
I’ll just wear my bikini and watch Kalix’s jaw drop.
Oh, I like that.
Just remember, what happens in Boracay–
- stays in Boracay! - Stays in Boracay!
Please excuse me. My boyfriend is calling.
Hi, Kalix!
Hey! I just called to say good night.
I’m still not used to this.
Get used to it,
you’re gonna hear it for the rest of your life anyway.
Too cheesy.
By the way,
have you prepared your toiletries and stuff?
Yes, look here.
I have my clothes here and my toiletries as well.
How about you, you good?
Yes. I’ve prepared it all including our boarding pass and our itinerary.
Thanks, by the way, for paying for our flight.
Not a problem. I still have savings from my school allowance.
Thank you for booking the hotel.
What did your dad say about it?
I told them about it since I don’t want them to be surprised
to see the credit card bill.
I also told them...
that I’ll be with my friends.
So he allowed me to go.
You naughty girl.
They won’t allow me to go if they knew that it’s just the two of us.
I can’t wait to have you alone.
Why, what are you going to do?
What lovers do when they’re alone.
Stop it!
We should be conservative, you know?
Don't be late. Let's go early to the airport.
Someone's really excited!
Of course.
I think this is gonna be the best trip ever!
Wow!
Our room is so beautiful and so spacious too.
This bed feels so comfortable.
Maybe we should just nap first and enjoy it.
Huh?
We should make the most out of the beach while it’s still sunny.
We have a lot of activities to do, so let’s go!
Thank you.
Thank you? For what?
For being here
and making me happy.
I’m so lucky to have you.
Glad you know.
Just kidding.
I feel the same way.
So let’s go!
Come on!
Okay…
So you still don't want to get up?
Well,
are you ready now?
How’s this?
You look stunning.
Really?
Don’t you think it’s revealing?
No.
You can wear whatever you want
as long as you’re comfortable.
Whatever makes you happy and pretty.
Come on!
I’m ready.
I think I’m ready to go to the beach.
Let's just put sunblock and go sunbathing there.
Kalix, can you put some sunblock on me?
On my back.
Yes.
Okay.
All done?
Uhm–
Yes, yes.
Okay.
Thank you.
Oh, you wanna eat?
- Here. - Yes.
It’s good.
We look so cute here.
Hashtag LuKal in Boracay!
I’m cuter though.
Wow!
So you know how to brag now?
It’s true though.
You are cute.
You know what?
Boracay is so beautiful.
According to my research–
this is consistent as one of the top beaches in the world.
It’s true.
Actually this is my first time here
so I’m really having fun.
I’ve been here a couple of times but
I don’t know why.
It’s more beautiful now.
I think you’re just blinded by love.
And you’re with someone as pretty as me.
My research said, top one most beautiful girl in the world.
You’re really learning how to hit those pickup lines, huh?
What do you expect?
I’m learning from the best.
You want me to shower you?
With all my love!
Silly you.
You’re so hot.
We should just go scuba diving.
We can also try parasailing,
island hopping…
Let’s make the most of this.
We’ve still got time.
Maybe we can just chill here for a bit.
We can try some local coffee shops.
And…
just enjoy the beach.
Okay.
I just don’t want to waste our time here.
We have plenty of time tomorrow.
Okay.
How about this? Let’s have dinner at the fusion restaurant.
I heard its owners are Moroccan and Italian.
They say it’s really good.
That sounds good but I’m craving seafood tonight.
They serve the best scallops here.
Would that be okay?
Okay.
Let’s just eat at the fusion restaurant tomorrow, okay?
Hello?
I’m in Boracay but–
yes, I can do it tonight.
No, it’s fine.
I’ll just take care of it and I will email you once it’s done.
Okay?
All right.
Who was that?
My blockmate.
Luna, can we just go back to our room?
I have to do something.
Huh?
I thought we're going to watch the sunset?
Yes, but–
we still have two hours and a half.
I’ll be done by then.
I promise.
Okay.
- Okay? - Yes.
Yes?
All right.
Come on.
Are you done?
It’s been two hours.
We’re not in a staycation,
so I wouldn’t want to miss the sunset.
Around ten pages more.
Kalix?
Maybe you can finish that later?
Please?
You know I’m all for supporting your studies and school work.
I promise it will just only take thirty minutes more.
Tops!
Thirty more minutes?
Yes, is that okay?
Okay, sure.
It’s been thirty minutes.
You done?
Yes!
Yay!
Hold on.
Yes.
I just received it right now.
Okay, I’ll revise all of it.
I’ll send it asap.
Luna, I’m sorry. I just need another thirty more minutes.
I thought it was just going to be quick?
Yes, but
our groupmate made a mistake
and we have to revise all of it.
Why are you doing it?
He can’t be reached through calls or anything else.
What about our sunset drinks later?
I’ve even reserved a table at the restaurant you like.
Well,
there’s gonna be another sunset tomorrow, right?
That’s not the point.
Come on.
I promise it will only take thirty more minutes.
And then we can go out for dinner, okay?
Are we good?
Whatever.
Miss Valeria?
Hi!
How are you?
I can’t believe I’d see you— here in Boracay.
I know.
Last time I saw you was during your first semester.
Ah, yes ma'am.
That was actually my favorite class.
Theory of Architecture 1.
Yes and you were killing it!
Just call me Amina.
All right then, Amina.
How’ve you been? Do you still teach?
No, I don’t.
I’m now focusing on my architecture job here in Boracay.
And–
OMG! Congratulations! Since when?
Three months ago.
How about you, how are you? Are you alone?
My companion’s busy in the hotel so I decided to go out by myself.
If you want, you can join us.
Let’s eat? My treat.
I’ll introduce you to my husband.
He’s on his way here.
Sure.
Luna!
It’s time for dinner.
Luna?
Luna, where are you?
I’m sorry if we missed the sunset. I’ll make it up to you.
Send a reply, Luna.
I’m impressed with your maturity.
Is it wrong for me to feel angry?
I mean,
it’s our first vacation together.
Can’t he just set aside his studies for just one day?
I’m not saying it’s not valid.
I just think that,
you can mind how you respond or compromise for now, you know?
Hello, ma’am!
- Hi! - Your table’s ready, ma’am.
All right.
- The food’s ready. - Looks good.
Let’s go ahead and enjoy the food.
Wow! Yummy.
Hi, babe.
Hi!
Babe, I want you to meet Luna.
She’s my former student in Architecture School.
One of the brightest, I must say.
Don't mention it.
Hi Luna, very nice to meet you.
Are you traveling solo?
She pretends to be.
Yes, I do have to say, this is absolutely delicious.
Mina really knows how to put a smile on my face.
It’s all about being attentive to details.
I envy you.
Come on, Luna!
You brought this to yourself.
Anyway, taste it.
You’ll seriously forget all your problems.
Are you avoiding someone?
Babe, they’re having a lover’s quarrel.
How cute!
Wait, I have a question.
Are you taking this guy seriously?
Do you really love him?
Yes.
If I can give you one piece of unsolicited advice,
he clearly wants to talk to you.
Just talk to him.
Don’t ruin the vacation that you’re having now over your feelings.
But he was the one that–
Does he even know that you’re mad?
You know, Luna…
buildings and relationships have a lot in common.
They both need a solid foundation to be strong.
Communication is key to building a solid relationship.
Don’t expect your partner to
know everything that goes through your mind.
I’ll have to agree with that.
I mean, Mina and I have been together for fifteen years
but I still haven’t figured out her mood swings.
Bastard!
Don’t be silly!
See? But nonetheless,
I always look to understand her because I love her.
Luna
don’t dwell on negative feelings.
Come on, just call him.
Luna!
Hello, Kalix?
Luna! Thank god, where are you?
Luna, I’m so sorry.
I know I’ve been insensitive.
I apologize.
- I’ve been looking for you. - Where are you?
I walked from station one to station three.
Looking around for you.
Kalix, I’m here at station three.
I’ll text you the location, okay?
I’ll be waiting.
All right, I’ll see you there.
Bye.
Kalix!
Luna!
I’m so sorry.
I’m so sorry, it’s my fault.
I should’ve been a better boyfriend.
I’m sorry, too.
I admit, I was really hurt.
But I shouldn’t have walked out on you.
I should have talked to you first.
I’m sorry.
Oh.
Amina, I’m sorry.
It’s okay.
We’re just happy that you two are okay.
Yes.
By the way— Amina, Gil, this is Kalix my boyfriend.
Hi.
I was Luna’s Architecture Professor.
Hey bro, I’m Gil.
Good evening.
I got lucky
I bump into her and kept me company.
Yes.
Thank you so much!
Would you like to join us for dinner?
No, it’s okay.
We already ate dinner
- and we have to go home already. - Yes.
It’s nice meeting you, though.
Yes, enjoy the night.
- Please take care of Luna. - I will.
Luna, keep in touch.
I shall see you soon.
You two enjoy the night, okay?
- Bye. - Thank you!
- Have a good night. - Bye.
Thank you.
Sir, table for two please!
Luna.
I’m so sorry, Luna—
for today.
I realized I made you feel unappreciated.
We came here to spend quality time and
I should have not prioritized things that I could have done later.
I’m sorry.
I’m sorry, too.
I admit, I was wrong, too.
I should have communicated with you first
instead of walking out on you.
I just felt that
I was rejected and ignored.
I’m sorry.
My ex-boyfriend made me feel that.
Like my needs and opinions weren’t necessary.
I’m sorry.
I’m really sorry, I made you feel that way.
I promise,
I will listen to your needs more.
I don’t wanna do anything to hurt you.
Okay?
I think, I’m not…
hungry anymore.
Should we go back to our room?
Should we?
Don’t put–
What?
Nothing.
Is that it?
Calm down, tigress.
Cheers!
Good morning, Ke!
Good morning! You’re up early.
I was just in the mood to get up early.
You know, carpe that diem.
Shit! It’s good to be alive.
You still have jitters from your vacation with Kalix.
You’re right.
You know what they say?
The first couple trip makes or breaks the relationship.
We sealed the deal.
We were level six before, now we’re at level eight.
Just because of that trip.
You should join us next time,
it would be more fun.
Sure.
Did you come home last night, Ke?
Of course.
How come I didn’t see you?
You might have been asleep already.
I came home around 1 AM.
But I fell asleep around 4 AM.
I just finished some plates and–
I edited our video.
Maybe it was past 4 AM. I'm not really sure.
I was too sleepy.
So, where were you last night anyway?
A-At home, did some laundry and got some stuff.
I think you’re hiding something from me.
Oh! I have something to tell you.
Christmas fest is coming. You better be there, okay?
- Yes. - Let’s invite the others.
I’ll bring Kalix.
Sure, that would be fun.
I gotta go, I need to buy some art supplies.
Oh, Ke!
- Ouch. - I’m sorry! What’s wrong?
Nothing, just a cramp.
Oh… Is it okay if you buy me a tech pen?
Sure.
Damn it!
It’s still early but the concert ground's already full.
I love all the bands playing tonight!
Actually, I’m not surprised. The line-up’s really good.
Before we go guys, I just want to congratulate all of us
for surviving the first semester!
- I’m so proud of us! - Well…
- I'll just get my bag. - By the way, where’s Ke?
She said she’s coming.
I noticed that she hasn’t been hanging out with us lately.
What’s up with that?
I think she has a boyfriend already, that’s why.
Boyfriend? Who?
She hasn’t said anything to us. Do you have an idea?
No idea.
But it’s weird ‘cause she’s been quite distant to me lately.
I even set up a bonding session but she ditched me.
Maybe she’s just busy.
Oh, you don't know?
- What? - She wasn’t able to pass her plates for finals.
The professor was lenient but gave deductions.
Luckily, her previous grades were high so it wasn’t affected that much.
You didn’t know?
Please open the door, Luna. I'll just retouch her makeup.
Sure, I think it's Ke.
Hi!
Who’s that?
This is Miguel, my boyfriend.
Oh.
Since when?
Two months ago.
Hi Miguel, I’m Sam.
This is everyone.
Everyone, say hello to Miguel.
What's up?
- Water? - Yes.
Babe, no ice.
What are you doing here?
Talk to your cousin-in-law!
- Crazy. - I just can’t.
I have a bad feeling about that guy.
Call me a critic, but he’s definitely a sketchy creep.
Hey, Yanna!
- It’s true. - Come on.
Isn’t he—
Isn’t he that guy from PolSci?
- Oh, yes. - Right?
The mayor’s son.
That mayor has a lot of history with corruption.
Ugh!
Are you sure?
Yes, you can easily search for it.
Why would Ke choose someone like him?
Let her be!
Let’s just talk to her later.
Okay?
Girls, girls!
I think he’s about to leave.
Just relax, okay?
Girls, Miguel’s leaving. He needs to be somewhere.
Yes, I’ll go ahead.
Ke, what was that?
What do you mean about that, Yanna?
He’s my boyfriend. What the heck?
What’s up with your reactions earlier? So embarrassing.
How could you treat someone like that?
Ke.
We were just surprised.
Right.
You guys have been together for two months but we’ve never heard of him.
Even Luna had no idea.
I just didn’t know how to tell you.
What?
What do you mean?
It’s so easy to say, “Luna, I have a boyfriend now.”
We always talk, right?
You have no right to tell me what’s easy and what's not.
Girls, wait. We need to calm down.
Wait a minute, what’s with the attitude?
We’re just worried about you.
I should ask you the same thing.
What’s happening? Why are you all ganging up on me? On us?
Look at you, all lined up.
- What? You’ll each have a piece with me? - Ganging up–
Ke, of course not!
We’re not ganging up on you, we’re here for you.
Luna’s right. We’re all just worried about you.
Seriously?
It doesn’t seem like worrying if you’re all judging me.
Ke, we’re not judging anyone here.
We just want to understand why you had to hide him from us?
Is there any reason?
You should have introduced him to us earlier, Ke.
Then we wouldn't be reacting this way.
Not like how it is now, we're all in shock.
Is that all?
Well, I just introduced Miguel. Are we good?
All good? Any more issues?
The problem is I don’t like him.
I have a bad feeling about that guy. You better be careful.
Yanna…
Wow!
You just met him and you already have a lot of bad things to say.
So you are being judgmental.
I never said anything about your men, Yanna.
- What did you just say? - Hey!
- Yanna! - Hey!
- I said, - Calm down.
you never heard me say anything about any of your men.
You better watch your mouth!
Ke, Ke!
- What? - Stop it!
What the hell?!
Why are you stopping me when I say something?
But if it’s you, it’s okay?
Ke, it’s not like that. Come on, calm down.
You shouldn’t have let Miguel feel that he's not welcome.
If you’re all mad at me, take it on me instead.
Girls, please. Let’s all calm down.
Am I not allowed to have a love life but you all can?
That’s just unfair.
When Kalix was introduced, you didn’t react this way.
Don’t you dare involve Kalix in this conversation.
You know what I mean, Luna!
Ke, we’re not enemies here. We are your friends.
Come on.
Friends?
I don’t think so.
I don't feel that way anymore.
Let her be. Just let her be.
- Hey, Luna. - Kalix, how's Kio’s Christmas party?
Well,
I’m about to go there. Why?
Can we meet after the Christmas party?
I just need a breather.
Okay. See you!
It’s so annoying.
I don't understand what's happening to Ke.
It seems like she’s hiding something.
I can feel it, she’s my bestfriend.
Maybe she just needs time.
I’m sure she’ll tell you everything once she’s ready.
I know but
I can’t help but worry, Kalix.
I know there’s a problem.
Yes, I understand but you can’t force things out of her.
This is all new to me and Ke.
We rarely fight and disagree.
She even walked out on us earlier.
Everything will be fine, I’m sure of that.
You and Kierra are like siblings.
It’s normal for siblings to fight.
At the end of the day, though,
you guys still love and care for each other.
You’re right.
You’re not angry or pissed off at her.
You’re just being protective
and you always protect the people you love, right?
We protect the people we love.
Everything will be fine.
Don’t worry.
I know we’re just starting out and we haven’t had a big fight.
But if we do,
let’s talk about it, please?
Let’s talk about the problem.
We should always fix it.
Promise?
Of course, I promise.
It’s for sure that we’re gonna have our own fights and arguments but,
I won’t walk away.
I won’t give up on us.
I promise.
Except if you cheat on me, though.
If you do, you’re dead. I’ll never forgive you.
I will never do that.
You wanna know why?
Why?
‘Cause I never wanna lose you.
I love you, Luna.
I love you in ways I didn’t even know I could.
I love you.
I love you, Kalix.
I love you so, so, much!
We won’t get along?
I’m already giving you full creative freedom.
That’s not the problem, Kalix.
- Then what’s the problem? - You really wanna know?
I don’t want to work with you.
I can’t work with people who don’t value their principles.
And I just realized that…
I hate you.
Really?!
We'll be together for Christmas in New York?
I still can't believe it!
Ah.
So, he’ll be in New York, too?
Kalix and I will meet there.
By the way, I’ve already introduced him to Dad.
Wow! I never realized
you were that serious.
Of course, this is for long-term.
I already met your parents,
and I think it’s time for you to meet mine.
No offense, dear, okay?
I just think that Kalix
had better grades last year when he was with his ex-girlfriend, Amethyst.