(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 33=
(Zhaomu Pavilion)
You're awake.
Leave me.
After all your scheming,
seeing me like this,
you must be quite pleased.
How could that be?
I'm only worried about you.
After the punishment,
you lost half your spirit power
and fell unconscious.
I cared for you the whole time.
I'm not so weak
as to need anyone's care.
When I opened the wilds in North Abyss,
evil spirits often attacked.
To protect those spirit soldiers
breaking the land,
I devised a secret Zone.
Your spirit power is weak now.
So, I placed this Zone
around this bedchamber
to keep you safe.
Simu,
don't you love your rest days most?
This is the perfect chance
for you to rest well.
With your spirit power as it is,
you can't leave this bedchamber.
What do you want?
What do I want?
Haven't you always known?
Everything I've done
was for you.
I've even become
like this because of you.
Don't use me as your excuse.
Do you still recall the moment
I gave you my vital gate?
Back then, I once thought
that if you said yes,
I would vow to serve you forever.
But my true heart
was cast aside like worn shoes.
Luckily, now,
everything can begin anew.
From now on,
everything here belongs
only to the two of us.
No matter what happens,
I will always stay by your side.
We have all the time we need.
I will wait
until the day you love me.
Simu, I know
you never wanted
to be the Sovereign.
I can help you.
I will be the Sovereign.
You'll be my Queen.
Let us share the Void.
I know what you need is company.
I can spend all eternity
by your side.
We are
a match made in heaven.
As I told you,
I will never hand the Void
to someone I can't stand.
The former Sovereign shaped you
too deeply.
I don't blame you.
His laws have bound you fast.
All you do is favor mortals.
You even punished yourself.
What is so great about mortals?
They are small and fragile;
their lives are fleeting.
Spirits stand
above all beings.
Simu,
from now on, your world has only me.
Every day, I'll bring you
some amusing little things.
Wait for my return.
And one more thing.
I must remind you.
Don't try to restore your spirit power.
Under this restriction,
your spirit power stays at its lowest.
No matter how much you recover,
this formation will drain it away.
And this formation
will only grow stronger.
Your Lordship, you're finally here.
Everyone's been waiting.
Since everyone is here,
let the morning assembly begin.
Now that you oversee
all affairs of the Void.
I have questions
about the spirit stones.
You do?
Let me hear it.
This concerns the expenses you reported
to Her Grace
about a North Abyss project.
After making inquiries, we found
the income and outgoings
vastly differ
from the reported accounts.
I found as well
that in recent years,
when you were in charge,
large sums went missing.
Afterward,
the same amount
was moved into your private name.
Someone is setting me up.
Many have submitted reports.
There must be more to this.
I have reported this to Her Grace.
Her Grace decreed
to remove Jiang Ai
from overseeing the Void affairs
and to investigate her corruption.
Also,
Her Grace will enter seclusion
for five years.
From this day forth,
I shall assume full authority
over the Void.
Why would Her Grace
enter seclusion for five years?
Guards!
Seize the Left Hand.
Yes!
I am the Void's Left Hand.
Without Her Grace's order,
who dares lay a hand on me?
Jiang Ai,
are you defying
Her Grace's oral decree?
Her Grace declared in public
that I'd govern the Void for her.
Everyone here heard it.
Where did your oral decree
come from?
Who can vouch for it?
Her Grace
told me so herself.
I'm the Left Hand.
If I'm to be seized
or investigated,
Her Grace must give a clear order.
Her Grace has ordered
that none may disturb her in seclusion.
Is that Her Grace's order
or the Right Hand's order?
Yan Ke,
you've gone this far.
You want to seize the Void,
but it won't come so easily.
Simu,
haven't I told you before?
Don't try to restore your spirit power.
Why are you so disobedient?
Why not lie down
and have some rest?
I'm fine.
Simu,
I gathered these kites from the Mortal World.
Each one is ingenious.
Do you like them?
I had the string
specially made.
It's made of gold silkworm thread.
Strong and durable.
It won't snap.
When I look at these kites,
I find them most pleasing.
A kite is held fast by its string,
so it can never truly
get away.
Isn't that nice?
Only with ties can you
have a place to return to.
From now on, I'll be your tie
and your place to return to.
Do you find this amusing?
Of course.
As long as I see you every day,
it all feels amusing to me.
Don't you like the Mortal World?
Every day,
I'll bring you something new.
Soon,
this place will be filled
with memories that belong to us alone.
Simu,
do you still remember?
After you became the Sovereign,
I personally built
this bedchamber for us.
Lamps lit in the night sky,
beneath the full moon high above,
this is our home,
just as its name promises,
Zhaomu Pavilion.
We'll always be together
and never be parted.
We are no longer ruler and subject,
nor are we merely friends.
We are each other's only
and forever companions.
Don't even dream about it.
Whether it's a dream
or a desperate plea,
don't you ever think of leaving my side.
I have exhausted every possible way
to love you.
I have even offered you my heart,
yet you refuse it utterly.
Then I'd rather you hate me
and blame me
than neglect me.
Since the things I gave you before
were never to your liking,
I will find you something else.
Once you become the Sovereign,
what will you make of the Void?
Spirits are born of obsession.
They should be free.
Why should they be bound
by all those rules and limits?
In the Void that I rule,
spirits should live as they please.
What does that even mean?
The strong endure and follow desire.
First, the curfew must be abolished.
Oh, right.
I forgot to tell you.
Your Left Hand
is already all alone.
No one obeys her anymore.
Don't gloat just yet.
If you could get
what you want so easily,
she would not be Jiang Ai.
Simu,
at a time like this,
stop putting on a brave front.
The time has come.
I should go clean up the mess.
Wait for my return.
The stronger one lives.
That is how spirits should be.
That's right.
The Right Hand should be Sovereign.
The Golden-wall Decrees
should be destroyed asap.
How did this happen?
The Void is in chaos.
My Lord,
the Xuling Temple is empty.
There's nothing left.
Jiang Ai, that sly old fox.
Send more men across all of the Void.
We must bring her back.
- Yes.
Bai Sanxing,
it really is you.
I'll kill you.
I'm going to kill you.
♪In silence, I gaze at you♪
♪My hand hangs and then falls♪
♪Let what stays unsaid pass♪
♪Why torture each other like this?♪
♪My wish might be♪
♪Scattering like ripples♪
♪With a gust of wind,
they fade like a dream♪
♪Daylight fades into ash♪
♪Fine rain falls dim and deep♪
♪For the rest of my life♪
♪I can hardly meet you again♪
Bai Sanxing,
once I have a chance,
I'll make sure you die.
Fine.
I'll be waiting.
♪Collapse piece by piece♪
♪I hate that I hesitated♪
♪And did not dare draw near again♪
♪Leaving all behind♪
♪The sudden pause of words unsaid♪
♪How I long to hold that silhouette close♪
Jiang Ai,
it's you.
♪All that is unfinished fade away♪
Wasn't I in the Prison?
♪In the end, love is the hardest to resist♪
You let me out?
♪Let memories drift and scatter♪
♪Alone, I gather them up♪
Her Grace spared your life.
Take care of yourself.
♪Till the past falls still again♪
♪And turns to clear daylight♪
(Shuozhou)
Han,
you were only framed
by Chong spies.
I'll avenge you.
But why must you leave now?
Shengliu, don't talk
like it's a last farewell.
We'll meet again.
Commandant Wu,
forgive me.
I have my reasons.
Captain Han,
we'll meet again.
Why did you save me?
I wasn't saving you.
I saved myself.
It was that one belief
that kept me going.
I've been through
what you're torn over now.
From that day on,
I was loyal only to myself.
But you're different.
Because of my selfish desire,
I ignored your wishes
and made that choice for you.
For my arrogance,
and for the scar on your face
I owe you an apology.
I'm sorry.
You saved my life
and apologized to me.
I'm not so ungrateful
as to miss your kindness.
General.
You're no longer who you once were.
You should go.
There are many things
you need time to think through.
You still have a long life ahead.
Don't be afraid.
(Liang)
(Jingzhou)
(Duan Xu played along)
(and took back Jingzhou from Chong forces.)
(Later,)
(the Fenglai Force attacked again.)
(Duan Xu pressed on to Qizhou)
(and killed the lead general.)
(Qizhou)
(Chong forces fled in defeat.)
(Duan Xu seized Qizhou in one stroke)
(and was titled Marquis of Ningyi.)
Let me do it.
Yes.
Xu,
what's wrong with you?
You fought like mad.
What are you rushing for?
It doesn't hurt that much.
But Xu,
you've lost a lot of blood.
If Xiaoxiao finds out,
she'll be worried.
I understand.
The General is eager to retake our land,
but there's no need to push so hard.
There is still time.
Xu, but...
General, get some rest.
We'll take our leave.
Come on.
Chenying.
Let's go.
Come on.
Move.
Xu.
Let's go.
Simu.
I called you.
Why didn't you appear?
Today, I made tea pastries
from the Mortal World for you.
Come.
Have a taste.
See if you like them.
Simu,
if only you'd yield a little.
Even if it were a lie, I'd accept it.
Why must you be so cold to me?
Why drive me to this?
Do you think I don't know
what it is you've hidden?
You still can't let go
of that mortal.
Other than me,
you can't think of anyone else.
I dote on you and cherish you,
not so your heart may dwell
upon another.
In your heart, there can only be me.
Everyone else must die.
Wait for me here.
I'll be back soon.
(Why has the Spirit Aura drifted here?)
Yan Ke,
what do you want?
Prophet Hejia.
Starhaven sorcerers.
How dare you, evil spirit,
harm mortals in the Mortal World?
The Starhaven Sect will not spare you.
Prophet Hejia,
are you okay?
It was to scare him.
I'm here with you.
Don't be afraid.
Prophet Hejia.
Prophet Hejia!
Prophet Hejia,
you're finally awake.
do you know where Simu is?
I can't find her.
The Void has been very busy lately.
As the Sovereign,
she's burdened with duties.
Even I dare not disturb her.
General Duan,
no need to worry.
Then why are you here?
You even saved me.
Great Ancestor came to me earlier.
She told me to keep you safe.
As soon as I got the order,
I rushed here without delay.
I even changed horses several times.
The horses never stopped.
I nearly lost my life
on the road.
Luckily,
your life was saved.
My life
was spared too.
But Prophet Hejia...
Easy now.
Great Ancestor is mighty.
She must be tied up and unable
to come out.
Don't worry.
I'll look after you from now on.
I still want to know where Simu is.
Time for his medicine.
You should go.
Thank you for today.
Please get some rest.
With your current conditions,
you should be resting at home.
Yet you insist on meddling in this.
Great Ancestor's affair
is no trivial matter.
She rarely entrusts me with much,
so no matter what,
I must see it through.
All things have their destined fate.
If you force your hand,
it may bring no good.
Aren't you interfering as well?
Take your medicine.
Your medicine
can't change my fate.
Great Ancestor's Pearl
gives no reply,
and spirits still wreak harm
in the Mortal World.
Something grave must've happened
in the Void.
This matches the star
of the great calamity
in the ancient texts.
The Mortal World faces a great calamity.
As the Lord of Starhaven Sect,
it is my duty to save the world.
I can't stand by and do nothing.
Only by staying alive
can you save the world.
Help!
The High Priest is here.
- High Priest.
Please save us.
Hold on.
It doesn't hurt anymore.
Thank you for your protection.
Cangshen protects my people.
My leg.
- High Priest.
- Yes.
- High Priest, save me.
- With the High Priest here,
we're safe.
Save me.
Report!
- Here.
- High Priest,
the General invites you
to the camp to plan
how to strike the foe
in the coming Battle of Weizhou.
Hold on.
Lead the way.
(Zhaomu Pavilion)
I went to kill Duan Xu.
He had just come from battle,
with his wounds unhealed.
I struck him down so hard
that he could only murmur your name.
He was mentally and physically shattered.
I doubt he has long to live.
How does it feel to be cut
by the Deliverance?
Starhaven sorcerers
were tough, right?
As expected of you, Simu.
You've arranged everything so well.
You truly feared I'd kill him.
You gave him an amulet
and even had the Lord of Starhaven Sect
protect him.
A mortal as lowly as an ant
can only cling to life under you.
What is it you love about him?
You said you loved me,
yet you used such tricks
to keep me trapped here.
Even with my spirit power lost,
you still can't do anything to me.
Yan Ke,
did you truly do all this for me?
Have you forgotten what birthed you?
You crave power and rank.
You're only obsessed
with power in your life.
Your desires will never end.
What you want is power,
the highest power of all.
Simu, you're wrong.
What I've wanted
has always been your heart.
Our lives are long.
I'll wait with you.
I'll make you watch him
fade away bit by bit.
I'll wait for the day
you finally forget him.
Foxy,
stay alive.
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪