No!
Do-hee.
Do-hee!
No!
"I can do all things…
through him…
who gives me strength."
Gu-won.
Do-hee.
Everything's okay now.
Gu-won.
Did you
save me?
I saved myself.
No.
Why?
Gu-won.
No, don't.
No, Gu-won.
I still have so much to tell you.
Gu-won, I know now.
I remembered everything.
I was Wolsim, wasn't I?
I was going to kill myself
the day we first met,
but meeting you
made me want to live again.
I don't care what you are.
Just stay with me.
Don't go.
Please don't leave me.
Gu-won.
Gu-won!
Please don't go!
So…
that's the choice you made.
DEMONS CANNOT KILL THE LIVING
OR BRING THE DEAD BACK TO LIFE
UPON BREAKING THIS RULE,
THEY PERISH THROUGH SPONTANEOUS COMBUSTION
FINALE
OUR PERSONAL HEAVEN
I guess it's not over till it's over.
Is Mr. Jeong still missing?
Yes. It's certain
that he was at the scene,
but he's been missing for over a week.
Ms. Do is still in shock
and refuses to say anything.
And Noh Suk-min
keeps rambling on about nonsense,
looking as if
he's just crawled out of hell.
I won.
I destroyed both of you
with my own two hands.
Do-hee, open the door!
I think we'll have to break the door open.
Please get started.
Ms. Do!
You'll catch a cold.
You should change first.
Go out in the sun and get some fresh air,
or you'll fall into a downward spiral.
I can't…
stand this world.
Gu-won is nowhere in this world.
I used to be able to sense…
that he was hovering around me
even if I couldn't see him.
But now…
I can't feel him anywhere.
Do-hee.
You can't go on like this.
At this rate,
you might die as well.
I won't die.
I can't.
Not after what
Gu-won went through to save me.
I'm going to endure this living hell.
That's my punishment.
Why should you be punished?
You didn't do anything wrong.
He died because of me.
It's my fault.
If only he hadn't met me.
I'm the one who killed him.
It's all my fault.
I killed him.
PATIENT CARD
DO DO-HEE
This is the second time
I've seen Ms. Do like this.
She was like this
at her parents' funeral too.
It was as if she had shut herself off
from the world.
She had…
barely been holding on,
but she's fallen apart in the end.
-Silent night
-Holy night
-All is calm
-All is bright
-Round yon virgin, mother and child
-Holy infant, so tender and mild
-Sleep in heavenly peace
Merry Christmas, Gu-won.
I thought we'd be spending
Christmas together,
but you're gone.
It feels like when you died,
a part of me
died with you.
Make a deal with me.
Gu-won.
My wish…
is to have you back.
Gu-won.
Are we
in hell?
Am I dead?
Or am I dreaming?
You're neither dreaming
nor dead.
Merry Christmas, Do-hee.
I'm back.
I still can't believe it.
The world without you was terrible.
Same here.
Being without you
is hell to me.
Give me your hand.
Let me charge up.
Go ahead.
Let's charge up.
Thank you.
Thank you so much!
Christmas miracles do happen.
But why did you do it?
You said you were a mere companion
on the journey of everything.
She wanted a deal.
Since you were gone, I had to step in.
A deal?
Are you saying you're sending her to hell?
Don't you play with us again--
Don't worry.
The payment for her deal
has already been made.
Let's make a bet.
If I get my powers back
and Do Do-hee lives,
you lose.
I told you.
That's never going to happen.
Is it still valid?
I mean the bet I won.
If I ever have a wish,
will you grant it?
Are you asking me for help?
Yes.
I need all the help I can get right now,
even if it's from you,
whom I trust the least.
If I had compassion,
I would've gone crazy.
There are too many
pitiful lives in the world.
So I didn't think I possessed
such human emotions.
You were right.
One should
never say never.
You were also right.
Happiness has no meaning
without misfortune.
I get that now.
So we're even now.
But come to think of it,
it's rather fortunate
that you don't have a knack for gambling.
-I don't?
-No.
-I don't have a knack for gambling?
-Not at all.
I've only lost once!
Let's make another bet!
If I win this time,
you'll cease to exist for good!
No!
Not in a million years.
I love living among humans now.
Also, you still need a worker.
You'd never find another worker
as handsome and hard-working as me.
Goodness!
I guess…
you're the perfect fit.
I agree.
My goodness.
SUNWOL FOUNDATION
"Without powers, the body of a demon
is no different from that of a human…"
Director Jeong!
My goodness. Director Jeong!
You scared me. What are you, a buffalo?
Director Jeong.
Ga-young. Please stay away.
I just barely escaped death.
Are you trying to kill me?
We thought you were gone for good.
What are you talking about? I'm a demon.
Why would I die?
Christmas is already over.
Why decorate the tree now?
Who cares?
Our Christmas is just beginning.
I'm starting to understand
what you said about Christmas.
What do you mean?
That Christmas somehow makes you excited.
I'm the same way.
Being with you makes me excited.
You must be my Christmas.
Do you feel like a kid again?
That's also true.
The most important part.
Can you tell me…
about the deal you made with my dad?
I want to know,
even if it's an inconvenient truth.
That day…
it was pouring rain.
Traffic update.
There was a 12-vehicle collision
at the intersection
south of the Seongsu Bridge.
due to heavy rainfall.
Honey.
Are you okay?
Doctor!
EMERGENCY MEDICAL CENTER
We're almost there.
Hang in there, honey.
Just a second, doctor!
Please examine my wife.
We were in a car accident.
Sorry. But all our beds are full,
even in the emergency room.
Please find another hospital. I'm sorry.
Honey!
Something doesn't feel right.
No, this can't be happening.
Help!
Someone help!
Please, someone save my wife.
No, honey.
Please help.
My wife will die
if she doesn't see a doctor right now.
Saving two lives by granting one wish.
Not bad.
I'll grant your wish.
On one condition.
It doesn't matter.
I'll do anything.
Shouldn't you still hear it?
You might regret it.
No.
I'll never regret it.
Well, suit yourself then.
You saved me back then too.
It wasn't me.
It was your father.
His sacrifice…
saved you.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
I didn't want to confuse you further.
Because it's true
that I made you miserable.
You didn't make me miserable.
I spent ten wonderful years
with my parents.
They did their absolute best
every moment,
probably because they knew
they had limited time with me.
You saved me.
Both in my past life
and in this one.
You saved me as well.
You saved me…
from eternal destruction.
MIRAE F&amp;B
Good morning.
Good morning to you too.
Long time no see.
Good morning.
Thank you, Ms. Shin.
No, thank you.
I'm happy to see you again.
Likewise.
Mr. Ju Seok-hoon is waiting for you.
They've been gone for a while,
and they're totally glowing.
They always have been.
Both Ms. Do and Mr. Jeong.
They must've been on a trip.
No, I have a feeling
there's something more to it.
Like what?
Beats me.
But they seem to share a strong bond,
as if they overcame
an immense hardship together.
After hearing
someone clueless like you say that,
I'm more convinced
that they were on a trip.
I'm telling you, that's not it.
Mr. Jeong.
Didn't I say I wouldn't just sit back
if you ever hurt Do-hee?
What's with him?
Don't you dare disappear again,
or I'll make you regret it.
You and your obsession with me.
I get it, so let go of me.
I'm glad to see you back.
I said I got it.
Jeez, our ears are touching.
Do-hee, help.
Look at me.
-Don't ever get hurt.
-Do-hee.
Do-hee.
I get it, okay?
-Two brisket soups to table seven.
-Here are two bowls of rice.
-Did you enjoy your meal?
-It was really good.
Thank you.
Collect ten stamps
and get a free bowl of rice soup.
Thank you.
We look forward to serving you again!
-We'll serve you again!
How dare you serve someone other than me?
CONGRATULATIONS ON THE GRAND OPENING
BYE, UNDERWORLD, HELLO, SUNNY SPOT
Welcome, boss!
-Welcome, boss!
You didn't have to.
I heard your rice soup
is all the rage now.
Bring me a bowl.
I'll go for the assorted toppings.
One drop-dead delicious rice soup
with assorted toppings, please!
-One rice soup with assorted toppings!
Will my food be on the house?
-It says "9,000 won," doesn't it?
-Then I'll pass.
It's on the house, of course.
How have you been?
-Your face has become so thin.
-I haven't been eating well lately.
What?
More than half the board
is on Do Do-hee's side?
I don't believe this!
Will that brat Do-hee
really become the chairwoman?
I can't give up like this.
I have one last resort.
What brings you here?
It's…
a family matter.
Ms. Noh Su-ahn,
who claims to be your family, is here.
Greet her, boys.
What are you doing here with your kids?
I'm sorry for everything, Do-hee.
My sincere apologies.
Do you remember?
Austin right here
used to be so fond of you.
I'm Justin.
Justin right here
used to be so fond of you.
Don't you worry
about the future of Mirae Group.
Austin and Justin are undergoing
thorough successor training.
They'll be supporting you
from either side of you in the future.
Justin on your left
and Austin on your right.
How reassuring is that?
Justin on your left
and Austin on your right.
Justin here on your left,
and Austin here on your right.
The two of them.
Do-hee!
I'll try harder.
I'm sure you'll recognize
my sincerity someday.
We're family, right? Do-hee!
Justin?
Austin?
Let's go.
Family?
CIVIL AFFAIRS OFFICE
NAME: DO DO-HEE
RELATIONSHIP: FAMILY
You seem fine.
You sure have a heart of stone.
Everyone around you
died off because of you,
but you don't bat an eye.
I'm sorry to tell you this,
but you failed to destroy anyone.
Gu-won's back,
and I'm unscathed, as you can see.
Do you expect me to believe that?
Look at me.
I'm not hurt by anything you say.
I can't just be pretending, can I?
The only thing you managed to destroy
is yourself.
Quiet!
Noh Suk-min!
Calm down, Noh Suk-min!
Once I get out of here,
I'll kill them with my own two hands.
No matter how long it takes,
I'll kill them myself.
Mother.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Don't look at me like that!
Stop it!
Someone help!
Hello?
I said stop it!
Go away!
Ma'am, should I tell them
to move the stuff out?
Yes, please go ahead.
Ma'am…
What do you want to do with this?
JIU-JITSU 2 DAN, NOH DO-GYEONG
-Just throw it away, please.
-Okay.
My goodness.
You should've been more careful.
I'm sorry.
10 YEARS AGO
Are you going to the gym again?
Do you realize what time it is?
Why do you have to go this far?
I need to protect…
myself…
and you.
Do…
Do-gyeong!
But this is…
ACNE SCAR TREATMENT
Goodness.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. I have one for wounds.
-Mom.
-Yeah?
See you later.
I'll video chat you every day.
To think how lonely you'll be
in a foreign country.
Let's part ways with a smile.
Take care of yourself in England.
Don't skip meals
even if you're not used to the food.
-Okay.
-Don't strain yourself while rehearsing.
And before going to bed…
Enough.
Jin Ga-young.
Are you leaving without saying goodbye?
I thought I might waver if I saw you.
Here.
I looked it up,
and it rains a lot in England.
Take this with you.
I could buy one there.
He wants you to think of him
every time it rains.
This will be a reminder of him for you.
That's reaching. It's just an umbrella.
Fine.
If you…
If you ever want to come back,
you're welcome here…
anytime.
See? You're making me waver.
Have a good life, Director Jeong.
You too, Mr. Park.
Sir, hold on.
I knew it.
I knew coming back here
would make me want to leave.
Are you okay?
Hey.
What happened to your face?
Come here.
I said come here.
Are you her dad?
So what if I am?
That doesn't give you
the right to hit her.
I didn't hit her.
She tripped and fell while playing.
Who are you anyway?
Why are you butting in--
Is this the police?
I'd like to report a child abuse case.
Hang up right now.
-Yes, the address is…
-Why, you little…
Don't you know what a guardian is?
I'm her parent.
Can't I even discipline my own child?
What is this nonsense?
Child abuse, my ass.
She tripped and fell while playing,
that's all.
I'll miss my flight if I don't leave now.
Aren't you going?
Ta-da.
These are for you.
They look good on you.
Are you an angel?
Me? What makes you think so?
You saved me.
Yes, I am.
Call me whenever something happens.
Don't forget.
Angels…
never come to save you.
…always come to save you.
Okay, angel.
Are you going or not?
I'm not.
I have unfinished business here.
Please drink.
I heard that
you're resigning from the board.
I plan on starting a center
for child victims of domestic violence.
I know it won't make up
for all my wrongdoings.
But…
I don't want to turn a blind eye anymore.
I'm sorry
for turning a blind eye all this time.
Thank you for finding the courage.
Please let me know
if I can help you with anything
regarding your center.
Okay,
I will.
My tarot reading predicted
I'd get a boyfriend this year,
but I've been single all year.
Cheer up, Ms. Choi.
There's still one day left
until the year ends.
That's right. It's too early to give up.
That only makes me feel more miserable.
On that note,
how about a team dinner?
Sounds good!
Let's go have that team dinner.
I guess she's getting old too.
Do we have another team dinner maniac now?
I'll pass.
I'd like to welcome the new year
with my family.
We're family too, aren't we?
Come on. Don't you have a personal life?
I don't have one, even at home.
Let's go have that team dinner.
Ms. Shin!
Where are we going?
Everyone, I have an announcement to make.
Why are you doing this?
The two of us are in a relationship.
This man here,
Mr. Park Bok-gyu, is my man.
He's the most innocent
and kind-hearted person in the world.
Ms. Shin.
-I see.
I see.
You've finally said it.
It's finally over.
It's been so hard to play dumb.
Does that mean you all had figured it out?
It's not that we figured it out.
Let's just take one photo strip.
All right. One strip and we're leaving.
We're leaving after one strip, okay?
All right, we will.
You look so cute.
All right.
Do I look pretty?
-No.
-In the name of love and justice…
-Is that…
-Ms.…
Shin?
Shall we say
you already made a declaration of sorts?
4 MONTHS LATER
How are you doing this?
Sir.
That's enough exercise. Let's go.
I can't die like this.
My mom
recently got diagnosed
with a terminal illness.
Once she passes away,
I'll go with you.
Stop acting so pitiful.
I'm starting to feel sorry.
My mom…
She'll be miserable without me.
Please have mercy on me.
Hold on.
Take five.
Yes, Mr. Park?
I've looked into Oh Jin-sang,
whose contract expires today.
And he's a real piece of work.
He beat up his own mother so often
that more than ten reports
have been made so far.
That little wimp
asked you to make him stronger
only to harass people.
It doesn't end there.
That'll be enough.
Thank you.
For what?
For being
a total scumbag.
Understood.
The chairperson is coming.
MIRAE GROUP
CHAIRPERSON
I made it just in time.
"Reach Zero through the Holy Spirit"?
I've repented and turned to Catholicism,
just like my mom.
This is a hybrid
of my faith and weight loss.
OVERCOME HUNGER THROUGH FAITH
-What does zero mean?
-Size zero.
Taking care of your soul isn't enough.
You should take care of your body as well.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I had a lot of documents to go over
before my first meeting as the chairman.
Let's get started.
Before we start the meeting,
each subsidiary will report
on their performance
for the first quarter.
I've already reviewed the reports.
Our first-half operating margin
significantly increased from last year.
However, my research reveals
that this rapid improvement
stemmed from a substantial reduction
in personnel expenses
and employee benefits,
which is the easiest way to boost numbers.
While results matter,
the process is much more important
in fostering better long-term performance.
Moving forward,
Mirae Group will not take any shortcuts
in order to create results.
Great job, sir.
-Thank you for your work.
-Thank you.
You came prepared.
Research is my forte.
By the way, Do-hee,
are you really okay
with my taking over the chairman position?
You know I refuse to get any help
from Madam Ju.
If I became the chairwoman,
it'd be mostly thanks to Madam Ju's will.
It would be frustrating
to need her help after all this time.
That's very like you.
I've always known
what an incredible person you are.
Don't let your guard down.
I might grow my company big enough
to take over Mirae Group.
-Seok-hoon.
-Hi, Su-ahn.
Excellent.
A young leader sure is different.
Thanks.
Do you remember?
Austin used to be so fond of you.
Don't you worry
about the future of Mirae Group.
Austin and Justin are undergoing
thorough successor training.
Justin will be on your left
and Austin on your right.
And I'll be supporting you as well.
-Su-ahn.
-Yeah?
-Come up with some new lines.
-I've got your back.
Take care of yourself.
Eat healthy and work out hard.
Keep in mind that I've got your back.
CHIEF PROSECUTOR CHOI WOO-SUN
Yes.
Okay, all right.
The Supreme Court
upheld the death sentence.
As you may know,
that implies no possibility of parole.
Noh Suk-min will now rot in prison
for the rest of his life.
That's a relief.
He can no longer harm anyone.
By the way,
something came to my attention
while investigating,
and I think you should know.
The late Chairwoman Ju Cheon-suk
had a health checkup before she passed.
That's right.
That was my condition
for going on a blind date with you.
But the checkup revealed
that she had terminal pancreatic cancer.
Pardon?
What are you talking about?
According to her doctor,
her symptoms were so severe
that she was aware of her condition.
Madam Ju.
Is that why you kept pestering me
to get married?
So that I wouldn't be left alone again?
Why didn't you tell me?
Then I would've been nicer to you
and loved you as much as I wanted.
You must've been in a lot of pain.
You said you had lies flowing
through your veins instead of blood,
and it was true.
Don't you worry anymore.
I have someone on my side now.
Humans can now live up to 130 years?
I mean, 130 years pass
in the blink of an eye.
It's too short.
Gu-won!
Time for cake, your favorite.
No!
-You can't eat it.
-Why not?
Do you know how bad sugar is for humans?
You should stay away from these things
to live long.
I'll have just a little.
No! Don't.
You can't.
I run a dessert company.
From now on, sell health foods only.
I'll have to eat all of it myself.
-Share it with me.
-No.
It looks so bad. Let me take care of it.
-Why?
-Eat something else.
Have some red ginseng
over there or something.
I paid for this.
Look at the night view.
You're missing such a beautiful sight.
It's involuntary.
I can't take my eyes off you.
I can't help it.
Do-hee.
Your time
goes by too fast.
That's what makes
this moment even more precious.
-Mr. Park.
-Director Jeong.
Listen, you should never get married.
-What?
-I had a fight with Do-hee,
and she's been playing hymns and chants
from all religions all day.
She'd even sell her soul
to get on my nerves.
Also!
Isn't this so childish?
Does she think this is a diary?
She thinks she can do whatever she wants.
Director Jeong.
Why aren't you taking my side?
Why are your eyes twitching? What is it?
What?
Hubby.
Can we talk?
I thought we were done talking.
No, we weren't.
I'll go work on the performance.
-Don't go, buffalo.
-Goodbye, Mr. Park.
I'll leave you two to talk.
What's this? A frog?
It's so pretty.
A frog, a flower,
-a chick…
-Hubby.
It scares me when you call me hubby.
-What?
-Never mind.
Is it so hard to tell me beforehand
when you'll be home late?
It slips my mind
when I'm too busy with work.
You stay out late making deals
without telling me too.
That's a different story.
How so?
How can you compare my deals
to the insignificant jobs humans do?
Do you know what I've been going through
to only make deals with scumbags?
Are you saying
that what you do is important
while what I do is trivial?
-That's not what I meant.
-Forget it.
Caught in the crossfire
of hatred and misfortune,
we ceaselessly
hurt each other
and destroy each other's souls.
However,
despite all that,
our lives
and this world continue.
Perhaps that's because
there are more people
who save each other
with their love and trust.
Let go.
I hate you the most.
I love you.
A lot.
I hate you the most,
but I love you the most too.
Do-hee.
You're my everything.
Silly humans.
-This looks good.
-How about this one?
That's a bit…
If you want something bright,
how about blue?
-It looks good.
-Do you like it?
-I think it's boring.
-It's boring?
Then how about pink?
-That's cute.
-Right?
-Do you like it?
-Yes.
Do you know why
the dinosaurs went extinct?
-A comet crashed into…
-Poor performance.
Their performance
didn't live up to their size.
No.
It was because of poor work-life balance.
Let's go home.
-Let's go home!
-Nice!
-That's what I'm talking about!
-Yes!
-Let's go home!
Let's go!
Let's go home!
One more time?
Gu-won!
I love you.
We may destroy each other at times,
but we're also the ones
who save each other.
Therefore,
we are both each other's destroyers
and saviors.
Subtitle translation by: Min-jin Kim