Dong-eun!
We didn't get to talk back there, did we?
My God, what a coincidence!
It's good to see you.
Can I have a word with you right now?
Shall we?
This way.
Spare me, Dong-eun.
Spare me just once.
I made a mistake back then.
I'm not asking you to understand.
I have no excuse for my actions.
I'm so sorry.
I've been repenting all my life,
and I'll never stop.
I swear, Dong-eun!
I haven't even gotten started yet.
Why are you kneeling already?
How will you beg later?
You know that my family runs
a dry cleaning business.
I really didn't want to do it, but they...
I didn't have a choice.
We were all so young, you know.
We all make mistakes growing up.
Please, Dong-eun?
So, is this a mistake
or is it intentional?
Are you crazy?
I'm a flight attendant!
This is what you call "intentional,"
Ms. Flight Attendant.
It's when you hurt someone,
knowing that it will hurt.
It's what you did to me every single day.
Okay. I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I've done something unforgivable.
But, Dong-eun,
can't you please forgive me
just this once?
Please don't tell my mother-in-law. No.
Please stop contacting her.
Just until I get married, please?
I've submitted my resignation forms,
so if I can't get married,
I won't have a source of income. I'll die!
Please, Dong-eun!
Your change of attitude is a good plan,
but it was too early and too clumsy.
I don't want anything from you,
whether it be money or an apology.
You've kneeled, begged,
and tried threatening me too.
Try your next move now.
Fuck!
So what?
What is it?
What do you want from me,
you fucking bitch?
You lost your phone before, right?
Yeah. That's the phone that you lost.
It was you?
Those photos weren't sent by Myeong-o?
You crazy bitch!
Just think about how much I know
about you now, Hye-jeong.
Now there's only one way to save yourself,
so think carefully.
It's what you do best.
Then I won't meet
with your future mother-in-law.
I will be on your side
until the day I die, Dong-eun.
What should I do first?
Report Myeong-o
as a missing person.
Thank you, sir.
Be careful.
Look ahead.
Do you have something left to say?
Oh, it's just nice
to look at children laughing.
It's like watching
an air purifier commercial.
I don't plan on marrying since married men
get the short end of the stick.
It's "romantic" if you're unmarried
but "adulterous" if you're married.
-Right?
-There are kids here.
Wow, you're a great father.
But you're not a fun one.
Ye-sol has a sense of humor.
I wonder who she got it from.
You've been like this
since the classroom. Why?
Wow, you look like you're about to hit me.
There are kids here.
Well, then.
I need to talk to my friend.
Did you reach Myeong-o?
I don't need to anymore.
I found out the reason today.
Stand right there.
Raise your hands and you're dead.
This way.
Hands down! I said I'll kill you!
Which homeroom are you in?
-The bell rang ages ago!
-Ugh, fuck!
Do you drink a lot of strawberry milk?
I think you can stop drinking now.
I was right, wasn't I?
Her boobs are freaking huge, right?
Hi, Dong-eun.
So Yeon-jin's pretty plaything
is Yeon-jin's daughter's teacher now.
A coincidence?
Yeon-jin didn't tell you?
I told her it wasn't a coincidence.
Hey, if it wasn't a coincidence,
it means you've planned everything out
from the time at the gym
to this moment.
That's scary as hell.
I didn't know you had a side like this.
I thought you'd be playing
basketball or something.
Why are bad feelings never wrong?
Well, it's too late to stop you now,
and it can't be avoided either.
Will your revenge only end
once everyone has suffered?
Like the summer rain back then?
Wow, so you know how to get angry now?
This is why I'm here,
to see how you've grown up.
Oh, right.
You have those scars, right?
Are they all better now?
Do they not feel hot anymore?
Hey, I asked you a question.
Oh my, they're still there.
Let me blow on it for you.
I'm warning you.
Don't touch Yeon-jin's daughter
in any way.
Did you get Ye-sol's toothbrush?
I used express delivery
because I figured it was urgent.
That...
was you?
Let me warn you too.
Don't help Yeon-jin in any way.
If you really want Ye-sol,
then I'm your ally.
Not Yeon-jin.
I guess you don't know,
so let me tell you.
That I was also somebody's daughter.
Okay, Jae-jun?
Wow.
Well, my mom always said...
that I should listen to the teacher.
Yeah.
Good to see you, friend.
A gift.
HA YE-SOL
An open house? Today?
Yeah. There were a lot of dads there,
but Dad was the coolest!
Ha Ye-sol!
Why didn't you keep your promise?
I told you to tell me
everything that happens at school.
Everything your teacher says!
You should have told me
about something like that!
I told you when we were eating dinner
a while ago.
I said that all the dads will be coming.
Oh, I'm just all over the place
these days.
Sorry.
Did your dad talk with the teacher?
Did they say hi?
No, they didn't.
Dad just talked with Uncle Jae-jun.
Uncle Jae-jun was at school?
In your classroom?
I thought it was fun
when you asked me out for a meal.
I was curious as to what you wanted.
But I never imagined
something like this would happen.
What do you mean by this?
It doesn't mean much.
It's like a fruit basket.
I couldn't come empty-handed.
I asked Gyeong-tae for your number
and what you like.
I hope that's okay.
It's okay, but I am a bit anxious.
Your fruit basket is totally my type.
You know Moon Dong-eun, right?
To be exact, I'd like to know
the relationship between her and Yeon-jin.
How do you know Dong-eun?
We play Go together.
Wow!
Wow. It's a small world, huh?
Does Yeon-jin know that you're meeting me?
She won't know
because I'm not going to tell her.
There's not much to say
about Yeon-jin and Dong-eun.
We all went to the same high school,
and Yeon-jin bullied Dong-eun
while we were there.
So, kind of like
school violence?
Not "like." It was exactly that.
How exactly?
Badly.
We're in the same homeroom,
but I've never talked to you.
Right, Dong-eun?
What do you need?
She won't say hello back.
Okay, then.
I don't need anything. It's just a favor.
I can't stand the smell of bleach,
you know.
But it's already my turn
to clean the bathroom.
What do you think?
What do you mean?
You know what I mean.
Does it hurt your pride less
if you put off your answer?
Anyway, can you clean the bathroom for me?
Another friend of mine helped me
until last week,
but now she's changed schools.
So-hee transferred?
Apparently.
Now we're going to find out
where she went.
Come on, answer me now.
I really want to hear your voice.
What will you do...
if I say no?
I like quick answers,
and I'm not so patient.
So, what? You don't want to?
God, I'm so impatient.
This won't do.
Hey, Myeong-o.
You can't be patient for even a minute?
That's how it started.
It all ended when Dong-eun dropped out.
Ask Yeon-jin
about what happened in between.
It's a pretty searing story.
So, Dong-eun wasn't the first victim?
I guess you don't talk much
with your wife.
Well, you should try it today.
I'll get going now.
Can I ask you for a favor?
When you see Dong-eun,
can you tell her
that I told you about all this stuff?
Please.
Is that the only gambling you do?
There was one time
when I bet my entire life on something.
Did you win?
I'm planning to.
Oh, come on. You shouldn't try so hard
to beat an old man like that!
You should let him go again.
He can re-do his last move, right?
I'll say. He's so skilled
for someone so young, huh?
Sure.
I've lost this match, sir.
Here.
My friend is here.
There you are.
Let's go.
Am I the friend?
-Let's play another match.
-Sure.
Help me out here. I just played
three rounds against four people.
Doesn't your wife hate it
when you play Go?
That's not the only thing she hates.
Do they still sell those?
I got invited by a friend I taught Go to.
I wasn't sure what to bring.
You two are adorable.
I'm guessing that
you're actually waiting for someone.
I have a call to make.
But I haven't collected my thoughts yet.
Do you live nearby?
Oh, I just moved here.
Semyeong is a good place to live, indeed.
The air is still nice.
I didn't move here
because of such a practical reason.
I'm here to help someone's revenge.
Revenge, in this country?
It won't be easy,
especially since there are no guns.
Although half of the country knows
how to shoot a gun, right?
But you can use knives.
You can shoot a gun from a distance,
but you need to get up close
to use a knife.
You need to get so close that you can see
your own eyes reflected in theirs and...
Oh, sorry!
I've been watching Netflix all day
because I don't have any patients.
Oh, right.
I've opened up a practice.
You should drop by.
I have a lot of male patients as well,
so don't feel uncomfortable.
Best of luck to you.
I hope I can pay my rent, at least.
No, I mean with your revenge.
I'll definitely need some of that, then.
He was pretty tall.
About 178 or 179 centimeters tall
and 76 or 77 kilograms, I'd say?
You're tall too, Yeo-jeong.
I wish I were the only tall guy around.
His watch, coat, shoes, and cologne...
They were all just right.
Not too showy but not too cheap.
How should I put this?
It was like opening page 17
of the January issue of GQ.
You see, my mother and father
are a bit weird.
My birthday is on January 16th,
and they thought it was so hard
to choose my birthday gifts.
I think it was my senior year.
They said they'd just get me whatever is
on page 16 of the January issue of GQ.
Sometimes it was a book,
and sometimes it was a coffee machine.
Once I even got a sports car.
I still don't get
why Ha Do-yeong is page 17.
When you flip to page 16,
you can always see page 17 too.
But you often find
something even nicer there.
Well, simply put,
"I was annoyed because he was so cool."
That's what I tried to say
without you finding out about it.
Did you get his call?
No.
I thought he'd call me
right after the open house,
but he hasn't yet.
He probably doesn't like the fact
that he has no control over the situation.
I could tell by his playing style.
Around Friday afternoon,
after finishing up work,
canceling all of his weekend arrangements,
and organizing the questions
inside his head, he'll call you.
You weren't answering my texts.
Where have you been?
Where's Ye-sol?
Don't you know what time it is?
By the way, Do-yeong,
maybe I should learn how to play Go too.
Let me ask you something.
Huh?
Are you friends
with Ye-sol's homeroom teacher?
Is she the one you said you don't like?
I heard you went to the open house.
Jeez, it seems
that she's been misunderstanding me.
As you probably noticed,
she and I are from different worlds.
But we talked it out.
What's wrong? Did she say something?
So there's something to say.
How exactly did you talk it out?
You told me a while ago
that Ye-sol's homeroom teacher was crazy.
Did you mean she might hurt Ye-sol?
Is that why you tried to send her abroad?
Do-yeong.
We dated for two years,
and we've been married for ten.
Twelve years in total.
You're my husband,
so you should always be on my side.
But you're scolding me right away.
No matter what you've heard, or will hear,
don't be like that.
You know, when you choose something,
you always choose the thing
that's the most aesthetically shiny.
Our marriage is one of those things.
You like my body, my voice,
my jokes, and my background.
You like them all.
So don't try to open the box
that should not be opened.
I love you, Do-yeong.
So I don't want you to find out
about anything.
I'm going to make sure that nothing
in this box comes out into the world
and that Ye-sol stays unharmed.
So, Do-yeong,
can you just let Ye-sol and I
shine like we do now?
Please.
This box isn't shiny at all, Do-yeong.
I'm so jealous.
I shouldn't be eating soup.
The shaman told me
to lose three kilograms.
I thought compatible fortunes
were all we needed.
Damn it, that's because you're skinny.
So what?
I haven't been matched with a guy yet.
It must be nice to have good fortunes.
Hey. The guy who got matched with you,
will good things keep happening to him?
I guess it's not too bad.
I have a lot of "earth" in my fortunes,
but he doesn't.
So, that's what's important?
How interesting.
What's wrong with my fortunes?
Well done, everyone.
-Good work.
-Thank you.
That scar's taking a long time to heal.
It's been there for a while.
Do you want a new band-aid?
No. Just don't get any more
sponsored products from them.
My feet are getting all scratched up!
Come out. I'm in the parking lot.
What are you talking about right now?
-End it.
-End what?
End it with your husband.
Let me be Ye-sol's father.
And you'll get a new husband.
You've lost your mind.
Is that why you went to Ye-sol's school?
Don't try to change the subject.
Do you love him?
You can't even talk to that bastard
about Dong-eun.
Because you're afraid
he won't take your side.
No, wait.
Is it because you know
he won't take your side?
But I know all about it.
I know, but I've always been there,
right next to you.
That's love.
You think that's love?
Yeah.
Love that you and I didn't know about.
Am I right?
I guess so.
I've never actually thought about it.
I love you, Do-yeong.
So I don't want you to find out
about anything.
Right? So...
Oh, I really do.
I really do love him.
I've loved him all along.
If I'm being honest, Yeon-jin...
SIESTA
...I've been giddy with anticipation lately.
Myeong-o never left the country,
and nobody can reach him.
Could this mean
that this is your confession?
To cover up one case,
could it be
that another case has taken place?
Here you go, ma'am.
The hydrogen peroxide is inside.
Are you hurt?
-Put it there and go back to work.
-Oh, okay.
I've been so excited thinking
that maybe you've unintentionally
opened Pandora's box
while trying to cover up your tracks.
CHIEF SHIN YEONG-JUN
Hello?
Do you have time at lunch tomorrow?
I need to give you
a few things you asked for.
From the factory job after dropping out,
all the way up to Semyeong Elementary,
it's all in there.
She's never had to pay a fine, and she's
always paid her health insurance on time.
The bitch is a model citizen.
What about the bitch's mom? Where's she?
Jeong Mi-hee?
You need that too?
It worked pretty well
when I was in high school.
If you are poor,
your family ends up doing the most harm.
PREPARATION TIME
By the way, who was that in the picture?
I could recognize most people based
on your explanations and the pictures,
but I couldn't recognize one.
The woman at the very left
wearing a red apron?
That's my mom.
You want to know why I put her there
along with the perpetrators?
Well, can I ask a different question?
Do you often wash your sheets?
-Yes.
-Oh...
Can I ask you a question too?
You finally want to know
something about me.
What is it?
Why is the passcode
to your front door 3724?
Usually, passcodes are a birthday,
the day when you first met somebody,
or a license plate number.
But I can't figure out what that is.
Can you ask a different question?
Inmate 3724, you have a visitor.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
After staying here for a while,
I've realized
that I did something terrible.
No matter how many times I apologize,
I know my sin won't go away.
I also know that I can't undo it.
I didn't know.
Excuse me?
I didn't know...
that a murdering bastard like you
had been sending letters to my son...
all this time.
Yes. I was mentally unstable...
"I couldn't withstand
the social pressures,
and I made a mistake"?
Bullshit. Dozens of your letters
all say the same thing.
Yes, I...
I...
I'm bad at writing.
Shut your mouth!
How dare you mess with my son
for a reduced sentence, you piece of shit!
How dare you make him go through hell!
I can never forgive a prick like you.
So if you ever send
a letter like that again...
I'll kill you.
But you're a doctor.
What?
All of your family members are doctors.
You can't kill people.
Your husband kicked the bucket
because of an oath like that.
I'm not doing this
because I want to get out of here.
I like this place. It's comfy.
They let me exercise.
They give me three meals a day
and medical attention too.
So, why...
are you sending those letters?
Because I'm bored.
So, is your son going through hell?
You son of a bitch!
HA YE-SOL
Hello.
Where?
Jongno Police Station?
Who was it? Was it you? You?
Who the hell reported Myeong-o as missing?
Maybe it was Yeon-jin.
She told us to do it.
Maybe she did it herself.
She'd never do something so annoying.
That leaves you. Was it you?
I got the call first because I'm his boss.
And an adult is treated
as a runaway at most.
The asshole is 36, for God's sake.
The special forces won't come running
just because we can't reach him.
So it was you, then.
You started looking for him first.
Why do you think it's me?
Why aren't you including yourself?
So it was you.
It was you. Yes, you fucking bitch.
Should I ask the cops if I'm right?
Yeah, you're right. It was me.
I reported it.
So what?
You said he's probably dead somewhere.
What if he's really dead?
Am I the weird one here
for reporting a friend as missing?
-He lives alone. Aren't you worried?
-This fucking bitch has gone insane.
Since when did you care
so much about Myeong-o?
I get why he asked you out now.
Did you sleep with him too? Huh?
What the fuck are you talking about?
He asked her out?
I got goosebumps.
Your pussy's always been
publicly available, right?
Hey, you did it on purpose, didn't you?
What's your intention?
You know that I bought drugs from him
and got prescriptions under his name
for a few years, don't you?
You also know that I'll be caught first
when they start investigating.
So, why the hell did you call the cops?
God. Too much information.
-I'm leaving.
-Let go.
Let go of me!
Fuck! Let me go!
Hey, if the cops start calling me,
then I'm really going
to fucking kill you, bitch!
EARLY MORNING DELIVERY
What is this?
Is it kimchi?
No.
Deposit the won and dollars separately,
and get proof of your average balance.
What is all this?
Did you make a passport for Sun-a?
What?
Here.
But why do you need a passport?
I'm going to submit these
to the overseas agency. Please sign them.
BEST OVERSEAS AGENCY
I'm going to send Sun-a to study abroad.
Study abroad?
I'm trying to hurry up my plans,
bit by bit.
I'll start doing what you asked for
on the day Sun-a leaves the country.
Sun-a will hear the news
of her father's death in the US.
I lied to you.
You won't get to have a proper dinner
with your daughter.
You
will lose Sun-a.
But Sun-a will be safe
from her abusive father
and her mother who took part in a murder.
That's the reality
of what we've planned to do.
If you want to stop,
then tell me now.
EDEN APARTMENTS
Is this really the right address?
Dong-eun's current address?
Yeah, it is.
She reported the new address shortly
before moving to her new job. Why?
Are you sure this is the place?
The bitch is living...
UNIT 301, EDEN APARTMENTS
71 SEMYEONG-RO, SEMYEONG
...right in front of my house.
Yes, sir.
Something personal came up.
Cancel all my plans for the weekend,
Monday, and Tuesday.
Text me if something urgent comes up.
-Yes, sir. Do you need anything else...
-No.
Where are you?
We should meet.
How much can I win per point here?
You must have a lot of questions.
Go for it.
Aren't you cold in those clothes?
I thought you would first ask me
if I had approached you on purpose.
Well, I wanted
to be unpredictable for once.
What would you have done
if I hadn't called you?
Held a parent-teacher meeting.
What if I had made a complaint?
It's a private school,
and I'm influential enough.
I know.
Your influence is
what I'm depending on, actually.
There's a lawyer
who taught me how to play Go.
That person told me that I had been born
holding the black stone.
So I've always had the upper hand.
It's always been easy for me.
But this match...
is a tough one.
I have a lot of questions
for both you and Yeon-jin.
But I'm planning on hearing you out first.
Why?
'Cause you seem to be claiming
that you're the victim.
Oh, are you here?
Yes. Unit 301.
How long will it take to unlock?
But this is illegal, you know.
If it were legal,
I wouldn't be paying you this much.
By the way,
aren't you the weathercaster?
Park Yeon-jin?
If I am,
does that change anything?
Open the door and wait here.
What?
Oh, okay.
You went to school with Yeon-jin.
Did you approach me on purpose?
Yes.
Then did you also...
learn how to play Go on purpose?
That's how it started,
but I've come to like it.
Because essentially,
Go is about building territories.
I dreamed of becoming an architect
until 11th grade, but gave up on it.
Did you send this picture?
I picked out the ones
that you look good in.
It doesn't look like it.
Where do you live?
If you've approached me on purpose,
I feel like it'd be very close.
I'm ready to find out.
I know this from experience,
but even if you've braced yourself,
brutality like this...
will hurt a lot.
I messed up.
I shouldn't have bullied that bitch.
I should have just killed her back then.
YOON SO-HEE, FEMALE
AGE 18
PROCESSED ON 12/15/2004