Hey, Adi!
Remember the time when
you said you had a friend
who was interested
in meeting me?
Lewis?
Is he still interested?
Can you set us up for a date?
Why are you here?
I missed you.
Sam!
Your boyfriend?
He’s my fiancé.
You're not even
wearing your ring.
What? I always wear it.
It’s always around your neck.
Fine. I’m going to wear it.
See?
I'm starting to think that
moving in was
actually a good idea.
And you’re the only person
in the world who
understands exactly how I feel.
I thought you’re
going to wait for—
How do you know when
you’re already falling in love?
Because I think I am.
Is he serious?
Or is he just
messing with me?
He is serious.
Honestly,
I don’t know how to answer that.
Because...
I haven’t fallen in love yet.
Really?
Why? I mean,
if you don’t mind me asking.
I’ve had a boyfriend before—
dated a few guys, too.
But I never really felt what
I thought love should be.
The kind of love
I saw my friends go through.
What kind of love have you seen?
You deserve this
happiness, lovebirds.
Kalix, you better watch out
if you make Luna cry.
Oh, don’t you dare.
I will not hurt, Luna.
I promise.
These two are too sweet.
He’s head over heels for me.
Hey!
Are you feeling giddy?
Bitch, no!
It’s just that I look
so gorgeous in the video.
The kind of love—
that’s hard to explain.
I can’t put it into words.
Let me.
More?
Yes, please.
Here.
Thank you.
Communication Arts graduate—
Communication—
Okay.
Media and content—
Huh?
Communication Arts graduate—
This career is in areas that—
Do you need anything?
I’m good.
I just have a lot
of stuff to do.
Hey, you don’t have to do that.
It’s all good.
It’s fine.
You look really busy.
Yes.
Our professor might give
a surprise quiz tomorrow.
You got this.
Here, for energy.
Thank you.
Wow,
you nailed the taste I like.
I pay attention.
Yours is pink.
Sometimes purple.
How the hell did you know that?
I pay attention.
Hey.
How are you today?
Tiring than usual.
We had back-to-back
Lab lectures.
You?
I spent hours in the library
doing research for my thesis.
But I had time
to prepare you this.
Oh!
Wow! For me?
- What’s this?
- Yes.
Read it.
ER kit.
Emergency Relaxation.
- Yes.
- Wow.
A little something to help you
relax and de-stress.
There’s a neck massager,
you know—
a neck pillow and an eye mask.
It’s silk! It’s gentle
for the skin.
It will not cause wrinkles.
- Okay.
- Like that.
This will really help a lot,
especially when
I’m feeling burnt out.
- Thanks, Maui.
- You’re welcome.
I’m glad you liked it.
What happened?
Hold still.
The bleeding will
stop eventually.
- Calm down.
- Okay.
Hey.
You should eat.
You haven’t eaten yet.
You need energy for whatever
you’re stressing over there.
I’m not hungry.
Go ahead and eat first.
You didn’t have
to trouble yourself.
What’s that? Your resume?
You’re applying
for jobs already?
Not yet.
I still have one more semester.
It’s actually a bit stressful.
I know my parents
will help me get a job,
but I don’t want that.
I want to get hired
on my own merit.
You know what?
The bigger problem is,
I don’t even know
what I really want anymore.
Didn’t you want to be a model?
That was just
a far-fetched dream.
Clyden, I can’t do
modeling as a career.
I’ll disappoint them.
Stop thinking
about what they want.
What do you want?
I want to showcase clothes.
Redefine beauty and—
tell stories through fashion
on a global stage.
Yeah.
I want to be
an international model.
But, what if
I’m not good enough?
I’m not even in shape.
You’re already rejecting
yourself even before it starts.
You’ll never know until you try.
Hey, don’t doubt yourself.
Should I start modeling?
You know what,
you definitely have
the look and the vibe.
I can help you.
I have such a good agent,
and they’re always
looking for people.
Actually,
a model friend
offered to help me.
Well, there you go!
It’s a sign.
But I haven’t decided yet.
You know my parents—
Parents!
Again with your parents?
What about you?
You have your own life, Maui.
Follow what you want
and do whatever makes you happy.
Your career is an
important part of your life.
Do what you actually want to do.
Yes, you’re right.
I’ll think about it.
Okay.
- Morning!
You’re up early.
Are you leaving already?
Yes, I have a quiz
in my first class.
Okay, wait. Hold on.
I made this for you.
What’s this?
Open it.
You cooked for me?
I hope you like it.
Thank you.
You’re welcome.
Maybe you have
some special requests?
I can cook your lunch everyday.
Cy, you don’t have to do that.
Come on, I insist.
Fine.
Sushi! I want sushi.
Sushi?
Sushi—
Yeah, no problem.
I can make that.
That’s easy.
Go now, you might be late.
Okay, thank you. Bye!
Bye.
Sam seems to be
in a good mood today.
What is this?
It’s just food.
Wow, Samantha!
You packed your lunch
for the first time?
That’s awesome!
Did you cook that?
Let me have a taste.
I can rate your food.
No! It’s all mine.
It’s all yours because
it was cooked by your
very own personal chef?
Hey, you’re smiling
from ear to ear.
For sure, your boyfriend
made that for you.
I can’t believe he actually
made this for me.
Sam: They taste good!
Next time, I hope
it has fewer calories.
I’m on a diet.
Cy: Don’t be picky.
Oh no, girls!
We’ve lost her.
She’s fallen so hard.
She’s fallen so in love.
Sam, just be careful, okay?
'Cause after the fall
usually comes the crash.
And sometimes it’s a very,
very hard impact.
She’s so annoying, right?
So dramatic!
Who? Naomi?
Yeah, I was just
about to say that.
Why is she even our friend
in the first place?
I don’t like her vibe!
I agree.
Naomi Vera is so moody.
Are they backstabbing Naomi?
Naomi Vera is so weird, right?
Like, where did she even
come from?
They’re really talking
about Naomi. This isn’t right.
Excuse me.
Yes?
It’s not good to talk about
people behind their backs.
If you’ve got
a problem with her,
just say it to her face.
What?
Who are you,
and why are you even listening
to other people’s
conversations, huh?
I’m your senior.
Your orgs must be ashamed
to have you as members.
What the hell? You’re weird!
Sam?
What are you doing?
God, you know her?
Well, I’m not surprised.
You’re both weird.
Right?
She suddenly shows up here
just to pick a fight?
What is her deal, really?
Go talk to her!
Let’s go.
Naomi, wait.
Let me explain—
- please.
- What’s your problem, Sam?
What exactly did
my friends do to you, huh?
They’re talking behind
your back, and I was just—
Are you planning to push
them away from me, too?
You just really want me
to end up alone, huh?
No, I was just—
Cut it out!
Stop meddling in my life!
Can’t you see that
the more you try to meddle,
the more you push
everyone away from me.
Dad,
your mom,
and now my friends?
Who’s next?
Jaron?
You want him out
of my life, too, right?
No, Naomi.
It’s not like that.
I was just trying to help and—
Please, just stop!
Stop playing the good sister!
It doesn’t suit you.
Mom: Maureen, I want you
to attend the party
of our business partner
this weekend.
I sent you three dresses.
Pick something
that will suit you.
Make sure you look elegant.
I don’t want to go.
Sam:
Cy, I’m having a bad day.
Sam: I feel tired.
Hey sorry.
Wrong send.
How are you?
Sam: Is everything okay?
Cy: What time
are you coming home?
Sam: I won’t go home tonight.
My friends are here
at the condo.
I’ll sleep here tonight.
Cy: It's better that
you sleep there.
Don't drive
if you've been drinking.
Enjoy your time
with your friends.
Sam: Okay.
Sam?
Hey,
Are you okay?
I just had a bad day.
What happened?
Should I tell them?
But I don’t want
to ruin the vibe.
Nothing. Just some school stuff.
You know, senior problems.
I think that’s the food.
What the hell
are you doing here?
Are you alone?
Yanna, you should
have called me!
I didn’t think about that.
I just hurriedly got on the bus
when I received your message.
Well? What happened to you?
Are you okay?
I’m okay.
Oh god, Yanna,
the whole group is here.
Sam, is the food there yet?
Oh, I thought
it was the delivery.
You want to come in?
Girls?
Yanna is here.
So, you're still alive.
You didn't even
bother to reach out.
You’re pregnant?
I’m sorry. I made a mis—
I’m so sorry, Yanna.
- I’m so sorry.
You were suffering alone,
and we didn’t know.
I’m so sorry.
I’m sorry,
I didn’t tell you sooner
because
I thought you all
might get mad at me.
I’m scared that
you might tell me
that I should have expected this
after all that I’ve done.
No. Yanna, I’m sorry.
We’re sorry that
you felt you had to
hide your pregnancy from us.
Yanna, I’m sorry.
I didn’t know what to do either.
Who’s the fa—
Nevermind.
Come, sit down.
That’s not important.
Sit here.
Hold on.
Be careful.
Cheers?
I’ll have water for now.
I can't drink alcohol yet.
Thanks for coming.
You said you were tired.
With everything
I’ve been through,
you've always been by my side.
So, when you’re feeling down,
I should also be by your side.
So, how are you?
I'm here to listen.
It's Naomi.
I heard some girls
were backstabbing her,
so I confronted them.
She saw me doing that
and she interpreted it
as me pushing her friends away.
You just did
what was right, okay?
You've been a good older sister.
Trust me,
she’ll get it eventually.
Just don’t get tired of being
a good sister to her, okay?
Thanks.
I think I just really
needed to hear that.
I thought it had something
to do with your love life.
Hey! Why aren’t you answering?
So there really
is an issue, huh?
Well, there’s no issue.
It’s more of a me problem.
Cy said he thinks that
he’s already
fallen in love with me.
What?
Then what’s the problem?
But I’m also
falling in love with him.
That’s perfect!
You’re falling
in love with each other.
But I'm scared of getting hurt.
I don’t know if
I can handle the heartbreak
if it doesn’t work out.
Come on!
Why are you already
thinking about the end?
Can’t you just enjoy the feeling
of falling in love?
Loving is amazing.
Being loved is amazing.
If you like him, just tell him!
If you keep waiting,
you might lose your chance.
And that's the most
important thing.
I really need to see him.
Then go! Go see him.
Thank you.
Hey, where are you going?
I just have to be somewhere.
I thought you
weren’t coming home?
Well, I’m here now.
Are you okay?
I’m tired.
I’m here.
What’s our problem, love?
Yes. I just want to come home.
To my home.
Who’s that?
My mom.
She’s just calling to remind me
about that event on Saturday.
What event?
A party for one
of our business partners.
I’m not in the mood to go.
Then don’t go.
But my mom will be
disappointed if I don’t go.
If I go with you,
will it make this party less
miserable?
A hundred percent.
All right, I’ll go with you.
Let’s just show up
and then bail.
- Really?
- Yes.
Thank you.
And it’s Naomi’s birthday
too this Saturday—
So, can we drop by our house and
give her my gift personally?
Yeah, of course.
But we'd better sleep now.
It's getting late.
Yes.
I need to wake up
early tomorrow too
‘cause Yanna visited
and I have to take her
back to Nueva Ecija.
Okay.
I’ll go downstairs now.
Cy.
Yes?
I—
Should I say it?
Should I confess now?
I appreciate everything you do.
Thanks, Maui.
I appreciate everything
that you do, too.
Maui, once we’re
officially together,
are we going to sleep
in the master’s bedroom?
I mean, sure.
If you want.
I’d want to.
Okay.
Rest well, okay?
- Good night.
Cy?
Hey!
You’re up early.
Didn’t I tell you I have
to head back to the condo
‘cause I still have
to take Yanna home?
Take this with you.
Sushi?
Yes.
Your special request.
This is my favorite.
You.
This looks like actual sushi.
Of course.
You’ve cooked this before,
haven’t you?
Yes, I have.
- Really?
- Yes, many times.
- Nice!
- This is basic.
Thanks.
Now, I definitely
won’t go hungry on the trip.
You’re welcome.
Wait a minute,
something’s still missing.
Let’s put this in here.
And this one’s
fruit juice for Yanna.
He cares about
my friends, too?
How cute.
Wow, you’re so thoughtful.
Thank you.
All right then. I’ll go now.
Okay. Drive safely.
Bye. Take care!
Preggy lady!
Stay there, I’ll handle this.
Go on, just stay there.
Bitch! If you two
didn’t break up,
you’d probably be
pregnant too, you know?
Wow.
Wow, this pregnant girl’s
too much.
Hey!
Hi!
Hey, Sam!
Where did you go
last night? You left us.
Sorry, girls.
I had an emergency.
But what happened last night?
Did Luna cry again?
You didn’t storm
into Kalix’s unit, did you?
Almost! Good thing
Ke stopped her.
She was about to
step into the elevator.
But yeah, that was the most
exciting thing that happened.
Nothing else.
Thank you for sharing!
- That’s all.
- Good thing you stopped her.
Crisis averted.
Right?
Hey! Give me a minute,
I’ll just get ready
so we can go, okay?
Hold on.
- Okay.
Yes?
Cy said to give this to you.
Wow!
Wooing the best friend, huh?
This is nice.
So, what else
happened last night?
Did you guys kiss?
Did you have sex?
No. It was just
wholesome. Come on.
But did you confess last night?
No, I didn’t.
Why didn’t you?
Maybe the moment wasn’t right,
and I was just waiting
for him to say it first,
then I would’ve said it too.
Sam!
What’s the story? Huh?
Do you have something to share?
I want to share it.
I really do.
But it’s just
not the right time.
I’ll tell my friends
when everything’s settled.
When it’s official.
When I’m sure.
I just had to go home.
There was an emergency
at home, that’s all.
Really?
Mom: Why are you not
answering my calls?
Don’t forget
the party this Saturday.
Sam: Yes, Mom.
I’m coming with Cy. See you.
Hey, calm down.
What did I say?
We’re just going
to show up and then bail.
Exactly.
Let me remind you,
I’m your fiancé.
I know.
And we don’t have
to pretend now.
What do you mean?
Come on, let’s go inside.
Hey!
I’ve been waiting for you
for a while now.
Come on, let me introduce you
to my business partner.
Mr. Barrera,
this is my daughter, Sam.
And her fiancé, Clyden Ramirez.
Hello, Sam.
I can tell by your looks that
you take after your father.
Nice to meet you,
Sam and Clyden.
You know that’s true. In fact,
Sam will be
graduating soon and—
I’m sure I'm going to be
able to convince her
to follow in
my footsteps, right?
A future politician?
That’s great!
Someone to continue
Senator Vera’s legacy.
And for sure,
we will be
working together, Sam.
Actually, I’m still figuring out
what career I want to pursue.
I’m thinking of something
more in the arts.
I’ve always had
an interest in other fields,
you know, like modeling.
Modeling?
Isn’t it, well…
Politics is more impactful.
That’s where
real power is made, Sam.
You know, Sam, she’s just
exploring her options.
You know, the young ones today.
- But she’ll come around.
- That's right.
I did the same thing,
I started with law before
I decided to go into business.
It’s okay.
I’m 90% decided, actually.
I want to be a model.
And I think it’s a career
that will make me happy
and fulfilled.
Please excuse us.
We’ll just grab our drinks.
Kids nowadays.
Yeah. I’m sorry
about that, you know—
I’m proud of you.
You’re taking little steps
to assert yourself.
I’m not going to lie.
I was nervous the entire time.
I’m sure my mom
is upset right now.
Well, let her be upset.
It’s your life to live.
Not hers.
Naomi: Help. Unit 6336.
Why is she there?
Why does she need help?
What’s that?
Naomi is asking for help.
- What?
- We need to go!
What the hell
are you doing here?
Where’s Naomi?
She’s having fun. Relax.
We’re just
celebrating her birthday.
Naomi?
Help, Sam!
-Naomi?
What’s happening here, huh?
Naomi.
Sam, what’s up?
What the hell did you do
to my sister, huh?
I was just talking to her.
I came here to
celebrate her birthday
because her friends said
she really likes me.
I thought, why not
make her happy, right?
Do you think she’s fucking
happy right now?
Look at her! She’s crying!
Oh, come on!
We were playing truth or dare.
We just dared her
to stay in the same room
with Jaron for 30 minutes.
Shut up!
We’re going.
Don’t ever talk
to my sister again.
I’ll go to your room, okay?
What happened?
Did they do anything to you?
No.
He was telling me
all about his girlfriend, Rina,
and the things they do together.
He made me
feel so uncomfortable.
He even said that we could be
together without Rina knowing.
He made me feel
like I’m desperate,
I’m a fool.
I’m sorry.
I already knew
about him and Rina.
I should have told you,
I’m so sorry.
No, Sam.
Maybe I was a fool.
Maybe I was desperate.
No, you’re not.
You’re not.
No. Just admit it, Sam.
I defended my
fake friends over you.
I was desperate to
keep them as my friends
because I have no one.
Naomi—
you have me.
You have me.
You just feel sorry,
and you pity me.
That’s not true.
No. It is true.
Why would you want to be
with someone like me?
You have your friends,
you have your parents,
you have your fiancé.
I’m all alone by myself.
Maybe it’s better this way
because the last time
I had someone in my life,
she died because of me.
I’m sorry.
I’m sorry you’re
going through this.
Eighteen years of existence,
and half of it
was barely living.
I’m here for you.
You’re not alone.
And I want you
in my life, Naomi.
You might not accept me now,
but I hope that you will, soon.
And we’ll get through
this together, okay?
Remember, I’m your sister.
You’ll always have me
as your big sister.
Hug?
Happy birthday.
My gift.
I hope this makes
your day a little bit better.
Now, you don’t have
to borrow my camera
‘cause you already
have your own
and it’s even a newer model.
You’re a great older sister.
Thank you.
You’re welcome,
my little sister.
Hey.
How did it go?
We talked.
It was hard,
but we’re getting there.
Baby steps.
I’m so proud of you
for being a big sister to her.
You showed up
when she needed you.
You’re really
a beautiful person, Maui.
I love you.
How do you know
if you’re falling in love?
Maybe you have
some special requests?
I can cook your lunch everyday.
Sushi! I want sushi.
When you start doing
generous things.
Even if it means
losing sleep.
When you find yourself
putting in effort
you never knew you had.
Cy?
Hey!
You’re up early.
Take this with you.
Sushi?
Your special request.
This looks like actual sushi.
Of course.
You’ve cooked this before,
haven’t you?
Yes, I have.
I’ll just go to the restroom.
Okay.
I heard, the daughter
of Stephen Vera
is entering politics too.
I won't be surprised
if she ends up like him.
Corrupt politician.
When you find yourself
defending the person
- even when she’s not around.
- For sure,
they’ll turn it
into a family business.
Getting money from
the government funds.
Wow, shameless people.
What if the daughter is worse?
When it feels like
it’s your responsibility
to protect her honor.
Excuse me.
I overheard your conversation.
I don’t mean to overstep, but
Sam isn’t like
her parents at all.
She’s a good person.
And she’s got
a strong moral compass.
Even as a college student,
she’s already involved
in a lot of charity work.
And no,
she’s not entering politics.
Excuse me.
When you want
to take her pain away,
because if she’s hurting,
you’re hurting the same.
I love you.
When you know, you know.
Cy, hi—
Are we together now?
Hey,
are we like,
a boyfriend-girlfriend
thing now?
So, what are we doing
for your birthday?
Got any plans?
Same club as last time?
I plan to host
the party at BGC.
Don’t invite him, please.
Whatever happens,
your big sister’s here for you.
Happy birthday!
Lewis!
Wait, I think
there’s something in your—
- What?
- An eyelash.
Goodbye! Enjoy!