Since you won't help
I'll do it then.
Since you don't wanna get involved in,
I'll step up instead.
I'll make sure you stay out of it.
Is that okay?
Chen Yi.
I'm here.
See Miss Gu home safely.
Miss Gu is strange...
You also think so?
She's always respectful to you.
But today...
it's like she comes here
to have a quarrel.
I reckon she's on purpose.
She wanna save Mrs. Nie and Xiangyun
And she knows I
have my reservations.
So she took this chance
to have a quarrel with me
and let the whole matter drop.
If Miss Gu
planned it in this way,
she's really thoughtful.
Yes,
she is.
With this quarrel,
Mr. Chen is finally separated
from the whole affair.
Yep.
But I haven't thought
Lord Nie
angered Mr. Chen on purpose.
Miss Gu...
Is...
Isn't this
the crime of deceit?
Don't ever
mention this again.
Keep it to yourself.
Yes, Miss.
How about
Mrs. Nie?
I found an old colleague of Lord Nie
from his days at Tongzhou Garrison
Mr. Lv.
He runs an embroidery workshop.
His family fell on hard times
but with fifty taels
Lord Nie gave him back then
as startup capital,
he managed to build up the business.
I told him about
Mrs. Nie's plight
and Mr. Lv
agreed to help
right away.
He wanna hire Mrs. Nie
as an instructor at his workshop
with room and board provided
and one more tael every month.
Does Mrs. Nie
agree?
She's sensible
She said yes the moment I told her.
Tomorrow,
I'll have men
secretly send her and her daughter
to the backyard behind the workshop.
The Nies will never
find them.
Great.
This settles
one of my biggest wishes.
Thank you, Mr. Ping.
You're welcome.
Aunt,
these are premium fried crisp rolls.
Fermented bean curd of Jin's
are in these jars.
These
are all your favorites.
I specially brought them for you.
Once you eat them up,
just let me know.
I'll have more delivered right away.
Alright, alright.
These are top-grade pine soot ink
and Writing Brush from Huzhou.
These are for Uncle.
You can keep them,
or send to others as gifts.
Either way, they're perfect.
Inside this big chest
are all the fabrics
Grandma picked out
for Jinzhao.
She asked me to bring them along.
Good.
Very good.
We're family.
You've come to the capital to study,
and we should look after you.
Yet you
bring so many gifts.
We're family.
No need for such formality.
Tonight,
treat Mr. Ji
with a slap-up meal
at Baiweiju Restaurant.
Okay.
By the way, where's Jinzhao?
There's business today
and she goes to do with it.
Fetch her back at once.
Mr. Ji is here.
Okay.
No hurry.
Nanny,
go check out the front.
As soon as Jinzhao's back,
tell her to come over quickly.
Okay.
Aunt,
there're some books on my carriage.
I don't trust the servants with them.
I need to go check.
Alright.
Suit yourself.
Once you're settled,
let nanny take you
to the guest quarters.
You must be worn out
from the long journey.
Thanks.
Ji!
What's wrong?
Why do you come alone?
Where's Grandma?
She's at home.
Is she ill?
I heard lots of trouble broke out at home
because of the land equalization.
She's fine.
Don't worry.
Really?
Don't lie to me.
She's really fine.
In a few days,
she'll come to the capital
to deliver Yulin Tuce herself.
Keep it secret.
Really?
So...
Has the land equalization finished?
Great!
Ji,
you must be tired.
Let me take you to have a rest.
No need.
I...I can go by myself.
What happened to you?
You've had your coming-of-age ceremony.
So...
what?
Does that mean
we can't
be together?
Where did you pick up such stuffy old-fashioned talk?
Stuffy talk?
You're a lady now,
and we're not in Tongzhou.
I'm only doing this
for your own good.
You're grown up.
Time to be sensible.
Enough.
I'm leaving.
Miss,
what Mr. Ji said does make sense.
Don't be upset.
I'm not.
I know he means well.
But in fact,
he's not just for my sake.
He's really afraid Grandma
will marry me off to him.
As if I'd ever marry him!
Thinks he's such a catch.
Cunshan Academy
is famed as No.1 in the capital.
It's not easy to study there.
Getting admitted
is quite an achievement.
It's all thanks to Xuruo.
Had he not written me a recommendation letter,
I'd never get admitted.
Xuruo?
Mr. Chen's nephew,
Chen Xuanqing.
Ji,
you'll be schoolmates with Xuanqing?
He's done you such a big favor.
We must prepare a generous gift
to thank him.
Grandma has got it ready.
I'll take it
when registering tomorrow.
Okay.
Ji,
you're going to the academy tomorrow?
I'll go with you.
What for?
To see you off.
As your younger sister,
I should send you off
to study in the capital.
Jinzhao's right.
If my health weren't so frail,
I'd also go see you off.
Let's talk over dinner.
Okay.
Mr. Ji,
cheers.
Jinzhao.
I can reach it.
What a future pillar of the nation!
What are you doing, mom?
We were having dinner.
Why did you pinch me?
So you felt it huh?
I thought you wouldn't notice.
Of course I noticed.
I also know
you pinched me to make me
go with Jinzhao and Brother Ji
to the academy together.
You know it, but still play dumb.
Cause' I don't wanna go.
Why not?
It's such a great chance.
Mr. Ji is close
with Chen Xuanqing.
You know Xuanqing well.
If you go along,
and spend time with him
after a few meetings,
something might come of it.
Come of what?
It's Jinzhao who likes
Xuanqing,
not me.
What?
Jinzhao fancies Chen Xuanqing?
Exactly.
She told you?
No need.
It's as plain as day,
impossible to miss.
I've known it for a long time.
No wonder Mrs. Ji
cozies up to the Chen.
So that's what she's after.
Though Chen Xuanqing
bears the Chen surname,
he is just adopted.
What he will achieve
is still uncertain.
Exactly.
Lan,
I know you have no interest
in Chen Xuanqing.
I won't force you.
But you need to understand
anyone admitted to Cunshan Academy
is not ordinary.
You're soon to come of age.
Go along tomorrow,
and you might meet a good match.
No.
My destiny
doesn't lie
in some academy.
You...
How's he?
He's recovered well
and out of danger now.
The prescription from the earlier doctor
suits his illness.
Just keep taking it.
However,
his heart condition is treacherous.
From now on, Mr. Ye
must carry his medicine at all times.
Don't neglect it.
Thank you.
I shall take my leave then.
It seems that
Doctor Xiao's medicine works best.
This works well too.
With the Imperial Medical Academy's confirmation,
we'll have
a proper reason
to get out of the Eastern Palace.
What?
You want me to leave?
I've heard Chen Yanyun is strict.
He pushes you to study nonstop,
and has you flogged at every turn.
Seeing your hands all bruised last time
tore my heart apart.
The Crown Prince is destined to rule.
You don't need to sit the imperial exam.
Our Marquis Manor
has only you as the sole heir.
How can we bear
seeing you suffer like this?
Come back, okay?
I'm not coming back.
Why must you
insist on staying in the Palace?
But I've already
talked to your dad about this.
Then go tell him again.
I'm not leaving anyway.
But...
No buts.
Please take your leave, mom.
I have a headache.
My Lord,
when your heart ailment flared up,
it was all thanks to Miss Gu
who saved you.
Shouldn't we
go thank her?
You sly lad.
You look honest and plain,
yet you're quite sharp.
But you're right.
I, Ye Xian,
never leave a kindness unpaid.
Prepare a gift tomorrow.
I'll call on the Gu residence.
Okay.
Greetings, Mr. Ye.
My respects, Mr. Ye.
Is Gu Jinzhao here?
Let her come out.
I have words to say to her.
What a pity!
Miss Gu has gone to the academy.
Academy?
Cousin Ji is
enrolling at Cunshan Academy.
He's registering today.
My mom asked her to go along.
Why?
I have no idea.
Maybe now that she's come of age,
she needs to socialize more
and go out in society.
Socialize, indeed.
Going to a place full of young men
perfect for seeking a marriage match.
Please don't put it that way.
My Lord,
should we head to
Cunshan Academy for Miss Gu?
Why would I go looking for her?
Am I that bored?
Didn't you say
you wanted to repay her kindness?
Who said I wanna repay her?
Forget it.
In a few days,
send her an invitation.
Tell her
I'm inviting her to dine with me.
Yes, my Lord.
Giddy up!
What lovely scenery!
Truly an ideal place for studying.
It calms the mind and lifts the spirit.
Yes.
When the old academy head chose the site,
he picked it at once for its hills and rivers.
He also sent for craftsmen
all the way from Suzhou to design it.
It took five years to complete.
No wonder.
If only I could
study in such a
wonderful place like this.
I agree.
So many women in the world
are full of knowledge and talent,
yet held back by old customs.
To be honest, Miss Gu,
the academy head has two daughters.
He's long wanted
to find a proper place
and open a school for girls.
Really?
When that happens,
please remember
to let me know.
I'm at the academy too.
If you want to know something,
I can tell you myself.
No need to trouble Xuruo.
You?
By the time you tell me,
the school will have opened,
and all spots taken.
What do you mean?
Do you think
I'd stand in your way
and stop you from learning?
I wouldn't put it past you.
Two years ago,
I found a nice shop in Baoping.
I just didn't have enough money that day.
I'd settled with the owner
to come back the next day.
But then what happened?
You rented it for yourself
with 10% more.
Knowing how you love
spoiling things for others for no reason,
I...
who knows what you might do next.
I rented that shop
for the Ji's own good.
Besides,
you only sell
rouge and cosmetics anyway.
Did you really need such a great shop?
What I sell is none of your business.
Snatching what I'm keen on
is simply bad manners.
- I...
- You guys
Inside there
is the reception hall.
Sorry for the quarrel, Xuruo.
We'll go pay our respects now.
Mr. Chen,
I'll wait for you over there.
Please take Mr. Ji in.
He always
speaks his mind without restraint.
I'd be grateful if you
could look after him.
There's a pavilion ahead.
If you are tired,
you can rest there.
Thank you.
Let's go.
With gentle breeze and verdant hills,
nothing blocks the white clouds flying free.
Mr. Chen wrote this?
Miss Gu.
Mr. Chen?
Why are you alone?
Where's Ji?
The academy head is testing him.
It's not proper for me to stay there,
so I stepped out.
Your calligraphy
is truly exquisite.
The charm and spirit in it
resemble your father quite a lot.
I have indeed studied calligraphy
from my father all these years.
Yet even after long practice,
I still fall far short of his skill.
You're too modest.
Looking at all the works on this wall,
yours is the best.
So your father likes to
copy Liu Gongquan's calligraphy.
You have a sharp eye, Miss Gu.
He admires Liu Gongquan
for his open and firm temperament.
He says I'm too reserved,
and tells me to practice Liu's style more.
Did he ever say
which model to start with
when learning Liu's calligraphy?
Stele Inscription of Xuanmi Pagoda?
He likes Vajracchedika-sutra Pagoda.
Why on earth
write Vajracchedika-sutra Pagoda?
You're so late!
Obviously you got lectured.
I did not!
How did your talk go
with the academy head?
He's very kind.
He didn't say too much
but gave me a quite challenging question.
What question?
Share with us.
The question
is something I've
never thought about before.
Did you
find out anything?
Yes.
That rascal Luo Guier
refused to tell me at first.
But once I gave him
half a tael of loose silver,
he spilled everything.
He said he didn't see much,
only that when Chen Xuanqing
picked them up from the academy,
Miss Gu looked
happier than Ji.
I knew Miss Gu
has her eye on Chen Xuanqing.
Miss,
Miss?
What happened?
It's been almost an hour,
and you're still staring at the same page.
Qingpu, let me ask you.
What do you
think of Chen Xuanqing?
Why bring him up
all of a sudden?
These days,
I've been thinking...
If I hadn't found a way myself
to get out of the marriage with Liu,
I'd have been married off.
Marrying into that family
would be a lifetime sentence.
In that household,
mom's words
carry no real weight.
As for my dad,
don't even get me started.
I'd be thankful enough
if he doesn't ruin my life.
If I wanna
live a comfortable life,
I must decide
my own marriage.
So Miss...
do you mean
you fancy Xuanqing?
I do think he's quite decent.
What do you think, Qingpu?
Well...
He's the top provincial scholar,
talented,
and gentle in nature.
But he's an adopted son.
I have no idea what life
is really like in the Chen Manor.
No one
is perfect.
Miss Gu.
Nanny, what brings you here so late?
Greetings, Miss.
Madam sent me to pass a message.
Grandma will arrive in the capital tomorrow morning
Madam's afraid she can't welcome her
cause' she feels unwell.
Miss, please go welcome on behalf of her.
Great!
Grandma's coming!
Yes.
So heavy!
Why hasn't Grandma arrived yet?
Wasn't she coming to deliver the Yulin Tuce?
Why are there so many dead bodies?
I'm afraid she's been attacked.
I'll go find Grandma.
I'd like to go too.
Stay here.
So many have been killed.
Take care, Ji.
Mr. Chen?
Miss Gu.
Mr. Chen told me to inform you
Mrs. Ji is sorting the accounts,
and will be out shortly.
Thank you
and Mr. Chen.
Grandma!
Your hair has turned white...
Are you alright?
You scared me to death.
I'm fine.
My dear.
Sir,
this time in Tongzhou Prefecture,
we oversaw Sanhe
Baodi,
Wuqing,
Huoxian,
these four counties.
After land surveying in full,
a total of 1,363,221 mu
[1 mu≈0.1647 acre]
of farmland was registered.
We compiled the Household Registers
and Yulin Tuce,
all storing in sixteen chests.
They are all here.
Please
examine them.
Yulin Tuce
record every household's land
across our Great Yan.
With these records,
the court can truly
control all taxes and corvée nationwide.
Only then do we know
how much manpower and resources are needed,
and where these
shall be sourced.
Only in this way
can all lands under heaven
be firmly brought
under imperial rule.
This is the foundation
of eternal peace and governance.
Great!
Congratulations, your Excellency
Congratulations, Sir.
Tongzhou has set an example
for the Great Yan.
You have rendered great merit.
And as for
Mrs. Ji,
she deserves great credit.
Together with all the local gentry
who lent their support,
grant them rewards in full.
I
speak on behalf of Mrs. Ji
to thank you, Sir.
It is only a pity...
What's wrong?
I cannot help
thinking of Fengming.
You've always been
a man of loyalty and sentiment.
Yet the time
has not come to petition rewards for him.
Yes, Sir.
How goes the investigation into
Your Highness' assassination?
Xiao Qishan has been investigated.
No report has returned.
But I have given strict orders:
Bring him back alive,
or bring back his body.
Make the search thorough.
Now that
His Majesty gets older,
he has grown far more lenient.
Prince Glorian is the
late Prince Chengqing's younger brother,
and His Majesty's only living sibling.
To move against him,
we must have irrefutable proof.
Okay.
You!
You insolent little brute!
Might as well
have it put down at once.
Wait!
Uncle Li,
it was wrong for Frost to bite you,
but it just bit through your clothes.
Not even a tooth mark was left.
Must you be so unforgiving?
You're indeed clever.
Does...
this mean...
in your opinion,
I must wait until the brute
bites me till I bleed,
before I may punish it?
That is not what I meant.
Indeed, Prince Glorian.
Son of a bitch!
You!
I'm speaking with him.
When did you get leave to interrupt?
You deserve to be beaten to death.
Guards!
Hold on!
Minister Ye!
Greetings, Your Highness.
Greetings, Prince Glorian.
So you are the one unfit for martial arts,
unable to go to the battlefield—
the heir of Lord Changxing?
Ye Guangsheng enjoyed a lifetime of fame.
What a pity!
One wonders
if this is his retribution.
I never thought you believed in karma.
If so,
the sudden death of your heir of Lord Chongguang in Tongzhou
must also be your karma.
You!
What a sharp tongue you have!
What are you doing here?
Frost has been unwell.
His Highness sent me to check on it.
I didn't expect just as it caused trouble.
May I ask where
Frost bit you?
Your Highness,
it was by the outer wall
at the north corner gate of the Eastern Palace.
Frost had indigestion,
and I was walking it there.
Then
we met Prince Glorian.
The north corner gate of the Eastern Palace...
It is very remote.
May I ask why you
went all the way out there?
Yes.
I almost forgot to ask.
Uncle Li, why would you
go outside the Eastern Palace?
I
entered the palace to congratulate His Majesty
on the successful land equalization in Tongzhou.
On my way out,
I just passed by the Eastern Palace.
What a fortunate "coincidence"
you have!
You...
Yes.
Uncle, coming all the way to this remote place,
what business do you have here?
Why did you not send word beforehand?
Does my Father know your visit?
I just think the weather is fine
and come out for a stroll.
I don't think there's a need.
It is 12 o'clock.
I have other affairs to attend to,
and shall not waste time
bickering here.
Goodbye.
Stand up.
Ye Xian,
what do you make of that old fox
sneaking around
outside the Eastern Palace?
I dare not speculate.
You dare not?
Then I dare.
Maybe this guy
was scouting the place.
Your Highness,
don't...
What are you afraid of?
Ye Xian is one of us.
Mom.
Having the two of you
attending to me like this,
somehow I feel
ill at ease.
Alright, alright.
Sit down and rest.
Let Jinzhao rest.
It has been so long since we met.
I wanna attend to you and show my filial piety.
I won't!
I wanna stay right here
and look after Grandma.
Very well, dear.
Mom,
can you stay a few more days this time?
I'm afraid not.
I've come on official business.
Early tomorrow morning,
I need to go to the Chen Manor to visit Mr. Chen.
The land equalization in Tongzhou went smoothly.
Next will be Beizhili.
I suspect Mr. Chen wanted me
to take charge of the next task.
After all,
I've had the experience.
But...
Mr. Chen really ought not to.
Land equalization is dangerous enough as it is,
and you're up in years.
Why treat you like an able-bodied laborer?
There's no other choice.
Grandma,
Let me go with you tomorrow.
Okay.
At your age,
you ought to go out
and see more of the world.
The land equalization in Tongzhou
was a great success.
When Lord Chief Councilor spoke of your merits
to His Majesty,
he was greatly pleased.
You'll
be granted official rewards shortly.
I merely followed
Mr. Chen's instructions.
I dare not claim any credit.
Lord Chief Councilor intends that
one province in the south
and one in the north
shall be chosen for further pilot.
Grandma!
Jinzhao,
what brings you here?
Greetings, Sir.
I saw Mrs. Chen
growing anxious waiting,
so I volunteered
to come fetch you.
My old friend
has always been impetuous.
Sir,
I shall take my leave first.
Okay.
If I have any doubts
about official affairs in days to come,
I shall seek your counsel.
You flatter me.
Mr. Chen, your ink bamboo painting
grows ever more vivid and lifelike.
Sir.
You're here.
Come in and speak.
You knew I'd come?
Your manner just now
shows you have something on your mind.
Speak. What do you seek of me?
I beg you
not to send my grandma
to take part in the land equalization of Beizhili.
Did your grandma send you to say this?
No, no, no.
It is my own thoughts.
Then your grandma must have
spoken to you about Beizhili's affairs.
Nope.
She has never told me
anything about land equalization.
I figured it out myself.
I reasoned that
now that it has succeeded in Tongzhou,
the next task might be Beizhili.
Then it will continue south along the Grand Canal.
You know far more than I expected.
You once told me
land equalization is a grave state affair,
and since ancient times,
it has never been achieved without bloodshed.
In Tongzhou this time,
it nearly cost
Grandma half her life.
I am afraid...
I...
I beg you to
let my Grandma
retire from all land equalization duties.
I can take over all
of Grandma's responsibilities.
If blood must be shed,
let it be mine.
You?
You cannot take the place
of your Grandma.
I can!
Everyone knows
Grandma dotes on me most.
If I stand forth
on behalf of Grandma and the Jis,
all will trust me.
Furthermore,
whether it be contacting local gentry,
or planning calculations,
I am fully capable.
I know the lands of Beizhili well.
If there is anything I do not know,
I can consult my Grandma.
Listening to you,
one would think land equalization
is a trivial matter
anyone can do.
It is surely no easy task,
but
I'm willing to learn.
Grandmother is advanced in years,
her strength fading.
I am still young,
and fear no hardship
in traveling to and fro.
Miss Gu,
this is a matter of imperial court importance,
not a trifling matter.
Chen Yi.
Sir!
Grandma is old,
and she has never
spent a day of peace and leisure.
Please.
spare my grandmother from this toil.
Show her out.
Yes, Sir.
Miss Gu,
this way please.
Sir,
had you not decided
to have Mrs. Ji write down
Tongzhou's experience
and spare her from Beizhili?
This is a matter of great gravity.
I can excuse her from going,
yet I can't yield to her plea.
If I grant her wish after that,
what will the court make of me?
I can't help but feel
you were just teasing Miss Gu.
By the way,
Mrs. Chen asked me the other day
to arrange a marriage for you,
and bid me ask you.
Right,
I heard of the southwest a few days ago.
There seems to be a lead on Xiao Qishan.
I think
you need to go there in person.
Is that okay?
The New Year is coming,
and bandits run rampant in the southwest.
Delay will be dangerous.
Set off tomorrow.
Okay.
Might as well return to my hometown.
Such a petty mind.
Take care of yourself.
Holding such a high office,
yet he remains so petty.
Not even a single room
for discussion.
Xuanqing?
Miss Gu?
I returned to the manor to fetch a few books today,
never expecting
to meet you here.
I came with my grandma
to pay respects to Mrs. Chen.
Xuanqing,
what book are you reading?
Better be deemed cunning than a false loyalist.
Better be unyielding than a worldly conformist.
This book is interesting.
Its criticisms are refreshingly blunt.
Are you in a hurry to read this book?
Xuanqing,
there you are.
I've been searching for you.
Miss Gu.
There's no hurry.
If you like it,
just take it and read it.
Fine, thank you.
I have to go.
My Grandma is waiting for me.
Okay.
Giddy up!
Miss Qingpu, wait a moment.
Stop.
Miss Qingpu,
Mr. Chen  sent me
with a letter for Mrs. Ji.
Grandma,
what does the letter read?
It read that
considering my advanced age,
the Jis is excused
from further land equalization affairs.
I just need to record my experience
in a book,
and hand it in to the court.
Really?
That's great!
You can finally
rest from all that traveling and toil.
Yes.
It seems Mr. Chen
does have consideration for the Jis.
Grandma returns
to Tongzhou tomorrow,
and you need to get up early.
Xuanqing never set a fixed date
for the book's return.
Why stay up
poring over it by lamp light?
You'll strain your eyes.
Now that Grandma
can head back to Tongzhou safe and sound,
my heart is at peace too.
But for this book,
Xuanqing went all the way back
from the academy just to fetch it.
It must matter.
He kindly lent it to me,
and I cannot be ungrateful.
I must finish it quickly
and return it to him.
What are you laughing at?
I'm laughing at how you keep saying "he" about Xuanqing.
You've said it three times.
I'm just saying.
Hurry and grind the ink.