[Fated Hearts – My Deep Feelings You Don't Understand]
[On-set of “Fated Hearts”] [Filming in progress]
[Hair sticking to face]
The wind won't stop blowing.
[Hair covering face]
Hair.
[You too]
Your earlobe.
[Let me help you]
[Mutual aid]
Hair.
Again.
One more time.
[Hairstylist emergency online]
The wind's getting worse.
What now?
Come on.
You can do it.
[Self-encouragement]
[Action!]
Don't cry.
[Awkward]
I'm not crying.
[Stubborn]
It's just too windy earlier.
Where's the wind even coming from indoors?
Doesn't matter—
the wind's just too strong.
Don't worry.
[Deep affection]
I'm here.
I won't let the wind or sand blow on you again.
[Exchange a smile]
[Blows gently]
[Teasing]
I helped you blow away that awful strand of hair.
[And you're not even thanking me?]
You blew it away with your hand!
Like this.
I'm being so affectionate here.
He's right there.
I said—
I'll never let the wind and sand blow on you again.
[No giggling]
[Giggling]