Doc, you’re trending
online right now.
I don’t know what
you’re referring to,
but sir, can we please
focus on your health?
We’re not even close
with the Vera family anymore.
And we even cancelled
the engagement of our son.
Why aren’t you answering me?
I’m sorry.
He’s already struggling with
his life without our support.
And a scandal like this
will burden him even more.
So please don’t add to it.
If you find someone else,
I hope she can
truly make you happy.
Don’t cry, baby.
You’re making me cry, too.
Let me hold you, bestie.
You’re making us all cry.
I just wanna say that
I’m really, really gonna miss you.
It’s been three years since
I’ve moved to New York.
Modeling…
Partying…
Meeting new friends…
Travelling around the
world doing what I love.
I’ve already
achieved my dreams.
Are you happy for me, Naomi?
You’re not here anymore, but,
you’ve brought out
the best in me.
And I’m genuinely happy now.
I did have to step back from
doing runway though.
It just got too tiring.
And I still do go
to Fashion Week.
But only as a guest.
And honestly,
I’m happier this way.
Just enjoying myself
doing what I truly want…
Freely.
And now, I get to
pursue other dreams.
I’m opening a club in Manila.
It’s actually surprising.
Haze helped me a lot.
And now, I’m heading home.
After everything,
I really miss getting to
share all these moments
with my friends.
And—
with him.
I haven’t really talked to Cy
for the past three years.
We did message a few times.
Birthdays. Special occasions.
But we haven’t messaged
again since then.
Maybe it’s for the best.
Maybe he’s moved on.
I’m not sure.
But if it’s true,
I’m happy for him.
As for me, I have no plans of
getting married or having kids.
I’m just focusing
on myself now.
So—
I’m just excited to go home.
[Sam] All packed and ready!
[Yanna] Should we pick you up?
[Yanna] I’ll have Sevi pick you up.
[Sam] Yes, please. Thank you!
- Hey! It’s Samantha Vera!
- Sam!
Sam!
- Hi!
- Can we take a picture with you?
Yeah, sure.
Thank you.
Please take a
picture with us too.
- Thank you.
- Hello, can we take a picture?
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
Hi, guys.
- Hi.
- Thank you.
Hello.
- Sev!
- Welcome back!
Thanks a lot.
Oh man, I really
missed the Philippines.
A lot has changed, actually.
Just like you!
You’ve changed a lot, huh.
Maybe you’re just
talking about my muscles.
They got bigger, didn’t they?
How are you?
Have you been well?
You’re talking to
the new Head Engineer
at Valeria Construction.
Wow! You’re still full of yourself.
How about you,
how have you been?
You're really so famous now.
And you even know
my favorite actor!
Didn’t I tell you
to bring a fansign?
Is that still a thing nowadays?
I have his number.
I can just text him.
How about a video
greeting instead?
Just kidding!
But seriously, Sam, you’re
super famous here now.
You’ve got tons
of ads in the mall
and even a billboard along EDSA.
Big time!
Yeah.
Also—
don’t you find it weird when
people take videos of you?
I used to dream about this.
The fame, the attention.
But now, I’m not so sure.
I just hope it doesn’t
end up like before.
I can’t go
through that again.
Let’s go.
- Let me help you with that.
- All right.
Okay. Thank you.
Sam Vera is back!
Is she here for good?
How’s her love life kaya?
What is she up to next?
So, Sam, are you finally going
to renovate your condo?
It’s totally empty.
Yes, but I might need some help
so I can finish it quickly.
Want me to help you out?
Sure, why not?
Well, the best engineer
for the job
is literally right in front of you.
Wow. The best.
Sam!
Luna!
I miss you!
Hey, chill! Me too!
Ke!
- You’re so pretty.
- You guys too.
You smell so good!
You smell like—
Like a rich lady.
That’s our diva.
You’re so loud.
Aren’t you gonna
compliment me too?
But Sevi, you smell like cement.
What a moron.
Wow! Speak for yourself.
Well, anyway, are you guys
also helping Sam
renovate her condo?
- Huh?
- What?
You’re renovating it?
Yes.
I’m in. Luna and I will
handle the design, right?
Yes! I’ll make it look
amazing so that
when guys come over, bang!
Speaking of banging…
Well? How’s your love life?
- Haven't heard anything.
- You know what, guys—
I’m still single.
Seriously? Single or just
waiting for someone?
Who was that again? That…
- Doc, Doc Clyden.
- It’s—
- Clyden?
- Him.
What? No! Come on—
No? Seriously?
No contact?
I only see him through
his social media.
We kinda drifted apart,
so I don’t think
there’s any chance
for us to reconnect.
And besides, my love life is not
the focus right now, okay?
Right. Of course.
The opening of my club
is my priority right now.
Yes.
Right? So, you guys are coming.
- When is it again?
- Yes.
Actually, it’s coming up soon.
I’m checking the place tomorrow.
Just make sure you come, okay?
Don’t you dare miss it.
Of course!
- We missed you!
- Me too!
Is the renovation free, though?
Of course! It’s you
we're talking about!
Okay!
- That’s up to the boss now.
- We’re in need, you know?
Come on.
- Yeah!
- No!
Beautiful, right?
Yes, it’s better than I expected.
All right, fine.
You did a good job.
Thank you for taking care of
the club while I was away.
Of course. All for you.
Now, I need to order
a ton of alcohol.
I’ll just call the suppliers later.
Have you contacted the event
organizer for the opening?
Yup, already did.
Didn’t I tell you?
I’m such a good boy.
I already ordered everything,
even the booze.
They should arrive this week.
What can I do without you?
Damn, that sounded so fake.
The only thing missing
now is your guest list.
Have you thought about it?
Should I invite him?
What do you think?
Who? Cy?
Are you still in love with him?
You two just can't
get over each other.
What do you mean?
Nothing. Invite him if you want.
I know you’re just making
an excuse to see him,
but go for it.
Who knows?
Maybe he’s just waiting
for you, too, right?
Anyway, if that’s
the only thing left,
I’ll head out now.
Okay.
You can figure that
one out on your own.
You’re old enough.
- Bye.
Yanna.
Sam, it’s Avi…
Why are you crying?
She fell down the stairs.
I just turned my back
for a second,
and when I looked again,
she was already unconscious!
What?
Where are you? I’ll go there.
We’re already at
the Emergency Room.
All right. I’m coming.
Send me the location, okay?
Bye.
Yeah! I’m here now, Haze.
Okay.
- Sam.
- How are you?
Worried about Avi.
How is she, Doc?
We’re still monitoring her,
but everything's going well.
Don’t worry.
Thanks, Doc.
Excuse me.
Maui.
Yes?
Do you wanna get
some food with me?
I didn’t expect us to
see each other again
in this situation.
It’s the worst.
Hey, but you don’t
have to worry.
Avi is in good hands.
The experts are
taking care of her.
Let’s just hope for the best.
Yeah.
Hey,
I went to one of your shows.
The lingerie show.
I watched it in person.
He saw me in my lingerie?
You looked so amazing.
Did I make your head
turn with my walk?
You always do.
Where’d you get
your ticket, by the way?
From Haze.
I just mention Haze,
and you blush immediately?
I’m blushing not because of him.
Why didn’t you call me when
you attended my show?
I just thought, maybe,
you didn’t want to see me.
But it’s okay.
Seeing you from afar was
already enough for me.
Why wouldn’t I want to see you?
You never contacted me.
I wanted to. A lot of times.
But, I didn’t want to
give you false hopes.
Maybe because you’d wait for me,
even if I had no plans
of coming back.
Even if there was no hope,
I’d still wait.
Were you waiting for me
to come back?
I told you to find
another woman.
You told me to find
a good woman,
not another woman.
And here she is now, beside me.
What more do you want?
Are we just waiting
on each other?
But I’m glad you’re here now.
Are you leaving again?
No.
I’m staying here for good.
By the way,
I’m opening my own club.
Really? Wow. Congratulations!
I’m so happy for you.
Where would it be?
Thank you.
It’s called Epitome, in BGC.
Yeah.
How about you?
How’s hospital life?
It’s fine.
My workload’s
lighter now.
I’ve got interns and
residents under me.
So, I have a little
bit more time,
and my weekends are also free.
Thank you for the dessert.
No problem.
If you’re free,
I’d really like you to come
to my club’s opening.
- It’s an exclusive party—
- That’s Samantha Vera, right?
and there won’t be
a lot of people.
Just close friends.
Yeah, I’d love to.
Let me just check
my schedule first.
Is it okay for you
to be seen with me?
Shouldn’t I be the
one asking you that?
Is it okay for you to be
seen with another guy?
Another guy?
More people are
starting to show up.
I think you need to go now.
Okay.
- I’ll see you tomorrow?
- I’ll see you.
Such a strong couple!
So they’re still together
after all these years?
Wow! They’ve been
through so much
and they’re still solid.
True love is so strong.
At least there’s no more
hate or bashing now.
Seeing him again...
just made me realize
how much I still love him.
But...
how does he feel?
He was kind of vague
about everything he said.
Does he think
I have a boyfriend?
She’s recovering quickly.
In no time,
she’ll be back to normal.
Avi, the doctor said you’re
going to get better soon.
Hey, but don’t forget to
drink your medicine, okay?
Okay, doc.
Wait. I remember you.
Daddy said you only
kiss people you like.
Do you like Auntie?
Yeah.
I like your Auntie.
Weren’t you the one who had
a crush on Auntie before?
Auntie, you’re here!
Of course, Auntie is
here to visit you.
Auntie, he’s Uncle, right?
Avi, I think you
need to rest now.
Go to sleep for a bit, baby.
Wow, she still remembers that.
All right then, I’ll leave you
two for now, okay?
The delivery’s downstairs.
Close your eyes now, baby.
You’re not sleeping.
Hey, it’s nice seeing you
again today.
Same here.
It feels nice to see you.
Are you free?
Do you wanna hang out?
Sure.
Okay.
I saw them walking together in BGC!
I saw Samantha Vera
and Doc Ramirez at a cafe!
I saw them at the supermarket too!
I’m sorry.
I still can’t believe
he’s here.
He even cooked tempura for me.
Let’s eat.
Thank you, Cy.
Anyway, your birthday’s
coming up soon, right?
Do you have anything planned?
Just clear your
schedule on that day.
But wait, where are you
throwing your party?
You can have it at my club.
Promoting it, huh?
I mean, thanks for the offer,
but you know
I don’t like parties.
I just wanna spend
that day with you.
Just you.
Cy,
do you have a girlfriend?
‘Cause I’m single.
To answer your question,
yes.
Yes? You have a girlfriend?
Yeah. She just came back
from New York.
Really? When did she get back?
I don’t know,
she didn’t tell me.
Am I your girlfriend?
You know what,
I owe you a lot.
Me doing Pediatric
Emergency Medicine.
You were the one who encouraged
me not to give up.
I don’t even know if I could’ve
handled all of it
without your help.
Come on,
that was all you.
And I’m sure
you went through a lot.
But you did it.
You made it happen.
- During my internship,
- Just a little more.
I was rotating through
different departments.
First,
I was assigned to
the OB-GYN department.
That’s what kept me
busy for a few weeks.
When I got assigned
to the Surgery department,
it just got more tiring.
I witnessed death after death.
I couldn’t face the families
crying after losing their loved ones.
But...
there was no choice
but to keep going.
After hospital duty, I still had
to study for rotation exams.
I studied all night, squeezing
in sleep whenever I could.
At that time, there were so
many thoughts running
through my head,
I needed a distraction.
So it was just studying
- and hospital work for me.
- Congratulations!
Thank you, Doc.
Good thing,
my hard work paid off.
I was recognized as one of the
top ten outstanding interns
with exemplary performance.
Eventually, I also graduated
magna cum laude.
But...
my perseverance
didn’t end there.
I topped the boards
with a rating of 91.33%
You did it all on your own, Cy.
And I’m so proud of you.
You know what kept me going?
You.
You had already achieved
so much back then.
I also wanted to achieve more
so that I can stand on
the same level as you.
I followed your journey.
There was even one time,
I’d been awake for 29 hours,
But I still chose to
watch your fashion show.
I wanted to witness
your greatness.
You were amazing.
Congrats.
Congratulations. You did well.
Paging Dr. Clyden Ramirez.
You should have messaged me.
I was actually waiting for that.
I thought you didn’t watch.
How hard is it to say,
“you did good”?
A congratulatory
message wouldn’t hurt.
I always watched your
shows whenever I could.
It was one
of my first big shows.
A core memory.
But I’ve already retired
from runway shows.
I came back to Manila
to focus on my club.
I already knew that you’d
eventually come back home
to the Philippines.
How?
Haze told me.
And I’m glad he did.
I would’ve most likely
moved to New York then.
I even talked to
my dad about it.
You’re going to New York?
Are you planning to practice there?
Yes, Dad.
Have you really
thought this through?
Many times.
And this isn’t just
about my career.
There’s someone in New York
that I wanna be with.
Clyden, I know we haven’t been
okay these past few years.
But despite that,
you have served the hospital
to the best of your abilities.
Even without support
from your mom and me.
Time and time again,
you’ve proven that
you’re an excellent doctor.
And a great son.
I’m so sorry for everything.
But if you truly want
to go to New York
to be with Samantha,
I will respect that.
Thank you, Dad.
You’re welcome, son.
I’m so happy you and
your dad are okay now.
Your relationship with him
has come a long way.
And now we’re here,
eating together.
Yeah.
Looking back, I think
we did the right thing,
don’t you agree?
Parting ways,
even if it was painful.
Yeah, it was painful,
but it was necessary.
We needed that to figure out
what we really wanted.
Maybe we wouldn’t
have found clarity
about what we want
or who we are
if we hadn’t separated
for a while.
He’s right.
That distance made us realize
we never wanted to be apart.
By the way, have you
confirmed if you’re coming
to my club’s opening?
Yes,
and I wouldn’t miss it.
- Let’s eat?
- Okay.
Are you guys dating?
Sam! Oh my god!
Oh my god, you’re here.
It’s so fun.
Hi! You guys are here!
Of course, how could
we miss your opening?
Yeah. This is a
fresh start for you.
Yeah.
Also I invited some friends
over for more publicity.
Really? Oh my gosh,
thank you, girls!
Get drinks and
enjoy the night, okay?
- I’ll be back.
- Okay. We’ll see you around.
Bye!
Guys!
Samantha Vera.
Oh my god. Congratulations!
The best club in town!
Right?
We used to just
party at other clubs.
Now, we have our own
regular hangout spot.
Congratulations, Sam!
Seriously, Samantha Vera.
This is freaking huge!
It’s so awesome!
This place is overwhelming.
Are there any pretty girls here?
Why? Are you looking
for a girlfriend, huh?
Pass! Work is life for now.
I love how he asked
if there were any girls here,
then immediately says pass—
- and then work is life?
- I know, right.
- Is it wrong to look?
- You don’t even do our work
properly, Sevi.
You still owe me.
Wait. I have an announcement.
- Wait for me.
- Huh?
I’ll be back, okay?
Oh my gosh!
You’re delayed, you know.
You’ve been two weeks
late already.
My bad. My bad.
Everyone!
Thank you for coming tonight.
This is a dream come true.
When I was younger,
going to parties with friends
was my escape and relief.
At the club,
I forget all my problems
and just enjoy the night.
So now, my hope is that everyone
who visits my club
feels the same way, too.
Let’s raise our glasses
and toast to this
brand-new start.
Welcome to Epitome! Cheers!
Cheers!
- Okay, again.
- Cheers to that!
- Cheers!
- Cheers, Samantha Vera.
It's time to party!
Hey! Why did you guys
start without me, huh?
- Yanna!
Jeez!
How’s Avi?
She’s okay now, thankfully.
Where's your boyfriend?
He's not here yet?
Hi.
- Speaking of?
- Yes.
- Cy, thank you for coming!
- Of course.
Wow. She hugged him?
Yeah, she did.
Okay, guys!
Clyden. You remember him, right?
Did they get back together?
I don’t know.
Cy, this is Architect Ynares—
Architect Valeria
and Engineer Camero.
So, you’re all
in the same field.
Yes! Yes.
Hello, Doc!
- Ashianna Juarez.
- I’m sorry.
No, just call me Cy.
Come on, give him
a sweet little kiss!
Guys, we’re not in college
anymore, all right?
You know what,
let’s just enjoy the night!
Pull up!
Let’s go, Sev.
- Pull up!
Cy! Come here.
I’m shy. I would just...
How lucky.
What?
Wait.
Are you dizzy now?
Drink some water first.
What?
Why? Is there something wrong?
Nothing.
You just look so pretty.
Let’s go back.
Okay.
Wait.
Be my girlfriend.
Did I hear that right?
What did you just say?
Be my girlfriend.
Let’s be together again.
We’ve been together
for two weeks now
and everything has been great.
At this age
and stage of our lives,
everything feels aligned
for us to be together.
We finally made it.
Come on,
I don’t drive in New York.
I just take the subway—
Whatever.
Bye!
Bye.
I’ll see you later.
We now have time and
space for each other.
Hey.
For you.
I love you.
I love you so much.
This looks good.
It’s good.
Hey. Let’s go.
Hi, Sam.
First of all, I just want
to say sorry
for all of the things
I said to you before.
I promise, I’m trying to change.
Yeah. That’s true.
He’s been seeing a therapist.
That’s all in the past.
And apology accepted.
I hope I still get the chance
to make it up to you.
Hi, Sam.
Hello.
Hi, Sam!
- Hello.
- Sam!
Good to see you here. Hello.
Hello.
Wait.
Are you guys together again?
Yes, Mom, Dad.
But I’m not asking for
permission. I hope that’s clear.
Sweetheart, we know.
You don’t need our permission.
Sam,
can I talk to you for a moment?
Sure.
- Please excuse us.
- Okay. Go ahead.
Boys, let’s go.
Sam, I’d like to apologize for
being so harsh in the past.
I know I should have
handled it better but,
you know…
I’m so proud of your success.
Thank you.
And apology accepted.
Well, just call me Mom
if you’re comfortable with it.
Okay… Mom.
Anyway, just follow us
outside, okay?
I’ll go ahead.
Boys, let’s go outside.
Let’s eat.
- Okay.
- Let’s go.
I’ll go check on Sam first, Dad.
Okay, go ahead.
Hey, how are you?
I’m okay.
You know, the atmosphere in
your family has really changed.
Before, it was always
full of arguments.
But now, it feels so peaceful.
You’re all so calm.
Yeah. After we watched your
tell-all interview
three years ago—
we realized we all played
a part in your suffering.
We just wish it didn’t
have to reach that point.
After all, we’re a family of doctors.
We should’ve been the
ones taking care of people.
We all did a lot of reflection
among ourselves.
I’m happy that you were all
able to forgive each other.
You know, not all families
get to heal like you did.
You’re a criminal!
Don’t you dare
act holier than thou.
You benefited
from my money, too!
It’s the people’s money,
and every day,
I feel fucking bad
being your daughter.
Are you okay? What’s wrong?
Can I see my parents?
Ma’am, the jail warden
has approved your request
to see your parents
in the same room.
But it will be a supervised
visit and will only last ten minutes.
Thank you.
All right.
Hey, do you want me
to come with you?
No, it’s okay.
I need to talk to them alone.
Okay.
Sam?
Sweetheart…
Sam, how are you?
Sweetheart,
I missed you so much.
We missed you so much.
Sam, how are you?
I’m good. How about you?
We’re fine. I guess.
Just taking it
one day at a time.
You treated us badly.
I was so mad at you.
I blame you for everything
that happened to us.
You didn’t just break her,
you broke me too.
You demanded so much from me.
And I wasted so much of my life
trying to reach
your expectations.
Maui, I’m so sorry.
We’re sorry.
Sweetheart, all we ever
wanted was to protect you.
Because we love you so much.
So much.
But your love suffocated me.
How could you do
that to me? To us?
Did you ever apologize to Naomi
for what you did to her?
Yes.
Every single day of my life.
Every day, I ask the
heavens for forgiveness.
If only you knew
how much I cried
because of how you belittled me.
And for forcing me into
things I never wanted to do.
I was even willing to arrange
my marriage to a stranger.
If it hadn’t been Clyden,
I probably would’ve gone
through something worse.
How could you do that?
We were worried about you.
We just wanted to
make sure you’d be okay
in case something
happened to us.
But you made it
look like I needed him.
That I used him.
Do you really think
I wouldn’t be able
to handle things on my own?
Why?
Because I’m a woman?
No… No.
I don’t need a husband
to save me from despair,
Mom, Dad.
Even up to my own wedding,
you still didn’t
give me the chance
to make decisions for myself.
I’m sorry…
I’m sorry to you,
to your sister.
For not being the father
you wanted me to be.
I’m sorry if I ever made you
feel like you weren’t enough.
You’ve done so much and
I’m so proud of you, Maureen.
I just wanted to be free,
to make decisions for myself,
because I am my own person.
You don’t own your children.
We have feelings too.
You even forced
Naomi into a course
she didn’t want, just to
make yourselves happy.
‘Cause what?
You became so
obsessed with politics,
money, and everything
else that you forgot
how to be decent parents
to your own children.
You’re right…
You’re right, Maui.
That’s true.
But I hope someday, somehow,
you’ll be able to forgive us.
I hope you can
forgive me and your dad.
We just wanted to protect you.
All I want is for you to
have peace in your heart.
And Maui, you are
such a strong girl.
Imagine you achieved all of this
on your own, by yourself.
And that alone is enough
for us to be so proud of you.
What’s done is done.
Anything you say now
won’t change the past.
I’ve already forgiven you
for everything you did to us.
I just came here
to let go of the pain
I’ve been holding on to.
Time’s up.
Wait.
Sweetheart, Maui—
Will you still visit us? Please?
I don’t know.
Mau... Maui.
I love you.
Mommy loves you.
Mommy loves you, baby.
Mommy loves you, sweetheart.
Hey.
Come here.
It’s okay, love.
Hey…
You did so well.
And you are so brave
for talking to them.
It was really hard,
but I feel relieved now.
Can we visit Naomi?
I know it’s your birthday,
but I’m making you do
all these things for me.
Hey, it’s okay.
That’s actually where I was
planning to take us anyway.
I already bought
flowers for her, too.
Hey, it's okay.
Thank you, Cy.
You’re welcome.
You didn’t see me
for a long time, huh.
Sorry, I haven’t been
able to visit.
But I always think about you,
wherever I am.
That should be okay, right?
Did you miss me?
She still does.
She loved you very much.
I haven’t even said anything
yet, and I’m already tearing up.
As you can see,
I’m here with the
person you trusted—
the one who promised to be with
me through all the ups and downs.
You must be happy and relieved.
I miss you a lot.
Every day, I think about how
I wish you were
still here with us.
You probably know this
already, but I love you.
And you’ll always
be with me in my heart.
We miss you, Naomi.
You’re also one
of the reasons why
I keep fighting in my work.
Why I want to save children
whenever and however I can.
I hope you’re proud of me.
Don’t worry,
I’ll take care of your sister.
And I will never leave her,
no matter what happens.
I mean it this time.
Here, keep it.
You’ll be okay, right?
I feel like you’re the
one wiping my tears.
Naomi, I’m now free.
Let’s go.
What are we doing here?
I just wanted to drop by here.
I missed this place.
The house hasn’t
been officially sold yet.
So, it’s still technically ours.
I miss this place.
I miss us, in this place.
Yeah, me too.
Let’s go to the veranda.
I’ll show you something.
Okay.
What’s this?
Wait, just stay right there.
Huh? Why?
Walk to me.
- Why?
- Just do it. Just walk to me.
I never really proposed
to you properly,
but I know you deserve this.
Samantha Maureen Vera—
will you marry me?
Yes. Of course, yes!
Let’s take a photo.
Okay.
- Can you hold this, please?
- Okay.
You posted it?
What’s the caption?
My final walk will be
on the aisle with you.
Ready!
Okay, in character.
Let’s just—
live together—
Oops, sorry?
Excuse me.
Who’s that ***?
I don’t know who’s that *** ***.
- Cut!
- Fuc—
Are we visible, Direk?
- You already know you’re not.
- Okay, cam—
Yes, you’re visible.
You don’t wear briefs, either.
So, you were checking this out?
Move a bit.
Lick it.
So-
Cut!
Yanna!
Why did you take
so long to answer?
You’re probably
hiding a gu-gu-do-do…
Sorry, Direk!
Cut!
I really thought we’ll continue.
Okay, one more!
*** hate you!
- We said three, two, one!
- Okay.
Let’s really do three, two, one.
Good luck.
Why are you still awake, love?
You’re still awake, love?
I’m sorry!
Okay, let’s go.
Turn to the cam.
Yeah, and then that happened.
Oh shit, I’m sorry!
Oh you wanna go again?
No.
I thought—
Cut!
I thought I’ll go again…
Mom, Dad—
Cut!
I didn’t know where to go.
- Hey, it’s not our turn yet!
- I’m sorry.
Sevi, you gotta chill.
Wait!
I’m sorry. Just quit it!
- Well, I’m here now.
- Oh!
I’m sorry!
Kidding! I’ll go Ariana—
Hail, eat your food.
Sorry! Sorry!
I’m really sorry!
I said, don’t kiss.
- Oh, don’t!
- I’m sorry.
- Just stare at each other.
- Sorry, Direk.
Just stare at each other.
Why are you kissing?
You’re not following
instructions.
I thought we were—
Oh come on!