[The Epoch of Miyu]
[Episode 25]
Hello, Mr. Tan.
We meet again.
Mr. Ji.
I'm really sorry
to disturb you during work hours.
Not at all.
Please sit.
Okay.
Actually, I came here today on purpose
because of something
related to me yesterday
that might drag Miss Xu Miyu
into unnecessary trouble.
Ms. Xu is a very important friend of mine.
So I came to clear things up for her.
Mr. Tan, you're willing to go
to great lengths for a friend.
I can understand that.
Rest assured.
According to the hotel's regulations,
if she didn't break any rules,
we absolutely won't wrong her.
Okay.
But it's a fact that she caused
a negative impact on the hotel.
We can only do things by the book.
Then I'll make it short.
I didn't stay in Room 1219 yesterday.
After I settled Ms. Xu down,
I went to Room 1810.
I slept on the sofa
in the living room in my father's suite
for the whole night.
Of course, this is
the best solution I could think of.
Then, Mr. Tan, have you ever thought
that if you didn't interfere,
things wouldn't be so complicated?
[Purong Hotel]
Mr. Ji, you think I'm being a busybody,
don't you?
Mr. Tan, you've misunderstood.
What I mean is,
you are also a public figure.
You should know better than us
how to avoid gossip.
A hotel is full of gossip.
This kind of rumor
can be a fatal blow to someone.
If you were there at the time, Mr. Ji,
seeing Ms. Xu being
humiliated by her family
and mocked by her colleagues,
would you just stand by and do nothing?
But I would never
take advantage of her vulnerability.
What do you think,
Mr. Tan?
Mr. Ji, may I ask you
a question in return?
In what capacity
are you saying these things to me?
And in what capacity
are you approaching
an employee of our hotel?
Mr. Ji, I think you've missed the point.
Actually, what you should care about
is why she got so drunk,
what exactly she's been through,
and how much she's endured
that she shouldn't have.
Don't focus on me.
What do you think?
Mr. Ji, I believe that
for employees as precious as gold,
just providing a shining stage
isn't enough.
You must also be there
for them in their vulnerable moments.
Of course, you have
a good eye for talent, Mr. Ji.
You must understand this principle.
I've also checked the surveillance.
Indeed,
Tan Jizhou stayed in room 1219
for less than 5 minutes
before coming out.
Two minutes later,
he appeared in the corridor
of the executive floor.
He wasn't seen on camera again
until around 8:40
the next morning.
I indirectly asked Mr. Tan Sr. about it.
It's true...
Hello, Mr. Ji.
Hello, Mr. Xue.
What are you whispering about?
Nothing.
Sorry, Mr. Ji.
Bro,
are you out of your mind?
You want to be a tyrant?
This way.
Okay.
Here.
Xiaoyan.
Do you think our complaint
will backfire?
Look at her, acting like nothing happened
after coming out of Mr. Ji's office.
Xu Miyu staying in
a guest's room late at night
is an undeniable fact.
We have it all recorded in the computer.
But that doesn't mean
they actually did anything.
It doesn't matter.
Giving people cause
for gossip is unacceptable.
How can a lobby manager
be so frivolous?
If word gets out,
it'll ruin our hotel's image.
You guys really don't get it.
No.
I have to go talk
to Director Bai again later.
After all this,
we still can't bring her down.
Is there no justice?
Come in.
Mr. Ji,
Director Bai is here.
Show him in.
Mr. Ji, you were looking for me?
Director Bai.
I heard you're very anxious to know
the investigation results of Ms. Xu
staying overnight in the guest room.
Not really.
They're just rumors among the staff.
The matter has been
thoroughly investigated.
Ms. Xu is not involved in any violations.
There will be no administrative penalties.
No punishment at all?
Mr. Ji, you might not
have heard the rumors.
It's said the scene was extremely indecent
and unsightly.
Did you see it with your own eyes?
No.
But the rumor is all over the place today.
Everyone is saying
that the lobby manager of our Front Office
got drunk and stayed in a guest's room.
This has a very negative impact.
I'm mainly afraid that the young girls
in the Front Office
will follow her example.
It will be hard to manage them later.
Didn't you just say
that the subordinates
love to spread rumors?
That is indeed the case.
A wise man does not believe rumors.
Director Bai.
Your department's employees
complained to you.
What investigations have you done?
I haven't yet...
Have you checked the hotel's surveillance?
No.
Have you asked the person involved?
Spreading rumors without evidence
is a clear violation of hotel rules.
Also,
this complaint letter of yours
states that Xu Miyu spent the night
with a guest in his room.
It's written in black and white.
If we look into it
and it doesn't match the facts,
every single person who signed this
will have to bear legal responsibility.
What is this?
These people do things without thinking.
Without any evidence,
and without reporting to their superiors,
they came straight to you.
Seriously.
So you were kept
in the dark too, Director Bai?
Yes, I was misled by them.
Mr. Ji.
Since you've investigated clearly,
and Ms. Xu was indeed wronged,
I'll go back
and give them a good talking-to.
Director Bai, if you can't handle it,
you can leave it to us.
I... I can handle it.
You don't need to
step in for such a small matter.
Rest assured, Mr. Ji.
I know what to do.
I promise
that today's rumors
will turn into a gust of wind
and blow far away.
Then I'll trouble you to take the lead
and set a good example
for the Front Office.
Yes, yes, Mr. Ji.
Lu Xiaoyan,
have you finished your situation report?
No.
Why not?
You haven't even cleaned up your own mess,
and you're asking me about my report?
Who do you think you are?
I'm your boss,
and you made a mistake at work.
My superior will handle my problems.
Please give me the report now.
I won't.
What are you going to do about it?
Do you want to know?
Yes.
Ying.
Give me the performance appraisal form.
Okay, Ma'am.
I've deducted 20 points
from your monthly performance.
If you don't submit it tomorrow,
I'll deduct 30 points.
You...
Director Bai!
Director Bai,
please come and judge for us!
Director Bai.
Ms. Xu.
It's lunch break.
Haven't you gone to eat?
I'll go after I handle this.
Director Bai, look at Ms. Xu.
She is crazy today.
Her own behavior is improper,
yet she deducts 20 points from me.
Will you leaders do something about it?
And with so many of us
signing the complaint letter,
will the general manager even read it?
You little girls,
I haven't settled the score with you yet.
What complaint letter?
What nonsense are you all making?
Whatever Ms. Xu does
is none of your business.
As for you, Lu Xiaoyan,
I haven't punished you for yesterday.
Get your self-criticism written now.
Write down the whole process
clearly and seriously.
Hand it in today once you finish.
She should hand it in to you, right?
Let Ms. Xu review it.
If you don't finish it today,
don't come to work tomorrow.
Did you hear me?
All of you,
starting today,
if anyone thinks
they are smart and talks nonsense,
or passes notes,
I'm warning you,
I won't protect you.
Ms. Xu, go have lunch.
When she finishes the self-criticism,
have her come to you.
It has to pass your approval.
If you are not satisfied,
make her rewrite it.
Thank you, Director Bai.
Thank you for your support.
It's my duty.
I'll go eat now.
Director Bai.
She...
Don't point.
Hurry up and write.
A bunch of troublesome girls.
Mr. Ji.
Morning.
I recently discovered
life is just a series of disappointments.
What do you think of this?
This is so impressive.
I actually really want to transfer Ya
to the Western restaurant.
But look at Bao's skills.
She really can't compare.
Ya's knife skills are excellent.
Isn't it good for her
to be in the Chinese restaurant?
She doesn't like it.
She just wants to make cakes.
Things just don't go as planned, do they?
Did you make this?
I just made it for fun.
Let me steam it.
What about Ya?
Ya?
I can only tell her
to let nature take its course,
and keep working with me
at the Chinese restaurant.
You should also let things be.
There are many things
you simply can't control.
As for those baseless rumors,
just ignore them.
What's the worst that could happen?
At most, it reaches Mr. Ji's office.
Mr. Ji will swat them
all like flies.
They've sent me
this joint compliant letter.
Of course, I could
suppress it
and keep you in your position
against broad objection.
But why should I do that?
Are you worth it?
Did he bully you again?
He is the general manager.
There is really nothing between us.
Stop always trying
to pair us up.
Okay.
I'll stop talking.
Then don't look so sad.
Smile a little.
Cheer up, okay?
That looks terrible.
You know how to make corn out of dough?
What else can you make?
I can also make little monkeys.
Wait.
They are all a bit lacking.
Kuanli has been interfering,
making it hard to find
good pastry chefs in this city.
We've made appointments with so many
foreign Michelin chefs.
You've met them all,
but you're not satisfied with any of them.
We can't just look at titles and sales.
Most importantly,
they have to match the style
and character of Purong Hotel.
Just like that Yan Du Xian from before.
As for the style of Purong Hotel,
it's the old Shanghai flavor.
For example, the almond pastries
and eclairs from Harbin Food Factory,
and the palmiers from Park Hotel.
That field is way too competitive.
Should we offer
Chinese-style afternoon tea?
Look.
Think about how many milk tea brands
are moving into Chinese tea now.
The lines for Shen Dacheng's Qingtuan
and Laodafang's Suzhou-style mooncakes
are so long.
That's enough to show
that the market for Chinese pastries
is not to be underestimated.
Besides, our Chinese restaurant
is currently trending.
Rather than crowding
into the Western dessert market,
we might as well
use Chinese tea snacks
to make a breakthrough.
Come help.
Mr. Bao.
Please introduce this to us.
This half is Chinese-style.
That half is Western-style.
Mr. Ji. Mr. Guo.
Mr. Xue. This apprentice of mine
is clumsy with words. He knows how to do
the job, just not how to explain it.
Like these today,
we have both Chinese and Western styles.
Mr. Bao's concept is
to embrace a mix of cultures.
It centers on Chinese desserts,
paired with Italian, Japanese,
and British classics,
to create
a cultural exchange on the plate.
As for the Chinese desserts,
are there any other new creations?
Take a look at this,
the Rainbow Mille-Feuille.
This looks good.
Let me try it.
It's delicious.
However,
Xinlong Hotel
is also making
the Four Seasons Mille-Feuille.
If we make it too,
it would be too competitive.
But of course,
if there are no other options,
we can try this first.
Wait a minute, Mr. Ji.
I have a hidden item here.
What secret weapon are you hiding?
Bring it out.
You said it.
Very good.
Who made this?
Xu Miyu.
Okay, are you ready?
Ready.
Okay, change your pose for another one.
Fix your hair. It's a bit messy.
[Mom]
Here we go.
Three, two, one.
Alright.
Here, take a look.
Thank you.
Hello, Mom. I'm working right now.
What's the matter?
Working overtime on the weekend?
It's just an excuse.
Whenever she doesn't want
to answer the phone,
she is always busy.
Miyu, I'm calling you for a reason.
We are family,
so I'll skip the pleasantries.
How much money do you
have left in your bank account?
Hello?
Are you listening?
Mom.
I still have to pay off
my debts every month.
Ms. Xu, the Chinese restaurant's kitchen
is looking for you.
Got it. I'll be right there.
Mom, I have work to do.
I'm hanging up now.
Hello?
She is busy.
She hung up.
Dad, what are you doing?
Are you okay?
See for yourself.
In the past,
even if you gave her
all the courage in the world,
she wouldn't dare.
Now look at her.
Staying in a big city,
living in a grand hotel.
Now that she's divorced,
she's doing great.
What about us?
We didn't get anything at all.
We're the ones losing out.
Xiumei.
If she hangs up, call again.
Keep calling.
Call until she answers.
Okay.
And you.
[Call]
[Miyu]
You don't even know your own limits.
Why did you enroll Man
in an international school?
Why are you scolding me?
Which parent doesn't
do everything for their child?
Hello, Mom.
Miyu,
you finally answered the phone.
I really couldn't go on otherwise.
Mom, my life isn't easy either.
I understand you,
but I'm fighting all alone in Shanghai.
Have you ever asked me how I'm doing?
I really have no choice.
Mom, I have no choice either.
I can't help you.
I'm sorry.
Did something happen to you?
No. You're looking for me?
Let's go.
Let me make a corn.
Have a taste.
You've learned to make
Suzhou-style boat pastries?
I didn't learn it systematically.
I just picked it up from watching.
They're just okay for a casual bite.
Who taught you?
My mom taught me.
She only taught me
to make these few types.
You mean your mom knows more?
Yes.
When my mom was young,
she learned from a master in town.
Every Chinese New Year, she also
makes some in different shapes for us.
She can even make Chinese zodiac animals.
How about this?
We'd like to invite your mother
to come to Purong Hotel.
We just want to observe
her boat pastries craftsmanship.
There's no pressure.
We just want her to come over
and talk it through with us.
If there's really
an opportunity for cooperation,
we'd be happy to see it happen.
If I had any other way,
I wouldn't come begging you.
[Staff Only]
Your sister is rummaging
through the house right now.
Mom, do you still want the money?
Yes, of course I do.
Do you have it?
If you want the money,
come here right now.
[Staff Only]
Your sister just finished tormenting you.
Now you've brought your mom here.
You really don't mind
the trouble your family brings you.
Actually, I was quite hesitant at first.
But then I thought,
instead of having them
wait for me to feed them every day,
it's better to let them
find their own way out.
Actually, my mom's skills
are really quite amazing.
It's just that she didn't have
a chance to show them off before.
The hotel happens to need it this time,
so I wanted to give her a chance
to discover her own value.
She shouldn't always entrust her life
to someone else.
That's a really nice thought.
But knowing your mom's personality,
once she's here,
you won't be able to control her at all.
She'll cause trouble
for you all over the hotel.
It absolutely won't happen this time.
I've already laid down the rules with her.
The hotel has its rules.
If she can't accept them,
she'll have to leave immediately.
Did you really say that?
Not bad, Xu Miyu.
You're getting tough now.
With you backing me up,
who am I afraid of?
Let's go.
Mr. Ji.
I have something else to do.
I'll get going.
Qiaoqi.
The desserts you made
are not only beautiful but also delicious.
Thank you, Mr. Ji.
About what happened last time,
I misunderstood you.
And I said those nonsensical things.
What things?
Like whether you are worth it or not.
I shouldn't meddle
in your private affairs.
Whether it's worth it or not
is not my place to judge.
So I apologize to you.
I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologize, Mr. Ji.
You have your standpoint,
and I also did something inappropriate.
If there's nothing else,
I'll get going.
Miyu.
Are you still angry with me?
Yes.
I am angry.
I do not want to be the kind of person
who forgives the moment
someone says sorry.
Is that okay?
It is.
Of course it is.
Isn't this Chef Li?
Why are you getting off work so late?
Where did you go to save the world again?
Mr. Duan Jr.,
with you not at the hotel today,
the world feels unusually peaceful.
Do you know how to talk properly?
I heard Mr. Ji
has been thinking about
improving the afternoon tea lately.
The stuff your restaurant makes
is even more choking than dirt.
Give it up.
You've already turned
the Chinese restaurant around.
Don't end up dragging
the Western one down.
Don't you worry about that.
Mr. Ji has his secret weapon.
What secret weapon?
No comment.
Is it that hard to admit defeat?
What do you say? Care to make a bet?
Within a month,
Purong's afternoon tea
will definitely be a big hit.
The loser will be
the winner's sidekick for a week.
You said it.
Handsome.
Come here.
Can you take a look?
Why can't I pay with WeChat?
Take a look.
Ma'am, you haven't linked your bank card.
I haven't linked my bank card?
Right, that's it.
Then could you pay for me?
-I…
-I heard that
your five-star hotel
puts the guest first.
Guest comes first, right?
Sorry. I'll do it.
I'll do it.
-Hello.
-I can’t pay.
Thank you.
Sweetie.
Give me a hug.
Take a look.
Do I look imposing?
I almost didn't recognize you.
Your sister picked it for me.
After all, she's
been around in the big city.
Right?
Let me tell you,
I've done my homework this time.
I won't let you down.
Okay. Let's go.
Let's go.
Slow down. Wait.
You're taking the food away too fast.
Just now, at the seafood section,
I almost didn't get the sashimi.
I'm sorry, Ma'am.
Look,
there's still so much left.
It's a waste not to eat it.
Miss,
could you please help me put this
on that table? That table over there.
Okay.
I'll hurry up and get some more.
Otherwise you guys will take it all away.
Have you checked her background clearly?
So far, we only know
she's Xu Miyu's mother,
named Jiao Xiumei.
She used to farm in the countryside,
and later opened
a guesthouse with her husband,
but the business wasn't very good.
Waiter!
Why is no one here?
I know.
Hold on, please.
Espresso?
Okay.
Keep going.
I can hear you guys.
I want to know about
the representative pieces.
Yeah.
Very impressive.
Why
is it as bitter as Chinese medicine?
This Ji Feng...
Bringing a village woman
to save afternoon tea
at a five-star hotel,
is he taking an unconventional approach
or is he out of options?
I guess he has no way out.
After all, we've given a heads-up
to all the dessert businesses in the city.
It's not that easy to hire a master chef.
I hope so.
We will work with local artists.
But we also want to
expand into international markets.
Yeah.
Besides...
Mom.
You took so much food.
Can you finish it?
I can.
I was in a hurry last time
I came to see you.
Today I'm going to eat as much as I want.
Then eat quickly.
You have to come with me later.
Many people in the kitchen
are waiting for you.
Don't rush me.
Morning, Ms. Xu.
-Morning, Mr. Tan.
-Morning.
This is...
This, this is my mother.
This is our guest, Mr. Tan.
Hello, Mrs. Xu.
So you can speak Chinese.
He was the one
who poured me coffee just now.
I heard him speaking English.
I haven't had the chance to thank you yet.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
Thank you, Mr. Tan.
You're welcome.
Well, take your time.
I'll get going.
I'm done eating too.
Let's go together.
It's fine.
What do you mean, go together?
He's a guest.
Don't try to get close to him.
Don't think I don't know who Mr. Tan is.
Your sister told me everything.
Tell me the truth.
How far have you two gone?
Nowhere.
I think he's pretty good.
He is good-looking,
and capable.
And he's good to you.
Don't be so indifferent.
Give him a chance.
Mom.
Let me say this to you again.
This is a hotel.
I'm here to work and make money,
and the guests
aren't here for blind dates.
Stop trying to play matchmaker,
okay?
Don't play innocent with me.
I'm doing this for your own good.
You're in your thirties.
Aren't you going to find a partner?
Without a family,
who's going to be
with you when you're old?
Think clearly about it.
Mom, stop meddling in my business.
There are people upstairs
waiting to assess you.
Mind your own business first.
Let's just live our own lives, okay?
Fine.
You're all grown up now,
and you don't listen to me anymore.
Let's get going.
Chef Jiao will be here soon.
So we need to hurry up.
That'll do.
Mr. Ji.
Why are you here?
Chef Jiao is visiting.
Of course I have to
welcome her personally.
Pleased to meet you.
So you are the general manager?
I've often heard Miyu talk about you.
Look at this temperament and appearance.
You're better than the stars on TV.
General Manager.
Are you married?
Mom, what are you saying?
It's okay.
I'm still single.
Then let's begin.
Okay.
I've prepared it for you.
We have prepared some tools for you.
See if they are suitable.
Things in a big hotel
are truly professional.
Then I'll use them.
Okay.
Blooming Prosperity.
Abundance Year After Year.
Look, this keeps the flowers fresh.
Look.
Right? So fresh.
Mom,
is your arthritis acting up again?
It's nothing. Just an old problem.
Come, Chef Jiao, please.
This room faces south.
Do I have to pay for this room?
Chef Jiao, you are
the boat pastry consultant
for our hotel.
All food and accommodation expenses
will be covered by us.
You don't need to worry.
Then,
if I eat and stay here,
will I still get paid?
Mom, let's talk about the contract later.
We can talk about the contract later,
but we must be clear about the money.
Your dad told me
to ask about the money clearly in person.
If the pay isn't clear,
I can't start working.
Right?
Yes, it's fine.
What is your ideal salary, Chef Jiao?
7,000 a month.
That's not too much, right?
No problem.
Okay.
No.
7,000 is too little.
Mom, we'll discuss this later.
8,000.
At least 8,500.
Chef Jiao, you don't
need to answer me right away.
We can talk when you've thought it over.
Ms. Xu,
please take care of
Chef Jiao's daily needs.
We hope Chef Jiao
can start working immediately.
We will also draft the contract
as soon as possible.
When the time comes, please
help Chef Jiao review it.
Okay, Mr. Ji. Thank you.
Right.
Um, here is the room card.
Get some rest.
Mom.
Congratulations.
So?
I'm quite capable, am I?
Of course.
Let's eat some fruit.
Look how fresh it is.
As expected of a five-star hotel.
Here, let me wipe it for you.
[Yunnan Baiyao Plaster]
Rui,
can Chef Jiao's contract
be ready this week?
There are a bunch of contracts lined up.
First come, first served, okay?
The afternoon tea project is urgent.
Please prioritize it.
It seems that what's urgent,
aside from afternoon tea,
is someone's eagerness
to show goodwill with an ulterior motive.
What?
Haven't apologized yet?
I have.
Then that's it.
But she didn't accept it.
Xu Miyu?
Actually, I'm quite glad.
She was willing to tell me
that she didn't accept my apology.
Glad?
Telling the truth
is always better than holding it in.
This way, I know what I should do.
Feng,
are you okay?
The contract.
Remember to give it to me this week.
Okay.
[Statement Regarding the Reception
of VIP Guest Mr. Ma Wenhui]
[During my reception of Mr. Ma Wenhui,]
[my attitude caused him
an unpleasant experience.]
[I hereby submit this statement.]
[Submitted by Lu Xiaoyan]
I understand the situation.
Learn from this.
Don't let it happen again.
Don't think I'm
scared of you because of this.
I don't need you to be scared of me.
These are the Western restaurant's
newly launched
afternoon tea boat pastries.
You've all worked hard
these past couple of days.
Try them.
They look so nice.
Then eat them yourself.
Then I won't be polite.
[Blooming Prosperity]
What is this?
This is also our specialty.
[Abundance Year After Year]
I'll take both then.
Sure, wait a moment.
[Employment Contract]
[Work content] [Reward]
20,000? So high?
Mom, your boat pastries became a hit
in our Western restaurant
in just one afternoon.
Really?
I've never had so much money
in my pocket my whole life.
Now I see it clearly.
That Mr. Ji
probably has his eye on you.
Mom, what nonsense are you talking about?
Otherwise,
why would he pay an old lady like me
such a high salary?
It's called a consulting fee.
Whatever fee it is,
he is doing it to please you.
This is the result of a joint assessment
by the HR Department,
the Administration Department,
and the Business Management Department.
It's not just his call.
Besides,
you should have some confidence
in your own skills, okay?
You are the one
who should have confidence.
When have I ever been wrong?
The way he looks at you is different.
Mr. Tan
and Mr. Ji.
Both seem like good catches.
Which one do you like more?
While I'm here,
I'll help you pull some strings.
Mom, stop dreaming, will you?
I understand your anxiety
about having an older,
divorced daughter.
But that's your problem.
It has nothing to do with me.
And it certainly has nothing to do
with Mr. Tan and Mr. Ji.
One is my guest,
and making sure he's not disturbed
is my job.
The other is my boss.
He could easily get us both fired
by lifting a finger.
They are not from the same world as me.
Do you understand?
What... what are you talking about?
Alright, alright.
Just focus on work
right now.
There's no problem with the contract.
Just sign it.
So stubborn.
Where do I sign?
Duan,
hurry up.
There are still pots to wash.
The water's barely running.
How can you wash them clean?
Li Qiaoqi, don't go too far.
Getting mad already?
You made the bet yourself.
You must accept the loss.
You don't really think
that just by improving the afternoon tea,
Purong can turn the tables, do you?
The best is yet to come.
You did that on purpose, didn't you?
Purong's dishes are too fragile.
Pay for it.
It's not like I can't afford to pay.
The contract is signed. Thank you, Mr. Ji.
You don't need to thank me.
Your mother's willingness to entrust
this craft to Purong Hotel
is our fortune.
[You don't need to thank me.
Your mother's willingness to entrust]
[this craft to Purong Hotel
is our fortune.]
[Xu Miyu]
If you must thank me,
how about
we have dinner together?