=Eight Hundred=
(Yingxiong Roller Skating Rink)
Chen Hui!
Songge.
Song...
Huo Kaiming.
Chen Hui, what's wrong?
I had a nightmare.
What did you dream about?
It's nothing.
Then, why did you keep shouting,
"Huo Kaiming, don't kill me?"
It was just a nightmare.
Are you hiding something from me?
No.
You're lying.
You always make that face when you lie.
I'm really not.
I just had a nightmare.
Then, why did you
get nervous on the bus
when the radio
mentioned the murder case?
And when they were
checking red cars on the road,
what were you looking at?
Is Huo Kaiming's car red?
I'm asking you.
Mr. Huo hasn't looked for you in years,
yet he came to see you
just a few days ago.
One day, you told me
that Lu Yuan had already left,
and the next day,
the news of the murder broke.
Then, the police
started checking red cars.
Why is that?
You're not going to talk?
Fine.
Songge.
Songge,
what are you doing?
I'm going to turn myself in.
Just like we said before.
I'll do all the dangerous things,
and I'll take all the blame.
Songge!
It's no use.
I killed someone.
What did you say?
I said I killed someone.
Who did you kill?
That day at the hospital,
when I was getting cough medicine,
Huo Kaiming caught me.
He threatened me
and made me find someone for him.
I thought it would be simple,
but he pressured me again and again.
Then, Lu Yuan got involved too,
and he also pressured me repeatedly.
I had no choice.
So I told Huo Kaiming
that Lu Yuan
was the man he was looking for.
I used Huo Kaiming's hands
to kill Lu Yuan.
It's because of me.
It's all because of me
that you ended up on this path.
Chen Hui...
I'm the one who ruined you.
I'm the sinner here.
I shouldn't even
be alive in this world.
How can I face your parents?
Songge.
What am I supposed to do?
Songge, believe me,
this isn't your fault.
Songge.
Now,
it's all been resolved.
Everything has been settled.
It's okay.
Let's just rest for a while, okay?
Once the heat dies down,
everything will be fine.
We'll act as if
none of this ever happened.
We can't go back,
Chen Hui.
=Episode 6=
(The Marked One)
(People's Public Security)
Based on our screening
of Lu Yuan's pager records,
on the day he was killed,
a mobile number
ending in 3023
paged him once.
It was through an automated system,
and the message was "1111".
This should be the code
his contact used to set a meeting.
Right. This mobile number
has no registered identity.
I investigated
all of its communication records.
In the past three months,
it had called 11
pager numbers here in Fengyang.
All the messages were strange.
They were all just sets of numbers.
Lu Yuan
(Lu Yuan)
is among these 11 people.
So I suspect these 11 people
are the downline dealers
of the cough syrup.
These are
all the call records
between this number and Lu Yuan.
Master.
Big guy.
On the night of October 8,
at 8:03 PM,
this number
sent Lu Yuan
a text message.
The content
(Water tank)
was "water tank".
Isn't this strange?
Could this water tank be
the location where Lu Yuan
and this supplier made their deals?
It's possible.
On October 8, we were doing
a night inspection.
Is it possible that this water tank
is related to our night inspection?
Currently, we have
no leads at all.
"Water tank" is just too broad.
Are there any other leads?
We also screened
the pager records
of the 11 downline dealers.
Among them, we've identified four.
Three of them
only had contact with
the supplier's mobile number.
Only one person named Ma Heping,
besides contacting
the supplier's number,
also had close contact
with another mobile number.
Whose phone is it?
Huang Liang's.
Huang Liang?
If it's Huang Liang,
Hongbing, we all know about
your relationship with him.
Don't you think
you need to recuse yourself?
Huang Liang and I aren't even relatives.
Why would I recuse myself?
Look,
give me Ma Heping's files.
I'll handle it.
(Ding Yue Clinic)
I'll take this call.
Hello?
Ding Yue,
can you come home a bit earlier
after work this afternoon?
What's up?
I want to invite
Huang Liang for dinner today.
Go back early and cook a few
of his favorite dishes.
Why don't you two just go out and eat?
I've already made plans with him.
Just go back early.
Fine, I got it.
Thanks.
Here comes the soup.
Here.
Mrs. Chen, look,
you've prepared such a feast.
I really feel...
These are all your favorite dishes.
Yes.
Look at him acting all polite.
You used to come over
for free meals every day.
I didn't see you being so polite then.
Huang Liang is a big boss now.
Hongbing, look what you're saying.
What "big boss"?
I heard you've found a girlfriend.
What does she do?
She sells suits at the department store.
Bring her over sometime
to get to know us.
Let us meet her too.
She's only two
or three years older than Hui.
She's still young.
How could she sit
at the same table as us?
Then your father-in-law,
when he sees me, he'd have to...
he'd have to call me "big brother".
That's right. If his dad sees you,
he really will have to call you that.
Are you two done?
Talk about something sensible.
Alright then. You guys eat.
Aren't you eating, Mrs. Chen?
I won't. I've already eaten.
Thank you, Mrs. Chen.
Thanks, Mrs. Chen.
It's nothing.
Look, she didn't even have a bite.
Huang Liang,
let's have this today.
I remember the old man
brought this back
from Yunchuan that year.
Yeah.
Wait, you...
Haven't you been
eyeing this for 30 years?
No.
Hongbing, please don't.
You can't do this. No.
Don't do this.
Hongbing, don't open it.
Save this liquor for Hui's wedding day.
Then we'll open it, okay?
You really opened it.
In our line of work,
living fast and free,
when we want a drink,
do we have to wait
for the lad's big day?
Come on.
Thanks, Hongbing.
Huang Liang.
The reason I called you here today
is to ask you something.
Go ahead, Hongbing.
You must
tell me the truth.
Hongbing, when have I ever
lied to you?
Ma Heping.
You know him, right?
You mean Ma?
He's one of my employees.
Where is he now?
I'm not sure.
He's your employee,
and you don't know where he is?
Hongbing, work is over now.
How can I keep track of where he goes?
I'm asking you now.
I'm giving you a chance.
Think carefully before you answer.
Hongbing,
in the past few years,
I have been running an illegal coal pit.
The Ma Heping you mentioned,
he's a cook at my pit.
Anything else?
There's nothing else.
Think about it again.
No matter how much I think,
there's nothing else, Hongbing.
Hongbing.
I asked you to do
a urine test last time.
You did it, right?
I did.
Alright, then.
Come.
After we finish this meal,
come back to the station with me.
First thing tomorrow morning,
take me to the mine
to find Ma Heping.
Drink up.
Hongbing,
can you help me out?
Mining without a license
is against the law.
I have to take you to turn yourself in.
Turn myself in?
How many years
will I get for that, Hongbing?
We caught someone last time.
He was fined 150,000
and sentenced to three years.
If there are other complications,
it will be more serious.
Hongbing,
you scared me to death!
Just two or three years...
I thought I was finished.
I thought this was a farewell drink.
I thought I was about to be
taken out and shot, Hongbing.
You really scared me.
That's enough.
Come on.
Cheers.
Look at you.
I'll take care of things at home.
- Thanks, Hongbing.
- Just reform yourself well.
Mr. Huang, you're here early today.
Everyone,
come over here.
No need to go down the shaft today.
Come gather around.
Come here.
Mr. Huang has something to say.
Hurry up.
Everyone, over here.
Put down whatever you're holding.
Listen to me.
First of all, I've let you all down.
Starting from today,
this coal pit,
due to
poor management,
is being shut down.
How can it be shutting down?
What are we supposed to do?
Let me tell you all,
operating this illegal coal pit
is a crime.
I hope that all of you
will do your best to be
good and law-abiding citizens.
Next,
look at me.
Whatever I do,
you all do the same.
What's going on?
Why are we holding our heads like this?
Don't move!
- Stop right there!
- Hurry up!
Hurry up!
- Squat down!
- Don't move!
Don't move!
Behave yourselves.
Where is Ma Heping?
He's over there in the kitchen cooking.
Limin, follow me.
Don't burn yourself.
Be careful.
Okay, I got it.
Ma Heping.
You are Ma Heping, right?
I'm from the Fengyang Police Station.
What are you doing?
You're not allowed to bully my dad!
Go away!
You bad guys!
Hey, little guy.
Who are you?
Tell me.
He's my son.
Little guy,
I'm good friends with your dad.
I want to talk to your dad
about something.
Is that okay?
Go out and play for a bit, alright?
I'm not going!
- Go with me, be good.
- Let go of me!
- Be good.
- Let me...
- Let go.
- Be good, be good.
- I'm not going!
- You have to be good.
- Be good.
- It's okay.
Good boy.
I...
I'm just a cook.
I don't know anything about the mine.
There's no need
to tell me about the mine.
Just tell me
about yourself.
Okay?
Search thoroughly.
- Yes, ma'am.
Officer,
I'm sorry, I beg you.
- Get up.
- I know I was wrong.
You can't take me away.
My child is so small.
You saw him.
He can't...
Your son is a son,
- and so are others', no?
- Yes.
How many people have you ruined?
How many families have you destroyed?
Do you even know?
- No.
- You broke the law.
I know I broke the law.
But you can't take me away.
My child is still young.
If you take me away,
he won't have a father.
I beg you...
Listen to me.
I'll give you a chance
to redeem yourself.
Do as I say.
Understand?
I'm not listening.
I still have my child.
Listen to me!
For your child,
we will make arrangements for him.
Let go of me!
- That's enough.
- Limin.
- I won't let you hurt my dad.
- What's going on here?
This is Ma Heping's son.
- Alright, I know.
- Let go of me.
Don't touch my dad.
Alright, no one is touching your dad.
See? They came out.
Sir,
I really have to thank you.
This leg of mine
has been bad for so many years.
You actually found me
a great doctor in Beijing to treat it.
It's the least I could do.
You don't know, with this leg,
on cloudy and rainy days,
I couldn't even get out of bed.
I'm glad I managed to cure your illness.
Good. Thank you.
You're welcome.
- A great man.
- You're welcome.
Dad!
Kai,
this is my good friend,
Mr. Chen.
Greet me.
They are bad people.
They want to catch you.
Nonsense.
No.
Mr. Chen
found a good hospital
in Beijing
and a good doctor
to treat my leg.
Tell me,
should we go or not?
Can it be cured?
Kid,
if your father goes to Beijing,
the best doctors are there.
Won't he be cured then?
Do you want
your father to get treatment?
Yes.
What a good child.
While I'm in Beijing,
how about staying at Mr. Chen's house?
Okay.
You must be good.
Good boy.
Limin,
take the father and son,
then drop the child off
at Ding Yue Clinic.
Sure thing.
Let's go. I will carry you.
Director Chen,
what are you up to now?
Who would have thought
a child would suddenly pop up?
What do you think we should do?
Recognize this?
This is Peidun Cough Syrup.
I've been selling it.
What do you want to know?
Just ask.
I'll tell you everything
I know.
Well, let's start with this cough syrup.
Where did you get it?
A man in town named
Lu Yuan introduced me.
Was the deal made with Lu Yuan?
No.
I picked up the goods from a woman.
What did she look like?
She was about 1.6 meters tall.
She always covered her face
when I saw her.
I couldn't see clearly.
But there was a scar under her left eye.
It was very noticeable.
A scar under her left eye?
How big was it?
How did you contact her?
By pager.
Four ones meant
picking up goods the next day.
Four zeros
meant run immediately.
How were the deals made
with this scarred woman?
Give us details.
She made us buy
tube popsicles ourselves,
pour out half of the drink,
and then fill it up with cough syrup.
The buyers weren't
allowed to see the bottle.
All the used bottles
had to be returned to her.
She wouldn't let us drink it ourselves,
and we couldn't sell
to students in Fengyang Town.
Where was the transaction site?
By the national highway
at the west town entrance.
You've never sold
the cough syrup by the bottle?
No.
I was relying on it to make money.
It's the supplier's rule,
so how would I dare break it?
Do you recognize this woman?
No.
(Peidun Cough Syrup,
contraband, illegal tube popsicles)
Director Chen, the statements from
the sellers are consistent.
This scarred woman manages
the Peidun Cough Syrup
bottles very strictly.
Which means Yu Susu
could only have gotten a full bottle
from the scarred woman.
Bring the map.
(Fengyang Town, Jiangbin City)
Director Chen,
you're familiar with Fengyang.
Where do you think
this scarred woman is hiding?
It's very strange.
What's strange?
Look, Chief Liu.
The odd thing is,
(Fengyang Town, Jiangbin City)
the places where these sellers live
are all in the villages around Fengyang.
Their daily lives and travels
are also centered in these villages.
The reason the scarred woman chose them
must be after careful vetting.
But their transaction site
is actually in Fengyang Town.
What does this indicate?
It means this scarred woman
lives right
in this town.
That makes sense.
If we compare
their deal locations in Fengyang,
can't we narrow down the search area?
Sit down.
But
the weird thing
is,
in this town,
if there were
a woman with a scar on her face,
it would leave
a deep impression on people.
Think about
all the cases we've handled
over the years
and all the people we've arrested.
But we've never heard of
a woman with a scar on her face,
right?
What's wrong with your eyelid?
It kept twitching.
So I stuck something on it.
Is it possible
that the scar
was fake?
Director Chen, the sketch of Lu Yuan
is out from the municipal PSB.
Based on image comparison,
his name has been confirmed
as Lu Zhengyuan.
He has a record for residential robbery
and served a year and a half.
Don't block the light.
I've seen this man before.
What are you doing? Go back!
The one in the blue shirt.
Police inspection.
It's you, come here.
Be quick.
What's wrong?
Why were you running?
I wasn't running.
When you called me,
I stopped.
You're here to play?
I wanted to play,
but seeing how busy you are,
I won't trouble you.
Let me trouble you for a second.
Go inside for a urine test.
Give me the records
from that night's inspection.
Why isn't Lu Zhengyuan's name here?
Director Chen, I've seen this man too.
He reported a case
at our station a few days ago.
(October 11, 1997)
What's the matter with you?
I'm talking to you.
Aren't you reporting a case?
Why are you here?
I lost my ID card.
You don't need
to call the police for a lost ID.
Don't you know that?
What's your name? Register here.
Wang Dali.
The urine test result was
negative.
That's not right.
The autopsy results for this man show
(Severe Kejianin overdose)
he was positive for Kejianin.
Why wasn't it detected
at the rink that night?
Is it possible his urine test
was tampered with?
The night inspection was a raid,
and the urine tests
were done on the spot.
Those who tested positive were detained,
and those who
were negative were released.
During the whole process,
there was no chance to fake it.
Then, there must be a problem
with the urine itself.
Is there a possibility
that Lu Zhengyuan's supplier
was also at the scene?
They were there for a deal
but ran into our spot check.
The supplier was worried
that if Lu Zhengyuan tested positive,
he would snitch,
so
they swapped the urine for him.
If that's the case,
his supplier
is likely among those
who tested negative.
That means
the "water tank" shown
on Lu Zhengyuan's pager
is the bathroom's water tank
in Hui's roller skating rink.
Could someone have
put the urine
in the tank in advance
and then notified him?
Then, anyone who went in
for a urine test
before Lu Zhengyuan is a suspect.
We need to investigate all of them.
Including the women's room,
we need to check that too.
We can't rule out the possibility
that they were helping
by making calls.
Thirty-two people.
Before Lu Zhengyuan went in,
thirty-two people had entered.
(Lu Yuan, around 182 cm,
thin build, wearing black)
(Supplier: Scarred woman)
Think carefully.
During the night inspection
that evening,
did anything
strange happen at the scene?
Actually, I just thought
of something strange.
But this person isn't on the list.
Master.
That day Songge
fainted, and then Lin...
Right.
I was the one
who accompanied Gao Songge to rest.
Were you two together the whole time?
Mostly.
I just stepped out to heat up her meal.
For how long?
About two or three minutes.
Then, Gao Songge's suspicion
hasn't been ruled out either.
Investigate her with the others.
Including Gao Songge.
Focus on those who might have
social connections with Lu Zhengyuan.
Someone fainted.
Dad, how about I go first?
That way, I can take care of Songge.
What are you doing here?
Reporting a case.
Reporting a case?
What's wrong?
Split up and investigate. Move out.
Yes, ma'am.
Wait.
Start with my son,
Hui.
Chen Hui?
Yes.
For this operation,
I'm stepping down.
Chief Liu will be in charge.
Move out.
(Yingxiong Roller Skating Rink)
Police!
(Jiangbin City People's Court Search Warrant)
This is a search warrant.
Please cooperate with the investigation.
Come with us to the station.
May I ask what this is about?
We'll talk when we get to the station.
Please.
(Interrogation Room 2)
Do you know this person?
No.
Think carefully.
I really don't know him.
But,
on October 8 at 7:40 PM,
this person appeared
at your roller skating rink.
I run a roller skating rink.
My doors are open for business.
It's normal not to know someone.
Have you seen this before?
Never.
October 16,
between 9:00 PM and 11:00 PM,
where were you?
I was at the roller skating rink.
Doing what?
Doing laundry.
Laundry takes three hours?
I got dirty painting
the wall the night before.
I hadn't had time to wash it.
Who can prove it?
The roller skating rink
was open that day.
Everyone there can prove it.
Director Tong,
how?
If there's nothing else,
we need to get back to our business.
You can go now.
She's about 160 cm tall.
There's a scar under her left eye.
It's very noticeable.
How big is the scar?
Is it possible
that the scar was just a fake?
(Scarred woman, around 165 cm tall,
face masked, scar near the left eye)
Wait.
Go inside.
Stand in a row in front of the table.
We have an identification process.
We need your cooperation.
Please put these clothes on.
Once we've changed,
are we good to go?
You'll need to wait
for a makeup artist we brought in.
We need to apply a scar
to your face.
Chief Liu, the equipment is ready.
Good. Bring him in.
Yes. Ma Heping,
come on in.
A life is at stake.
Observe closely later.
See if the woman
who contacted you is on the screen.
Okay.
Begin the identification.
No. 1, step forward.
It's not her.
No. 2.
No.
No. 3.
It's her.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
It's her.
No. 3,
read the script in front of you.
Do you want to make more money?
Just listen to me.
You can't let others see the bottles.
The empty bottles
must be brought back to me next time.
This stuff cannot be sold in Fengyang.
If anyone breaks the rules,
you're out for good.
Wait, no.
That woman had a raspy voice.
She sounded very hoarse.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
No. 4.
From now on, when you're moving goods,
spray this into your throat.
What is this?
Diluoshusong.
It makes your voice hoarse.
Director Chen.
Chen Hui and Gao Songge
have been cleared as suspects.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Hui.
Songge.
I'll go down for a moment.
Okay.
Songge,
what's wrong? You don't look so good.
She's fine.
Just a bit dizzy.
Dad, I have to say,
aren't you guys going too far?
It's not like you don't know
Songge's health condition.
Between the arrest
and the interrogation,
who could handle that?
It's just part of the job.
I didn't have a choice.
Songge just had dialysis two days ago.
She's already feeling unwell.
And you're still
putting her through this.
Listen to you.
What?
You think you're the only one who cares?
So, I don't care about her?
Songge,
I'm sorry.
I
apologize to you.
It's okay, Mr. Chen.
Cooperating is the right thing to do.
Such a sensible girl.
Alright.
Take Songge back home.
What happened just now?
I was put in a lineup.
One of our dealers
must have been caught.
It's okay.
We weren't identified, right?
Let's go.
Let's get back quickly.
You go back first.
Don't worry. Go.
Don't go.
Mr. Huo.
Family shouldn't pay for one's sins.
Code of honor, huh?
Have you no shame?
Either come with me,
or we will go
turn ourselves in together.
Pick one.
You sit in the back.
She sits in the front.
Where are you taking us?
You'll know when we get there.
I did everything you asked.
What else do you want from me?
Do you think I'm that easy to fool?
Let me tell you,
I hate people who lie to me the most.
The coward wasn't the person
I'm looking for at all.
Did Chen Hui send you?
Where is Jiao Yuqin?
You're crazy.
Who's Jiao Yuqin? I don't know her.
- Right?
- Keep your voice down, I'm telling you!
Give me the stuff!
He didn't know Jiao Yuqin at all.
There must be
something else between you two.
Mr. Huo,
is it true that no matter what I say,
you won't believe me?
From the moment
I killed the first person,
I made up my mind.
Those who hit me,
those who lied to me,
and those who harmed me,
they all must die.
(Inspection)
Chen Hui,
if you say a word,
she dies.
Wasn't this car originally red?
I didn't like that color much,
so I changed it.
Please pull over ahead.
We need to do an inspection.
Come forward.
Chen Hui.
Don't worry about me, just run.
Shut up!
What are you waiting for? Run!
I'll kill you right now.
Do you believe me?
Mr. Huo,
is there any point
in us all dying together?
I'm not afraid to die.
If I take her with me, I win.
Weren't you looking
for the one who harmed you?
He's not dead yet.
If you die here today,
can you really rest in peace?
I'll stab her to death right now,
and let's see if you can rest in peace.
You can't threaten him.
With this body of mine,
I'm going to die anyway.
Just kill me. I don't want
to live anymore anyway.
Mr. Huo,
the police are right ahead.
If you kill her now,
do you think you can get away?
Only I can help you now.
Listen to me,
otherwise you won't get out of this.
And you won't escape either.
You darn drug dealer.
You're no different
from a murderer like me.
You won't escape.
How can you prove I sell drugs?
I saw it.
Where's the evidence?
Don't forget,
your phone is still with me.
Right.
The phone is with you.
But I forgot to tell you something.
In the future, after making a call,
remember to wipe off your fingerprints.
The goods I gave you
were for you to give to Lu Yuan.
Since you killed him,
those goods must be at your house, right?
Along with that phone
with your fingerprints...
But none of that matters now anyway.
After all,
they can't execute you twice.