It's been a month since
I've always known him
But as Min Ho, my boyfriend?
Well, our relationship
In the obvious ways,
But in the surprising ways too,
Like, he's a total gentleman, Who knew?
Even though I can get my own banchan,
But okay, it's sweet that
I like to think
With my Sunset List, for example,
which he finds
But I'm his girlfriend now, so I get
I think he secretly likes it,
We were friends for so long,
I thought I knew everything
But as it turns out,
If only a pesky thing called school
would stop getting in the way
Of course, the hardest class at KISS
And I get that Jiwon said
but she could at least, like,
What about me? I'm fluent,
For Monday, read Yi Kwang-su's Mujong,
a ten-page essay
for historical context,
Have a good weekend,
Jiwon, I love Korean Lit
but Professor Lee doesn't even assign
Oh, I'm aware,
When I showed him my syllabus,
That's great,
Well, this weekend, Min Ho is shooting
and I really want to be there
So is there any chance
No, Kitty, You're already
and not on what really matters,
I love my cousin, but I am not
Hi,
Um, Professor Ahn,
I was wondering if you needed
I may be new, but I can assure you
that my classroom is well-stocked,
Great, Well, if you did need anything,
How did I not see this sooner?
It's a grumpy sunshine match
I am telling you,
- I don't see it,
What are we talking about?
What a cute couple
I shall call them "Jilex,"
I don't see it,
Oh my God, can everyone stop doubting
All right, calm down,
Besides, we've got a thousand things
I can't believe your dad
Will Baby Moo Moo make a cameo?
Baby who-who?
Baby Moo Moo, the newborn manatee,
only the most viral thing
Yeah, unfortunately no Baby Moo Moo,
but I did cast Tae-Oh
Ew, the handsy limo guy?
I know, he's not exactly my first choice,
Oh, but guess who's designing
- Yisoo,
That's amazing, I didn't think your dad
I have no idea what changed her mind,
but Eunice and I are meeting
to go over costumes,
Well, I have to get going
But I'd rather spend time with you,
- Mm,
Yeah, but what if we squeeze in
- Bye,
- Are we that annoying?
I was thinking I need a Korean lesson too,
Want me to teach you?
Exactly,
It's all about the tongue,
Oh, is it now?
Try to keep the tip of your tongue
What am I even saying anyway?
It means, "You are so handsome,"
I think I'm going to be…
…sick,
- Oh! Is she okay?
Honestly, I am as well,
After all the money
we really can't afford a flop,
All right, I better go check on her,
By the way, can you keep an eye out
She should be here any minute now,
Yeah, and don't be stressed,
Okay,
Damn, Who is that?
Oh my God, she's coming towards me,
Oh my God, she's here!
Excuse me, by chance
- Oh, um…
Sorry, Thought you spoke Korean,
You must be Yisoo's assistant,
- Min Ho's super excited to meet you,
Hey,
- What are you doing here?
What a great surprise!
You look amazing,
Is it me,
Uh, my Korean's not perfect,
Do you already know each other?
I'm sorry, Kitty, this is Gigi, She's a
family friend,
Wait, so you're working for Yisoo?
But this is next level! Does this mean
- What happened to FIT?
That's a cool job
I took a semester off
but I had no idea
Damn! Did I miss the big reunion?
Mwah,
- What's up, Kathy?
Well, when I heard
I figured you were the perfect person
Plus, you two together again? Fire!
I can't believe you got Yisoo to give me
Don't act so surprised,
- Literally,
You're the best,
So, I'll see you at the video shoot,
That's the gig,
Yisoo fired her part-time third assistant,
I'm doing both jobs,
That sounds like a huge responsibility
I did not steal my dad's Porsche,
Yeah, that was a crazy night,
How crazy are we talkin'?
Long story,
Mm,
So, um, should we go find Eunice?
Bye,
Gigi's pretty lush, isn't she?
It'll be great for Min Ho
The more the merrier,
A family friend?
It's just a funny way to put it,
Don't get me wrong, I mean,
Min Ho's family
You know, his feelings were just
Oh, like, Min Ho used to have
I mean, can you blame him? She's so cool,
I mean, hard agree, But just real talk,
She was Min Ho's first love,
Hey, How'd you sleep?
Fine, Did anyone see you sneak out?
No, I think the coast was clear,
Oh! I was thinking maybe, if you're free,
would you want to come
Or we could go dancing
Okay, Okay, let's do culture,
- Let's do culture,
- Okay, I'll see you later,
Black sesame latte, right?
I can buy my own coffee,
I'm hoping we can move past
I saw on Instagram you like these,
so I figured I'd get you one
Please take it,
Thanks,
Find anything interesting
Other than photos of her looking chic?
There's one at Nobu with Min Ho's mom,
Did I mention that his family loves her?
Min Ho is with you now,
I don't know,
Maybe because his dad made it clear
and Gigi clearly does,
I mean, they both
they both speak Korean, and they both look
- No wonder she was his first love,
Really? How long did it take you
I… will let you know,
Mm-hmm,
Whatever, The only reason
is because she's looking for someone
You'd be perfect for the job,
I don't know, I was the one
Yes, In hindsight, not your finest moment,
Anyway, you could come with me
help Gigi with the wardrobe stuff,
And assist you in keeping tabs
To be a good assistant,
And to be a good girlfriend,
Yuri's right, I'm spiraling for nothing,
Min Ho's always been Team Kitty,
And it's about time I show him
- Hey, Uh, Min Ho's just getting ready,
I think he's a bit stressed
Yeah,
Oh, and speaking of,
I've been thinking about
I'm sure she would love that,
- You look amazing,
- Hi,
But it's not that kind of date,
Look, I know you're stressed,
I got your favorite facialist
And matching sweatsuits,
Shoot, I'm so sorry, Covey,
Something came up, I've just been so busy,
Gigi and I have
Eunice vetoed all her costumes,
Oh, uh, that sounds so stressful,
Yes, but luckily, Gigi's quite talented,
She's already putting together
Wow, Gigi to the rescue,
What is the story with you two anyway?
Uh, we've basically been friends
Gigi's mum's an actress too,
Sounds glamorous, When was
Don't know,
- What's with all the questions?
I'm gonna go,
Marius told me
And it made me feel kinda weird
With all your inside jokes,
You have nothing to worry about,
Whatever feelings I had, it's in the past,
And whatever you and I have
And besides,
I'd be on the perfect spa date
That's you, by the way,
I might even wear that fire hazard,
I promise not to let you
Mm,
See you at the shoot,
If I'm gonna be a good girlfriend,
I need to be there for Min Ho
Which means I need to win Jiwon over
Jiwon! I heard some teachers
- Maybe you and Alex could--
- What about gelato?
Have you heard of Baby Moo Moo?
Baby Moo Moo? Who hasn't?
The entire aquarium is sold out for weeks,
What if I told you I could get you in?
Then would you give me
For a national treasure?
Oh my gosh, I cannot believe
I mean, it's no Australian Dugong,
which I understand
And speaking of cousins…
What?
Professor Finnerty,
Kitty invited me,
I didn't know you'd be here,
Ah,
Please tell me this isn't
Well, I should be getting to set now,
But you two get your Moo Moo on,
I will, uh, check in later,
Have fun,
Action!
At the start you had my heart
Then you tried to dull my light
I can't be tamed, don't say my name
I'm too smart, too hot
To get caught up in your games
All the boys wanna see me
All the girls wanna be me
At the end of the night
All the guys and the girls
It ain't surprising
I'm hypnotizing
I get them so excited when they dream
'Cause I'm Euniq!
- Cut!
Okay, Kitty, Be cool,
Oh God, I didn't overdress, did I?
Hey, Kitty, You look amazing,
Oh, this? It's nothing,
Oh, well, I go full dirtbag
Confirming, I overdressed, Crap,
Um…
- Hi,
And I'm also willing to work for money
if you're still looking
Oh, also, I saw on Instagram
You must have scrolled really far back,
But… thanks,
Okay, I'm gonna be over there,
Uh, have you seen Min Ho?
Yeah, they're over there,
arguing about whether or not
Got it,
This is such a big day for Min Ho,
I'm sure, especially after all that stuff
Uh, Marius told me,
Hmm, Well, it was
Obviously,
Uh, I… I think that's my cue,
Maybe I can help too,
Why would you be shirtless in an aquarium?
Do I have to say it?
Ah,
Tae-Oh, I understand what you're saying,
But Yisoo made this tank top
Really?
If they were arguing
But they're not, so I need to figure out
What are you doing here?
The same as you, I'm supporting Min Ho,
Please, the only reason
As if you're here
What other reason would I have?
I don't know, Gee, maybe you wanted
Okay, maybe I had
Well, I mean, no one can blame you,
And you have a knack
You deleted the pic I sent you
Q, relax, You can trust me,
Thought I wouldn't go far
You thought you hurt me
While you chase girls
I'll be trapping boys like Jay Park
All the boys wanna see me
Cut!
This isn't working, and we're late,
I hate this choreo!
Well, it's too late to change it,
Okay, then can we
Can't you just hold it?
No, not when we're surrounded by water!
Can somebody please get me green juice?
That will just make you pee even more,
- I've never seen her like this,
Min Ho, I think I know what's wrong,
Eunice and Tae-Oh probably hooked up
Are you serious?
If their fans figure this out,
And my dad will kill me,
Hey, hey, hey,
Have you seen where Min Ho went?
Yeah, he just went along with Gige,
I'm glad I got them back together,
You're watching
and you're not even smiling,
Something's up,
Gigi was Min Ho's first love,
Dae was your first love,
No, but Gigi and Min Ho
I've been watching them all day
and I don't know how to be there
I wish Marius never even told me,
Wait, You're telling me Marius
and made sure
This guy loves leveraging secrets
- Oh my God, I'm so screwed!
You first,
Marius is totally just using Gigi
and gaslighting me,
But that ends now,
So, over the summer
that you don't send when
- Q!
And it's not an excuse, but…
Jin hadn't visited me at USC,
Marius told me he deleted the photo,
If he wants to mess with
that photo's gonna do it,
And if you don't want Marius
I think you have to tell Jin the truth,
Okay, Wish me luck,
What are you doing?
Oh my God, I'm so sorry, I didn't know,
My maid used to do this for me,
This was our only backup dress,
I get that you want to help, but… don't,
Oh, Sorry,
Hey, is Eunice around?
What's that?
Macarons, I ordered them overnight,
Eunice loved them on her Paris tour stop,
I just wanted to remind her
- Are you okay?
There's no way I'm getting this job now,
Hey, if you want this job
don't give up,
Wish me luck,
Action!
You
- Cut!
Oh my God, I'm so sorry, guys,
- Q, we are already delayed,
Guys, no more delays, Come on,
Phones in the bin,
Hey, you signed an NDA,
Um… thanks, Thank you,
Thank you, Dae,
Oh, thank you, guys,
All right, listen up, everyone!
Gigi, Eunice, and I
All right, the song "EUNIQ"
By the way, brilliant idea, Gige,
So, Tae-Oh will be in the background,
- That's my cue!
Are you kidding me? Dude…
- Are you okay?
I can't believe I'm doing this again,
Maybe you shouldn't, Covey,
Gigi, can you fix this?
- No, I'm not a designer,
Yes, yes, great idea,
If anybody can turn this dress
Let me try, I know what I'm doing,
And frankly,
Please, allow me,
I told you I deleted it,
I'm just supposed to believe you?
You thrive on chaos,
You reached out to Gigi to mess
Yeah, because Kitty
For the last time,
I deleted the picture, but you can't
Obviously, you still have
I don't know
'Cause I'm Euniq, Euniq, Euniq
She's fine, I guess, but can't compete
Is that that kid's shirt?
Yep, I dyed Dae's shirt
and the yellow is from the iced turmeric
You know, any kiss-ass can buy coffee,
If you wanna be Yisoo's third assistant,
Euniq, hey!
Cut! Okay, that's a wrap!
- Eunice! Here--
Hey, you think I can meet up
Ah…
I'm not sure,
Then, can you give her these macarons?
Dae, I don't know how to say this…
I think Eunice hooked up
I'm sorry,
No, thanks for telling me,
- Hey,
I know I've been acting a little crazy,
I just wanted to be
and have your back,
But then, Gigi showed up,
and you have all this history
like, effortless together,
So, I guess I felt…
Threatened?
Don't be,
Kitty, you and I aren't effortless, but…
I do like that you make me do things
Like doing that stupid Gangnam dance,
And you do have my back,
You believe in me
And sure, maybe you go overboard
I wouldn't change a thing,
Really?
Yes, And thanks
we're making
Well, I'm happy to do
You mean like our spa date?
Which I hope is still on,
I'll even wear the sweatsuit,
Well, as much as I would love a massage,
I have a ten-page essay due Tuesday,
Tell you what, let me wrap up here,
grab my stuff,
I'll even bring over
You got this, and I've got you,
Hi, roomies,
You're in a good mood,
I got a job interview with Yisoo,
- Oh my God,
Oh, and I totally ripped off
Just not in the way I expected,
You can tell me all the details
- Okay,
Oh my God,
I didn't realize
- Care to catch me up?
- Stay down,
Oh, you… Okay,
You've met your master,
Hey, How'd it go with Alex?
I don't know, Kitty,
What? Why?
Because if we'd known this was a setup,
There are rules against teachers dating,
If Principal Lee found out,
- I didn't mean to cause--
I've seen Clueless,
Whatever spark
I find his cheerfulness annoying,
and his love of boat shoes just deranged,
Wow, okay, I thought
Stop, This isn't about me and Alex at all,
It's about you,
You manipulated me so you could
who I still think
And you put my job in danger, again,
You definitely don't have
so I'm gonna help you with that,
I'm taking back your extension
No, if I don't pass your class,
Then I suggest you hit the books, Hard,
I was so busy
that I forgot
If I don't pass Jiwon's class,
That's the moral of the story, babe
They say it's better to have loved
Than never to have loved at all
That could be a load of shit
But I just need to tell you all
Some mistakes get made
You can think that you're in love
In the end, it's better for me