To hell with him and his ring!
Sulu, listen.
You're better off now.
You got lucky.
That loser never knew how to value you.
At his own wedding,
he was still watching you!
What a loser!
It's a good thing
you didn't end up with him.
- Absolutely right.
- Of course. I'm always right.
Excited much, douche?
Keep it in your pants.
Got it?
The same goes for you.
- Where are you going?
- Hey, Sulu…
- Hey, bozo!
There goes my shot.
I've been working on this forever.
You had to come in between
and spoil my chances.
- If you cross me now…
- Hey!
If you two just sit there,
you'll both miss your chance.
Jackpot!
Guess it's your lucky day!
Hey!
Sulu!
Hey,
I can't swim that well!
Sulu!
Where are you?
Where did she go?
Hey!
Sulu!
Enough with the teasing.
Where are you?
I told you…
Once I catch you,
I'm never letting go.
Sulu!
Come on…
Where are you?
Sulu!
Yes!
Gotcha.
I got her…
Oh no! What the hell!
It's all my fault.
You didn't do anything, right?
No, I did.
I followed you here.
So go back.
- Go… just leave.
- Go where?
Where?
Damn it, I'm trapped in here now.
Help!
Somebody help!
Ready?
I was born ready.
Ready, sir?
Did you ask me?
I've been waiting forever.
You guys took ages to set up.
Get your party started
Shall we start with you, ma'am?
Ms. Vanity.
But you know that already, so…
Avani Shah.
My name is Maruti Kadam.
But they call me AF in my hood.
Aala Flowpara from Nala Sopara.
I want cash. I want fun
When did you decide
to become an influencer?
I've been a performer since I was a kid.
I'm not just an influencer.
I'm all-in-one.
A content creator, director,
assistant director, producer,
singer, and rapper.
Basically, I'm the whole package.
Wanna get busy
I want cash. I want fun
- I want money. And your love
- And your followers?
2.3 million and growing.
Not many, just in the thousands for now.
But it's going to blow up soon.
I want cash. I want fun
- Your favorite food?
- Sushi.
Onion fritters with bread,
anything fried with bread…
Potato patty, mashed veggies,
mincemeat… with bread!
- Coffee or tea?
- Tea, obviously.
Matcha for life.
Nagori tea. Cutting.
Ever tried it?
Come to my hood,
and I will give you a taste.
Wanna get busy
Get your party started
Come, come, O rain!
Watch my swag
Yo fool, I'm amazingly strong
I'm not afraid of the whole world
Come, come, O rain!
Watch my swag
Yo fool, I'm amazingly strong
I'm not afraid of the whole world
I want fame. I got style…
And a million-watt smile
No cash, I'm on fire
My street and my empire
I want cash. I want fun
I want money. And your love
I wanna dance and move up
Wanna get busy
Get your party started
I want cash. I want fun
I want money. And your love
I wanna dance and move up
Wanna get busy
Get your party started
So how did your epic collab come about?
How did that happen?
You're making basic
Marathi grammar mistakes!
How are you going
to write a whole essay?
Grammar accounts for 20 marks…
Maruti, take him.
I just woke up mummy.
So? You stay up all night making videos
and sleep till noon.
When are you actually going
to work and start earning?
This is my work and how I earn.
That's where my revenue
stream comes from.
And I've told you,
it's not "videos", I make reels.
If the public doesn't see my reels,
how will they know of my rap songs?
Just wait till it goes viral…
Only fevers go viral,
nothing else.
- Now go get some water.
- When my reel actually goes viral,
I'll get a solid gold
water tank just for us.
People will be lining up outside,
you'll see.
My class is on!
Sister,
tell your cat to stop licking
my protein powder.
- Or I swear, I'll make her vanish.
- Go fill the water and…
Let her do some work, you pig.
You know what?
No one respects an artist here.
I'm no pig, bro.
Aala Flowpara from Nala Sopara!
You know what I'm saying?!
You feel me, bro?
I'll slap you, silly.
Everyone here is dripping sweat!
When I catch a break
I'm taking you with me, I bet
My drip, my swag
Catch them off guard
No matter the feels
The vibe should hit hard
When I say Nala, you say Sopara!
Nala Sopara!
- Nala Sopara!
- Hey, Maruti…
What now?
Cut the singing and think about
making money, you idiot.
Fine, I'll find someone to
pay my bills as well.
- Hard, bro!
- Disgusting. He has no shame…
and neither do you guys.
Of course, I'm ashamed.
I'm ashamed of living here.
To live in Andheri,
you'll have to work hard, you know.
With a nine-to-five job,
we'll get running water here
before I ever make it to Andheri.
Right!
Like, some rich girl
is just sitting idly waiting for you.
Of course, she is.
Except, she's not sitting idly…
but lying on her buttery soft bed
instead, waiting for me to arrive.
I've been waiting here for 15 minutes.
Hoping you'd stop to catch a breath.
Why is my brother-in-law
practicing golf near the pool?
He's waiting for your approval.
He's thinking that I'm going
to convince you to take a picture
with his business associates
and their families.
Who just have to have
a picture with Ms. Vanity!
Oh my God!
They literally just crashed
into the club just to see you.
We are huge fans.
Can I please get a picture?
Jeej.
I will finish up and come.
Ms. Vanity is always at your service.
Avani,
you know you don't have to, right?
Yeah, but…
I want to.
Okay, Flow, ready?
Camera rolling.
- Cut, cut, cut! One second…
- And action!
Back up a little.
The "F" is crooked again. Yeah.
I am obstinate that
I will get it for sure
Nala Sopara represent
Music.
What you waiting for
What you what you waiting for
- Look up to sky, try to fly
- You did well, bro!
What you waiting for
Wasted so much time
and energy to make this video…
Flashy, but still looks cheap.
We can do better.
I will see my dream come true
You can chop my feet, but I won't kneel
My success will shimmer everywhere
My heart and my mind say
to go with the flow
My thinking is different
My friends are supporting me
Here comes Flowpara
Nala Sopara represent
I said whatever was in my heart
I am the talk of the town
I did whatever my heart said
Bro! Hey!
You can't film here.
Filming isn't prohibited here.
- You broke my camera!
- Who's going to pay for this?
Quit arguing and get out.
Listen, dirtbag, you don't know…
We might live in Nala Sopara,
but this camera's imported
from Taiwan.
How dare you fly
a drone over our house?
House?
You've got to be kidding us!
The drone was in the sky.
- Did the bungalow come with the sky, too?
- Tell me!
I don't care.
Just don't film outside our house.
- Wait a second.
- You can't do that.
If you didn't want anyone
near your place,
why build such a flashy house?
- I said no shooting around here.
- Why…
- They're shooting too!
- Forget them.
Did you even realize
whose house that was?
- No.
- That was Ms. Vanity.
Ms. Vanity… two million followers.
The girl from those underwater pool shots!
- Oh, I see…
- Yeah.
She was checking me out.
And I was looking right back.
Right.
And in the middle of that moment,
if the watchman cracked your skull,
you'd have lost the few brain
cells you have left.
Can I say something?
I want to blow up like her.
I want those numbers.
She's Ms. Vanity.
She's an OG in this field.
That's why she's on top.
You don't get the game.
No. You don't get me.
I'm not here to learn the game.
I'm here to play it.
To win.
I've had a headache since this morning.
- Want some tea?
- Oh!
You get a five-rupee tea for just 2.5.
And that too, only half a cup.
This hotel's king-size bed
has amazing springs.
It's got an attached bathroom too.
- Hey…
- So…
Mark my words.
One day, Ms. Vanity will like, share,
and subscribe to Aala Flowpara.
I swear.
Our brother is sitting there
Bantai, order a bottle
He carries a fragrance
But you ask for the champa flower
The public may be naive
But don't show fake bravado
Don't ask for an Apsara here
Go ahead and ask for Ramba instead
So the plan is, we swish pan
from the main performance…
Can you stop?
From the main performance to Avani,
two or three times.
You should be sipping this
or holding this, okay?
It's orange juice.
Whatever you say, boss.
Mumbai is a city of chaos
You have to pay if you take a ride
Whenever friends gather
There has to be fun
Along with Ramba, some liquor too
Our brother is sitting there
Bantai, order a bottle
He carries a fragrance
But you ask for the champa flower
The public may be naive
But don't show fake bravado
Don't ask for an Apsara here
Go ahead and ask for Ramba instead
Our brother is sitting there
Bantai, order a bottle
He carries a fragrance, but…
I'm jittery, bro.
- Is it gas?
- No.
Here's your jacket.
Fixed it up.
And here's your crown.
- Go, kill it!
- Kill it, man!
What's up, Mumbai?
Let's hear…
Tonight it's the audience
that'll crown me.
India's number one rap concert…
- Yes! Exactly like that!
- Go, just like that. Too good.
- Local hero today, superstar tomorrow.
- Kill it, bro!
So, here's your new firecracker!
Spotify's new find of the year!
Give it up for…
Aala Flowpara
from Nala Sopara!
What's up, peeps?
Once again, Aala Flowpara?
- What the hell?
- Scram!
Spit it, bro.
Maruti!
- Come on, sing.
- Start the song.
Flow…
Hey, hit the music.
He's not singing.
- Just play the track.
- Okay, I will.
Let's go, Maruti!
My youth questions me
And my circumstances ignore me
My pocket is empty
But my morale is still high
Sweat adorns my shoulders
Shoot off the powerful guy
It's the rule of the business
That's why I am still standing here
I am not less than anyone
I have nothing to lose
So I'm not afraid to fail
What will the world say
It doesn't matter to me
The world exists because of me
I don't exist because of the world
Here comes Flowpara from Nala Sopara
I have highlighted it on the map
Don't pity me
I am singing the song straight
From my heart
My home and life may be humble
But I'll unleash riches of my talent
Courage is all I have till the end
I don't want an ordinary death
I want to be immortal
My morale will never break
Even if my back breaks
I have the eyes of a vulture
The lions are roaming fearlessly
The dreams of those
With open eyes should come true
Whoever bears pain should do so wisely
Work shouldn't be sloppy
It should be precise
Let the feels be anything…
But the vibes should rock hard!
Ain't no dream, this is my journey and…
Yo, Miss Vanity, pool girl
It ends where you're at!
That's why life seems like a game
My company has got hard players
This courage isn't borrowed, it's inherent
Nobody knows it now
But I am tomorrow's sensational news
My brother is here!
Crazy…
You nailed it.
What a set!
Even Ms. Vanity was vibing.
- I gave her a look too…
- Side…
- That was hard, bro.
- Thank you.
- See you on the field.
- That was cool.
Thank you.
- Looking smart.
- Thank you.
Oh my God, bro!
Let's go, ladies and gentlemen…
- Where's she?
- Who?
Ms. Vanity.
…for Hip-Hop.
Let's go.
She'll be in the crowd.
It's an old story
From the alleys of Bombay
The message of terror
Suhani in the locality
At such a tender age
There is so much tension
My father is a drunkard
Who splurges my mother's pension
Jaggu also says, boss, agree
Jai Veeru from Kurla consume cannabis
A road of black and yellow taxis and autos
From Andheri to Churchgate
Breakfast on the train
This is Bombay
No, bro. It's Mumbai
No, bro. No, bro
Move, move, move.
She's in the blue dress.
Blue dress.
What are you doing?
Ms. Vanity!
What did you think of the set?
My performance.
Not bad.
For a noob.
She said, not bad, bro!
- Wanna collab?
- Collab?
Avani, stop indulging these losers.
And get in the car.
Collab.
You and I.
DM on Picsta.
She's asking you to DM her.
I already did.
I slid in.
But you didn't reply.
Shut up, loser!
I don't reply to strangers.
This stranger isn't a danger.
Get off my car!
I dropped your name on stage.
That doesn't make us friends.
So, let's get acquaint--
Let's go, bro.
We should get acquainted.
- Yes, acquainted.
- And that means?
You are a rapper, bro
This is Bombay
Avani,
why do you entertain such bums?
Just because he dropped
your name in the rap
doesn't mean you have
to give him attention.
But he was singing so well.
The guy's got talent.
Indeed. Quite talented.
It's not about the talent.
Why are you so bothered
by their interaction?
Please, Shubhangi.
He was acting like a total hood rat.
I thought he was kind of cute.
Are you serious?
Avani, please.
You call him cute?
Hey Avani,
Stray dogs are also cute.
Doesn't mean you take them home.
This has always been her problem.
She feeds a stray dog,
and it follows her home.
I wish he were following me home.
You've got to be kidding me.
Seriously?
Are they following us?
Shall we collab?
Don't encourage him.
Hey, man, drive straight.
Yash, chill.
Be careful, please.
Will you stop?
Why are you overthinking it?
You could pick your nose
and still get likes.
She doesn't pick her nose.
Once in a while, you should.
- It's hygienic.
- Come on, slow down.
Slow down, please.
Yash, please, calm down.
Are we going to pick
our noses together in the collab?
We'll do something epic.
The content will speak for itself.
Neither you nor me.
What is wrong with you?
Slow down!
Shubhangi, shut up.
Who's more popular?
You or me?
Yet, who's the one scared of a collab?
Who's chasing after me desperately?
You or me?
Bro, she's calling me a despo!
You don't get it.
I'm already set.
No duress.
What say?
Stop the car.
What?
Have you lost it?
Stop the car.
I'm not stopping this car.
Stop the car!
- Shubhangi, I am not--
- Stop it!
Has she gone insane?
Let's get out of here.
But where?
You want a collab, right?
Be creative.
Stealthily and slyly
When our eyes lock, what happens?
Should we follow them?
Exactly, follow him.
His ID is Aala Flowpara.
20K followers.
Like, share, and subscribe.
And my ID is…
Fabric_HeartStealer.
Listen, bro.
Drop me at the circle?
I'll take a rickshaw home.
You can even charge me if you want.
Showing off because
the girls are watching?!
Hope you won't make me fall.
Come on.
They call me
the Valentino Rossi of Nala Sopara.
Wanna see a wheelie?
- Okay, let's test your riding skills.
- What?
What are you doing?
Are you nuts?
Are you mad?
How are you, my little Vanities?
Do not try this at home.
I'm taking a small risk today because
I saw someone risk it all on stage,
and ended up just owning it.
Meet my new friend, Aala Flowpara.
Wassup, peeps?
I've accepted his special collab request.
So, bike boy, spill.
- His name…
- Maruti!
Bro, sis said you got home at dawn.
I want the play-by-play.
What went down for three hours?
How? How many times?
- Don't bore me.
- I want every detail.
- Tell me what you did.
- Bro!
Don't be a scum. Let me sleep.
Okay, bro. Okay, I get it.
Is this your friendship?
Is this your love, bro?
You broke my heart for sure.
Well done.
What were you doing
with him all that time?
Tell me!
Why?
What are you doing, bro?
Did you even hit the brakes?
Why do you wanna know?
And what's this you're doing?
- Tell me.
- What's it to you?
- Tell me, please.
- This is exactly why you scare away girls.
Please, tell me.
Back off.
Where did you go with him?
What?!
You ate carbs after midnight?
Please tell me it was only
mixed veggies, not the bread.
I didn't have the bread roll.
I had bread rolls.
With extra butter.
No!
Here.
It tastes amazing.
Just like mom-made things.
Too good.
Does your mom make good
pav bhaji too?
No, my mom makes farsan.
Farsan meaning?
Farsan…
It's a snack.
Like you.
Serious snack attack, you gave
Ms. Vanity.
You've got her feeling the aura,
my bro is Aala Flowpara!
Babe…
He called you a snack,
and you got impressed?
Not exactly.
But yeah, he's kind of interesting.
Interesting.
What next?
Spill.
Come on.
Bro, she isn’t going to text.
You had a shot just for the one night.
So tell me,
did you make good of the chance?
She was the one doing the dance…
Where?
I've seen quite a few verses
in your posts.
You write too?
Why?
Don't I look the type?
It's not that.
My dad loved verses.
Watch out…
or you'll fall to your death in vain,
and I'll spend my youth rotting in jail.
If I wanted to die,
I would've drowned myself
in my pool already.
You know what your tragedy is?
There's a huge ocean out there.
But you want to die in
your 20x20 swimming pool.
Learn from me.
I live in a 10x10 room.
But I live life king-size,
from Virar to Churchgate.
Show me your life then,
from Virar to Churchgate…
Of course.
Whenever you say.
I'll come pick you up.
This one?
Yeah.
Thanks.
I had a good time.
I mean, I enjoyed myself.
Hit me up if you feel like it.
Not that I'm waiting or something.
Ms. Vanity…
I don't have your number.
I'll slide into your DM.
If I feel like it.
She didn't text, did she?
Told you she wouldn't.
Why are you waiting on her?
She texted, didn't she?
Told you she would!
What's this?
She dropped a location pin.
Challenge accepted, bro!
- I got to run!
- Where to?
Catch you in the evening.
- Where are you headed, pumpkin?
- I'll fill you in later.
Never thought you'd hit me up.
Were you waiting for it?
Not really.
You know my friend, Fabric?
He said a girl like you won't
be interested in a guy like me.
Not sure if you're my type.
I always bet on hope.
And in any case,
I have no interest
in becoming your type.
But there's a chance
you could become like me.
Stealthily and slyly
When our eyes lock, what happens?
When the crazy heart beats
For the first time, what happens?
Strangers become
Lovers, lovers, lovers
Unknowingly and inadvertently
They fall in love
What is this?
How does it happen?
Nobody knows that
Oh, wow! Amazing!
This is a sick phone!
For you, this is chump change.
Flow, I'm not your sugar mommy.
Then become one.
- I really don't have an ego.
- So what?
You're only interested
in me because I'm rich?
When I was a kid, I'd decided
my girlfriend had to be
from a posh part of downtown.
Girlfriend?
- So it's official now?
- Let's do it.
Zero percent toxic.
Hundred percent satisfaction.
Or a full refund is guaranteed.
What do you say?
Should I put it on my status?
Stealthily and slyly
When our eyes lock, what happens?
I wandered
All over town
I saw many beauties
I am quite sure
Nobody anywhere
Is like you
It makes the heart go crazy
What is that union?
It's now that I know
What first love really is
Strangers become
Lovers, lovers, lovers
Unknowingly and inadvertently
They fall in love
What is this?
- How does it happen?
- So, what do you think?
Nobody knows that
Fabric and I set this up for you!
Hey, hey, it’s getting away.
My heart prays
If I am destined for it
Then your love is what I seek
When you meet someone
Who strikes the chord of your heart
Then what happens?
When your breaths
Start ringing, what is it?
Strangers become
Lovers, lovers, lovers
Unknowingly and inadvertently
They fall in love
What is this?
How does it happen?
Nobody knows that
Lyra was asking if we're both dating
or just like hooking up?
What did you say?
I said,
"Have you gone nuts, homie?"
Nice!
Company matters.
Homie.
I hope you're not catching feelings.
Are you crazy?
You're casual too, right?
If there's no future to us,
why am I wasting my time with you?
Wait.
Are you mad?
Quit playing.
I can't swim.
I could've drowned.
I won't let you ever drown, Flow.
Remember I told you about a girl?
Avani, my friend.
Mom, hope it's not too spicy
for her.
She is so pretty, right?
Let's take a picture.
I'm shy…
Too good, Auntie.
Thank you.
Hope it's not too spicy.
No, not at all.
Even if it is,
she won't say it to your face.
Just shut up.
Water?
Do you make poha at home?
Sometimes.
But not as tasty as this.
You should try her snacks.
From Nala Sopara to Borivali,
Mom supplies snacks
to every chemist and grocery store.
Under the brand "Kusum Vitthal".
She's Ms. Vanity, sis.
She won't promote
our snacks on her reels.
Flow, don't underestimate me.
Ms. Vanity can do anything.
You just enjoy the fritters.
Okay?
What can I say now?
I'm out of here.
How do you like my mom?
She's awesome.
Isn't she?
She takes after me.
And how do you like my kingdom?
Bet you don't get this view
from your bungalow terrace.
I sit here and write all my tracks.
When Mom starts yapping too much,
I escape here.
Where's your dad?
He bailed when I was five.
Sister says,
Mom and Dad fought a lot.
I don't remember much.
Did you ever try to find him?
Uncle saw him in Satara once.
With a new family.
He looked happy.
Fate has its ways.
Same story here.
But your scene is different.
Both your parents are gone.
But…
how was it before?
Did they love you a lot?
They fought too… like cats and dogs.
I mean,
it didn't faze Tara much or…
I don't know.
Maybe she was used to the drama.
But whenever they fought,
I used to bawl my eyes out.
That day, too, they were yelling,
and I started crying loudly.
Like, like uncontrollably.
Then to cheer me up,
dad took us for a drive and…
And?
They both died in that car accident.
But I survived.
Come on, come on, come on!
Hello!
Is anyone there?
Avani!
Help!
I'm sorry, I panicked.
I didn't know what to do.
You panic. You come to me.
Why did you tell Di and Jeej?
Avani!
- Come outside, I need to talk to you.
- Look what you've done.
I'll take care of it, I'm sorry.
Avani, open the door.
I need to talk to you.
Is that the guy?
Seriously, Avani?
Please tell me you slept with him
out of some weird sense of pity.
Ever heard of protection?
Tara.
Why are we even looking
for a reason here?
She's not serious about him.
She can't be.
Look at him.
It's just Avani being Avani.
Di, I can't have this conversation
with you in front of Vikram.
You should have set boundaries earlier.
I'm not done talking to you.
- Avani, wait! Avani!
- Avani!
- Close to the station?
- At the station.
- Avani, are you serious?
- I'll call you.
- Yeah, you do that.
- Avani, wait.
- Call me.
- Okay?
- Vikram, do something.
- Alright.
- What?
- Let's go.
- Avani.
- What's wrong?
Can we just go, Flow?
- Avani!
- Unbelievable!
What happened?
The vibe at home was tense.
Di and Jeej found out about us.
So? Big deal.
You're unbelievable.
I'm…
pregnant.
Do you want tea?
No, Auntie.
I'm okay, thank you.
Want some fried snacks?
I'll make it in two minutes.
Why are you bugging her?
She said no.
Why are you getting annoyed?
- Are you hungry?
- No.
Auntie, I'm hungry.
Then go home.
Hello?
I'm coming.
What's the matter?
How's the ride?
- Avani wants to take off for a few days.
- Take off?
A trip to Goa with you, homie.
These are the keys to
the beach house in Goa.
The caretaker knows you're coming.
Also…
Tara and Vikram want to talk to you.
They're waiting downstairs.
Here?
- Jojo!
- Popo!
Tara.
Where's Avani?
She's upstairs.
And she's upset.
If she sees you two, she'll lose it.
Yes, I know.
That's why I wanted to talk to you.
Look where you are.
What the hell are you doing, Avani?
Have you lost your mind?
- Tea.
- No, thanks.
- You?
- No.
If you need anything, I'm inside.
Okay?
Are you having his kid now?
Are you going to pack snacks
for the rest of your life?
Let's get real, Avani.
I've spoken to Dr. Bhatia.
- Once you're back from Goa…
- Whose idea was this?
Yours, or Tara and Vikram's?
How does that matter?
We just want what's best for you.
Okay, Lyra.
I decide what's best for me.
Not you.
Not Tara. Not Vikram.
Avani goes through these phases.
She's a kid,
she's not thinking straight.
You're smart and sensible.
I can tell.
What do you mean?
Just convince her to come home.
Please.
And we will take care of the situation.
Situation?
She's pregnant.
Just say it.
- Talk to her.
- Tara…
Why are we dragging this out?
This is about money, right?
Name your price.
Consider it your fee or something.
- Just get her to come home.
- Maruti!
- We'll handle the rest.
What's going on?
Who is it?
What's the matter?
Who's he?
A friend.
- What?
- A friend.
You go ahead.
Go. It's nothing.
When a man knows his own worth,
no amount of money
in the world can buy him.
So, how are you going to afford me?
Beat it. Go.
Buzz off. Go away.
He's just as crazy as she is.
Hey, you, come here.
Yes, I'm talking to you.
What is it?
Middle-class dreams often die…
due to the arrogance of poverty.
You know what?
I used to dream of hearing
my voice on the radio.
I wanted to be a singer.
But I couldn't.
I became a husband.
And then a father.
To carry that weight,
I became a driver.
I thought it was just a temporary thing,
but I never realized
when it became permanent.
Are you going to be an artist
with a kid in your arms?
Hold a crying baby in one hand,
and a mic in the other?
All this swagger
will vanish in a snap,
once you see a wet nappy.
And only the stench will remain…
The stench of dying dreams.
He gets it, ma'am.
Don't worry.
Rai Harrie…
You ask who runnin' this?
It's 7Bantaiz.
Your man is cut from a rare breed
Baby girl, the whole world knows
My face and my creed
Even the goons
In your city bow down at my feet
My lane, my game, my fame
It's unmatched, it's elite
Bros are asking that it's so crowded
First you leave my hand
And then you say it's my fault
I've contacts with all influential people
My name is branded
Gold necklace is what I wear
From zero to hero
From coals to diamonds
I've counted all the stars
Munna Bhai talk
Collar up Jackie Shroff
I'm on top
Whatever I do is top notch
Yeah, we bringing
All this fire outta Mumbai City
Punjabi flow
Marathi boy and this song rocks
Just like India's winning shot of '83!
This is real hip hop
And not some nonsense
Those who stand by me are special
Rest are inconsequential
I can bring powerful people to tears
It's no mean feat for me
Here, everything gets done slowly, slowly
You ask who runnin' this?
It's 7Bantaiz
Your man is cut from a rare breed
Baby girl, the whole world knows
My face and my creed
Even the goons
In your city bow down at my feet
My lane, my game, my fame
It's unmatched, it's elite
Bengali Baba calls it the curse of Saturn.
Meaning?
When your stars go astray,
you're helpless in every way.
If you got something to say,
say it to my face.
Police!
Two-wheeler…
- Sir.
- Parked near the road.
What's the problem?
Where are you from?
Hey, listen, Pesky Tawde is outside.
How long are you going to take?
Look at this mess.
Tell your boss to loosen his pockets.
Or this pool's going
to look just like the lake outside.
Get it?
Then go swim with the fishes.
Keep it down.
Tawde will hear you.
I will handle him.
But wrap this up quickly.
I got to drain the pool tomorrow.
Such a headache.
Why'd he show up
when I'm already swamped?
Jai Hind, sir.
Tell me,
whose car is that?
Well, I was going to tell you…
- No, I mean…
- Not your boss's, right?
No.
- Is your license renewed?
- No, sir.
- No?
- No.
Then who are these new faces?
For training?
Last batch of the season, sir.
They're leaving in the morning.
I'll drain the pool
for maintenance, too.
You said that last week.
You playing me?
No, sir.
Promise this time.
Come tomorrow.
The pool will be closed.
Listen,
if I come back
and see anyone else with you,
I'm going to lock all of you up.
- Clear?
- Yes, sir.
Full of crap.
These are our guests.
They've come from Mumbai.
Their bike broke down.
Give them a deluxe room.
- Okay?
- Yes, sir.
Madam, you can stay here.
No issues.
It's safe.
Okay?
Call me if you need anything.
- You have my number?
- Yes, I do.
- Take good care of them.
- Sure, sir.
Jai Hind, sir.
Come,
I'll show you the room.
Come, brother.
This way.
I don't want to crowd the house.
And what? Am I supposed to raise
my kid in a dump?
What will I eat?
What will I feed them?
This just got real, bro.
Now I get why my dad left.
He had two kids at 21.
It must've scared the hell out of him.
Is the kid yours?
Are you sure?
Stop talking trash.
I'll slap the hell out of you.
My Avani is loyal.
And it is my baby.
It's just that I don't want to be a dad.
Is that so hard to get?
I got it.
But you explain it to her.
Explain it with love.
And let me know what she says.
Okay, catch you later.
You think I'm trapping you, Flow?
It's not that.
Then…
Don't be so distant.
We'll figure this out.
Lyra gave the doctor's
number to Fabric.
Should we go there after this trip?
Do you really want to raise a child?
Did I say that?
You don't want to raise a kid,
and you don't want to abort either.
- Then what do you want?
- Nothing.
You, Lyra, and Fabric already
planned it all out, right?
What?
Stop acting like you're concerned
and involved.
So I'm acting?
Where are you going?
Are you okay?
What?
I am fine.
Want a beer?
A little bit, come on!
Congratulations.
No one and nothing is worth
burdening your heart like this.
Take a deep breath and just exhale all
that is bothering you.
Remember this.
Madam, maintenance is underway.
The pool's filthy.
What do you want for lunch?
Whatever you get.
I'm down with that.
I don't give a…
We don't have a kitchen here.
Stash it in the red cupboard.
We have to order in.
Tell me quickly so I can call.
Listen, just order two Chinese dishes
and be done with it.
Okay.
Tell me something.
Where's the nearest garage?
It's three kilometers out.
The mechanic is at the corner.
- Near the market?
- Yes.
- Sir.
- Yes?
- Tell madam to get out.
- Okay.
I got to drain the pool.
Police will come and chew me out.
- I'll let her know. Keep this.
- Please.
Please tell her.
- Sure.
- I'll bring your food.
Okay.
Ms. Vanity.
This isn’t your kitchen…
where a chef snaps his fingers,
and a buffet appears.
You've got to tell them what to order.
Don't throw shade at me, Flow.
I'm stuck here because
we took your bike.
Because you said
you needed a break.
In one second, my life went from Gully Boy
to Sairat.
I just hope your crazy Jeej hasn't
wiped out my family yet.
Oh, please.
Don't be so dramatic.
Besides, this isn't some inter-caste
or love-jihad romance drama.
Popo,
if I speak up now, she'll lose it.
You're Avani Shah,
and I'm Maruti Kadam.
Your family will have a bigger issue with
this poor Kadam than with some rich Khan.
Just go figure out how
we're moving forward, Maruti.
I'm already on it,
but you've got to get out
of the pool first.
Come to the garage with me.
Just admit you need cash
for bike repair.
Take it from my bag.
Look here…
Hello! Excuse me!
I only took this much.
Don't accuse me of looting you later.
And don't worry,
I'll pay you back when we return home.
You keep floating.
We're in deep shit,
and she wants to be a mermaid.
Now chin up and smile!
You’re gonna be fine!
You're my destination, my love
You're my--
Bapya, write this order down.
One fried rice.
Two chicken gravies.
Yeah, whatever works.
Yes, of course.
And add 500 extra for us.
Yeah, sure.
Guess it's your lucky day.
Stop whining.
We'll square it soon.
Let me handle the pump house.
It's a mess.
Send it fast.
This plumber is useless.
He didn't fix a damn thing.
Pick up the phone, slacker!
I'm never hiring him again.
Who knows where the hell he is!
Didn't fix anything.
I'll have to clean this up.
What the hell did he do?
Damn it.
What's the issue?
Just try and ask for work again, Keshu!
Keshu, what kind of mess
have you stuck me in?
Who's there?
Who is it?
Rascal!
Who's there?
What's going on?
Turn on! Come on!
Hey… come on!
You're my destination, my love
My heart says that, my love
Ganga!
Whenever a monster
is born on this planet…
A savior is born to slay him.
Wow, man.
That was sick.
Hurry up!
Listen, the parcel's ready,
I'm going to deliver it. Got it?
Vasanta!
I got your order!
Hello, madam!
Madam!
Hello!
Your noodles, ma'am.
Rise and shine.
Hope she's not dead.
Anyone there?
It's not for you.
It's for her.
Got it?
Yes.
Don't eat it.
Or you're on the menu.
Okay, bye.
Yes.
I don't see a soul in these ruins.
Yes. Don't worry,
I delivered it to madam.
It's done, boss.
Guess it's your lucky day.
Yes, don't stress.
Okay, fine.
I'm calling it a day, okay?
Yes.
Eyes of a vulture
The lions are roaming fearlessly
Dreams of those with open eyes
Help!
Hasn't it been fixed yet?
No, sir. It took some time
to find the replacement wire.
Hey!
Don't ruin Konkan's reputation.
Want me to lock you up?
Even the bike is scared of you.
Finally, it starts.
But how will you ride in this storm?
What can I do, sir?
I have to leave now
to reach Goa by tonight.
- Take this.
- No thanks, sir.
Take it.
Chow down.
Don't be formal.
Honestly, I was starving.
- Sir.
- Yes?
Can I take a selfie?
- With me?
- Yes, sir.
I'll have some major cred
with the boys in
my hood when they see
I'm pals with a top cop.
Click, fast.
Duty calls.
A crocodile wandered
into the village nearby.
- Into a coconut factory.
- Really?
Yes.
Locals pelted it with
coconuts and killed it.
- Really?
- Yeah.
See, we wrecked the forests,
blew up the mountains.
Filled lakes to build towers.
- Where are the crocodiles supposed to go?
- Right.
- I'm off. Duty first.
- Okay, sir.
- Catch you later.
- Thanks for everything.
Bye.
- Sir.
- Yes?
- Seatbelt.
- Oh.
See, I noticed.
Hope it doesn't act up again.
Popo!
Is anyone there?
Help!
Flow!
Is anyone there?
Help!
Flow!
Call Flow!
Come on, pick up.
Pick up.
Pick up--
Avani?!
Hey, how did she leave you here?
Avani!
Hello!
Help!
Anyone?
Vasanta!
Avani!
Come on!
Avani, get up.
Avani!
Get up, Avani, please.
Hello!
Avani!
What happened?
How did you fall?
How did you get hurt?
I don't know.
How did you fall?
Did Vasanta do something?
I don't know.
Okay, wait.
I'll figure something out. Wait.
Flow!
Are you okay? Flow?
- Are you okay?
- No. No. My arm…
My arm.
My arm! I can't move it.
Don't worry, Flow.
- What is it?
- Wait,
- give me your hand.
- No, don't touch it.
- Hold still. No, don't.
- Okay.
- Avani, please.
- Nothing will happen.
- Are you mad? Don't touch it.
- Just stop moving.
- Just trust me, okay?
- Please.
On the count of three.
- Okay?
- Yes.
One…
You broke my arm.
Shut up!
You said on count of three.
My arm. You broke my arm.
- Shut up, I fixed it.
- My hand…
Try lifting your arm!
Yes.
You're my destination, my love
My heart says that, my love
Where the hell is the caretaker?
Hello, Fabric?
Hello! Hello--
Fabric?
You called Fabric?
Phone's dead.
- Should have called the cops instead!
- The phone is dead.
You better not say a word.
This is all your fault.
You're jinxed.
You think this is my fault?
You were told to stay away
from the pool.
But do you ever listen to anyone?
Keep swimming in your pool now.
How do you even unlock this phone?
Unbelievable!
You think I did this on purpose?
We're stuck here because of you.
If you hadn't been so stubborn,
we'd be halfway to Goa.
It's all my fault.
You didn't do anything, right?
No, I did.
I followed you here.
So go back.
- Go… just leave.
- Go where?
Where?
Some genius made this pool
20 feet deep with no ladders!
Damn it, I'm trapped in here now.
Help!
Somebody, help!
Somebody help!
Oh God, please save me as well.
Avani!
I unscrewed it.
Come on, come on, come on!
Hello!
Is anyone there?
Avani.
Help!
Avani!
- Who was it?
- Help.
Did someone come?
I heard a car.
- Help!
Is anyone out there?
Help!
I think they are gone.
You should've screamed louder.
Had you screamed louder…
What else could I do?
Someone was here, but they left.
You blew our chance.
Avani, you just kept whistling…
And just shut him up!
Popo, quiet!
Did you see an exit through the drain?
Shut him up, or I will…
Did you find a way out?
No, the water was too high.
So I didn't go any further.
- What do you mean you didn't go ahead?
- Means I didn't go ahead.
How many times have I told you?
I can't swim!
You go if you want to.
Fine.
I'll go.
You keep ranting, I'll go check.
Popo, quiet!
Popo!
Avani!
- Quiet, Popo.
- Avani! Avani!
What the hell is that?
Avani, get back.
Back up slowly.
I'm right here.
Don't worry.
Don't look at it.
Don't make eye contact.
Keep moving.
Back up.
Avani, back up.
Move!
Stay back…
It's going…
Where did it come from?
Why did you open the drain?
We had to try something
to get out of here.
How was I supposed to know…
the Godzilla of the gutter
was hiding in there.
Flow.
Why isn't it attacking us?
No clue, I'm also confused.
In Khoon Bhari Maang,
it tore off Rekha's face in an instant.
- Khoon Bhari Maang?
- Yes.
I'm yours, my love
You're my beloved
An action thriller by Hrithik's dad.
Haven't you seen it on cable TV?
Flow, can you focus?
Yeah, just saying.
How do we get out?
Should've thought about
that before jumping in.
Quiet.
It didn't come because of my noise.
It came because
of the smell of your blood.
Should we try to escape
through the drain?
Wow! Genius!
And what if it follows?
No need.
Let's just sit tight.
Someone will show up, eventually.
The moonlight is grinning
How could I ever sleep?
She didn't meet me
But I'll definitely miss her
Let me live in her memories
Because she's miles away from me
The moonlight is grinning
How could I ever sleep?
She didn't meet me
But I'll definitely miss her
Let me live in her memories
Because she's miles away from me
You also smile a little
My life is so boring
Make it cheery
My dream is unfulfilled
Make it come true
I want to live
But you are far away from me
The little flowers have turned
Into withered leaves
I belong to her now
Her arrival has brought me to a halt
I no longer live in this world
I love you, but I don't say it to you
I don't cry copiously
In this black and white world
She was colorful and bright
At times her fault, at times mine
These are only filmy dialogues, though
She is my ride, it feels she is by my side
You're the only true one
Nobody by the side
Used to fly high, my kite
I remember all those wild nights
Wild nights
The moonlight is grinning
How could I ever sleep?
She didn't meet me
But I'll definitely miss her
Let me live in her memories
Because she's miles away from me
Avani, I think it's gone.
Looks like it's gone.
Avani!
What happened?
Are you okay?
Look over there.
She was pregnant.
That's why she didn't attack.
She just wants a safe space.
Safe space?
For whom?
She wants a safe space!
This is why I prefer beaches.
Pools are useless.
The sight of those eggs
is making me hungry.
What?
Have you trained Popo?
Sit, stand, fetch?
Can he order food online?
He's way smarter than you.
Oh really?
Let's test him then.
And see how smart he really is.
Popo!
Fetch the parcel.
Pick it up and throw it.
Popo!
Pick up the box and throw.
- Pick up the box and throw.
- Come on, Popo.
- Pick up and throw, baby.
- Grab it with your mouth and throw!
- Pick up and throw.
- I'm telling him the same thing.
He understands me better.
What nonsense?
Popo!
- Yes, come on, baby.
- Pick up, pick up!
- Hey, you idiot. Not there, over here.
- Come on…
- Don't talk to him like that.
- That's how we show love in the hood.
Popo!
- Come, Popo. Yes, yes!
- Popo, look at me.
- Bring it to me.
- Come on, Popo.
Grab and throw, baby.
- Bring it to me.
- Come on, Popo.
- Yes, baby.
- Grab that box.
- Box. Grab it.
- Yes, Popo.
- Yes.
- Grab it.
- Come on.
- Popo!
Popo!
What?
- Yes. Jump, baby.
- Popo, grab it by your mouth.
- Yes, drop it.
- Yes.
- Back up, back up a little
- Come on, Popo.
- Tell him to back up.
- Yes.
Run! Take a run up!
Run and throw.
- Yes. Yes, you got this.
- Oh shit… we're done for!
Popo is really smart.
Shut up.
That's it for me.
I can't stay here waiting to die.
Let's get out of here.
Can you reach the light?
No, push me up.
You said you're 5'8"?
And you said you're 5'7".
Okay, forget that…
Reach for the light.
There's a crevice under it.
- See it?
- Yeah, but…
Then what?
Grab the light, then the crevice.
You can easily get
to the top from there.
Easy on my left shoulder, though.
On the count of three.
I'll push you up.
Got it?
- Okay.
Three.
Two.
One.
You good?
Come on, let's try again.
Avani, you've got to hurry!
She's coming this way.
Grab the crevice, Avani.
Hurry up!
Avani, please.
Smash the glass.
I can't hold on any longer, Avani!
Please hurry!
Hurry up, Avani!
Come on.
Avani, you've got to hurry up!
She's almost here!
She's too close, Avani.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Did you get a grip?
Avani, pull yourself up! Lift your legs…
Come on.
Hey!
Hold on, Avani!
Flow…
Oh God.
How's your hand?
Put your weight on it and keep it steady.
Yeah, I've reached out
to all her friends in Goa.
Called all her favorite properties.
Nothing.
This is her last location.
Yeah, we're talking
to the cops right now.
I'll keep you updated.
Arjun, this is so not like Avani.
To go AWOL like this for 24 hours now.
Something's really wrong.
You dragged me here
as if I kidnapped them!
Our friend is also missing.
Did we blame you?
You're the last person he called!
But that call dropped!
I've been trying to tell that to the cops!
Sir, what's this?
Take what you want and let us go.
Hey, silence!
- What's this?
- Hey!
- What's your full name?
- Fabric.
Your real name!
Purushottam Dhamdhere.
Yes, hold on.
A team from the Goa Police is patrolling
and alerting every hospital, checkpoint,
and toll booth
along the Goa-Bombay highway.
Cyber team is triangulating
their last available location.
So, don't worry.
- Tara…
- Thank you.
We'll find them, okay?
I really want her to be safe.
- Don't worry, they're looking for her.
- One minute, bro.
Excuse me, madam.
Maruti is a solid guy.
Don't worry.
He's got her back.
You also chill.
Just wanted to say that.
Eat up. It's good.
We aren't going anywhere.
Let me know if you need cash.
Sorry.
What are you getting out of this?
What are you trying to prove?
Just tell me.
If you were me,
what would you do?
I wouldn't have a baby.
I have so much left to do, Avani.
I want to be someone, make it big…
Escape from my hellhole.
If I were you,
I'd appreciate that
we aren't ready for this baby.
You hooked up with me because you
wanted a thrill in your boring life.
Now this kid is your escape,
your new "project".
If you were a project to me,
then what was I to you?
You also used me
to escape your shitty life!
So please, stop acting like
you're real, and I'm fake.
You think I'm ready?
- You think I planned all of this?
- Then why are you doing this?
Why do you want the baby, Avani?
Listen, we can fake the fame
and the followers.
But parenting isn’t an act.
You have to do it for real.
Haven't you seen my mom and sister?
Yes.
I've seen them.
I've seen a lot of love
in that small house.
Oh, God!
Spare me the rich-kid drama.
Don't romanticize my poverty for me.
You live in 10,000 square feet.
With a pool.
We get one water tank
for the whole locality.
You have everything, Avani.
But you don't value it.
I have everything I don't want, Flow.
I'm alone in that
10,000 square feet home.
Maybe this baby…
Maybe I won't feel lonely anymore.
I don't know.
Maybe when it's here,
I won't miss my parents so much.
I don't know.
Exactly.
You don't know.
You don't know, Avani.
You're placing a huge bet
on this "maybe".
A baby won't fix your loneliness
or your issues.
Someday you'll find a deeper reason
to have a baby… not an excuse.
Till then, I'm with you.
I promise.
I'll stand by you like a one-man army.
Can't tell if it's rain or tears.
Damn it!
Nothing works in this dump!
Two ladders, both useless.
It's rusted.
Its screws are loose too.
If there were another ladder,
I'd manage to climb up.
What shoddy construction!
Shall we try again, Avani?
Flow!
- Flow!
- Yeah?
Flow.
Popo!
She's the same limping croc.
How the hell did it get up there?
She went down the drain, right?
She's heading for Popo.
There has to be a way
out through the drain.
Flow!
Avani, should we go check it?
- Flow!
- What?
She's heading towards Popo!
Yeah, we have to do something.
We've got to do something.
Let's go.
Popo! Come down.
- Popo!
- Get down here.
Popo!
Come on, Popo.
Look at me.
Popo, come on, come on.
Come on.
Come here.
Popo.
Popo, come here.
Come here.
Please, please, please, just jump.
Baby, come on, please, just jump.
Come on, come on.
Hurry up!
Flow!
Please!
No!
Avani…
Avani!
Listen.
You've got to get out of here, okay?
You'll go down the drain
and get out of here.
And get help.
Okay?
Avani!
Avani.
Listen, listen, Avani.
Listen to me.
Get out through the drain,
and get help, okay?
- No.
- What happened?
I'm not going without you.
I can't swim.
You know that.
But you'll go.
You know why?
Because you're brave.
You're strong. Right?
You'll go, right?
You'll go, won't you, Avani?
- Okay?
- Yes, okay.
Wait a second.
Take this.
It's my pendant.
Pry open the drain cover
with its sharp edge.
And keep this lighter…
Just in case…
You need to start a fire.
Okay? Okay.
Avani, wait up.
You'll come back for me, right?
You won't forget me, right?
I know you'll be back.
I know.
Okay.
Go, go, go.
Go fast.
Hurry up.
Help!
Is anyone there?
Is anybody there?
Who is fragrant and who nourishes all
Like the fruit falls off from
The bondage of the stem
May we be liberated from death
From mortality
We worship the three-eyed One
You're my destination, my love
My heart says that, my love
Hello!
- Hello!
- Yes, Vasanta?
- Yes--
- Hello!
Now, it's switched off.
Something's wrong.
Let's go check.
Sir…
- My brother-in-law…
- Yes.
- He's getting married.
- Okay.
I need to go buy some stuff.
Didn't he just get married last year?
This is his second marriage.
I'll be damned!
He's having fun!
- Alright, off you go.
- Okay.
Guess, it's your lucky day.
Please, please, please.
Oh God, please.
Hello!
Come on, please.
I'll be damned!
- Sir!
- Hey!
- Sir! It's me, sir!
- Come out.
Save me, sir.
What are you doing down there?
Come on out.
Sir, I'm stuck in here.
Please, help.
Come out, slowly.
Come on.
I can't swim.
I'll drown.
- The water is rising!
- Okay.
- My feet aren't touching the bottom!
- Fine, let me think.
Sir, help.
Yes, hang on.
- Sir, hurry up, please.
- Yeah, yeah.
No, not that way.
- Don't go there. It's locked.
- What?
It's locked.
Damn it!
- Find a rope or something.
- Wait.
Find a rope. Hurry up!
Yes, wait.
Let me look.
- Hurry up, sir.
- Coming!
Sir!
- Sir! Sir!
- Come here!
Come over here. Slow and steady.
I can't.
- Damn it.
- Hurry up, sir.
Hang on,
I'm coming.
Flow!
Avani!
There are two of them.
I know.
Avani…
Flow!
Keep kicking.
Avani…
Come on.
Grab the door handle!
Get in.
Flow…
It's got a radio!
Hello!
Can anyone hear me?
- Hello! Anybody there?
- Hello?
- Hello!
- Check the dashboard.
Here…
Be careful with that.
How do you open this?
- Flow.
- Yeah?
Flow!
The second one is behind you.
Go, go, go now!
Hurry up, Avani.
Hurry up.
Hit harder, Avani!
Avani!
Be careful.
Watch out for the shards.
Watch out!
You'll hurt yourself.
Go, go, go!
Flow!
Avani, fire!
Fire! Fire! Fire!
Shoot at it!
- Flow!
- Fire!
Maruti, move!
Flow…
The drain…
We'll have to use the drain.
It's our only way out.
Flow!
We'll have to use the drain, okay?
It's our only way out.
Flow!
Flow, listen to me!
Listen to me!
Flow!
Do you trust me?
Okay?
- You go. Leave…
- No.
No, Flow.
I'm not going alone this time.
Do you trust me?
Do you trust me?!
Okay?
Flow! Flow!
Flow, are you okay?
Flow, you okay?
You go ahead.
I can't.
Flow. Listen to me. Listen to me, okay?
There's a way out.
There is a way out. Okay?
There is a way out. I saw it. Okay?
- Stay strong. We're almost there. Okay?
- Go…
Just trust me.
- Flow!
- Please.
Flow!
Now! Now!
Flow?
One, two, three…
Flow.
Come on.
One, two, three…
Flow?
Flow? Flow, come on.
Flow, come on!
Come on, I know you're in there.
I know you are.
One, two, three…
Come on, Flow!
Please, come on, wake up!
Maruti, please, come on!
Please!
Please.
Please…
Flow…
Hey.
Flow.
You saved me.
And you saved me.
My leg… I can't feel my leg.
Are they still there,
or did the croc get to them?
They're there.
Maybe the croc didn't like the taste.
Don't make me laugh, Missy.
Everything hurts.
Stop it.
Can I say something?
Yeah.
Who was the brave one in the pool?
You or me?
Who got us to this cursed place?
Who was willing to make
the ultimate sacrifice?
You or me?
Who killed the crocodile?
You…
or me?
My heart lived wholeheartedly
Once I was set free
I've taken a swig
From the cup of my dreams
I've started to live…
After all that you've gone through,
- what do you think love is?
- Love is…
All real.
No filter.
Love is… something else.
It's beyond words.
I can't describe what I feel.
Too deep?
Simply put…
love is a collab.
Where you got to like,
share, and subscribe.
So, when's your next collab dropping?
What do you say?