♪ Hold me tight,
let the darkness drown me ♪
♪ Even one second of truth is enough
to lose myself in it ♪
♪ Hold me tight,
let the darkness drown me ♪
♪ Even one second of truth is enough
to lose myself in it ♪
♪ Whether you're light or a lie,
I can't pull myself away ♪
♪ In this game,
truth or lie no longer matters ♪
[Queen of Darkness]
[Episode 23]
These fair-weather folks
used to treat me like their savior,
but the moment things turned,
they ran faster than anyone else.
Dad,
Ye Ying and Huo Xiao
raided the illicit warehouse,
tracked down
everyone tied to gang crime,
and even found our
secret gang crime accounts.
Dad,
are we done for?
Shut up!
Worthless fool.
Scared like this over a little setback?
It's not even over yet.
Quit looking so glum.
Dad.
Why don't we just run, Dad?
As long as we're still standing,
there's always another way, Dad.
Can we outrun this?
Besides, making me give up
what I've plotted half my life,
what I've slaved to build,
how's that any different from dying?
Fine then.
If they want to play,
I'll play to the end.
The higher-ups just want a result.
So I'll find a scapegoat
to shut them up.
There's no loyalty
money can't buy.
Don't move.
Put it on.
Someone sent me to get you out.
Let's go.
Chairman Song.
I knew it.
You'd never leave me behind.
Don't worry.
They didn't get a word
out of me.
You're smart.
You know what to say, and what not to.
Once I'm overseas,
you'll finally be able to relax.
You're not going anywhere.
I've already planned
where you should go.
What do you mean?
What are you doing?
[Business Plan]
Song Pa!
I've always been loyal to you.
You want me to be your scapegoat?
Your death
will make all the crimes
naturally.
[Business Plan] fall on you.
Then I'll finally sleep in peace.
Do it.
Song Pa!
What are you doing?
Don't let him go that easily.
Song Pa!
Inspector Jiang.
Scared already?
The real show hasn't started.
So arrogant usually.
What a coward.
Other places aren't safe anymore.
Only here.
Song Pa's influence can't reach here.
I've got people guarding all exits outside.
But there are many new faces.
Probably Song Pa's spies.
They found us this fast.
You've got two choices now.
Either
cooperate with me
and become a key witness
under our protection.
You're the reason I'm in this mess.
And now you want to
climb over my back?
Dream on!
And you,
you're just like Ye Hong.
Can't appreciate a peaceful life,
but had to dig into the dirty business,
stirring up all this trouble.
Let me sober you up.
If it weren't for us,
you'd be concrete by now.
I'm not like Huo Xiao.
Our gang's ways
are not exactly civilized.
I've got ways to make you agree.
Shall we start with your eyes,
or...?
A hundred million.
Give me a hundred million.
Then send me abroad.
In Song Pa's eyes,
you're just a disposable pawn.
To me,
you're just a criminal.
Bargaining with me?
Are you crazy?
If you insist on walking the path to death,
we won't stop you.
In fact,
we'd be happy to see you off.
I'm curious though,
if we toss you out right now,
how long do you think you'll last?
Rong.
What are you doing?
What are you all doing?
Let me go!
I said let me go!
I see you're acting more
like a gangster lately.
You become like the company
you keep.
Maybe
this is what they call a match.
I agree.
I agree to testify as a witness.
But you have to keep me alive.
Song Pa has huge influence here.
[Hengyu County] Deep roots run strong.
Officail Website : kissasian.be  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
This time,
he'll do everything to stop us.
It'll be dangerous.
But it's also
our one shot to bring him down.
This isn't just about
revenge for the gang.
It's personal too.
Every one of us in Qingyun Gang,
isn't afraid of death.
Avenge Leader Ye!
According to Jiang Meng,
we found a recording of his dirty deals
with Song Pa.
But a few of our guys
got ambushed and hurt.
Go treat your wounds first.
Okay.
To make sure nothing goes wrong.
I'll take Jiang Meng
and head out of the city from the north.
At that time,
all police units will
escort us along the way.
You take the evidence
and go south.
The terrain there is flat,
harder to ambush.
It's relatively safe.
Everyone, get ready.
Yes.
Be careful.
You still owe me a lot of promises.
I'm not letting anything happen to you.
Relax.
I'm not that easy to kill.
What are you staring at?
Get back to work.
Useless bunch!
No matter what happens.
Get Jiang Meng
and all that evidence back!
Dad.
Right now,
the police are protecting them too.
I'm afraid
they won't be easy to take down.
Push me to the edge.
Then a lot of people
will go down with me.
Use all connections,
all strength.
No matter what it takes,
we can't let them survive this!
Yes.
Hear that?
Yes, yes.
Prosecutor,
this is the witness
in the Song family gang crime case.
I formally
hand him over to you.
Okay, Inspector Huo.
It's finally over.
Why?
We're colleagues.
Why help Song Pa silence him?
Inspector Huo.
Song Pa took my family hostage.
He said if I didn't kill Jiang Meng by 3,
my whole family would die.
I didn't have a choice.
Take him away.
Yes, sir.
Wait.
No.
No...
Move!
- Move!
- No.
[Huo Xiao]
I shook off the killers
and reached the chief's office.
Jiang Meng is dead.
There's a mole.
Go, now!
Ye Ying.
Ye Ying!
What a pity.
You almost made it.
But with Jiang Meng dead,
the fence-sitters are back to me.
Now
it's my turn to strike back.
The best strategy is to retreat.
Time to slip away first.
Ye Ying.
Didn't expect to
end up in my hands, huh?
This is called.
"Wait for the prey to come to you."
So what do you want?
To kill me?
If you fell into my dad's hands,
you might be dead.
But in mine,
I'm willing to
take the risk
to take you
far away.
The old me might've said no,
but now it's different.
But
how will you protect me?
As long as you obediently follow me
and do as I say,
I'd never let anything happen to you.
Then I better show you what I've got.
So kinky.
Quite a few tricks, huh?
Why pretend to be a pure saint before?
See.
Showing your wild side at last.
The exciting part
is yet to come.
Remember your masterpiece?
You're not Ye Ying.
You're An Ning!
You're alive.
You shameless woman.
You dared to lie to me!
I just love your unrepentant ways.
Otherwise, I might've hesitated.
♪ Mist coils around the sleeping forest ♪
♪ Memories scattered
through cracks of darkness ♪
♪ How to escape this real-feeling dream ♪
♪ Lies reflect in water's gleam ♪
♪ Traces of existence
can never be erased ♪
♪ How to find the self I can't reclaim ♪
♪ Fly away, hear she says ♪
♪ She'll fly out from
thorns of woven lies ♪
♪ Pierce the fog,
shatter this dream tonight ♪
♪ Burn like fire ♪
♪ Just burn like fire ♪
♪ The maze in the abyss starts to clear ♪
♪ Yet night keep on whispering ♪
♪ Surrender to fate,
no clear direction ahead ♪
♪ She will rise as the dawn
that breaks the darkness ♪
♪ Never slowing down,
for tomorrow cannot be stopped ♪
♪ Surrender to love and find the way ♪
♪ Even if fate tries to forget her ♪
♪ Never despair,
for the heart burns with endless light ♪
♪ Waiting for dawn ♪
[Copyright of this short drama
belongs to]
[Shanghai Chuqi Weishi
Culture Media Co., Ltd.]
[and Youku Information Technology (Beijing)
[Co., Ltd.]
[Youku Information Technology (Beijing)
[holds exclusive global online
and broadcast rights]