QUEEN OF TEARS
EPISODE 6
Why did Hae-in suddenly go to Germany?
Beats me.
She just said it was a private matter.
What are you doing?
I can't smoke
since there are cameras everywhere.
All the cameras are off,
and the helpers are gone.
This is my only chance.
Let me smoke one and have a glass.
Let's do that next time, okay?
Take your time. The night is young.
Hae-in is gone, and Hyun-woo left too.
It may look like they don't get along,
but I beg to differ.
They like each other,
but they don't know that.
That's why they're never
on the same page. Fools.
Hong Hae-in!
Dream on if your plan is to find something
on Hyun-woo and kick him out.
Grace has been watching him
for three years
and has found nothing.
-Really?
-I'm telling you.
But someone who's clean
wouldn't have something like this.
Mr. Kim, why are you calling me?
We shouldn't call each other
when our bosses are on vacation.
Where are you? Jeju Island?
Somewhere better.
Get to the point.
I'll hang up if you talk shop.
Is Ms. Hong in Frankfurt?
I think Mr. Baek flew out yesterday,
but he didn't tell me his destination.
How would I know where your boss went?
Why did Ms. Hong go to Germany?
Why are you curious?
Both of them suddenly left,
and I'm in the dark.
Don't bother looking for them
if they don't tell you.
It's wrong.
Plus, I haven't had
a week-long break in years.
So don't call me for trivial
or important matters. Okay?
I'm sure
that something's up.
Where in the world are they?
Let's go home.
I thought I'd find it here.
A miraculous way to live.
Or a place of no sadness.
But there was none.
All I wanted
was to go home with you.
You two must be madly in love.
But do you think
you can do that somewhere else?
My lovely wife is also waiting for me
back home.
I wonder what secret he's hiding.
It might be nothing.
It doesn't matter.
A relationship
is bound to crumble with a secret.
That's the power of it.
Why cup noodles out of the blue?
I want to give it a try.
I know it's full of chemicals and MSG,
but I'd be upset if I died
without having a taste.
Just wait three minutes.
Then I'll talk in the meantime.
I'll talk while we wait so it won't seem
too serious.
About what?
Things I'd like you to do.
I'm listening.
Don't hold
memorial services for me.
I don't like any of the food.
If you want to commemorate me,
just think of me while having
some wine at a nice place.
And place a few Hercyna handbags
on the table.
Are you being like this
because the clinic rejected you?
They could call you back
with good news down the road.
Write up a nice obituary as well.
Add some moving stories about me.
There are none.
No, I'm sure there are some.
Also…
There's more?
Stay alert at my funeral.
Everyone who disliked me will attend.
Hyeon-ju, Jeong-mi, Eun-jin, and Ye-na.
Listen carefully
to what they say.
And?
Sue them all if they bad-mouth me.
Sue them for defaming the dead.
-Me?
-Then, should I?
-I'll be in the coffin.
-Come on.
I don't think anyone would mourn.
So, you should.
You'll cry, right?
Cry when there are many people.
It's better if there are cameras around.
Do you want me
to cry?
Yes and no.
I want you to feel sad.
But I don't want you
to be too sad.
I'd feel uneasy
if you remembered me forever,
but I'd be enraged
if you moved on quickly.
Then what should I do?
I'd…
like you
to think it's a shame.
I'd like you to pity
that I'm no longer around.
That's enough.
Your three minutes are up.
Last one.
I have a will.
I wrote it before we married.
My mom refused to give us
her blessings if I didn't write one.
You won't inherit anything.
That's what it says. But…
I'm going to revise it.
I didn't know this day would come so soon.
I just wrote it so we could get married.
What's wrong?
Are you upset?
No.
I'm thankful
that you'd do that.
Please do that.
But…
not right now.
I won't allow it.
Then when?
Later.
Once you're fully recovered,
you can do that.
But for now…
Let's eat.
It's been over three minutes.
They'll get soggy.
JUSEONG TECH 24
Put that back. We need to go.
I couldn't buy this
even after waiting for months.
But she has it stashed in her closet.
Hey, how would things have turned out
had we been rich like this?
Would our lives have been different?
Are you envious?
I know I would've been smarter
than Soo-cheol.
How is he so dumb?
I've never met anyone
who was easier to fool than him.
That's why you could marry him.
Do you know what he said to me?
I don't like Lee Seung-gi,
despite his fame.
Why?
He sang about a woman older than him.
I don't like women who are older than me.
My sister's bullied me
ever since I was little,
so I'm traumatized.
I see.
My body reacts first
when I meet an older woman.
I get goosebumps and rashes.
Even I'm fascinated by myself.
I'm like an age detector.
How do you think he'll react
if he finds out that his wife
is actually five years older than him?
Goodness.
You don't touch the head with iron.
Bring me the bamboo knife.
Yes, ma'am.
What is that?
This? It's wild ginseng.
It's not just any wild ginseng.
It's a century old.
This gift from God
can even bring the dead back to life.
Are you serious?
Figuratively speaking.
Soo-cheol's anxiety and excessive sweating
are due to his weak energy.
So he needs to eat this regularly.
The entire length
of this wild ginseng is 1.3 meters.
I've had wild ginseng for 20 years now,
but I've never seen one this big before.
Hey, give this to me.
Don't be silly.
Do you like wild ginseng?
Seon-hwa, how much was this?
I'll pay you more.
I bought this for no one else but my son.
I can't do that.
It's not for me.
It's for your other child, Hae-in.
What? Why would you
when she's already so strong?
Do you want her to become Superwoman?
She's not strong!
She could get sick too.
Hae-in has rarely caught a cold
in her lifetime, so don't worry about her.
Seon-hwa.
You can never guarantee one's health.
It doesn't mean she'll be healthy forever.
Let me take care of my children's health.
Hey, you said this was 1.3 meters long.
Why don't you split it with Hae-in?
It's not that I don't want to share.
Wild ginseng is only effective
if you have it whole.
Okay, then let Hae-in have it all.
You haven't said anything
for the past 20 years, so why now?
Stop being greedy if you've had it
for that long, you scumbag!
Goodness. What's the matter with her?
I think it's menopause.
Hey, eat it before she comes back.
Take it.
-Please chop it into thirds.
-Okay.
Beom-jun.
Hey, Beom-ja.
Beom-seok left for Hawaii last night.
We never got to get together.
What are you doing?
What is that?
Are you feeding the snail right now?
Paengsun's shell broke.
She must be in so much pain.
She needs to eat eggshells
for more calcium,
but she just won't eat any.
What's it to you if that snail
broke its shell and has no appetite?
There you go again.
When a snail loses its shell--
I don't care!
It'll probably turn into a slug!
She'll die without her shell.
Simply put,
she's suffering from an incurable illness.
She's terminally ill.
-What's wrong?
-Beom-jun.
What is it?
Who is it this time?
My poor Beom-jun…
Beom-ja.
I'm sorry to say this.
But you're our most pitiful family member
after Paengsun.
Beom-jun.
Have a glass.
You're just dying to drink, aren't you?
What should I do with my poor brother?
They're all in German.
We're in Germany after all.
Should I turn it off?
I'll sleep in that room.
You can sleep wherever you want.
Do you want me to take that room?
That's not what I said.
Just sleep wherever you want.
Do as you want. Follow your heart.
What is it?
Can I…
I mean, from today on…
Can I sleep in your room?
I guess
you're still uncomfortable.
I never said that.
I didn't say anything.
Don't jump to conclusions. I'm…
thinking about it.
Okay.
All right.
Think about it.
So…
just today?
Or from now on?
From this day until forever?
Yes, this day until forever.
Deal.
-Deal.
-I see. "Deal"?
That's what you said, right?
Unbelievable.
Do you know Kim Ye-na?
The CEO of Royal,
whom we met at the Hercyna party.
Yes, I do.
She got
into a car accident last week.
She fainted and went to the ER.
Then, her husband
and her attorney rushed over.
-Her attorney?
-Yes.
Her husband thought she was dying,
so he wanted her to sign a few things.
I see.
He desperately told the doctor
that she couldn't die just yet
because she had to sign something.
He caused a scene
and said she had to revise her will.
He was so noisy that she woke up.
I see.
I saw it coming.
He looks like a human version of Shrek.
How could that monster be so heinous?
His wife is on the brink of death,
and he only cares for her money?
He deserves to die.
Don't talk so harshly.
Right. It's not just him.
The first thing people ask
when they hear about someone's death is,
"So who's receiving all the inheritance?"
"The cash? Real estate?
Stocks? Inheritance tax?"
Some even say there are husbands
who laugh in the toilet
at their wife's funeral.
Not everyone…
is like you.
What? Like me?
Do you remember the first thing you said
when I said I was sick?
I love you, Hong Hae-in.
I love you.
"I love you."
Oh, did I?
Did you know
that those words comforted me so much?
Well…
Don't put too much emphasis
on what I said--
You wanted to see if I was breathing well.
Good morning.
You panicked when I coughed.
Are you okay? Please call the ambulance.
You didn't care about my will
or the fortune you'd get.
You never asked.
You stayed up all night worrying about me.
That's my husband.
You're one of a kind.
Yes.
You're right.
There's no one like me.
And now,
you flew across the world just for me.
It was only possible
thanks to the direct flight.
I'm truly blessed with a good husband.
No.
That's one thing you don't have.
Hyun-woo, where are you?
You haven't been picking up.
Sorry, I can't go.
I should've told you, but I was too busy.
Where are you?
I can't say right now. Later.
Just answer me "yes" or "no."
Are you being held against your will?
What are you saying? No, I'm not.
Then why can't you come?
Cheol-seung told his wife
she couldn't come,
and she hit him with a slipper.
But he still came.
-She hit my head.
-So where are you?
We're having a blast.
-Dae-ho--
-I know.
He probably brought crates
full of soju and beer.
Yeong-beom and Sang-pil
are probably lighting the wood,
and you're holding a pair of tongs.
-Who bought this meat?
-Gosh.
Cheol-seung probably bought pork shoulder
since it's chewier than pork belly.
We even have pork neck.
It's juicy and soft.
Yes, there's juicy pork neck,
chewy pork shoulder,
beer, and soju.
But we wouldn't have finished them
if I was there.
I would've ruined the mood.
So where are you?
Germany.
So you ended up going.
You better not regret it.
We're going to dip
some grilled pork neck in red pepper paste
and mix some alcohol too.
Okay, have fun.
Hae-in and I will have beer
and schweinshaxe.
-Hey, what's "schweinshaxe"?
-Isn't that German pig feet?
I don't care. You'll pay for this.
I'm not returning your entry fee.
What is it?
Hyun-woo can't come.
-Did he get caught?
-Did he?
No.
He's changed.
He's totally changed.
Honey, look at this.
The lab reached out.
There's this treatment called
the Filgrastim shot.
They want to raise my WBC with that
even though it's not guaranteed.
They still want to try.
Hey, that's great.
See? I told you there'd be good news.
You're right.
Maintaining a good immune system
is crucial for this treatment.
Maintain a good body temperature
so you won't catch a cold.
Make sure you have protein too.
And stay away from raw foods
in case of blood poisoning.
I see.
How do you know these things?
It's common sense.
Since when?
JUSEONG TECH 24
Hello. How may I help you?
Yes, you do need to help me.
Pardon?
How was it?
-It was great.
-I'm glad.
Thank you, ma'am.
Stay alert, will you?
-What's wrong?
-"What's wrong?"
Hey.
Look at this.
You're on the dashcam footage.
Why am I…
Yes, you idiot. You could've been caught.
Why do I look so fat?
Is that important?
Why were you standing there
when there were cars driving around?
-Is it my fault?
-Then is it mine?
Aren't we on the same team?
You should support me
so I can do well out there.
But what is this?
I did all the work and almost got caught,
thanks to your incompetence.
Be quiet.
What if Mr. Yoon hadn't found this?
Stay alert.
We're almost there.
Almost where?
Will Eun-sung bring the big shots
and swallow Queens whole?
It's none of your business.
Just take your share and leave.
That's true.
But what'll happen to the family
once he takes over Queens?
Don't tell me you're worried
about Soo-cheol?
Me?
Stay professional.
That was insulting.
Do you think
I have feelings for that idiot?
Forget it then.
Don't forget. You're not a rich madam
just because people treat you like one.
Whatever. I don't even want to become one.
I can't even smoke in peace.
Right. Quit smoking, will you?
I had to learn how to edit videos
so I could erase
footage of you smoking in the garden!
That's great.
Become a YouTuber once you retire.
Hey!
Mother.
Hello, ma'am.
When did you arrive?
Who were you shouting at?
Sorry? Who?
It was your voice.
I didn't say anything.
Ma'am, did you hear something?
No, I didn't hear anything.
Mother, you're scaring me.
I have a headache
since I couldn't sleep last night.
Oh, dear.
You need a scalp massage.
You should dip your body
in some pink salt first.
After you.
You're the best masseuse ever.
I feel much better already.
By the way,
I heard Mr. Baek went to Germany.
I guess so.
I see.
Why?
It's nothing.
Tell me.
To be honest,
I made a mistake.
What mistake?
A few days ago,
I accidentally told Mr. Baek
about Ms. Hong's will.
What?
He said he heard everything
and demanded me to tell the truth.
So?
I knew he'd eventually find out,
so I told him roughly.
And he's been causing
issues at work ever since.
Hyun-woo?
Mr. Hong is doing his utmost best
to carry out
an investment project with Mr. Yoon.
But Mr. Baek said they had
to get a validity test first,
so the project is at risk
of getting canceled.
What did you say?
We're on a time crunch, Grandfather.
What if Mr. Yoon changes his mind?
So? Business is about being tenacious.
You shouldn't be anxious.
Come on. We're not the ones investing.
He's the investor here,
so why are we being calculating?
I'm so frustrated.
We should be.
Do you think his money is free, you fool?
Hyun-woo is careful
and meticulous, if anything.
So do as he says.
Hyun-woo is so annoying.
Chairman Hong.
The scholarship ceremony will soon begin.
Soo-cheol, play with your friends.
This way.
But they're not my friends.
Hey, how dare you
throw a ball at my brother's head?
He's already dumb as is.
What if he becomes even dumber?
What's your name?
Hong Hae-in. Why?
What's his deal?
Stop crying.
You're so noisy.
Hey.
Yes?
Are you the chairman's grandson?
Yes.
And is she your older sister?
Are you the only son?
I used to have an older brother
but not anymore.
I see. So you're the only son.
Blow into it.
Let's get married later.
-No.
-Why not?
You little…
Grandfather!
Don't only listen to him.
Hear me out too. I…
I thought long and hard
before bringing this up.
-So why would you…
-What an idiot.
By the way, how is Geon-u
so handsome?
Thank you.
He doesn't take after you.
What do you mean? We're practically twins.
Did he take a DNA test?
Of course. As soon as he was born.
You saw the result.
They're 99.99% a match.
Do you not see Da-hye here?
Hey, the DNA test is a formality.
You all took one.
Don't be rude to your grandfather.
I was only joking since Geon-u
is so handsome and smart.
I can put up with people
bad-mouthing my parents,
but not my wife or son.
I don't think I can eat.
Let's go, honey.
What a terrible son.
Yes, he can put up well
with people bad-mouthing his parents.
Look at his eyebrows.
I had the same ones as a baby.
They thickened with time.
And look at his nose.
I hit my nose while playing soccer,
so it's a bit low.
But I had the same nose.
My nose bridge was so high.
-People thought I was mixed.
-I see.
His thick hair and his toes…
I feel bad for you.
Our family must have strong genes.
He doesn't resemble you.
I'm sorry.
-About what?
-I'm the weakest one in the family.
My sister bosses me around,
and my grandfather scolds me all the time.
That's why you're being mistreated.
I'll do better
so that no one will dare mistreat you.
The resort complex project will be a hit.
I'll do my best for your sake.
Trust me.
It's a bit undercooked.
It'll cook more as we eat.
Hello, sir. Can I ask you for directions?
Goodness, you found the right guy.
I know all the paved
and unpaved roads around here.
I know where the dogs go
and even where the birds fly.
I know everything.
-So ask me.
-Okay.
It's a place that was on YouTube.
-Do you know where it is?
-YouTube?
Was our village on YouTube?
Which area was it?
-Here.
-Hold on.
This must be it.
Didn't Hong Hae-in sit here?
Hong Hae-in.
You look pretty.
What are they all doing there?
That's where Hae-in sat.
A conglomerate heiress's seat.
And that's the wall she leaned on.
It's like posing
in front of the Berlin Wall.
Something like that.
What do you mean?
They're copying what Hae-in did
in her free time.
Isn't that the dog?
Hae-in, please say something.
Hello. I'm Hong Hae-in of Queens Group.
He's the best leader.
Isn't this the dog?
Yes, it is.
We were right.
Smile.
Father, Yongdu-ri has become famous.
HONG HAE-IN VISITED
HONG HAE-IN WAS HERE
Hae-in was here.
Why won't they let us in?
Hae-in took one bite of their duck.
Now, people line up to eat here
in the early morning,
but still can't get in.
Both the marinated crab
and frozen pork belly restaurants
are fully booked
and delivering everywhere.
It's crazy.
Why are they doing this?
Well… They may not be able
to dress like the rich,
so they want to at least eat like them.
I guess it's something like that.
Hae-in is the best.
I strived for decades
to make Yongdu-ri known.
But she achieved that in less than a day.
It's safe to say that you have
the upper hand in the election.
Your daughter-in-law
is helping our economy.
What is Seok-hun up to?
I bet he feels defeated.
Maybe he wishes Hae-in would visit
his mother's restaurant.
I doubt it.
Chew slowly,
or you'll have an upset stomach.
Apples are best for indigestion.
Why?
Why would she eat that?
She should've had pears instead.
So why apples?
Seok-hun, that sly scumbag.
Yongdu-ri has become home to apples
to outsiders
just because Hae-in took a bite.
I think it's game over.
YONGDU-RI EQUALS DELICIOUS APPLES
Let's hurry.
You're finally busy now.
What a great day.
Take the entire box.
-The video is trending.
-Yes.
It's reached over 500,000 views.
Mi-seon, I became a fan
of Ms. Hong after her visit.
How was there a halo around her
when she introduced herself
as the family's daughter-in-law?
There was a lobster truck behind her.
Maybe that was it.
Here. Check this out.
Someone from Jeju ordered
our marinated crab.
Goodness, my crabs
will get to visit Jeju before I do.
-Lucky you.
-Right.
Hold on.
-What's wrong?
-What do you mean?
You look like a famished woman
who's disappointed
to find no rice in the cooker.
Seok-hun has been promoting his apples,
so how could you upload a video
of Hae-in eating one?
-Did you?
-Did I?
Sorry, I'll edit it out.
Forget it. Over 500,000 people watched it.
It's too late now!
Then let's ask Hae-in to visit again.
-Yes.
-She should come.
She can do an eating show
with your dad's pears
and strut down Hong Hae-in's Path.
What path?
The women's association began
a new project.
Since our village has become famous,
we'll decorate the entrance
and call it "Hong Hae-in's Path."
-That's right.
-We'll get the portrait rights.
Then, we'll display
a photo of her and Hyun-woo.
Also known as "Yongdu-ri Queen's Path."
"Walk down this path,
and your love will come true."
Let's add that too.
-Get out!
-Goodness!
Get out and don't visit anytime soon!
Goodness.
Gosh.
What?
QUEEN'S HAIR SALON
Too late. He's married.
You should've come five years sooner.
Just go away, will you?
People here
easily say hello if you lock eyes.
It's a nice culture.
You must be happy
that you're popular with all women,
including
the Yongdu-ri principal's daughter.
The principal's daughter?
So-yeong?
I see. Is that her name?
I heard she was kind and pretty.
Well…
She was cute and had short hair.
Yes, she did.
I see.
Is she your first love
that Mi-seon mentioned?
She wasn't my first love.
If your entire family knew her,
does that mean you were engaged?
Come on.
That's ridiculous.
We never even had lunch.
We never did anything,
so how's she my first love?
You don't have to do anything.
You're happy to watch them from afar.
You can't stop thinking about them.
You take a detour
just to see them once more.
If you did those for the first time,
then that's your first love.
That was quite specific.
Speaking from experience?
You could say that.
You were happy to see him from afar.
You couldn't stop thinking about him.
And you even took a detour?
Right.
Who was he?
Every girl falls in love with one
at least once.
A guy on the bus.
A guy on the bus?
Did you take the bus to school?
That can't be.
Who are they?
The CCTV cameras have been malfunctioning
lately, and they're the repairmen.
It'll take about an hour, sir.
It's all done.
Yes, I'm sure it was tough for you too.
You stayed around long enough.
Did you find it?
No.
-Are you sure this is it?
-I think so.
It was three years ago.
Maybe they threw it away.
Do you think so?
It's good.
Do they have that much time?
Those people are doing nothing
in front of that fountain.
They're just wasting time sunbathing.
They're just feeding the pigeons.
They're resting
while doing meaningless things.
Exactly. They're wasting time
doing meaningless things.
Are they bragging
about the time they have?
How extravagant.
Trying to make money off
of common four-leaf clovers?
What a fraud.
What kind of fool would buy such things?
Are you getting one?
Yeah. Just for fun.
That's expensive for some leaves.
What's wrong?
I'm a bit stunned right now.
Why? What's wrong?
-My weight…
-Your weight?
It went up by 3 kg.
I've gained 3 kg
since my hospital visit in Korea.
-What?
-Don't you normally lose weight when sick?
Is that important right now?
What do you know? No one has ever told you
that you had three months left to live.
I've been pretty all my life,
so what if I turn ugly?
You'll only remember my ugly face.
I won't allow that.
Well…
You won't believe me
if I said you're pretty
no matter your weight, will you?
So…
I have gained weight.
-That's not what I meant.
-Just watch.
I'm going to be gorgeous until I die.
I'll be back.
I'm hungry.
How long were you looking for me?
For about an hour.
Time keeps fading away.
I don't have much time as is.
Do you not remember again?
No, I do.
-I just saw someone.
-Who?
My older brother.
When I was nine,
we went on a boat ride
during our summer vacation.
We got into a mysterious accident.
-There!
-Hae-in!
Hae-in! Goodness!
Gosh, Hae-in!
Are you okay?
-Are you all right?
-Mom, where's Su-wan?
He saved me.
Su-wan?
He was just…
Su-wan!
Please save my boy!
-Su-wan!
-One, two, three, four.
-Five, six, seven, eight, nine…
-Su-wan!
That's how
he died.
After losing her son,
my mom couldn't
eat, sleep, or forgive me
for a very long time.
And I felt bad
for Su-wan.
It wasn't your fault.
I know.
But I couldn't shake off the guilt.
Because it felt like
I stole his life.
I heard this somewhere.
When you're about to die,
the person who loved you the most
picks you up
in the form of an angel.
Su-wan…
who sacrificed his life for me…
Maybe he came
because it's time.
Delirium is one of the many side effects
of your injection.
It's a hallucination. It's not an angel.
Is that so?
It's part of the treatment.
It's not easy
to survive an illness.
But…
you must pull through, Hae-in.
You're right.
And I will.
But…
let's say a lot of time passed,
and you died.
Then I'll become an angel and pick you up.
If I show up,
it'll be less scary for you.
Are you sure?
That it'll be less scary?
Of course. I'll be the prettiest angel.
What is it?
Okay.
You do that.
But for now,
let's dig in.
What?
Let's eat up
and stay strong.
JUSEONG TECH
JUSEONG TECH 24
CLOSED
DATA RECOVERY
JUSEONG TECH 24
WE HAVE SHUT DOWN FOR PERSONAL REASONS
Yes. That's perfect.
This is northwest.
This is the direction that's in charge
of money, success, and luck.
It's great that you put up
an enterprising painting
like this here.
It finally found its owner.
It looks much better here.
You've given me such a huge gift.
How can I repay you?
There's no need.
I only gave it to you out of respect.
Right.
About that resort complex…
I heard a consulting firm is checking
its validity and profitability.
Yes, my grandson-in-law
advised me to do so.
I'm glad. It's good to be sure.
I'm talking to other companies too,
so don't feel pressured.
What? Other companies? I heard
Chairman Yeom has been busy lately.
Are you speaking with him too?
Gosh, I hope Chairman Yeom
doesn't steal
this great opportunity from us.
That can't happen.
-Sir.
-What is it?
How much money did Mr. Song embezzle?
Thirteen billion won, sir.
And no one knew?
-This whole time?
-I'm sorry.
He set the workers' wages
higher than normal
or manipulated financial statements
based on the certificates of deposit.
Will he keep his mouth shut?
Our attorneys are present
while the prosecution interrogates him.
He won't tell a soul.
But here's the problem.
It was quite a hefty sum,
so the higher-ups will be involved.
They could summon you too,
so you should brace yourself.
But of course, our law firm
will do their best to prevent that.
Beom-jun.
Yes, Father.
This isn't
about Mr. Song.
They were after me!
Who the hell did it?
Who told the prosecution about it?
It must've been someone very close to you.
I'll find them.
They will pay for this.
Goodness.
What is that?
What is it?
It's an RF transmitter
VOX listening device.
It's only activated when it hears
a certain level of noise or human voice.
Who the hell was brazen enough to do this?
Given the size of this device,
I think we can find
a microwave receiver in a 2-km radius.
We can wire the 30 billion
to Mr. Jin's account.
Then, sell the stocks under borrowed names
and send them in small chunks.
Yes, do that and inform Mr. Jin.
-Hold on.
-Yes, sir.
Why was this in Hyun-woo's office?
Anything else?
There was a safe in Mr. Baek's room.
Open it.
Why can't I get a hold of you?
Do you know what happened last night?
Your grandfather's study was bugged.
He's already on edge
because his financial manager
was accused of embezzlement.
-So?
-"So?"
Your husband set up the bug.
Do you have proof?
That's exactly why I'm calling.
We found a receiver in his room.
Anyone could've placed it there
while we were gone.
The house was empty for days.
Are you all stupid?
Don't take his side.
I had found it odd that Hyun-woo
was so against Soo-cheol's business idea.
Check the CCTV cameras
before pointing your finger at him.
MOM
See? I'm all you got, aren't I?
Just admit it.
Yes, I'm here.
The store is closed.
No, for good. They've shut down.
What did you give them?
Then look across the street.
My car is there.
PUBLIC PARKING LOT
What? You weren't lying.
Why did you park here?
The key is on the front right wheel.
What's going on?
Send me my dashcam's SD card.
And find out when the store closed.
Is this a case? With a suspect?
Something like that. Thanks in advance.
I may be a divorce attorney,
but I've always wanted
to work on criminal cases.
Don't you worry.
Where'd you go?
I was on the phone.
What's it about?
I was calling Yang-gi.
Did anyone else call you?
Like who?
My mom or others.
Don't pick up any calls from my family.
Why not?
Just don't.
MOTHER-IN-LAW
Don't answer it.
I can't be stressed
when taking the injections.
POWER OFF
This is Moh Seul-hee.
It's Oh Sun-yeong.
What do you mean? It's Seul-hee.
She's Oh Sun-yeong
who died thirty years ago.
So this Oh Sun-yeong died 30 years ago.
-And she's actually Moh Seul-hee?
-Exactly.
Then where is the real Moh Seul-hee?
I'm not sure. However…
Sun-yeong was arrested for adultery
three years prior to her death,
and she gave birth behind bars.
She has a child?
Unbelievable.
IMPRISONED WHEN 4 MONTHS PREGNANT
GAVE BIRTH TO A BOY
Father, we should wait
until Hyun-woo comes.
Be quiet!
What?
-How dare he?
-What is it?
DIVORCE SETTLEMENT AGREEMENT
Goodness.
SIGNED BAEK HYUN-WOO
HONG HAE-IN
Do I need to pray?
The therapy results come out tomorrow.
I need all the luck I can get.
Why is there a long line?
Should we check it out?
You don't like to wait in line.
Right, I don't do that.
I'd feel like an ordinary person.
I hate that.
But?
But…
strangely enough,
I'd like to be ordinary for once.
I want to wait in line and just hope
that they'll still have a kebab
left for me.
Why don't you get in line?
I'll be back.
She needs…
all the luck she can get.
Can you still not reach them?
No, their phones are turned off.
-Jeez.
-A divorce?
I looked into him,
and the friend he met
the most often these days
was Kim Yang-gi, a divorce attorney.
That might not be anything,
but there's a bigger problem.
It's where Mr. Kim works.
-It's Apollon.
-What?
Isn't that Chairman Yeom's law firm?
Yes, so I'm worried
that Mr. Baek may have handed over
the bugged files to him.
That must mean Hyun-woo
was the whistleblower, right?
You shouldn't jump to conclusions.
She's right.
Hyun-woo doesn't know anything
about the secret fund.
I don't want to hear it. Call them.
Tell them to come home right now!
I found it.
It was still here.
Are you serious?
MOM
DAD
Hyun-woo.
I got it.
What's that? What is he holding?
MOM
NEW MESSAGE
Hae-in, I found it. On my way here--
DIVORCE SETTLEMENT AGREEMENT
Tell me this isn't true.
Say it.
Deny it.
-Hae-in--
-Say it.
Tell me it's not true.
Tell me it wasn't you.
No.
It was me.
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you.
-I'm okay. Take it.
-Mr. Baek--
I'm really okay.
But I--
I have a driver.
Wait. Slow down.
Sorry?
Slow down a bit.
You're happy to watch them from afar.
You can't stop thinking about them.
You take a detour
just to see them once more.
If you did those for the first time,
then that's your first love.
Sir, please follow that bus.
Sorry?
That bus will cross the bridge.
It's okay. Please follow it.
QUEEN OF TEARS
You've given up everything?
What will you do? Do something if you can!
Stop playing. You disgust me.
He bugged your room.
But I can look past them.
Why would you?
She knows about the divorce.
The Audit Team will do that.
You will be kicked out mercilessly.
-He sent the flowers to a Kim Min-ji.
-Where is she right now?
How feisty.
What if I replaced him?
But please keep your distance
from Yoon Eun-sung.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim