- Didn’t you say you wanted to
act in something I direct?
- Why did you include Raffy in this project?
- Was there really no one else?
- Why? Scared of losing?
- I never lose.
- How about this, Rome?
- Let me serve him up for you.
Whether you take him or not, that’s your call.
- If we do it one more time, will you tell Jack?
- Why would I?
- Something this delicious…
- I’d rather keep to myself.
- Nice move.
Sneaking your crush into the project.
- If you like him that much,
you should try kissing him.
- Am I too late?
- Guys, this is my friend Boston.
- Mind if I join your friend group?
Tua.
Check that guy out.
He’s a looker.
Damn.
Is this place always this wild?
It always is.
If you want to have fun tonight,
don’t hold back.
Come on, Tua. Come!
Dean.
What took you so long?
I had to drag Tua here.
He’s drunk and whining about going home.
This is my friend Boston.
We studied Business Management together
before I transferred here.
This is Dean, my boyfriend.
And that’s Tua,
a friend from the same faculty.
You’ve got good taste.
Of course.
What about you, Tua?
Why didn’t you bring your partner?
He doesn’t have one.
Help him find one.
Don’t.
Hey, I’ll go get us some drinks.
Come with me.
Sure.
Go all in tonight.
I’ll take care of you.
Hey.
Keep this pose.
Why?
Let me take a photo of you.
I like capturing moments after sex.
Do you take photos
of everyone you sleep with?
Not everyone.
Only some who are special to me.
Here we go.
Okay.
Remember, this is your mark.
Let me check your shirt.
Ready?
One, two, three.
Here you go.
Tua, are you okay seeing your first again?
You don’t have to rub it in.
Poor you. Your first had to be
the most notorious one out there.
Yes, he is.
And you’re the one who
dragged me to see him that night.
So that’s my fault?
You left with him on your own.
I didn’t force you. Right?
Yeah. Just forget it.
I’ll take that as material to grow from.
Art never comes from happiness anyway.
Okay, okay.
Hey.
If you want to erase someone from the past,
you need someone new.
Here he comes. Your someone new.
So, how was the kiss?
I haven’t had the guts to talk to him yet.
Then talk to him. Go on.
Trust me.
Bye now.
See you upstairs, Arnold.
Tua.
What’s the next outfit?
I’ll grab it for you.
Let me help.
Hey.
Hm?
I want to talk about that kiss.
You should know, that night I…
Oh, come on.
It’s totally fine.
No problem at all.
You were drunk. I was drunk too.
Don’t overthink it.
I’m not thinking about it either.
Yeah. I’m not overthinking it.
I just wanted to tease you.
Now that we’ve kissed,
your love scenes should be easier.
Change your pants.
You somehow managed to
sneak into this project.
What could I do?
Jack asked me.
Did he? Or did he just feel sorry for you?
At least that’s better than
sleeping your way into a role.
What’s that called?
That’s called ex-boyfriends
who are still in love and still hooking up.
Come on.
Get to the set. Go.
Poor thing.
You confessed to Jack,
but he turned you down.
You decided to audition,
and all you got was a supporting role.
Just don’t fall.
Or I will step right on you.
Someone like you can’t touch me.
Ready?
Get to your mark.
Right here?
Yeah. Get ready to shoot.
Hey.
I’m heading out. In a rush.
Aren’t you going to eat?
No. I need to
open a bank account for the play.
See you. Bye.
What’s wrong? You can’t eat that?
I don’t like seafood.
It sometimes gives me a rash.
Then take this.
Mine is chicken and garlic.
You can eat chicken, right?
It’s fine. I can order something.
You eat your food.
Oh, just eat. Here.
People don’t know you’re allergic to seafood.
If you order something else,
they might think badly of you.
Is there some subtext here?
Subtext, my ass.
It’s just food.
You’ve been watching too many dramas?
Hey.
Should we go swimming after this?
I want to work out.
Don’t read too much into it
Our one-night—
No. Our two-night stand stays between us.
Oh, please.
I’m just trying to be friends.
Just because we hooked up
doesn’t mean we can’t be friends.
So?
How about that swim?
Let me check my mood first.
I’ll give you an answer after the shoot.
Water.
Why did you bring Boston in
to work with you?
Why?
I just asked him to help out.
And did you know that…
the guy helping you out
nailed and bailed on Tua?
Are you serious?
Dead serious.
Tell Boston he can be on his way
after this shoot.
I can’t.
I told him he’d be doing behind-the-scenes
photos until the project ends.
Then cancel him.
I gave him my word.
Besides, you know
we don’t have any sponsors yet.
It’s good to have his support.
It saves us money.
How about this? You keep an eye on Tua.
And I’ll keep an eye on Boston.
I’ll keep him at arm’s length.
Okay then.
Just watch him.
Yeah.
One more thing.
I’m coming over today.
What for?
Well…
I left my wallet there that night.
No need.
I’ll bring it to you.
Your guard’s really up.
What is this? A nail-and-bail on me, too?
You’re just like your friend.
All the outfits look great.
Mm.
Still mad about before?
No.
Why would I be?
Not mad, but it’s still on your mind, yeah?
It’s never easy to forget our first.
Especially when they set the bar high.
Who said you set the bar high?
There are plenty of people better than you.
Does that mean
you’re seeing someone new?
Do I have to answer that?
Come on.
Let’s just leave the past behind.
I want to start over.
It’d be nice to start over with you.
You don’t have to answer me right now.
I just want you to know…
that I’m courting you.
I am back.
What are you looking at?
At someone so easy to fool.
One box of food
and you’re already here with me.
I can just leave now.
Hey!
I’m kidding.
You get worked up so easily.
Hey, Rome.
Hi, Bas.
Hi.
I rarely see you.
It’s hard to book you for a party these days.
Come on, bro. It’s my final year.
The workload’s a bit heavy.
But tonight, the client
specifically asked for you, Rome.
Don’t bail on me.
Of course not. A deal’s a deal.
I’ll see you then.
Sure.
Hold on, the client
asked for someone else too.
What’s his name again?
Your friend…
James Dean?
Where’s he working now? He just vanished.
Lots of my clients ask about him.
I don’t know, bro. I can’t remember.
What a shame.
If you see him, tell him to come back.
He’s always welcome.
Of course.
Okay.
I’ll see you tonight.
See you.
Let’s go.
What’s up with you?
What are you doing?
This is a public place.
Isn’t that your thing? Doing it outdoors.
So you work as a host or something?
No.
I don’t do that kind of work.
Then, who was that James Dean
you used to work with?
I don’t know. I don’t remember.
I’m just a DJ at rich people’s birthday parties.
Ah.
You’re working tonight?
Mm.
Can I tag along?
No.
It’s work.
Hey.
Why did you stop?
If you don’t take me with you,
I’m not continuing.
Come on.
Can’t you at least get me off first?
No.
Fine, you can come.
But there are tons of secrets at this party.
Whatever you see, keep it to yourself.
Wow.
We barely made it before the rain.
Right.
I rode as fast as I could.
Hey, Tua.
You’ve got more stuff?
Just in case I need them for future projects.
What’s wrong, Tua?
You’ve looked uneasy since the studio.
It’s…
It’s nothing. I’m just tired.
Are you sure?
I shouldn’t have asked you to take me home.
Sorry for the hassle.
What hassle, Tua?
It’s fine.
But it’s pouring.
I don’t think I can leave anytime soon.
You can crash here.
Wait until the rain lets up.
Can I really?
I don’t want to bother Dean.
Oh, come on.
Dean’s hardly ever here.
Don’t worry about it.
Mm. Okay.
Then I’ll take your offer.
Mm.
I’ll just go take a shower.
I feel sticky all over.
I’ll grab you a towel.
Thank you.
So, how was New York?
Had fun with all your one-night stands?
Wow, it was fucking amazing.
Everyone can just be themselves.
They do whatever they want,
get laid with whoever they like.
Then why did you come back?
I didn’t think you’d return to Thailand.
Honestly, it was fun at first.
But after a while, I found it hard.
It’s more comfortable here.
But I think you’d love it there.
You can watch
Broadway shows all year round.
Mm.
I’d love to visit too.
So, are you back with Dean?
No.
We’re just working on the play together.
Seriously?
I don’t think it’s just that.
Can someone like you work with your ex?
I know my boundaries.
Okay.
Wow. Speak of the devil.
(Did you change the door passcode?)
That’s none of your concern.
(This is how you want to play it, Jack?)
I’ll hang up now. I’m busy.
He’s still blowing up your phone.
Clearly, he’s not letting go.
Go set things straight.
Sir, I can’t reach my partner.
Could you please open his room for me?
I can’t.
Only the resident can open the door.
But I can’t wait anymore.
He’s been so stressed lately.
He hasn’t been sleeping,
and he’s been saying weird things.
I’m scared, sir.
I’m afraid he might do something bad.
I can’t.
Please, sir. Please help me.
If he dies, what am I gonna do?
He could be dying up there right now.
Please help.
I’ll wait here.
Talk things out calmly, okay?
Sure. Thank you.
He’s just drunk and sleeping.
There’s nothing to worry about.
Thank you for your help. I’ll take it from here.
Are you sure?
Should I call an ambulance or the police?
No, sir.
Thank you so much.
How did you get into my room?
Why can’t I get in?
Are you hiding something from me?
What would I be hiding?
So what is this?
None of your business.
When did you go to rehab?
Why didn’t I know about it?
Are you an alcoholic, Jack?
Why do you care?
Why didn’t you take care of yourself?
How did you let this happen?
I ended up in rehab because of you.
But I’m fine now.
I’m clean.
Why didn’t you ever tell me?
Doesn’t what I’m doing these days
make up for what I did?
Are you really going to stay mad at me
for the same thing forever?
I swear, it was just work.
Nothing else happened.
It’s fine, Dean.
Because no matter what you say,
I’m not putting myself
in the same spot again.
Therefore…
Leave.
I’m not leaving.
I said leave.
I’m not leaving!
You’re not?
No.
Hey, Jack!
Jack, you asshole. Let me go!
Jack!
- Go!
- Ouch!
Ouch.
Jack!
Hey!
It’s in the past.
I don’t want to remember.
Here.
Did Dean forget his key?
I’ll get it. You keep watching.
Mm.
Why are you here?
To see you.
Hey, Boston.
Hey, Arnold.
What are you guys up to?
Watching a movie.
Looks interesting. Mind if I join?
Of course. The more the merrier.
Tua, why are you just standing there?
Oh, hey, Arnold.
I forgot to tell you back on set.
You have a great body.
And those Romeo outfits suit you.
Tua’s the real talent.
He makes amazing costumes.
You give off the same vibe as
the models I photographed in New York.
( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
Me?
Yes, really.
With your looks, with a little practice,
you could audition to walk the runway.
What was your job like?
My job?
Something like this.
People hire me to shoot their profile photos
so they can send them to
high-end or streetwear brands.
Boston, you take really good photos.
Why don’t you model for me?
Me?
All right.
You’d be perfect.
I’ll go get more snacks.
Can you grab me a beer too?
Honestly, Boston is the last person
I want Arnold to associate with.
So this is your side gig?
Why do you do it?
You don’t look like you need the money.
I’m not doing it for the money.
I just want the experience.
For what?
So you can become some big DJ?
Playing in huge clubs?
No.
I want to DJ at festivals.
One day, I’ll play at Tomorrowland.
Whoa. You dream big.
If you make it, I’ll buy a ticket.
You’d better start saving now. Because I will.
You’re kind of like Jack.
Is ambition in both of your DNA?
What the hell are you talking about?
I don’t share his DNA.
Don’t compare me to him.
Hey, dude!
Hi, Bas.
What’s up, man? Haven’t seen you in ages.
Why are you sitting here? Already drunk?
My hosts are all great, you know?
Sure thing. They’re incredible.
Hey, I’ll be right back.
Okay.
I’m stepping out for a smoke.
Yeah.
Hi, Bas.
Hey.
Rome brought you here?
Are you two really friends?
Of course, we are.
By the way,
If I’m interested in this kind of work,
could I join your team?
Sure.
If you’re serious, you can even start tonight.
Would I get the same rate as James Dean?
You’re friends with James Dean?
I’m not sure if
we’re talking about the same Dean.
But if we are, I could
bring him back to work for you.
We’re friends.
We can come to work together.
Do you have a photo of him, though?
I do.
Actually, he only started last year.
Not hosting like this, though.
He mostly just entertained
some clients over meals.
Mm.
Here.
Hey, Bas. Come here.
The birthday boy is blowing out the candles.
Alright, alright.
Hold on.
Add my contact.
You can send me your comp card later.
I’m coming!
Whoo-hoo!
FRIEND SEARCH
ADD
UNSEND THIS MESSAGE?
UNSEND
Alright, everyone. Are we ready?
Let’s begin our first read-through
of Romeo &amp; Romeo.
Take out your scripts.
Let’s start.
Everybody, please mute your phones.
This won’t take long.
Once we’re done, we can get back to work.
Dean.
Hmm?
Jack, I think we should call it a day.
Alright, guys.
We’ll stop here for today.
I’ll reschedule the meeting.
Sorry.
Go on.
I’m sorry.
Thank you for today. You’re all free to go.
Can you wait outside? We’ll talk later.
Who the hell did this?
Isn’t it just the four of us who know?
Did you tell someone
when you were drunk, Dean?
I never told anyone.
They sent it to the faculty group chat,
using a fake account.
Someone’s targeting you.
Be honest with me, Jack.
You didn’t spread this
because you were mad at me, did you?
What the fuck are you saying?
You hated my job.
Damn right I did.
But I could accept that.
What I couldn’t accept was you lying to me.
Guys, it was a long time ago.
Can you drop it?
Why should I, Timmy?
He did lie to me.
He told me he’d stop
taking jobs from that guy.
But you…
kept contacting him behind my back.
I told you I still had financial problems.
I didn’t have the same choices you did, Jack.
What an excuse.
Everybody has a choice.
You just chose to do it.
Easy for you to say.
You didn’t have it as tough as I did.
You’ve never had to struggle like I did!
That’s not the point, Dean!
You must accept the choice you made.
And you don’t have the right
to doubt me or get mad at me!
Jack, you bastard!
What?
You fucking asshole!
It’s the truth!
Hey!
Enough!
Pull your shit together!
Why would Jack do it?
Stop fighting and find the one who did it.
Screw this.
Everyone’s already judged me.
Nobody cares anyway.
Just like you said, Jack.
I have to face
the consequences of my choices.
Sorry about that.
My friend group can be a bit dramatic.
We didn’t even get to start the read-through.
No worries.
If I were Jack, I’d take a break too.
Is Dean okay, though?
I think he is now.
I talked to him.
He just wanted some time alone.
Mm.
That’s good.
Now that I have some free time,
I’m going to be a TikToker.
A TikToker?
♪ Would you mind ♪
♪ If I fell for you? ♪
People who can dance are cool.
Anyone can get good at it
with enough practice.
Come. Practice with me.
Come on.
Practice what?
Dancing.
Me? Dancing?
Yes.
Come on.
♪ Would you mind ♪
Wait.
Start over.
Okay. Let’s start again.
♪ Would you mind ♪
♪ If I fell for you? ♪
I’d rather sit and watch you.
Let’s pause for now.
Tua, can I ask you something?
What’s up with you and Boston?
You don’t like him?
Well…
It’s a long story.
Oh please. I’ve got time.
Unless you don’t want to talk about it.
Then I’ll stop asking.
I’m asking because
you seem uncomfortable around him.
So what’s the deal?
Do you remember
when I told you about my first kiss?
Mm.
It’s him.
My first kiss.
But… It’s…
Why?
You guys didn’t end it well?
I guess it’s my fault for catching feelings.
I wanted something more.
But he ghosted me in every way possible.
I guess he found someone new.
It’s shit luck we met again on this project.
But I don’t have
any feelings for him anymore.
It’s just… seeing him again
caught me off guard.
Someone like Boston
doesn’t deserve to be your first.
He should be labeled as just your ex-enemy.
That’s true.
How about this?
Next time you see him
and feel uncomfortable, tell me.
Give me a signal,
and I’ll be your human shield.
You’re working as a bodyguard now?
Sure. Of course, I am.
Tua.
Someone as lovely as you
won’t stay single for long.
Okay?
If you feel uncomfortable, let me know.
Mm.
If I’m not okay, I’ll tell you.
You fished that info out of Bas, didn’t you?
And you’re the one
who leaked the news about Dean?
I didn’t do it.
Who else could it be?
After you followed me to that party,
the video got out.
Isn’t that too convenient?
Hey.
People who choose that kind of work
should know their digital footprint
follows them for life.
Besides, anyone could’ve done it.
It’s not just me who knows about it.
How are you so sure it was me?
Okay.
Is this what you want?
Fine.
I’ve been a fool all this time.
You won’t get anything from me ever again.
Are you done?
I’m going to see Jack.
I think he could use some comfort right now.
There’s no point in doing that.
We’ll see if I score some points doing that.
Why are you here? Hm?
I’m not in the mood to fight you.
I’m not here to fight.
I understand why
you did what you did back then.
You wanted to ease your sister’s burden.
She worked every day to pay for your tuition.
You wanted to be the one
who helped your family get out of debt.
Dean.
I don’t mind at all that you used to be a host.
If I chose you, it means
I accepted that part of you.
If you really accepted it,
then why did you break up with me?
Because it broke my heart that
my boyfriend asked someone else for help
instead of coming to me first.
Why, Dean?
I think I’m capable of taking care of people.
I never want to be a burden to anyone.
People in love don’t
see their partner as a burden.
It’s fine if you don’t believe me,
but I had nothing to do
with your secret coming out.
No matter how angry I was,
I could never hurt you.
Seeing you hurt…
hurts me too.
I’m fine.
You’re not.
You’re just pretending you are.
Right now, you’re here with me.
You can feel whatever you need to feel.
I won’t judge you.
I haven’t seen this side of you in a long time.
Let yourself be weak or lose sometimes.
It won’t kill you.
I’m sorry…
for being the reason you went to rehab.
It’s alright.
I’m sorry too.
Yes, I used to be James Dean.
The VIP host you’re gossiping about.
You’ve got an ugly face
and an uglier personality, motherfucker!
Boston DMed me.
He asked me to model for a shoot at his studio.
What exactly do you want, Boston?
I want to go after you.
Do you still love me?
You got your answer.
Jack is an idiot!
He’s back with that asshole Dean, damn it!
Didn’t I tell you?
No matter how hard you tried,
he’d never want you.