Officail Website : kissasia.id  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
♪ Hold me tight,
let the darkness drown me ♪
♪ Even one second of truth is enough
to lose myself in it ♪
♪ Hold me tight,
let the darkness drown me ♪
♪ Even one second of truth is enough
to lose myself in it ♪
♪ Whether you're light or a lie,
I can't pull myself away ♪
♪ In this game,
truth or lie no longer matters ♪
[Queen of Darkness]
[Episode 16]
You want to ruin me.
Then I won't let you walk away safe!
Let's go down together.
And you shareholders,
if this sneaky woman can
kick me out today,
she can do that to you tomorrow!
None of you will get away!
Mr. Fang,
what you're doing now
won't solve anything.
You'll only push yourself to the edge.
You don't want to
spend the rest of your life
in prison, do you?
I can put the gun down.
But you have to reinstate my position.
Otherwise,
I'll take someone down
with me even if I die!
What a loser.
Still wants to drag someone down
even in death.
That scheming woman An Ning.
[Equity Transfer Agreement]
signed an Equity Transfer Agreement.
We can't use force against her anymore.
Go coax her.
Maybe if she softens up,
we can trick her out of her shares.
Mom.
I was cuckolded by my own dad.
I'm in no mood to care about this.
You think I am, huh?
You're not the only one
who got betrayed.
The shares are what matter now.
If we don't seize her shares soon,
our company will be gone.
And you're still
thinking about that nonsense?
This... this...
Just think carefully.
Here's the current
stock price of the group.
You forced the Fang family out
of the group.
It did serve as a warning.
Many shareholders
act obedient out of fear.
But that doesn't mean
they truly accept it.
Shareholders only care about profit.
As long as the money keeps coming in,
they don't care what you do.
But the Fang family
will never let this go.
The Fang family is already cornered.
If they dare to bare their teeth again,
then hit back hard.
Why are you here?
You're my wife.
Is there a problem with me
coming to see you?
Also,
why is he here?
What...
What exactly are you trying to do?
Huo Xiao is a director of the group.
We were just discussing work.
Discussing work?
Is that what you call discussing work?
Ti Cha.
Calm down.
Don't do anything you'll regret.
What a joke.
I'm talking to An Ning.
What's it got to do with you?
Besides, I haven't even asked you yet.
What are you doing in my wife's office
in broad daylight?
Huh?
You must have heard about
that Fang guy being fired from the group
and holding the board at gunpoint.
The Chairman and I
were discussing prevention plans.
An Ning,
is what he said true?
Whether it's true or not,
you'll know if you go ask yourself.
You shameless woman,
daring to give me attitude.
Fine, for the sake of the shares,
I'll let it slide this time.
Ning,
I was wrong
before.
I... I apologize to you.
No need.
Just stop using those nasty thoughts
to judge others.
If there's nothing else,
please leave.
I...
I... I'll eave here.
He should be the one to leave.
Huo Xiao has no right to
even stand here.
Huo Xiao, let me tell you.
Me and Ning
are still married.
And you'll always be a home wrecker.
Ning.
In the past,
it was all my fault.
I promise you
I'll change and make things right.
Look.
I
Bought you your favorite flowers
and booked a table
at your favorite restaurant.
Plus
the tickets to your favorite concert.
That's enough.
This is Longxing Group.
I still have a meeting to attend.
This...
An Ning used to fall for that easily.
Just a little gesture,
and she'd give me whatever I asked for.
Huo Xiao.
If you want to compete,
then let's see who's better.
Let's see
who ends up embarrassed.
Wait, wait.
Don't lose your temper, seriously.
You, you, you...
Dad.
Please don't be angry.
I have a way to deal with
that sneaky woman.
What other way?
This time I used every connection I have.
Paid a huge price for it.
Barely managed to get bailed out.
If she doesn't fall,
our family
will never rise again.
Though we can't
take her spot as chairman,
we can
approach this from another angle.
Good.
Dear,
look at her.
Look.
Sly woman, I knew you would cheat.
How could you do something
so disgraceful?
You've completely humiliated our family.
Don't you think
you owe us an explanation?
Is that all?
Anything else?
Is that not enough?
How many shameless things have you done?
Our family must've
run out of luck ages ago
to marry
such a shameless daughter-in-law.
Can't you see
this is a cheap frame-up?
These are just
fake computer-generated photos.
If I wanted to,
I could replace the face in the photos
with anyone's.
You shameless woman.
Still trying to talk your way out of it?
I'll beat you!
An Ning!
You're accusing your own family
without reason.
If you want an explanation,
go talk to whoever
gave you those photos.
Don't think we don't know about
the shameful things you've done.
If this gets out,
it'll damage the company's image.
You must resign!
You don't need to worry about that.
I'll give you an explanation for this today.
Dear, look at her.
Chairman An.
What's really going on here?
You must give the board an explanation.
As a responsible group
with a sense of duty,
Longxing Group will never tolerate
such unfounded slander!
As the group's main shareholder,
I'm not even rushing this.
So why are you all panicking?
Before figuring out the truth,
you're already desperate to cut ties.
Isn't that exactly what the person
behind this wants?
If we don't find who's pulling the strings,
whoever takes that chairman seat
won't have it easy.
Chairman An,
the board really can't be accused of
not giving you a chance now.
I'm here to handle
the resignation procedures.
The process isn't done yet,
so I can't leave for now.
Luckily I got to catch this drama unfold.
Otherwise I'd have missed
my best friend's brilliant move.
That would've been such a shame.
I'm really curious.
With such a huge scandal
hanging over you,
the whole group's about to sink with you.
How do you plan to make a comeback now?
- Chairman An.
- Make way, please.
Chairman An, can we get a comment?
Stop filming, stop filming!
- Chairman An.
- No more filming!
Chairman An!
What do you want to say
about this incident?
- Yeah.
- Exactly.
Exactly, any comment on this incident?
- About this incident...
- Please look at the camera.
Will there be any further impact?
Please answer our question.
- Please say something.
- Yeah, give us an answer.
Exactly, please respond directly
to our question.
You must be very proud now, right?
The woman in that video
has a mole on her left shoulder.
But I don't.
She's got two studs on her right ear.
And I don't wear any.
I know spreading rumors is easy,
but clearing them isn't.
Many people only care about
clicks and sensationalism,
not the truth.
I'm not just explaining this
to prove my innocence.
I also want to ask one thing.
Can't you see how shoddy
this computer-generated video is?
Do you think you can fool everyone
with just a few vague words
to prove the video is fake?
Then do you think
it's real?
Stop filming, all of you, stop!
Stop filming!
An Ning, how dare you!
It's fake, completely fake!
Of course it's fake.
I was just using you as an example.
After all,
you're the one behind all of this.
I've already found
the original IP address of this video
and the on-site surveillance footage.
Fang Yao,
do you have anything else to say?
Miss Fang,
is any of this real?
Could you please explain?
An Ning, I...
You don't have to explain it to me.
You should explain it to the police.
Even if the video's fake,
flirting with
the Inspector as a married woman
is totally true.
Nonsense!
You think you know my wife
better than I do?
Honey.
Fang Yao,
you're a woman too.
Don't you know
how harmful
these rumors are once they spread?
They can even
destroy her whole life.
I don't care at all.
I just want you gone!
Yao.
What a pity.
Justice always wins.
I'm Police Inspector Huo Xiao.
I'm also the person involved in
the so-called slut-shaming incident
you all stirred up.
I know many of the media love
stirring up trouble
and make things up out of nothing.
Let me give you one piece of advice.
There's no limit to
how far wrongdoing can go,
but being a decent person
takes conscience.
Do too many bad things,
and you'll have to
face the consequences.
If you dare to report this again,
just feel free to write that
it was me, Huo Xiao,
who seduced the married woman An Ning.
During such a sensitive period,
you really didn't have to come.
After all,
they're using my identity as a headline.
And that could hurt your reputation.
But lies like these
will fall apart
the moment you question them.
Do you really think
the law is just for show?
Let me help you apply some medicine.
Officail Website : kissasia.id  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Honestly, to me,
you're not that so-called married woman.
Nor are you "An Ning" they talk about.
You're just yourself.
No matter who I am,
being in this position,
I have to play the role well.
Are you alright?
Did I hurt you?
If one day,
your memory comes back,
have you thought
how you'd handle it?
Without a past,
how can I plan the future?
I just want a happy ending.
Waiting for a good outcome.
We'll only know what the future holds
when it comes.
Whether the ending is good or not
depends on people's hearts.
♪ Mist coils around the sleeping forest ♪
♪ Memories scattered
through cracks of darkness ♪
♪ How to escape this real-feeling dream ♪
♪ Lies reflect in water's gleam ♪
♪ Traces of existence
can never be erased ♪
♪ How to find the self I can't reclaim ♪
♪ Fly away, hear she says ♪
♪ She'll fly out from
thorns of woven lies ♪
♪ Pierce the fog,
shatter this dream tonight ♪
♪ Burn like fire ♪
♪ Just burn like fire ♪
♪ The maze in the abyss starts to clear ♪
♪ Yet night keep on whispering ♪
♪ Surrender to fate,
no clear direction ahead ♪
♪ She will rise as the dawn
that breaks the darkness ♪
♪ Never slowing down,
for tomorrow cannot be stopped ♪
♪ Surrender to love and find the way ♪
♪ Even if fate tries to forget her ♪
♪ Never despair,
for the heart burns with endless light ♪
♪ Waiting for dawn ♪
[Copyright of this short drama
belongs to]
[Shanghai Chuqi Weishi
Culture Media Co., Ltd.]
[and Youku Information Technology (Beijing)
[Co., Ltd.]
[Youku Information Technology (Beijing)
[holds exclusive global online
and broadcast rights]