Subtitle Provide By Kisskh.Club Translate Admin [ Quari]
(Previously)
I want to know more about you.
You don't tell me anything.
Can you ask Fadel out
on a double date tonight?
Babe got ganged up on
by his bullies at school.
He's hiding right now.
(The mad buffalo is heading to your place.)
Hey!
I'm really lucky to have met you.
I can feel that my life is about to change.
One day,
I'll be your 100%.
Style.
Wake up.
Five more minutes, Papa.
Who are you calling Papa?
Wake up.
I told you last night, didn't I?
You should have set an alarm.
I told you to hold back
and you didn't listen to me, either.
My entire body is sore.
I can't go to work today.
I'm sorry.
I'll take you to the hospital.
Alright, get up.
Hey. Stop it.
What are you doing?
I was just being over-dramatic.
I know you're like a block of walking ice,
but you should learn to
read between the lines.
They say we should
hit it right where it hurts.
It's like exercising.
That's how your body
builds stronger muscles.
Thanks for the trivia,
but I don't see why you're telling me this.
You need to exercise daily.
"The Heart Killers"
(Episode 6)
Hey, who the hell are you?
How'd you get in my house?
I…
I'm a friend of Style's.
Style's friend?
I've never seen your mug before.
I haven't known him long.
Did you stay the night?
Yes.
You slept with him, did you?
Uh…
I…
I'm not calling you out or anything.
I'm just telling you to use protection.
There's all kinds of diseases
you can get from this.
I read up on those kinds
of things, too, you know?
Well?
Are you his one-time thing
or are you taking him seriously?
Dad?
When did you get back?
Just right at the moment this
handsome mug left your room.
What?
Rough night?
What are you talking about?
This ain't no business for you, old man.
This is Fadel, my friend.
It's nothing.
It's not like I forbid you
from dating, you know?
Just make sure you're
not a bad influence on him.
Can you just stop, Dad?
You're embarrassing me.
You can go.
Goodbye.
Oh, well, who'd have
guessed that's your type?
We've got a whole lot of mechanics
looking exactly like him, you know?
I can set you up.
Dad, please.
Stop trying to set
me up with someone.
How was your fishing trip?
Tell me all about it.
Got loads of fish for ya.
Let's get in the kitchen.
Really?
What would you like to eat?
I want them fresh and raw.
Alright. Sashimi coming right up.
Sashimi, huh?
You know me well!
What's that you're reading, Babe?
It's Shakespeare's Othello.
What is it about?
It's about a man who is being used.
How so?
The main character, Othello,
is being manipulated by someone he trusts.
He's so in love that it
hurts him in the end.
Something like that.
Whoa.
Sounds intense.
I want to try reading that.
Hey, don't go along with him.
He reads a lot so everything
sounds like a novel to him.
Hey, my reading is getting
me a scholarship soon.
I won't be depending on
your tattooing money anymore.
Who did you take that big mouth after?
Who do you think raised me?
Oh, hey.
The grilled pork is pretty good.
Where did you buy it?
It's an old recipe.
The place is really good.
They're always sold out.
It's the old recipe with no-milk marinade.
Oh, yeah, I hate when they
add milk to the marinade.
I think this recipe tastes better.
With some fat like this.
It's so good when it's a little charred.
Okay.
Noted.
Oh, hey.
I have to go.
Don't want Fadel blowing my ear off.
Okay.
Come by any time.
You're always welcomed here.
Bye, Babe.
Gotta bounce.
Bye.
Bye-bye.
Will you tell me now
why you had me lie about being bullied?
There are things
you're better off not knowing.
It keeps you safe.
I think Ruerat is their next victim.
You certainly lived up to my expectations.
If that's all you need,
then, we're done here.
Keep your word.
Who said we are done?
What the hell does that mean?
You haven't figured out who their boss is.
So this is your ploy, Cap?
I'm not doing it.
I don't want to.
And if you force me into this,
I'm going to come out with your bullshit.
You think they'll let you live
once I get those two arrested?
I'd say you actually fell for Bison.
Why don't you try telling him the truth?
See if he wouldn't shoot
you dead immediately.
Hitmen are hitmen.
If you want to stay safe,
help me root out their whole organization.
What do you say?
Think about it.
Yeah.
I'm checking the CCTV footage.
I'll be right in.
(Wanna meet up tonight?)
(Let's do something fun.)
(Sure.)
(But it'd better be fun.)
(Or else…)
Fadel.
Honestly.
What do you think of Style?
Stay out of my business
and focus on the work at hand.
What?
We're brothers.
We gotta talk about this kind of thing.
Kant and his brother talk
about everything, you know?
They even mess around sometimes.
I want something like that, too.
Can't I?
Fadel!
That's the kind of
brother you want, isn't it?
I'm being serious, jerk.
Why is everyone so eager to know?
First, his dad, and now you?
The easy way out is to just tell me.
Fine. I like him.
What do you like about him?
His damn cockiness.
It's funny.
What about his appearance?
Anything you like in particular?
What's with that question?
Just answer me.
I like his lips.
Full lips make for a good kisser, huh?
I like Kant's eyes.
When I get close to him for a kiss,
I think I might get lost in those eyes.
It's mesmerizing.
And when we're doing it...
Hey, hold it.
I don't need the details.
Brothers don't need to know
everything about each other.
Hey.
I don't know if you feel for
Style what I feel for Kant,
but Kant makes me want
to wake up every morning,
hoping my life would be different.
I want to tell him about myself
without lying.
I'm tired, Fadel,
of keeping to myself.
What about you?
You don't want that?
I just want him to accept me for who I am.
I think it's time for us to quit.
Once we're done with Ruerat,
I'll talk to Mother again.
Alright.
Let's avenge our parents,
and we can finally
date without any worries.
If they really decided to carry
out their operation tomorrow,
and got arrested by Captain,
what should we do?
Kant, I'll be honest.
Let's stop them.
You want me to walk up to Bison and say,
“Don't kill people.
A police captain is waiting
to arrest you tomorrow”?
If he ever found out the truth,
do you think I'll...
You're a goner.
Unless you leave him right now.
Can you do that?
Whether you can or not is beyond me.
But as for me, I'm getting
kinda attached to Fadel.
Can you hurry up and get this done?
Once their boss gets arrested,
this will end.
Those two will be free,
and we can go on with our lives.
You think Captain would let them walk?
They kill people for a living.
If they ain't shot dead on the spot,
they'd at least get a life sentence.
Does that mean
tonight could be the last night I see him?
You're meeting up with him tonight?
Yeah.
At the rock club.
Sorry about this, bud.
We have two options today.
If we don't stop them tonight,
then we can only make the
most of what we have now.
Why are we at the bowling alley?
Isn't it closed today?
That won't stop us.
I can get you inside.
What is this?
I thought you weren't
breaking into places anymore.
Well…
I want to spend some quality time with you.
I want to do something special.
But what's the… occasion?
Nothing in particular.
I just want to be with you.
Please.
Please?
Hey.
You're being weird.
It's getting suspicious.
Did you do something wrong?
Well?
Which ex of yours decided to show up again?
Huh?
None.
And I didn't do anything wrong.
Fine, then.
Shall we get inside?
You sure?
Let's go.
Hey.
Hurry up.
This is pretty cool.
Seeing the back of bowling
alleys is a first for me.
If you keep having me around,
I can show you even cooler places.
What are you planning to do?
Why do you want to be
here when it's closed?
You scared?
Doesn't sound like you.
As if I ever get scared.
That was close.
You sure love risky things.
Wait here.
What's this?
You wanted to bowl so
bad you became a burglar?
No.
I just want to spend
some alone time with you
at the place we first met.
Hey.
This place is full of safety cams.
What do you think you're doing?
You think a former thief
like me is that careless?
I got it all covered.
That means…
We can do whatever the hell
we want and no one will see it?
What do you have in mind?
What else is there to do at a bowling alley
but play bowling?
This is the first time
I'm here with someone.
Happiness shared is happiness doubled.
How many tickets?
Two, please.
Alright.
This band is playing
for the last time tonight.
We're their last audience.
I gotta say
it's gonna be a memorable night.
You're right.
For me,
tonight is certainly going
to be a memorable night.
Excuse me.
Fadel.
Yeah?
I have a confession to make.
What?
Well, I…
I…
Just say it.
I don't really like heavy metal.
Why the hell did you have to shout that?
You wanna get beat or something?
Sorry.
You're not mad at me, are you?
Why would I?
I already knew that.
What?
Of course I knew.
You only pretended to
like it to get close to me,
but you're not into it.
You're more into pop rock music.
All I want to know is
that you're not mad at me.
You don't have to do
anything to impress me.
I want to see the real you.
But still, liars should be punished.
Punished?
What do you mean?
Hey, what do you mean by “punished”?
Why am I doing this?
You're a fake fan.
You gotta blend in.
Some people here don't
wear makeup, you know?
You, for one, don't.
Stay still.
You're gonna mess it up.
You know what you're doing?
I used to wear the same
makeup as my favorite band.
Then you should put some makeup on, too.
A matching makeup.
No.
I never wear it in public.
Why not?
If you're sick of sneaking about,
you don't have to do it.
How long are you going
to live someone else's life?
What do you think you're doing, Style?
We're outside.
Why not?
No one recognizes me anyway.
Try just being someone you want to be.
We'll do it together.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Hey.
Can I get on your shoulders?
You're heavy, you know?
Are you drunk?
How could I be?
I hardly drank.
Hey, you think we're gonna get arrested?
If we are,
the charges are gonna be long.
Trespassing, stealing, damage to property,
we're literally eating their snacks.
We're definitely going to jail.
What should we do, then?
Should we…
get in the car and run?
We can just...
Hey.
I really can't go with you tonight.
But don't worry.
After tomorrow, I'm
quitting at the restaurant,
and I'll be free.
More importantly,
I wanna get a cat.
I have one right now, though.
Since when?
Since you came along,
'cause you're my cat.
What nonsense…
Can't you just do what
you said you want to today?
Can't you?
I really can't.
Will you try to understand?
I gave Fadel my word about something.
But after that,
you're the only one I'll
make any promises with.
You'll be in all of my plans, Kant.
Will you wait here for me for a sec?
Where are you going?
You'll know soon.
It's beautiful.
It is, right?
When I was in your room,
I saw all the northern light posters there.
I thought you might like it.
You're very thoughtful, aren't you?
Do you like it?
Of course, I do.
You know,
it's been a dream of mine
to see the northern lights in Iceland.
Take a drive around the islands.
Watch some waterfalls.
Get in a hot bath.
I want to see the real puffins, too.
Puffins?
Yeah, you know them?
What are they?
They're like penguins,
but with their orange beaks.
They're adorbs.
Now you make me want to see them, too.
If we're lucky,
maybe we can go together.
Of course we can.
How many days should we spend there?
10?
I think 15.
Can we make it a road trip?
I'll drive.
I'll make a playlist for the road.
Perfect.
I'll go anywhere
as long as I'm with you.
Hey.
Mind taking a photo with us?
I love your band.
I love you so much.
Gimme a hug.
Let's make it rock 'n roll, guys!
One more.
Some selfies, too, please.
Thank you.
Thanks for coming with me.
If it weren't for you,
I'd probably have sat alone over there.
It's alright.
It makes me happy just seeing your smile.
You wanna come over tonight?
I want to cuddle you to sleep.
Should I?
Your Dad's home, isn't he?
One more thing,
I've got work tomorrow.
What work?
Grocery shopping?
I'll help.
It's something else.
You're doing a lot of
second jobs, aren't you?
What else do you do
besides working as a host?
You can tell me.
I won't judge.
It's personal.
I'm helping someone else out.
You don't need to know any of that.
I'll tell you when I'm ready.
What? What's wrong?
It's just tonight.
You act like we're not going
to see each other again.
It's been a good night.
I don't want it to end.
When I'm back,
there'll be more nights like this.
Promise?
I'm very happy tonight.
Me, too.
How long is this gonna take?
Don't ask.
Better to just get it done and over with.
I'm too tired for this.
RUERAT FOUNDATION FOR EDUCATION
Alright.
Please make yourself comfortable.
I'm going to go get ready.
Thank you.
Keep an eye on them.
I'm pretty sure they're
going to do it today,
like Kant said they would.
Yes, Captain.
Oh, little bear!
How adorable!
Let's take a photo together.
What an adorable bear.
One photo, please.
Over here.
Stand in the middle.
You should go over there.
Let me see.
Thank you for coming.
Can I have a photo, please?
Can you take it for me?
Babe?
Mr. Bear?
This way.
Boy, it's time.
This way, please.
Yes.
Wait, hold on.
I want another photo.
That one wasn't very good.
Take one, please.
Ugh, lady, quit it already!
Hello.
Welcome to the Ruerat Foundation's
charity for better education.
Tonight's event begins with a surprise.
We're revealing the newest mascot, which
will be on the Ruerat Foundation's logo.
Please welcome Handsome Bear!
Fadel, don't do it now.
Babe, get out of there!
Babe!
Bison.
Run!
Hurry!
They're here!
Quickly!
Follow them!
Police!
Everyone, on the ground.
Go over there.
You, check out that way.
What the hell did you do that for?
I missed that shot because of you.
But Babe could get hurt.
Babe who?
Who is he?
A student at the event.
He's Kant's brother.
I was aiming for Ruerat.
You think I'd kill a kid?
He could have gotten caught in the fire.
Did I ever miss my shot?
You ended up mixing
personal business with work.
Well?
We're ruined!
I'm sorry.
Enough of that.
Let's get back and recoup.
And come up with how
to break this to Mother.
I got super lucky.
The bear mascot saved my life.
Did you see the man inside the bear suit?
No.
I only saw him run after the other mascot.
I'm glad you're safe.
Babe.
Can you grab some coffee
for me from next door?
Of course.
Crap.
To think my brother
nearly died because of that.
I think…
Bison saved him.
You think Fadel would shoot Babe?
You think he knows you're a snitch?
I don't think so.
I've been pretty lowkey.
But well,
my work here is over.
I'm done being a snitch.
I want to see Fadel.
Style.
You have to get over it.
You can't ever get together with him.
Move on.
It'll become a funny
story for your children later
about how you once dated a hitman.
We're sorry, Mother,
for messing up this mission.
Did anyone get hurt?
No.
We ran immediately.
Nobody saw us.
Then that's good.
I just can't believe
you two would mess up
such an important job.
We might have been a little careless.
We haven't figured out how
the cops knew to be there.
I think you just didn't
take it seriously enough.
You weren't on the field with us.
What would you even know?
All you do is sit your ass in an office.
What the hell do you ever do?
Bison!
I don't see it the same way.
The police would never find out about this
unless they got some tip off
about the time and place.
Is there anyone suspicious
in your life right now?
No, there isn't.
We barely talk or reveal
ourselves to anyone.
There are only the
customers at the burger joint
that we have to talk to to put up the act.
Maybe you're overlooking someone.
Someone you can't bring
yourselves to suspect.
Never mind.
I'll have someone make
sure this news doesn't get out.
But I have to warn you,
he's alive,
and he can come back
to hurt us at any moment.
It wouldn't hurt to be careful.
I've always told you
how we can never know someone truly.
The closer you are,
the less you see.
Make sure you find that suspicious someone
and take them out.
Before this messes all of us up.
You really think it's them?
Besides customers,
they're the only two people around us.
Kant? A police informant?
And Style as well?
It's all possible.
We need to suspect everyone right now.
What do you want to do?
Should we go back to the restaurant
or should we run?
How about my parents' place on that island?
We can lay low there.
How about…
We go back to the restaurant
and act normal.
Just be more careful.
After this,
I'll keep my eyes on them.
If you found out they're the snitches,
what would you do?
What I always do.
Kill them.
It's closed.
Whose cat is that?
He's too chubby to be a stray.
Bison's cat.
He always feeds the little guy.
I guess he misses Bison, then.
He's a food source, after all.
I think you should take him in, Kant.
Yeah, I will.
We gave them enough trouble.
I don't want this cat to get
dragged into this mess, too.
Why do I have a feeling
that this isn't over?
What do you mean?
They can't run forever, that's for sure.
If they haven't completed their mission,
they will definitely come back.
I guess you're right.
Before things went down,
you saw how attached they were to us.
Who knows?
No matter how much you love someone,
you gotta prioritize saving
your own butts, right?
Hey, there.
ONE WEEK LATER
I was thinking of going to your place.
But you were more impatient than me, huh?
Where have you been?
You didn't reply to any of my texts.
My phone broke.
I had to change both my
phone and my number.
I was busy, too.
And you didn't think
to contact me a little?
I was worried sick about you, you know?
I was out of town.
But I'm here now, aren't I?
What are you complaining about now?
Sit down.
I'll whip up something in the kitchen.
Anything you'd like to eat?
Anything's fine.
You decide.
Everything you make is good anyway.
You sure are a sweet talker.
What do you want?
Did you do something wrong?
No.
I just really missed you.
Is it so weird to get
a little affectionate?
You know, all this time apart
really frustrated me.
Stop it.
I said stop.
Not here.
Well, how about some spaghetti?
Okay.
You'll be in all of my plans, Kant.
I'll go anywhere
as long as I'm with you.
Slow down.
You'll just pass out drunk
at the bar at this rate.
Bison.
Where have you been?
I couldn't reach you at all.
Sorry.
I was out of town on
an errand with Fadel.
I see.
What kind of errand?
Did anything happen?
It's just some petty family issue.
Never mind that.
What about you?
Drinking beer all alone like this…
Anything weighing on your mind?
If there's anything weighing on my mind,
it's gotta be you disappearing on me.
Were you worried about me?
Who else would I be worried
about if not my boyfriend?
Oh, hey.
I adopted the black cat you always fed.
I went to see you at the
restaurant and he was just here.
I didn't want him to starve.
Thank you
for remembering what I love.
OLD FART
Who was that?
Don't you have to take the call?
Just someone who wants a tattoo.
He keeps changing his mind about the tatt.
I don't want to talk to him anymore.
I want to talk to you more.
How about we drink and go back to my place?
I can't.
I have work later.
I just showed up here
because I wanted to see you.
I have to go.
Fadel is gonna have
my head if I'm late.
Okay.
Please don't just
disappear like that again.
Bye.
Hey.
You don't have to help.
I'll clean up later.
Come on.
You fed me.
Think of my service as payment.
Hello.
Yeah, Bison?
Hang on.
Oh, what's with the music?
We're closed, aren't we?
Can't I get a little romantic?
You were just calling me
out for being affectionate.
Now you wanna be romantic?
What did Bison say?
Is he with Kant?
Yeah.
Said he'd be home late.
He must really have missed Kant.
I've missed you.
I've got no one messing with me
when you're not there.
So I'm just annoying you.
Is that even a good thing?
It is.
Having someone to miss is good.
It makes me want to go grocery shopping
and go jogging
with the hopes of running into you.
Are we officially entering
romantic territory?
I want to do what lovers do.
It's alright.
I don't want you to do
what you don't want to do.
But I can be exactly what you want.
I think…
I'm in love with you.
(Fadel.)
(They're the snitches.)
♪ Go on, hurt me to my core ♪
You have my heart now,
so take good care of it.
♪ Flames in the hand are burning ♪
♪ From head to toe, the
heat is all consuming ♪
♪ Splash water on me ♪
♪ Hurt me please, dearest love ♪
♪ Hurt me please, can't get enough ♪
(Next Week)
I'm happy just having a boyfriend like you.
Ever since I met you,
I've gotten to know a
different side of myself.
You're serious about him, aren't you?
Cheers!
Bison!
We still have to see the
northern lights together.
I'm arresting the little one.
If you don't want to get in trouble,
go home and be with your brother.
Hey.
Hey!