[intriguing music playing]
[Orlick] Here's all you need to know.
You have to run.
[Joana] That's Mason Kane's wife.
- We have her.
- [Sharpe] You had a mole
within Citadel.
It was you.
If I see you again, I will kill you.
Russian president Dmitry Aronov
is set to attend the G8 Summit next week.
[Paulo] I need my assassin in ten days.
We lost the one man
who could build what we need.
[Joana] There's someone else
who can fix this software.
A Korean hacker.
[Orlick] If we have
any chance of stopping Paulo Braga,
we cannot do it alone.
Bernard's still alive?
[in Swedish] Brad Headmeaer
of Townon, California,
- [in English] Isn't that your friend?
- It is.
We got to go.
[atmospheric music playing]
♪ ♪
[door opens]
- You look nice.
- And you're alive.
You don't seem thrilled.
I'm over the moon.
Well, your face
isn't exactly conveying that.
Why the SOS, Bernard?
"Baha Mar, 2:00 p.m."
After all these years,
you still don't trust me, do you?
I don't trust dead men that suddenly
resurrect when the timing's convenient.
[Hutch] Okay, guys, we get it,
you don't trust each other.
But can we keep this moving?
- We haven't got all day.
- Who's this clown?
Hutch. Jim.
It's a pleasure.
This is my partner Celine Rohr.
Not a pleasure.
Please tell me what I'm doing here.
They're former CIA,
and this is your new mission.
- You really know how to pick 'em, huh?
- Mm.
[door opens]
[dramatic music playing]
Nadia. Nadia.
- Get fucked, Bernard.
- Nadia, wait.
I know it was him.
How?
I spent eight years in a bunker.
I had a lot of time to think.
I figured it either had to be you or him.
And when I saw the way
you looked at him in there...
...I had my answer.
If you knew he was the mole,
- why did you bring him back?
- I needed him then
and I need him now.
- He's impossible to trust.
- Maybe. But all I know is,
Manticore is gonna come after you
and your daughter and me and mine.
And if you want to get out of this thing,
if you want to get truly out for good,
then what you have to do is,
you have to kill them first.
All eight families,
starting with Paulo Braga.
That's the only way.
And if Mason Kane is good at one thing,
it's killing people.
[somber music playing]
I need you, Nadia.
Please.
Just give me 72 hours, all right?
And if he makes one wrong move,
I will fucking kill him myself.
Come on.
[Hutch] Orlick said you two were married.
That's cool.
I can fuck with a guy
who punches above his weight.
She is smoking. Like a ten.
And he's a 9.5.
Who the fuck are you?
- Who the fuck are you, Boy Scout?
- [door opens]
So these are your best
and brightest, Bernard?
[Orlick] Enough. Come over here.
Paulo Braga is days away
from perfecting tech
that can co-opt a person's mind
and turn them into an assassin.
He will then use that assassin to kill
Russian President Aronov at the G8.
- Why?
- I believe he wants eyes everywhere.
The Russian spy satellite network.
It's the cutting edge
of surveillance technology.
It can track you down to your DNA.
The only problem for Paulo
is that President Aronov is a nationalist.
But if Paulo kills Aronov
and puts their corrupt prime minister
in power--
Then he would have eyes everywhere.
The G8 is in seven days,
and we have to find Paulo
before he kills Aronov.
They have Abby.
Saving the world isn't my problem.
[Orlick] You can't save Abby
without getting to Paulo.
And you get to Paulo
by stopping his assassin.
There are two steps
to getting the assassin operational.
Step one is the easy part:
implanting a receiver chip
into the host's cerebellum.
Step two: the programming itself
that hijacks the brain.
I purposely sabotaged the programming,
creating a firewall to block
any transmission longer than a minute.
And there are only two people in the world
who could disable that firewall
and get the code to work.
One is me, and the other is
a Korean hacker by the name of Edison.
We have to get him before Braga does.
There's only one photograph
of Edison that exists,
from a surveillance photo,
like, 15 years ago. Here.
Unfortunately--
because why would this shit be easy?--
he had a black bag over his fucking head.
[Nadia] I know that guy with Edison.
That's Frank Sharpe,
maître d' of the European spy world.
Maybe he can lead us to Edison.
Except he's a major pain in the ass.
Well, I guess he's about
to become our pain in the ass.
- Great.
- Look, okay, I get it.
As a team, we're a fucking disaster.
Don't undersell it.
But we are the only ones
standing in the way of this lunatic.
[somber music playing]
[children chattering playfully
in distance]
I always wonder why some children
draw pigs and rabbits
and others draw wolves.
Well, thank you for coming in, Mr. Braga,
I know you're a very busy man.
There was an incident this morning.
Edgar punched a boy, made him bleed.
And as we have a zero tolerance policy
for violence,
we have to suspend your son for a week.
I think that sounds very fair,
Ms. Turrant.
- You do?
- Mm-hmm.
Thank you, Mr. Braga.
Hold still.
Please.
Who else will be punished?
I'm sorry?
I know my son would never hurt
another child without good reason.
Well, the other boy teased Edgar.
But we tell the children that words
are never justification for violence.
Edgar speaks about this boy Pierre.
Parents Jeanette and Tomas, they live
at 7 Rue Volney. Is that the one?
Mr. Braga, this is perhaps inappropriate--
The brown one, please.
The brown one.
Thanks.
Edgar says Pierre screams,
pulls the girls' hair,
teases anyone who raises their hand.
Edgar worst of all.
Pierre has some learning difficulties
that he's working through.
[laughing]
Ms. Turrant, no.
I don't blame the child.
I don't think he should be punished.
You have a freckle on your nose.
You know that?
Pierre is poisoning the education
of these children,
and it was left to my son
to restore order.
Green, please.
- Green!
- [slams table]
[crayons clatter]
[ominous music playing]
As you're the adult in the room,
you're meant to keep order, right?
So it feels like it's you
who should be punished
for allowing this kind of behavior.
For forcing my boy to do your job.
Edgar is suspended for a week,
and what will be your punishment?
What will be your punishment?
I don't know.
Don't you ever put my boy
in that position again.
Or you will be punished.
Big smile, please.
Mm-hmm.
Put it on your fridge.
[chair scrapes]
Nothing wrong in drawing wolves.
Without wolves,
we'd still have houses
of sticks and stones...
...not bricks.
Apparently, she's in Stockholm.
She's very hard to reach.
Try her again.
She's difficult to wrangle.
[Joana] Talented ones always are.
I could get you five others just like her.
No, not like her. Trust me.
Try her again.
[slow, eerie music playing]
♪ ♪
[exhales]
[phone buzzing]
[Joana] Why are you in Stockholm?
I told you to get off Sinh.
She's not gonna be another one
of your infatuations.
We both remember
how the last one turned out.
I am on a limb for you,
so go find me the Korean.
Whatever it costs. We have one week.
Don't let me down, Aparna.
[train passes]
How much farther? I have to pee.
- Hold it.
- I'm eight.
Show a little compassion.
[indistinct chatter]
[indistinct announcement over P.A.]
[beeping]
Hi, Mom.
We have 95 seconds till Olympia Station.
That is where we part.
It's all right. We usually destroy
each other in under one minute anyway.
Was I somehow unclear when I told you,
you could never see me again?
- Couldn't have been clearer.
- [train whooshing]
Trust me, I wish I didn't have to see the
woman that abandoned her daughter either.
Abandoned.
I did what I did as a mother
to protect you.
If you knew where I was, any number
of organizations would have tried
to kill you to get that information.
You're as much a martyr
as you're a mother.
I'm a spy.
You made me one.
I could have handled it.
60 seconds. Why are you here?
I need you to keep her safe.
At least until I'm back.
Look, I know you know about her, okay?
You're my only choice.
Her name is Asha.
Asha?
[Nadia] It's just a matter
of a couple of weeks.
How can you be so sure?
Because when I leave, I come back.
My mother's name was Asha.
30 seconds. Let's, uh...
This is your grandmother.
She'll keep you safe.
[in Hindi] You're the lady from the movie.
[in English] Call me Honey.
I'll be back before you even know it.
- Okay?
- Mm-hmm.
[Honey] Nadia,
if you fall into trouble,
and only then, you call him.
You understand?
And, Nadia...
[in Hindi] Come back for her.
[slow, suspenseful music playing]
- I love you.
- [in English] I love you, too.
I'll be back.
[Honey] Asha.
Come.
Come sit here.
[train chugging]
What'd I tell you?
I needed to see Asha one last time.
I don't want you anywhere near her.
I'm sorry.
You've never been sorry for anything.
You need to let me move forward.
There is a way forward for you.
And deep down you know what it is.
You're just too much of a coward to do it.
♪ ♪
[birds chirping]
[gun cocks]
Now, I'm guessing
you're not here for the massage?
He does look broke, doesn't he?
Kind of like a sad, old Artful Dodger.
Well, then what the fuck do you look like?
Apart from a shit Tom Cruise
with your dad's sunglasses on?
He's plucky. I like him.
I don't.
Who cares? Come on, then.
What do you want?
[Orlick] Maybe some fusilli.
With fresh tomato and basil.
Where the hell did he come from?
Does he have to point a gun at me?
It was one job, 15 years ago,
IDing a weapons shipment in North Korea.
Edison was a hacker,
which is what he did, and then he left.
That's it?
Do you remember what he looked like?
I didn't see his face.
He had a bag over his head.
Plus I don't really have a good memory
for faces nor names.
What is he good at?
Who was he with?
- Was he with Korean NIS?
- No.
- He was handled by the CIA.
- [Hutch scoffs]
How do you know it was the CIA,
you crumpet-eating motherfucker?
Because CIA always tell you they're CIA,
'cause it adds a tiny centimeter
to their tiny penises.
[Celine laughs]
Why is that funny?
I never say I'm CIA.
- At least twice a day.
- [Sharpe scoffs]
Oh, there's...
there's mold on that cheese.
[Sharpe] Yeah.
It's well-aged. Mold is decadence.
[laughing] You remind me of someone.
A handsome former lover?
- No. My, um, my uncle Frédéric.
- Ah.
He was very sad.
- Right.
- And poor.
- Mm-hmm.
- And he died alone.
Okay. Must I listen to this?
[Orlick] So, if Edison
was handled by the CIA,
they would know his true identity,
they would know his whereabouts,
and that intel would be stored
at CIA European headquarters
- in Rome.
- [Hutch] Whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa, Bernard.
- That's where it is.
- You can't talk about the Library.
- [Orlick] What?
- You can't talk... Can't...
- We don't know this guy.
- [Orlick] I can't hear you.
What are you saying?
You want to break in there?
- Yeah.
- That information
is in an air-gapped server
in an ultra-secure room...
- I literally can't hear you.
- ...on a floor
that you have to have top-level
security clearance just to get onto.
It's never gonna happen.
We can't just walk in there.
There's only one person in the entire
Agency who operates that database.
- Hutch, this is...
- It's not gonna happen.
...the fucking CIA we're talking about.
They're absolute morons.
We can do this blindfolded.
We can do this.
- Now, you said "We."
- Yeah.
That made me nervous.
I assume you mean you three.
Yeah, because it'd be very strange
to include me in any kind of "we,"
seeing as I'm me,
seeing as I don't know you,
seeing as I've never met any of you.
So why would I want
to be part of your "we"?
Why are you staring at me?
You're broke, and I'm hiring.
There's no need to overcomplicate this.
I understand that you're a master
in the art of accruing
compromising information.
Well, then you must have been misinformed.
Well, I may have some knowledge
of the debauched.
I need dirt on people.
I need fetishes, I need addictions,
I need predilections.
Well, if you double that, I'll make it
fucking disgusting. How's that?
Cheers.
- Cheers.
- Put the gun away.
- [Italian song playing]
- [clock chiming]
The bank foreclosed on this place
three weeks ago.
I'm just waiting for them
to kick me out. [chuckles]
Now, you wouldn't be a chap
and take these bags for me, would you?
- 36 years in the service. No nobility.
- [Orlick] What?
What I said was, there's no nobility.
Well, it's not just about nobility.
You know that.
Someday, very soon, they're gonna realize
they can't have former spies
running around
with institutional knowledge.
And they're gonna come for you.
And it won't be for fusilli.
All right.
[slow, suspenseful music playing]
It's all right. I'll load my bags.
Fucking cheek.
Oh, you're fucking kidding.
[Hutch] What the fuck?
Can we really trust Orlick?
- I don't know.
- [gun cocks]
And the pretty ones.
[in French] I don't like their energy.
I can't tell if they want
to kill each other or fuck each other.
[in English] Yeah. So fucking annoying.
Dicey. Very dicey.
Super dice.
So, if we have to,
I mean, you know,
if the time comes, we, uh...
[in French] We do what we always do.
[in English] Look out for numero uno.
And numero duo.
Numero uno is... That mean... Yeah.
That means me and you is numero uno.
It's the royal uno.
I'm breaking your chops.
- You're breaking my balls.
- [laughs]
- You're busting my chops.
- Oh, shut up.
Okay.
[dramatic, suspenseful music playing]
[Cash] Celine Rohr. Agents Benjamin Cash
- and Charles Bantam.
- Pleased to meet you.
You're being assigned a new level
of responsibility at the agency.
You're gonna be nuts-deep in it,
so buckle up, bob cut.
- It's not a bob cut.
- Go to the slides.
Trigger warning, Gen Z.
I'm a millennial.
[Cash] You know where this is?
- No idea.
- [Cash] Dar al-Makhzen,
legislative building, Morocco.
Seimas Palace, Lithuania.
- The Children's Museum, Oslo.
- The goddamn butterfly exhibit.
I-Is this the work of a terrorist?
This is the work of your new partner
James Hutch.
Oh, he's an A-plus agent.
[Bantam] Oh, and he is an A-plus asshole.
- He's a maniac.
- [Cash] A menace.
[Bantam] He is the best damn reaper we've
ever unleashed on the POSs of the world.
[Cash] He's very effective, very hard
to rein in, and that's where you come in.
To do what?
We think you'll be a good yin to his yang.
You know, help focus him,
keep him in line. He does not like orders.
[chuckles] So I help him stay on mission.
You bet your sweet ass you do.
- [Cash] And out of The Hague.
[Bantam] And us out of The Hague.
- But you answer to us.
- Both of us.
- Not him.
- No fucking way.
- And in the event...
- The very likely event.
...that he goes off the reservation...
We're talking full Bonnie and Clyde.
[Cash] ...you have to promise us
that you'll extinguish him.
- Take him out.
- You'll do as we ask.
- Without hesitation.
- Would that be a problem, Ms. Rohr?
Great fucking flow.
♪ ♪
[clock chiming]
The movies always portray them
as Mr. and Mrs. Smith types.
Yet my experience of the CIA is, uh,
well, they're just a box of dickheads.
Case in point.
You're cute
when you're trying to be funny.
- [Celine chuckles]
- [Sharpe] You wipe away the mystique,
and what are you left with?
A sloppy slut with a huge bank account.
- It's not a job when you love what you do.
- [Sharpe chuckles]
That's good, and lucky for us,
in front of you all is a mark.
It is human error,
but we plan to make them
work for us.
[speaks indistinctly]
[speaking Italian]
[upbeat music playing]
Have a lovely day.
Pleasure, as always.
- She's in.
- Okay.
- Good.
- She's really very good.
If ever you're in the market
for a Ukrainian sex worker,
I highly recommend.
I've just used her for something else.
Oh. Was that something else
paying her to have sex with you?
How dare you, Bernard?
What's her going rate?
Reasonable. [chuckles]
♪ ♪
- [fighter grunts]
- [bell clangs]
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Yeah, I know how to walk.
Just keep moving, you limey bastard.
[suspenseful music playing]
Can I help you?
Uh, we're already being helped.
You're gonna want to use her as a shield.
It'll just be a second.
In five, four, three, two, one.
Go, go! Get down!
[overlapping shouting]
- On your knees!
- [Hutch] All right, relax.
We come with a peace offering: Nadia Sinh
- and Frank Sharpe.
- Francis.
[Celine] Check the files.
- Langley will want them.
- [officer] Hutch, you're AWOL.
I'm not AWOL. It's a side mission.
- Keep your hands where I can see 'em.
- Just tell Bantam and Cash
to get out here.
We're gonna make a deal.
You don't get to make demands, Hutch,
- not in your position.
- We want back in.
- [officer 2] Hands where we can see them.
- [officer 3] Let me see the hands. Hands!
- Oh, fuck.
- [officer 2] I swear to God,
on the ground...
- Gun! She has a gun.
- Everybody stop shouting!
I've also got a gun.
We've all got guns,
but we're not going to use 'em, right?
- Get on the ground.
- Drop it right now.
Fuck you!
- [officer] I will open fire.
- [officer 2] On the floor!
[officer 3] Lay the fuck down!
Hey! So, they're not here
to make a deal with you.
They're here to steal intel.
- What are you doing?
- [Nadia] I will shoot
your pasty-ass face. Shut the fuck up.
- On the floor now!
- He's fucking you. Badly!
You're a lying sack of shit.
I am telling the truth. You listen.
- Drop your weapon.
- I have a daughter, okay?
- Oh, my God, here we go.
- I have a daughter, and I need
to get her out,
and I will make you a trade.
Mason Kane and Bernard Orlick.
You don't think
Langley would kill for them?
All you have to do is disappear me
and my daughter.
Get me Bantam and Cash.
[watch ticking]
Bantam and Cash.
Last time I saw you, Bantam,
you'd had too many edibles.
You were freaking out in the corner,
remember that?
[laughs mockingly] You're
so fucking juvenile.
You had to come all the way
to this shithole to get a promotion, huh?
Don't get cute, wiseass.
To what do we owe this visit, Hutch?
- You've been dark for five months.
- [Bantam] Ever since your little blow-up
- about Braga.
- [Cash] You haven't checked in
- with your security supervisor.
- [Bantam] Or your logistics officer.
The question is,
where the fuck have you been?
Going against our orders
and trying to kill Braga?
Guys, guys, guys,
don't give yourselves a hernia.
You really think I'm that stupid?
I've been on what you might call a little
- self-directed mission, and here I am.
- Okay.
With Nadia Sinh and Frank Sharpe in hand,
all wrapped up for you. You're welcome.
- [Cash] First off--
- Nobody knows your boy Sharpe.
- [Cash] He's a wet fish.
- A nobody.
Analysts had to look him up.
[Bantam] They still
couldn't find anything.
- That's how good he is.
- [Bantam] Oh, really?
MI6. Mossad. Manticore.
The guy knows the internal workings
of countless intelligence agencies.
But I'm sure you're gonna
waterboard that out of him.
I don't know what you've been told,
but, um,
uh, so, I was at the Dean Street Casino
at the roulette wheel.
I was up
and sat next to the most beautiful lady,
who said her name was Camilla
and she worked for the government.
I'm here, and I'm psyched
to get back to work.
So what have you got for me?
[Bantam] Yeah, well, you see,
the thing is, Hutch,
right now you're an enemy of the state.
A turncoat.
[Bantam] As far as Langley's concerned,
you're a double agent
working with the bad guys.
- [Hutch] What?
- And Nadia Sinh is corroborating that.
Hmm.
[Stahl] Bold move coming in.
I'd say you were double-crossing if there
was still an agency for you to cross.
Now tell me, how'd you get in
with Hutch and Rohr?
That is a really long, boring part of
the story, and we're running out of time.
I really need you to believe
I'm telling you the truth.
- How do I know that?
- You don't.
But I will give you Mason Kane
and Bernard Orlick.
In exchange for?
You disappear me and my daughter for good.
Make the fucking deal,
or I'll shop 'em to the Chinese.
[Celine] You remind me of someone.
You remind me of my uncle.
He was, uh, boring.
Nobody wanted to have sex with him,
and so he had to see prostitutes.
[Sharpe] Um, I took some Viagra
that night, so there was a bit
- of a spring in my step, so to speak.
- [phone buzzing]
[in Italian] This is Katherine.
Madam Delaney, this is Leon Brezzi
at San Vincenzo's.
What's wrong?
Everything's fine, but Felix had
a small accident on the monkey bars.
Oh God.
We think his arm might be broken.
We're taking him to
San Giovanni's emergency wing.
Oh my God. I'm coming now.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
Thank you so much, Madam.
[upbeat music playing]
[Cash] Let's get to the truth, okay?
[Bantam] Yeah, enough fucking around.
Okay. Can I get a coffee first?
[Bantam] You give me the truth,
or I will literally shit in you.
Get him a fucking coffee.
[lock beeps]
All right, Chuck, you want the truth?
I'd fucking love to know the truth, Hutch.
Here's the truth.
This last year has taken a huge toll
on my mental health.
- [scoffs]
- [Bantam] Jesus Christ.
I don't have time for this shit.
I'm on my way back from my last mission
in Damascus on a Qatari air flight.
And I'm watching
The Best Exotic Marigold Hotel.
And I start bawling my fucking eyes out.
Now, you might be thinking, Maggie Smith,
Judi Dench, it's gonna be emotional.
This wasn't that.
I was a fucking wreck.
I didn't stop crying for three days.
- [lock beeps]
- [door opens]
Oh, is that for me?
Thank you.
[Cash] Langley tracked you from Syria
to Dallas and then lost all trace of you.
[Bantam] You dumped all your devices
in the bathroom of an airport Sbarro's.
Well, after my breakdown,
I needed a little me time.
And where was that?
Uh...
Belize, naturally.
So, I ended up
in a spiritual retreat center
for a month of amplified self-reflection.
Not my usual cup of chowder,
you might say,
but I was desperate and needed answers.
I was willing to try anything: yoga,
veganism, ayahuasca.
I even read a fucking book.
Have you ever tried reading a book, Cash?
One night I'm laying there
in a sound bath,
freebasing my own subconscious.
And all of a sudden I hear this voice
that says, "The answer lies at sunset."
And it was just like
the universal consciousness came down
and popped a finger right up my butthole.
[Bantam] Did you also get Sinh and Sharpe
- out of your finger-blasted asshole?
- I, uh...
I spotted them on the streets of Belize.
- Believe it or not.
- [Bantam] Oh.
[Hutch] Yeah, while I was walking around,
drinking a beer.
And, uh, my instinct kicked in,
knew I had to bag 'em and tag 'em.
Knocked Sinh out with the beer bottle.
God, lady, I'm giving this
to you on a silver platter,
and you're fucking it up.
We've run out of time.
Just accept the fucking deal.
And as I'm folding up Sharpe's clothes,
with him still in 'em,
- by the way...
- [watch ticking]
...I see the light starting
to fade from his eyes.
Okay, so I just get what I need.
- [Hutch] And it dawned on me.
- [siren wailing]
[siren quiets]
This is my sunset.
And for the first time since I saw
Judi Dench in that Marigold Hotel...
I say, you don't have any earplugs,
do you?
...I found my smile again.
And I knew
that this is what I've been put
on God's green Earth to do.
[Cash] That's quite a story.
I've got chills.
Bantam forgot to mention, though,
you were also spotted by agents in France.
Never in Belize, though.
[Bantam] So we know,
with absolute 1,000% certainty,
that what you just
told us is 100%, first-class,
grade A bullshit.
- [watch beeps]
- [Hutch] All right, guys,
you got me, yeah.
- Well, look.
- [Bantam clears throat]
- I need help. I'm in way too deep.
- [high-pitched tone]
[distorted] That's why I came here.
We're renditioning your ass
back to the States. Fuck.
[Cash and Bantam groaning]
[yells] God.
You are in no position to make any kind
of demands, do you understand that?
- I am, though. I am in that position.
- How?
- [high-pitched tone]
- How? Ow! Fuck!
How much more?
Ten more seconds.
Otherwise we cook them.
Well, I guess I'm just gonna finish
my coffee and get out of here.
[Bantam and Cash groaning]
Three, four, five, eight, eight,
one, two, three, nine, five, six.
[to "She'll be Coming 'Round the
Mountain"] ♪ Three, four, five, eight ♪
♪ Eight, one, two, three,
nine, five, six ♪
♪ Three, four, five, eight, eight,
one, two, three, nine, five, six ♪
one, two, three ♪
♪ Four, five, eight, eight, one, two ♪
- Excuse me, buddy. Yoink.
- Get away from me.
- Later, homies.
- [retches]
- [fighter grunts]
- [bell clangs]
[Celine] How bad is it?
Like $200,000?
$400K.
Oh, shit.
And I'm sure the people you owe
the money to are not very nice.
I'm sure they're very mean.
[Erik] They are. Very mean.
And what if I told you
I could give you your money?
But?
[Celine] But I just need
one thing from you.
[Erik] And what's that?
Oh, just a cup of coffee.
- Get him a fucking coffee.
- [Bantam] You heard the man.
[Hutch] I literally couldn't stop crying
for three days.
Oh, is that for me?
Thanks.
[alarm blaring]
[guard] Code blue! Code blue! Code blue!
[Stahl whimpers]
[Nadia] Should've just taken the deal.
- Fuck, he took my ID.
- [Cash whimpering]
Open the door, Tony.
[lock beeps]
- You good?
- Yeah, fine.
What was all that "turning everybody in,"
"we're up to something" shit?
That's not what we talked about.
Well, it was a shit show.
No one believed you.
I had to improvise.
You fucked us.
- [gunshot]
- [grunts, gasps]
That's a one-strike rule in my book.
[groaning]
Jesus, Hutch.
[suspenseful, dramatic music playing]
Suspect shot.
We need medical.
Hutch is in the east wing.
He's, he's headed towards the Library.
Nobody let him leave this building.
Hutch!
[fading] Hutch!
[gasping]
[exciting music playing]
♪ ♪