It is time for war.
- Help.
-  Better to stay hidden
and wait for him to recover.
You said
you didn't love my other mom.
My real mom.
That she was a mistake.
Am I a mistake, too?
I'll always find my way back to you.
I'm gonna miss it here.
You were out almost two months.
Thaedus believes
he has won this war.
That he and his allies are safe
on his adopted planet.
Thragg's returning to Viltrum.
He's gonna regroup there.
If we strike Thragg now,
before he's joined
by his remaining forces,
we may have a chance
to end this war forever.
This is the third act of sabotage
by the Relonian natives this week.
The species remains unusually defiant,
despite our clear demonstrations
of Viltrumite superiority.
I recommend
a planet-wide cull of the population
before they disrupt
our mining operations any further.
They resist us because we are occupiers
and we are cruel.
If we restrain ourselves,
their labor will only aid in our goals.
Their labor is nothing
without their fear and respect.
Decimation sets an example,
not only for them,
but for the next misguided species.
Misguided?
Do Viltrumites not respect strength?
The courage
to challenge one's oppressors?
They are nothing to us.
The fact
that you believe otherwise makes me--
Regent Thragg.
Emperor Argall.
What is your counsel?
Thaedus, you say
Viltrumites respect strength.
That is correct. We do.
But these creatures,
their strength is not true strength.
We must educate them
not because of their defiance,
but because their weakness is an offense
to the natural order of the universe.
You are young, Regent.
Perhaps you do not yet
see the longer game--
Regent Thragg is correct.
Reduce the planet's population by 25%.
If they continue to resist,
eradicate them.
Emperor, I urge you to reconsider.
Do you?
Thaedus and I fought
side by side at Capida Minor.
He was the strongest among our company,
the most ruthless.
Yet ever since he returned
from his years in the Lay quadrant,
he speaks of mercy
and questions our ways.
It is troubling.
If you feel his weakness harms the empire,
take action.
Perhaps I am... mistaken.
Emperor Argall showed us our strength,
taught us our greatness,
gave us our destiny.
Because of him, all is ours.
All is ours.
The traitor has fled, but he will be found
and pay the price for his treason.
Be sure of that.
Even in death, Emperor Argall shows us
there is a sickness in our society,
poisoning us from within.
We will cut this cancer out.
You. Might you also betray us someday?
I will not, Grand Regent.
I do not believe you.
As our customs dictate,
I now assume the throne
as Grand Regent of Viltrum
until one of Argall's
heirs can be found.
This is my first command.
Seek out the weakness
that allowed this betrayal...
...and purge it from our midst.
Yes.
No.
It is done.
I will not repeat myself.
Yes, Grand Regent.
The blood
that ran through our streets
has cleansed us.
For you, the strong,
your life is its own reward.
But our work is not yet done.
For even in death,
Argall still guides us.
We will follow his path
and take our place
as the rightful rulers of the galaxy.
The universe itself will kneel.
As it was meant to be.
All is ours.
All is ours!
All is ours! All...
is ours!
I failed you, my emperor.
But I will not fail our people.
Not again.
All our intelligence agrees.
Thragg has retreated to Viltrum
with no more than a few of his people.
The rest are on their way there,
but will not arrive for several days.
This is our chance,
a brief moment
when the regent is vulnerable.
Um, Great Thaedus?
Don't get me wrong,
I would love to kill Thragg
for, like, a million reasons.
But won't that still leave us
with 40-something extra pissed-off
Viltrumites out for revenge?
Since the assassination of Emperor Argall,
they have known no leader but Thragg.
His loss will leave them
weak and directionless,
fighting amongst themselves
as they did before.
It will not be easy,
but once Thragg is gone,
the others will fall one by one.
Alone, Thragg could defeat any one of us.
But together,
we have a chance to end this war forever.
The future of the galaxy
depends on us,
and we may not all return.
But it is worth any price
to show the Viltrum Empire,
once and for all,
that even their strength
does not make them...
We're on our way
to fight this Thragg guy.
Um, it's just him,
plus two or three others,
versus eight of us, so... easy, right?
But apparently,
he was specially trained from birth
to be the strongest Viltrumite ever.
Even my dad's freaking out
about facing him.
Eve, I don't know.
This feels, uh...
this feels different.
And it's my last chance
to record a message for you
just in case something happens,
and, um...
You know what?
You're never even gonna see this because
I love you and I'm coming back.
I cannot believe it. You, too?
I didn't say they were gross.
I said I didn't want one.
Yeah, I know. No one does.
Hey, I'll eat anything.
My dad calls me
the human garbage disposal.
I just never have
much of an appetite when I'm nervous.
Also, those things have faces.
Your moo-cows have faces.
Okay, first, no one older than three
calls them "moo-cows."
And second, they don't have faces
when I eat them.
Why is everyone so nervous
about fighting this Thragg guy?
No way he lives up to the hype.
You haven't seen the reports.
What do they say?
That he lives up to the hype.
We'll see.
You guys are all crazy.
You gotta eat something.
The Unopan is correct.
We must nourish ourselves before battle.
Later, we will feast
on our enemies' entrails.
Or they on ours.
So this might be our last meal, huh?
Fantastic.
If you could eat anything
right now, what would it be?
Burger Mart drive-thru.
Boom. Triple triple. Yes.
Ooh, with loaded fries
from the secret menu.
It's my thing with my dad.
Actually, if I really had to pick,
Paul's spaghetti.
He's my mom's boyfriend.
He makes his own meatballs
and everything.
Mm. The Brain Bowl at the Galactic Grill.
I am already eating it.
My final meal will be my own blood,
as I choke on it, breathing my last breath
after a legendary battle
with a superior opponent.
That will be a satisfying meal indeed.
Mmm!
Right?
You seem worried, Nolan.
I am.
You should be, too.
This is the best chance
we've had in centuries
to end this conflict.
But that is not what troubles you.
No.
Thragg must die.
But the other Viltrumites...
You said it yourself,
they'll be weak and scattered
without him.
And yet, still capable
of untold death and destruction.
I will not risk even the smallest chance
their empire could rise again.
Mark and Oliver are part Viltrumite, too.
Everyone, we've reached
Viltrum's sensor range.
Time to get ready.
We've only got ten of these?
You have no idea
how difficult that sinlak poison
was to extract and refine.
Ah. Soon.
Thaedus is coming too?
He's, like, a million years...
...old.
Never mind.
Listen to me.
However strong you think you are,
Thragg is stronger.
Don't let him draw you
away from the group.
That also means you don't
try to take him on alone, Oliver.
I won't.
We stick together.
That's how we win this.
If anything happens,
just remember I...
Ah...
We know.
I am gonna be so bummed
if I don't survive this.
Is everyone ready?
Stick to the plan.
Sneak in past their sensors,
then scour the planet
as quickly as possible.
You all have coordinates
for the regent's most likely locations.
When you find him,
call in everyone else.
Remember, Thragg's death
is the only thing that matters.
What are you waiting for?
Go save the galaxy already.
Whoa. Are those...
Yes.
After Emperor Argall's assassination
and the Purge,
our empire expanded rapidly
as we conquered planets
in memory of the leader we lost.
But it wasn't long
before the scourge virus came
and took almost all of us.
This was the most fitting tomb
we could think of.
Every time we left our home,
we'd be reminded of our weakness
and failure.
They will help
conceal our approach.
Uh... guys?
Well, at least now
we don't need to waste a lot of time
looking for him, right? Heh.
This changes nothing.
They knew we were coming.
It doesn't matter. Kill Thragg!
Yes!
Traitor!
You dare return here--
This bug juice better work!
Huh?
Eat shit!
Okay, it works!
It definitely works!
Great! Shoot someone else!
I should have killed you both
on Thraxa!
The betrayer!
You were always weak, Kregg.
Oliver!
So disappointing.
Your time on Earth has
made you soft.
Don't count on it.
More!
Allen! Get to Thaedus!
What? Oh, shit. On my way!
Kill him before he fires again!
It's not my gun
you should be worried about.
Now!
Allen!
Save the darts!
These things are doing
just fine on their own.
Go!
It's been too long, Nolan.
What do you want, Thragg?
Simply to talk to an old friend.
Since when do we talk?
We've always talked.
Some simply chose not to listen.
Then talk.
Come home, Nolan.
Come home and all will be forgiven.
We have no home.
This place is a tomb.
Viltrum is not a tomb!
Mm.
It is who we are.
We will restore it to what it was,
as we will restore our people
to their rightful place
in the galaxy.
There's barely 40 of us left, Thragg.
Forty Viltrumites who know you
better than you know yourself.
Who have fought beside you.
Who have suffered
exactly the same way you have.
You're not my family anymore.
But the man
who almost caused our extinction is?
I know Thaedus created
the scourge virus.
And yet, you fight beside him.
He committed genocide on his own people.
To stop us from committing it on others.
You know we only ever did
what was necessary to preserve order.
Like coming after my sons?
We tested your sons,
as we have all been tested.
Do you think Thaedus will be
as kind to them if he wins this war?
Ah.
I see you're not as naive as I feared.
Ridiculous creatures.
A distraction at best.
That is what you think
of every species but your own, Lucan.
You'll soon learn better.
Hold on.
Repairing exterior object.
Thank... thank you.
It's all good.
Just keep kicking ass.
This room once echoed
with thousands of voices.
All united with the knowledge
that the universe belonged to Viltrum.
Argall showed us this.
Taught us our true power.
Thaedus...
Thaedus was a coward.
You know that, don't you?
It doesn't change anything.
Fighting for him is
fighting for your own destruction.
Your family's destruction.
I won't let him hurt my family.
You already have.
It's over, Thragg.
The entire galaxy is unified against us.
But it doesn't have to end
with our extinction.
Agree to terms and I will stop this,
no matter what Thaedus wants.
Would our emperor ever agree to terms?
Look around, Thragg.
We lost.
Can't you see why all this fell?
This is our home.
We will rebuild it.
No.
You won't.
The death of any Viltrumite
leaves a void in me.
Uh...
Hey, dickhead!
A black hole called.
It wants its suck back!
You are not one of us.
Oliver!
No!
The child was a failure.
He was no brother to you.
I killed Conquest.
I'll kill you, too.
Show me.
I'm not impressed.
Zoe!
Quick!
Ammunition depleted.
Oh, shit. I'm out.
Kill me if you can,
and die if you cannot,
so I may find a better foe.
Animal.
Finally!
No.
Everyone with me. Now.
Forget him. I need you.
What are we doing?
Space Racer, out front.
No! Stay with me.
No.
No way. We can't.
Mark. Trust me.
Space Racer.
Now!
No.
No!
Keep close.
Hold together!
Whoa.
Zoe!
It was the only way
to show them the truth.
I know.
Oliver. Where's Oliver?
Viltrumites!
Your world is destroyed.
Surrender is your only option.
No!
I choose death!
Emperor Argall, you are avenged.
You are all next.
Thaedus. Oh, God.
Allen.
Find Oliver.
Allen!
Yeah. Yeah, o-okay.
I offered you forgiveness.
I offered you an honorable death.
Instead,
you destroyed everything.
I was too quick with Thaedus.
I won't make the same mistake with you.
Okay. I understand
you are all a little surprised
and upset about what just happened.
Uh, Space Racer?
Space Racer!
Allen!
-  Zoe!
-  It's okay,
I got him.
We have to go.
We can't leave Mark and Nolan.
And where's Oliver?
We can't help them.
You could have been
a Viltrumite...
...but you chose to be noth--
How... how do we beat him?
Mark...
Dad!
What a waste.
Grand Regent, kill him.
They destroyed our home.
Silence.
We are too few already.
What are your orders,
Grand Regent?
Hey.
Hey, buddy. Mark?
You awake?
You are.
Look at that. Welcome back.
Allen. How long...
Couple weeks.
It was touch and go for a while.
Tell you, you guys sure know
how to stress a Unopan out.
Where's Oliver? Where's my dad?
Dad.
You're alive.
Woke up yesterday.
Oliver.
He'll be okay.
He just needs time to heal.
What happened to Thragg and the others?
What's the last thing
you remember?
Thragg had me.
You were... I-I thought you were dead.
Why'd he let us live?
Good question.
But we've got a bigger one.
What? Where are they?
That is the thing.
As all of you know...
Um, as all of you know, Thaedus is dead.
So the council asked someone to lead
until there's time
to appoint his replacement.
And, well, believe it or not,
it's this guy.
They mostly want me to deal
with one small problem.
The remaining Viltrumites.
Yep. General Telia?
We have ships searching sector by sector,
but so far, they've just disappeared.
It's freaking everyone out.
I mean,
the hiding is a good sign, right?
It's not generally
what Viltrumites like to, uh...
Uh, Mark? What's up?
They've gone to Earth.