[The Epoch of Miyu]
[Episode 19]
How is it?
Is it not good?
Let me try it.
Qiaoqi, I haven't finished speaking.
It's pretty good.
-Qiaoqi.
-What’s wrong?
What are you doing?
We're done for today.
We're off work.
-That’s all for today.
-Let me make another pot.
Qiaoqi, listen to me.
No more cooking today.
We're off work.
Come on, drink.
If you keep drinking like this,
you won't be able to go home later.
It's fine.
I'm not going back. I'll just drink.
Fine.
I'll drink with you.
Join me.
Be careful.
Are you okay?
Let's dance together. Come on.
Get down.
That's dangerous.
Dance here.
No.
Get down.
Qiaoqi.
The Chinese restaurant
is temporarily closed.
So, there's a young and beautiful
female head chef
waiting to get promoted, huh?
It's a pity.
She only has good looks.
As for her skills,
they are far from good enough.
I think this woman
is either well-connected
with the higher-ups
or being used as a tool by them,
to be built up and then torn down.
Anyway, the Chinese restaurant
has gone too far this time.
It's completely shut down.
Everything will be fine.
Wake up.
Time to eat.
I've been a chef for so many years.
This is the first time
someone has cooked for me.
Get up first.
Eat after you get up.
Hurry up.
I'm taking you somewhere later.
Where to?
It's the weekend.
Wherever we go, it'll just be crowded.
I'm not taking you sightseeing.
We have to go back to our hometown.
I've already bought the tickets.
Just tell me.
Are your parents
causing trouble for you again?
Rui.
I have no idea what's going on.
Watch my back.
Mr. Ji, you're very punctual.
I won't let you make a wasted trip.
Just make sure you bring enough money.
Me? I'm penniless.
How come you're getting stingier
since you became the boss?
Hello, Eva.
Please go ahead.
Navigate to Linglong Town.
[Navigate to Linglong Town]
Got it.
Which destination is it?
[Linglong Town]
Okay.
Recommending the best route.
Out of nowhere,
why are we going there?
I've dropped enough hints.
Do you really have to make me mention
the disappointing Yan Du Xian?
Fu Man Xiang.
Are you talking about Fu Man Xiang?
What's the owner's name again?
Old Fu.
Right.
The Cured Meat Stew from Old Fu's place
is the base for Yan Du Xian.
How could I forget him?
I remember when we
were back in our hometown,
what I craved the most
was that Cured Meat Stew.
More than 10 years have passed in a flash.
You are my savior.
I love you to death.
Alright, enough.
Stop being so cheesy.
Who got drunk
and cried last night?
So you're okay now?
If only
we could always be this happy.
Do you know how long
it's been since I came back?
Oh, no.
Xu Miyu,
if I lose my fighting spirit like this,
I'll count on you.
Okay.
Just kidding.
I'm going to fight
in the kitchen for 30 years.
I envy you.
You are always full of fighting spirit.
Sailing against the current,
you either forge ahead or fall behind.
People always need a goal.
Yeah.
[Qi Fang Li]
Here?
It's quite far.
Let's go.
Is this where you said
we can get cured pork?
[Qi Fang Li]
Just follow my lead today.
Okay.
Smell that?
I'm already hungry.
No seats.
Business is really good...
You'll have to share a table.
Do you still want to stay?
We do.
Follow me.
You must have been here many times,
knowing your way around.
It's my first time too.
I'm just a person
who is curious, gossipy,
and loves to ask around.
Wow,
there's really no empty seat.
Smells so good.
These are the only 2 seats left.
You guys share a table.
Let's not share a table.
Let's wait outside a bit more.
Okay.
Mr. Ji?
Ms. Xu?
Why are you here?
So many guests on the weekend,
don't you need to be on duty?
I've arranged everything.
You can check my work when you go back.
She came with me to find cured pork.
We're here for cured pork too.
Looks like we had the same idea.
Have a seat.
Did you know?
This shop
is the locals' hidden eatery.
Especially that dish called...
Cured Meat Stew.
Miyu and I have been
eating it since we were kids.
Is your hometown here?
We used to be neighbors.
We met experts today.
We can't go wrong following our Chef Li.
Aren't you exaggerating?
I'm fine now.
You recovered pretty fast.
Am I that fragile?
Hurry up and order.
What are you doing?
Don't keep a straight face.
We're not at the hotel.
You order first.
I'll go return a call.
Come on.
What do you like to eat?
You order.
You're familiar with this place.
This one.
So, the two you
are locals?
Yes.
We used to be neighbors.
Miyu took good care
of me when I was little.
She always stood up for me.
No wonder you always want to help Miyu.
This is the taste.
I'm glad you brought me here.
Right?
It tastes just like when we were kids.
How is it? Good?
The taste is really good.
After we finish eating,
we should talk to the lady
who runs this place.
The one serving tables
is the one in charge.
The real owner is Old Fu.
But I heard he's very hard to deal with.
He only works with people he likes.
What kind of people does he like?
That's hard to say.
Do you remember when we were little,
every time we came here to eat,
Old Fu would always be in the yard
drinking with some customers?
How good do you think
Old Fu is at drinking?
Hello, Sir.
Sir.
Oh please, don't "sir" me.
I am
just a cook.
Mr. Fu.
If you don't mind,
I'll handle the first round with you.
Qiaoqi and I grew up eating your food.
We never had the chance to drink with you.
I will drink this cup first
to show my respect.
So you are regular customers.
Ever since the old customers moved away,
no one's had a drink
with me in a long time.
It's really nice to meet you today.
Come on, let's keep drinking.
Let me
have this drink
with you, Sir.
Come.
Okay.
Since today is a rare opportunity,
why don't
you guys
all come at me?
Let's see
how much I can drink now.
Okay.
Let's toast to you.
-Okay.
-To you.
Come on.
To you.
Cheers.
Come on,
let's keep drinking.
As for this wine,
the most delicious part
has to be the last bit.
Now that we've drunk this much,
it's not too much to call you Uncle Fu,
is it?
Calling me so intimately,
what do you want?
Well, I...
Well...
Ji Feng.
You speak.
Uncle Fu,
we just had your Cured Meat Stew.
We think the taste
is absolutely incredible.
What's the secret to that rich flavor?
We'd like to ask for some guidance.
It's just a simple, home-style flavor.
Nothing special.
Nothing special at all.
Raise the seven-burner stove,
a copper kettle boils waters
from rivers far they rove.
Set the table, welcome all;
guests from every corner call.
-All who come are honored here.
-It's all in how you work them near.
-Meet with smiles, part with ease,
-no regrets, no memories.
-Once they leave, the tea goes cold.
My tongue
is getting tied up.
Hope that wasn't too bad.
Don't laugh.
It's nice.
Thank you.
Mr. Fu.
Once they leave, the tea goes cold.
That's what they sing in the opera.
But it's not like that in reality.
Qiaoqi and I have loved
your Cured Meat Stew since we were kids.
Now we've encountered
some problems at work.
You were the first person we thought of.
We wanted to come back
and taste this delicacy.
As for me,
I don't have any superb culinary skills.
I just have a little experience
accumulated over the years.
Uncle Fu.
You are too modest.
Let alone anything else,
I've never had better
cured pork anywhere else.
You mean this cured pork?
How exactly is it made?
It's absolutely amazing.
This cured pork...
To be honest,
I didn't
make it myself.
It's sourced from outside.
Where did you get it from?
It's where that scene
we just sang
took place.
In...
Chunlai Teahouse?
Go find it on Wanghu Island yourself.
[Wanghu Island]
If anyone asks,
just say
I had too much to drink
and let it slip.
Thank you, Mr. Fu.
You're welcome.
I'll get going.
The morning glow
falls upon
the shores of Yangcheng Lake.
There is a place called
Chunlai Inn.
Without you,
none of us could've
handled Mr. Fu's lines.
I was just winging it.
When I was little,
my dad loved Peking Opera.
I used to hear him
humming those lines at home.
Xu Datong can sing opera?
Not Xu Datong.
It was my biological father.
[Chunlai Inn]
Why is there no one here?
Hello!
No way.
We came at a really bad time.
Went to restock.
Will be back before dinner.
How much longer do we have to wait?
Don't be so tense, everyone.
We finally got to
come out for the weekend,
and then this happens.
I see a riverbank over there.
How about we
hang out and sober up while we wait?
Relax.
Let's go.
[Chunlai Inn]
Mr. Ji.
Aren't you coming?
Coming.
How do I throw this?
Here.
Use this.
This one?
Right.
♪ Life is full of ♪
No.
A bit lower.
♪ Countless crossroads ♪
Lower.
Right, come on.
♪ Chase joy too hard, and it slips away ♪
You need to throw it flat.
I know how to do this.
♪ All those confusions ♪
♪ No answers, no reasons ♪
♪ Throwing ourselves
into the tide of the unknown ♪
Are you okay?
What happened?
He twisted his ankle.
It's fine.
He sprained his ankle.
What's wrong?
I sprained my ankle.
You sprained it?
How did that happen?
My bad.
I accidentally pushed him.
It's not your fault.
I lost my balance.
Let me help you.
No. No.
Let me rest for a while.
Is it serious?
How about this?
Go back and see a doctor first.
Come back later.
I'll go with him.
He can't manage alone.
Then...
-Ms. Xu, you…
-I’d better stay.
I'm a local.
If anything happens,
he'll still have me
to talk things through with.
We can't let Mr. Ji wait here alone.
Okay.
Hurry up then.
The boat is arriving soon.
Slow down.
Be careful.
Take it slow.
-Take it slow.
-Are you OK?
OK. OK.
No rush.
Take it slow.
Hello?
What is it?
What's wrong?
Hello?
What happened?
It seems there's a problem
with the production team's accommodation.
My signal is bad,
so I didn't hear clearly.
But I think I need
to go back and handle it.
You go back first.
I'll wait here.
No.
We don't have to
order the cured pork today.
Let's go back first,
and come back another day.
Okay.
Let's go.
It's gone.
We have to wait for the next one.
The next boat isn't coming.
What do you mean?
Isn't there another one in half an hour?
Look at the sky.
We've been notified.
The ferry is suspended.
Then how do we get back?
Forget about going back.
It's about to rain.
Hurry inside and take cover.
This...
♪ Just lift your head, oh ♪
♪ Don't look back ♪
♪ I've already learned ♪
Let's find a place to take cover.
♪ If it's not mine, I won't force it ♪
♪ No matter how you force it ♪
♪ It'll only turn into a long,
endless wait ♪
♪ Waiting to make peace with myself ♪
♪ And waiting to meet someone again ♪
♪ Wave goodbye ♪
Be careful.
Watch your step.
Slow down.
Over there.
Get on the boat.
Is anyone here?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You are soaked.
Here is a towel.
Dry yourself quickly.
It absorbs water fast.
Okay.
What about the hotel?
There's no signal.
We'll have to wait until tomorrow.
Here's a space heater.
Come over here and warm up.
Give me this.
It's hot.
Let me see.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Let me do it.
The bulb seems to be burnt out.
Let's use this for light.
Xu Miyu.
Regarding Li Bingyan...
I want to apologize to you.
You did a great job getting Li Bingyan
to withdraw the case.
It's just that
I haven't found a chance
to tell you.
I was too emotional that day.
I yelled at you without thinking.
I'm sorry.
I never thought
that one day
I would receive
an apology from you, Mr. Ji.
I accept it.
Actually, I thought about it.
Maybe you were right that day.
Because of Mr. Tan,
I left my post without permission,
causing the hotel to
almost lose 2 big clients.
But I'm a forewoman
of the HSKP Department.
I only care about my own duties.
All I have to do
is satisfy all the guests' needs.
I don't know anything else,
and I don't need to know.
So,
I became the person
most suitable to be used by Li Bingyan.
If I can only see the tip of the iceberg,
how can I go further on this path?
Or rather,
where is my path?
I've always felt that
spending too much time
thinking about one problem
only brings unnecessary anxiety.
If you really
don't know where your path is,
why not start with trial and error?
Step out of your comfort zone
and look at the other sides
of that iceberg.
I thought...
Thought I wouldn't understand
the troubles of bottom-level employees?
I never said that.
I thought in your eyes,
I was just a hopeless canary.
I never said that either.
But when I first saw you,
I did think so a little...
When I first saw you,
I had a very good impression.
I'm sorry
for disappointing you later.
You're burning up.
It looks like the rain won't stop today.
You have a fever right now.
Let's just make do
and sleep here for the night.
We'll figure things out tomorrow.
I'm fine.
You should get some rest.
I'll just sit over here.
Hurry, lie down first.
You're awake.
It's already morning.
How are you feeling?
Do you still have a fever?
I...
I think I'm feeling much better.
That's good.
By the way, I just used this to
rinse my mouth and wash my face.
Here.
Hello, Mr. Qian.
Alright, I'll leave
the sales department to you for now.
But we'll talk about the contract
with the production team when I get back.
I'm hanging up.
Okay, that's it for now.
How are things with the production team?
Rui has gone back to deal with it for me.
So no rush.
Let's go get the cured pork first.
Okay.
[Chunlai Inn]
There are quite a lot of people.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Enjoy your meal.
Ma'am.
You are making us drool.
[Chunlai Inn]
Thank you for coming, Mr. Tang.
You're getting extra Yan Du Xian today,
on the house.
Great.
Please come this way.
Here, try this.
You guys too.
-Enjoy.
-Ma'am, is there any seat left?
Welcome.
Come sit inside.
Try this.
We came to the right place.
[Chunlai Inn]
Excuse me, Sir.
I'm from Shanghai.
I'm Ji Feng, the general manager
of Shanghai Purong Hotel.
Here's my card.
We really like your cured pork.
The quality is very good and authentic.
I want to ask if we can
buy it wholesale from you.
I didn't make it.
[Chunlai Inn]
She made it.
Hello.
I'm Ji Feng.
You want to buy cured pork, right?
My side of the family runs a butcher shop.
We do everything
from breeding to processing.
If we order 500 kilograms a year,
can you supply it?
500 kilograms?
Yes.
Wait a moment.
Let me make a phone call.
Hello, Mom.
We got a big order.
It's 500 kilograms a year.
Can you handle it?
Okay, okay.
[Chunlai Inn]
It's settled.
No problem.
We can sign the contract right away.
Thank you. Thank you.
Ma'am,
can we take some back first?
[Chunlai Inn]
Sure.
Give her all the pork
we have left in the kitchen.
Okay.
Wait a minute. We'll get it for you.
Thank you.
That's great.
[Chunlai Inn]
[Repayment Reminder]
[Dear Customer,]
[amount due this month: RMB 5,000]
[Repayment Reminder]
[Dear Customer,]
[amount due this month: RMB 5,000]
Let me help you.
Mr. Xue.
How is your foot?
Is your foot okay?
Where's the meat?
The meat.
Here it is.
There's more.
Those guys in the sales department
wanted to raise the price.
I held them down for you.
What do I get in return?
Thanks, Rui.
I'll treat you to
a big meal some other day.
Is that okay?
That's more like it.
Also,
the production team is waiting upstairs
for you to sign the contract.
Hurry up.
Okay, I'll go then.
Okay.
Um...
Come to my office when you're done today.
I have something for you.
I'll head up now.
I'm going to work.
♪ Life is full of ♪
♪ Countless crossroads ♪
♪ Chase joy too hard, and it slips away ♪
Thank you.
♪ All those confusions ♪
This essential oil
and
♪ No answers, no reasons ♪
the essential oil in this soap
should be the same.
[Internal Office] [Convention Center]
♪ Throwing ourselves
into the tide of the unknown ♪
You two look into it.
I'll leave the 19th floor to you two.
♪ Knowing when to advance or retreat,
yet still asleep ♪
Same goes for the front desk.
For the guests' registration information,
♪ Rushing to ripen before our time ♪
ensure its security, alright?
That's all for today. Meeting adjourned.
♪ Sighing at partings,
who meets whom at which crossing ♪
♪ Busy and restless ♪
♪ No turning back, no stopping ♪
♪ Our path—do you see it now ♪
Come in.
Mr. Ji,
you asked for me.
Yes.
Marcos from Liberty Group
asked me to give this to you.
[Purong Hotel]
[Dear Miss Xu, I feel so lucky to have
enjoyed your incredible butler service]
[at the Purong Hotel in Shanghai, China.]
Mr. Yang actually remembers me.
His commercial director,
Ms. Brown, told me
that the reason he chose
to sign the contract with Purong Hotel
was because of you.
You deserve the credit this time.
But I did make
a misjudgment on this matter.
What kind of reward do you want?
You can go back and think about it.
My promise is valid long-term.
I have thought about it.
Doesn't our hotel
have quarterly
career development assessment?
Employees who have been here
for less than a year
are not qualified to take it,
but I want to take it.
Can you tell me why?
[Purong Hotel]
I thought about what you said.
I want to step out of my comfort zone,
but I don't know for now
which direction to go in.
So I hope the results of this assessment
can give me a direction.
Okay.
I promise you.
Then take out your phone.
[Purong Hotel]
Open WeChat.
Scan mine.
Once the assessment results are ready,
we'll be in touch.
[Miyu]
Okay.
I'll get going then.
[WeChat]
[I'm Kenny J]
[Kenny J]
I'm not surprised.
[WeChat]
[Discover]
[Moments]
[1 new message]
[Message]
[Details] [Miyu]
Come and try it.
Miyu.
Thank you.
-Try the cured pork.
-Careful, it's hot.
Careful, it's hot.
How is it?
That's the taste.
One bite and it hits the soul.
Mr. Ji,
when will it open?
Very soon.