"Episode 1"
Hey, this way.
- Yay! - Dammit.
Please show your code.
I'm an acquaintance of the host.
If you don't have a code,
you cannot enter.
Yahoo!
- Whoa! - Hey! Hey!
- It's not to that extend.
- What are you doing?
Let's return.
I'm going in.
Are you serious?
No matter how you look at it,
this is dangerous.
But we have to confirm if he's in there.
Wait here,
I don't want to drag you into this.
Hey, Rei!
That troublemaker...
Where should we go today?
- Huh? - That's cheating. Invite me too.
Everyone's going.
Let's go.
- I'm going too. - Let's go.
Ah. Wait a minute.
- Huh? - Why?
See you later.
- Please don't go. - See you later.
You're really pumped up, Arashi.
Of course. Vanished from the race.
More like forced to be vanished.
The legendary racers and mechanics
are competing tonight
without holding back.
Gets my adrenaline going.
You're still the same.
If it's exciting then it means
there's some serious money and
shady organizations involved.
You don't look like you're hating it.
Huh?
Because your kids are cute so I like it.
- Wow! - Hey.
I get it.
Nice body lines, right?
Still the same as ever.
Yay!
Lost badly, damn it! Not worth it!
There's still the big finale.
Apparently, that guy Arashi
will be in the final race.
Arashi... I just heard Arashi!
Excuse me, may I check your pass?
I'm a local resident.
I heard the noise and
came to check it out.
Trespassing, huh?
Let go of me!
We've got a rat! Catch that kid!
There is an intruder!
A hero here to crash the race?
But if there's someone scarier,
there's one person right here.
Hey!
Whoa!
Let go!
Sorry about this, Arashi-san!
Arashi.
Pretty bold of you to call me
that without honorifics.
You troublemaker.
Strange, isn't it?
That someone as ordinary as me
would end up in an illegal race venue.
It all started on
a stormy night...
Heavy rain is covering all over.
Drivers, please drive safely.
Listening to 'Love in the Air'.
I'm Hideshima Fumika, the host.
No way! What's going on?
Huh?
Please start!
Ah, damn it! I give up!
Yes?
I'll take a look at the engine.
Open the hood of the car.
Huh? Really?
I can't help, so
this is the least I can do.
Hold this.
I was really stuck.
Thank you so much for helping me.
It's an old car.
It's my father's most important car.
If you're going to keep driving it,
you'd better learn some maintenance.
Next time, handle it yourself.
The helmet.
Ah.
You're really handsome.
Ah, no...
Thanks for the compliment.
I'll be taking this back.
You'd better get home soon,
or you'll catch a cold.
I'd like to get home too.
Thank you so much!
Never mind. Hurry back.
"Love in The Air -Premonition of Love-"
(Kaminichi University)
(Faculty of Engineering,
Department of Architecture)
He waited until I left and watched me
drive off before he went back.
At first, I was like,
'Is he going to kill me?'
But he was really kind,
a genius mechanic.
And his face…
So handsome that everyone just
clears the road for him, right.
How'd you know?
Because this is the third time
you've told that story.
I just want to talk about it,
so listen, will you?
Do you realize you're being annoying?
Do you realize how
cold you're being, Kai?
Now I do.
Hey!
Come on, just listen! You're being mean!
What's the conversation about?
Rinka.
Did you need me?
No, I was looking for Kai.
Huh? Are you two secretly dating?
Are you crazy?
So, what's up?
The seminar's get-together next month.
Do you know if any alumni are attending?
Oh, alumni…
I just met my senior Arashi before,
so I knew.
You saw Arashi-senpai?
He was on campus?
He graduated already, so why?
- When? How!? - Too close.
Back up a bit.
Sorry.
By the way, who's Arashi-senpai?
You don't know?
No way…
You don't know Arashi-senpai?
Which Arashi?
He entered on a special scholarship,
graduated at the top of his class with
the highest scores in history.
From what I heard,
he's been selected multiple times in
international design competitions.
It is said that his family is
involved in some kind of business,
but the details are still a mystery.
The mystery around him
is part of the charm!
I get that.
My older brother was
always praising Arashi-senpai.
I admired him so much that I joined,
but it's disappointing
he graduated already.
Does your brother like guys?
Haa...
Rei.
Didn't you also praise that biker guy?
I was just complimenting him.
- We're just complimenting him too, yes?
- I don't know why you're upset,
but it's weird to say that.
If you think something is beautiful,
gender has nothing to do with it.
And at least for our generation,
stop looking at others with prejudice.
Kai, let me know if you hear about
the alumni coming to the event?
- I'll check for you. - Yeah.
Rinka.
I don't have any prejudice! It's just...
Speaking without thinking.
Let me sum it up in two words,
heart broken.
I haven't been rejected yet!
I'm still courting.
What's so special about Arashi anyway?
Can't even compete
with the motorcycle guy.
- Rinka, need any help?
- I'm fine. Focus on your own work.
- Rinka, let me carry that for you.
- No, it's super light.
Rinka, aren't you getting hungry?
Rei.
Hey, first-year, what's up?
Looking so down.
Want some of my drink?
Hey, control yourself a bit.
If you keep acting up,
you'll regret it later.
No, I don't have the guts...
No, not you. I meant
the legendary alumnus,
also known as 'the Savior.'
Senpai shows up
just at the right time.
That... Don't tell me that...
It's a storm out there.
Let's give a round of applause for
Arashi-san, who arrived with the storm!
- Yay! - Arashi-senpai!
Well...
You are...
Arashi-senpai?
Yeah. And...
Who are you?
Arashi-senpai is...
is the motorcycle guy...
The harsh truth.
And he didn't even remember me.
I guess I don't need to thank anymore.
Let's go home.
Ah. Huh?
Hey! Don't tell me that...
Ah, dammit!
Am I cursed with cars?
Dammit!
Ugh, dumb head...
Arashi...
Senpai!
Are you honking?
Oh, no, um...
The engine won't start.
Senpai, please help me.
Rei, was it?
Yes, that's right.
If you want to seduce me,
try being more subtle.
The battery is broken.
Did I hear him wrong?
I hear an unusual noise.
Give up. Leave it here tonight,
no tow company will come in this rain.
Wait.
This car means a lot to me…
I want to call a tow service right now.
Do you know a good one?
I know one.
It's expensive, though. Can you pay?
Yes, I can.
Thank you for letting me
use the bathroom.
Kai, I figured out what Arashi-senpai's
family does for a living.
You should have told me your family
owns a repair shop.
If I'd known, I wouldn't have hesitated.
I mean, about the repair fee, of course.
Sit here.
Let me dry your hair.
That feels nice.
Want me to keep going?
Is that okay?
Huh?
Wait. What are you doing?
Just discussing your payment.
You mean you like guys?
Depends on the person.
But you're the one
who started this, right?
No, I didn't.
Didn't you?
Hey.
Staring at me all that time,
holding on to me?
That...
I'm not trying to seduce you.
Really?
Huh? Wait...
Why is he so handsome?
But...
Don't tease me,
you came here yourself.
Let go!
Don't misinterpret things!
Even if you paid me,
I wouldn't sleep with you!
Where are you going?
I'm going home.
I don't want to be here.
Is your only good feature
your face, you bastard?
What do you want?
Go to sleep.
I'm not in the mood anymore.
Who would believe that?
Then go outside and catch a cold.
I'm going to sleep.
(00:12 AM)
(01:25 AM)
(02:29 AM)
Haa... I survived.
Just because you're wearing clothes
doesn't mean anything.
Don't look! You jerk!
What's that?
Want me to show you
what a real jerk is?
Go die and turn into stardust!
Oww. That hurt.
Rei.
As your senpai,
let me give you some advice,
stop acting foolish.
Aren't you going?
Do you want to continue?
I'll tell everyone at the university
you're a jerk!
Dammit, so annoying.
Both the weather and that guy!
Do you need to go to the hospital?
I'm perfectly fine!
Then is there something
you want to talk about?
You've been acting different
since the drinking party.
And then you suddenly went home.
It's obviously weird.
Yes.
Oh, the repairs.
Yes, I'll pick it up tomorrow.
Yes.
Thank you.
Great,
I totally forgot.
The alternator has been replaced and
a new battery has also been installed.
Wow, the engine is running.
Now, here's the bill.
(Invoice Mr. Amemiya Rei
Amount charged: 700 000 yen)
Amamiya-san?
Oh no. There's no way I can pay this!
Oh, you're Arashi's boy?
Huh? B-boy?
If you're Arashi's boy, then you don't
have to worry about this.
Boy? No, I'm...
It seems he did some
of the repairs himself.
If you're Arashi's boy,
the charges are waived.
I'm not anything to him!
Besides,
what if he tampered with my car?
Customer,
Listen, I don't mean to brag,
but he is exceptionally skilled.
Besides his work
in architectural design,
he occasionally takes on repairs
for VIP clients.
His skills and passion for cars
are unquestionable.
I'm sorry.
Then just sign this receipt.
(Receipt Signation: Amemiya Rei)
All done.
Contract completed.
I asked if you could pay
the high fee, didn't I,
Rei?
Huh?
Nothing in this world is free.
(Not Just the Rain,
but the Storm Approaches)
"Love in The Air -Premonition of Love-"
You were so loud earlier.
You're cute.