[birds chirping]
[gentle music playing]
You gotta wake them.
They're worn out, I fear.
The judge will soon
find out about the house.
She can't uncover this or they're screwed.
She'll have them placed ASAP.
- I'll find a solution.
- Is that so?
Aunt Régine.
It's our only option. I'll speak with her.
Speak to who?
[Marvin] The teacher.
You're late. I'll have to explain, Cass.
Get up, sunshines.
[kid groans]
You okay?
I'm out of socks.
Can you wear your sister's socks?
She has smaller feet than me.
- These yours?
- Yes.
Here.
Let's go. Come on, come on, come on.
We're already late, come on.
[Chloé] Come on, let's go.
[Chloé] Marvin.
What is it?
There's nothing still.
Give it time. It'll arrive soon.
Needs more pizzazz.
Look, I've made something.
SOS
GARDENING
[Marvin] Is it too much?
Who gives a shit?
It's for obtaining funds.
- We'll change it after.
- [chuckles]
It's fine.
[somber music playing]
[music fades]
[Marvin] I have it.
[bag unzips]
What are you doing here?
Didn't you do enough already?
Did I start this damn fire?
I wouldn't be surprised.
What?
You gonna send your goons?
[sighs]
Why the hell are you here?
This isn't your trap house here, Kylian.
Don't be a child.
You saw the state of the house.
I know this is your fault!
I am sure. It wasn't an accident.
You're crazy.
You must have made some enemies.
I'm certain. And now they're after us.
- You're wrong.
- [sucks teeth]
Mama would've burned it!
Get lost then, you douche!
Hey, Milord!
So, what's your plan?
What do you mean?
Well, you're a boss, no?
You're bagging a lot.
It's a bit complicated.
- [scoffs]
- Wait.
Come work then with me.
Maybe you could support me.
[exhales heavily]
It's a no, bro.
If you asked back then,
what do you think I would've said?
But then again…
No hard feelings?
Now we're even.
That's for the kids.
What are you gonna do, Kingsley?
I don't have to explain anything.
Maybe I can help.
[chuckles] You gonna try to coax me
to share my secrets?
You must really think I'm an idiot.
[sucks teeth] Scram.
[somber music playing]
[teacher] So, class,
and it is from Balzac to Shakespeare,
the variety of narratives
illuminate the multifaceted nature
of this grave act we witness.
Lafleur?
This crime was long considered
the worst act that can be imagined,
meriting punishment that is exceptional.
But why?
Because it undermines
the authority of the father
and the natural order of the world,
as well as divine order.
"Tu quoque, mi fili?"
Is this a phrase you know?
[intriguing music playing]
"You too, my son."
The words of Caesar
when Brutus killed him.
Very good, Kylian.
Except Brutus wasn't exactly
the son of Julius Caesar, right?
But with this, we can see
that the destruction of the father,
a parricide, is an act
that is both foundational and symbolic.
The destruction of the father,
or of Caesar,
is the price to pay
for their descendants' existence.
PRICE TO PAY
[knock on door]
- Does your brother know you're here?
- No.
I said no.
Come in.
- [door closes]
- This is where you're staying then?
I can still rely on some people.
He robbed you, but you trust him for real?
He could've killed me but didn't, so…
Did you bring your computer?
[Pearl] That's him.
FAST, EFFICIENT, DISCREET
He taught my brother everything.
Hey bro
ZEBLEDXXX
Tiny tight pussy?
[typing]
PEARL
The one and only
I need a deep cleaning.
ZEBLEDXXX
Express?
[typing]
PEARL
Yes.
ZEBLEDXXX
Where?
Ducos.
Ducos? The prison?
Can you get to somebody?
Tell him.
[typing]
ZEBLEDXXX
Interesting! We'll need to meet up
[Pearl] Care to explain?
Where is the container?
[pensive music playing softly]
I'm surprised it's this cold
this time of year. Put on the heat.
I'm not turning on the car.
[sucks teeth]
This sucks.
It's cold!
Fuck, man, close the door!
Where are you going?
I need to piss! Want to come hold my dick?
Douchebag!
[foghorn blows in background
[exhales slowly]
[car approaching]
[Annabelle] Someone's here.
Who is it?
Is it them?
I don't know.
- [Annabelle] Something's off, isn't it?
- [phone vibrates]
It's them.
Wait, how'd you smuggle that in?
[bag unzips]
Stay here.
All right, we got five minutes.
- Who is that?
- Oh apologies, I forgot my manners.
You can call me "Dede."
William.
Meet my life insurance.
All good? We've all been introduced now.
Who's this? Your girlfriend?
- I told you to stay in the car, didn't I?
- Do you think I'm just some puppet?
I'm the one who's leading the operation!
[laughs softly] Okay, love birds.
We gotta be quick. Hey.
Okay. We have some things to clear up.
You came because
your brother insisted I bring you for--
Hey, hold on!
I am here because I brought in the client.
And what's your problem?
Just because my brother did this, or…
Who's your boss?
And who am I to Kylian?
Exactly.
I'll always outrank you.
Now, let's go!
[upbeat music playing
on speakers in background]
[Kingsley] Dang, bro.
You had a tattoo this whole time?
[man] I was piss drunk, bro.
I don't even remember getting it.
Just woke up with a flower on my ass.
I was in Phuket.
Phuket? Which Phuket?
Phuket in Thailand, bro.
How many Phukets do you know?
- Phuket? More like Ducos, right?
- [all chuckling]
- [man] Just because you don't travel…
- Fuck off, bro. Come on.
I'm a globetrotter.
Yo!
[car approaching]
What are they doin'?
They're trying to be stealthy, my friend.
[man] Are you sure the dope is in there?
This haul is the fourth made
since breakfast.
They're not goin' on a cruise.
We've gotta be fast.
Shit! What the hell's happenin' there?
- Forget the plan, King.
- Don't start again.
Yeah, I'm not so sure anymore.
Customs has showed up, bro.
Be for real, it's too risky.
If you see a blue light,
it doesn't mean it's customs, homie.
Not important, I got a bad feeling.
Guys, don't let me down.
I'm talking about the jackpot here.
And you're shitting yourselves?
Okay, King.
Well?
[Pearl] Let him talk.
[softly] And don't upset him.
Ah!
Do you lick her pussy?
No.
- Why not? Too pretty for you?
- [Pearl scoffs]
Okay, please fucking focus.
We didn't come here about my pussy, okay?
Ducos? I'll have to contact a few guys.
Need to pick the right man.
Is the prey a boss?
Nah, he's a nobody.
Who is he?
Fabrice Sifflet.
He's my father.
Your father?
You want to have your father killed?
You do that by your own hand.
[sighs] How much?
I'm telling you, for this,
I'm not your man, yeah?
Have you lost your mind?
Even if he tried raping you
as a fucking kid, I don't do that.
Do this by yourself!
- What the hell?
- I didn't know.
He's your blood, man.
Your father, your mother, your brothers,
those are family.
A hitman shouldn't have to touch those!
Now look here.
Your father's blood won't be on my hands.
Did you hear me? No fuckin' way, kid!
What's wrong with you?
[expectant music playing]
GROCERY STORE
- [lighter flicks]
- Shit.
Mmm.
[yelps and groans]
[groaning softly]
Top half is yours, the bottom's mine.
[Jocelyn weakly] What? Guys?
No…
- [Jocelyn groans]
- [flesh squelching]
- [squelching continues]
- [Jocelyn screaming]
Mmm!
It's super good!
Were you a cook before?
Before what?
Before… all this, the business.
I'm not a pro cook.
- I just love a job well done.
- Mmm-mmm.
No, this is another level.
I mean, the pasta is perfect.
The bit of basil put on top, master move!
And…
this business, how'd it begin,
Kylian and you?
What do you mean?
Well… you're an unexpected pair.
And?
Forget about it.
Started in middle school.
Weren't y'all in different middle schools?
Yeah.
I mugged Kylian after school.
Mugged? You really mugged him?
The knife I carried was… like this big.
- I was starving.
- [gentle music playing]
I got so angry watching bougie pricks
splurge on sandwiches at the local deli.
[gentle music continues]
So one day,
I decided to mug one at random.
So I grabbed Kylian by the collar,
and I told him,
"Yo, what you got on you?"
"Gimme your money."
He looked me in the eyes,
and said to me calmly…
"I have none on me."
"But if you're needing a job…
we should talk."
What?
Come on, for real?
It was beyond what he said or…
how he said it.
[gentle music continues]
It was his look.
- What happened? After that?
- [phone vibrating]
[music stops]
To be continued.
Who this?
Yo, Xhésus.
[whispers] Give me the phone after you.
Yeah, all clear. We made it safely.
- We're waiting for you.
- Could you pass me that?
[snapping]
At 2:00 p.m.
Okay. Okay.
- Could you hand me the phone?
- [line disconnects]
You seriously hung up?
I said pass me the phone!
What's your problem?
Damn it!
[line ringing]
- [automated voice] Your call has been--
- Fuck! I'm gonna kill him!
[exhales]
DUCOS PENITENTIARY
- [dark music playing]
- [door buzzing]
[Fabrice] Aren't you gonna sit down?
What happened? Are you sick?
[exhales weakly]
- [Fabrice] No way, brother.
- [crying softly]
We'll make him pay. I promise.
I'll take the kids in gladly.
But for the two eldest, I have no space.
Auntie, cut the bullshit.
The floor is half empty.
Okay, children,
hop up to each of your rooms.
I prepared the beds.
Head up.
Here.
Régine…
they'll place Cass and Léo with strangers.
I'm also a stranger, apparently.
You made that clear to me.
That one, he broke my arm.
And that one there, he insulted me.
Do you take me for an idiot?
Wait.
Try to understand.
We lost our minds with the grief.
The children especially.
It was hard being separated.
As an apology, Auntie.
This is for this week.
I'll bring the same for next week
and the one after that.
[sucks teeth]
[bittersweet music playing]
The streets, brother.
We gotta work them too, to our advantage.
[music fading]
[Léo] Uncle, can we talk for a minute?
About what?
It's, um, a bit, um…
What? Don't be shy.
What is it?
Kylian told me
to tell you that you gotta take a trip.
Wherever you want.
[chuckles] Yeah, okay. I'll be in Miami.
Are you paying my ticket?
You're leaving tonight
and coming back when we say so.
Huh. You're all completely insane.
Get out before daylight
or your face will have a huge hole.
Or I might even kill you.
[insects chirping in background]
[floorboard creaks]
It wasn't me.
[groggily] What?
The fire wasn't me.
I would never do that.
What do you want, Nat?
There's nothing to steal here.
[angrily] Brother, I'm not a thief!
Listen to me!
I can't fucking believe this.
This is crazy.
[Kingsley] Yo! What are you looking for?
- What are you looking for?
- Bro, my ring!
I don't want it to burn
like the rest of the house!
[muttering] Besides,
that's all I have left of her.
[crying softly]
That's all I have left of her.
It's in mom's jewelry box, man.
Marv has it.
["Selling Dope 2" by Evil P playing]
["Selling Dope 2" continues playing]
Wow! Thanks a lot. My guys.
Thanks? It's our job, bro.
Why are you thanking us?
Yeah, but I mean, thank you for your work.
No problem.
Would y'all be interested
in a job for a few extra hours?
It pays very well.
[song fading]
[knock on door]
I'm here for the birthday.
Keep it open.
We're waiting on someone else.
Did all go as planned?
As you can see.
Perfect.
My guys are on site waiting for info.
The sample.
It checks out.
- [light knock on door]
- We're good.
[suspenseful music playing]
- I told you to stay in the room.
- Yes, I know. I heard.
Gentlemen.
Leave, we're good.
[Annabelle] Continue.
Don't mind me. Go ahead.
The payment will be done by installments.
First two will be done today.
Twenty-four crypto accounts
will be credited.
The key will be shared privately
by email with Milord.
Another payment will be made in cash,
which corresponds
to about 8% of the total.
The rest will be paid in cannabis.
Our shipment is en route to Mada.
So 20 kilos are for you.
In case of loss of cargo, you'll receive
the equivalent in crypto within 48 hours.
How can we be sure of that?
I'm taking 70% percent as my commission.
It's all here in detail in the group
on Telegram about this transaction.
The total is 2.3 million in euros.
Minus my commission,
that makes two million for you.
We're just missing…
the locker number for this.
And the code.
[suspenseful music continues]
[text message whooshes]
[sighs]
[phone vibrating]
Yes?
Yeah.
Okay.
We're good.
No, there's a problem.
A problem?
Just something to settle.
Xhésus? Can I talk to you real quick?
- I can hear you.
- [laughs dryly] No. This way, please.
[suspenseful music continues]
[door slams]
[shouts] What's your problem?
We fuck, then you ghost me?
- [softly] Lower your voice.
- If I feel like it!
Am I a sex doll, is that it?
You know, I see when you read my messages.
[faintly] Don't roll your eyes at me
or I swear I'll beat the shit out of you.
- Like I give a shit. I would do anything.
- [door locks]
Yo!
- What's happening there?
- What do I know?
Do you know the men out there? Trust me,
you don't want to fuck with them.
- [sucks teeth]
- [tensely] Hey man, what are you doing?
Calling the purity police.
I'm kidding.
[Annabelle faintly] This is the time
to make trouble, sweetheart.
Xhésus! Everything okay?
You're completely insane.
What's with you? Let me out!
You're not leaving.
[suspenseful music continues]
[sighs]
[music fades]
Hi.
Hello.
Are you still at the boarding school?
Yes.
You could've messaged me, all the same.
I mean…
You got nothing? Super.
Your uncle.
He made it clear
he doesn't want us to be together.
What? What did he say to you, exactly?
He said that I'm a bad match
for you, your family.
That I'm not welcome, among other things.
That fucking dumbass racist! Pathetic!
Is it even possible to be such an ass?
You should've told me.
[phone ringing]
- I gotta take it. I'm sorry.
- Come on.
What?
[Fatso] Your sister's being a pain
in the ass. She's gonna ruin everything.
A simple "yes, no, leave me alone"
would've sufficed.
What the fuck do you want?
One, an apology.
- Two, an explanation.
- [phone ringing]
Then we'll see.
Fuck! She's a pain, bro!
- A family of clowns. My life's a circus.
- [phone beeps]
[phone vibrating]
You know what?
This is pissing me the fuck off, bro.
- [bangs]
- [phone vibrating]
- They're screwing us over! Take the bag!
- [vibrating continues]
- You better stay put.
- Are you fucking crazy, bro?
- You don't want to mess with me, fucker!
- [vibrating continues]
All good. We're cool.
We are good.
Something wrong?
I'm sorry, Lily.
My life is bizarre.
Maybe your uncle has a point.
It's pointless.
Tell me what's happening. Let me in.
Forget it.
[man 1] I'd buy a real bed
for my little boy.
[man 2] I'd take my dad right away
to see snow for the first time.
[expectant music playing]
[expectant music continues]
[music fades]
[man] He's making us rob Croquet?
It's Croquet, bro!
- Yeah, and?
- You should have said that!
Go back to the cabin. Keep looking.
Yeah, but this is bold! Be for real!
It's riskier the more you drag.
Now, return to the cabin.
You can come back in, uh, two hours?
Okay, boss.
We're already splitting three ways.
What do you want? More than my share?
Screw you!
You lied big time, bro!
You owe us a bonus!
If you continue to stand there,
a big smack is the bonus you'll find.
Go, now.
That idiot Michel forget to close up?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- May I take that?
- Yes, please.
[footsteps in background]
[woman laughing]
[footsteps continues]
[glasses tinkle]
- [Croquet] Champagne?
- Please!
- [cork pops]
- [Croquet laughs]
- [Croquet] To you.
- To us.
[Croquet] Let's continue the tour.
Oh wow!
- You like it?
- Yes.
[both moaning]
[Croquet] Is the sub-prefect
in favor of the resolution?
- [woman] It's approved, yes.
- Yeah? Mmm!
[woman moaning]
[softly] Oh fuck.
[phone vibrates]
- [woman moaning]
- [phone chimes]
[moaning continues]
[Kingsley] We have to get out of here.
Hurry up.
- [both moaning]
- [thud in background]
[soft thud]
[beeping]
EMERGENCY CALL
THE POLICE RECEIVED YOUR ALERT
[Croquet] Hello, assholes.
- [gun fires]
- [groans] Fuck!
- [Croquet] That's me being nice.
- That bitch shot me!
- [indistinct police chatter on radio]
- Fuck.
- Your destiny is on its way.
- [radio chatter continues]
Take off your hoods
so I can see your dumb faces.
[radio chatter continues in background]
You'll have to shoot us all, boss,
and then explain yourself for the camera.
"Oh, Mr. Agent, these robbers
boarded all this stuff in my boat."
"Good thing I phoned before it left."
"Oh really? But how's that?"
- "Why would they do such a thing?"
- Stop your shit.
Did you manage to film everything earlier?
Post on Insta?
[Kingsley chuckles]
Could you put on shorts?
I'm sick of seeing your wood!
- [siren blaring]
- ["Chalawa" by Yaniss Odua playing]
["Chalawa" continues playing]