( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
Song Hui-na's contract ends
in three months.
Team 1, get in touch and check with her.
Any ideas for the empty Tuesday slot?
We're targeting a genre that clearly
differentiates us from our competitors.
For now, the most likely candidates
are Hwany and Jingom.
Oh, and how's Friday coming along?
Another company ran a promotion last week.
It didn't hurt us, did it?
What is she up to?
Yun Song suddenly went on hiatus, so…
If you can't control your authors,
you should have a contingency plan!
Stay sharp, or we could fall behind fast!
This goes for all of you, okay?
Keep that in mind.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
It's finally here.
-You have to go with me.
-Okay.
Look, isn't it pretty?
I can't wait to see it!
At first, it was just
a string of coincidences.
I ran into her when I least expected it.
Mere coincidence.
Next up, Seo Mi-rae. Pick your gift.
Pick a cute one!
What is it?
No way!
-Thank you.
-It looks like you!
So adorable. It looks just like you!
Of all the gifts there, you picked mine.
A coincidence.
Every day, we got on the same elevator.
I realized then…
that I was waiting
for another coincidence.
That won't work.
Okay.
Some days, I got a little greedy.
Cliché.
Not a cliché, but a classic.
One iced Americano, please.
And an iced latte with that.
-Here to buy coffee?
-Yes.
Iced latte, please.
That will be 4,500 won.
Thank you.
Some days, I tried to act
like I didn't care and give up.
Ta-da! It's this, right?
There we go.
But whenever I did, you would…
You actually made it?
…keep stepping into my side.
EPISODE 7
THE ALGORITHM OF FEELINGS
So warm.
What are you doing here?
Hello?
Mr. Park…
Why are you here?
Oh, I…
I just…
I was just getting some fresh air.
I was just about to head inside.
Then let's go.
No, I'm good. I can go by myself.
You're tipsy.
I'm really fine though…
Back there,
you said, "You actually made it."
What did you mean by that?
It was probably the alcohol. I'm sorry.
Did you mistake me for someone else?
No. It's not like that.
But weren't you drinking with the others?
Why did you come out here?
I just thought
I might get some fresh air too.
Is your relationship going well?
Yes.
Glad to hear it.
This is my room.
Okay.
Good night.
Kyeong-nam, where are you?
Why aren't you coming back?
Dong-min's totally hammered right now.
It's hilarious!
Hye-bin's more drunk than I am.
Did you go back to your room?
You're coming back, right?
I'm tired, so I'm going to sleep now.
Have fun, everyone.
Did Mi-rae pass out with Yun Song
after taking her back?
Yeah. I guess I was really tired.
Have fun, guys.
She's always lying.
Ms. Yun, I just got us a taxi.
Time for you to go to your room
and go to bed. Okay?
-Give me your arm.
-Let me go!
Hey, why won't you ever date anyone?
You had a boyfriend
back when you used to work with me.
You haven't met anyone
since you broke up with him, huh?
Why are you bringing that up now?
Besides, how am I supposed to date anyone
when you're always giving me a hard time?
If no one likes you, you should at least
have a crush on someone.
I'll handle that myself, okay?
The taxi's here. Let's go.
I'm going!
I have two cats at home.
They're super adorable.
I think I'll step outside for a bit.
Huh?
Don't take too long.
The person you are calling
is not available. Please leave a message…
CHOI DONG-MIN
Hello?
Kyeong-nam. Where are you, man?
Hwany is looking for you.
I stepped outside and…
Come back already.
Come on, man. Where are you?
Hey, where's Mi-rae?
Huh?
Mi-rae, where are you?
Ms. Seo's not with you?
She told Hye-bin that she left the hotel,
but she didn't come here.
Where's she gone this time?
Hurry back!
Why do I keep getting my hopes up?
I shouldn't be happy
that she doesn't have a boyfriend.
Is your relationship going well?
Yes.
She's lying to me
about having a boyfriend.
Glad to hear it.
Think about what that means.
It's about time I accepted it.
Be right there.
Ms. Yun.
Let's go.
What?
Ms. Yun!
We didn't even have breakfast.
Why are you in such a hurry?
Breakfast? Who needs breakfast?
You did drink too much last night--
Stop talking about last night!
What? Did something happen last night?
I knew it. It was just a dream, wasn't it?
You received an award yesterday,
and then we went for a drink…
Oh, then you told Hwany--
Stop!
What am I going to do now? Keep up.
Oh, right.
Did you remember
to call your boyfriend back?
What?
I didn't believe you at first,
but he was gentle, with a great voice.
How did you know about…
While you were passed out last night,
I answered a call from your boyfriend.
Hey!
-Why the hell would you do that?
-What?
The phone kept ringing, so I figured
someone must be very worried--
You're really annoying!
Ms. Yun!
What's her problem?
Kyeong-nam!
Man, I'm dying here.
Let's go and get some gukbap.
-And the others?
-Getting coffee.
Here. Coffee!
Mr. Park, your coffee.
Thank you.
Hot coffee for me.
Where's Mi-rae?
She and Ms. Yun left early.
Hangover cure, everyone?
-Sounds good.
-Let's go.
Yeah.
Hey, why did you leave me so early
last night?
God, you reek of alcohol.
Don't be like that, partner.
Get away from me.
Kyeong-nam, why didn't you come back?
Don't be such a stranger!
Sure enough, there's no place like home.
DONG-MIN SENT 10 PHOTOS
Looks like they had fun.
-Hello?
-Did you get home safely yesterday?
I did.
I felt bad about
not being able to go yesterday.
It's okay.
I was surprised to get a call from you.
I thought if I saw your face,
it'd be hard for me to leave.
But I guess you weren't that sad.
What do you mean? Are you going somewhere?
Let's talk in person.
Right now?
I'll be waiting.
What was that? What's going on?
You're here early.
Would you like a drink?
No.
Okay, then.
So where are you going?
I've been here way too long.
That wasn't the plan,
but then I met a certain someone here.
It's time for me to move on.
Where will you be going?
Nothing's decided yet.
I'll see where the road takes me.
Then will you be going by yourself?
Will you go with me?
We can travel together,
go sightseeing, and try delicious food.
I suppose you could chalk it up
to my profession,
but the moment I heard those words,
I realized.
I want to go with you.
My journey with Gu Yeong-il
was only just beginning.
It'll be ready in a bit.
-It looks good.
-Let's eat.
Like this. Hang on.
How is it?
Nice and cool, huh?
Come with me.
What are you doing here?
Why are you here?
Why does that keep happening?
Seo Mi-rae.
Ms. Seo.
Right now…
What is it?
Why do you do that?
…who am I with?
What was that?
Why can't I separate the two?
This isn't how it's supposed to be.
I just got home. See you all tomorrow.
Hello.
Hi.
Our company really made waves this time.
Am I right?
But compared to the major platforms,
we still have a long way to go.
You know that, right?
Let's stay focused
on both artistic quality and public appeal
and work toward winning
another award next year. Okay?
On that note,
I'd like to add that yesterday…
He might be avoiding me. Fair enough.
-Aren't we all blessed with work!
-I know, right?
I feel bad for Mr. Park.
You've already got so much on your plate.
I know.
It's still a good thing.
I'll take things one at a time.
Anyway, are you doing okay?
That event looks like a lot of work.
It is. That's why you should help me out.
I'd be happy to.
We're not even on the same team,
so it's totally understandable.
He's Park Kyeong-nam, after all.
Oh, right.
Let's pick this up when we get there.
Okay.
I'm going to have some makgeolli.
You know I don't drink.
-Come on. That's not fair.
-Come on.
-Yeah, drink with us.
-Damn it!
You're no fun.
Wait a minute.
Why am I avoiding him?
Can't we just have dinner tomorrow?
It's cold today.
I'll be there within 30 minutes.
Wait there. I think I took the wrong turn.
Hey, come on… Let me…
Seriously?
Hey, just let me in!
I'll wait for you at the café.
Hello, Ms. Seo.
Hello. What brings you here?
I'm here for a meeting with Kyeong-nam.
Your latte is ready.
Damn it.
Yes. It's just like Park Kyeong-nam said.
I'm not the one who got rejected.
I don't have to keep this up.
Be confident.
Stand tall.
And smile.
What? Too pretty to handle?
Are you okay? That was really loud.
I'm totally fine.
It was just loud, that's all.
Code red. Where are you?
I'm gonna wait outside.
How come?
I'll be at least another 20 minutes.
Hey, it's freezing outside.
Just stay there.
I'll be there soon.
Are you leaving?
Oh, I just need to use the restroom.
I'm worried about her.
What is this?
When did this show up?
What am I gonna do?
Goodbye.
Put some ointment on that, okay?
She's so scatterbrained.
She's going to hit her head again soon.
Where were we?
Hold on a second.
Look alike much?
I'm so sorry.
I think I've turned my blinker on
a hundred times on my way here.
Hey!
What happened there?
Did you get into a fight?
No.
-Hey, let's just get out of here. Hurry!
-Okay.
Goddamn it,
that was freaking embarrassing!
Hey, come on. Let's go.
Okay.
-Go!
-Okay.
Here.
Thanks.
Hey, just laugh out loud.
Hold up.
You got hit pretty hard.
Just how were you walking?
Hey. If you hadn't brought your car
and ended up being late…
Forget it.
I was only trying to let you ride along
in comfort on this cold day.
How are you even free today?
No more blind dates?
Huh?
I'm just taking a break.
How come?
I don't know.
I just think it's a waste of time.
Someone's a copycat.
I mean, I get dolled up
early in the morning
just to see a guy I don't even like,
acting all cute and polite.
Then I get home, wash off my makeup,
and feel so pathetic.
"Am I wasting my peak years?"
That's how it makes me feel.
Could there be something more fun
than dating in the world,
and I'm the only one
who doesn't know about it?
Hey, starting now,
you should look into that.
Nope. I don't think
there's anything more fun than dating.
It's just that it's so damn hard
to find a guy I like!
Are you talking to yourself?
Why ask if you had an answer?
Anyway, think about
how you're going to deal with that.
You can't go to work like that.
Perfect. It's just perfect.
You can't tell at all.
Really?
Seriously? I think it's pretty obvious.
Should I just cut my bangs?
Don't you know that 97% of women
who get bangs regret it right away?
As soon as you get them, it becomes
your goal to grow your hair out again.
You'll thank me later.
You got a haircut? It looks good on you.
-Very nice.
-Thank you.
It suits you well.
-Oh my God!
-Wow.
What's going on?
Oh, is it a wig?
Does it show?
A little from up close.
What happened?
Are you going for a new look?
Huh?
No, it's not like that.
I just felt
like changing things up a little.
Hello.
What do we have here?
A sudden change in hairstyle?
God, so embarrassing.
You crazy bitch…
I honestly wasn't going to bring this up.
-What?
-Are you not over me yet?
You crazy bitch!
Ms. Yun.
-Are you okay?
-What do you mean?
You've been having these random outbursts
for the last few days,
which is a little strange.
Huh?
You were the one who secretly left snacks
in front of my room.
Hold it right there. That was…
-Those were…
-What?
Those were meant for So-yeong!
So-yeong, just go. Get out.
I'm really struggling right now. Go.
Okay.
Are you kidding me?
I'll give you just ten more minutes.
What?
God, it's cold.
Come on. Don't do this to me!
Just 30 more minutes.
Seriously?
It's always 30 minutes with her.
Cold!
Oh God…
I was cold too.
This was the only heater we had.
Oh, but…
You said you were cold too.
Let's share it.
How's that bump from yesterday?
Oh, it's gone down a lot.
That's a relief.
Dong-min said you guys came back to Seoul
later than usual on Sunday.
I guess you had a lot of fun.
Yes, well,
we saw the ocean and had some good food.
We just…
Yeah.
I saw the pictures,
and I was really jealous.
Ms. Yun wanted to come back early,
so I had to eat ramyeon at the airport.
Then did you
want to stay longer?
Well…
Yes, I wanted to stay
and have good food as well.
Next time,
I plan on staying a little longer.
I see.
UPLOAD COMPLETE
I'll see you tomorrow.
Right.
I WANTED TO TELL YOU THAT I LIKE YOU
I wanted to tell you that I like you.
Did you get my letter?
This is kind of embarrassing.
What's this?
To be honest,
I was a little mad at you.
For not even answering me
when I asked you to come with me.
So I was just going to get over you, but
it's harder than I thought.
I miss you.
1: PLANC
2: THE MAN TO KNOW
TMTK was number one forever until today.
-Once you slip, it's all downhill.
-Deepest condolences.
-It lasted longer than expected.
-Hwany sure is no joke.
Isn't this the first time
she got dethroned?
Winning an award sure does help a lot,
doesn't it?
Don't get excited just yet.
Would it kill you to play along for once?
You saw what happened to me in Busan.
What are you doing tomorrow?
Let's get a drink.
Aren't you working?
This calls for a proper celebration.
I might lose my spot next week, after all.
Okay. I'll get back to you.
-Yeah. I had absolutely no idea.
-I know.
Hey!
-Hi, Mi-rae.
-Hi.
Are you okay?
Yup, I'm okay.
It happens all the time.
Don't worry about it too much.
Sure.
It can make it back to the top!
Definitely.
Sure, they are going to keep
trading places,
but all you need is for the author
to keep her head. Right?
Oh man.
Cheer up, it's okay. These things happen.
PlanC won a big award,
and it got a lot of press, after all.
Mr. Hwang.
So what's the game plan now?
-What?
-You do have a plan, don't you?
Oh, right. Well, I…
I'll put in the work with Ms. Yun
to give it our best shot.
Hey, Seo Mi-rae.
Do you have any idea how much
the coin sales for TMTK have fallen?
What?
Yun Song's contract is almost up.
At this rate, we'll never renew
the contract on good terms.
Her next season
would have to be the final one.
You have other authors to manage.
Stop letting her drag you around.
It's exhausting.
I'll talk to her and see what I can do.
Okay. So how?
How will you talk to her about it?
Excuse me?
So you're clueless.
Hey, you're not blameless here.
You know that?
If the producer gives it everything,
the title doesn't sink so easily.
But look at what you've done!
She's our most expensive author,
and look what happened
in just a few months.
I'm sorry, sir.
Hello?
I'm not sure.
She hasn't been lashing out as usual,
and she's being quiet.
I'll come over tomorrow.
I said go.
Your words of comfort
won't change a thing.
Just throw a fit instead.
I knew this day would come eventually.
It's a downward spiral.
That's all there is to it.
Ms. Yun.
I told you, didn't I?
I only blew up because of Choi Si-woo.
I don't have what it takes.
It's time for me to put it all down.
Sell my car, sell my home,
and sell… the building.
What's this about selling stuff?
Ms. Yun.
I'm not going to give up
on TMTK like this.
It's true that I was distracted
by some personal stuff,
and I'm sorry I couldn't give it
everything I've got.
What personal stuff?
You slacked off, didn't you?
No, it's not like that. I…
Anyway, I'm going to go all-in
from now on.
So I need you to get a grip too. Okay?
I'll do whatever it takes
to get TMTK back to number one.
Really?
So let's go eat something nice today.
My treat!
You're buying?
It's on me today!
PLANC
THE MAN TO KNOW
Stop looking. Don't you get tired of it?
Back when Mr. Cho got me and Yun Song
office spaces in the same building,
he put me in the semi-basement
and her on the top floor. Did I tell you?
A hundred times.
I've been dreaming of this moment
since then.
So stop being such a buzzkill.
Fine. Enjoy it.
But I feel bad for Ms. Seo.
Do you think she's upset?
I'm sure she is.
God, it's freezing.
Why did we come all the way out here?
How am I supposed to get home?
You never get out of your neighborhood.
They have amazing food here.
What is this place? It's freezing.
You can have whatever you want today!
Isn't that Park?
Damn it, let's go somewhere else.
Ms. Yun. Hello.
-Hello.
-Hi.
Hello.
Hwany's studio is around here, right?
Is this a celebration?
We just had a meeting. What about you?
We just came here to clear our heads.
-How are you doing?
-Not well.
-Cool.
-Damn it.
-I said let's go.
-Right. We'll be going now.
Annoying prick.
Hell, we should have left before they did.
Ms. Yun!
I'm sorry I'm late.
We're going somewhere else.
-What? Where?
-Let's go.
Wait!
Wait a second.
-Let me--
-No, I insist.
Have some of this.
-Thank you.
-No problem.
What the heck is wrong with him?
Hey, we'll be leaving soon. Keep it on.
Man, such an eyesore.
Oh, we're leaving soon?
I'll just use the bathroom, then.
Sure.
Excuse me.
Can you not ruin the mood?
You're making her walk on eggshells!
Stop picking a fight.
I'll just take So-yeong and leave.
Hey, that's just low. You can't do that.
Why can't I do that?
What will you offer to make us stay?
You going on hiatus?
-Hiatus?
-Yeah!
Sure. Yeah, I would--
-Hey.
-What?
Don't be so difficult.
We're negotiating as authors here.
Ms. Yun.
I'll do whatever you want.
Just don't take So-yeong.
-Come on.
-Did you hear that?
Please stop.
Stop what?
You said we should do whatever it takes.
So when are we leaving?
What? We're not.
What?
The food here is good. You should eat up.
-It's hot in here. Take off your coat.
-You should.
Raise our glasses?
-Yes!
-All right.
Good stuff.
-Cheers!
Goodness.
There. Let's drink hard.
Yeah, drink away.
-Let's go!
Drink milk in the morning…
Milk!
She drinks milk.
Oh, really?
To like someone…
Forward, into the heart of the enemy!
It's here.
…means coming up with excuses…
Yes?
Would you like to borrow this?
You can take your time returning it.
-Oh, if you don't mind…
-Okay.
…to spend more time together.
So, So-yeong, this Christmas…
Chris…
Do you have plans for Christmas?
Well, I guess I'll be watching anime
and movies at home.
In that case--
Sheesh, nowadays,
the younger ones
are living duller lives than us.
And your life is such a barrel of laughs?
Have you got plans for Christmas?
Hey, didn't I say last time
that I have a boyfriend?
I told you.
Right. So you said.
You don't believe me, do you?
Seo here even talked to my boyfriend
on the phone.
-Right?
-Yes.
Wait, really?
Yes.
He seemed to really like her.
How do you find the time to meet him?
You're always working.
Huh?
You know, I just
make do with what little time I can spare.
Anyway, so am I the only one here
dating someone?
What's wrong with all of you?
You're in your prime.
Whatever.
I'm jealous. So jealous.
I think I'll just have more snacks.
Damn it. It slipped my mind.
We're out of snacks.
We're also out of booze.
Go get some more liquor.
I…
I'm sorry I lied to you.
Lied to me about what?
Well…
You know,
how I told you that I had a boyfriend.
I didn't mean to lie to you,
but I'd never been in that situation
before, so I was panicking a little.
I'm sorry too.
What?
I should've known bringing up my feelings
like that would make you uncomfortable,
but I only thought of myself.
Thank you for saying that.
To be honest, recently,
it has been bothering me a bit.
I kept
thinking about how you said you were upset
before we left for Busan.
I'm not upset anymore.
Really?
That's good.
Ms. Seo.
Yes?
Now…
is it official
that you don't have a boyfriend?
Can I act like I'm also in the know?
Yes, I guess so.
From now on…
can I do as I please?
Subtitle translation by: Daham Yoon