(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
Yingge courtyard
I used to want to leave here day and night
I never thought that one day I would come back to remember you
follow me
what are you looking for
This piece of jade
My grandmother left it to my mother
It was passed down to me before my mother passed away.
Back then we were in Yingge Courtyard
I just want to give it to you
But I don’t know what you think of me
So I haven’t been able to send it out.
The situation was critical when we left the courtyard
I can't take this piece of jade away either.
Now we can come back here again
Maybe there is some secret arrangement
Achu
Can we forget the past?
back together
I already expected that you wouldn't accept this piece of jade
I did too many wrong things
already lost you
Just holding a trace of fantasy
Want one last try
Yan Xun
Go through the woods ahead
It’s the southernmost part of Yanbei
To the west are Ximeng and Bian Tang
To the east is Dayong
We can go through Dayong to the south
You can also stay in a nearby village
This is near Parle
Transportation is also convenient
If we get tired of living here in the future
You can also change places at any time
Do you remember Yunzhou?
You are talking about Yunzhou next to Bian Tang
right
That's not far from here
When we returned to Yanbei from Biantang,
passed there
I heard from the merchants there that
They are located in Dayong
The junction of Yanbei, Bian and Tang Dynasties
It's a no-nonsense zone
But business and trade are also developed
You can sell the silk brocades from Bian and Tang Dynasties to Dayong
Or you can use Yanbei’s horse jade
Sold to Bian Tang
do anything
Everyone can live peacefully
good
listen to you
let's go there
Have you heard about it?
The world is going to be in chaos
Our envoy from Bian Tang
Killed in Dayong
Forget it
More than just our messenger
I heard that Yan Xun, the king of Yanbei,
And that Chu Qiao is trapped in Dayong
I don’t know if I’m alive or dead yet.
You two, stop talking nonsense.
Our king is still in Yandu
I just killed Lan Chuan a while ago
With the two rebels from Helian?
What nonsense
How would you know that you do business here every day?
We just came out of Yandu
During those days, soldiers and horses came and went on the streets.
There is only one female general in charge
I have never seen your King Yan appear at all.
That's not being trapped in Dayong
What is it again
that is
That can't be nonsense
Cheng Yuan, stop drinking tea.
Walk
If you don’t drink, don’t drink.
Go, go, go
No one comes to this shitty place
I bought this in a nearby town
How many days will it take you to go to Dayong?
Tired of traveling and traveling
I prepared some more dry food for you
Helian
I know
in your heart
Yan Xun is very important
If you don't save him
We can't live in peace either
What's more, he is the king of Yanbei
If something happens to him
Yanbei will definitely be in chaos
My Helian tribe
It is also one of the thirteen tribes in Yanbei
Under the crowd
An egg is complete
You and I both understand this.
But you have to promise me
no matter what happens
You must come back safely
I will always wait for you
Helian
I promise you
Wait until I find Yan Xun
I will return safely
Let’s go to Yunzhou
go wherever you want
Live a life just the two of us
Where is this place?
What is hidden under the white cloth?
I heard it’s a newly built Faceless Temple
Kneel down quickly. This is the Imperial Master.
contract with blood
Use fire as a medium
Faceless God
Hear my call
Punish evil and impiety, destroy disrespect
last night
The faceless god descends before me
Give three sacred prophecies
When the three prophecies are fulfilled one by one
She will come to the world in person
Save all people from suffering
What's the meaning
The Faceless God's first prophecy
That is to punish four sinners
Use their blood to wash away the filth of the world
To punish the sinners
What does that mean?
Is someone going to die?
I heard something happened to the head of the Mu He family.
The young master is in a hurry to come back for the funeral.
Isn't that General Meng's cousin?
Could it be that something happened to General Meng?
four gate valves
Something happened between the two families
and General Meng, who commanded the Southwest General Army.
Today’s military strength in the southwest
All have been handed in
In the hands of the Zhuge family and the Mu family
Among the four gate valves
Only the Mu family is Zhao Che's confidant
Both the Mu He family and the Wei family are from the Zhao Yang faction.
General Meng is a member of Emperor Yong
Zhao Che wants to use the Faceless God Cult
eradicate dissidents
It seems like this
Emperor Yong will soon become Zhao Che's puppet
One more thing
What
In the Prophecy of the Faceless God
Four people are going to die
Now
One more to go
It's Xing Le
Half of Dayong's foreign troops are in his hands
If Zhao Che wants to control Dayong
I'll definitely take action against him
We have to save Xing Le
Achu
You know I have a blood feud with Dayong
If they fight like a snipe and a clam
Of course I am willing to watch them kill themselves
Are you sure you want to mind this business?
Yan Xun
This is definitely not a trivial matter
When I promised you to leave Dayong
It's because you told me
Yanbei
He is an independent and fair Yanbei
But it was ruined by Emperor Yong
now
Zhuge Yue and I have gone through a lot of hardships
Create a place like this
But still not tolerated by the world
There is never any peace of mind
If Dayong's serious illness cannot be cured,
This world
will never be okay
Leave this matter to me
Wait for my news
Congratulations to Prince Jing
The four noble families in Zhenhuang City
The Mu He family and the Wei family have all collapsed
General Meng, who was in charge of the southwest military power, also died suddenly.
The four gate valves of Dayong in the future
Prince Jing’s family is the only one left.
That's also thanks to His Highness the Crown Prince's blessing.
Just don't know
His Royal Highness the Crown Prince promised
The matter of military power in the Southwest
Aoyamain’s spy will be put into action tonight
General Xing Le died
Military power in the southwest
I can leave it in your hands, Prince Jing.
Thank you very much Mr. Zhuge.
Come out
I know it's you
Now the whole city is looking for you
You follow me rashly
Aren't you afraid that I will order you to besieged and suppressed again?
I know
Wei Guang and Mu Helie are dead
The power of the Wei family and the Mu He family will inevitably weaken.
The Four Gates of Zhenhuang City
Only the Zhuge family and the Mu family were left.
Zhuge Yue
What are your plans?
we can do it together
do you think
What plan can I have
We've been through so many things together
you can't lie to me
Back then, in the smoky Zhuge Mansion,
You pretend to be Aoyamain
The ruthless Fourth Young Master
But we are still in Zhenhuang City, where people cannibalize people
saved me
Also saved those slaves like me
i believe
You won't become the one who helps others do evil.
A person who does not distinguish between good and evil
That self-righteous one
The Fourth Young Master who thinks he can help the world
already dead
Now there are only powerful ministers of Yong Dynasty
Zhuge Yue, the head of Qingshan Academy
If you don't leave again
Wait for the spies from Aoyamain to arrive
You can't leave
Zhuge Yue
Lord Mu
Send so many Mu guards to follow me late at night
What's the purpose?
General Zhuge laughed.
I'm just anxious
I want to catch this slave girl to share His Majesty’s worries.
Unexpectedly, General Zhuge happened to be there too
In this case
How about General Zhuge condescending to give in?
let me kill her
Let's go together to ask for the reward from His Highness the Crown Prince.
General Mu
This is all due to you alone
How am I embarrassed to share
General Mu, please take action
Let's help His Royal Highness share his worries and solve his problems.
Thanks to General Zhuge for making it possible
kill
缳缳
Kill Chu Qiao
I'm heavily rewarded
Since General Mu is not afraid of death
I will make it happen for you
let them go
Everyone, step back
Thank you for saving me today
No need
I owe you this
General Chu
I want to cooperate with you
Cooperation is possible
But I won't eat it again
Anything you gave me
let me go let me go
General Xing
Thank you, General Chu, for coming to the rescue.
What happened?
He insisted
I am not Zhao Che’s ally
Said he didn’t know any of Zhao Che’s plans
Press again
just started yelling
Acting crazy and acting stupid
You knocked him unconscious
He bounces around on his own
dizzy
They've gone back and forth
General Xing Le was rescued
Whereabouts unknown
Mu Shen
Was also kidnapped by Chu Qiao
Just one soldier and one cannon
No need to be sorry
you promised me before
We won’t let Chu Qiao hinder our actions
But now
This chess game is missing this pawn and one cannon
It became a dead end
Aoyama-in is already in the city
Searching for Chu Qiao and Yan Xun
Spies are also posted at every city gate.
As long as they make the slightest move
They will never escape the eyes of Aoyamain
Kameng in the Temple of the Faceless
second prophecy announced
Talking about the Faceless God
will bring down a sinful land
wash away their sins with the flood
Since she said that
It’s been raining heavily in Ximeng
Floods occurred in many mountains
The climate in Ximeng is already extreme
The turn of summer and autumn in previous years
It’s also the time when it rains the most
The heavy rain at this time continued
Nothing strange at all
But I'm afraid
Only the local people in Ximeng know about it
Everyone else will believe it
It's the prophecy of Kammon
But what good can this prophecy do to Zhao Che?
Is it just to make the Faceless God more convincing?
I'm afraid it's not just that
Zhao Che is likely to take the next step
We are going to take action against Ximeng
His Royal Highness the Crown Prince
I know that I served the Thirteenth Prince
to gain your trust
Must prove yourself first
And now
I've proven it to you with two prophecies
first prophecy
Eliminate those who oppose you in the DPRK
before the second prophecy
I have observed the sky
Heavy rains in Ximeng will last for half a month
Just in fulfillment of the condemned land
This was done well
Tomorrow Dayong's army will set off from Zhenhuang
Go to Ximeng
I want to do it in the name of the faceless god
Take back Western Alliance
Once Ximeng's Wujin Mine
Fall into your control, Your Highness
Don’t say it’s Dayong
The situation in all directions will be in the hands of His Highness
General Meng is dead
Military power in the southwest
From now on, it will be handed over to Prince Jing to take over.
This time we sent troops to the Western Alliance
It’s up to the prince to plan the strategy
minister
Take orders
There was a fierce battle on the battlefield
This leg of the minister
It's a disability that was left behind to save the driver.
Don't want to but because of this
Abandoned by His Majesty like worn-out shoes
In these years, ministers should not worry about state affairs
Sitting for years
now
His Highness entrusted him with an important task
I am filled with emotion
Although I am old
Danchen's mansion
They are all people who are willing to serve His Highness.
Please rest assured, Your Highness
I will live up to my trust
Look at the direction
Probably leaving the city
You were right
Now Zhao Che is taking advantage of the rain
Proclaim to the world that it was the Western Alliance that angered the Faceless God
He is sending troops now
It became in the name of the Faceless God
To take over Western Alliance
Previously Zhuge Muqing
There were 20,000 Yong troops brought outside the Ximeng Pass.
No retreat yet
Coupled with the newly mobilized troops in the past few days,
I'm worried
He Xiao and the others can't hold on
you don't have to worry
I will set off immediately to return to Yanbei to mobilize troops.
Support West Alliance
good
King of Yanbei
Thank you for your help that day
Now Zhenhuang City has been blocked
You take this token and go through the southeast gate.
The guard at the southeast gate is my confidant
When he sees the token, he will let you go
Thank you, General Xing
I will return to Yanbei as soon as possible to prepare for counterattack
Now Zhao Che has gone crazy
The prophecy of Kammon has been spoken twice
It will only be more severe next time
You and Ning Ning stay here
Must be more careful
I represent the Faceless God
Announcing the third prophecy
on this land
The last person chosen by the Faceless God
Will be baptized by heavenly fire
in the ashes of heavenly fire
The next person chosen by the Faceless God
About to come to this world
Let's go, let's go
where are you going
Walk
you
stop him
Zhuge Yue
you told me
As long as I take good care of Ah Chu
you will come back
Sir, King Yan is injured
Immediately capture the King of Yanbei
The ice and snow arrows hurt the bones
Bear with it
Cheng Yuan
You quickly take the token of the Black Hawk Army with you.
Immediately return to Yanbei to mobilize troops to support the Western Alliance
Zhao Che's soldiers and horses
Already on the way to Ximeng
Go quickly
I'll go find you some water
Cheng Yuan
Come
Zhao Che captured the Western League
The next target is Yanbei
You must be like a helper
Fully support Achu in fighting Dayong
This is not just for Achu
It’s for the sake of Yanbei’s safety
I'll carry you and go with me
no
I have difficulty moving now
It's not safe for you to take me with you
Everyone outside is from Aoyama-in
critical situation
You go first
Nothing will happen to me alone
I know you like Princess Helian
I will give you a marriage after being orphaned
Just back to the foot of the mountain
Your Majesty
before
You don’t understand Gu’s feelings for Ah Chu
Now
You should be able to understand
Cheng Yuan
You have had no home since you were a child
You once said to me
Yanbei Military Camp is your home
over the years
I always hope
you can find someone you love
have a real home
Now it’s finally okay to be alone
Don't worry
Your Majesty
Sir, there are blood stains here
Search along this forest
Be sure to bring the person back to me
yes
Walk
Cheng Yuan, go quickly
Go quickly
Zhuge Yue and I have been fighting for so many years
I can't kill him
He can't kill me either
Cheng Yuan
I order you to go quickly
Your Majesty
This is the king's order
yes
Sorry, Your Majesty
these years
You and I are kings and ministers
Also brothers
Forgive me as an elder brother
I won't listen to you again this time
It's Yan Xun
catch him
Yan Xun
Zhuge Yue
you lose
we were fooled
King Yan must be nearby
Keep searching for me
yes
Wait
I've searched
There is a cliff over there
There's blood on it
Yan Xun was hit by two arrows in his leg
He must have rolled off the cliff and been shattered to pieces.
Walk
take the body away
His Royal Highness Qiyu
We also went to the mountain col on the other side.
Indeed, no trace of King Yan was found.
Walk
Cheng Yuan
you can't die
You can't die without Gu's orders
i want you back
Cheng Yuan
The minister and the king went to Yanbei
but one body
Life and death, honor and disgrace, the blue sky and the underworld
whenever
The minister and the king advance and retreat together
Don’t let me see you from now on
I have been in the army since I was a child
Yanbei Military Camp is my home
The Black Hawk Army and the King are my relatives
Yanbei is so big
I don't know where to go
Cheng Yuan
I'll take you home
red eagle
Did Cheng Yuan ask you to come?
Your Majesty
Red Eagle knows the way back to Yanbei
it will take you home
Take good care of Helianling
Your Highness, please wait.
Chu Qiao is here to surrender
The third prophecy to be announced by Carmon
It's the Faceless Gods who want to use the holy fire
Burn the current Chosen One to death
Your Majesty
What did you say
It's not suitable for us to meet again
Please Lord Zhuge
self-respect