( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(Lee Na Young)
(Jung Eun Chae)
(Lee Chung Ah)
(Honour)
(Supported by the Culture Ministry and Korea's Creative Content Agency)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and animals were filmed under production guidelines.)
(Thank you, Mom, for killing my Dad.)
(Han Min Seo)
(The late Lee Ga On)
(Baby of the Day: 189 days left)
(Uninstall this app?)
(Okay)
(Episode 10)
They've assigned the judges for the trial.
The presiding judge is Judge Lee Hyeong Il.
Judge Lee Hyeong Il?
He's known to be sympathetic to self-defence claims.
- This is a godsend for us. - Thanks, Jeong Woo.
For taking on Ra Young's case.
Hey, save your thanks for after we win the self-defence claim.
Thanks to you guys, I might finally be a star lawyer.
She's refusing to come out again today?
Yes.
It's so hard to get a meeting with Yoon Ra Young.
What is she trying to pull?
I'm sorry, but if the inmate refuses, we can't force her.
Look, are you sure she's even in there and okay?
I really don't get it.
I have to see for myself.
- Hyun Jin, stop. - It's strange.
Her behaviour is understandable. You know that.
I still haven't even heard her voice.
Not a single call. And she's refusing every visit.
Why is she being like this? Seriously.
Hold on.
She asked me to give you this.
(Find Han Min Seo.)
Goodness. It's a Gyeomjae.
I figured you'd want it on display, not locked away in a vault.
A sentiment I'm sure both you and the artist would share.
Pack it up again. We're sending it back.
I already told you, didn't I?
Your request is out of the question.
I don't care what you bring me. My answer is no.
How can you ask me to defend a murderer?
She wasn't murdering. She was saving people.
Six people about to be killed by some psycho with a gun.
Just keep fanning the flames,
be it on the news or a show, by pushing the self-defence angle.
Just keep bringing it to the public's attention.
That's well within your power, isn't it?
I...
never liked the look in your eyes from the beginning.
I only allowed the marriage because our families insisted,
but you've always been stubborn, never willing to yield.
Look at you now.
You have no intention of begging, "Please help me."
So you brought a fancy gift, didn't you?
Please help me.
I'm begging you.
Seeing you go to such lengths...
Fine. I'll speak with In Jun's family on his mother's side.
Take this to the vault.
And issue a press release with the donation details.
Yes, Director.
(Attorney Yoon Ra Young)
How was meeting your jobless mother-in-law?
The old fox.
And to think she was the one so desperate for me to marry her son.
So, is she going to help?
She's wanted it since my wedding. Of course she took it.
Did you get to see Ra Young?
This is driving me crazy.
The judge assignment is in our favour,
and Su Eun and everyone at the villa that day agreed to testify.
So why on earth is she acting like this?
Tell me about it.
This is all she sent? Again?
She won't even show her face to us,
so why is she so obsessed with finding Han Min Seo?
The Connect In video leak scandal broke three weeks ago.
Amid mounting criticism of the slow Joint Investigation HQ probe,
the political fallout has been immense.
The Future Strategy Minister and Representative Hong Jin Ki...
of the ruling party, who were central to the scandal,
ultimately resigned due to intense public backlash.
Thank you, Mom, for killing Dad.
Did you find anything?
After looking into it,
the only bodies found at the time were those of her adoptive parents.
The police concluded the child's body was lost,
so she was pronounced dead.
So you mean the child...
was never found?
Which means she might still be alive.
And the adoptive parents...
had a record of being investigated for habitual child abuse.
Neighbours made several reports,
so an investigation had already begun when it happened.
I was so hungry, so I stole my neighbour's milk.
When I was six.
I hadn't eaten in three days.
But at least when I called her "Mom," she'd smile and answer me.
Even when she hit me and cursed me out,
she would turn right around and call me her daughter again.
Unless I can make them suffer exactly what they did to me... No.
Unless I can make them suffer even more,
none of it means anything to me.
Shouldn't we be popping champagne instead of drinking whiskey?
The Prime actually won the Smart City bid.
Unfortunately, it's still too soon for that.
Everyone backing the competition is gone.
The Minister of Future Strategy quit.
The ruling party representative and the mayor of Mujin were all fired.
It's a good thing. It means the system's working at last.
The videos were what delivered the final blow,
but it's ironic that it came from the late Prosecutor Park.
About the videos...
Park Je Yeol wasn't the one who leaked it.
I heard it myself.
Han Min Seo was the one who posted the videos?
Not you?
I didn't even know the darn thing existed.
So who could it be?
Who convinced her to leak the videos at the perfect moment,
just to frame Park Je Yeol for it?
Videos that Park Je Yeol himself didn't even know existed.
Be careful of Baek Tae Joo.
He has us both you and me...
in the palm of his hand.
The girl Park Je Yeol mentioned...
I'm looking for Han Min Seo.
Once I find her, I'm sure I'll figure it out...
who's really behind all of this.
(The late Park Je Yeol)
I came to give this back.
Thank you.
Thanks to this, I finally know for sure...
what we are to each other.
(The late Park Je Yeol)
(Father: Park Je Yeol)
(The probability of paternity is 99.99 percent or higher.)
Too bad.
Your expression when you realised what you did to your own child...
I wanted to see it so badly.
I won't say rest in peace.
Because I know you're in the fiery pit anyway.
How do you feel?
Do you feel a sense of closure now?
Would you like to shower first?
That won't be necessary.
- Then... - No, really. I mean it.
I just came here to get some rest.
Then why did you ask me to come here?
Like when you're walking down the street and find a bill,
or winning a raffle.
You know, a little stroke of luck?
Everyone needs that, don't they?
Just relax. Make yourself comfortable.
To be honest, I didn't believe you at first.
I've never met any decent adults.
Do you believe me now?
I just thought...
maybe I was due for two hours of good luck.
That's about it.
Maybe there's more good fortune waiting for you.
Want me to help?
I think I can find them.
The people who've made your life so difficult.
(Notice of full adoption)
(Mother Yoon Ra Young consents.)
(Yoon Ra Young)
What do you think? Do you like my gift?
Is this woman really...
- my mother? - Yes.
But...
I don't know what to do now.
If I were you,
I'd make them pay for everything.
To the devils who used me like a thing and trampled all over me,
to the monsters who left me these scars that will never heal,
and to the people who abandoned me and forced me into this life.
You have the right to judge them, don't you?
And I know just how to do it.
If you want, I can even help you.
You?
Why?
The Seo Ji Yoon list.
It was 20 years ago, so you might not know about it.
Back then, Seo Ji Yoon was a powerless, up-and-coming actress.
Unable to bear exploitation by high-ranking officials,
she took her own life.
But in the end, the guilty were never punished.
Their depraved connection became even stronger,
and protected by that connection, their twisted desires...
grew more secretive...
and more depraved.
So that's what became Connect In this time.
That's why unless we eradicate them,
no matter what new system you put in place,
nothing will ever change.
It's taken me all this time just to get here.
Thanks to the courage you gave me.
Do you regret it? Posting those videos?
How did you get those videos?
I got lucky, and they weren't.
They may've used a digital platform for a better cover-up this time,
but for me, that's like them walking right into my own backyard.
About posting the videos...
To make those people pay,
that really was the only way, wasn't it?
Ultimately, there are only two meaningful outcomes.
Either you achieve your objective,
or you fail.
We achieved the outcome we wanted.
And I think you should leave a little earlier than we planned.
It's one of the accounts registered with Han Min Seo's phone number.
Looks like a burner account. There's nothing on it.
Did you get any login history?
They said she hasn't logged in since she disappeared.
And...
I think we should end things.
- Hyun Jin... - I should've spoken sooner. Sorry.
With everything going on, I haven't had a clear head.
I'll agree to whatever terms you want.
If this is...
about the baby...
You know very well that's not the problem.
The point is, I crossed a line.
And there's no going back.
Even if I say I'm okay with it, that I don't care...
I'm not okay with it.
I should get going now.
Just let me know when you're ready.
(CEO Seong Tae Im)
You look a little rough.
Sit.
Have you just been cooped up at home this whole time?
I told you to get out and get some air.
No, ma'am.
If you were going to feel this guilty,
why did you have the nerve to do it in the first place?
This has gone on long enough.
Now all we have to do is quietly manage the fallout.
The fallout was too big for that.
Many politicians have already lost their seats over this.
This will be a blow to Haeil moving forward.
That's exactly why we need to manage this.
Do you know what's most important right now?
Never admitting it, no matter what.
What a funny world. Nobody cares about the truth.
They just want to believe their version of the truth.
It'll be the same in court.
Not as exploitation.
We'll frame it as a consensual transaction.
Is that even considered a crime in this country?
At worst, we're looking at a suspended sentence.
Then, one by one, everyone slowly returns to their posts,
and nothing will have changed.
There will be an uproar. It might not be so easy this time.
What do you think we've been doing all this time?
For all these years.
We've been turning the law into our shield.
No. We've taught the public...
to feel powerless.
If we have a shield, that's it.
They'll get mad and rage for a little while,
but they'll forget about it soon enough.
Because they learned that no matter what they do, nothing changes.
I hear Attorney Yoon Ra Young...
may be released soon for self-defence.
We can't add fuel to the fire.
Stop Ra Young from being released.
That's what we need to do right now.
I found the place Han Min Seo was last seen.
It's Room Nine.
(Room 9)
Inmate 4211. Aren't you going to your visitation?
No.
Officer!
Officer?
(Room 9)
This is a good look for you.
Paying for your crimes and being responsible.
How long...
have you known?
(Yoon Ra Young, Han Min Seo)
Shin Jae.
(DNA results show a match.)
(The probability of parentage is 99.99 percent or higher.)
No way...
I've been thinking about it this whole time.
I wondered if you would recognise me.
They say blood calls to blood.
"Could she really not know, right to the end?"
I couldn't even bring myself to think it.
I just thought you were dead.
- So... - No, you just refused to think it.
You were probably relieved that I was dead.
Because I'm your horrible memory, Attorney.
- Min Seo. - Don't call me that.
Why did you do it?
Why bring me into this world just to abandon me in the fiery pit?
I didn't abandon you.
I...
wanted to protect you from me, from my past.
I just wanted to keep you safe.
I hoped you'd never know anything.
I wanted you to live...
completely removed from my past.
And look how that turned out.
While I was going through all of this,
where were you, Attorney?
What justice were you upholding? Who were you protecting?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, Min Seo.
For not being able to save you...
For not knowing anything...
It's all my fault.
I'm...
so sorry.
It's too late for that now.
Because I've already settled the score.
The Connect videos...
I'm the one who uploaded them.
What are you talking about?
But how?
I guess even the Almighty decided to send someone my way.
Someone to help me.
He's the one who told me...
who my birth mother was.
You won't be seeing me again.
Goodbye, Mom.
Min Seo.
Min Seo!
So, you're saying Han Min Seo...
The one in the green hoodie is Ra Young's daughter?
Looks that way.
Then what she did to me in the subway station...
Revenge.
She blames us.
That's why she came after us.
She's the one who lured Park Je Yeol to the villa too.
And Ra Young knows it all now, doesn't she?
That must be why she asked us to find her.
How much of it is our fault?
All the misery in her life.
Telling Ra Young to give up the baby back then...
I don't regret it.
Not when I thought she was dead,
and not now, knowing her life was a living fiery pit.
I still think the same way.
We had no other choice back then.
Let's just wait outside.
If she knows we're here, she'll just take off.
So who could it be?
Who convinced her to leak the videos at the perfect moment,
just to frame Park Je Yeol for it?
The pests take the bait without ever knowing it's a trap.
Did you get everything done?
- Yes. - What about your things?
I threw them all away.
I want to make a completely fresh start.
All right. Let's go, then.
Hey! You awful...
You rotten little wench.
Do you only think about yourself? Did you ever stop to think about us?
I'm sorry.
(Seoul Mujin Police Station: Park Je Yeol Murder case)
(The probability of paternity is 99.99 percent or higher.)
You knew all along, didn't you?
She didn't return to the boarding house since then.
I think she knew we were there.
- Shin Jae's looking for her, but... - Hyun Jin.
I have to get out of here.
Someone's backing Min Seo.
They knew who I was and who Min Seo was.
From the very beginning.
Since this whole thing started.
They've been manipulating her...
and treating this whole situation like their personal chessboard.
Maybe...
It's not just Min Seo. All of us...
might have been played.
I have an interesting theory for you.
I'm all ears.
I found who first told Reporter Lee about the Connect In app.
The one who handed over the VIP list.
They used anonymous encrypted mails to hide their tracks, but just once,
they left a trace of logging in from a public place.
And as luck would have it,
that location matched their publicly reported movements.
Plausible.
That person helped us at every critical juncture.
Making sure the issue would snowball.
The victim could be in danger.
I guess I'm in.
(Verification complete)
And then they dropped the bombshell at the most crucial moment.
Evidence that couldn't be obtained through legal channels.
How did that person get their hands on the video evidence?
And how on earth did they crack the password for Park Je Yeol's app?
So, have you figured it out?
There's only one possible conclusion.
Want me to take a guess?
I'm the one who made the app.
Did Park Je Yeol know...
who you were?
He probably thought I was a developer he met on the deep web.
He was a quick study when it came to shady dealings,
so it wasn't that hard.
What this app and system could be used for.
What the demand would be. He caught on to my intent quickly.
Why would you do something like this?
Because it was time to clean it all up.
I heard you had fun with two new faces...
from Connect In yesterday.
You've still got it.
Of course. I quashed the Financial Services Commission investigation,
Swap the investigation team for ours. Things will quiet down.
Who's the new guy that joined our little club?
I heard you got him to sign up for Connect In too.
There's no way that warrant is getting issued.
I can expect the bidding information by tomorrow, right?
I set aside the private expressway project...
for your district's construction company. You know that, right?
Did you hear that?
In their own little sanctuary,
they're not just satisfying their urges.
They trade power...
and cover for each other to strengthen their cartel.
Sexual desire is just...
the easiest chain that binds them.
So?
Don't you think this is enough to defeat that untouchable cartel?
You set a trap using prostitution as bait?
Think of the outcome, Shin Jae.
If this can completely clean up this rotten system,
isn't that an outcome you'd want too?
That's nonsense.
Do you even hear yourself right now?
That means you used the victims as bait.
What about the victims' pain?
You don't care what happens to them?
Come on, Shin Jae. You know.
How do you cut out a festering wound without shedding blood?
You're insane.
We've come this far. Let's be honest with each other.
Does that really matter to you?
- What did you say? - You know how it is, Shin Jae.
For the sake of the goal, the means...
aren't about what you rule out but what you choose.
That's what I liked about you.
Because at our core, we're the same.
We hold paradise in our hearts...
but are willing to go all the way to the fiery pit.
Don't be ridiculous.
I have a line.
A line that can't be crossed. A line that must never be crossed.
Then shall we put that to the test?
And see if I'm wrong?
You want to save Attorney Yoon, right?
Then come gladly all the way to the fiery pit.
What on earth is that supposed to mean?
I know how those people operate better than anyone.
They will never let Attorney Yoon out of prison.
And that includes your mother, Shin Jae.
Even if Attorney Yoon means the world to her only daughter.
If you want proof, open your mother's safe.
You'll understand why Haeil has to disappear.
What's going on? What do you mean the judge changed?
Judge Lee Hyeong Il was transferred.
- Who's the new judge? - Judge Jeong Yeong Gyu.
Why? You know him?
I do. All too well.
But the problem is...
he knows Ra Young all too well too.
Judge Jeong Yeong Gyu has a record for soliciting prostitution.
And for that, his only punishment was a three-month pay cut.
And the one who tore him to shreds for it on TV...
It was Ra Young.
(CEO Seong Tae Im)
It's 6358.
(Phone Number, User: Seo Ji Yoon)
(Call Log)
Why is this here?
This is the Seo Ji Yoon List.
Seo Ji Yoon's call log, the one prosecutors couldn't find.
So why is it in Haeil's safe?
Because I needed it more than the prosecutors did.
Haeil was the one that covered up the Seo Ji Yoon case?
Are you done playing the hero?
Then it's time you looked down at your feet.
See what you've been standing on this whole time,
and see clearly what you must endure and protect from now on.
LnJ will be dissolved at Haeil.
I've had enough of this infighting under one roof.
Besides, Ra Young won't be coming back anyway.
(Haeil Law Firm)
Mom... All this time,
what have I even been doing here?
Do you realise what this means?
You've just destroyed my entire life.
Everything I fought so hard to protect.
You've ruined it all.
(Haeil Law Firm)
What are you doing here?
What are we going to do?
Should we file a motion to have the judge recused?
Hyun Jin.
I think I was wrong.
About what?
I only fought battles I knew I could win...
and thought I was changing the world.
I was just hiding under someone's wing,
but I thought I was the one in charge.
Hey.
Did something happen?
- Hey, isn't that him? - It is. It's him.
- No way. - I guess he works here.
This is wild.
He's really handsome, though.
I guess he didn't make much money if he's working here.
I guess so.
Those glasses look good on you.
Just get to the point and leave, please.
There are a few misunderstandings between us that we need to clear up.
I think you were just being used by LnJ.
Look. In the end, who's the one who got torn to shreds?
You were. I want to compensate you for your suffering.
You said it was your dream to run a cafe like this, right?
This should be more than enough.
It's a hardware wallet.
I've made it untraceable, so don't worry.
But just to be safe, it's best to use a foreign exchange.
This is a ticket for tomorrow morning.
You want me to skip Attorney Yoon Ra Young's trial?
And of course, you'll have to drop the lawsuit.
I'm giving you a chance at a new life.
By the way,
your witness testimony during the trial will be public.
Any request for a closed hearing will be denied.
Is no one here yet?
We need them to prove self-defence. Hurry up and call them.
I can't.
How can I pressure them?
How can I force them to come?
If the court really denies our request for a closed hearing,
they'd have to publicly admit that they're victims of Connect.
How can I ask those kids to get on the witness stand?
(Consultation Room)
(Courthouse)
Are you well-prepared for the trial?
I'm sure it wasn't easy.
It certainly wasn't, thanks to you.
Ra Young and I go way back,
so I came to see how it all ends.
After all, I don't think we'll be seeing her around for a while.
If that's why you're here, then you've wasted your time.
Because you'll be seeing plenty of her.
Out in the world, after today.
I'm going to take your advice and start acting like an adult.
Weighing what I stand to gain and lose with every step I take.
(Court in Session)
Witness, you were the first to find the victim, Park Je Yeol, that day.
Please describe what happened.
(Witness Stand)
I had just stepped outside the villa to get to my car...
when I saw Park Je Yeol waiting for me with a gun.
And what did he do with that gun?
He fired a warning shot over my head,
and then started shooting indiscriminately at the villa...
where the victims were.
His intent to kill was clear.
You, in an effort to protect the other witness, Kang Shin Jae,
shielded her with your own body.
I was ten weeks pregnant then,
and I miscarried as a result of that assault.
- Oh, my... - He beat her.
What were the circumstances at the moment of the victim's death?
He aimed the gun at me and Hwang Hyun Jin...
as we lay on the ground.
If she had been a second later,
Kang Shin Jae and I would have died instantly.
Based on the witnesses' testimonies,
the defendant acted...
just before the victim was about to shoot, intending to kill.
It was the only choice available...
to save herself and the witnesses.
Yes, that's correct.
Nothing further.
The biggest flaw in this case...
is that the only witnesses are...
Hwang Hyun Jin and Kang Shin Jae, who have a special relationship...
to the defendant.
They've been friends with the defendant for 20 years,
and they're even lawyers at the same firm.
Can we really consider their testimony to be objective?
In order to save the defendant,
they may have exaggerated key facts,
or even colluded on their stories. We cannot rule out that possibility.
Counsel, do you have other witnesses to rebut the prosecution's claims?
The thing is,
the other witnesses from the scene were due in court today, but...
As you can see, the defence has no objective evidence for its claims,
nor any other witnesses.
I apologise.
I'm a little late.
Your Honour, a witness for the defence.
The other witnesses have all arrived as well.
They're in the waiting room right now.
Very well.
Bring in the first witness.
Witness, what is your relationship to the defendant, Yoon Ra Young?
I am...
a victim of the Connect In case.
And Attorney Yoon Ra Young was my legal counsel.
I know it couldn't have been easy for you to be here today.
So what made you decide to testify today?
I was told without our testimony as eyewitnesses,
it would be detrimental to her case.
(Defendant, Witness Stand)
And yet, the attorneys from LnJ...
never asked us to be here.
That is why we're here.
Very well, witness.
Please describe what you witnessed at the scene.
Thank you, witness.
So, according to your testimony,
neither you nor the other Connect In victims...
witnessed the moment Prosecutor Park was killed, then.
Attorney Yoon Ra Young moved me to a safe back room, so...
The moment the defendant struck the victim.
Did you see it or not?
I did...
not witness it.
What is he here for, then?
Your Honour.
As the witness himself has testified,
he missed the most critical moment of the incident.
A key element for self-defence is the imminence of the threat.
Contrary to the defence's claims,
at the very moment the defendant struck Prosecutor Park Je Yeol,
it's possible Prosecutor Park had stopped his attack or was subdued.
If the imminent threat had already passed,
yet the defendant proceeded to strike the victim's head,
then it is no longer self-defence but an act of aggression,
which would demonstrate a clear intent to kill.
Objection. The prosecutor...
is twisting the facts with mere speculation.
Is it merely speculation? She has a motive, does she not?
The defendant recently claimed on television...
that the victim had sexually assaulted her.
Your Honour.
The prosecutor's muddying the waters with facts irrelevant to this case.
It seems relevant to understanding the background of this case.
Counsel, is the prosecutor's statement true?
Your Honour,
may I answer the prosecutor's question myself?
Proceed, defendant.
(Prosecution)
It's true I was sexually assaulted by the victim 20 years ago.
It is also true that I have hated him so much,
I've wanted him dead.
But at the same time, to overcome what happened,
I have fought with every fiber of my being.
So that what I went through wouldn't consume the rest of my life.
Because that was the only thing I could do.
Your Honour.
My 20 years of pain is not a motive for murder.
It is the strongest proof of why I could never commit this crime.
I never had any intention of killing him.
I couldn't destroy the life I built with my own two hands.
Please do not tarnish all the years I fought desperately to survive...
by reducing it to mere revenge.
Counsel, do you have any further evidence to present?
We have nothing further, Your Honour.
Then this concludes the evidentiary hearing for this case.
Prosecutor, you may begin your closing argument.
Your Honour.
This case rests on the defendant's one-sided, emotional appeals...
and biased testimonies.
There is no objective evidence to support any of it.
The defendant's tragic past...
cannot be an excuse for the heinous crime of murder.
Therefore, the prosecution requests...
a 20-year sentence for the defendant.
That is all.
Very well.
This concludes the closing arguments...
in the case against Defendant Yoon Ra Young.
You know how it is, Shin Jae.
For the sake of the goal, the means...
aren't about what you rule out but what you choose.
The sentencing will be held in 3 weeks at 2pm...
here in this courtroom.
Your Honour.
Pursuant to Article 305 of the Criminal Procedure Act,
I move to reopen closing arguments.
Your Honour, a witness does not have the standing to file such a motion.
I'm aware.
This is an official defence motion. We move to reopen closing arguments.
Are there grounds for reopening the arguments?
I will offer new, objective evidence that will corroborate...
what the prosecution called "biased claims and testimony."
It's video footage recorded at the scene of the incident.
This evidence was not submitted beforehand. I object.
Your Honour.
This is a public trial, and the entire nation is watching.
In the interest of the core principles of a fair trial...
to guarantee the right to a defence and find the truth,
we believe this evidence must be examined.
We request the evidence be examined by playing it in court.
If it is indeed footage of what transpired at the scene,
it would be the most vital evidence to prove the charges as well.
It seems prudent to proceed with examining this evidence.
If you have issues with the video, you can argue them later. All right?
- Understood. - Counsel, present the evidence.
What do you think you're doing?
Hey, Kang Shin Jae!
You put her up to this, didn't you?
Trying to get revenge on me? Is that it?
You want to save Attorney Yoon, right?
Then come gladly all the way to the fiery pit.
If saving Ra Young is the price, then fine.
I'll go to the fiery pit.
Gladly.
This will be enough to get Attorney Yoon out.
But you're aware of what this means, aren't you?
It means that to take your hand,
I have to let go of Ra Young and Hyun Jin.
Once they find out the truth,
they will never forgive me.
(Honour)
What was that video from the trial?
Let's just go our separate ways.
This is the detonator that will blow up Haeil.
Shin Jae reported Haeil?
This isn't like Shin Jae. Something's up with her, right?
Running into the fire was my only option.
From now on, all who wronged you will pay the price.
I never could have imagined that I would lose you like this.