♪Shrugging off past burdens♪
♪Beneath the mask, who am I?♪
♪Release and find wider shores♪
♪Love's a riddle, and rain pours heavy♪
♪Crossed paths, now downward fall♪
♪From dust arises starlight's spark♪
♪Tearing through
the night's dense blockade♪
♪Heart's flame illuminates all solitude♪
♪Let time's sails drift endlessly♪
♪Through wandering exile♪
♪Breaking free from the cocoon,
I start anew♪
♪Moon as song, life as flame♪
♪Nameless heart clings fiercely♪
♪Let me♪
♪Charge toward the next raging river♪
♪Moon darts, snow falls♪
♪We tread rugged paths to reunite♪
♪Hands held tight♪
♪We forever live for love's sake♪
♪Shadow's spear burns fiercely♪
=Legend of The Female General=
That's all
for today.
Remember
to review what you've learned.
Tomorrow,
I will personally test you.
Understood.
He always wears a mask.
What's wrong with him?
You'll know.
(Huainanzi)
Give it back!
Come take it back.
Come on!
Come get it.
Come on.
You can't get it.
Give it back!
Let's go.
Thanks.
Short and dumb.
I wonder
how you got in.
You eat more at night.
Xianchang Academy
doesn't select me by height.
Besides,
I'm not dumb.
=Episode 3=
Bye, Commander Xiao.
It's you again.
(Xiao)
He's doing great today.
He doesn't lag behind.
When fighting me yesterday,
he wasn't weak at all.
So, he's been pretending.
Seems we need a more enticing bait.
Let's see
when his true colors emerge.
Since you've doubted
He Yan's identity,
why stay quiet?
When fighting him,
I sensed his physical weakness,
yet his moves flowed effortlessly.
Clearly, he's not an amateur.
He's slippery.
Without solid evidence,
he won't confess.
Our task
is to expose his flaws openly.
Shen Han.
Do something for me.
Yes.
- Let me help you.
- Move.
Come on!
(Jiuqi Camp)
So impressive!
If I could
be as brave as them,
that'd be great.
Who are they?
Why so valiant?
Jiuqi Camp.
Jiuqi Camp?
What's that?
You don't know?
It was founded by Marshal Xiao.
It accepts elite warriors only.
All in black armor.
They're invincible,
the core force of Xiao Army.
All enemies fear them.
Why's everyone
suddenly talking about them?
Someone
started it.
But no one
would refuse joining, right?
(They're talking about Jiuqi Camp.)
(Could it be planned?)
(Xiao Jue noticed something)
(during last night's fight.)
(He set a bait)
(to hook me.)
(Baiting me?)
(I'll play along)
(and join the camp.)
(I will do it honorably,)
(flawlessly.)
(Who's bait? Who's prey?)
(Game's still on.)
Mr. Shen.
Zoning out?
Work harder,
and you can join them too.
They're so formidable.
I'm joining them.
Don't rush to join them
just because of that.
They often spearhead the frontlines,
where casualties
remain alarmingly high.
That's perfect then.
They need fresh recruits.
I need military merits.
If I join the Jiuqi Camp,
it's win-win.
We do
select one recruit annually.
However,
it must be
the most outstanding candidate.
This year,
save yourselves the trouble.
The best candidate is
right before you.
Good.
I'll be watching your performance.
He.
Come quick!
Look, meat flatbreads.
That flatbread
is mine.
Yours?
Call its name
and see if it answers you.
Who can prove this is yours?
I'm eating it.
What can you do?
What can I do about it?
You...
Yes.
I did it.
Who can verify that?
What can you do about it?
You...
Want a fight?
Fine.
Wait for me after training.
I'll make you pay.
Enough, He.
Don't stoop to his level.
Since he took my food once,
he might do it again.
If he takes my food daily,
should I starve
every single day?
That is
so not fair.
Are you talking with me
about fairness?
With your weakness,
you won't
survive a month here.
Not even a month.
No need to wait.
In ten days,
at training field,
I'll defeat you in archery,
your best skill.
Are you crazy?
You understand your own words?
Which part
did you not hear?
Let me repeat myself.
In ten days,
I will defeat you.
Pretty boy,
you're very bold.
Alright.
That's a bold wager.
- Yes.
- Good.
If you lose,
you'll become an army cook.
Deal.
But if you lose,
you'll call me boss.
Don't humiliate yourself.
In ten days,
I'll challenge you to a spear duel.
Do you dare to accept it?
Since you're so reckless,
I'll play along.
Good.
In ten days,
we'll compete.
How dare you!
- Commander.
Brawling right after joining the army?
Have you no respect for discipline?
It's okay.
He wants to join the Jiuqi Camp.
I'll see
if he's qualified.
♪I've seen the mountains♪
♪And trodden through ice♪
♪Day after day, I venture alone♪
♪Destiny is my creed♪
♪Ideals surge beneath the surface♪
♪Igniting the flame against the winds♪
♪A restless yearning in my soul♪
♪Gazing through the mire♪
♪Who cares about this boundless void♪
♪Charge ahead with blazing fervor♪
♪Stubbornly fighting with my life♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪
You work so hard,
yet you're still weak.
The sneaky person at the bathing pool
was you, right?
A while ago,
I was exhausted from training.
So, I went to bathe to relax.
The person who was bathing that night
was actually you.
However,
I panicked and fled recklessly
that night.
I hope you won't blame me.
You panicked?
Sure, I did.
You're suspicious
and a liar.
What's your real intention?
I want a trainer.
What?
No offense,
but please train me, Commander.
What makes you think
I'll train you?
Otherwise, did you
come out so late at night
to ambush a recruit for fun?
I know
you're concerned about me.
You think
I have potential.
Practice needs a partner.
Practicing alone
won't work out.
If you train me,
I'm certain I'll make great progress.
Quite cheeky.
If you can resist ten strikes
in a circle,
I'll train you.
Deal.
Can't even hold it.
Why should I train you?
I...
Commander.
Ten strikes done.
I'm still in.
My fault.
Accidentally,
I offended you.
Commander.
A promise
is a promise.
You can't go back on it.
Breaking a promise
is a disgrace.
Commander.
Every night, Xu hour.
Thank you.
Thank you, master.
This is your first lesson.
Remember your words.
If you can't win,
get out of Yezhou Garrison.
Since you're using
the Jiuqi Camp as bait,
I'll absolutely
take this chance.
I'll certainly use you
to succeed.
He learned quite quickly.
(Commander.)
(A promise)
(is a promise.)
(You can't go back on it.)
(Breaking a promise)
(is a disgrace.)
I never agreed to anything.
I've mastered the techniques,
yet he shows no concern.
It's not good.
I must make him
witness my progress.
Commander.
Are you there?
Qinglang.
Long time no see.
(I once asked a swordsmith)
to forge two swords.
One is named Yinqiu.
I gave that to Huaijin
when he came of age.
This one
is named Qinglang.
Today,
I'll give it to you.
Father.
Why did you give him Qinglang?
This sword is valuable.
I can't take it.
Constant effort
brings success.
Someday,
you two will become
the twin stars of Wei,
working together.
Wielding swords
to defend our land
and protect people.
Take it.
I will not
betray your trust.
You're unworthy of this Qinglang Sword
from my father.
It's quite a sharp sword.
It's rare to see.
So, I couldn't help
touching it.
Commander.
You're magnanimous.
You won't blame me, will you?
The sword you're holding
is quite great too!
Why did you come to my tent?
I've practiced diligently
and mastered what you taught me.
Aren't you going to check on me?
I'm busy.
Come.
I knew
you were responsible.
Bet on Wang Ba.
Quick! Tell me!
Who to bet on?
On Wang Ba.
- On Wang Ba.
- Me too.
And you?
Jiang Jiao.
Jiang Jiao? Two on Jiang Jiao?
(Jiang Jiao, He Yan, Wang Ba)
Three flatbreads?
I'm all in!
My bet's on Wang Ba.
Great!
- Wang Ba!
- One!
- On Jiang Jiao?
- Six!
- Jiang Jiao!
(Wang Ba)
Five on Jiang.
Who's got flatbreads left?
Six on Wang Ba.
- And you?
- Jiang Jiao!
You note it all down?
(He Yan)
Of course.
(Someone actually bet)
(on He Yan earlier than me.)
Guys!
Listen,
I am
betting ten flatbreads
(Jiang Jiao, He Yan, Wang Ba)
on He Yan.
- What?
- Sir.
Are you sure?
Absolutely!
Very impressive, Mr. Cheng.
He's never short on flatbreads.
Place your bets! Quickly!
Wang Ba!
- Wang Ba!
- Go!
Wang Ba, come on!
You'll win.
- You'll win.
- Wang Ba will win!
- He!
- Wang Ba!
Go for it!
Show your skills!
Go, Wang Ba!
Wang Ba!
Wang Ba, come on!
Show your skills!
You'll win!
Wang Ba!
Go for it, He!
He!
Wang Ba!
Go for it, He!
You'll win!
Lei Hou.
You bet on me?
I didn't bet on anyone.
Hey.
Change your mind now,
or you'll humiliate yourself.
Exactly!
Give it up!
So funny.
I was about to say the same.
You'll regret it.
Wang Ba!
You'll win!
Wang Ba, come on!
Wang Ba won!
Impressive!
Wang Ba won.
Awesome!
Wang Ba won!
Impressive.
Give it up!
- Give it up!
- Be quiet!
You're humiliating yourself.
Exactly.
Indeed.
Give it up!
Look at him.
I knew it.
He's bound to lose.
Give it up!
Get out of here.
Well...
Pierced right through!
Quite strong.
Is he that skilled?
- Well...
- Precise and powerful.
He's pretty strong.
Congrats!
Among these recruits,
you've got a capable heroine.
No,
a capable hero.
Both Wang Ba and He Yan
are doing great.
Credit goes to Mr. Shen.
Not really, Mr. Cheng.
I can't claim the credit.
Commander Xiao's
training methods work.
My discerning eyes
never misjudge talent.
Remember our wager?
No backing out.
Mr. Shen.
Who's your pick?
Wang Ba
has potential.
He was a bandit
and a rebel.
But he's good
at archery.
He Yan
works hard.
He's mild-tempered.
A few years later,
he'll become
the best of the recruits.
You've misjudged, Mr. Shen.
The rebellious one
isn't Wang Ba.
But He Yan
is getting more interesting.
After your rest,
- let's...
- I'm rested.
Let's begin.
- Go!
- You can do it!
- Jiang Jiao, go for it!
- Go!
Go for it!
- Come on!
- You can do it!
Good!
Excellent!
Keep going!
Go for it!
Amazing!
Bravo!
Splendid!
Who won?
(Given his strength,)
(is he actually a recruit?)
Why
is He just defending?
Faster! Quicker!
One more strike to beat him!
(He's testing me.)
That dodge
was so good.
Commander.
He Yan's evasive maneuver is
like yours.
Yet he failed
to dodge your stone?
He chose not to dodge.
(No weapons)
(can defeat)
(spears.)
He Yan!
Few people are skilled at spear.
But once they do,
they will not
fear all other weapons.
Well done!
This Jiang Jiao is useless.
Unbelievable.
Pretty boy.
What?
A bet's a bet.
Boss.
Oh, right.
I almost forgot.
There's someone else
who needs to call me boss.
Wang Ba.
It's your turn.
You're not trying to back out, are you?
Move aside!
B-Bo...
You can...
Boss.
You heard me.
Sure, I did.
I just never expected
you'd actually do it.
As a real man...
That's it.
I did it.
Stop looking!
Get out of here!
Let's go.
- Get out of here.
- Go.
Let's train harder.
I lost the bet,
but I watched a good match.
Sure.
Let's go.
Commander.
You forgot this.
You did well.
Keep it.
I'll remember
your kindness forever.
Coming!
Flatbreads.
Guys! Listen up!
Thanks to Mr. He,
I won the bet
in today's match.
Tonight,
it's my treat.
Just help yourselves.
What are you waiting for?
All of us
should thank Mr. Cheng.
Thank you, Mr. Cheng.
Let's eat!
Smells good!
I know
I am good-looking.
However,
you staring so boldly at me
is making me
feel rather uncomfortable.
Mr. Cheng.
You're overthinking.
I doubt
the flatbreads you won
are enough for us.
This is my way of repaying you.
You may lose more than you gain.
It's worth it.
Bring the soup if it's ready.
Great!
Smells so good.
Exactly! Where are the bowls?
- Give me a bowl.
- Thanks, Mr. Cheng!
The soup is served.
Your title as Yezhou's top warrior
might be in jeopardy.
Mr. He
has trained hard this month.
That's why he shocked everyone today.
Both of us
stop being jealous.
Mr. He.
Congrats!
Thanks, Mr. Lei.
Commander.
At the training field,
you said
he chose not to dodge.
What did you mean?
I used the Jiuqi Camp as bait
to lure him to duel.
While he was overwhelmed,
I secretly acted
to force him to reveal some flaw.
Unexpectedly,
he actually
discerned my intention.
So, he didn't dodge.
He's not only resilient,
but also clever.
He's a formidable opponent.
Anyway,
He Yan
is definitely up to no good.
Shall I go arrest him first?
No rush.
So, you already have a plan?
These new recruits
have been training
for a full month.
It's time for their competition.
Then
the truth will reveal itself.
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪I've seen the mountains♪
♪And trodden through ice♪
♪Day after day, I venture alone♪
♪Destiny is my creed♪
♪Ideals surge beneath the surface♪
♪Igniting the flame against the winds♪
♪A restless yearning in my soul♪
♪Gazing through the mire♪
♪Who cares about this boundless void♪
♪Charge ahead with blazing fervor♪
♪Stubbornly fighting with my life♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪