Subtitle by Kisskh.Asia Translator [ Admin Qari ]
May I be like the stars
and you like the moon.
As long as the world remains,
so shall we.
I only wish to stay with the one I love,
watching every sunrise and sunset.
I want to be with you forever.
Eternals and demons walk different paths.
You and she are ultimately different.
Have you ever
truly cared for me?
No.
Never.
In this life and the next, through all lifetimes…
May we live and die together,
and share life and death as one.
[Moonlight Mystique]
[Episode 1]
[Ning'an City]
There is a city in the mortal realm
[Bai Residence]
called Ning'an.
Its governor has a daughter
called Bai Shuo.
Speaking of Bai Shuo,
she's been obsessed with immortality since she was little,
[Immortality]
dreaming day and night
of becoming immortal.
[Where there's a will, there's an immortal.]
To become immortal,
she tried almost everything:
spending a fortune on talismans,
buying every book on immortality in the city,
and fumbling around with divination.
[Ominous]
Bai Shuo!
You naughty girl!
You're messing with this superstitious nonsense again!
Today,
I have to give you a good beating!
Running around the house hiding from her father.
Everyone told her
there were no immortals in this world,
but she firmly believed there were.
Because
she once met one.
No, to be precise,
I met one.
That Lantern Festival night,
my sister Bai Xi and I snuck out of the manor to have fun.
Unexpectedly,
we were taken away by a demon.
Run!
[Young Bai Shuo]
Xi, run!
[Young Bai Xi]
I won't leave you!
Run, Shuo!
No!
-You leave!
Xi!
Run, Shuo!
Run!
Your fate is extraordinary. Your spiritual energy is pure.
It's your greatest honor
to help me become more powerful!
Xi!
Xi.
Please.
Please save Xi.
If there truly are immortals in this world,
please, save Xi.
Xi.
-Stupid human.
-Xi.
How dare you hurt me?
I'll ensure your souls are destroyed
and you fall into eternal damnation!
Souls destroyed.
Eternal damnation.
Those words were actually
uttered by someone other than me.
Purple moon…
You…
You're…
Are you an immortal?
Divine Lord,
please save Xi.
She's already dead.
I never interfere with the life and death of any living being.
Saving you
was already an exception.
Please, Divine Lord,
please save Xi.
As long as you save her,
I promise to repay you in the future.
I beg you,
please.
Repay me?
The next time I descend to the mortal world,
it may be thousands of years from now.
You, a mortal, won't live beyond a hundred years.
How could you possibly repay me?
I can repay you!
I'll seek immortality and learn immortal arts.
I'll live for a thousand, or even ten thousand years.
I'll become very powerful.
The next time I meet you,
I'll repay you with my life!
I beg you, please, I beg you!
Xi!
Xi, are you okay?
Shuo.
Are you okay?
I'm glad you're alright.
Many thanks, Divine Lord.
Not all immortals pity mortals.
You're lucky
to have eyes resembling hers.
Divine Lord?
♫A lifetime of guarding everything with you♫
♫Crossing the abyss to fulfill our vow♫
♫I'll leap without a thought for tomorrow♫
♫This moment feels like forever♫
♫I've missed too much time in my life♫
♫I'll throw myself into this flame for you♫
♫Even if I'll perish♫
♫At lease I can still kiss your face♫
When I woke up,
Xi and Father were watching me by my bedside.
I asked Xi if she remembered that powerful immortal,
but she said…
Father,
Xi,
why am I here?
When did I come back?
Xi, do you remember that powerful immortal?
Shuo,
what are you talking about?
What immortal?
I-I don't understand what you're saying.
What's wrong, Shuo?
[Bai Xun, Human Race, Governor of Ning'an City]
Nothing ever happened.
What's wrong with you?
Xi forgot everything.
Father also said nothing ever happened.
And I, for some reason,
could no longer recall the face of that immortal.
But when there is a debt,
it must be repaid.
I made a promise to that immortal.
Not long after,
Xi fell gravely ill for some unknown reason.
Every doctor in the city said there was no saving her.
How is she?
Forgive me. There's nothing I can do.
She
won't make it.
Xi!
Xi, wake up!
Fortunately, a wandering Taoist passed by
and saved her life.
Please save Xi.
This girl has an unusual destiny.
Only by staying far from the mortal world
can she grow up safely.
The Taoist said
Xi has a special destiny.
She must stay far from the mortal world to grow up safely.
Father, to keep Xi alive,
had no choice but to let her leave
with that Taoist.
[Bai Residence]
Unexpectedly,
we never heard from her again.
Xi.
Xi!
♫Across thousands of miles♫
Everyone said
Governor Bai had two daughters.
♫The pain of parting lingers♫
One was lost,
the other was obsessed with immortality.
No one understood me.
♫ I light a lamp with no wick to carry me through the rest of my days♫
Not even my father.
But even so,
my marriage
was decided early on.
♫Flowers in the wind, sand in the water♫
Yes.
It was.
His name was Chong Zhao,
the son of the steamed bun stall owner on the next street.
Our families knew each other.
After his parents died in an accident,
my father took him in
and cared for him like his own son.
Over time,
my father grew fond of him
and arranged an engagement between us.
Chong Zhao was so good to me.
He never made fun of my immortality dream.
Though, the steamed buns he gave me were ridiculously big.
My father said
we were family from then on.
That's true.
Family
doesn't have to mean husband and wife.
It can also mean brother and sister.
I never took that engagement seriously.
Chong Zhao never mentioned it either.
Year after year,
through meals and seasons,
the meaning of home
and family
perhaps lies in these simple, ordinary days.
In the blink of an eye, ten years passed.
Many things have changed,
but some things remain the same.
For example…
[Guanze Hall]
Master Sun,
our ten-year friendship
is over just like this?
[Master Sun, Human Race]
The governor has talked to me.
I can't see you again,
[Bai Shuo, Human Race]
or he'll tear down my temple.
[Guanze Hall]
Please, cut me some slack.
All the scriptures and talismans
can be yours.
Please show me some mercy and leave.
Please leave.
[Guanze Hall]
Leave?
Immortals have their rules,
and demons have theirs.
In Ning'an City,
you have to follow my rules.
If you don't tell me
how to become immortal today,
before my father comes,
I'll tear down your temple myself.
I'm talking to her,
not you.
Still want to run away?
Fine.
I've been
keeping this secret
for many years.
I'm touched by your eagerness today.
With the sun and moon as witnesses,
I'll share it
with you.
Go ahead.
To protect the people with utmost dedication,
[Unbridled Pavilion, Ning'an City, Human Race]
the Eternals assign an envoy
to every city
for secret observation.
If you can find that envoy
and move them with unmatched sincerity
to get them to guide you,
you'll be able to become an Eternal.
I can tell you
who the envoy in this city is.
Who is it?
He is
the owner of Unbridled Pavilion!
Why has the top courtesan been replaced?
Drink up!
Look at her waist.
Look at those legs.
Great!
Bravo!
Gorgeous!
The new top courtesan?
Not bad.
Flower demons excel at seduction.
She can stir up more Contemplations
to help you with your plans.
Master,
we've been in Ning'an City for a month.
The city is full of groundless rumors now,
saying you're
astonishingly beautiful—
a rare sight in the world.
Many dignitaries in the city have asked to meet you.
Are you interested in meeting
one or two of them?
A bunch of humans
don't deserve my attention.
Unless it's about the Desireless Stone,
don't bother me
with anything else.
What are you standing around for?
Go serve the wine.
Me?
Since we're in the human world,
we must follow human rules.
We're running a business here.
We must keep our guests entertained.
Go on.
Fine.
I'm going.
The Eternal Envoy
is a businessman in the mortal world?
That sounds like something you made up to fool me.
He just keeps a low profile.
[Qingyun Temple]
If everyone knew he's an immortal,
they'd be flocking to him to seek immortality.
That'd be chaos!
That makes sense.
But you said earlier
he's only been in Ning'an City for a month,
and he doesn't know me.
If he wouldn't meet anyone,
why would he meet me?
Since
you both work for the Eternals,
why don't you take me to see him?
No, no, no!
Seeking immortality is very serious.
If you take shortcuts, how can you prove your dedication?
If I can become an Eternal,
I won't forget your guidance today.
But if you're lying to me…
No way.
Impossible.
Good.
Hurry up.
[Guanze Hall]
Pack your things. We gotta go.
Hurry up.
Master,
haven't you already told Miss Bai
about the Eternal Envoy?
Why are we running?
There's no such thing as an Eternal Envoy.
There aren't even immortals in this world!
The owner of Unbridled Pavilion
[Guanze Hall]
is tough and arrogant. He's been here for a month,
yet no one has seen him in person.
Well,
Bai Shuo,
the governor's daughter,
is obsessed with becoming immortal,
and she's more stubborn than a mule.
My genius plan
is just to buy us time
to run away!
She can't find out I lied to her.
Hurry up,
or we're as good as dead!
Hurry up.
[Guanze Hall]
[Unbridled Pavilion]
[Furong, Demon Race, the top courtesan of Unbridled Pavilion]
Isn't that the governor's daughter, a little troublemaker?
Yes.
What's...
What's she doing here?
Yeah.
An immortal
lives in a place like this?
It's not what the storybooks say.
It looks more like a demon's den.
Miss, you look unfamiliar.
First time here?
You want a Jiangnan singer
or a Mobei dancer?
This guy is strapping.
If the greeter here looks so impressive,
the owner must be extraordinary.
I'm Bai Shuo.
I came with priceless treasures
to meet your boss.
Meet my boss?
We get at least 80,
maybe even 100 people a day,
who come with treasures
to see my boss.
Shoo, shoo!
My treasures
are nothing like those of ordinary mortals.
Open them all.
I'm not just the governor's daughter.
I've studied immortal arts for many years.
These
are the treasures I've gathered
that can vanquish any demons.
Today, I offer them as a gift to your boss.
What do you think?
Am I sincere enough?
Now bring your boss to meet me!
You said you want to vanquish demons?
[Fan Yue, Demon Race, King of the Polar Realm, Master of Bright Moon Palace]
The owner of Unbridled Pavilion?
So this is an immortal?
He seems more of a hardass than me.
Sir.
Don't push.
-I've been asking to see you for days.
-Don't push.
You finally show up.
Back. Back.
Don't speak
unless spoken to.
I don't like noise,
especially from humans.
So arrogant.
I like that.
Are you the one
who wants to vanquish demons?
Yes.
It's me.
You came to my turf
to spout such nonsense.
You've got some nerve.
What's your name?
Bai Shuo.
Since childhood, I've pursued immortality.
It's been ten years now.
My devotion is sincere, and I've never wavered.
Astrology, divination, talismans, and formations—
I'm skilled in all of them.
If you don't believe me,
you can test me however you like.
May I ask if you can communicate
with the heavens?
Are you an Eternal?
You don't get to ask
if I'm an Eternal.
Testing aptitude
requires this kind of approach?
I thought the idiots from Lanling came after me.
It turns out she's just an ordinary human.
In that case…
Is that
the etiquette of the Eternals?
Eternal,
have I gotten the etiquette right?
Master, you can't kill in human territory.
[Cang Shan, Demon Race, a guardian of Bright Moon Palace]
City patrol, routine inspection!
Father?
Bai Shuo!
What are you doing here?
[Lanling Sect, Eternal Race]
Everyone,
it's been a long time since the last time
[Lanling Sect]
we held a meeting.
We finally gathered together again.
Now,
let's first hear a few words
from our sect leader.
[Chong Zhao, Eternal Race, the head disciple of Lanling]
Master,
are you alright?
I'm fine.
[Jin Yao, Eternal Race, Sect Leader of Lanling]
Well…
Guys,
let's make do with it.
[Jing Lei, Eternal Race, Lanling Sect] [Yan Huo, Eternal Race, Lanling Sect]
[Yu Feng, Eternal Race, Lanling Sect] [Feng Yu, Eternal Race, Lanling Sect]
Sect Leader,
next time we hold a meeting,
can we find a proper place with an intact roof?
Every time we hold a meeting,
we either stand in the wind or under the scorching sun.
-Yeah.
You all know
the current state of the sect.
We can't avoid the wind and sun,
but I promise I won't let you
get rained on.
Look.
I came prepared.
Now,
let's begin.
[Purchase Contract]
These are the city office's approvals,
the restaurant's property deed,
and all the required documents.
My lord,
although we've only just arrived,
our business is legitimate.
Many citizens have gone missing recently.
It's just a routine inspection.
Your paperwork is complete,
[Tian Huo, Demon Race, a guardian of Bright Moon Palace]
but you must not slack off
[Bai Yu, Human Race, Deputy General of Ning'an City]
in the future.
Of course.
We're all law-abiding people.
We're not done talking yet.
You brat!
You're quite bold lately, aren't you?
You failed to become an immortal,
then used my money to hang out at a brothel with some pretty boy.
Do you think that's fair to me?
Or to Chong Zhao?
Father,
don't make a fuss.
I came here for a proper reason.
What proper reason?
Stop right there!
Am I done talking?
You brat.
You're good-looking,
and tall.
You look like a gentleman,
but you're a male courtesan!
Disgusting.
Filthy!
Listen.
If you want to keep the Unbridled Pavilion running in Ning'an City,
stay away from my daughter.
Master,
you must hold back.
We can't use demon power
in front of the human race.
Father,
you can't offend him.
So what if I do?
You've disgraced me.
The Desireless Stone
reacted.
Not a mortal item, as expected.
Let go!
Don't test me or else I'll seal off
the Unbridled Pavilion!
Today is not the right time.
Wait for me.
I'll come back another day.
You can't come again!
Father, it's none of your business.
How is it not?
Go home.
I'll seal off your Unbridled Pavilion!
You've disgraced me.
Shut up.
Wait for me at home.
Let's go.
All right.
This is the end of the Eternal Envoy assembly.
Thank you for taking the time to join us from each city.
I've recorded all the demon situations reported.
I will reply later.
However,
there is another troublesome matter
to discuss with you all.
What is it?
You've snuffed out the little bit of warmth here.
Okay.
Let me say it then.
Everyone remembers the Desireless Stone, right?
Lanling has been keeping
Goddess Xingyue's divine object all this time.
After so many years,
we became lax.
Maybe...
Perhaps...
Anyway,
well,
it was lost. Dismissed.
What?
Wait, wait, wait.
-Lost it?
This can't be lost.
No way.
Why didn't you say so earlier?
That's a divine object.
How can it be lost?
-Yeah.
-You must make it clear.
What exactly happened?
You must explain.
-Yes.
-Yeah.
-Make it clear.
-You have to explain.
Make it clear.
As we all know,
the Desireless Stone belonged to the Goddess Xingyue.
Although it has been damaged
and can't show its divine power,
it's still a divine object of the Eternal Race
and the dignity of Lanling.
So we've been keeping it in the sect's secret realm
without disturbing it.
Last month,
we accidentally discovered that it was stolen.
And the only thing left at the scene
was the Demon Race's aura.
The Demon Race even attacked our home.
We're doomed!
Although it's a useless item,
it's still the face of Lanling.
We can't
just let this go.
-We can’t let it go.
Yes, we can't let it go.
I agree with you all.
But take a look.
Our sect
is short of money
and shorthanded.
There are many things we're unable to do.
Anyway,
if you find any clues
of the Desireless Stone in your cities,
just report it back. Dismissed.
No!
-No!
-The Demon Race has gone too far.
We must seek an explanation from the Demon Race!
At worse, we'll just fight them!
Get it back!
How dare they!
Let's go together.
You're all right!
The missing of the Desireless Stone
has embarrassed Lanling.
We should ask the demons for an explanation.
But if we fight the demons for this,
it will definitely
affect the entire Lanling Sect.
I should bear
such a big mistake by myself.
Yu Feng!
Come here!
Sect Leader.
After I leave,
this huge Lanling
and the responsibility of the world
will be in the hands of you all.
Please!
Master!
Sect Leader!
-Sect Leader!
-Master! Master!
You've all been graced by the sect for years.
Are you really going to blame Sect Leader for this?
Sect Leader,
we just said a few words.
Why did you take it seriously?
The demons in Baihua City are rampant.
We're very busy.
Sect Leader,
I'll take my leave.
Me too.
I have to collect rent from my shops.
Yes.
Me too.
Let's go.
Sect Leader, wake up!
Sect Leader!
You're all dismissed.
Chong Zhao, stay here.
Chong Zhao,
you were scared on my behalf?
Come, help me up.
Kneel.
Do you admit your mistake?
You want to compete in being stubborn with me?
Were you wrong?
You—
I'm usually busy with city matters.
I don't have time to discipline you.
I didn't expect you to be so spoiled,
causing trouble everywhere.
Don't think I don't know.
You made a scene at the Taoist temple during the day
and went to a brothel at night.
Is this what the governor's daughter should do?
I'm the governor's daughter,
but I am also myself.
I know what I'm doing.
Before you be yourself,
do you still remember how your mother raised you?
[Spirit Tablet of Madam Han of the Bai Family]
Do you remember today is her death anniversary?
These years, what do you remember
other than becoming an Eternal?
What else do you care about?
I advised you to give up many times, but you didn't listen.
In the past,
you were clever and mischievous but still obedient.
Now,
you're stubborn and arrogant.
Today,
in this ancestral hall
and before your mother,
[Spirit Tablet of Madam Han of the Bai Family]
I want you to swear
to give up your Eternal obsession.
Otherwise,
I'll disown you.
Swearing is easy,
but I don't want to lie in front of my mother.
[Spirit Tablet of Madam Han of the Bai Family]
I want to become an Eternal
to repay one's kindness.
This is my lifelong wish.
No matter how many years it's been or how many people oppose it,
I won't give up.
Even if you break ties with your father?
Answer me!
Yes.
Remember what you said.
From now on, don't call me your father.
It's been a long time since we've stolen the Desireless Stone from the divine race.
We've been to so many places
and tried hundreds of ways,
but it never lit up.
What is
so special about Bai Shuo
that she could make the divine stone light up?
Have you forgotten
why we came to the Human Race's territory?
Of course.
The Desireless Stone is an ancient
divine object of the Lunar Race's Goddess Xingyue.
During the Divine War 60,000 years ago,
countless deities died.
The Desireless Stone was damaged during the Divine War.
No one has been able to activate it.
Legend has it
that as long as one gathers
the Five Contemplations of love, hate, kill, greed, and benevolence,
one can reactivate the Desireless Stone
and get the divine power
that Goddess Xingyue left in the Desireless Stone.
The purpose of establishing
the Unbridled Pavilion was to absorb human Contemplations.
Humans
are the most complicated creatures in the world.
Welcome.
Happiness.
-Is it good?
-Yes!
Sadness.
How dare you sell it?
-Anger.
-What are you doing?
Love.
-Thank you.
-Take your time.
Envy.
Fear.
Bloodthirstiness.
Greed.
All emotions and distractions converge in them.
I thought that as long as I mixed in with humans,
the contemplation power needed by the Desireless Stone would be collected.
But now, it seems
that Bai Shuo
is the key.
How about
we kidnap her?
Idiot.
Bai Shuo is the governor's daughter.
Ning'an City is guarded by the Lanling Sect.
If we make a scene
and the Eternal Envoy here reports to the sect,
Master’s whereabouts will be leaked.
But you're the Demon King of the Polar Region and master of the Bright Moon Palace.
Unless the Divine Race is revived,
no current Eternal or demon
is a match for you.
We don't need to be afraid of the Lanling Sect.
I don't like trouble.
The scum from Jingyou Mountain and Cold Spring Palace
are looking for me everywhere.
If they know
we have the Desireless Stone,
it'll just add more trouble.
Boring.
You're foresighted
and confident.
I admire you.
Is this what I want to hear?
Then what do you mean?
Master means
that the Desireless Stone responds to Bai Shuo,
so it's very likely that she has one of the Contemplations.
I'll go to the Governor's Mansion to keep an eye on her.
I...
Me too.
Bai Shuo.
Interesting.
[Spirit Tablet of Madam Han of the Bai Family]
Mother.
I'm sorry.
I forgot your death anniversary.
I'm an unfilial daughter.
Actually, I don't want to make Father angry.
But...
Mother,
if it weren't for that immortal ten years ago,
Xi and I would have died.
Many people live
but don't know what they're living for.
But I know myself.
[Spirit Tablet of Madam Han of the Bai Family]
I want to become an Eternal
to repay his kindness.
That was my promise to the divine deity.
I must repay
the favor I was given.
I've lost contact with Xi.
I don't know whether she’s alive or dead.
I'll repay on her behalf too.
Everyone can say I'm stubborn
and stupid.
But if even I break my promise,
it'll be no different from me being dead.
[Spirit Tablet of Madam Han of the Bai Family]
Right,
Mother?
Yesterday, your uncle and I observed the tray
and found there are demons in Ning'an City.
But we haven't found the exact location yet.
You're the immortal in charge of Ning'an City.
Be careful when you go back.
Don't worry, Master.
I understand.
All these years,
you've been my most capable and outstanding disciple.
You've become
a city's immortal
at such a young age.
So I have
a very important task for you.
Master,
do you want me
to track down the whereabouts of the Desireless Stone?
No.
I just wanted to ask
about the business of your steamed bun stall
in Ning'an City.
Any profits?
The cost of saving humans has been too high recently.
Besides, this house is old and shabby.
It needs renovation.
-Master, Senior Uncle.
-So...
We are Eternals.
Why can't we just use magic?
No.
Hundreds of years ago, when demons and Eternals had a truce,
they promised
not to use magic in the human race's territory.
But we're in the Eternal Race's territory right now.
We have to make a habit out of things.
If you rely on magic for everything,
you might accidentally expose yourself
in the human race's territory.
By then, if the demons find something on us
and trouble us first,
that would be bad.
What if the demons break their promise
and wreak havoc among the humans?
Can't we use magic against them?
Don't worry.
Recently, there's been chaos among the demons.
Even if they want to harm the human race,
I'm afraid
they don't have the energy for that.
Also, Master,
about the Desireless Stone, I still think that...
60,000 years ago,
Hidden Lord caused a disaster and the Divine Race fell.
Since then, there is no divine deity in the world.
Now the upholding of justice
lies with us, the Eternals.
And you
are my
favorite private disciple.
So the burden of all living beings
must fall on your shoulders.
Don't worry, Master.
I will follow your teachings.
I won't use magic to run the steamed bun stall.
I won't let all living beings down.
Thank you for your hard work.
Hurry and return to the city.
What a naive child.
Yeah.
But what do living beings
have to do with making money?
They have everything to do with it.
The demons are wreaking havoc nowadays.
The Cold Spring Palace is especially eager to make a move.
Zhen Yu is ruthless
and keeps expanding his power.
We'll have to fight this battle sooner or later.
Have you ever heard of
winning a war without provisions?
This is the territory of the human race.
How dare the Cold Spring Palace make trouble here
and besiege the Eternal Race?
Where is the Desireless Stone?
Tell me,
and you live.
Don't tell me,
and you die.
It's a secret of the Eternal Race.
You will never know!
Fellow Eternal.
Are you all right?
Who are you?
I'm just a wandering Eternal, passing by.
Thank you for saving my life.
No need to thank me.
The demons
besieged my fellow kind.
Of course I had to help.
Just now,
I heard that the demon mentioned the Desireless Stone.
Could that be
the cause of the fight tonight?
Yes.
Everyone knows that
the Desireless Stone is with the Lanling Sect.
Why did he ask that?
You don't know.
The Desireless Stone
was stolen some time ago.
Stolen?
By whom?
I don't know who it was.
I only know it was done by a demon.
A demon?
Any more leads?
No.
If you have
no other leads,
I have
no reason to let you live.
[Fu Ling, Demon, General of Cold Spring Palace]
Grand Master.
[Zhen Yu, Demon, Master of Cold Spring Palace]
You're just impatient.
Couldn't you have waited till he was further away?
You got blood all over me.
I don't have the patience.
When you killed our people,
you didn't hesitate either.
So quick to talk back.
The Desireless Stone was in the secret realm of Lanling.
Even I can't enter and get it easily.
A demon managed to
silently sneak in and steal it.
In this world,
there's only
one person who can do that.
The Master of Bright Moon Palace?
Yes.
That Fan Yue...
Back then, he used the Zhanhuang Chain
to chop off my demon tail.
It cut off the possibility
of me raising my cultivation level.
I will
make him pay with his life.
I've disguised myself as a top courtesan
and successfully infiltrated Unbridled Pavilion.
Hurry up.
While you
find the Desireless Stone's whereabouts,
lead the Eternals
to fight against Bright Moon Palace.
Even if they can’t die together,
we can
reap the benefits.
Yes.
Just tell me if you want to starve me to death.
Someone is proud
and full of ambition.
She won’t starve to death.
Didn’t Zhao say he went out for business yesterday?
Why hasn’t he come back?
When someone went to the brothel,
why didn't she remember that
she had a fiance named Zhao?
I didn’t go to a brothel.
That wasn't a brothel either.
That someone doesn't have to explain anything.
I've already cut familial ties with that person.
She can go wherever she wants.
Patrol.
Go wherever I want?
You said it yourself.
How did it go?
Bai Shuo is indeed the daughter of Bai Xun, the governor.
She has been searching in vain for a Eternal for the past decade.
People call her the Eternal fanatic.
A Eternal fanatic?
She made the Desireless Stone glow.
I don't believe she's just an ordinary person.
Unless...
Master was mistaken last night,
and the Desireless Stone did not glow.
But that's impossible,
Master.
Why don't I catch her
and let you interrogate her?
No need.
She's here.
Boss.
I'm here to see you.
Let's continue our chat
from last night.
Master.
Shall I catch and interrogate her,
or throw her out?
This is the human race's territory.
Calm down.
Don't make trouble.
Since we know what she wants, why interrogate her?
I just need to pretend to be a immortal
and fool her into believing it.
Then, she'll happily answer my questions.
By then, it won't be hard
to test if her emotions can really
affect the Desireless Stone.
Look at this extravagant style
and untamed demeanor.
Can this really belong to a deity?
I'll have to find out.