[Yi'ang]
[Born with Luck]
[Episode 24]
I did swindle Zhou Rong out of 30 million
to pay my gambling debts.
I'm guilty.
That's all.
You did more.
My greed has led to
a terribly negative impact on the society
and caused grave trouble
for the police.
I'm guilty.
Really, that's all.
Why don't you give me a reminder?
Ye Jian.
Well...
I-I need one more reminder.
Yesterday, before Lu Yibo
went for the bianzhong deal,
he told Zhou Qi...
Go find Lang Bowen
and ask him to help me.
Just tell him
I will definitely not tell anyone
about what happened
on the night Ye Jian died.
Ask him to please help me.
What exactly happened
on the night Ye Jian died?
Fine.
I'll give you one last tip.
How would I dare lie to you?
Everything I said is true.
Where is Bowen?
He got drunk and left.
If you don't believe me, I'll call him
so you can ask him.
Call him now!
So Ye Jian called you?
Don't tell him, everybody.
Hurry! Catch him quickly!
[Lu Yibo]
Yes.
Ye used Yibo's phone
and
gave me a call.
What did he want with you?
He just asked me about that watch.
I told him I had given it to Lu Yibo.
Then,
Ye asked me about
what happened to Lu Zheng that day.
Ye was my good friend,
so I told the truth.
He then hung up the phone.
After that,
I got more and more worried.
So, I called
Zhou Rong.
You called Zhou Rong?
That was because...
Did you also tell him the truth?
How would I dare to do so?
I just told him
Ye found out what happened to Lu Zheng.
When Zhou Rong
was on the phone,
were his emotion
and tone
the same as usual?
At first, he was quite calm.
Then, as I brought up about Lu Zheng,
he went livid.
He started throwing and smashing stuff.
Are you sure
you told him about the watch?
Yes.
Anything wrong?
It seems odd.
Given Zhou Rong's
temperament,
if he knew
that watch could be evidence,
would he have let Lu Yibo wear it
and walk around for such a long time?
I guess I probably told him about it.
I have a bad memory.
Your memory is never good.
See if this is the truth:
Zhou Rong actually ordered you
to retrieve the phone
and kill those two people.
But you didn't plan to do any of that.
You were there for the deal.
I heard you meant
to take 5 million out of your own pocket
to pay those guys and have them
leave Sanjiangkou as soon as possible.
Why?
It feels like
you were eager to get the phone back
and put this matter behind.
That phone wouldn't
cause you any harm.
Why did you want it?
Were you worried
-that if we got the phone...
-I killed Ye Jian.
Now that your investigation
has gone this far,
I might as well
tell the truth.
[Lu Yibo]
Ye,
this must be kept secret from Mr. Zhou.
Listen up!
It's too noisy on your end.
Let's talk face-to-face.
Meet me in Binhe Park
by the creek
we used to swim in.
I'll be on the way now.
Where
is the car now?
In my garage.
Chief.
We found biology traces.
Go back and get some rest.
I'll wait here for the results.
Why did Lang Bowen
kill a man
in such a strange way?
I did some analysis.
First of all,
Given his skills,
it must be hard for him to fight
and kill Ye alone.
Second,
they were childhood friends.
With the means he choice,
he didn't have to confront Ye.
It's a sunny day.
Time to eat!
[Zhou Rong] [Hu Jianren] [Lang Bowen]
[Li Penggai] [Lu Yibo] [Zhou Qi]
[Zheng Yongbing] [Liu Bei]
[Mao Hongwei] [Xia Tinggang]
[A stone with "Yi'ang" written on it]
[Fenglinwan Hotel Pub]
[Ye Jian] [Lu Zheng]
Chief Zhang, the results are in.
It's Ye's blood.
Has the murder weapon been found?
Not yet.
According to the recovery team,
it was likely brought to the downstream
by the water,
with slim chances of finding it.
But Dr. Chen
and the experts
from the Provincial Department
all think Captain Ye died the way
Lang Bowen described.
[Zhou Rong] [Hu Jianren] [Lang Bowen]
If Lang Bowen were not the murderer,
He couldn't possibly know that.
Besides, in that SUV,
only Lang Bowen's
and Lang Botu's fingerprints were found.
So, the murderer is Lang Bowen.
Lang Bowen
spoke of a cutting board.
It is no easy job to make such a thing.
Suppose Lang Bowen killed Ye Jian
in the heat of passion
like he said,
then how did he
get that cutting board?
What's more,
he had the guts to kill Ye Jian,
yet he would rather
pay 5 million
than go after those two street loafers.
Don't you find
this logic strange?
But now, all the testimonies
and the chain of evidence
point to no one but Lang Bowen
as the killer.
Li Qian.
Who is Yangyang?
[I went to take a shower
and I remember this clearly]
[I felt terrible in the shower,
and Yangyang came in to take care of me]
Yangyang...
It's Lang Botu's nickname.
Thank you.
"Yang..."
"Yangyang."
"Yi'ang."
♪ Doubt ♪
[Yi'ang]
"Yi'ang..."
♪ Doubt, doubt the doubt ♪
[Yang]
"Yi'ang."
"Yi-ang."
"Yang."
Ye Jian wrote my name
on the stone not because
he hoped I could solve the case.
It is pinyin.
"Yi'ang."
Read "Yi" and "Yang" fast,
and you'll get "Yang."
"Yangyang."
It refers to Lang Botu.
Whether Lang Botu killed him or not,
the murderer
was probably still at the scene.
Ye Jian feared that the murderer
might see him leave a clue,
so he used my name
as pinyin to give us a hint.
"Yi'ang" and "Yang."
"Yangyang."
It's Lang Botu.
His fingerprints
were found in the SUV.
He is highly suspicious.
Improbable, Chief Zhang.
As far as I know,
this boy rarely engages
himself in their business.
How could it be him?
Call Lang Botu.
Hello.
Yes, it's me.
I'm heading to the airport.
He's flying abroad
at 2 p.m. today.
With his elder brother in detention,
he's going abroad right now?
It's no surprise.
Isn't he supposed to go abroad
for postgraduate studies?
He received his acceptance letter
long time ago
and got his visa done.
The program starts
on the 10th of next month.
Maybe he's going overseas
a few days earlier
to rent a place?
Stop him.
On what grounds?
He is suspected of murdering Ye Jian.
Got it.
Shall we interrogate Lang Bowen again?
Yes, make a call for it.
Hello.
Chief Zhang asks
to interrogate Lang Bowen now.
Right now.
When?
Is it serious?
What did the doctor say?
Thank you.
Lang Bowen has been sent
to the People's Hospital
due to intestinal obstruction.
How did that suddenly happen?
He choked on food.
The doctor said he's fine
and prescribed anti-inflammatory medicine
and two bags of glucose.
Lang Bowen is on IVs now.
What a coincidence.
A great coincidence, isn't it?
He pulled the same trick
in prison before.
He deliberately chocked on food
till intestinal obstruction happened.
Then he was sent to the infirmary,
and cured by a tube of glycerin.
He did it
only to chat with the nurses there.
How long will the IVs take?
It takes 4 hours
to finish 2 bags of glucose.
Four hours...
What time is it now?
The process will end at about 2:00.
That is...
when Lang Botu's flight take off.
There is another situation.
Lang Bowen has been inquiring
about today's weather
since yesterday.
He was afraid
that the flight wouldn't take off.
There must be something wrong.
What should we do?
After all,
Lang Bowen is a patient now.
Is it appropriate to get him back
f-for interrogation?
Two 500 ml bags of glucose take 4 hours
if infused slowly,
and 3 if infused quickly.
That could give us
a window of one hour.
Why is the fluid level so low?
What's with it?
This might cause an embolism.
Don't move.
What are you looking at?
You perv.
No.
I'm looking at your watch.
[Infusion Room]
[Please keep quiet]
Thank you.
He's over there.
[Washroom]
Have you noticed the airport police?
Yes.
[First Class &amp; Business Class Only]
Hello.
We've notified the police station
in the airport.
Okay, just a second.
Let me check.
Please make it quick.
Three officers in total, right?
Right.
Please go through security check.
Okay. Thanks.
[Infusion Room]
Wait.
Nurse,
there's much liquid left.
Why...
are you replacing it so soon?
Are you the nurse or am I the nurse here?
Please don't be mad.
I was looking at your watch just now.
How long will it take
to finish this bottle?
About an hour.
[Man]
Officer.
Officer!
What time is it now?
Two o'clock, right?
Please have the nurse remove my IV.
I want to see Chief Zhang.
Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen.
This is a pre-boarding announcement
for Flight ML4420
passengers.
Please have your boarding pass
and identification ready.
Regular boarding will begin
in approximately 10 minutes.
Chief Zhang.
I lied.
What did you lie about?
I didn't kill Ye Jian.
You spoke clearly about the details.
Who else other than you
would have killed him?
I don't know who did it,
but it really wasn't me.
T-The details...
I made them all up.
W-Was I right about them?
But I was just guessing.
You...
I can prove I'm innocent.
From my home...
You know where I live, right?
[Stick to the truth,
follow the law in handling cases]
From my home to Binhe Park,
[Remain committed to strict, fair,
and civilized law enforcement]
one has to pass through Jiefang Road,
right?
Then, leave Jiefang West Road
for the Second Ring Road.
Exit from Xiangcheng Road.
After that, just go straight
to Binhe Park.
Right?
Do you remember this?
On the night Ye died, there was
a joint operation
against drunk driving in the city.
The police set up checkpoints
at all the intersections.
That night,
I was blotto.
There's no way you'd have missed me.
We collected the fingerprints
of two people
on the SUV—
only two.
One was from you;
another one was from Lang Botu.
If you didn't kill him,
would Lang Botu be the murderer?
He's just a kid.
There's no way he'd have
the guts to do this.
Besides,
why would he kill Ye?
Why would he kill Ye?
If you really suspect him,
just ask him to come over for an inquiry.
But I guess it's too late.
His flight has already taken off.
Can we make it?
Yes.
There are 20 minutes left
before it takes off.
That's impossible.
His flight left at 2 PM.
It's been airborne for 40 minutes.
Of course we know you lied.
I also know why you lied.
You were buying time
to cover for your younger brother.
I'm sorry.
We also lied.
[13:40]
It's 1:40 PM now.
Copy that.
Lang Botu.
[Police]
You are suspected of killing Ye Jian.
Please come with me
to the bureau for the investigation.
I am now
arresting you for your suspicion
of intentional murder.
There are too many people.
Come with us.
Go.
Chief Zhang!
Chief Zhang, I... I lied again!
I killed Ye Jian!
I really killed him!
There was a serious traffic jam
that night!
Once I was stuck in traffic,
I just took the alleys
and didn't get checked!
Zhang Yi'ang!
I lied again. Trust me.
Chief Zhang.
Chief Zhang!
Ye Jian...
I killed Mr. Ye.
Tell us more details.
♪ Throw, throw, throw the handkerchief ♪
♪ Secretly put it ♪
♪ Behind the kid ♪
[Lu Yibo]
♪ Everyone, don't tell him ♪
♪ Hurry up and catch him ♪
Bowen, you've got a call.
Bowen!
♪ Throw ♪
Hello?
It's me!
Ye Jian!
Tell me
where you were the night Chief Lu
had his accident.
Ye is our friend. That's true.
But Ye is also a cop.
You broke the law.
Do you think Ye would let you go?
Did you have this watch
on the day Lu Zheng died?
Even though the police
know the watch is mine,
they won't link Lu Zheng's case
to us.
I hired a hitman half a year ago.
Why did you kill him?
Lu Zheng's death
is a good thing for us.
He was the Chief
of the Public Security Bureau!
Ye Jian didn't notice it was me.
He said
the CCTV caught my brother's watch.
At that time, I believed
my brother had killed Lu Zheng.
Let's meet and talk face to face.
Let's meet by the small river
we used to swim in
when we were little.
I'll leave for it right away.
What's that?
I made it
for the robot combat competition.
I had never killed anyone.
So I could only use this method.
Yangyang?
Why is it you?
How come it's you?
Two days ago, Zhou Rong asked my brother
to trade for the phone.
My brother didn't want to go.
Go
a little further later.
Find a payphone
and call the police.
No matter what,
don't tell them who you are.
Tell the police
about the phone deal.
If the police catch those two first,
we'll be safe.
Do you hear me?
No way, Bowen.
Why?
I killed Ye Jian.
What did you say?
I drove and hit him to death.
Do you think I'll let you go
if you say this?
You killed someone. You're amazing.
Yangyang.
Don't joke about this kind of thing.
Why?
I thought you killed Lu Zheng,
and Jian had found out about you.
Which car did you drive to hit him?
The SUV.
Where's the car?
In the parking lot.
Where did you hit him?
By the river
we used to swim in.
What time was it?
11:30 PM.
Did anyone see you?
No.
There were just the two of us.
Lili,
book the earliest flight
to Mankesid for my brother.
Once we book the ticket,
you'll leave immediately.
If anyone asks,
just say you want to go there early
for house rental and other procedures.
Bowen, I can't leave.
You're going to leave anyway.
You're just leaving early.
I can't leave you alone
here.
Why are you staying here?
Waiting to die?
If I leave, what about you?
I'm going to trade for the phone.
Once those two bastards take the money
and get out of Sanjiangkou,
we'll be fine.
What if they don't leave?
-What if the police find out about this?
-Then I'll take the fall for killing him!
No way.
I must turn myself in.
Turn yourself in?
Even if that happens,
I'll be fine.
I'll admit that I killed him first.
When your plane takes off,
I'll change my statement.
I have solid evidence
that it has nothing to do with me.
You'll be
abroad then.
Even if they suspect you,
it'll be too late.
Yangyang.
Our Lang family
has accumulated the merits
to have a college student like you.
I can't let anything happen to you.
I'm sorry, Bowen.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You have a bright future.
Why did you
get involved in this mess?
That's my brother.
I can do anything for him.
When I was 9,
my parents had a car accident
and passed away.
He is
my only family left.
"Sticking together for survival" might be
just an idiom for you guys.
You can say it easily without thinking
about its deep meaning.
But it's different for my brother and me.
You won't understand.
Taking others' lives
to help you stick together for survival
is what I can't understand.
Take him away.
Chief Zhang.
Can I see my brother?
No.
I killed... I killed Ye Jian!
Chief Zhang!
I want to see Chief Zhang!
I killed Ye Jian! I...
Chief Zhang,
I killed Ye Jian. Really.
It has nothing to do with Yangyang.
Please let him go.
I'm begging you.
Chief Zhang,
please.
Stand up.
You will see no one if you don't stand up.
Yangyang!
I'm here!
Yangyang...
-Let's go.
-Go.
Sorry, Yangyang.
I'm sorry.
It's finally over.
What?
I'd like to thank you on behalf
of everyone in the public security system
of Sanjiangkou.
What time is it?
What time is it now?
What's the matter?
Take me to the hospital.
I need an IV.
Let's go.
Be careful.
I'm fine.
[Two months later]
I almost forgot my shoes.
Zhang.
Is it really appropriate for us
to leave quietly?
We came quietly,
just like we're leaving quietly.
Parting is always sad.
We can't leave quietly.
Yi'ang.
Why didn't you tell us you were leaving?
We know everything.
What do you know?
You're transferred back
to the provincial capital.
It hasn't been announced yet.
We know
an amazing detective like you
can't stay in this small place.
Yi'ang,
Sanjiangkou
has been a lucky place for you.
If you agree,
I'll call Director Gao right away
to ask for his permission.
No need.
Yi'ang,
on behalf of all the colleagues
in the bureau,
I want you to stay.
I'm sincerely asking you to stay.
Why does this scene
seem kind of familiar?
Looks like Chief Zhang can't leave again.
A land that doesn't belong to me
is always worth remembering.
Well...
You should know when to quit.
W-What do you mean by this?
[Building 2]
Nothing hurts
more than
an untold story
hidden in your heart.
Congratulations...
On your glorious return
to the Provincial Department.
It's not easy to work
in the Criminal Investigation Corps.
Yes, yes.
[Building 2]
Since you're all here,
let's officially say goodbye.
During the days at Sanjiangkou,
your support
for me at work
is something I will
never ever forget.
Comrades,
see you again someday.
Thank you.
Take care.
Li.
Chief Qi.
You're always welcome to come back.
You are the best partner
I've ever met.
Don't tell Li Qian.
We couldn't have solved
these cases without you.
I'm leaving.
Bye.
Yi'ang.
In a moment like this,
don't you want to recite a poem again?
"If life deceives you,
don't be sad
and don't rush.
Joyful days will surely come."
Chief Qi,
what did Chief Zhang tell you
that made you laugh so much?
It's a secret.
How painful it is
to keep a secret to yourself?
What is Chief Zhang's new position
back in the CI Corps?
It's a secret.
[Another two months later]
[Logistics Service]
Zhang!
Come on in.
You...
Well,
the ink box of the printer.
The ink box.
Thank you.
Come on.
By the way, I brought you a box of tea.
[Liu'an Melon Slices]
You did it on purpose?
Testing me?
Liu'an melon slices.
Thank you.
You're not busy?
Stay with me for a bit.
We've been back
for almost two months, right?
Two months and three days.
Do you want to go back to the front line?
Yes, sure.
But one should build up strength
before making a move
and not rush for rewards.
We should also give young people like you
more opportunities
to grow well.
How have you been?
What cases have you solved?
They're all small cases.
No big ones.
Someone who has solved big cases
is indeed different.
Don't rush.
Wait patiently.
Just like this drinking machine.
The logistics center has one;
CID has one;
the Director's office has one;
the Veteran Cadre Bureau also has one.
It may look ordinary,
but it never slacks off.
Wherever it is,
it will stand still
and always be prepared.
Maybe the position is ordinary,
and the duty is normal,
but this is its mission.
[Police]
As long as the organization needs it,
it can heat up quickly,
giving light in its heart
to the people,
and offering the burning passion
to the public security cause.