It's too lonely to drink alone.
Wanna hang out with me?
No.
I have a boyfriend.
Oh, do you have one?
But he broke up with me.
He's not coming back.
I have to fix this…
I miss him so much,
but I don't know what to do.
Then I wish you can win him back.
Stealing my girl like that?
You think you're hot?
You want some, punks?!
- Come at me!
- I'll get you.
So much for Mr. Hotshot.
P'Toh.
Did you see that?
I didn't go with another guy.
Am I a good boy?
Good boy, your ass!
You wouldn't hurt my brother
if you were actually good!
Please help me, man.
I beg you.
Since I've broken up with him,
I've always missed him.
If I could've turned back time,
I would've done everything better.
I wouldn't have disappointed him.
I wouldn't have loved you like this.
"Love Alert"
(Episode 1)
(Three months earlier)
You can stay if you want.
I'll take a bath.
Let me think.
That smells amazing.
What're you making for me today?
Here.
Why the long face?
You just said it smelled good.
Don't you like it now?
No.
Just the thought of…
some guy taking you away from me
puts me in a bad mood.
Oh, come on.
I'm here all day. Who would I meet?
I'll put a sign out front that says:
“Hands off the owner.
His brother bites.”
Yeah, right.
People will think you're crazy.
I'm serious.
I won't let you date anyone without my permission.
Deal?
Alright…
Just eat up. You'll be late.
See?
Knowing I hate whole oranges,
you juiced them for me.
Who else could I love if not you?
Cheeky.
You didn't let me date, did you?
What about you? You've had many
boyfriends and never introduced them.
It's true I have many,
but they weren't good enough to see you.
I dumped them first.
I'd love to see someone who can handle you.
Will you forget about me
if you really love someone?
No!
I'm not sure about it.
Still, you're not allowed to date.
Wow…
What a gatekeeping.
If you won't let me date,
you'd better take care of
me for the rest of my life.
I thought you'd sleep in.
What's the hurry?
Texting someone else again?
What do you mean?
Someone just texted your phone.
Did you snoop through my phone?
I didn't.
It was on the screen.
Planned to hook up again, didn't you?!
It's just for fun.
No strings attached.
Why so serious?
This is the third damn time!
Do you even know what loyalty is?!
I was like this before we even dated.
Why can't you handle it now?
God damn…
You selfish asshole.
If you can't keep it in
your pants, we're done!
Fine!
Don't come crawling back to me!
You've been broken up
with Run so many times.
When can you stop being a mess?
Look who's talking.
You're not that different.
Don't compare me to a jerk like you.
I date one man at a time.
I break up first, then move on.
Unlike you!
I told him before I dated him
that this is who I am.
Oh, wow.
No remorse at all.
So, it's really over this time?
I don't care at all. You know I never beg.
Can't handle me? Go.
Also,
I've got a new target.
Who?
P'Fah?!
He's a campus heartthrob.
So what?
I'm hot stuff too.
Mark my words,
I'm gonna make Fah mine.
You've got some nerve.
That's me.
Have some nerve like me sometimes.
You're a total asshole.
Just watch me.
Hey!
Have you seen Fah?
Oh, he might be in the building.
Thanks.
Fah,
can I talk with you?
What's up, Amy?
I heard you're single now, right?
Yeah.
The rumor's true. Can I hit on you?
If it's you,
I don't mind.
I'm kinda over guys lately.
Thinking of dating a girl for a change.
Ooh, sounds good.
But I'm not that...
easy.
Not impossible…
if you want to try.
Drop your Line and IG, then.
Some friend you are,
kicking me while I'm down.
That's right, my best friend.
Don't cry.
Teh.
Oh, P'Toh.
You forgot your iPad at home.
Didn't you say you need it?
And you didn't even answer my call.
It seems I turned it off.
Thank you so much, my dearest bro.
Jimmy, my brother, Toh.
Toh, Jimmy.
The friend I keep telling you about.
Hello, P'Toh.
You don't have to be formal with me.
Just saying hi is enough.
P'Toh,
don't believe everything your
brother says. I'm a good guy.
Get defensive already?
Shut up.
Toh?
Fah!
When did you get back?
It's been a while.
I'm busy getting cafe ready at home.
Just come by once it opens. Coffee's on me.
No way. I want to support you.
Oh.
Fah was a freshman in the
union when I was a senior.
Nice to meet you.
Don't need for that. Just call me Fah.
I'm Teh, Toh's younger brother.
I'm Jimmy, Teh's friend.
So you don't remember me?
Looks like it.
You met Fah when you visited
me on campus back in high school.
Guess you've forgotten...
Really?
I remember you.
I knew you studied here but
never ran into each other.
I was here to give Teh his stuff.
Need to head back now.
Appointed with a plumber.
You can use me car.
I can walk back.
I'll walk you to the car.
(Watch on www.kisskh,la to support Admin)
I'm going.
Fah and P'Toh.
They knew each other.
P'Toh and Fah.
Teh,
I'll walk you home today.
Fine.
Let's go.
P'Toh!
Jimmy walked me home,
so I let him in for a bit.
Sorry to bother you.
What are you working on?
Oh, browsing cafe references.
Gonna shower first.
Played basketball. I'm reeking now.
Have a seat.
I'm such a bad host.
I forgot to offer you a drink.
I'll get a glass for you.
I don't mind that at all.
I insist.
I'll make you one of the cafe's
special drinks. Sounds good?
Thank you.
I'll be quick.
What's wrong with the faucet?
Oh, that's your drink.
The water won't run.
Must be the valve acting up again.
Let me take a look.
Please, no.
You're our guest.
I'm the one disturbing you at this hour.
Let me help you.
Well, I'll get the call now.
Hello, Mr. Wet.
Oh, please tell me the total budget.
Yes, thank you. See you.
Where's Jimmy?
Fixing the faucet for me.
What the…
What the hell did you break in my house?
I fixed the faucet for
your brother. All Done.
What was wrong with it?
The valve wasn't tightened.
I took it out and put it back.
I see.
Thanks so much.
You're soaked. Go change first.
It's okay. It'll be dried soon.
You must!
You're soaking wet.
You're not wearing my shirt.
I don't wanna wear yours anyway.
Just the thought of it creeps me out.
I'll lend you one of mine.
Let me find if there's a bigger shirt.
Give me a minute.
Go change in the bathroom.
Just go already!
Thank you!
Just say it.
Don't fall for Jimmy.
Come on!
I don't think of anything.
He's your friend.
Jimmy is a certified player.
He's my friend. Don't ever cross
that line. It's for your own good.
That bad?
I don't want you getting hurt.
Keep your distant from him,
or you're asking for trouble.
Nothing's gonna happen.
You're overthinking.
Everything's delicious.
I'll come by and eat here again sometime.
My house's not a restaurant!
Go eat somewhere else!
Teh,
Jimmy's your friend!
Yeah, P'Toh.
Teh's always so mean to me.
P'Toh,
your food's amazing.
And will open a cafe soon?
Your desserts must be tasty too.
If I come to have your food again,
what should I bring you next time?
You don't have to.
Just come over.
I can't do that. If I eat for free,
I should give something back.
If anything, maybe some Thai desserts.
That's one thing I can't make.
My go-to shop is right across from campus.
But don't get too much.
I don't wanna gain weight.
Roger that!
Enough with the flirting!
You're banned from my house.
Frickin' eat up and go home.
Sue Teh!
Yes, P'Toh. Tell him off.
He's always like this.
You'll hurt your friend's feelings.
(Serves you right.)
What's with the face?
Toh, try this.
You should eat more too.
Come here!
Teh! That hurts!
What's wrong with you?!
I did mean it!
About what?
Banning you from my house.
Why?
I don't want my brother to fall for you.
And I'm also sure you'd hurt him.
You're exaggerating.
My brother is such an…
‘easy target'.
And I know exactly what you're like.
I haven't thought of him that
way at all. You're overthinking.
I'm cutting you off right now.
If you cross the line, you're dead.
Brother-obsessed freak.
Fine.
I promise not to touch your brother.
Catch ya later.
See you at the uni.
Don't fall for Jimmy.
Jimmy is a certified player.
He's my friend. Don't ever cross
that line. It's for your own good.
That bad?
I don't want you getting hurt.
Keep your distant from him,
or you're asking for trouble.
Who falls for him?
Teh was just talking.
Time to sleep.
Jimmy, my brother, Toh.
Toh, Jimmy.
The friend I keep telling you about.
Hello, P'Toh.
You don't have to be formal with me.
Just saying hi is enough.
Teh,
your brother…
is really ‘tempting'.
Zip it properly.
Got everything?
Here.
If I do, I'll just call you to bring it over.
I'm not your rider.
If there's next time, I'll charge you a fee.
Don't forget to tell me
what you want for dinner.
Let me think. I'll tell you later.
I'm heading out.
Focused on studying.
Can't you zip your bag?
Drive safely.
P'Toh!
Oh, Jimmy.
Teh just went out.
I'm not here for Teh.
Thai desserts from your favorite shop.
Thank you so much.
Don't tell me you bought
these just to bring them here.
To thank you for dinner last night.
And…
And…?
Can I have a free cup of coffee?
Oh, sure.
Of course.
Let's get inside the house.
This is exactly my taste.
Tell me when your cafe opens.
I'll be your first regular customer.
I'll call and nag you if you don't show up.
By the way…
That shop opens really early.
It's always crowded
and sells out fast.
What time did you go?
So early.
I'm not a morning person,
but I can…
manage for you.
Your lips have crumps.
You're treating like a kid.
To me, you kind of are.
As adorable as a little kid.
P'Toh,
About the shirt I borrowed,
I'll wash it and bring it back later.
Oh, that's all right.
Anytime's fine.
That's good.
Can I keep it for now?
It smells like you.
How about I keep it for good?
Is it good?
Thanks for buying desserts for me.
It's been a long time. I'm satisfied now.
Please, don't yet.
What?
Don't get over this place too fast.
If you do, what excuse will
I have to come see you again?
Uh…
P'Toh,
you know you're cute when you blush?
It's Teh.
Don't answer him now!
Don't tell him I'm here.
I must work on a presentation
with Teh, but I came to see you first.
I see.
You should head out. I'll call him later.
Well… I'm off then.
Before Teh kicks my ass.
- Bye.
- Bye bye.
Bye bye.
Forgot something, young master?
A rider delivered something,
so I came out to get it.
Don't forget to tell me
what you want for dinner.
Okay.
Fah.
I bought you desserts.
Thank you.
Okay…
See you later.
Hope you enjoy it.
You can have them.
Thank you.
You bastard, Jimmy!
What's your problem, Teh?
Look at this.
What the hell is this?!
It obviously your house's camera.
Don't forget that I'm your
friend who knows your nature.
So what?
I just bought desserts to
thank your brother for dinner.
Didn't I tell you to stay away from my brother?!
- I don't trust you!
- So what?!
- What's your game?! Spit it out!
- I don't have a plan!
You're soaked. Go change first.
I'll lend you one of mine.
Let me find if there's a bigger shirt.
Give me a minute.
(Next Episode) I totally get you for being
protective of your brother.
You should know that I am.
I'm worried about him.
I don't want him to be hurt.
I can't help it. He's so cute.
P'Fah!
Hello.
Still call me ‘P'?
You'll see.
P'Toh.
I have something to tell you.
It's important.