Nanny Zhou!
Why were you being unwilling?
Didn't you hear that?
Mr. Liu is being
promoted to Junior Vice Minister of Revenue.
It's a third-rank official!
Such a good match
should be for my daughter Lan.
Why should Jinzhao take him!
This match only appears good,
nothing more.
How?
That Young Master Liu
is no good.
Only eighteen,
he's already bedded
several maids in his house.
Any girl who marries him will
have nothing but hardship ahead.
I may not have that much
bad blood with Jinzhao.
My dear Mistress!
You're too kind!
Jinzhao didn't go easy on you
when she bullied you.
Besides, Master
only asked you to make the arrangements.
Whether she
actually marries into
that family isn't your call.
It's up to Master and Madame.
Why bother going against Master's wishes?
Haven't you always wanted to
have leverage over Jinzhao?
This marriage
is the best leverage.
Indeed.
Alright,
I'll take this task.
Miss,
as you instructed,
I've secretly checked
everyone in our courtyard.
No holes
found yet.
I'll check again
the carriage house
and the errand office.
Everyone and everything
that's had contact with us,
I'll go it through.
I know,
even if I
find out that lurker,
I can't do much with them.
But at least I'll know
where we stand.
Here comes Lan!
Jinzhao!
Please have a seat.
Someone just came to propose marriage for you!
I was behind the screen
when the matchmaker arrived,
and when I heard
it was for you,
I rushed right over.
They asked the matchmaker to send word
to the Liu family today.
If the Liu find it suitable,
they'll deliver the birth-date betrothal slip!
The Liu family
is an old noble house,
having produced several Jinshi scholars.
If Mr. Liu is promoted
to Junior Vice Minister of Revenue,
that would be another step up.
And Mrs. Liu
is the sister of the Changxing Marchioness.
What kind of person is the boy?
Since Master has chosen him,
he must be a good man.
Am I right, Master?
His father
and I have served together in the Revenue Ministry for years,
so we know each other well.
I've never heard anything wrong
with that boy.
Besides, he's also passed the preliminary exams.
I hear he's even
taken the autumn provincial exam this session.
Busy studying for the exams,
his character
can't be too bad.
Sounds good enough.
Jinzhao has already turned fifteen,
so we should start looking into marriage prospects.
Jinzhao,
what do you think?
So,
the matchmaker
has already sent word to the Liu family?
Yes.
Two families
haven't met for the viewing.
I don't even know what the young Liu
looks like.
Why the rush?
As if I'm the one
rushing to marry him.
That's right.
After all, we're the bride's family.
What's noble being the bride's family?
Jinzhao has just arrived in the capital
and hadn't started socializing yet.
They don't know her at all.
How could they come to propose first?
Besides,
given the Liu family's status,
what's wrong with lowering ourselves a bit?
The real benefit is what counts,
isn't it?
Does my grandmother
know about this?
I just found out myself
and haven't written to her.
She raised me up.
If marriage is being arranged for me,
she should have been told first.
Right.
She is far away in Tongzhou.
Once this matter takes shape,
it's still soon enough
to tell her.
Are you
deliberately
keeping this from her?
What are you talking about?
Since ancient times,
marriage is decided
by parents
and matchmakers.
Your grandmother
just needs to be informed.
Whether she agrees
or not,
she doesn't get the final say.
Oh really?
But I heard that
Grandmother strongly opposed it
when my mother married you.
Your own parents also disagreed.
Yet you insisted
on marrying anyway.
Why didn't you
obey your parents
back then?
You unfilial daughter!
How dare you say such a thing?
Fine.
In any case, this matter
must have Grandmother's consent,
otherwise, I won't agree.
You!
I'll take my leave now.
Ma'am!
I'll go check on
the lunch preparations.
See?
This is your pampered daughter!
I don't think
she's completely wrong.
I should inform my mother first.
There's no rush.
Besides,
arranging a marriage for Jinzhao
right after she came back
is indeed too early.
Too early?
You've seen
how she defies her elders.
Making a scene at her coming-of-age ceremony
was bad enough, but that's
on your Ji family's turf.
The Lin's birthday banquet was such a formal occasion,
and she dared to openly talk back to me in front of everyone!
Which family with a son
would want to
marry her after that?
I tell you,
we must quickly arrange
a match for her before
she causes even bigger trouble,
then she really won't marry off at all!
Talk some sense into her!
Why didn't you try to stop Master?
Enough about him.
This Young Master Liu.
Master thinks highly of him,
but I still don't feel sure.
Have Luo Yongping
go make some inquiries.
Yes, ma'am.
You've never even met Liu Xiancheng.
Why this refusal?
Is it because of
Mr. Ye Xian?
What does that have to do with him?
I'm just saying.
Why does Father
suddenly care about my marriage?
This can't be
that simple.
We need more information
from outside.
What are you doing?
How dare you trespass
on my Miss's grounds?
What are you doing?
Master has ordered
that from today, Jinzhao should
remain in the residence and
may not leave
without his consent.
He's going to ground me?
Miss,
he ordered us to
keep you here no matter what.
Anyone who
let you out without permission
will be beaten and then
taken away by slave brokers.
We're just following orders.
We hope you won't take offense.
You old hag! I...
Miss, why are you stopping me?
Is there any way you can help me get out of here?
Thanks for your help.
But if Father
finds out,
will he punish you?
It's okay.
He's never once
blamed me
since I was little.
You can
take off
Ziling's clothes later.
Take this.
If this match goes through,
there'll be a great reward.
By the way,
when you
see Mrs. Ji,
remember to tell her...
Jinzhao,
your new outfit
is really beautiful.
What fabric is this?
If you like it,
I'll buy you
another bolt.
Thank you, Jinzhao.
Miss Jinzhao.
Miss Lan.
When I heard Mr. Liu took
this session's exam,
I sent someone
to watch near the exam hall.
How one acts when the results are posted
shows a person's true color most clearly.
He's at the Fuchun Teahouse.
What a coincidence.
As you want to inquire about him,
Madame also ordered
me to look into the Liu family,
saying his character comes first.
My mother
also asked you?
Yes. It's only proper
for her to care about
your marriage.
I was
wondering
whether to report to Mrs. Ji,
but the servant
back from Tongzhou said
she had been ill,
so I hesitated.
Grandmother had been ill?
[The head of the family, Mrs. Ji,]
[has had several fires set on her property.]
[Now,]
[before every meal,]
[she must use a silver needle to test for poison.]
Don't tell her just yet.
Yes, Miss.
Let's go inside.
Okay.
Miss,
that's Liu Xiancheng.
Isn't that Chen Xuanqing?
I was wondering why there are so many girls.
Turns out they are here to see him.
Look,
that one looks good
with a pair of dimples.
The one next to her? No.
Doesn't deserve to sit here.
Please be cautious, Mr. Liu.
What's there to be cautious about?
These girls chase you
all the way to the exam hall.
They aren't cautious,
so why should I be?
Mr. Liu,
you've got it wrong.
First, these girls may not
even be here for me.
Even if they are,
they're courteous
and haven't bothered us.
For us to scrutinize them
would violate a gentleman's way.
Moreover,
women already have
a harder time in this world.
Men shoot their mouths off
and move on, but if
those words get out, it could
become a stain
on a woman's name
and no chance for her to defend herself.
We all have sisters.
Put yourself in their place.
Be more cautious.
Fine, fine.
I won't talk.
Mr. Liu, I envy your carefree attitude.
The rest of us are on edge,
yet you still have
romance on your mind.
I wasn't going to pass anyway.
If my mother hadn't forced me,
I wouldn't have come.
No wonder Xuanqing
is so well-liked.
He speaks so convincingly.
Liu Xiancheng,
on the other hand, is just too crude.
Crude? That's putting it mildly.
On results day,
a candidate dares to
act so recklessly
right in front of the exam hall.
Either he's got some backing,
or he's a complete fool.
The results are out!
Let's go!
Xuruo,
let's go down and take a look.
Let's go.
Go, go.
Look!
The results are out!
Take a good look!
That's fast!
Am I included?
Look!
Yes!
Jinzhao, look!
The results are out!
Yes!
Sir,
why are you still here?
Let's go down and take a look!
When the Bingzi provincial exam results
were announced,
Uncle Yanyun was waiting right here.
Today,
I'll wait here too.
Then I'll stay with you.
The 49th place of Yiyou
is Chen Yanwen from Xiheyan Street.
Wanping County,
Shuntian Prefecture.
Elective: The Book of Songs.
Sir!
I passed!
Congratulations!
It's Mr. Chen Yanwen!
Sir, your uncle Yanwen passed!
Shouldn't we congratulate him?
Xuruo,
why did your uncle
also take this exam?
Congratulations!
Mr. Liu,
I'll go congratulate my uncle.
Miss Gu.
Congratulations!
Congratulations on passing it!
Thank you! Thank you!
Congratulations!
Thank you!
Thank you, everyone!
Mr. Jiang found out
the truth about my father's death,
so I brought it to you.
It was
Uncle Yanwen.
That day,
he and my father
met on a bridge.
They argued.
Uncle Yanwen pushed
my father into a pond.
He struggled to the bank
and nearly got out of the water,
but Uncle Yanwen
pried his fingers open
and pushed him off again.
Congratulations!
Congrats!
Sir,
shouldn't we go congratulate?
Never mind,
let's just stay here.
Thank you!
I'll treat you later!
Congrats!
Congratulations!
The 3rd place of Yiyou
is Zhuang Zhengyu
from Xisipailou,
Wanping County,
Shuntian Prefecture.
- Elective: The Book of Documents.
- It's me!
It's me!
I passed!
Congratulations!
Thank you! Thank you!
Only the top two are left.
Liu Xiancheng definitely won't make it.
But there's
still no Chen Xuanqing.
He couldn't have failed, could he?
The 2nd place of Yiyou
is Liu Kezuan
from Xiaowang Town, Gaoyang County,
Baoping Prefecture.
Elective: The Book of Rites.
It's me!
Congratulations!
Thank you!
Congrats!
The 1st place of Yiyou,
with elective:
The Spring and Autumn Annals,
is the one from Xiheyan Street,
Wanping County,
Shuntian Prefecture—
Chen Xuanqing.
Sir! Sir!
It's you!
You're in the first place!
Here's the winner!
Here he is!
Congratulations!
Congratulations to the winner!
Congratulats!
Congratulations!
Sir,
here's
the autumn exam pass list.
Please take a look.
He's being too conspicuous.
Passing is enough.
Why did he aim for the first place?
As for Yanwen,
he doesn't live up to this.
There's nothing we can do about it.
The Shuntian chief examiner
has long wanted your favor.
This time, it just
happens to coincide
that Xuanqing and Yanwen are taking the exam.
Of course he's eager to curry favor.
I've read Yanwen's essay.
Passing or not,
it could go either way.
Thanks to you,
of course he passed.
That's what I'm worried about.
Next spring
he'll surely take the exams.
What if he meets
an ambitious
chief examiner?
Are you worried about him
because of the Fifth Master?
You know Yanwen.
He'll get himself trouble
once he enters officialdom.
What happened?
Sir, the axle is broken.
Can it be repaired?
Yes.
It'll only take a quarter.
Send someone to check
if Lan has finished picking.
If so,
tell her we should go back.
Besides the crate of Wu silk
and the crate of plain gauze
I just picked,
go to Simingzhai
and choose two Song carvings.
And our Linxia House's
new pastries.
Pack them in an eight-treasure box,
and send it to the Chen residence.
Understood?
When giving gifts,
we must send the very best.
Yes, Miss.
[It's Chen Yanyun.]
Can you handle it?
Don't worry, sir.
Congratulations, sir.
I heard Chen Xuanqing
and Chen Yanwen
both passed the imperial exams.
Congratulations.
I've prepared gifts
and had someone
all sent to the Chen residence.
Thank you for your trouble.
Would you like a piece?
This jujube pastry
is made by
our shop's chef.
You can't buy it elsewhere.
Sir,
it's done.
[It's because of his broken carriage.]
That's enough.
Thank you.
[He is so strange]
[and hard to read.]
Miss,
Mr. Chen
seems a bit
unhappy.
You also think so?
Looks like the Chen family
has plenty of secrets.
Look,
don't send those four
I picked.
Just pick four
ordinary ones.
No rush.
Send them quietly
with the rest of their guests.
Yes, Miss.
Why are you
so happy today?
The autumn
exam results came out.
Liu Xiancheng didn't pass.
That makes
this marriage
secure.
No wonder they sent his birth-date
betrothal slip
right over
in the afternoon.
It's because he failed the exam.
People are always like that.
Nothing surprising.
It won't be too late
to marry Jinzhao to him
after he passes the exams later.
He won't pass.
I had people inquire.
This boy
is lecherous.
Young as he is,
he already keeps several chamber maids
and even a mistress outside
for nearly a year.
How can such a person
pass the exams?
Is this match
still worth pursuing?
A man being lustful
is nothing
but a minor flaw.
This boy may be disappointing,
but his father is not.
Word's already out.
The Junior Vice Minister of Revenue
is bound to be his father,
Liu Siyu.
Really?
With this marriage connection,
even if I don't get praised
in this performance review,
at least
a passable rating is safe.
Come on.
Why are you sighing?
What does Mrs. Ji's reply say?
She didn't say it outright.
It's an unsaid understanding.
For now, we should focus on
this marriage arrangement.
The Liu sent over
the birth-date betrothal
slip today.
Mistress Song even asked Madame
for your birth details.
But Madame hasn't given her yet,
saying she needed to think it over.
Once the slips are exchanged,
backing out
would cause
bad rumors.
Anyway, no matter what they do,
I won't ever marry
into the Liu family.
Madame is too soft
and has no real power.
Speaking to her is useless.
Grandmother is ill,
yet she didn't mention it
at all in her letter.
The more she's like this,
the less I should trouble her.
If it really comes down to it,
I'll fight our way out
and back to Tongzhou.
Who cares about the Liu!
Keep that move
for the very end of our rope.
For now,
there are two men who can help.
Who are they?
This Rain of Pear Blossom
Needles devised by
Mr. Xiao is deadly.
If I hadn't been wearing chest armor,
I would be dead for sure.
So I should coat these needles
with a potent poison.
Then I wouldn't need to aim for the chest,
but a scratch
would be fatal.
We'll test it later.
Who to test it on?
Hey!
Sir, don't look at me!
I...
There is actually someone.
Shut up!
Say that again,
and I might not be able to stop myself
from seeking justice
for this horse.
Sir. Master has returned.
He's waiting for you.
Why did you give away
your personal sword?
That
should have been kept for Xian.
Kept for him?
Could he even lift it?
Look at that scrawny frame.
He'll never wield a sword in this lifetime.
I know.
You blame me for not
giving you a son to be a general on horseback.
Dear,
don't be angry.
Come on.
Sir.
Let him know I'm here.
Yes, sir.
Master. Ma'am.
Here comes the young master.
Father. Mother.
I heard you're tinkering with hidden weapons again.
Tricks and gadgets.
Even if you can't ride a horse,
or wield a sword,
you should still learn military texts.
What do we
martial nobles rely on?
Real military merit!
Enough.
First thing first.
His Majesty has appointed you
as the Crown Prince's companion.
Go pack. Tomorrow, you
come with me to the palace.
The Crown Prince's companion?
Why would His Majesty
think of me out of the blue?
Why you?
Because the Office thought you're
at the perfect age.
So you're going.
It's Chen Yanyun.
Listen well.
To accompany the Crown Prince,
you must be careful with
your behavior and learn hard.
Learn what?
Learn whatever you're told to learn!
What about military texts?
You!
- Sir!
- You're asking for trouble!
What are you doing?
Tomorrow morning,
send someone to deliver this letter
to the Changxing.
How can that be?
It's so important.
I'd better deliver it myself.
No need.
Just send anyone.
If the letter doesn't arrive,
send this one
to Ye Xian.
Are you trying to...
Haven't we always wanted to find out
who the lurker is?
Then,
let's lure the snake out of its hole.
Huang?
You have great taste, young lady.
Miss Gu
is grasping at straws.
How could the Changxing heir
ever help with that?
Who knows.
Dispose of this letter, Chen Yi.
Not to send it to
the Changxing as is?
No.
The one she really meant to send
has probably already arrived.
Sorry,
but I don't get it.
Your mole is probably
already blown.
No way!
She's at most gotten
suspicious.
No way she knows who it is!
Then let me ask.
Last time, Miss Gu's letter
to Mrs. Ji
was sealed with wax.
This time, none.
What do you think?
That maid beside Miss Gu
knows martial arts, right?
Maybe she's
already
tailed your men.
Sir, forgive me.
I deserve death for my mistake.
Not quite,
but there are indeed lapses.
Go receive your punishment.
As for those watching Gu Jinzhao.
Pull them back.
Yes, sir.
This Gu Jinzhao
is truly clever.
Clever,
and bold too.
She's scheming against me as well.
You think this letter
was just for Ye Xian?
No way!
She thought you'd
help her too
after reading it?
Would you?
No.
Of course not!
That thought of hers
is just too arrogant.
To you, it's arrogance.
To her, it's an opportunity.
One letter, but shown to two people.
If even one of them agrees to help,
she wins.
Why not do it?
Indeed.
A trades-person's way of thinking
is completely different
from a scholar's.
There are plenty of scholars at court.
If half knew how to do trade,
the treasury wouldn't be so empty.
This Gu Jinzhao
has something of
Mrs. Ji's style about her.
No wonder you wanted
to test her.
Suddenly I feel
it'd be a pity
to withdraw the mole.
What do you mean?
It's been a while
since I've seen you this happy.
It's the driver, Huang.
Huang?
It's actually him?
When we were in danger in the capital,
I saw how quickly he reacted.
I thought it's just because he's skilled.
But thinking back,
he probably knows martial arts.
I gave the letter to the Changxing.
Bodyguard Li,
who serves Ye Xian, told me
Ye Xian has entered the palace
as the Crown Prince's companion
and can't come out
until his rest day,
which means we should wait
at least a month.
A month?
That's too long.
I need another idea.
Qingpu,
go keep an eye on the Liu.
Rest for a quarter.
Bring Frost over.
Here comes Frost!
Frost!
Go catch it!
Stop!
Frost is there!
It's over there!
Go catch it!
Come on!
There!
Over there!
Quick!
Surround it!
Frost!
Come here!
Mr. Ye is so capable.
In just a few days,
you have Frost
completely tamed.
I merely used a trivial trick.
It's honey!
Thank you for the lesson, Mr. Ye.
Your Highness.
Mr. Ye.
You have a letter.
[I wanted to refuse outright,]
[but I hear the Liu family is related to the marquisate.]
[Making a scene would be a small matter,]
[while hurting the marquisate's face is not.]
Threatening me?
What nerve!
Sir, I'll take my leave
if there's nothing else.
Amazing!
That's just so amazing!
His Highness bestows a reward!
It's mine! It's mine!
Quick!
Ye Xian,
look at these scoundrels.
Quick! Whoever grabs it keeps it.
Mine, mine!
What?
Mr. Chen is here?
Mine!
Quick!
Put these away!
Move!
Come here, this way!
Quick, quick!
Put these away!
Over there!
Chen Yanyun, Chief of the Crown Prince's Office
and Lecturer to the Eastern Palace,
requests an audience with His Highness.
Your servant
kowtows to Your Highness.
Rise, Mr. Chen.
I was just reading
Direct Explanations of the Four Books
and recalled that you once said: extending
knowledge comes from the Great Learning,
and innate knowledge comes from Mencius.
I've gained some insight.
Your Highness.
You neglected your studies
and falsified things.
According to the rules,
you should be
punished with three strikes on the palm.
Does Your Highness
have any objection?
N-no.
Good.
Take the tool.
Wait.
What?
What do you want to say?
You saw His Highness playing
and assumed he has neglected his studies.
What you don't know is that
His Highness rose at three,
first studied two hours
with Lecturer Wang,
then continued reading
until afternoon.
Still underage, His Highness
sleeps barely three hours a night.
His workload is far heavier
than that of ordinary scholars.
He just relaxes briefly.
Mr. Chen,
why be so harsh?
His Highness
is the Crown Prince,
not ordinary scholar.
That's the first point.
If His Highness finds
the workload too heavy,
he could simply order me to revise the schedule.
Instead, he hid the truth
from me with his servants' help.
My punishment
is not for playing.
It's for deceiving himself and others.
That's the second point.
Does Your Highness
accept the punishment?
You're right, sir.
I accept the punishment.
Alright. Take the tool.
Wait.
As His Highness's companion,
I can't bear to see him punished.
I'll take the punishment in his place.
Ye Xian.
Mr. Ye
is truly loyal.
But unfortunately,
you're not qualified to take
His Highness's punishment.
As his companion,
your failure to counsel him
already warrants punishment.
The tool!
Crown Prince,
three strikes on the hand.
Mr. Ye,
thirty.
Mr. Ye, forgive me.
Twelve.
Twenty-seven, twenty-eight, twenty-nine.
Thirty.
Mr. ye,
do you admit your fault?
You did this to get back at me
for what I said
at Lin Xianzhong's house, didn't you?
That's why you made me a companion
in the East Palace.
You're really petty.
How about another thirty strikes?
I admit my fault.
What you have taught me today,
I dare not forget.
Your Highness,
it's getting late.
Please go rest
after you catch up on your studies.
Your servant
takes leave.
You're strict with the Crown Prince,
but rarely resorts to physical punishment.
Why the strikes today?
Ye Xian has been in the palace less than three days,
yet the Crown Prince's tricks
are already evolving.
Without a few strikes,
he wouldn't learn the seriousness
and he'd get more and more out of hand.
Actually,
this is also doing Ye Xian a favor.
Unless I'm mistaken,
after those thirty strikes,
Ye Xian will be able to leave tomorrow.
You're not
helping Mr. Ye.
You're helping Miss Gu!
That Madame Liu is so unbearable.
The first time you meet,
she grabbed your hand and wouldn't let go,
keeping going on about figure, eyes, brows, something like that.
Looked like she wanted to touch you already!
She's nothing like
the sister of the Marchioness.
She's just like a slave trader!
Who's tired of living,
daring to badmouth the marquisate?
Sir.
It's just my foolish rambling.
Please forgive me, sir.
Get up.
How did you get in?
Why was there no announcement?
I haven't seen you in days,
yet you've grown bold,
talking to me like this.
I heard you're grounded.
No bother announcing.
I just climbed the wall.
Qingpu, go outside and keep watch.
Yes, Miss.
What are you waiting for?
Serve me some tea.
What tea is this?
Smells bad already.
Never mind.
Back to business.
You don't want to marry into the Liu family?
No.
If my father insists,
even if I have to make a scene,
I'll do it to refuse.
Always making a scene.
You really
don't care about your own face.
For a woman,
marriage is a lifetime matter.
What is face
compared to that?
Look at you.
All you've got left
is this pretty face.
Otherwise, with your terrible attitude,
who would dare to marry you?