( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(Previously)
I really like you.
Would you like to try dating me?
Please help me get back with your brother.
I know.
The one who brought me home was you…
Please give me one more chance.
Time's up, Jimmy.
A guy like me never begs.
That dentist customer already
asked P'Toh to be his boyfriend.
Do you still want to be with me?
Of course I do.
My answer is "yes."
"Love Alert"
(Episode 9)
Toh, you should try this.
How is it? Good?
Yes, it's good.
See? I told you to trust my taste.
Next time, I'll take you
to more great places.
Try this one too.
Toh?
Toh...
Yes?
Is something wrong?
Nothing's wrong.
Let's just keep eating.
Why does it have to hurt this much?
So, Toh.
Where do you see yourself
in the next two years?
Nothing big, really.
I just want to grow the café and take care
of Teh until he can stand on his own feet.
So, your life is only about the cafe
and your brother right now?
P'Freeze, please don't take it that way.
I was talking about my life as of right
now.
As for us, I'd like to take things
slow and get to know each other better.
I get it.
But... why the sudden question?
I felt like I was in a job interview.
Well, in two years, I have
to study abroad in England.
I just wanted to know what your plans are.
And... is there any possibility that...
you'd move there with me?
Hey... if you don't have
an answer yet, that's totally fine.
I know how much you
care about the café and Teh.
Let's wait until the time comes.
Please don't be mad at me.
I'm not mad.
I'm just...
a little surprised.
I didn't expect things to move this fast.
Like I said,
I still want to take my time with you.
I don't want to rush into anything.
I understand.
I'm terrible, aren't I? We've only been together
for a day and I'm already being so impatient.
I would never hurt you.
You're too precious...
And yet...
so tempting to break.
I messed up.
Please give me one more chance.
Time's up, Jimmy.
I love you, P'Toh!
He told us he ended it
because he was bored.
A guy like me never begs. And I've
never fallen in love with anyone either.
Did you ever really love me?
What is going on in your mind, Jimmy?
I don't have any water.
Want a beer?
Jim... you really love him that much?
I didn't thought so either…
that I'd love P'Toh this much.
Run...
I'm so sorry.
For everything I did to hurt you.
I was a total jerk.
It's okay. That's all in the past now.
No matter what, Jimmy...
you were the best love I ever had.
Can we be together again?
I can't love anyone else anymore, Run.
It's only P'Toh.
But he doesn't love me anymore.
I miss him so much.
What am I supposed to do?
I'm such an asshole.
P'Toh, I heard you're dating
Dr. Freeze. I'm so happy for you.
P'Toh…
are you sure it's what your heart wants?
Teh, I told you to stay back and let him
be.
I want to give P'Freeze a chance.
And more importantly,
I want to give myself a chance too.
That's good then.
I just want you to be happy.
Toh!
I'm here.
See you guys later.
Wanna check on your best friend?
I'll leave him be.
Some scars just need to heal on their own.
Fah!
I'm done with my exams!
How was it?
At least… I didn't leave the paper blank.
So, no expectations, no disappointments.
Let's have a vacation.
Can we go to Taiwan?
Sure. I've been wanting
to go there for a photoshoot.
You're the sweetest.
Jimmy,
Are you still drinking during finals week?
I ran out of water at home.
Are you back with Run?
No... I'm not.
I just checked on Jim.
He looks like total crap.
But he insisted that
he's not back with Run.
Are you sure he's not lying?
You're being way too hard on him.
I can't help it. Your
friend hasn't been nice.
And besides, you're always taking his side.
I'll only believe it when I
hear it from his ex's mouth.
P'Fah. Teh.
So, that's everything. I tried to get back
with him, but he wouldn't give me a chance.
And you came to us because you
want our help to get back with Jimmy?
No. I just want Jim to be himself again.
He truly, deeply loves P'Toh.
Toh,
take a break. I bought you some porridge.
Eat it before taking your meds.
Thank you, P'Freeze.
You shouldn't have gone to the trouble.
Don't mention it. I also got you
some vitamins and medicines.
I noticed your cabinet
was missing some of these.
Yes, P'Freeze. Thank you so much.
And about these household supplies...
the ones you're using aren't great.
I bought better ones to replace them. They're
more expensive but much higher quality.
If you need anything,
don't hesitate to tell me.
Eat up, Toh. I'll go put these
away at your house for you.
Teh told me he'd prepare my meds,
but why did he leave them here?
Serves Jimmy right.
He had a gem but couldn't keep it.
Now, P'Toh is so happy with Dr. Freeze.
Happy?
I don't think so.
I can feel he's not happy.
He was forcing that smile.
It's nothing like when he was with Jim.
Are you taking his side again?
Can't you remember what he did to P'Toh?
I remember. But I believe everyone
deserves a second chance.
Not just Jim, but P'Toh deserves
to give his own heart a chance too.
How did you become so wise?
It's because I'm in love.
And besides, he's my own flesh and blood.
How could I not know
how my own brother feels?
What?
A hug?
What's gotten into you?
Please?
Encouragement.
What are you doing?
Give me some love.
You pervert.
Want me to stop?
I know…
I should love myself more.
But the person I love
doesn't love me anymore.
If I'm not drunk...
I can't stop missing your mom.
I think this cream is better for you.
It's for sensitive skin.
I noticed you've been having trouble
sleeping, so I got you this pillow spray.
Lavender aroma. It helps you with sleeping.
It's a natural essential oil.
Sleep well.
And don't forget your meds, my champion.
Oh,
whose is this?
Aren't you supposed to be happy… Toh?
You're early, P'Freeze.
Here's your coffee.
Thank you.
Thanks for stopping by.
Actually…
I have something to talk to you about.
What is it?
It's about Jimmy.
He's in a really bad shape.
He pretends like he's
okay in front of others,
but inside, he's completely shattered.
I've never seen him this broken before.
Why are you telling me this?
My relationship with him… is over.
There's no…
going back for us.
Not even as friends.
Isn't this what you wanted?
Now you can get back together with him.
It takes two to tango.
I tried, but he won't let me in.
His heart belongs only to you.
That day at his house...
it was just concern between friends.
I could never come between you two.
Never.
But... I have a boyfriend now.
I know.
But I'm telling you this…
because I thought you might
have a way to make him feel better.
At least...
you two loved each other.
Saensee, my boy.
Let Daddy find you something to eat.
Are you hungry?
Meow, meow, meow…
Want some treats?
It's all my fault.
I didn't take good care of him.
I love you, P'Toh.
Please come back to me.
Excuse me!
If it's not too much to ask,
could you tell me more about Toh's ex?
Did Run really go talk to P'Toh for me?
Yeah.
He talked to me and
Fah before heading there.
I thought you asked him to do it,
but looking at your face now,
I know I was wrong.
I truly love your brother.
But he has someone new now.
I don't want to cause any more trouble...
for anyone.
The only thing I can do is… accept it.
You've really changed, Jimmy.
Acting like a decent human being.
If you'd acted like this from the start,
you'd probably be happy with him by now
instead of moping around like a lost puppy.
It's too late.
No matter how much I improve...
I can't compete with his new guy.
I'm nothing…
compared to him.
Toh.
P'Freeze.
You bought so many things.
Picanha and some red wine.
I'm making you steak tonight.
What's the occasion?
It's our two-month anniversary.
I'll… make you a steak in your house.
Okay.
Aren't you going to fight for him?
Are you giving up that easily?
What do I even have to fight him with?
Your sincerity, determination,
"never give up" attitude, anything.
Have you tried talking to him how you feel?
Even Run went out of his
way to speak up for you.
I'm going to see P'Toh.
I'll ask for one last chance.
Here, Toh.
Take this.
Thank you.
So,
how's my cooking?
It's good.
Toh,
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
I got the scholarship to study in England.
Come with me, Toh.
Hey, Jimmy. I'll drive you home.
It's okay. I want to be alone.
Jimmy…
But... I thought you said it
would be in another two years.
Why is it so sudden?
Well, the scholarship results just came in.
I'll have to return as
a professor afterward.
I was hesitant at first,
but a teaching career is very stable.
But...
I don't think I'm ready.
I understand. It probably feels
like everything is moving too fast.
We can learn more about
each other over there.
It'll be just the two of us;
our relationship will be even stronger.
And I'm not asking you to go
because I'm jealous or possessive.
I trust you.
I'm just afraid I won't be
able to stand missing you.
Come with me.
P'Freeze…
let's break up.
Why, Toh?
Did I say something wrong?
Did I do something to hurt you?
Not at all, P'Freeze.
You are a good man.
You're decent.
The best man I've ever met.
But...
I can't keep forcing myself anymore.
I'm so sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I'm just so afraid of hurting
a good person like you.
It's okay.
I understand.
Can you look after the café for a bit?
- Of course.
- I'm not feeling very well.
I'm going to lie down for a moment.
No problem, P'Toh. Go get some rest.
Oh, and if P'Freeze shows up,
please come get me.
Will do.
Welcome. What can I get for you?
A hot Americano to go, please.
Coming right up.
(Next Episode)
P'Toh broke up with Dr. Freeze?
It was P'Toh who ended it himself.
Do you think he'll go back to Jimmy?
Why would I go back to
someone who never truly loved me?
From now on,
I'm only going to love myself.
Jim isn't doing any better
than P'Toh right now.
Since he heard that P'Toh might move to England
with the doctor, he's completely shut himself in.
I'm scared he might do something reckless.