[The Epoch of Miyu]
[Episode 21]
Mr. Ji, you didn't call me out
just to accompany you
to pick up a teacup, did you?
You gave me the tea.
So it's only right to ask your opinion
on what kind of teacup
would be suitable.
By the way,
how's your hand
doing after earlier today?
It's fine.
It's getting late.
Just walk me this far.
It's not much further ahead.
-I can walk back by myself.
-It's okay.
It's just a few steps.
You really don't have to.
What happened that night...
It was an accident.
Wasn't it?
Yes,
it was an accident.
And on top of that,
I was running a fever.
Could barely stand.
So...
I accidentally...
I just want to say sorry to you.
I caused you
too much trouble that night.
It's fine.
Let's forget about it.
Okay.
Let's forget it.
It's getting late.
I'll go back now.
Get some rest.
Okay.
Good night.
♪ A flicker of dim light ♪
♪ A bowl of warm soup ♪
Miyu.
Now, do you still want
to start a new relationship?
♪ People in the city ♪
♪ Squeezing into the hustle and bustle ♪
Maybe it's because we've been through
so much together at work.
♪ The palms of time ♪
Or maybe it's because he's helped me out
so many times.
♪ Grinding away the simple days ♪
I admit.
I have fallen
for this man.
♪ Sprinkling them into this busy world ♪
In the past,
I wouldn't have hesitated
to see where it went.
♪ To be tasted, bit by bit ♪
But now?
♪ Embracing this radiant world ♪
I've just got out of
a failed marriage
and been back at work.
♪ Keeps the heart from fading to grey ♪
I still have a huge debt to pay.
Love
♪ Life's joy, sorrow, cold, and warmth ♪
isn't going to be the cure to my life.
[Purong Hotel Staff Apartment]
♪ Intertwined within the mundane ♪
♪ Let us bravely gather up ♪
♪ The forgotten past ♪
♪ There may be regrets ♪
♪ There may be loneliness ♪
[Charoro]
It doesn't matter.
Let's forget about it.
[Charoro]
[Haven't been in touch for a while.
I guess you haven't changed your number.]
Haven't been in touch for a while.
I guess you haven't changed your number.
[I'm glad you're back.
Let's meet up sometime.]
[Jiang Zhichun]
I'm glad you're back.
Let's meet up sometime.
[BBQ]
Ma'am.
Is everyone here?
They're waiting for you.
In the back.
I'll take you there.
This way, please.
There are others?
All the way in the back.
Got it. You go ahead.
[Spicy]
Who's it?
Mr. Guo,
I've invited her here.
You should do the talking.
Chef Li,
all those problems
in the Chinese restaurant—
I didn't cause them on purpose.
But
I didn't do anything to stop it.
I failed in my duty.
I, Guo Luda, cannot shirk the blame.
Of course,
bringing this up now
seems a bit like beating a dead horse.
But these are truly my honest thoughts.
When the Chinese restaurant opened,
I really didn't swap the cured pork.
I'm not well-educated,
but I know right from wrong.
If I had done something like that,
my late master wouldn't
forgive me, even in heaven.
Chef,
my brothers and I here
are neither Chef Jia's men
nor Wei's men.
We all
studied under Zheng Shuolin,
the great Huaiyang cuisine master.
We started from
small family restaurants,
got bought out by Purong Hotel,
and stayed on in the kitchen.
We earned our place here with real skill.
I hope you can see that.
Let's go in and sit.
There are still many things you don't know
that they want to tell you.
Then take a seat, chefs.
Ma'am.
We'll take 200 lamb skewers first.
Okay, coming right up.
Cheers.
[Purong By Your Side]
Come in.
Ms. Yang,
you're looking for me?
Ms. Xu,
you applied
for the career direction
assessment test, right?
Yes.
But I'm not qualified
to take this test yet, right?
The general manager's office
has reformed the employee
development system.
Employees who‘ve been here
for less than a year
are now also entitled to know
their career potential.
I called you here
just to let you know
that you can take the test anytime.
That's great. Thank you.
[Purong Hotel
Career Direction Assessment Test]
The test will take about
45 to 60 minutes.
[Work order]
[Expenses] [Expenses Items]
[Your Authority (yuan): ]
Just try to stay relaxed
while you're completing it.
[Work time]
Thank you.
[Name: Xu Miyu]
Purong represents a classic style of life
[Purong Hotel]
and a kind of top-level dignity.
But
at its core, a hotel
exists to serve its guests
and the people who live in this city.
So,
what's important
is stay connected with current trends
and promote the Purong lifestyle
to more guests.
True.
Adding items that interest customers
does help boost revenue.
So,
colleagues from sales—
[Customer Repurchase Intention Survey]
We're planning to launch a new package
for the 520 promotion.
Ms. Xu,
there's noise in Room 1810.
[Customer Repurchase Intention Survey]
The guest next door
has already complained.
I'll be right there.
Look.
Miyu.
These are my old friends.
None of us have anything to do now.
so we're just
having fun.
Daniel,
I understand what you want to do,
but
the hotel is a semi-public
place after all.
Other guests are already complaining.
So if you want to rehearse together,
you probably can't do it
on the executive floor
It is a bit disturbing.
But where can we go?
Let me figure this out.
Watch out for the uphill.
Here we are.
Come.
Come on.
Be careful.
Look.
This place
doesn't have many people around.
There are warehouses on both sides,
so it won't disturb anyone's work.
It's perfect for your rehearsals.
Also,
I've prepared power strips and chairs.
There is a clothes rack here
for you to hang your clothes.
Miyu.
Fantastic.
How's it, old friends?
Great.
Good.
This is outrageous.
You secretly moved
a band with an average age of over 70
[Purong Hotel]
to the basement warehouse.
What were you thinking?
I know that place has no windows
and poor ventilation.
So I agreed with them
that daily rehearsals
can't exceed one hour.
If any accidents happen within that hour,
how do you plan to handle it?
I'm sorry.
I’ll go find another place.
Why didn't you ask me for help?
Forget it.
Bring the seniors out first.
From now on,
don't let guests
use that storage room without my approval.
Help me check
all the currently available
empty spaces in the hotel.
Soundproof
and well-ventilated.
Ms. Xu just left with a long face.
Thank you.
Did you pick on her again?
[Purong Hotel]
Who picked on her?
Wait.
Is there something
going on between you two?
Just get to the point.
Mr. Zheng from the Lusia University
Alumni Association
will be here soon.
He wants to go over
the activity flow
for the 60th anniversary reunion.
Isn't it basically settled?
They want to add a small request.
They said they'd like
to look for the old Shanghai vibe.
Should we put on a cheongsam show
or a medley of classic old songs?
If we really turn the banquet hall
into old Shanghai style,
then we will
have to spend more money.
And we might
mess it up.
It's too hard.
Old man.
Take one more step. I dare you.
I've told you many times.
Daniel,
my colleagues
from the Engineering Department
are just doing their job.
The main issue
is this place is too risky.
The hotel cannot bear this responsibility.
What responsibility?
To put it bluntly,
you're afraid we'll die here,
right?
Drawing a conclusion
without considering probability—
that's a bit rogue.
Daniel, calm down.
The hotel has its concerns,
but it's mainly to ensure
the health and safety of the guests.
Ji Feng told you to say this, right?
Go ask him. I helped him
fix the Chinese restaurant's design,
and now he turns his back on me?
If he's got the guts,
let him come kick us out himself.
It's a misunderstanding.
Definitely a misunderstanding.
Look,
it's too stuffy here,
and the air quality is poor.
Ms. Xu and I discussed it.
Right next
to
the restaurant on the second floor,
we've set aside a space
just for you to rehearse.
If you're willing
to move upstairs,
no one
will ever bother you again.
You can focus on
practicing.
Really?
How about we go and have a look first?
-See if you like it.
-Yes.
That's fine.
We can take a look.
I'll take you up.
Come on.
Come.
Please.
Not bad.
What do you think?
The environment here isn't the best yet,
But don't worry,
we'll keep improving it.
But...
nothing comes for free.
Are you
asking me for another favor?
As expected,
I can't hide anything from you, Mr. Tan.
I do have something
that I hope you can help with.
Tell me.
The alumni reunion of Lusia University
is going to be held at our hotel.
The attendees are all
elderly people.
And what they want to hear the most
are the claasic
old Shanghai jazz tunes
from their younger days.
That's exactly
the kind of music you love to play.
And you guys are here
at our hotel at the same time.
So,
maybe it's fate.
That's good.
Great.
It's fate.
Ms. Xu.
I didn't discuss this
with you beforehand.
Mr. Ji, you don't need
my opinion for any decision you make.
Besides, this is my job.
I didn't do it well.
I'll go back and reflect on it.
Don't say that.
Meeting the guests' needs
is your responsibility.
Supporting you is mine.
I mean—
a superior supporting a subordinate.
I have something else to do. I'll...
No matter what happens,
I hope you won't avoid me.
I'm your superior.
I will take responsibility for you.
You can trust me a little more,
okay?
I've said what I needed to say.
Coming?
According
to the data from our
Business Management Department,
the Chinese restaurant's revenue
has hit a new high
in the first week since it  opened.
The occupancy rate of
HSKP Department is also steadily climbing—
far beyond our projections.
That's enough of the good news.
Next, let's have
Mr. Xue
brief us
on tomorrow's reception work.
The number of the alumni group tomorrow
is over 100.
Among them,
there are 68 seniors
who are over 80 years old.
We need to accommodate their needs
as much as possible.
For example,
the lighting and ventilation
in the guest rooms,
and the guests' dietary preferences.
If necessary,
we can provide some medical services.
Hello.
I'd like to check in.
You'd like a south-facing room, right?
Yes.
Let me check for you.
[Room Status Center]
[Executive Room 1812]
He...
checked out?
♪ A flicker of dim light ♪
♪ A bowl of warm soup ♪
♪ People in the city ♪
♪ Squeezing into the hustle and bustle ♪
♪ The palms of time ♪
♪ Grinding away the simple days ♪
♪ Sprinkling them into this busy world ♪
♪ To be tasted, bit by bit ♪
♪ Embracing this radiant world ♪
♪ Keeps the heart from fading to grey ♪
♪ Life's joy, sorrow, cold, and warmth ♪
♪ Intertwined within the mundane ♪
Room service.
♪ Let us bravely gather up ♪
♪ The forgotten past ♪
Good morning, Mr. Ji.
♪ There may be regrets ♪
Hello, Mr. Ji.
I am the 10th-floor forewoman.
♪ There may be loneliness ♪
Feel free to call me if you need anything.
Thank you.
[Lusia University Alumni Association
Anniversary Reunion]
[Alumni Association of Lusia University]
[60th Anniversary of Establishment]
The car to the airport
has already left.
Why go to the airport?
Sorry.
My mistake.
Go on.
Two shuttles each
in the morning and afternoon.
That should guarantee
none of the guests
from the Lusia Alumni Association
wait more than
half an hour at the airport.
What's wrong?
Moving rooms got you feeling sentimental?
Not at all.
Just make do for a few days.
Once the alumni association leaves,
I'll give 1812 back to you right away.
I'm fine staying anywhere.
By the way,
has the car to the airport left yet?
Mr. Ji,
what was I just reporting to you?
I... I asked the wrong question.
I meant to ask about
the banquet hall.
16 tables, 182 people.
By the way, Mr. Ji.
How many alumni are coming
to reunion again?
Mr. Ji,
who exactly is on your mind?
No one.
I stayed up late last night
and didn't sleep well.
My brain is a bit slow.
You're just being stubborn.
As your senior,
let me give you a little piece of advice.
When your heart starts churning,
just think of Duan Aoxiang
staring you down.
And think about
the cutthroat competition in the industry.
Works pretty well.
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
I'm going out for a bit.
Mr. Ji.
What is it?
Mr. Ji,
I'm here to deliver
the candidate materials
for the front office lobby manager.
Isn't Anna about to take maternity leave?
Director Bai said
we need to fill
the lobby manager role quickly.
[Employee Internal Promotion
Application Form]
[Lusia University Alumni Association
Anniversary Reunion]
Put it here.
A little further forward.
Let me help you.
Thanks, but I'm fine.
Help me with the luggage.
Okay. This way, please.
[Alumni Association of Lusia University]
Jialing!
[60th Anniversary of Establishment]
You're back too!
My old deskmate!
I've missed you so much!
Meilan,
it's been so many years.
I'm so happy today.
I'll take you to see Wang.
He's been waiting for us all morning.
Okay.
It's been so many years.
Hello.
Your room is on the third floor.
The elevator is over there.
Just walk in that direction.
Welcome.
Why is there
such a long line at the reception?
Clear it out quickly.
Open another line here.
Copy that.
The reception is short of staff.
We need help.
Xu,
the reception is short of staff.
Come help with the check-in.
Okay.
Ms. An,
are you okay?
You go
and turn on the check-in system first.
I need a moment.
Okay.
Ms. Xu.
Do you have
a printed list of executive floor guests?
All the guest lists are here.
Look for yourselves.
We'll go blind reading this.
Ms. Xu,
-I'll go back to the executive floor.
-Wait.
I have a digital copy here.
We'll print it ourselves.
Give it to me.
Ms. An.
Ms. Xu,
that's thoughtful of you.
You don't look well.
Go rest for a while.
I'm fine.
Thanks for your help.
Be careful.
Let me do it.
Okay.
Everyone,
you can check in here too.
Welcome.
Help me find the materials.
Please show your ID.
No, this is too slow.
Huanhuan, lend me your microphone.
Xiaoyan, microphone.
Dear guests
of the Lusia Alumni Association,
hello, everyone,
welcome to Purong Hotel.
Next, the guests whose names I call,
please bring your passports
and come to me.
I will take everyone upstairs
to check in, okay?
First, Ms. Fu Meilan.
I'm here.
This way.
This way, please.
Mr. Jing Zekai.
Here.
Ms. Qin Jialing.
M-My passport is in this suitcase.
In the suitcase.
It's fine.
Who put this on top of it?
Wait a moment.
It's okay.
Okay.
Oh, really.
I've got it.
[Qin 1802]
Please go upstairs and check in first.
The bellman will bring your luggage
to your room later.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Please follow me this way.
Okay.
Next,
Mr. Xiao Qiankun.
Hello, welcome to our hotel.
Ms. An,
what's wrong?
Ms. An! Ms. An!
Ms. An!
-Ms. An!
-What’s wrong?
Ms. An!
Lay her flat.
What should we do?
Well, Director Bai isn't here either.
Call an ambulance!
Right, call an ambulance.
Ms. An.
It'll be fine.
The ambulance will be here soon.
Hello, 911?
This is Purong Hotel.
A pregnant woman just fainted.
Okay. Okay.
[Ambulance]
Excuse me!
Careful.
Which one of you is going with her?
I'll go.
Don't.
You stay...
to take care of the guests for me, okay?
None of you need to come.
Xiaoyan,
call my husband
and ask him
to take my mom to the hospital.
Okay.
Okay. Come on. Please make way.
-Come on.
-Excuse me.
Come on. Give me a hand.
Let's go.
Xiaoyan,
go to the Front Office
and get all the receptionists
who are available
from other shifts.
Fill in these empty spots.
Once the pressure
at the reception eases up,
the main hall won't be a mess.
Go quickly.
Hello?
Next group of executive floor guests,
please follow me.
Okay. This way.
This way, please.
Okay, thank you.
Young man,
excuse me,
is there a pharmacy nearby?
Pharmacy?
I really don't know.
You can ask at the information desk.
Information desk?
Right.
Xia.
Come here.
What's wrong with that gentleman?
He asked where the pharmacy is.
I don't know either.
I'm going up first.
Go ahead.
Hello.
How can I help you?
Where is the information desk?
Are you looking to buy medicine?
Yes.
How did you know?
I need
to get some diabetes medication.
Please wait a moment.
See if any of these
are what you need.
This one.
Okay, I'll place the order now.
It should be delivered
in about half an hour.
Is that okay?
Okay. Great.
I'll have it delivered to your room.
Room 817.
Okay, got it. Thank you.
Thank you.
Xiaoxi, come help me
move this over there.
Let's go.
It's a bit heavy.
Okay.
There's someone behind.
Madam,
I really don't know the answer to this.
I'm just here to enter your information.
If you have any questions,
please go to the information desk.
There's a long line behind you.
Hello?
Guests with questions,
please come to the information desk.
Come, this way.
Please move over there.
Thank you.
Excuse me,
could you get me a cup of hot water?
Sure.
[Passport]
Thank you.
Xiaoyan.
You scared me.
Sorry about that.
What's wrong?
Can you help this gentleman
check in first?
Mr. Jiang Zhongchen
has a herniated lumbar disc.
He needs to lie down immediately.
I can't do that.
Ms. Xu, we have to go in order.
But it's what the guest needs.
Listen to me.
Just ignore him.
Tell you what.
I'll take him to the executive floor
and find a place for him to rest.
Let me know when it's his turn.
Hello, this way please.
Let me carry this for you.
This woman loves showing off too much.
Ungrateful.
Are you the manager?
How can I help you?
Could you please check
if my room faces the sun?
Luo Qingping,
please take this gentleman
to the executive floor,
find him an empty room,
and send me the room number.
Okay.
-You can follow her.
-This way, please.
Okay, thank you.
You're welcome.
Let me check for you.
Okay. I have rheumatism in my legs.
My doctor says I need
to get sunlight every day.
So I'd like to switch
to a south-facing room.
Do you remember which receptionist
checked you in?
The one in the middle.
Right there.
Okay, give this to me.
Please wait a moment.
Okay.
Enjoy your stay.
Thank you.
Xiaoyan.
Why is it you again?
Could you help this lady
switch to a south-facing room?
Go find someone else.
These computers are connected.
You're so fast.
It'd be easy for you to switch it.
I'm fast,
but it's not to clean up your mess.
If you don't know the job,
don't play the hero here.
Hello, please show me your ID.
Please give me a corner room.
I don't sleep well,
so I want it to be quiet.
I'm sorry, sir.
We don't have a room
that meets your needs right now.
You could try swapping
with another alumnus after you check in.
Wait a moment.
Excuse me, may I see your room card?
I might have a guest here
who can swap rooms with you.
Okay.
Please follow me.
Your rooms have been swapped.
This one,
1119, is facing the sun.
This one, 1126, is a corner room.
You can go upstairs to rest.
I'll go over there
and swap your information.
Okay.
Xiaoyan,
please swap the guest information
for rooms 1119
and 1126.
Got it.
Tell them to come over
for facial recognition.
Okay.
Attention, everyone.
When I call your name,
please come over here
to take a photo
and get your passport and room card.
First, Mr. Zhang Mingyuan.
Wait here a moment.
Ms. Wen Yan.
Mr. Wang Zhifan.
Mr. Ma Zhendong.
Okay, please follow me
to do facial recognition here.
Hello, could you tell me
where the elevator is?
The elevator is this way.
Okay. Please come and register too.
Hello, where's the restroom?
There's one this way,
and also one over there.
Both ones will do.
Why was the information desk
moved here?
Ms. Xu asked me to move it.
She said there are a lot of guests today,
most of them elderly,
and they have trouble walking.
Moving it here makes it easier for them,
and we can also help out the reception.
Okay.
Hello.
Two of us have officially checked in.
I was wondering if...
Xu Miyu? Is Xu Miyu here?
Here.
Okay.
You're delivering medicine, right?
Okay, thanks.
What kind of medicine?
I don't know.
Ms. Xu ordered it.
I'll ask her to come get it now.
I'll take it to her. It's on my way.
Okay.
Mr. Ji.
Is there anything you need?
Just checking in on the elderly
guests.
How's your new room?
It's only for a few days. I can make do.
Once the event is over,
I'll move back.
So you moved rooms to make space
for the Lusia University
Alumni Association?
What else?
Makes sense.
[Rest early after taking the medicine.]
Your delivery from downstairs.
Thank you.
Are you feeling okay?
I-I bought medicine for a guest.
It's fine.
[Lusia University Alumni Association
Anniversary Reunion]
Finally done.
I'm exhausted.
I'm so hungry.
Let's go eat.
[Purong Hotel]
Let's go eat!
Good job.
Thank you.
What are you guys eating?
Director Bai, what took you so long?
His daughter is sick. Haven't you heard?
Director Bai, how's your daughter?
Has her fever gone down?
She finished her checkup and went home.
Fortunately, it's not
mycoplasma or adenovirus.
You must have been so worried
about your daughter.
It would be a lie to say I wasn't.
But while I was in the hospital,
I kept thinking about you guys.
Over 100 people checking in at once,
most of them elderly.
You've all worked hard.
You did a great job today.
Everything went smoothly.
I'm starving.
Why is there only one left?
Did I take someone's meal?
What are you talking about?
You're our leader.
Of course there's a box lunch for you.
Sorry, Ms. Xu.
We didn't get enough box lunches.
Go to the cafeteria
and see if there are any left.
I feel so bad.
How about I order you some takeout?
No need.
I'm not hungry.
Ms. Xu, you can have mine.
You've been busy all day.
It's fine. You eat it.
Hurry up and eat.
Eat more.
Mr. Ji.
You haven't had dinner yet, have you?
Here.
I have food.
I accidentally ordered extra.
It'd be a waste not to eat it.
Thank you.
Take care of yourself.
Ms. Xu,
Room 1801 is looking for you.
Copy...
Eat first.
Yin Xiang, go to Room 1801.
Copy that.
[Purong Hotel]
Starting tomorrow,
the lobby will be short a manager.
If you don't decide soon,
Bai Yongjun will come crying to you.
What do you think of her?
[Employee Internal Promotion
Application Form]
What do you think?
I think her abilities are average.
She has some authority among those
young receptionists,
but when it comes to
professional and leadership skills,
she's definitely not qualified.
If Xu Miyu hadn't
been backing her up
with the elderly group today,
she couldn't have handled it on her own.
Do you have any other candidates in mind?
[Purong Hotel]
If we want to be fair,
external recruitment would be the fairest.
But we simply don't have the time.
Maybe we should just go with Lu Xiaoyan.
Consider it a favor to Bai Yongjun.
After all, she's
his strong recommendation.
Do you have someone in mind?
Take a look at this.
[Career Direction Assessment Report]
This person's assessment data
is quite impressive.
A natural for the hotel industry.
Bound to go far.
Who's this?
Xu Miyu.