=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 36=
So you were prepared all along.
He Simu!
He Simu,
you and your father enslaved us
with the Decrees all along.
Now, you don't have the Lantern.
How can you still restrain us?
Without the Lantern,
you're not the Sovereign of Spirits.
Then the throne
is available to anyone.
It's not a throne
unless I sit on it.
With or without the Lantern,
I am the Sovereign of Spirits.
But without the Lantern,
the Void will never be at peace.
Simu,
did you really give it to Yan Ke?
Without the Lantern,
you and I are peers.
Come on.
Let me sit on it.
That explains it.
Yan Ke issued an edict
to the 24 Temples,
calling for surrender
in the name of the Lantern.
He even sent puppet spirits
to attack Fusang Tree
and mess up the Void.
Luckily, you set up a formation
to seal the exit of Fusang Tree.
My father left this formation.
It was meant to stop the spirits
who didn't want to obey the Decrees.
It's controlled by spirit power.
From this day on,
I'll take command of the Void.
Apart from me,
spirits may enter but never leave.
I have such great power.
Why can't I make you
accept me as your master yet?
Yan Ke cornered the Sovereign like this.
He is
also a tough one.
I sent lords of Shaoling Temple
and Zhuangling Temple
to detain puppet spirits.
But too many puppet spirits
are hiding throughout the Void.
It will take some days to find them all.
Before, Yan Zhang
could only control puppets in the Void
with Chiling Secret Technique.
Why can Yan Ke
control those puppet spirits
even in the Mortal World?
He must have
much stronger power now.
Within such a short time,
he must have devoured many spirits.
He stole my Chiling Secret Technique.
Thief.
In that case,
he even has the Lantern.
Why is he trying hard
to mess up the Void
instead of attacking it?
He does have the Lantern.
But it doesn't mean he can use it.
Yan Ke is making such a big scene
just to pin me down
and figure out how to use it.
The Lantern follows the strongest.
We don't know how Yan Ke
has been growing his power out there.
But the submission of the Lantern
is only a matter of time.
The Lantern
won't yield to him
unless I'm dead.
Xu,
you just recovered from the poison.
Go get some more rest.
I feel much better now.
Luda's poison is fierce.
But the physician cured me in time.
Yeah.
Xu,
don't push yourself too hard.
When Xiaoxiao calms down and returns,
we'll drink and eat meat pies.
You're right.
She may refuse to see me.
But she'll come to see you.
Prophet.
You're back already?
These red spots...
Did you meet evil spirits?
It's the duty of our sect
to punish the evil spirits
in the Mortal World.
It's just...
I haven't found the elixir for you.
I thought it was something serious.
Never mind.
Ziji.
This is the Rescue Pill of our sect.
It can help you restore your vitality.
But it can't cure
the trauma from your fading senses.
That's actually irreversible.
This is good enough.
I'll always remember
how you've saved my life.
Prophet,
may I ask one more favor?
What is it?
Could you please
take a message to Simu?
Tell her I'm confused
and I want to see her again.
I can be bold enough
to take this message.
But...
Great Ancestor won't agree.
She is
quite resolute.
Actually,
she has always been
indulgent with you.
Maybe...
When the war is over,
you can go find her in the Void.
When the war is over...
Whenever she wants to see me,
she can come anytime.
I can't do the same.
This is so unfair.
You should have known it early.
I know.
Great Ancestor.
Things are tricky?
Many evil spirits
have appeared in Youzhou
like attending a market.
They came from other cities.
It took a great deal of effort.
It's Yan Ke.
He took the Spirits Lantern
and hid it in Youzhou.
He can't operate it.
But he might use it
to suppress the spirits there
to serve his needs.
I've locked down the Void,
so spirits can't get out.
In the Mortal World,
you must be careful.
Great Ancestor,
that's too much for you.
You have to defend the Void
and protect the Mortal World.
I...
Wait, wait.
Great Ancestor,
will you really
not see him again?
He asked me to take a message.
He said
he was confused
and wanted to see you again.
I'm just doing
what I promised him.
Are you done?
The last time I saw him,
he wasn't feeling very well.
You just found out?
Just as I thought,
nothing can escape you.
I didn't dare to tell you
about his fading senses.
I thought
I could find a way to cure him.
But I just can't.
Great Ancestor,
so...
Will you go see him?
Watch over Duan Shunxi.
Ziji,
I almost feel like
I'm seeing my own ancestors.
I guess I'm dying.
Just a hallucination.
You saw them last year.
Take your medicine.
Ziji,
in this world,
Great Ancestor must have been
the best Sovereign ever.
Don't you think so?
The Sovereign who has no wishes
restrains the spirits
born of obsessions.
Everything in this world
is deliberately designed
with connected links
just for smooth operation.
Ziji.
Do you think this is good?
Like you said,
the world operates smoothly.
So,
either it's Great Ancestor
who doesn't want to be the Sovereign,
or it's me who has a short life.
Neither of us is given a choice.
We're nothing but tools.
Do you still think this way
after living here for so long?
Take your medicine.
Don't change the subject.
Oh no, you noticed.
After I spit out
that blood,
I felt
much more refreshed.
How about
I don't take this medicine?
You know it doesn't work on me.
You should go back soon.
Youzhou has complex terrain.
We managed to guard some cities.
But our losses are much greater.
This arrowhead
is forged from Tianluo Ore
just like my armor.
It's lightweight and sharp
and penetrates better
than iron arrowheads.
This is my lethal weapon
for the Chong Army.
Impressive.
You're a genius, Marshal.
Their High Priest
used poison to scare us
and demoralize us.
Now, we have this new arrowhead.
I can imagine how awesome
it would be to shoot them with this.
Xu.
You...
Go supervise the arrowhead forging
and set the tactics.
Yes.
Let's go.
Xu,
Mr. Fang sent a message.
He's back in Nandu for work.
(Emperor of Liang fell ill.)
(Prince Su and Prince Ji
besieged Nandu,)
(forcing him to abdicate.)
(Prince Jin and Fang Xianye)
(took the Emperor to the Royal Villa.)
(Without an emperor,
Nandu is in great chaos.)
(Royal Villa)
There you are, Fang.
Your Majesty,
I've brought some medicinal supplements.
Over all these years,
you and Duan Xu worked hard
to assist my son Jin.
By Your Majesty's grace,
Duan Shunxi and I assist Prince Jin.
It is our honor.
We won't complain.
The three of you are destined to meet.
In the same year's exam,
you were
the top three scholars.
And you all wanted to uphold our nation.
All the officials in court
either support
Chancellor Du or Duke Pei.
All they want to do
is fight for power.
They never want to help our people.
I'm really relieved
to see
people like you.
The Chong invaded our territories
to enslave our people.
Our people have been suffering.
I became an official
just to change this situation.
Prince Su and Prince Ji
are each backed
by Chancellor Du and Duke Pei.
They want to force me to abdicate
when I'm seriously ill.
I won't let them have their way.
I told Jin
to send out secret decrees everywhere.
The reinforcements
will soon arrive.
And of course...
I also issued a decree to Duan Xu,
asking him to return soon and help us.
How is Miss Duan?
Don't worry.
Everything is fine.
Send this letter
to Miss Duan
as fast as you can.
(Decree)
Duan Xu misled the army.
Duke Pei ordered
all secret letters from Nandu to Youzhou
should be intercepted. Let's go.
Yes.
What exactly is the Spirits Lantern?
The supreme treasure
of the Spirit World.
It can make a spirit
have immense power,
command all the spirits,
and reign in the Void.
It's a symbol of the Sovereign
and a symbol of power.
The Spirits Lantern.
What will happen
if a human has it?
(Liang)
Why are evil spirits here?
Yan Ke,
I hear you're now a traitor
that everyone wants to beat.
Duan Shunxi,
let's see how long you'll be laughing.
(The Lantern?)
(Why does he have it?)
Simu,
did you receive the present
I left in the Void?
So sad.
Yan Zhang worked so hard
to collect those puppets.
But they were fragile.
Since you don't like this present,
I'll show you something else.
You've shielded him
so well.
It took me quite a lot of trouble
to take him.
Simu.
You know you're doomed.
That's why
you pull such a dirty trick.
Last time, you traded the Lantern
for his life.
This time,
what will you trade?
Don't be silly.
You know exactly
how the Lantern works.
(Simu traded the Lantern)
(for my antidote.)
I've done my best for him.
He means nothing to me now.
If you want to kill him, kill him.
Simu, you're always kind to mortals.
If I kill him,
you'll be sad, won't you?
How pathetic you are, Yan Ke.
It's been 300 years.
You still can't find my vital gate.
I gave you the Lantern,
but you can't use it.
You can't beat me
and you can't kill me.
You've even fallen for me.
Now all you can do is threaten me
with a mere mortal.
How could you be so silly?
Seeing how miserable you are,
let me tell you something.
300 years ago,
I tore out my vital gate
and melted it into the Lantern.
As for him...
His business isn't my concern.
You can't kill me
unless you destroy the Lantern.
But would you do that?
You traded the Lantern for me.
So you care about me!
Only a real rival makes it exciting.
You're right, Simu.
I wouldn't destroy it.
I told you.
She's never had trouble finding love.
What do you think you are?
You're just nothing.
She traded the Lantern for you
because she had a backup plan.
If she really had to lose something,
she wouldn't hesitate to leave you.
She fooled you.
You're just a toy.
I don't believe it.
Simu wouldn't do this to me.
I used to think
the physician cured me.
I just found out
Simu traded the Lantern
for my life.
She wouldn't give up on me.
Stop daydreaming!
Since He Simu has abandoned you,
you're no longer
of any use to me.
Even if she doesn't care about me,
she has to care
about her spell bearer.
She wouldn't leave me alone.
Since you're her spell bearer,
you can
exchange senses anytime.
I want you to exchange senses with her
at the moment I tell you.
When I defeat and capture her,
the Lantern will take me as its master.
Then I'll make her stay by your side
for the rest of your life.
What do you say?
Where's Marshal Duan?
Why is he gone?
Still no news of Marshal Duan?
Terrible enemies.
They want to annihilate us
when Marshal Duan isn't here.
We can't let them win!
Commandant Xia,
you lead reinforcements
to Fengzhou right now.
Rest assured. Count on me.
Meng Wan,
Qizhou is our granary.
You must guard it well!
Yes!
Report!
The Chong army is attacking fiercely!
Now?
- Yeah.
- What do we do?
I'll serve as the vanguard.
Youzhou determines
the fate of the war
and hundreds of thousands of lives.
Xu isn't here now.
We must fight desperately
and never retreat.
Protect yourself.
The puppet spirits caught yesterday
have all been put in the Prison.
The unrest in the Void
has been quelled for now.
Yan Ke is right there in Youzhou.
I'll take him down myself.
I have my own plans
for the Mortal World.
Xiaoxiao.
Xiaoxiao!
I just want to follow you.
I can eat less.
You took care of me.
Now I have money.
I'll take care of you.
Xiaoxiao is a nice person.
She would never make me kill anyone!
♪Cross your legs♪
(Liang)
♪Subdue dragon and tiger;
tether horse and ape♪
♪Mind still as water,
breath soft as silk♪
♪Be a sage, not an immortal♪
♪Cross your legs for three years♪
♪Subdue dragon and tiger;
tether horse and ape♪
♪Mind still as water,
breath soft as silk♪
♪Be a sage, not an immortal♪
♪A lamp in the east lights the west♪
♪No lamp in the west,
but it's still bright♪
Xiaoxiao, don't die.
I promise I'll grow stronger.
The General said
those who always protect others
are very lonely.
From now on,
the General and I
will protect you together
just like how you protected us.
All right?
(Liang)
(Tomb of My Brother Xue Chenying)
So Xiaoxiao,
you're a magician.
(Tomb of My Brother Xue Chenying)
Simu,
it's been a long time.
You finally dared to come
out of the Glazed Pagoda.
Try to trap me
in this little formation?
This is especially for you.
It's not perfect yet.
But trapping you for a little while
will suffice.
Now.
It is time.
The formation blocks
He Simu's aura.
The blessed flower won't work.
What are you plotting?
Her vital gate is in the Lantern.
Maybe we can use that
to exchange senses.
I need a blessed flower
This is the last one.
After it activates,
the spell must be done
within a short while.
Or it will be useless.
Duan Xu,
don't be stupid.
Are you scared, Your Grace?
When you gave up on me,
did you see this coming?
You ant!
How dare you grab the Lantern?
A human can also
use the Spirits Lantern.
Yan Ke,
I have to thank you
for the spirit power you gave me.
Duan Xu.
Simu.
Sorry.
I failed to help you
get back the Lantern.
Great Ancestor.
I'll leave you alone.
You spat blood
because of the sense exchange,
didn't you?
Why did you keep it from me?
If I had told you,
you wouldn't
exchange senses anymore.
Then you couldn't feel the colors,
warmth,
scent,
or melody.
Too bad, then.
Duan Shunxi.
♪Falling down like snow♪
What am I in your eyes?
A bad woman who will
drain your senses and then walk off?
Won't I feel sad?
Don't I have a heart?
I know
you wouldn't drain my senses.
I willingly lent you
all my senses.
And I've never expected
to live a very long life.
Compared to your lifespan...
♪Dawn and dusk rise and set♪
Mine would never be long.
To me,
the senses are just feelings.
But to you...
♪Wander to the other shore
with the lantern♪
They mean the whole world.
♪As all things turn and flow♪
What do you mean "just feelings"?
Duan Shunxi.
You live only once.
For only a few decades.
Your senses are also your whole world.
Can you understand?
To me, you...
Do you know
why I left you?
You didn't want Yan Ke to hurt me
because of our bond.
It's just one of the reasons.
There's one more important reason.
I've realized...
I've realized
I love you far too much.
♪I'd be a guest in a sweet dream♪
I can't accept
that one day
I have to helplessly
watch you leave me.
♪Longing to meet, yet parted by destiny♪
♪Let me wander through♪
♪Light and dark, without turning back♪
All men die.
♪Wander to the other shore
with the lantern♪
I think you're used to that.
♪Accompanied by eternity♪
♪As all things turn and flow♪
Yes.
I'm used to that.
And I'm tired of that.
I won't feel sad
and I want to see no more of it.
But when it comes to you,
I still can't accept that.
I never want
to leave anyone again.
Simu.
Chenying died in war.
♪A lone lamp shines on the other shore♪
I buried him
next to his father.
♪Accompanied by the abyss♪
♪Moments may last♪
♪Love and hate will fade away♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪