( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
Phoon, do you want to move in with me?
You won’t get bored of me, right, P'Fah?
No way.
Do you want to see your mom?
You said you’d take me anywhere I want to go.
I already know where I want to go.
P'Fah, can we head back now?
- Why?
- I didn’t think it would be this cold.
Help me find Phoon's mom.
His real mom.
Could you stop interfering with Phoon's life?
He has endured enough already.
Please let him go.
Thank you, P'Fah, for helping me find my mom.
It’s nothing.
Half Japanese.
She has one son and is now 39 years old.
Then she must have had me at 19.
P'Fah.
Yes?
She must not have been ready when she had me.
Ready or not, I don’t know.
But she sent you gifts every year, didn’t she?
Besides,
Your name and your mom’s in Japanese,
they both mean flowers.
How so?
Yuri.
It means lily.
And Ren means lotus.
Do you want to see your mom?
I’m not sure.
She already has a new family.
If I go see her, I’m afraid
I might ruin the new life she’s built.
Then why don’t you try contacting her first?
If she seems uncomfortable, you can step back.
Did I make you feel uneasy?
You don’t have to overthink it.
If you don’t want to go, it’s okay.
Actually,
I do want to see her at least once.
Her son’s name is Daiki.
I’m going to have a younger sibling.
That’s cute.
Maew, are you mixed?
Not exactly.
My mom is mixed.
Oh, so you’re 25% Japanese?
You get half from your mom, right?
So?
Are you going to see her?
I don’t know.
My mom already has a new family.
I don’t know
if I should go or not.
I think you should.
She probably misses you a lot.
Otherwise, why would she send gifts?
Yeah, true.
Why don’t you try contacting her first?
Like sending a letter.
Well,
that could work.
I’ll write her a letter first.
If she doesn’t reply, I’ll deal with it then.
She will reply.
Anyway, congratulations.
You finally know who your mom is.
Yeah.
What about your dad?
That’s probably over now.
He’s already paid for what he did.
I’ll live my own life.
Living separately like this is fine.
I’m really proud of you.
You’ve grown so much. You’ve really matured.
- You used to cry whenever your dad came up.
- True.
- You did great.
- Whenever he talked about his dad, his face was like a cat that ate poop.
What’s wrong with you?
Serves you right.
There you go again.
Thanks.
When I was at my worst,
you guys were the only ones
who made things better.
I’m an unlucky guy.
I used up all my luck
on meeting good friends like you guys.
- Maew, stop it, he’s about to cry.
- I’m not crying. You are. Don’t push it.
You’re sniffling.
Maew, honestly, it’s nothing.
You don’t have to thank us.
Just pay for our drinks instead.
Seriously.
You have zero common sense and can’t read the room.
I just don’t like this kind of mood.
It’s too tense.
Hey.
Thanks.
What are you saying?
Thanks for helping me with everything.
And when Phoon got into trouble, too.
Do you even realize?
- You’re like the group’s hero.
- Hero, my ass.
- Are you crazy, thanking me out of nowhere?
- North’s blushing.
I’m serious.
I’m really glad to have a friend like you.
Having a friend like you in this life
is better than winning the lottery.
I really love you.
Hey, what kind of love talk is that?
Are you crazy, Ter? What are you saying?
- No way.
- Acting cool, but you’re blushed, right?
- No, I’m not.
- You are blushed.
- I can tell.
- Are you nuts? Enough.
There are tons of people here. What are you doing?
But really,
I’m really happy
to have you as my friend.
Do you know you’ve always been positive energy for us?
Love you, man.
Hey, stop with the love stuff. No.
- Say you love us.
- What love nonsense again?
- I was getting emotional just now.
- Emotional about what?
- Hurry up.
- Ter, behave yourself.
Are you crazy?
He's just shy.
Three people are done.
No, I’m not saying it.
Hey.
- Thanks, Dao.
- Thanks so much, Dao.
Dao gives really good advice.
- If we don't have you.
- Seriously, the group would’ve fallen apart.
We’d be screwed without Dao.
I’m really glad.
Even though you never eat with us.
To Ms. Nakamura Yuri.
Hello, my name is Typhoon.
I am your son. May I call you Mom?
I don’t know if it’s okay to write to you.
But I want you to know how happy I am to know who my real mom is.
I only recently found out that someone sent me birthday gifts every year.
If it was you, I’m happy you still think of me.
I’m not angry that you weren’t with me.
No matter the reason, I just hope you’re doing well.
As for me, I’m doing well.
I’ve met someone I love, and who loves me.
Thank you.
Can I hire you to dress me for life?
Sure, but
there’s a small fee.
Is it expensive?
Not at all. Just...
one kiss.
What are you saying?
You’ve gotten really cute lately.
Whenever I talk like that, you get shy.
You’re cute, P'Fah.
Stop it.
I have friends and good people around me.
Hey.
Faculty of Fine Arts.
I’ve found my purpose and goals in life.
If one day you ever wonder whether I’m doing well,
I’m doing fine. Don’t worry.
Do you best, Phoon.
Ok.
I want to see you, Mom.
But if you don’t want to see me, that’s okay. I understand.
I wish you happiness and smiles every day. From Typhoon.
Ren.
Is there any?
Just a moment.
Maybe she doesn’t want to see me.
That’s why she hasn’t replied.
Don’t jump to conclusions.
What are you going to do next?
I will probably look for work.
Start a new life with Fai, just the two of us.
That must be tough.
At least I’ll have peace of mind knowing no one will hurt us again.
You too, Phoon.
Live your life happily.
I’ll bring Fai to visit often.
Okay.
Please take good care of yourself, Aunt Phrae.
You’re back?
Ren, I’m sorry. I miss you. I’ll wait.
From Mom
That’s wonderful.
Yeah.
Enjoy your sweets.
What does it mean?
It means “Enjoy your sweets.”
I will
take you to see your mom.
You're so kind.
Hmm? Me?
Yes.
You must get complimented a lot, huh?
Not really.
With other people, it’s just normal.
But with you…
I can really do anything for you.
I can’t wait to see what the dessert looks like.
How to open it?
Here you go.
This is called Manju.
Do you want to try it, P'Fah?
You try it first, Phoon.
Here.
My mom sent it for me.
Wow, you’re all smiles just thinking about seeing your mama.
Let him smile for once.
- True.
- Sure.
Congrats, Maew.
Mm.
So where are you meeting your mama?
She sent me the address. We’ll meet there.
There? Japan?
Yeah.
Whoa.
So that means you and P'Fah get to go on another date in Japan, right?
- Hey!
- No, no!
Hey, Ter, stop teasing him. Look at that smile—his cheeks must hurt already.
Awww, so much shy, huh.
I'm just happy. What’s wrong with that?
- Here, take some sweets.
- Thanks.
Handing out snacks!
- I’ll give you two.
- Thanks a lot.
- Here.
- Hey, why do I only get one? Can I have two?
- He eats a lot.
- Why?.
- You're not handsome enough to get two.
- Then it should be you who get just one.
- Hey!
- Too slow.
Speed belongs to the devil—don’t compete with me.
You steal my stuff all the time.
You didn’t even split the bill last time.
Look at you, pretending to be sulky.
- Here, kids.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Oh, P'Gib.
My mom sent these.
Whoa.
- Wow.
- Would you like to try some?
Thank you, Phoon.
Ever since you started dating Doctor Fah, you’re glowing.
That’s what love does.
Not just that.
- He's even going on a honeymoon in Japan.
- What honeymoon?
You’re exaggerating, North.
Don’t tell me you’ve already packed your bags.
You’ve already planned it, right?
Come on. Are you planning to introduce him to your mom too?
He must be trying outfits from day one to the last day.
- The sweets are really good. Try them.
- Hey, are you changing the subject?
Which one should I get?
What do you think, P'Fah?
Both of them.
One is enough.
Why? I’ll buy it for you.
Hm?
Then, is there any other one you want to see, Phoon?
Um…
No.
Should I buy a new camera?
Sure.
P'Fah, you should stop me sometimes.
You spoil me completely.
I like seeing you happy.
Now I understand Jo and Hill.
When you have a boyfriend, you just want to indulge him.
You’re not buying it?
Thinking about it…
I already have a lot of cameras.
I’d rather save the money to visit my mom in Japan.
Are you excited about seeing your mom?
I am.
I never thought I’d really get to see her.
At first, I thought she didn’t want to see me anymore.
Why would you think that?
I don’t know.
Maybe I’m just not used to being happy.
Don’t think like that.
You deserve happiness more than anyone. You know that, right?
Thank you.
Are you excited?
Yes.
Very excited.
Do you think it’ll be okay?
It’ll definitely be okay.
Trust me.
Ren.
Mom.
You’ve grown so much.
I came to see you.
Let’s go inside first.
Your name is Tonfah, right?
Yes.
The one who called me.
Well…
Phoon really wanted to see you.
So I helped look for you until I found you.
Thank you for bringing my son to see me.
I'm...
I’m really sorry.
Mama loves you.
Mama missed you so much.
I missed you too.
I’ve always wanted to see you.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
I’m P'Tonfah.
I’m Daiki.
Daiki.
- Tonfah.
- You're so cute.
Thank you.
The first time I went to Phuket was to bring my mother’s ashes back to her hometown.
That’s when I met him.
So my grand-mother was from Phuket.
He…
told me
that he had no family.
And I believed him.
Until I got pregnant.
It’s okay.
Please go on.
He told me to get an abortion.
But I couldn’t do it.
I wanted to raise my child as best as I could.
But it wasn’t easy.
I couldn’t bear seeing you starve.
So I took you to ask him for help.
His wife was furious.
But she felt sorry for you.
So she agreed to raise you.
On the condition that I never interfered with their family again.
She must have been hurt just as much.
We were both hurt by the same man.
I thought
it was better for you. I secretly came to see you many times, but I never dared to approach.
All I could do was send gifts.
I’m sorry. This is my fault.
I’m not here to decide who’s right or wrong.
I don’t resent anyone.
I don’t blame anyone.
That’s all in the past.
Please don’t feel guilty anymore.
At first,
Mama named you Ren.
But they changed your name, didn’t they?
Why did you name me Ren?
Ren
means a lotus.
A lotus that is already beautiful when it’s in the right place.
Daiki.
Go say hello to your big brother.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
He said 'My name is Daiki.
Nice to meet you.'
He’s wanted an older brother for a long time.
He said he’s wanted an older brother for a long time.
Really?
I’ve always wanted a younger brother too.
He said he’s wanted a younger brother too.
Hello.
Thank you for letting me come see you.
Why are you talking like we won’t see each other again?
I just wanted you to see
that I’m doing well.
This time,
I just wanted to see
that you’re doing well too.
I want you to be happy
with the path you chose.
As for me,
I’ll be happy with the path I chose too.
Even if we don’t live together,
we still have each other, right?
Mama.
I can still be your mama, right?
No matter what,
I still want you to be my mama.
And I
will always be your Ren.
We’ll get to see each other again, right?
Come visit often, okay?
I’ll come back to visit often.
He said he’ll come back to visit again.
Goodbye.
Please take care of your health.
I will.
Goodbye.
Thank you.
Please take good care of Ren.
I’ll take care of and protect your son with my life.
Thank you.
You're really kind.
Yes, you are.
You're incredibly kind.
Not many people would be happy when their parents remarry.
And on top of that, you love you half-brother like this.
Well, Daiki is adorable.
I think you and your mom are really alike.
How so?
Probably you guys faces look similar.
Especially the eyes.
Thank you for giving him such a beautiful and radiant smile.
He’s beautiful and radiant on his own.
Because of the path you chose twenty years ago, I’ve had him to love until today.
Thank you so much.
How's going?
How are things?
Well…
It’s cold.
Where’s P'Fah?
He looked tired, so he fell asleep.
So I came out for a walk in the garden.
Morning, little one.
Why did you get out of bed?
Uh…
Whoa.
Why are you calling?
He wanted to talk to Phoon.
Oh?
I’ll hang up now.
Are you okay, Phoon?
P'Fah, it’s just that…
Earlier…
What is it?
Everyone saw it already.
The morning kiss?
It’s okay.
Don’t overthink it, Phoon.
How can it be okay?
Are you upset?
Yes.
Very upset.
- What are you doing?
- Making it up to you.
Who makes up like this?
I do.
Who told you to get out of bed?
You looked tired.
So I didn’t want to disturb you.
Okay.
Okay?
I understand now.
But you can’t tease mr like that.
I wasn’t teasing you.
I really didn’t see it.
- Really?
- Really.
I never tease you.
You tease me the most.
Hey.
Then…
Let’s not count what just happened.
I think we need a proper round.
A proper round?
Well…
A real morning kiss.
That’s not it.
Right?
Just one morning kiss.
Good morning again.
Good morning.
I heard from Ter that today’s Phoon's birthday?
Yeah.
I sent my gift with Ter.
Thanks, man.
Every birthday gives me a headache.
I never know what to buy.
I let North choose, I’ll pay for it.
That’s so you, Jo.
Hey, buy one for me too.
- Go ask your Papa.
- Hey, watch your mouth.
Hi, Papa.
So what did you buy for him?
Happy Birthday, my little one.
May every day from now on be a good day for you.
May all your wishes come true.
P'Fah will always be cheering you on.
Thank you.
A camera?
How much?
Just over a hundred thousand.
What?!
So you’re one of those people too now?
Fah, once you have a boyfriend, you love like crazy, huh?
- You don’t have one.
- Hey.
- Watch your mouth.
- Better that way.
- I pity for his boyfriend.
- Wow.
You guys are such jerks.
Is Arthit sulking?
Wow, P'Fah bought a camera as a gift?
Yeah.
That’s huge. My gift and Jo’s look so little now.
What gift of yours?
Here.
- From me and P'Hill.
- Thank you.
You’re definitely going to like it.
Just the fact that you guys remembered my birthday already makes me happy.
If you’re really happy, then I’ll take it back.
- No.
- What?
Hey!
You’re pulling so hard.
Why did you have to be born today?
I want to go celebrate too.
Then cancel your family plans and come celebrate my birthday with me.
Oh, so if I get cut out of the inheritance,
are you going to take care of me?
Nope.
Ugh.
Let’s check out the birthday gifts and see what I got.
Whose should we open first?
Save mine for last. Start with the gloomy-looking box first—it looks nicely depressing.
- That’s bullying.
- It’s cool.
Bullying. You’re exaggerating.
It’s style, just look at it.
Simple but classy.
Or start from Dao's?
Did you get me an amulet or what?
Taking photos again?
P'Fah, look.
You look like a model.
That’s because the photographer is good.
Time really flies, doesn’t it?
It feels like we were just here not long ago.
Yeah.
Do you remember, P'Fah?
You said that…
"I can’t be the sky for anyone."
I remember.
Do you still feel that way now?
If that’s what Phoon wants,
I can be anything for you.
Thank you for bringing me here.
Thank you again.
Thank you so much.
Even though you have been so busy,
you still made time to be with me on my birthday.
I don’t really do much for you, P'Fah.
Just being a good kid is enough, Phoon.
I'm a good kid.
- And not naughty.
- You are. A naughty cat.
I’m not naughty. And I’m not a cat either.
Why not?
Even your friends call you maew.
- Maew.
- Yes?
See? You said you weren’t a cat.
Then why did you answer?
If I were a cat,
and really had nine lives,
I’d give them all to you, P'Fah.
Hmm? All of them?
All of them.
I’ll put them right into your hands.
Okay.
Then I’ll gladly take them all.
Happy birthday.
Thank you for becoming the best thing in my life.
Come on, cheers!
Yeah.
Thanks for coming, Dao.
It’s Maew’s birthday—how could I not come?
Yeah, if you don’t come to my birthday, we’ll see about that.
You get sulky so easily.
It’s empty—time for a refill.
Straight up.
Hey, Jo.
Control your boyfriend.
Hey, he’s having fun.
- Right?
- I am.
- North.
- What?
Are you trying to get me drunk?
No way.
How are you this strong with alcohol?
That’s impossible.
Let’s settle this.
Whoever gets drunk wins—
no, whoever gets drunk first loses.
- Deal.
- Yeah.
Let’s go.
- Bring it on.
- Yeah, bring it.
- Come on.
- Let’s go.
Cheers. Bottoms up.
I love P'Hill the most.
Throwing up doesn’t count—but if you pass out, you lose.
Cheers.
Yes! I won!
Yes, little one.
You won.
Ugh.
Why was I even born a refrigerator?
If I can’t even chill chicken in it.
So annoying.
I’ll go get a towel to wipe you down, okay?
No.
- I’ll just go grab a towel for a second, Phoon.
- No.
No matter how good a person you meet,
don’t ever leave me behind, okay?
What are you talking about, Phoon?
I don’t know. I’m drunk.
P’Mhor.
P’Mhor Fah.
Yes?
Don’t let me find out, okay?
Find out about what?
That you were secretly checking someone else out during class.
Really?
P’Fah, do you like kids?
Kids?
Yeah, I do.
Why?
I like kids too.
I want to have children.
A whole house full of them.
But P’Fah probably won’t have time for the kids.
They’d love me more than you anyway.
I would be Papa.
The Papa who understands the kids the most.
Why aren’t you answering, P’Fah?
Well…
You didn’t really ask me anything, Phoon.
Then what would P’Fah name our child?
A name?
What should it be?
I don’t know. You can decide, Phoon.
But P’Fah works really hard.
Will P’Fah even have time for me and the kids?
Don’t worry, Phoon. I’ll try my best to make time for you and the kids.
Then P’Fah has to be a really sweet Papa to them.
I will.
But right now,
it’s already late.
Let’s go to sleep, okay?
No. I won’t sleep. I’m not sleepy.
- But you’re drunk, Phoon.
- I’m not.
Why is Papa arguing with me?
Wait a second…
"Papa"?
Papa’s arguing with me.
Phoon, don’t be naughty.
Papa scolds me—do you scold the kids too?
If they’re naughty, then I have to.
No, don’t scold them.
If Papa scolds the kids, I’ll take them and run away.
I won’t let them see you.
In that case…
Mama, don’t be so mean to Papa, okay?
Ow, it hurts here.
It hurts here.
It hurts here too.
Good night.
Here you go, Phoon.
Careful, it’s hot.
Do you have a headache?
A little.
Next time,
don’t drink this much, okay?
Mm.
It’s good. Did you make this yourself, P’Fah?
I did.
If you like it,
eat a lot, okay?
Phoon.
Do you remember what you said
last night?
Last night?
Why?
You talked about
having kids.
Kids?
Yes.
You asked, “Does P’Fah like kids?”
"Does P’Fah want to have kids?"
Oh… I must’ve been drunk last night.
I was just rambling.
I won’t drink anymore.
Why not?
I think you’re pretty cute when you’re drunk.
But you just told me not to drink too much.
That’s true.
I mean, you can drink—but only when I’m with you.
Eat a lot, okay?
- Mama.
- Hmm?
If you’re still hungry, Papa can make more for you.
Daotok.
If you keep staring at us like that, I’m gonna puke on you.
Don’t talk about puking.
Enough. Stop arguing and help me check the exam results.
Come help me root for this.
Get up.
Exam Results Announcement
Faculty of Fine Arts, Bachelor of Fine Arts Program, Creative Photography
Teerapat Chaowakornkul
Shit.
It’s okay, man.
If I don’t get in this year, I can try again next year.
You got in—holy shit, you got in!
Your name’s on it. Come take a look.
Thirasophon University announces the admission results for Program Choice No. 6
Teerapat Chaowakornkul
- I got in!
- Yeah.
Yes!
The sky is never the same each day, but it’s still just as captivating.
To Typhoon,
Even though I’ve written countless letters,
to so many people,
this is probably the first time I’ve ever written one to myself.
Thank you.
Thank you for growing stronger,
and for accepting your own pain.
Thank you for finding yourself in the end.
Thank you for daring to open your heart, and for meeting so many good people along the way.
Hey, you.
The classroom’s this way.
Yeah, I’m in the faculty.
What should we do? That Phoon still gets lost like always.
Will he survive without us?
Are classes over yet? I’ll come pick you up.
No need.
Why not?
Thank you for believing in love, enough to realize just how deeply you’re capable of loving someone.
- Where to next?
- Maybe go eat.
What about you?
No idea.
I’m hungry too.
But I don’t feel like eating with you.
What’s wrong with you?
Phoon won’t let me go pick him up.
Or maybe he’s studying photography now and totally surrounded by people.
- Yeah, probably.
- Like Hill said.
Oh, poor you, P'Fah.
Your life is so tragic.
Don’t listen to those idiots too much.
You know Phoon loves you to death.
I know.
I don’t believe a word those two say anyway.
Huh?
- Hey, Jo, did you hear that?
- Yeah.
- See you at P'Gib’s shop.
- What the hell?
He’s getting bold these days.
Smiling nonstop.
Where’s Phoon?
Here.
If it’s not too much trouble, may I see you again?
There’s something important I’d like to talk to you about.
- Thank you.
- You’re welcome.
What’s up, little one?
Hello.
Thank you for meeting me.
Thank you for coming to see me as well.
Have you ever wondered what you would’ve done if I had walked away back then?
Like I said before, I’d go back to the same place—where we feel at ease.
No matter how long it takes.
No matter how long, you’d still wait?
Yes.
One year.
That’s fine.
Two years.
That’s still fine.
Five years.
That’s fine too.
Then ten years.
Phoon, stop teasing me already.
I’m going to start counting down.
If you still don’t say anything, you’ll be punished.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
- Four.
- P'Fah.
- Three.
I just—
- Two.
- wanted to surprise you, that’s all.
One.
P'…
I loves you, P'Fah.
I loves you too, phoon.