RECTORY
Oh, my darling beloved
We’ve waited so long
Despite all those people
Who didn’t believe in us
I waited for you
Spring, winter, summer
So you would love me
In front of the whole world
Oh, my beloved darling
I will love you
Winter, spring, summer
Even in autumn
When the leaves fall
Because I vowed…
IT TAKES A VILLAGE
Wherever my feet take me
Don’t know the destination or the way
Jan carved Halina out of love
She dumped him
But don’t think, Jan, it was out of malice
OLIWKA’S RESTAURANT
POLICE
…sings all of creation
COSMIC POWER-IN-LAW
CROP CIRCLES
OLIWIA’S
I see you eat those dumplings
As if you want to kiss me
My heart is faithful
Although broken
Lurking for ladies at the promenade
Nothing worse in this world
Since I first saw you
I can’t eat, I can’t sleep
’Cause of your eyes, your green eyes
I went crazy
To your eyes
And my heart, thirsty for love…
FOR SALE
BODZKI
Love will save the day!
Love will save the day