(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
Host
the ceremony?
Sure.
But don't expect me
to pay for it.
The Ji family will handle all costs.
Not just the catering.
I'm her father,
arriving empty-handed
would be humiliating.
The Ji name carries weight.
Ordinary gold
and silk?
Beneath you.
So perhaps
you'd cover
my gift as well?
[Right then, I understood.]
[Every love that ever truly existed]
[was a gift of fortune.]
[Parent and child.]
[Husband and wife.]
[None of them any different.]
[When it's there, it's there.]
[When it isn't...]
[no force on earth can conjure it.]
Grandmother's already
sorted your gift.
It's sitting in the storehouse.
Give us your word,
and
it's yours tomorrow.
To think this slip of a girl
could shadow
my love's entire fate.
Bind her.
Send her away.
Yes, my lord.
[I will never beg]
[to be loved again.]
[I'll only tend to the hearts]
[that have already chosen me.]
What's done is done.
You've had your say.
But the ceremony
will go forward.
And your father will be invited.
Why hold
a ceremony at all?
Every woman comes of age.
There's nothing remarkable about that.
What kind of nonsense is that?
I know it stings,
watching us
go to your father hat in hand.
But hear me:
none of that matters.
What matters is this ceremony.
The defining rite
of a woman's life.
Your first true entrance into the world.
And it determines
the match you'll make.
Without it,
how will anyone ever see
the woman you've become?
What exactly is so amusing?
Grandmother,
rest easy.
The concern isn't that
no one knows her.
It's that far too many already do.
You're asking for it!
Very well.
Honestly?
I'd never feel right
handing her to strangers.
You two are so close already,
why not
keep things simple?
Spare us all those
hollow formalities.
No, no,
Grandmother, please...
That ceremony
is happening.
I was being ridiculous.
I get it now.
Quite right, Grandmother!
A girl like her
deserves nothing less
than the grandest ceremony
imaginable!
Let every village...
no,
let the whole realm
witness her extraordinary grace
and beauty!
Enough.
I know precisely
what you're after.
Now out,
we have matters
to attend to.
Where did you dig those words up?
Hey,
that was uncalled for!
You mocked me first!
So
you did notice.
And I haven't even touched on
your little bonfire yet.
Aren't you the insensitive one!
Every last coin,
I'll earn it back!
I'm not asking you for a single coin.
I'm saying,
at least do it
for Grandmother.
Can you just show some grace?
What would grace accomplish?
If the ceremony falls apart,
my name suffers a little, nothing new.
Grandmother will never bring herself
to give me away to anyone.
And in any case...
I still have you,
my dear cousin, don't I?
Don't flatter yourself.
Hey...
Jinzhao!
Who is...
Greet Lord Chen, now!
My greetings, Lord Chen!
Please, rise.
This is your cousin?
Yes.
She's a bit of a free spirit,
doesn't get out much,
had no idea you'd be here.
My apologies
if she's caused any offense.
Not at all.
You must have come
to see my grandmother.
I wouldn't impose,
we shall withdraw.
Alright, enough!
There's no fire. Walk.
Quiet!
Keep your distance
from him.
He pushed
a sweeping tax reform,
persuaded His Majesty to dispatch
royal auditors to noble estates.
Now half the court hates him.
Prince Glorian especially.
Now he's "taken ill"
and taken refuge here.
Surely he's the very man
Grandmother's often spoken of,
Lord Chen?
She said his reform
would wipe out half their wealth!
You have no idea
how bad it's gotten.
The whole court is a mess.
Those guys
are in the Emperor's ear
every other day.
And as for Lord Chen?
They would
see him destroyed.
You know,
cut their purse, cut their throat.
These are
merciless men.
Assassination is within their reach.
I must see to
more guards at once.
Not a soul in her own family...
Yeah.
Deigned to
hold a ceremony.
Quite.
So she installs herself here,
and lets the Jis bear it...
-My lady...
Go...
My lady,
dusk is falling.
Where are you off to?
The back hill.
Do not follow.
What a perverse world.
I had barely
drawn first breath,
when my father cast me out,
a blemish upon his ambitions.
The moment I found my way home,
he barred the door against me.
Tell me,
was I wrong
to act?
The gift is burned. So be it.
What truly galls me
is that the ceremony must proceed.
And that man
must still be invited.
I should have
found another way...
I've taken the trouble
to draft a petition,
calling for the full repeal
of
your tax reform.
You need only add your seal
and things
will end here.
And
should I refuse?
Then I shall
end you here.
Then
so be it.
Chen Yanyun...
a secret army...
How dare you!
This is treason!
You're insane!
Chen Yanyun...
Kill me...
and you'll follow me to the grave!
Is that so?
Chen Yanyun...
Spare my life.
And the nobles
will be on your side!
Spare me and
every man of influence
will back your reform.
What is that...
Did I fall asleep?
Jinzhao,
you OK?
Are you in
any pain?
Yao...
you pulled me out?
Wasn't me.
Xuanqing did.
Madam's here.
I must go greet her.
Do not leave her side.
Grandmother.
Madam.
Greetings, Master Chen.
I'm told it was you
who brought her back.
We are deeply
in your debt.
Pray, think nothing of it.
Please,
attend to
Ms. Gu now.
I shall
take my leave,
ma'am.
How does she fare?
Awake. The healer's seen her.
Nothing grave.
And the back hill...
has it been properly attended to?
Taken care of.
Yet something
weighs upon me.
Once she had been
pulled from the water,
he arranged for word to reach me.
But in such a downpour,
a man who leaps into the water
or even lingers at its edge
does not emerge dry.
When I came upon Xuanqing,
there was not a trace of water on him.
Grandmother,
I don't think he's the one
who saved her.
Grandmother,
if it was Lord Chen
who pulled her out...
is it possible she witnessed...
Should Lord Chen have saved her,
whatever she may have seen...
it need not trouble us.
I shall speak with her,
then sound out Lord Chen.
But this
stays quiet.
Even if she asks,
the answer is Chen Xuanqing.
Understood.
Uncle.
And?
Did they
buy your story?
When Ms. Gu woke up,
I didn't speak with her at all.
Mrs. Ji seemed to read
what you intended.
She let the matter lie.
Yeah.
I have
two jars of
royal warming wine here.
Tomorrow,
send them to Ms. Gu.
And remember,
you saved her.
The wine's from you.
Understood.
Apply yourself to the exams.
You may go.
Kneel in honor of the parents.
We don't need that part.
Cut it.
Go and rest.
The rest of you too.
Yes, madam.
My dear child,
what is it now?
You were getting on so well.
I'm not kneeling to Gu Dezhao.
The rites are
the rites, child.
I find myself weary.
But...
It...
Qingpu,
that inkstone
I received a few days back,
go grab it for me.
I wish to present it to Master Chen.
Yes, my lady.
Master Chen.
Ms. Gu.
I was on my way to see you.
Yunting.
After last night's misfortune,
one must guard against the cold.
This is an imperially bestowed
warming wine,
a measure or two
ought to offer some relief.
You are most considerate.
My sincere thanks.
And how perfectly timed,
you arrive bearing wine,
and I have a token of gratitude too.
Qingpu.
A Nightslate inkstone,
and a box of Umbral Ink.
The ink is ordinary enough,
but the inkstone
is an antique.
I find its plainness rather endearing.
It belongs now with you.
A scholar like you
ought to have it.
I accept with gratitude,
Ms. Gu.
Actually,
when you came to my aid,
were you alone upon the hill?
I was.
May I ask what brought you there?
I arrived here but yesterday.
With certain matters weighing on me,
so I went for a walk.
I happened to pass the hill
and saw you in the water.
I see.
I have other pressing matters.
I shall not
impose further.
Take care.
Did you notice?
He couldn't quite look at me.
Maybe it's just... manners?
His words did not
ring true to me.
I can still dimly recall
the figure I glimpsed
before the water took me...
I don't believe it resembled him.
[Lord Chen...]
[That silhouette...]
[Feels like I've seen it somewhere.]
[Could it truly have been him?]
My lady...
What is it you are looking at?
A bird,
my lord.
I thought you might have remembered.
Remembered... what?
The lantern.
So that was you!
Apologies.
Think nothing of it.
My lord,
all is ready.
We may set out at your word.
[He just meant the lantern.]
[I was imagining things.]
My lord.
A total of
114 crates of classified files
have been salvaged from the water
and secured here.
Mute servants keep vigil here.
You can rest easy.
No one else knows this place exists.
Very well.
My lord...
I have...
a favor to ask...
Last night...
Jinzhao had too much wine.
She stumbled in by accident.
I pressed her on the matter...
She saw nothing...
That girl has never
had a scheming bone in her body.
I ask you to
extend your forgiveness,
for my sake.
Not a scheming bone, huh?
I hear there's
quite a ceremony being planned for her.
Indeed.
It's only a few days
from now.
We'd be very honored
if you could come,
my lord.
It goes without saying.
Actually...
I'll write to my mother,
ask her to come as a guest.
How's that sound?
Oh, truly,
a grace beyond measure...
After the ceremony,
send her to the capital.
As you wish.
I shall
take my leave.
Lord Chen!
Mr. Jiang!
I can see from your face
that our pledge of loyalty
has found its mark.
It has.
From the prime minister himself.
He's giving me the Crown Seneschal.
Our deepest congratulations!
The Cabinet is within reach.
Enough. Rise.
That said,
this one played out
just like you called it.
The PM has had
his eye on
Prince Glorian for a long time.
That wasn't me calling anything.
It was...
Right.
Material like this
on every major figure
means the reform
is as good as done.
We can come back to that.
According to the letter,
the appointment may come any day now.
It may
well coincide with
Ms. Gu's ceremony.
All the
local bigwigs will be there.
We would do well
to raise the land reform.
Test the waters.
Easy there.
Yes.
Pick up the pace.
Hear me, all of you!
Guests are beginning to arrive.
Sharp eyes and ready hands.
Understood.
Word has it Ms. Gu's ceremony
is no ordinary affair.
Nothing like the rites
- one usually sees.
- Congratulations!
- Welcome!
Is that so?
Word is, the capital's finest are in town.
Men and women together,
all bets are off.
Greetings!
Congratulations!
Gentlemen, please!
Women have run the Ji family for ages.
Congratulations!
And Mrs. Ji? A force of nature.
Nothing to raise an eyebrow at.
Uncle!
They say these lotus cakes
are the finest in town.
I bought some.
Do try one.
Meh.
"Meh?"
Fine, what about the plum drops?
Consider this,
she's not of Ji blood,
just the daughter's child.
Yet the family puts on
all this for her?
Some people are
just born under a lucky star.
Lucky for days,
and a temper to match!
A few days ago,
she struck the Chang boy.
His father demanded a proper account
and Ms. Gu declared,
without a trace of remorse,
that Master Chang
had struck first.
Absolutely hilarious!
Please, allow me!
Wait a moment,
could this Ms. Gu be my cousin?
Which cousin?
Uncle Dezhao's eldest daughter.
A diviner said
she'd ruin his prospects,
so they handed her off to the Jis
barely after she was born.
I believe her name is...
Jinzhao.
Has to be her.
Uncle,
it's not like
we've got plans.
Why not swing by the Ji estate
and see what this
mystery cousin of mine
actually
looks like?
Sure, go and strike her.
For what cause?
I am a man of honor.
Greetings!
My respects, Mrs. Chen.
Oh, we've been
like sisters for decades!
None of that, please.
Jinzhao,
come and greet Mrs. Chen.
Greetings,
Mrs. Chen.
That must be...
the cousin I have never met.
So this is our Jinzhao!
Yes.
I met you once, when you were
- barely this tall.
- Chen Yanyun?
And now here you are.
It really is him.
Didn't expect to find him sheltered here.
Take the seat of honor!
An imperial edict!
An imperial edict has arrived!
Imperial edict?
Madam, Lord Chen,
an edict has come from the palace.
It's for Lord Chen.
I'm afraid I'll have to ask everyone
to join me.
By imperial decree,
Chen Yanyun, faithful in service
and resolute in duty,
a man of talent and integrity,
is hereby appointed the Crown Seneschal,
with concurrent duties in the Bureau of Coins.
Serve well,
and honor my trust.
So decreed.
Gratitude,
Your Majesty!
Long live the Emperor!
Please rise, my lord.
Congratulations!
He's officially
the Crown Seneschal.
One foot in the door
of real power.
He knows precisely
whose favor is worth cultivating.
A long journey, my lord,
a room's been
set for you.
Right this way.
I'll excuse myself.
Please, my lord.
Congratulations, my lord.
Congratulations, Lord Chen!
Xu Shiqi, at your service!
Silk merchants, generations running.
Should you find a moment,
I'd be most honored
to host you at my table.
How did my ceremony...
Aye.
turn into his victory party?
Your kindness, Mr. Xu,
- I shall look forward to it.
- That cousin of yours...
is quite the character!
Where are you going?
You're not greeting Lord Chen?
[the heir of Lord Changxing...]
[What's he doing here?]
The nerve!
Chen Yanyun gets promoted, fine!
But did he have to steal my thunder?
Maybe he
didn't know
the edict was coming today.
He knew.
He absolutely knew.
I should have seen it
from the start.
Why would someone like him
show up to
my ceremony?
He just needed a stage.
And I handed it to him!
What is it?
Is Gu Dezhao here?
Never mind.
I'll deal with it when it comes.
No, my lady...
It is...
What is it?
Your father...
he did not bring your mother.
He came with a concubine.
Where are they?
With Madam...
That
is the concubine.
Let's go.
I have
come as promised.
The ceremony has concluded.
Her marriage must be considered.
For her own sake,
she should come home with me.
How very convenient.
Was it not you who refused
to hold the ceremony at all?
We had to
pay you
to come today.
And now you want to take her back.
You take me for a fool?
Show him
the gazette.
Yes, ma'am.
Four men in the capital,
reprimanded.
All for neglecting their families.
The censorate is watching.
You're terrified of being
named among them.
So now, suddenly,
you want her back.
Tell me I'm wrong.
This is... preposterous!
Yes, she's been raised here.
But abandoning my own flesh?
That's a very serious accusation!
You absolute...
Enough!
You've already burnt a fortune!
Don't make a scene!
My lady...
I'm not making a scene.
I don't need to.
He wants to bring me home?
Welcome to keep wanting.
It's him...
OK, listen...
Exquisite.
Quite so.
Simply exquisite.
That bamboo...
It's so vivid.
Almost like it's breathing.
Lovely view from out here.
There is... lotus...
Lord Chen is staying here,
they say.
We must present ourselves...
Jinzhao?
You have some nerve.
What was that!
No quarrel from me, it demeans.
You stand before your father;
is this your manner of greeting?
I see so little of you, Father.
I cannot even recall your rank.
What office do you hold now?
Entered the cabinet yet?
Watch how you speak!
Gentlemen, tea!
Right this way...
Ah, yes, right...
Please!
Maybe Father didn't catch that.
Then I shall repeat.
You cast me aside,
afraid I'd curse
your precious career.
Fifteen years have passed.
What office do you hold now?
Entered the cabinet yet?
You... you insolent...
Talk reached me,
of your boundless disgrace.
I called it lies.
Alas,
they ring true!
Grandmother's
coddling
bred your chaos.
Post-ceremony,
you join me in the capital.
Speak no further!
Not happening!
I will do no such thing!
You...
Kneel! Now!
Fine...
I tried...
being reasonable!
Go for it!
Lord Chen, newly elevated
and presently overseeing
the entirety of
the Bureau of Coins,
stands behind you,
observing.
Impress him enough,
and he might
vouch for you.
Your career shall advance, shall it not?
Of all things ungovernable,
women top the list.
Truer words were never written!
My lord...
Tell her,
I stole her thunder.
She just called it even.
We're square.
Gratitude, my lord.
My lord,
Lord Changxing's heir
came with the Gu boy,
purely for leisure's sake.
He came without
making himself known.
Fine, let him be.
Understood.
My lady,
those two
are from the Gus.
Maybe we go around?
I'd avoid anyone else.
The Gus?
Absolutely not.
Quite the boldness,
to pass before me
without a greeting.
I don't even flinch at Lord Chen.
And you think I'd bow for you?
Unbelievable...
Please.
The Jis have mounted
quite the spectacle!
What are they up to?
I know.
Let the ceremony begin!