( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
I mean…
Let's not say anything for now.
I can't say that it was a mistake,
that we should pretend…
it never happened.
Because it wasn't a mistake.
We're here.
Wait.
Here. It's the last day
of the exhibition tomorrow.
I'll be waiting.
Goodbye, then.
Right.
LEE KYU-TAE SOLO EXHIBITION
Stay there. I'll come to you.
Sorry I'm late.
No, it's okay.
That's…
Let's hurry. We're gonna be late.
Right.
Why were you late?
What matters is I'm here.
Why are you here?
EPISODE 9
LIKE OR LOVE
To see you.
Are you okay?
Of course. I'm totally fine.
Drink this.
I'll protect you.
Yellow? Really?
It's pretty!
The V sign?
Come here.
Ta-da. I'm good, aren't I?
Are you okay?
-I've got this.
-You've got this?
There are five of us,
so we need three toppings.
-Lovely.
-Two kinds of noodles.
-And cheese. Make that two.
-Glass noodles.
Order jjolmyeon noodles, too,
with a side of dumplings.
-Awesome.
-Love it!
Let's eat by ourselves.
Sounds good.
Ta-da.
Okay. Ta-da!
That's so cute.
How is it? Isn't it good?
It's delicious.
Let me try one.
Why don't you try the pork cutlet first?
You shouldn't…
It's way too salty. Are you okay?
-I love it. Really.
-No. Don't eat it.
Sounds delicious.
Thank you.
Here, let me pour you a drink.
Two lids for two bottles!
-I can handle just one glass.
-Whoa, no.
Yes. For lunch,
I had tuna gimbap and jjolmyeon.
My wrist?
It's better than yesterday,
but I'm still struggling. Yeah.
Okay. I'll call you back later.
He calls me ten times a day.
You don't mind hearing us, do you?
Of course not.
He's far away right now, you see.
-What is it?
-You look happy, that's all.
Really? I do?
Oh, right. I should wrap that up.
We managed to sneak past his manager
out of the green room,
but there were fans everywhere.
I held my bias's hand and ran for it.
We arrived at the parking lot,
but the fans were there too,
so we ended up huddling down together
between the van and the wall.
-I could hear his heart beating fast.
-Oh God.
And with it, I could feel his warmth.
And then…
This is insane.
Here?
What? Is there a problem?
No. There's no problem.
Babe, wait.
What if my manager walks in on--
Be quiet.
Okay.
Stay still.
Stop.
You… want to pick another one?
Yes.
Calm down a bit.
Let's try just ten themes a week.
How come? I have tons of free time.
Well, at this rate,
you'll have met all 900 of them
by next month.
You know,
I really like it here.
I can see that.
It's a massive dopamine boost.
My confidence is soaring.
And no one here is calling me man-crazy,
dissing me for not taking
my relationships seriously.
I can just move on to the next guy.
On top of all that,
even when I try the themes
everyone else is having trouble with,
I can clear them in one go.
I really, really love that.
Being overwhelmingly good at something.
It's such a rush!
Submit.
THANK YOU
BOYFRIEND ON DEMAND 178TH THEME REVIEW
THE GUY NEXT DOOR
592 LIKES, 930 COMMENTS
What's this?
Why are there so many comments?
YOUR POST JUST HIT 10,000 VIEWS!
Your post just hit 10,000 views!
Wait, what is happening right now?
Who put up all these decorations,
and when?
I wonder.
What are you doing for Seollal?
Me? I'm just going to eat tangerines
and read comic books.
My mom told me not to come over
since she's going on a trip,
so I'll be rotting away at home
for five days.
Well, all the better.
Take the chance to rest.
He offered to help us with this.
I'll put the tree in the storeroom later.
Should I start with this one?
Yes.
Do you have plans for the holidays?
I'm going to read comic books
and eat tangerines.
What?
You guys really…
Whatever am I gonna do about you nerds?
You're reading comic books
in the age of OTT platforms?
Mr. Hwang keeps calling me uncultured,
and it's all because of you guys.
Stop reading them now.
You guys have read enough.
I'll go put these in the archives.
It's dangerous out there.
What are you doing?
You can't follow me in here.
What's wrong?
I'm only here to put this away.
Hey! Then I'll go out first.
Wait a second.
-What if someone sees us?
-Just act natural.
That's easier said than done.
Man, I'm a terrible liar.
The office life will be the death of me.
Should we just get caught?
You are insane.
Sweetie.
-Are you okay?
-Huh?
I am okay.
Having fun teasing me?
What about dinner?
I have a meeting with Ms. Yun.
Eat without me.
I'll pick you up later.
Order some food for me.
My wrist is killing me!
This industry overworks its authors
way too much.
I'll reduce the number of panels
in my next contract.
Soon, I won't even be able to
hold up a spoon.
Yun Song's contract is almost up.
At this rate, we'll never renew
the contract on good terms.
Have you talked to Director Hwang
about your next contract yet?
No. Come to think of it,
he hasn't mentioned it yet.
I'm sure he will soon.
Ms. Yun, if we wait until the next season,
it will be too late.
Do you have a solution?
Do you remember
when PlanC first joined us on Fridays?
It's time for us to find out what's wrong
and make changes like we did then.
This is something you need to do.
There has to be something only you can do.
Seo.
Are you trying to dump it on me?
It's not like that.
I'm also going to give it my all.
But still, please don't forget
that this is your work.
I just don't know anymore.
This is too difficult.
Can I take a look?
Sure.
THE MAN TO KNOW
STORY DEVELOPMENT OUTLINE
What do you think?
It might catch attention
for a little while, but…
But that's it, huh?
Yes.
This won't do at all.
We need to get through this
if we want to beat PlanC.
Stop looking. I've already shown
too much to my competition.
Adorable.
What?
I mean,
why are you so adorable?
Hey now, that's no way to talk about
someone who's working hard.
-Hmph.
-"Hey now"?
Could you draw a picture for me too?
Like the one you gave to Hwany.
Sure.
Really? You mean it?
Yes.
Would you like me to draw you?
What?
Want me to draw you?
You don't like that?
No, I love it.
This is something you need to do.
There has to be something only you can do.
Oh God, seriously.
Why does everyone keep bitching at me?
For goodness' sake.
I mean, everyone with a mouth
keeps spouting off at the author!
Easy for them to say.
I'd like to see them try.
They'd manage, what, three panels?
No, not even a single panel,
and they keep giving me orders.
I work hard, they say, "Make it fun."
I make it fun, they say, "Work faster."
Damn it! It's so annoying, seriously!
Going on another hiatus, then?
No. I mean, I have to push through.
So you don't put that producer
in a hard spot?
It's not that, but…
You know,
I just don't want to let her down.
Why's that? Because she's your friend?
You've got such a kind heart, Song.
You're the only person who says I'm kind.
People don't know
what they're talking about.
I should get going.
Huh? Where to?
You should work hard
to not let your friend down,
and I should help you get motivated.
Come see me at my workplace in a bit.
What's this? He told me to come here.
Oh my!
You're here.
What's this? Hansel and Gretel?
Nothing beats sweet treats
when you're feeling down.
It seems to be working.
HANDMADE TOFU RESTAURANT
Why does this guy always tag along
when our team comes out to eat?
Come on, Naemo's a small company.
We're all on the same team.
Oh, right you are.
This is a place where any romance…
That ad is everywhere these days.
There are 900 themes just for you.
It's getting a ton of buzz right now,
so they are striking while the iron's hot.
I think that's our real competition,
not the other webtoon platforms.
Why would anyone use that anyway?
What do you mean, why?
What girl wouldn't want to date
an attractive guy?
Are you a subscriber?
-Just eat your food.
-Okay.
So, who will you be dating today?
It's been a while. Go for drinks?
Seriously?
Why even ask? We definitely should!
What time do you finish work today?
Join us as soon as you can.
I can't promise anything.
Ms. Yun is so unpredictable.
Goodness, you poor thing.
Kyeong-nam, you should come with us.
I also have a deadline.
I should head back with her.
How come?
Hwany's already submitted his work.
-What?
-Look.
Going home now! Enjoy today's episode!
Since when did he post that kind of stuff?
I guess that means
you can come with us, right?
Call me when you finish.
-Let's go!
-Let's go.
Wait, I…
I…
To that place we went to last time.
Okay!
DON'T BE TOO LATE, BUT TAKE YOUR TIME!
Maybe I pushed her too much.
Seo Mi-rae!
Did you hear something just now?
Sorry?
I didn't hear
a thing.
I see.
Am I hearing things?
Why did you come here?
Wow, it's Seo Mi-rae.
I put my finger on this thingy,
but it wouldn't open.
-Thank God.
-It's supposed to open, right?
How much did you drink?
Why are you so drunk?
Enjoy.
I've never seen anyone get drunk
and go home before the food is served.
I know, right?
Why did you offer him a drink
as soon as we got here?
Who knew one glass would knock him out?
I wonder if he got home safe.
Oh God!
I'm fine though.
No. The fact that you came here
means you're not fine.
What did you even tell the others
before you left?
I told them I was heading home.
You did well.
Stay here until I finish my work, okay?
So I did well?
-Stay.
Hey. I'll be going home now.
Sure. Good night.
-Get home safe. See you tomorrow.
-Sure.
-Good work today.
-Goodbye, then.
Really? It's only ten o'clock.
Have you sobered up a bit?
You really shouldn't have come here.
That was so close.
I'm sorry. I just missed you so much.
Oh, you. You did well.
Let's go now.
Ms. Yun submitted her work early,
so I'm heading out.
Did you match them up again?
I think I might have.
So how many did you match up today?
I can go by myself.
I should still walk you all the way.
Okay, then.
-Haven't you forgotten something?
-What do you mean?
Just go already.
Anything else?
Keep that up, and I won't let you go.
I'm home.
I hereby forbid you from drinking
without me. See you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow.
Sheesh, he never sends me
so much as a heart.
1: THE MAN TO KNOW
2: PLANC
Hey.
Ms. Yun, have you seen the rankings?
Yes, I just saw.
I'm exhausted after working all night.
Our readers are loving it right now.
I knew you could do it.
But how did you even come up with
something like that at the perfect moment?
A chef with a big heart
who's the polar opposite of Choi Si-woo
as the second male lead.
The hotel will make a great setup
for a love triangle.
It just…
came to me out of the blue.
We all have those days to be grateful for.
Well, I'm loving it.
Glad to hear that.
Enjoy the holidays.
Let's keep at it when we get back.
Ms. Yun.
I'm so glad to be working with you.
Didn't expect that.
Go to bed. I'm hanging up now.
Okay. Good night.
Awesome!
Congratulations.
Thank you.
You've done well.
What?
What's up with him?
That heart emoji came out of nowhere.
Everything is just perfect.
Is it okay for me to be this happy?
-Hey, so--
-What am I going to do?
-Huh?
-What am I supposed to do?
What do you mean? Just work hard.
Damn it. You never have a game plan
for anything, ever.
No author needs to have a game plan.
Just have fun, work hard, and draw well.
God, just forget I said anything.
Why are you putting your coat on?
Huh?
Isn't it a bit chilly in here?
Why are you being so weird?
What do you mean?
You've been fidgeting
like you need a bathroom break.
Do you have somewhere to be?
Huh?
I have to leave before dinner.
Come on! Such a buzzkill.
We finally found the time to hang out.
I can't believe you used to go on
about him being a jerk.
This is why I never believe you.
Hey, that was, like, ages ago.
It wasn't even that long ago.
Hey, but really--
You have to go soon?
Don't worry. I'll let you off soon.
I'm busy too, you know.
Why are you busy?
-I also have a date.
-You said you were going home.
That's right. An at-home date.
You said you weren't dating,
and you're already having a guy over?
I guess I am.
Yeah, I think you should get a set today.
What?
Hey! I was just looking.
The red one?
What do you think of that one?
I'm good. Just hurry up.
-I think it'll look good on you!
-Hurry up.
A little late, huh? Sorry.
Come on in.
-You must be cold.
-First, a gift.
Are you hungry?
I'm good for now.
Tell me if you get hungry.
I'll cook for you.
No, you're the guest.
I should be the one to cook.
I'll make you tteokguk.
I bought the ingredients.
What? You know how to do that too?
Man, I'm hungry.
I don't want to age another year.
Careful, I'm holding a knife.
Fine.
Then shall we eat later?
Shall we?
Sir, I think you should
take a look at this.
CONQUERING BOD BY BOYFRIENDKILLER
What am I looking at?
Apparently, it's all the rage
among our subscribers.
What is it?
Basically, it's like a walkthrough.
It seems the subscribers who had trouble
with their dates are really into it.
But it's not a game.
Who needs a walkthrough?
This user must be treating it like a game.
Eun-ho.
Do you have someone you like?
There's only one thing we need to
keep in mind in Boyfriend on Demand.
Want to try liking me?
Sure.
No matter how desirable a guy may be,
you are the star of the show.
What do you think? Do you like it?
Yes.
I'll take the necklace,
but can you throw in this hotel too?
So you don't need to feel intimidated
just because he is a chaebol…
Bang!
…or nervous about him being an NIS agent.
Are you okay?
Ms. Lee Ji-yeon,
you have obtained a love triangle item.
Oh my.
Are you worried about two-timing?
Well, don't be.
Dating two men isn't that bad.
I've done a lot worse.
So here's my recommendation.
"At night, play the love triangle theme
and pop two items to end up with four…"
Four? Four men?
Who… Who is this person?
We're investigating.
This must be all she ever thinks about.
A dating sim writer? Or a web novelist?
If this kind of fast-paced dating
becomes a trend,
the long-term subscription
will inevitably drop.
She dated 220 men in two months?
Is she out of her mind?
What's this?
Turns out I left one out
when I gave you those books.
I'd been wondering about that. Thanks.
I'll see you tonight.
I have a meeting to attend.
Okay.
-Ms. Seo.
-Huh?
Yes. What is it?
An article just came out.
An article? What article?
I think you need to see this right away.
TMTK ACCUSED OF PLAGIARIZING
BOYFRIEND ON DEMAND
Famous author Yun Song
has been caught up in another scandal.
Several posts pointed out the similarities
between a new male character
in her hit webtoon, The Man to Know,
and a character from Boyfriend on Demand,
the dating subscription service.
The allegations claim that
the character's stature, thick eyebrows,
and occupation as a five-star hotel chef
all come together to make him
a carbon copy of a character
from Boyfriend on Demand.
This device is switched off.
Is Ms. Yun not picking up?
What are we going to do?
-What's going on?
-Sir.
-Hello?
-Hey, is what they're saying true?
-I'll call them right now.
-Do it now!
Call the reporters right now
and find out what happened.
Hold on. Can anyone reach Yun Song?
Has she really been on
this Boyfriend on Demand thing?
FEELINGS ARE NOW A PRODUCT
POPULAR WEBTOON AUTHOR YUN SONG UNDER FIRE
Our birth rates are low as it is.
This is unacceptable.
What's this got to do
with low birth rates?
It's giving people such high standards
that they don't even want to date anymore.
The subscription fee is so high.
It's left countless young people in debt.
How do you afford the subscription?
Are your parents paying for you?
-You're so pathetic.
-Pathetic?
Goofing around in the virtual world.
I bet she's a total loser.
Loser?
You lousy little shits!
Where is she?
I don't know.
I waited, thinking she might show up,
but she didn't.
What are we going to do?
It's going to be okay. Let me come inside.
Are you kidding? So this was the boyfriend
she bragged about back then.
I can't even…
Didn't she get all preachy on us, saying
that our lives are duller than hers?
Man, she turned out to be
one hell of a woman.
That's what I call a poker face.
-Did you even prepare for this meeting?
-Hey.
Isn't this going to hurt So-yeong as well?
I mean, think about it.
If TMTK were to get cancelled,
So-yeong would end up jobless, right?
Well, I guess that could happen.
No, we can't let that happen. No way.
Hey, don't do it.
So-yeong, are you doing okay?
If you find yourself in need of a new job,
I'll set you up with a good one.
Don't send that.
What on earth was she thinking?
How could she screw you over like this?
Please get back to me.
I'm worried about you.
She didn't screw me over. Got it?
Besides, I'm also on Boyfriend on Demand,
so mind your own business!
Huh?
Kyeong-nam.
God, I told you not to send it.
Hello.
Have you eaten?
No.
Where are you?
At Ms. Yun's studio.
So-yeong just left,
but I think I'll wait a little longer.
She might show up late, after all.
If you just got off work,
can you do me a favor?
Of course. What is it?
The thumb drive with our meeting notes
is at my place,
and I want to check them right now.
But I'm worried Ms. Yun might come here
while I'm away.
I'm sorry, but could you go to my place
and send them to me?
I'll head over right now.
Thank you.
I think I'll be home really late.
But can you still wait for me?
Sure. I'll see you later.
See you.
BOYFRIEND ON DEMAND
Why would anyone use that anyway?
BOYFRIEND ON DEMAND REVIEW
TRIAL TIME: 50 HOURS
USER SATISFACTION SURVEY
Damn it.
Damn it. Come on!
Why isn't he picking up?
SEO MI-RAE
Taxi!
Yongsan, please.
Pick up!
8. REVIEW
Damn it.
Mi-rae.
Why are you here?
Well, your phone…
Why didn't you pick up your phone?
I was busy cleaning.
Are you all right?
Thank you.
Is something wrong?
Is it because of Ms. Yun?
No.
Or did the director say something?
Why did you race home? I'm worried.
It's just that
I was scared.
Of what?
Just
scared of everything.
I'm sure Ms. Yun will be okay.
I can't tell him what I'm scared of.
I just can't bring myself to tell him.
When was this taken?
She looks good in it.
I WANTED TO TELL YOU THAT I LIKE YOU
I was a little mad at you.
For not even answering me
when I asked you to come with me.
So I was just going to get over you, but
it's harder than I thought.
I miss you.
Seo Mi-rae.
What took you so long?
What?
How is this…
Subtitle translation by: Daham Yoon