I’ve got another job for you.
Get close to some hitmen.
What’s your name?
Bison
What the hell are you doing?
What do I have to do if I want to be the first guy to take you out?
Win Fadel over.
You want me to hit on that jerk?
Give me your dad’s car.
- Deal.
I’d be dancing so close to you.
Let go!
I’m gonna take you out!
You’re friends?
Ugh, wait.
Hold on.
He’s way too heavy.
What the hell are you whining about now?
We’ve dealt with much heavier trash.
You’ve been slacking off.
Where’s your mind at?
Don’t blame me.
I’m neat like I always am with all my jobs.
Neat?
You forgot to bring our gloves.
Come on. It happens.
Don’t mix things up.
Please, Fadel.
Can’t you just give him a chance.
He’s just a normal harmless tattooist.
His parents are both dead.
Now he lives with his brother.
What’s so suspicious about him?
He only shows you what he wants you to see.
The same way he doesn’t know who you really are.
What if I want him to know?
I’ll make sure he’s dead.
Come on, Fadel.
You know damn well
Mother doesn’t want us getting involved with anyone.
So we’re just supposed to live like this?
No social life with anyone else?
What’s wrong with that?
You don’t need anyone else.
Hurry up.
Too bad I have an actual beating heart,
unlike the dead cold thing in your chest.
You talk too much.
Uncle.
Three sticky rice and fried pork, please.
Of course.
You mind waiting, son?
It’s better fresh off the stove.
No problem.
Excuse me. Make way.
Make way, please.
Uncle!
I’ll be back.
Can I borrow your cart?
What do you need it for?
I’m on my way to sell the fresh produce.
Please.
I’ll help you sell it.
I’ll sell it all.
Thank you.
Excuse me. Make way.
Heavy stuff incoming.
Make way, please.
Oh, I’m sorry.
You!
You’re in the way.
Look how you ruined my produce.
You work pushing carts in the market?
Yeah, what about it?
You got a problem with that?
Are you looking down on me?
Hey.
I haven’t said a thing.
I can see it in your eyes.
See how you don’t seem to help me pick them up?
You’re blowing my ears off.
When’d I have time to pick them up?
And I didn’t do anything wrong.
I was just walking when you knocked into me.
If this is the best you can do with a cart, don’t bother.
You’re a menace to everyone else.
Now how’d I sell anything today?
You have to take responsibility for this.
What are you talking about?
Don’t you realize every baht I make is hard earned?
How unlucky I am to run into a mean guy like you.
My dear fellow hardworking people,
listen up.
This guy ruined my produce,
and then blamed me and looked down on me.
This is just unacceptable!
Enough.
- My dear fellow hardworking people.
- Hey!
- Look at him!
- That’s enough!
That’s enough!
I’ll take responsibility for it.
So this is as little as you think of me?
Hey, take it or leave it.
Thank you.
You humiliated me.
Now it’s my turn.
We’re even.
Your produce are all dirty now.
I don’t think you can sell them like this.
I’ll clean them up.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Can I borrow this?
Of course.
Thank you.
Take it.
Thanks.
Hey!
You’re supposed to clean the vegetables, not me!
Watch out!
Hey!
There you go.
Is this your cat?
No.
Just something I came up with.
You want a cat tattoo but you don’t have a cat?
That’s weird.
I like that they’re unpredictable.
Sometimes they act like they love you and want you,
and then go ahead and ignore you.
Treat you like a total stranger.
It’s challenging.
So you love a challenge.
But this is quite detailed.
It’s going to take some time.
You’re not afraid of needles, are you?
Pain kinda excites me, really.
Where would you like it done, dear customer?
I don’t know.
I’ll print it out and see where it fits.
You decide where you want it.
This doesn't look bad.
It lines up nicely.
I think it’s going to look great.
I was thinking I wanted it done on my thigh.
What do you think?
It’d peak out when I wear shorts.
Quite cool, isn’t it?
Let’s try it.
How about here?
A little higher.
Here?
Higher.
Hey.
Any higher than this
and it’s not inking we’re doing soon.
What are you gonna do?
If I start anything here,
don’t blame me, Mr. Customer.
Inappropriately touching a client is illegal, you know?
But I can’t help myself
when you’re literally coaxing me into it.
Well, then…
I’ll think about where I want the tattoo to be
and I’ll tell you.
I want it somewhere I can show it off,
but also somewhere I can hide easily.
I think…
Having it somewhere discreet might not be bad.
Make it exclusive for your special someone.
Then I guess no one will ever get to see it,
seeing that I don’t have someone like that.
It’s all up to you, then.
Just let me know where you want it.
I can do it anywhere.
Do what?
What’s on your mind?
I’m talking about the tattoo, of course.
Anywhere on your body, I’ll etch it.
Every nook and cranny.
I’m leaving.
See you.
I have to help my brother out at the restaurant.
Bye.
Ain’t no way I’m doing it.
Style.
You can’t give up now.
You promised you’d help me.
It’s impossible.
aking that mad dog out is impossible.
Did you know he literally threw me out of his joint?
He’s a damn barbarian.
Don’t be a puss.
You gotta give it a try, dude.
You said you’d do anything for my car, right?
Help me out, then.
Meet me halfway.
Find out what that mad dog does all day.
I’ll find a way to get close to him.
How’d I even know that?
I don’t care.
Ask your man or whatever.
They’re brothers, aren’t they?
Help me,
and you might get with him sooner.
Aww, did you miss me?
Look at you.
Bison.
Don’t even think about it.
You know cats tend to stay in one place.
Don’t even think about taking it in.
I’m not.
But look at him.
He’s so damn cute.
How could I resist?
Am I right, little guy?
If you play with him every day like that,
you’ll only regret it when we have to move again.
I don’t want to move.
I told you, Fadel.
I need a break.
Fine. I’ll talk to Mother.
But before that, come help me out inside.
We get a lot of customers during lunch break.
I can’t handle everything myself.
Do it yourself.
Right?
Bison!
Yeah.
I’m coming.
Hurry up.
Yeah.
Let me repeat your order.
So there’s one cheeseburger,
one fries,
one beef burger,
and one carbonara.
One water with two ice.
Is that correct?
Yes.
Okay.
Please wait a moment.
Here’s the menu.
TOILET
You…
Kant.
Hey.
What are you showing up here for?
Aren’t you scared of my brother?
Your place is crawling with customers.
I doubt your brother has time to welcome me.
Who knows?
What are you doing?
We can’t do it here.
But I miss you.
No can do.
What are you here for, honestly?
Well…
The friend I asked to take your brother out said
he wanted some information on Fadel.
He wants to know how he spends his day.
So he knows how to approach him.
What does that have to do with me?
I need your help.
Please.
I don’t know anything like that.
We might be brothers,
but he doesn’t tell me stuff.
You sure your friend knows what he’s doing?
This isn’t very promising.
Find someone else.
I swear no one is as shameless as this guy.
Give Style some time.
Once he gets your brother hooked,
we can…
Bison?
Bison!
Yeah?
What?
What the hell are you doing in there?
Hurry up and help me out.
We’re busy as hell.
Ow!
Ow, my tummy!
I’m having some stomach issues here, man.
Just make it quick.
And wash your hands.
Yeah, alright.
See?
You can’t see me here anymore.
It’s too dangerous.
We’ll meet outside.
Okay.
But I can’t wait to spend more time with you.
With no interruptions, that is.
Okay?
Alright.
I’ll try to look something up.
Okay?
Enough.
Let’s go.
Fadel.
What’s your problem?
Look at this.
Who the hell did this to us?
Who could it be?
Where did you get this?
Someone sent it into our restaurant’s inbox.
I think it’s some kids in the area.
I’ve seen them around for a while.
We might need to teach them kids a lesson or two.
Alright.
Let’s go.
What is it?
My tummy hurts.
Since this morning.
I don’t know what happened.
Does it hurt that bad?
Shouldn’t you see a doctor?
I just need a little rest.
Why don’t you just go before they ruin our place?
Fine.
I’ll be back quickly,
with some medicine.
Bye, big bro.
GROCERY SHOPPING
You drew these?
You’re quite good.
Your brother does all these in a day?
That about sums him up, yeah.
He plans everything
down from years, months, weeks, to days.
Your friend has to show up
at exactly the time I wrote down.
Or else he’s going to miss him.
Alright.
I’ll tell him.
I think this is gonna be helpful.
Give your friend a fair warning.
Fadel’s a cautious guy.
If he knows your friend is there to hit on him,
he might just disappear.
You can trust him.
He’ll get it done soon.
Let’s talk about us.
Did you give it a thought?
Are you asking me out?
What else could I possibly be doing?
Don’t you think you get serious too soon?
We just met.
What’s the hurry?
You greenlit me to have my friend take your brother out.
Wasn’t it because you wanted us to be something?
I just want Fadel to let his hair down a bit.
I need some time to live my own life.
Don’t you think we should
just keep it casual between you and me?
I don’t want no casual.
I’m serious.
We jumped into bed on our first night,
and you want me to believe you’re serious about me?
But I stopped doing that
since the day I met you.
You’re the only one I’ve been chasing around.
Don’t you trust me at all?
You’ve still got a lot to prove.
Is your customer gone?
Yeah.
I doubt he’s just a regular customer.
You guys seemed awfully close at one point.
Were you sneaking around?
Of course not.
This place just isn’t that big.
I couldn’t help it, you know?
Well, well.
So he refused to be your boyfriend?
Poor guy.
After all that effort, he said no.
Your Romeo day has come to an end, brother.
That hurts.
It was supposed to.
Might shut you up a bit.
Don’t you know this kind of thing well?
What, you got someone?
No.
I just learned these things from my books.
Well, then, based on your books,
what should I do in this situation?
In my books,
there’s always some obstacles
before they end up together.
Obstacles?
Something to overcome to show them
that you’re willing to fight for them.
Like in Romeo and Juliet,
you know their parents forbid them, right?
So Romeo does everything to be with Juliet.
When Juliet sees that,
she realizes that Romeo really loves her.
What should I do?
Make sure he knows he really matters to you.
JOGGING
Good morning, there.
Are you following me?
Surely not.
I live around here.
I just want to be healthy and strong
and take in the fresh morning air.
But jogging alone is kinda lonely, don’t you think?
Can I join you?
It’s jogging,
not badminton.
You can do it solo.
But some things are better done together.
Hey.
What are you gonna do?
You gonna wash me up again?
Scared?
Of course not.
I just don’t want to get soaked today.
If you follow me again,
you’re not just getting soaked next time.
What you gonna do to me?
Hey!
That hurts!
If you want to join me, catch up.
Wait!
F-A-D-E-L.
Fadel, Fadel, Fadel.
Fadel!
Guys, let’s cheer him on.
Fadel, do your best.
Fadel, run that race.
Fadel, go chase.
Fadel, do your best.
He’s the best-best.
Fadel’s the best-best.
Better than the rest!
F-A.
D-E-L!
Fadel, Fadel, Fadel.
Fadel!
Thank you.
Here.
Your produce is fresh as always.
Thank you.
Hello.
What would you like today?
Some ground pork and tenderloin, please.
Hello, there.
How much do you want for that?
Don’t tell me you’re a butcher, too.
Hell yeah.
I’m taking odd jobs.
I fix cars.
I push carts.
I sell pork.
I can’t be a chooser when I don’t want to be a beggar.
How much do you want for that?
Go on.
Two kilograms of ground pork.
And two of tenderloin.
Would you like your pork farm-raised,
or grass-fed?
Hey.
I’m in a hurry to open my restaurant.
Can you stop messing around?
I’m not messing with you.
It’s all about the quality, you know?
Ask her if you don’t believe me.
Never mind.
I’ll buy it somewhere else.
Hey, hold it.
It runs out everywhere else.
You’re late to the market today.
You were wasting my time.
Fine.
I’ll sell it to you.
Under one condition.
You have to let me eat at your place for a week,
on the house.
And no chasing me out.
I threw you out
because you were drunk
and disorderly.
Yeah.
That was my bad.
I’ll behave next time I go to your place.
I’ll be the perfect customer for you to serve.
Auntie.
Let’s get him what he asked for.
Do we deliver?
We do.
For our regulars.
It’s alright.
Hey.
Don’t you know
it’s bad manners to turn her down?
Here.
How much?
Well, let’s go.
We’re here.
Now go.
Hey.
I told you not to chase me out.
I have to get ready to open.
I don’t have time to cook for you.
I’ll wait right here
until you’re done.
I’d like to be the first to eat…
you.
Wow. Wow. Wow.
I was wondering why you took so long at the market.
So someone was walking you home.
You don’t get to scold me for this anymore, you know?
Walk me home, my ass.
He was in the way.
He’s trouble.
One more thing,
this guy is friends with that tattooist.
Careful.
They might be working together.
“That tattooist” is called Kant.
I don’t give two rat’s ass what he’s called.
Just be careful.
What’s with you?
You overanalyze everything.
What are you, a conspiracy theorist?
If this wasn’t just pure coincidence,
then it was…
Destiny.
Destiny, my foot.
I bet you’re at least curious about him.
♪ My brother is in love ♪
♪ Someone walks him to his burger joint ♪
Beef… Burger.
Cheese…
Hey.
Hi?
Style, right?
I’m Bison.
I’m Fadel’s brother.
Right.
Kant told me about you.
Sorry I was taking orders from some customers for you.
Oh, hey, it’s no biggie.
Thanks.
Well,
now that I see you up close, I get him.
How he’s so head over heels for you.
Oh, I doubt it’s like that.
Kant has never fallen for anyone like this.
This is the most down bad I’ve ever seen him.
I don’t think so.
I think it’s too soon for him to be down bad.
We just met, you know?
Hey.
I know Kant asked you to hit on my brother.
I just want to tell you that,
I know you’re doing this for Kant,
but if you actually like him at some point,
just go for it.
I just want to see him with someone.
It’s unlikely at the moment.
He can’t even talk to me nicely.
Do your best.
That’s Fadel for you.
He’s rough on the outside,
and on the inside.
You gotta give him a good beating.
Bye.
Chef, one juicy beef burger.
One crispy fries with lots of ketchup.
No veggies, please.
And now,
you have 15 minutes to impress the judges.
If you’re ready,
grab your tools.
Begin.
Go for it.
Chop faster.
Slice faster.
Do it faster.
Faster.
Faster!
Can you do it even faster?
Is this the best you can do?
We’ve got hungry customers outside.
Hurry up.
Hey there.
Are you talking to me?
Yeah.
Mind if I join you?
Oh.
I’m waiting for a friend.
He’s probably working.
But he’ll be here any minute.
How about we bowl together while you wait?
It’d be more fun that way.
Sure.
I’m Tawan.
Bison.
That’s a cool name.
Strong,
but adorable.
Thanks.
That was alright.
Look up there.
Well done.
That was a good stance.
You think?
You mean this one?
Yeah.
I throw so much better.
Should we go another round?
Bison.
Oh.
Sorry I’m late.
Something urgent came up.
No need to apologize.
I wasn’t going anywhere anyway.
Oh.
Tawan, this is Kant.
Kant, this is Tawan.
He was just joining me.
Hey.
I saw he was waiting all alone
so I kept him company.
Didn’t want him getting stood up.
He was just teaching me how to bowl like this.
Did he?
I didn’t ask, though.
And I taught him that trick.
Oh.
I see.
And I was just trying to keep him off the radar.
Someone as cute as him would attract so many guys, you know?
But now that I think about it,
I’m one of those guys myself.
Well, I’m here now.
Bison doesn’t need your protection.
Unless…
you’re the one I need to protect him from.
I get it.
I’ll go back to my alley, alright.
It was nice to meet you.
We’re not dating, you know?
And you’re getting jealous already?
Just a bit.
I’ll do anything for you.
If the next set is too much,
let me help.
Don’t worry about me.
I know my limits.
Whoa.
Your veins look so cool.
How’d you find out about my gym?
Hey.
This is a public gym.
It opens 24/7.
799 baht a month.
As if I would miss out on such a good deal.
I’ve been trying to build my muscles, you see.
Maybe one day I’ll look as good as you.
If you plan to frequent this place,
come during the day.
Because I’m here at night.
What?
We can’t show up at the same time?
No.
It’s less crowded at night.
I don’t like when it’s crowded.
But I get frustrated at night.
I need to let off some steam.
I need to sweat it out.
If you need a spotter,
just holler.
I’ll be around here.
Yes!
See?
Told you I never lose.
You know what?
I let you win.
I just love seeing that smile on your face.
Oh, hey.
Your friend Style is quite something.
He’s not afraid of Fadel at all.
I’m a bit shaken to think he’d find out
I have something to do with this.
He’d kill me if he knew.
I doubt it.
You guys are brothers.
I’m sure you can talk it out.
You did this because you’re worried about him.
You just want him to enjoy life, don’t you?
Yeah.
Mother did say
Fadel is too high strung,
while I’m too laid-back.
No middle ground between us.
You call your mom “Mother”?
What are you, a young master?
Not at all.
It’s just our family’s inside joke.
I see.
Hello!
And here’s the moment you’ve all been waiting for:
“Murder on the Dancefloor.”
You’re all welcome on the dancefloor to set it ablaze.
We don’t mind friend duos, couples, or whatever.
Just waltz right on!
The winner takes home this week’s trophy
and a 3000-baht voucher at our diner.
Let’s go!
Count me in!
Hey, you serious?
Of course.
I want that trophy.
Will you dance with me?
I don’t know how to dance.
It’s embarrassing.
Embarrassing?
You were just telling me you’d do anything for me.
But not this little thing?
Let’s do it, then.
Let’s go.
♪ You’re all so sweet ♪
♪ Babe, you’re not being discreet ♪
♪ Every word I say, you heed ♪
♪ I think there’s something from me you need ♪
♪ Honey, I see you right through ♪
♪ There’s no hiding with you ♪
♪ That old joke you bring up, too ♪
♪ I think I know what you’re trying to do ♪
♪ You know, you’re not very subtle ♪
♪ What you show me isn’t mixed signal ♪
♪ Honestly, it’s nothing you have to say ♪
♪ You’re scheming ♪
♪ Your eyes give it away ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ Oh, I know ♪
♪ Baby, exactly what you think ♪
♪ With that look in your eyes ♪
♪ I know what your heart feels inside ♪
Hot, isn’t it?
What are you doing?
What?
Does my naked body make you feel uncomfortable?
There’s no rule against being naked in a sauna.
I just need the heat to seep through every pore on my body.
I’m not uncomfortable.
Do whatever you want.
Just leave me alone.
Alright.
But you’re allowed to look, you know?
I don’t mind.
I know it’s kinda irresistible.
But hey.
Why does it have to be a burger joint?
Why not local food or barbeque?
Why not hot pot or dumplings?
Those are the trends, you know.
No talking in the sauna.
Be quiet.
I really like your name, by the way.
“Fadel.”
It has such a nice ring.
And a good meaning.
“Someone who is virtuous,
generous,
and pure.”
How’d you know that?
Well, it’s such a unique name.
I got curious.
Well, the meaning doesn’t reflect you, to be fair.
You’re not generous,
and you’re not…
I don’t think you’re “pure.”
Cool tattoo.
Damn it, uncle.
Where’d he gone?
Who sent you?
No one did.
Who’d you think you are?
A celebrity?
You’re lying.
You suddenly live at my pace.
Morning jogging, grocery shopping,
showing up at my burger joint,
and now frequenting the same gym?
You want me to believe it’s all coincidental?
Of course not.
It’s not a coincidence.
I follow you.
So you’re finally admitting it.
Who sent you?
I like you.
I liked you the moment I crashed into you that night.
It was love at first sight.
So damn romantic.
Straight out of a movie.
Or a freaking soap opera.
I don’t believe you.
You don’t believe me
because you’ve never felt like that with anybody.
This is the kind of thing that takes a heart to understand.
When you know you meet the right one,
you do whatever it takes to get them.
What the hell are you doing?
Stop following me.
Don’t say I didn’t warn you.
Is this even worth dying for?
You said you didn’t know how to dance.
You did it so well that I had the courage to do it, too.
I think we match each other’s pace so well.
Both in dancing,
and in…
In what?
In whatever we were doing that first night we met.
I don’t remember, really.
Well, wanna come over tonight?
We can retrace our steps.
Oh, you pervert, you.
I can’t.
Fadel won’t let me.
Okay.
Understandable.
But I’ll wait until we…
get to retrace our steps.
Enough of that.
I’m leaving.
I park over there.
Don’t I deserve something, too?
You get the trophy.
I get nothing.
What do you want?
That’s hardly enough.
One more here, please.
Actually…
Something’s still missing.
I think around here.
You really don’t know when to stop, huh?
I’m going.
Get home safe.
Bye.
Kant.
Crap!
Tawan.
It’s me, dude.
Well, how was that?
Did I do a good job hitting on your boyfriend?
You did amazing.
But he’s not my boyfriend yet.
I’ll hire you for something else next time.
Sure, sure.
Here.
With tips.
Of course.
Thanks, man.
Keep me in the loops.
See ya.
Make sure he knows he really matters to you.
♪ You know, you’re not very subtle ♪
♪ What you show me isn’t mixed signal ♪
♪ Honestly, it’s nothing you have to say ♪
♪ You’re scheming ♪
♪ Your eyes give it away ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ Oh, I know ♪
♪ Baby, exactly what you think ♪
Shit!
Ugh, Fadel.
What the hell are you playing?
I thought you were a burglar.
Idiot.
Why were you being so careless?
If it wasn’t me, you’d have been in a hearse already.
Where have you been to come home in the morning?
It’s Friday night.
Get used to it.
What’s with the trophy?
Oh.
It’s…
I won a sushi-eating competition.
I was so good at it.
I ate almost 50 sushis within 30 minutes.
I was, like, so stuffed, Fadel.
And–And…
They make really good sushi.
I’ll probably take you there and try it some time.
That’s the best story you can come up with?
Fadel, come on.
This is why I didn’t want to tell you.
What if someone made you out?
Fadel.
We’re in the internet era.
Don’t you think having no social media
would be weirder?
People will just clock us immediately.
I’m doing this for us, you know?
I’m trying to blend in.
Stop bullshiting me.
Fine.
Who posted that?
Was it the bowling place?
I’ll tell them to delete it.
If they refuse, I’ll blow their heads off.
Alright?
Save your sarcasm.
What about that tattooist?
What is he to you?
We’re not dating yet, if that’s what you mean.
We’re just taking it slow.
What about you?
What of that guy who won’t leave you alone?
Does he pique your interest?
He’s kinda cute.
And he doesn’t seem to be scared of you.
I like him.
He annoys the hell out of me.
Don’t change the subject.
We’re talking about you.
He clearly wants something from you.
What else do you think he wants from me, Fadel?
He wants my body.
He wants my heart.
Look at how adorable I am.
Fadel!
How should I even help you now?
If you want a break, behave.
Or else everything’s just coming back to bite you in the ass.
Understood?
Fine.
I just need the heat to seep through every pore on my body.
You’re allowed to look.
I know it’s kinda irresistible.
I really like your name, by the way.
“Fadel.”
Cool tattoo.
I think you should get inside their house.
You want me to enter the tigers’ lair,
you sure I won’t get clawed to death?
If I win,
we’re going to your house tonight.
And if I win,
can I continue what we were doing at your tattoo parlour?
I’ll give you a good time.
I don’t like being pursued.
You don’t fall for me just a little?
I think there’s something fishy about Fadel.
He’s suspicious.
I don’t like being left in the dark.