(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
YUMI'S CELLS 3
EPISODE 13
BETWEEN COLDNESS AND PASSION
So? So what happened?
So I asked him.
"Why has the dragon
kept appearing all this time?"
A dragon wouldn't just fly around
in the sky for no reason, right?
"The sky looked empty,
so I just drew a dragon."
- Does that make any sense?
- He's always like that. He truly is.
And when he gets criticized for it,
he's like, "What did I do wrong?"
This is how someone in Low Power Mode
endures a company dinner.
They stop thinking.
Let's just rest.
To conserve energy
the village is dark.
EMOTION
And it's always kind of chilly.
It's cold.
What do you think, Shin PD?
Well.
- Is that it?
- I'm not thinking of anything.
- So cold.
- You're so cold.
People call that being cold.
There's rarely anything
to be passionate about.
However...
- Shin PD.
- Yes?
You can go ahead.
- Sorry?
- We'll look around
- eat, and return.
- I see.
- Then I'll...
- It's okay. We'll take care of it.
- No, I'll make a reservation...
- Hey.
We'll take care of it.
So you can go ahead.
Okay.
See you later.
I don't like him.
He mixes his work and private life.
And only his own feelings matter.
NOVELS, MARTIAL ARTS NOVELS,
COMICS, CHILDREN'S BOOKS
WE BUY AND SELL USED BOOKS
- Hello.
I really don't like him. You know?
Whatever. Just ignore it.
It's a fire.
Wait, what?
I didn't start a fire.
It's warm.
They were together all day
and just came in a little while ago.
I wonder if it's going well.
I mean
he was just so excited.
Really?
This is so annoying. Seriously.
The only time a person
in Low Power Mode flares up
is not because they like someone
but because they dislike them.
But don't you think
they look good together?
Not really.
What?
They don't look good together.
You don't think so? Why?
- Don't they look good together?
- No.
They don't.
WRITER KIM JU-HO
What is it now?
Yes, Mr. Kim.
Hey, Shin PD.
I heard you left with Ms. Kim.
Well...
Yeah, I did.
So?
Yes, since it's late.
I see.
She's probably not asleep yet, right?
But she's not answering her phone.
Bring Ms. Kim
and come over here.
Sorry?
That condescending jerk.
I really hate him.
Ms. Kim can't make it.
Why?
She went to the theater
to watch a movie.
- It just started, so it's two hours.
- What?
Wait, Soon-rok.
But that's a lie.
- What movie?
- So don't call Ms. Kim.
She won't pick up.
Wait, Soon-rok. Is this okay?
Yes.
Yes, I understand.
You don't have to interfere like this.
Wait, who is this?
I'm the only cell awake.
Who gave you the right?
Emotion! Why aren't you sleeping?
I'm starting a fire.
Why are you starting a fire?
No! Don't do anything stupid.
Well, I hate that guy.
- Hey, let go!
- I said no!
Hold it in!
Do you want to watch the movie together?
What is that?
DO YOU WANT TO
WATCH THE MOVIE TOGETHER?
You said you're more comfortable
watching alone.
No, wait. Soon-rok.
Do you want to watch it together?
I'll be right there.
It'll take me ten minutes.
I'll buy the tickets.
I'LL BUY THE TICKETS
This is so unlike Soon-rok.
Why is he interfering?
Ms. Kim said she wanted
to see the movie too.
That's why.
There it is.
NUMBER OF TICKETS
What?
Did Ms. Kim fly over here already?
What's going on?
What is this?
I'm screwed.
Ms. Kim.
What would you like to drink?
Coffee? Cola?
It's nighttime, so cola would be better.
Hey, let's order another cola.
Okay. I'll add one more cola.
I'm here too.
I heard you were watching a movie.
Well...
I wanted to see this movie too
so I rushed over.
Luckily, it hasn't started yet.
What?
Wait, what's going on?
Mr. Kim must have made Soon-rok
to send the text.
No way.
I think so.
Because he thought Yu-mi wouldn't come.
Are these guys serious?
I've let it slide, but I've had enough!
I see.
We were going
for a second round...
But a movie is better.
I like art too.
I see.
Oh, right. Which way is the theater?
- Is it that way?
- Yes.
Ms. Kim, let's go.
Let's go.
We have to stop them here.
The storm is coming.
There is nowhere left to hide.
Mr. Kim.
Mr. Kim?
- Ms. Kim.
- Thank you.
Gosh.
It feels new, watching a movie
all the way in Busan.
- It reminds me of the old days.
- Yes.
Gosh, when I came to Busan
to watch a baseball game
I didn't want to go home early
so I'd see a film and take the train.
- Yes.
- You are currently in Theater One.
Hey!
Gosh, that's funny.
That was funnier than I thought.
That was fun.
I thought it would be serious.
I'll go on ahead to the restroom.
Sure.
Shin PD.
- Where for the third round?
- Sorry?
- A third round?
- I don't want to leave just yet.
I don't think Ms. Kim will go to a bar.
Should we get beer
and go for a walk on the beach?
I told you not
to needlessly butt in, didn't I?
What is this?
This happened because you
needlessly started a fire.
I didn't start it.
It's your campfire. So who did it?
I don't know.
When I woke up, there was a fire.
You're not making any sense.
Just go to sleep, please.
I don't even have the energy to talk.
Yu-mi, let's hold back today.
It's too late.
The beach is nice.
Ms. Kim.
So, would you like to have a beer?
- With a nice beach breeze...
- Mr. Kim.
Do you like me?
- Sorry?
- I hate guys
who are not direct
and sneakily approach me
pretending it's just a joke.
I don't know if you think
that's how you hit on women
but it doesn't work on me at all.
You always use Shin PD as a front
and then send him away.
Isn't that method...
a bit old-fashioned?
Oh, no. You... You've misunderstood.
- No, that's not it.
- Do you like me?
Do you have feelings for me?
Do you want to date me?
Why don't you just be honest?
You always talk about "our generation."
That's right. We're old enough
to know better, aren't we?
- Right?
- Yes, that's right.
Do you have feelings for me?
Do you want to date me?
Yes.
I want to date you.
I see.
But...
I don't want to.
- What?
- I don't intend to date you.
So from now on
could you please stop with this approach?
And Shin PD.
Is this part of your job, Shin PD?
Do you take care of the writers
you're in charge of to this extent?
This isn't your job.
You're just being nosy.
I don't think taking care of things
like this
makes you a good PD.
Well, I enjoyed the movie.
Since I saw it for free, I'll buy you
both a cup of coffee tomorrow.
I'll be going now. See you tomorrow.
Wait, did I just get rejected?
Did I?
Hey.
She just flat-out rejected him, huh?
Man.
She just completely shot me down.
Jeez.
This is unbelievable, damn it.
Good job.
I start to like him, then he plays me?
I said you did a good job!
You have to say what's on your mind.
Forget it.
I'm done.
Let's just quit.
Okay, let's do that.
Gosh.
- Thank you.
- Goodbye.
Excuse me.
Where are the umbrellas?
We just sold the last one.
YOU NEED AN UMBRELLA ON A RAINY DAY
THE 22ND BUSAN FIREWORKS FESTIVAL
Emotion, you were here.
What are you doing?
You were all fired up just a moment ago.
I'm sad.
My heart fluttered for Soon-rok
for the first time in a while.
I was so excited
Don't cry.
Ms. Kim.
You were here.
It started pouring, so I came after you.
But you don't even have an umbrella.
Why did you follow me?
I was going to buy you an umbrella.
They're all...
sold out.
That's why I'm just standing here.
Oh, I see.
There should be
another convenience store nearby.
About earlier...
I'm sorry.
I got upset.
Even if you didn't have bad intentions...
No.
You were cool.
Sorry?
You're cool.
There... there's a convenience store
over there too.
Wait here for a second.
EPISODE 14
SOON-ROK'S PRINCIPLE
CONVENIENCE STORE
But Soon-rok.
Why did you just say that?
That Ms. Kim is cool.
Are you sure you're allowed to say that?
That seems like a violation
of the principle.
- Do you have any umbrellas?
- Over there.
- Thank you.
- Wait.
This won't do.
Activating emergency power!
What?
What's that sound?
I was sleeping. Why are you waking me up?
This isn't a situation we can just ignore.
Bring me Writer Kim Yu-mi's chart. Now!
- Here!
- Name, Kim Yu-mi.
Occupation, writer.
Relationship, work-related.
Importance, high.
Closeness, low.
Likeability, average.
Now, look.
It's just a work relationship
with nothing special about it.
She's just one of the writers
contracted with the publishing house.
I'm not even her PD anymore.
But were Soon-rok's remarks
today appropriate?
Did they follow his principles?
Soon-rok's Principle One.
Ms. Kim.
Do you want to watch the movie together?
Never see a movie alone with someone
you have no romantic feelings for.
Soon-rok's Principle Two.
You're cool.
Never make comments about a writer
other than about their writing.
Soon-rok broke two of his main principles.
- Blame impulsive Emotional Cell.
- What?
Emotional Cell? Really?
I'm not the one that started it.
Anyway, you broke the principles.
- To a writer you know from work!
- Gosh.
Is that really true?
Is there only one umbrella?
Yes, that's all we have.
Okay, let's sort this out.
Are we close enough to see a movie
alone with Ms. Kim?
No. Are we close enough to praise her
without hesitation?
No. Are we close enough
to share an umbrella?
No.
Conclusion.
Do not cross the line any further.
How far did he go?
I think that's Soon-rok.
It's Soon-rok!
Ms. Kim.
Where have you been?
There was one umbrella too.
I see...
Take this and go.
Then, what about you?
I'm already soaked anyway.
I'll be on my way to Mr. Kim.
Wait...
Well then, I'll be going.
Hold on...
Okay, it's settled.
- The emergency is over.
- Hey, look behind you!
How can I use this alone?
I'd feel too bad.
We can just go to the hotel together
and borrow one.
Let's go.
In a situation like this...
What are you going to do
in a situation like this?
What if the writer asks to share?
In that case...
This isn't
in Soon-rok's Principles.
Jeez, what is this?
Why are you walking so far away?
Are you blatantly keeping your distance?
Come closer.
You're getting all wet.
I'm already soaked
so it doesn't matter.
He's lost it.
What's with him again?
This is like a drama.
I'll hold the umbrella.
Okay.
Let's go.
This way...
Okay...
Do you think
Mr. Kim was very upset?
You don't have to worry about it.
I can't help but worry.
You said what you had to say
so don't worry about it.
A Maltese!
- Isn't that a Maltese?
- This?
Yes, it's a Maltese.
But you hate Maltese dogs.
Why do you have a picture of a Maltese...
She's my family's dog.
Kongsuni.
My parents are raising her now,
so I don't see her often.
But I don't think
I've ever said that I hate Maltese dogs.
You definitely did back then...
You said it back then.
Okay.
By any chance...
do you not like dogs?
You asked if I'm scared or allergic
and I'm sure I said not really.
No, not really.
Oh, that's a relief.
In that case, would you mind petting her?
Me, pet her?
But you wouldn't even pet her...
I was afraid she might bite.
My Kongsuni bites
when strangers touch her.
But Maltese dogs aren't very smart.
Oh, and
that Maltese dogs are dumb.
My Kongsuni isn't that smart.
She can't even find her own house.
Wait.
Don't Maltese dogs...
eat their own poop?
That's right.
You said they eat their poop.
Kongsuni eats her poop sometimes.
But she's so cute, right?
We got her when I was in high school.
She's already 13 years old.
I mean...
usually when you see a dog
don't you talk about your own dog too?
I don't usually get personal
when it's for a meeting.
That's amazing, really.
Sorry?
It's a compliment.
It doesn't sound like a compliment.
It is a compliment.
Let's go.
- Yes, here you go.
- Thank you.
You can keep the umbrella, Ms. Kim.
It might rain tomorrow too.
Okay.
Well, get some rest.
Now I know
what kind of person Soon-rok is.
Soon-rok is a person
who only speaks the truth.
He won't speak if it's not sincere.
Everything he says is the truth.
That's right.
That means
when he said Yu-mi was cool
he really meant it.
Gosh. Shin Soon-rok really knows
how to stir up this village.
He's a charmer, that one.
CINEOOP
- Mr. Kim.
- Yeah.
Have you been waiting long?
The umbrellas were all sold out
so I borrowed one from the hotel.
I see.
Did Ms. KIm get to the hotel okay?
- Yes.
- Good.
I was so incredibly embarrassed earlier
but instead
something suddenly came to me.
What was it?
Inspiration.
You know how we were stuck on
Ji-hun and Su-jeong's story?
But after getting shot down so hard
inspiration just suddenly hit me.
So I was quickly jotting it down.
- That's a relief.
- It is.
At least I got something out of it.
It wasn't a complete waste of a day.
- Let's go.
- Yeah.
Let's go.
Oh, but...
Something's been bothering me.
It's about what you said earlier.
Why say Yu-mi was watching a movie
when she hadn't even arrived yet?
I've been wondering why you said that.
Damn it.
It's another emergency!
Name, Kim Ju-ho.
Relationship, the writer in charge.
Importance, very high.
Closeness, average.
Likability, very low.
Focus. The importance is very high here.
Focus.
Is this a relationship
where I can speak my mind?
No.
Will speaking my mind help with work?
- Right.
- That's right.
Soon-rok's Principle Three.
When you can't
speak your mind, stay silent.
I thought about why you would do that.
And it's just that you don't like
what I'm doing.
Right?
"Hey, you pathetic writer."
"Stop doing useless things and shut up."
That's it, right?
Okay, you don't like me.
So.
If we think differently
do I have to be the one
to adjust to you, Shin PD?
- No.
- Then?
Let's not say anything, Soon-rok.
Ms. Kim!
Gosh.
- Did you sleep well?
- Yes. Did you sleep well?
Yes.
But I heard you went for four rounds
yet you woke up early.
I completely passed out and then woke up.
But you look so refreshed.
I'm telling you,
the water at the sauna here is great.
Also, the rice noodles are a must.
It's a perfect hangover cure.
So that's why you're so refreshed.
Would you like some coffee?
Yes. A hot latte, please.
I heard you saw a movie yesterday.
Oh, yes.
It was one I wanted to see
and they said it was the last showing.
But how did you know?
Especially since you were out til late.
I talked to Ju-ho.
He's already on the train.
Oh, he went back to Seoul?
Yes.
It's not because of Yu-mi, is it?
Right.
But why so suddenly...
Oh, he has a scheduled interview.
I see.
It's not. What a relief.
Then did Soon-rok go too?
Already?
Then Shin PD must have
gone with him, right?
No, he's in our room.
He caught a bad cold
after getting rained on yesterday.
He's laid up in bed.
Oh, my.
But last night...
- Yes?
- Did something...
I'm sorry, I'll be leaving first.
Please make sure to eat.
Yes, Chairman.
Yes.
What's this? I have a bad feeling.
Gosh, I have a bad feeling.
Mr. Kim left for Seoul at dawn.
Yes?
Shin PD, this is Kim Yu-mi.
Ms. Kim?
Are you okay? I heard you were sick.
Well...
Yes, I have a bit of a cold.
It's nothing serious.
Weren't you in the rain yesterday?
Oh dear.
I'm fine. I took some medicine.
But...
is something wrong?
- Sorry?
- I heard Mr. Kim
left early...
Oh.
He has an interview.
But you didn't go with him?
Me?
Well...
there's no need for me
to go with him anymore.
Why?
I got fired yesterday.
EPISODE 15
THE X-RAY OF LOVE
Wait, you got fired from Mr. Kim's team?
Yesterday?
Suddenly?
I guess
he really was upset yesterday.
It's because of me, isn't it?
- No.
- I think
it's because of me.
- No.
- If it's not that, then...
Ms. Kim!
You're going to
Gamcheon Culture Village today, yes?
The Gamcheon team leaves in ten minutes.
- You should get ready.
- Okay.
Shin PD was supposed to be the guide
but he's sick.
I'm sorry.
Yoo PD will take the Gamcheon team.
- Ms. Kim, head to the lobby right away.
- Okay.
- Then...
- Hello?
- Have a good trip, Ms. Kim.
- Are you sleeping now?
Thank you. Get some rest.
What the heck is up with that writer?
Kim Ju-ho is ridiculous.
So his pride was hurt? Is that it?
I mean, he couldn't say a word
before Yu-mi
so why fire Soon-rok?
I should just call
and give him a piece of my mind.
I really can't
just stand by and do nothing.
I have to say something.
This isn't right.
Ms. Kim, over here.
- Hurry up!
- Yes, yes, just a moment.
Hurry. Everyone else is on board.
- Hurry, over here.
- Hello. Get on here.
- Yoo PD, take care of them.
- Okay.
Have a good trip, Ms. KIm.
Ms. Kim.
Did you get a good night's rest?
Oh, yes.
Last night...
did something happen with Ju-ho?
Why?
I heard he got super offended
and went back to Seoul.
Yeah, and he fired Shin PD too.
What?
The rumor is spreading like wildfire!
Who did you hear that from?
Who do you think?
Ju-ho, himself.
He was complaining
to Writer Yoon all night.
He was offended by Shin PD
just going on and on about him.
Saying... what was it?
That he was arrogant or something?
He gets offended easily.
That's why his nickname is Pouty Boy.
Wait a minute. Are we...
I think we should go this way.
Let's all head this way.
- Okay.
Oh, this is crazy nice.
It's freeing, isn't it?
I chose the wrong outfit.
- Excuse me, Yoo PD.
- Yes?
Go on ahead.
I just have to make a phone call.
Just follow this path.
- We'll be walking slowly ahead.
- Okay.
- Yes, Ms. Kim?
- Hello, Chief Editor Ahn.
- Yes?
- Is now a good time to talk?
Of course. Enjoying the sights?
Yes.
By the way, about what you started to say.
What I started to say?
Yes. When you asked about last night.
Oh, right, right.
Since they said the three of you
watched a movie
I was wondering if you knew anything.
Ju-ho really likes Soon-rok
but suddenly he can't work with him.
Something about being disrespected.
This morning?
Yes. He suddenly called me
so I was a bit taken aback.
But Shin PD won't say a word
and I don't know if anything happened
while they were drinking or what.
Well, something did happen.
What happened?
Well this is...
It's really childish.
It's a little awkward
for me to say it myself.
I think it'd be better
if you heard it from him directly.
So it's something childish?
Yes. It's very, very childish.
Oh, right. He can be a bit childish.
But then again,
that's also part of his charm.
That's not charming to everyone, though.
Is it charming to someone you've just met?
No, you're right.
You can't be like that with someone new.
Anyway, if things stay this way
I'll feel too bad for Shin PD.
This doesn't feel right.
It'd be great if you resolved this.
Well, in that case...
How about Shin PD
rejoins your team?
- Sorry?
- Since you felt sorry for Soon-rok...
I was just throwing it out there.
Say yes.
That would be fine.
I'm fine with it.
Oh, really?
Yes, I mean
he only left
because of a scheduling conflict, right?
I actually liked Shin PD's feedback.
Okay, that is great.
But
what Shin PD thinks is important too.
What choice does he have?
He caused trouble, so he must listen.
That's not the case.
I'll go back
and discuss it with him.
- Okay, then.
- Okay.
I mean...
Is this how things are turning out?
Is this a good thing?
Of course it's a good thing!
Everyone, Soon-rok is coming back!
- Yay!
When he comes back,
let's have meetings every single day.
Then we can see him every day.
Are you crazy? Writers must write.
When are they supposed to write? Ugh!
I don't care.
I'm just so, so happy right now.
Yeah, well.
I guess it turned out well.
Shouldn't we tell Soon-rok too?
It'd be awkward if he heard it
from Chief Editor Ahn.
That's true.
What? He's not picking up.
- The caller is unavailable...
- Ms. Kim!
Everyone's waiting for you.
Oh, yes. I'm coming.
- Oh, this place is nice!
- It's so nice!
- We should take a picture here.
- Yes, that's a great idea.
- Okay, everyone, gather around.
- Okay.
- Ms. Kim.
- Yes?
Over here. The center spot.
Oh, no, I'm okay.
- Come on.
- Oh, thank you.
Okay, let's make a heart shape.
That's a great idea.
- One, two, three.
- Heart!
- Oh, it's so pretty.
- Yay!
- Wow, the colors are so pretty.
- Hey, this place has a great view.
Every house here is a different color.
One, two, three.
Over there. Look at the water.
Look at that.
He's not calling back.
Busan is really something, huh?
So, will you two come directly
to the restaurant?
I'm hot.
I'll grab an iced Americano
to cool down and then join you.
Gosh, I'm sweating so much.
It's okay if I skip it, right?
I ate so much for breakfast
that I don't really feel like it.
Of course. We have a team dinner tonight.
- We'll go on ahead then.
- Okay.
Want a drink?
Maybe I shouldn't wake him
if he's sleeping.
Shin PD, how are you feel...
Excuse me.
Are you with the guest from room 410?
Oh, yes.
Is he okay? The young man?
Sorry?
What do you mean by "okay"?
He was very sick earlier,
so he went to the hospital.
- I was wondering if he's okay now.
- What?
I recommended a nearby clinic to him.
Where is it?
You're all set.
Hello, welcome.
Excuse me, has
a Mr. Shin Soon-rok been here?
- Mr. Shin Soon-rok?
- Yes.
- Could you please check for me?
- Of course.
He has a high fever,
so he's on an IV drip.
Oh, I see.
I was just checking
if your fever went down.
The nurse said your fever was too high.
Thankfully, it seems like
it has gone down a lot.
How did you know I was here?
The hotel staff told me.
I was worried when I couldn't reach you.
- The Gamcheon Culture Village...
- Oh, I already went.
I see.
Just a moment.
- I'll take the needle out for you.
- Okay.
I'll wait outside.
- All done.
- Thank you.
MISSED CALL MS. KIM
MS. KIM
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
EMOTIONS
I knew it.
Hey, what are you doing?
You've lit the fire again.
No, it wasn't me.
I was sleeping.
Hey, I told you it wasn't me.
Right. It wasn't you.
It was Writer Yu-mi.
She was the one who suggested
watching a movie together.
She suggested sharing an umbrella.
And she touched his forehead.
See? I told you it wasn't me.
I have to go see Love.
Love.
Soon-rok's Love Cell
is a renowned surgeon.
Is this a picture of Writer Yu-mi?
Yes. You're great at reading X-rays.
Try to interpret Writer Yu-mi's heart.
What do you see?
This, right here.
You see something, right?
Something that looks like a heart.
What is it?
- Is it cancer?
- No.
The X-ray of love!
This substance is a combination
of affection and curiosity.
Affection and curiosity?
It's still in the early stages.
But if this continues to grow
it becomes love.
Then what should Soon-rok do?
If Soon-rok accepts her feelings
that's when the relationship starts.
Soon-rok doesn't date people
he works with.
ONGYEOL INTERNAL MEDICINE
BONJUK RESEARCH CENTER,
HAEUNDAE BRANCH PORRIDGE
Have you been waiting long?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I feel alive again.
I got your prescription
and bought the medicine.
Oh, thank you.
Let's go get some lunch.
The porridge place up ahead
has good reviews.
It's okay. I have no appetite.
You have to eat to take medicine.
And I'm hungry too.
I'll pay. Let's go.
They say this place is good.
I heard not all porridge is the same.
It looks popular here.
You've been through a lot
since yesterday because of me.
Not at all.
What kind of work will you do
when you go back to Seoul?
Since you left Mr. Kim's team.
Well...
I'll have to hand over my duties first
and I think I'll be doing
desk work for a while.
Things like overseas copyrights
and tedious paperwork.
You should be
in charge of me again.
You quit because of a scheduling conflict
so now the schedule's sorted out
it's only right you rejoin. Right?
That's not for me to decide.
Then I'll discuss it with Chief Editor Ahn
and decide then, right?
All right.
I'll make sure to discuss it well.
Good job.
It was cool and professional.
You didn't show it at all, Yu-mi.
Join Writer Yu-mi's team?
What are you going to do?
It would be great to join.
Soon-rok likes Writer Yu-mi's writing.
And she's a good person.
She's different from Writer Ju-ho.
Then what about this? Huh?
Should he accept her feelings or not?
I told you, Soon-rok doesn't date
people he works with.
We can't ruin the relationship.
And I hate dealing with headaches.
Then you should cut things off now.
Before your feelings get bigger.
SURGERY IN PROGRESS
We will now begin the resection procedure.
- Scalpel.
The other party might get hurt
but this is for the best.
- Enjoy your meal.
- Thank you.
Wow, the portions are huge!
Let me get you some.
Yes, ma'am.
Where are you?
I'm at lunch after the hospital
with Writer Yu-mi.
No, she came a little early too.
About 30 minutes?
Yes, I'll head over after we eat.
Okay.
Oh, by the way
that thing I mentioned before...
Can you...
set it up?
Oh my gosh, what's gotten into you?
I'm going to set it up.
I can't believe it. Really.
I just...
had a change of heart.
I'll try to make time.
Okay.
That was Jang PD.
She said her team is at the hotel now.
I see.
But what kind of appointment
would make her voice get so high?
I could hear the excitement in her voice.
Oh...
a blind date.
I kept turning them down
because I was busy.
But now I have some free time
so I think I can do it.
I didn't know you do blind dates, Shin PD.
Well, I'm against them.
Oh, I see.
Well, good luck.
Do you know anyone, Ms. Kim?
- Who?
- Someone
for a blind date.
The person on the receiving end knows
that you're drawing a line.
So it hurts
but what can you do?
I'll see if I can find someone.
Who could there be?
Okay.
This is delicious.
Thank you for today.
Okay, get some rest.
And make sure to take your medicine.
Okay.
Good.
The surgery seems to have been a success.
This workshop was a disaster.
I broke my principles by mixing
my personal and professional life.
Let's never let that happen again.
- Good work.
- Yeah.
- Let's get some rest now.
- Okay.
Huh? What's this?
There was another photo?
Wait a minute. Huh?
This is different from the one
we removed earlier.
What is this?
What is it?
I just thought of a good junior for you.
You two would be a good match.
Are you interested?
This...
isn't a photo of Writer Yu-mi.
SHIN SOON-ROK
This is a picture of Soon-rok.
YUMI'S CELLS 3
Are you still at the studio?
Call me anytime if you have trouble.
I'm terrible at games.
- I have plans.
- Good luck.
Today's Sunday.
It's Soon-rok's blind date.
How was it?
She even called to wish him well.
What if he drew the line for no reason?
Did you contact Jennie?
Do I really have to?
Isn't that Shin PD over there?
You.