Why are you so good to me?
I feel like I'm just a burden.
I've never been able
to do anything nice for you.
You're slowly improving in your own way.
If one day Solar isn't around, we're doomed.
Solar. Are you okay?
I... am... Sun!
Hey! Why are you doing this?
I get tired too, you know!
I want to see my mom.
Have you seen my boyfriend?
Pobmek.
What's going on?
What?
I was acting like a 7-year-old kid,
and said my name was Sun?
Well, yeah.
The room was a complete mess yesterday.
I had to clean up by myself all night.
Don't tell me
you don't remember anything from yesterday.
What I remember is...
I heard a really loud car horn.
After that, I don't remember anything.
This morning I woke up here,
took a shower, and went to the market.
Hey! Where are you going?
What? I'm going to teach.
Solar, you just hit your head
on the ground yesterday.
Then you woke up this morning
and couldn't remember anything.
Don't go to work today.
Stay here and rest.
It's too last-minute.
I didn't apply for leave in advance.
What about the kids in my class?
Who would take care of them?
Are you joking?
No, I'm not.
I'm a teacher too.
I may not be their homeroom teacher
like you,
but I can take care of the kids just fine.
Hey.
Stay here and rest.
I'll talk to Sodchuen for you, okay?
- Is that okay?
- Fine.
Go take a shower. You're already late.
You're the cutest.
One, two, three!
Roar!
- Come on, good job!
- Good job!
Now go to class.
Hey, Teacher Pobmek.
I didn't see you earlier this morning.
You must've slept well.
I made it in time to teach, didn't I?
Morning, Sodchuen.
Morning.
Didn't Solar come with you?
Is he still not feeling better?
He's better.
He was being stubborn
and insisted on coming to teach,
but I asked him to take the day off.
I think I'm going to cover Grade 2, Class 1
for him today.
Are you sure?
Solar's students are quite stubborn.
I think the stubborn one is him.
Solar!
Solar really wouldn't give up teaching.
Teacher Solar is really responsible.
He's perfect for you, Teacher Pobmek.
Alright.
It's time to teach.
Let's go do the work we love.
Teacher Jee, don't forget
what I asked you to do.
Yes, ma'am.
Bye. See you.
[Teacher Maprang: OK, Teacher Don: OK,
Teacher Solar: Seems fine]
Hey, hold on.
- What are you writing down?
- This?
It's the student safeguarding log.
What's that?
A teacher at the main campus
has been acting off.
On the outside, everything seemed normal,
but one day,
the teacher suddenly had mood swings,
and was later diagnosed
with a mental condition.
I think Sodchuen's worried
our teachers might end up like that.
And how is that teacher now?
He hasn't been teaching for a while.
It's been taken care of, I heard.
But why did Sodchuen assign you to this?
She probably just wanted to see how I'd do.
She keeps praising me, saying I'm amazing.
She just says things like that, doesn't she?
Jee is amazing, isn't he?
He represented the university
in an academic competition abroad
and even came back with a scholarship.
You should reach out to him sometime, Pobmek.
Do you want me to ask for his number
so you two can reconnect?
No, Mom.
Jee has his own circle of friends.
And I have mine here.
By the way, who's your roommate?
What's he studying?
He's studying to become a teacher.
I feel like anyone can become a teacher
these days.
I even see some teachers looking things up
on the internet
just to teach their students.
If you could spend time
with people studying medicine or accounting...
Mom, I have to go.
Solar.
I...
I apologize on behalf of my mom for...
Damn!
I got straight As.
I'm top of the class.
Damn. Congrats.
How are your grades?
Is something wrong?
No.
You just won't admit it, huh?
Come on. Let me show you something.
In child psychology, there's a concept called
an idiosyncratic mand.
It's a unique word or phrase a child uses
to communicate when they need help.
For example,
some children may have been taught
to be afraid of asking for help.
They might think
they have to solve every problem
on their own,
so they keep everything to themselves.
So we teach them to use another word instead,
so they don't have to worry
about saying it out loud.
What word?
It can be anything.
For example, this kid doesn't like the rain.
When he needs help, what does he say?
Raincoat?
Yes.
As soon as he says that,
his friends know he needs help.
Wait, why are you telling me this?
I'm not a kid.
Are you sure?
Silent, huh? No answer?
Alright. Just let me know when you're ready.
Has anyone learned this before?
Does anyone know?
- Me.
- Okay.
Alright, I'll tell you the first one.
What are these pink things?
- Flowers.
- Flowers? Okay, write "flowers".
What do they look like?
Go ahead and draw them.
Yeah.
[Boyfriend]
So you're napping here.
Wake up, Teacher.
Uncle Kidnapper.
Sun?
What is this place?
It's... the school.
So Mom is going to pick me up, right?
Yay!
No, no, no.
Little Sun, let's go home with Uncle.
- Mom's home, right?
- Our home.
No! I'm not going!
I'm going to see Mom!
Sun, come back here!
Where did he go?
Oh!
Hello.
There you are!
No!
Teacher Solar, could you check my vocab?
Teacher Solar, could you check my homework?
Teacher Solar, could you check my answers?
Hey! I said my name's not Solar!
My name is Sun! It's Sun, got it?
- It hurts!
- Then stay still!
Stay still?
Ouch!
Make it fierce and powerful!
One, two, three!
Go ahead and stretch. I'll be right back.
Hey, Pobmek.
What's going on, Elsa?
Yeah, what's going on?
The Teacher Pobmek-Teacher Jee ship
is sailing!
What are you looking for?
Nothing. I just came to get some air.
"I'm worried about you."
"Solar isn't treating you right, is he?"
Don't you have a class to teach?
Why are you out here getting some air?
You're not teaching during class time either.
"Don't make me lose control
and kiss you right now."
Are you sick?
You feel a little warm.
What are you doing?
I'm fine.
What are you guys doing?
Teacher Solar! I swear I didn't skip P.E.
You looked so cool just now!
Huh?
I'm Sun.
What are your names?
I'm Four. He's King.
Oh, I need your help.
I need to get out of here.
Do you know any secret ways out?
Please. Don't try to trick us, Teacher Solar.
You're going to send us to
Principal Sodchuen, aren't you?
Hey, I'm not tricking you guys.
My name's really Sun, not Solar.
If you're really not Teacher Solar,
then show us the secret code.
Gen Y wouldn't know how to do it.
Damn. That's so sigma!
Hey! Teacher Pobmek is coming!
Guys, I have to go!
Please tell me the way.
Behind the gym, there's a wall
you can jump over to get out.
Hurry there, Sun.
Cool.
Hey, have you guys seen Teacher Solar?
Are you going to tell me or not?
If not, I'll give you
a huge set of math problems.
Are you going to tell me or not?
Hey, Teacher Solar.
You're not teaching?
I saw Teacher Pobmek earlier.
He seemed a little off. He felt kind of warm.
I think he's unwell.
But now you seem even more off than him.
Hey!
Uncle Kidnapper, let go!
Uncle Kidnapper?
What's that?
Is something going on?
I said no!
Let go!
Something's definitely going on.
Teacher Solar is squirming like crazy.
The kids are watching.
Just tell me what's going on.
Hey! Pobmek!
I don't use pencils! I only use pens!
Hey!
Write whatever you want.
No one is as good as you, Jee!
Let's go!
Hey!
Aren't you tired?
You've been running away from Uncle all day.
I told you. I just want to see Mom.
And I already told you
I'd take you to see her.
Can't you wait until school is over?
Luckily, Solar is free all day today.
This afternoon he only has to teach...
[Teacher Solar's Schedule]
What should I do?
Can a kidnapper be a teacher too?
I said I'm not a kidnapper.
You sure look like one.
What kind of teacher
has no kids who like him?
Even I'm better than you.
I've only been here a little while,
but I've already made two friends.
Sure.
You're the best.
But there's one thing you can't beat me at.
What?
Teaching.
You're a kid.
Even if I were a kidnapper,
I'd still be better at teaching than you.
Please!
I'm sure I can teach better than you, Uncle.
Anyone who gets out of their seat
will be in big trouble.
[Do all the questions on Page 36]
[Class 2/1]
Alright, kids.
Today, Teacher Solar is going to...
This word is pronounced "sun".
Who knows what it means in Thai?
Sun means "Phra Arthit".
Very good.
It's also my name.
- Huh? How come?
- His name is Solar.
Well, Teacher Solar just wants
to use the name Sun for a day.
Excuse me, can I change my name to Anna?
Then can I change my name to Jaii?
No! My name is really Sun!
So your name is "Really Sun", not just "Sun"?
Teachers!
Hey, no one beats kids with sticks anymore.
Okay, let's learn how to count
from 1 to 10 in English.
But we learned that in first grade already.
Here. "Head" means "Hua",
and "neck" means "Kor".
And...
Teacher!
What's the difference
between neck and throat?
(Kor.)
What do you think?
"Neck" probably means
the outside part of the neck,
because you wear a necklace
around your neck.
And "throat" probably means the inside,
like when you say, "My throat hurts".
Beautiful and smart. Ten out of ten!
Can I play too?
Hey! You guys are loud over there!
Teacher Sun is teaching.
- Be quiet!
- That's right!
How can you be playing in my class?
Oh, race cars.
Keep playing in my class
and those hands are done!
Where's the class leader?
Write their names down.
Come on, Teacher Solar.
Don't you remember my name?
I said I'm Sun.
- Write your own name down too.
- Huh?
So, can I change my name to Anna?
Write her name down too.
What? How come
you can change your name, but I can't?
I want to change my name from Tinker Bell
to Tinky Winky too.
Hey!
I told you not to get out of your seats!
I didn't get out of my seat, Teacher.
I'll send you all to Principal Sodchuen
for not listening to me.
We've all finished copying the answers.
Look. Did I do well?
You got this!
Teacher Solar!
What are you doing?
Hey! Students!
Who made the room such a mess, huh?
Teacher Solar?
What happened?
I've said it hundreds of times.
My name is Sun!
It's Sun!
Teacher Pobmek, this is serious.
Why is Solar acting like that?
Why is he referring to himself as Sun?
Yeah.
He's acting strange, almost like a child.
There's nothing wrong with Solar.
He's perfectly fine.
Perfectly fine? How?
That's way out of character for him.
Wait...
Are you okay?
Are you not feeling well?
Here.
Put this on.
Teacher Jee, what should we do?
Jee! Don't write a report about Solar!
Then don't keep everything to yourself!
You said you're fine, but you're clearly not.
It's not going to solve anything.
Jee is amazing, isn't he?
He represented the university
in an academic competition abroad,
and even came back with a scholarship.
Jee is amazing, isn't he?
[If Jee is so amazing,
why not make him your own kid, Mom?]
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Nothing's wrong with me.
I know you like to solve problems
on your own,
but the more you do this, the worse I feel.
You act like I can't help you at all.
I'm sorry.
If you don't want to say it directly,
why don't you try using a magic word?
Sponge bath.
I'm giving you a sponge bath, aren't I?
No.
I mean, my magic word is "sponge bath".
If there's ever a day
I can't take it anymore,
can you give me a sponge bath?
Of course.
If there's ever a day
you can't take it anymore,
I'll give you a sponge bath.
Sponge bath.
What did you say?
I mean...
can you help me?
Well...
Solar's mind reverts to that of a 7-year-old.
I think it's the effect
from his accident the other day.
But he seemed fine this morning.
Yeah.
But somehow, this afternoon,
he suddenly went back to being a kid,
as you can see.
I didn't want anyone to see Solar like this.
But it can't be helped. It was an accident.
You didn't have to hide it from us.
I was just afraid Jee would report it.
You know
how much Solar loves being a teacher.
I was afraid that if the school found out,
then...
Jee! I told you not to write it down!
Teacher Jee, write it big.
Teacher Solar is the one
we need to support the most.
Huh?
What do you mean?
We're going to help Solar, of course.
Yes, just like how we helped
the teacher at the main campus.
Hold on.
Didn't that teacher get fired?
I thought you said that teacher was gone.
I meant the teacher has been taken care of,
as in recovered.
The school is aware
and concerned about all the teachers,
so I asked Teacher Jee
to help keep an eye on our teachers.
In case something happens,
we can support them in time.
Let us help, Pobmek.
Solar is my junior too.
But how are you?
Will you be alright?
You don't really get along well with kids.
On the bright side,
it's a good coincidence
that Sun is 7 years old.
This should be easy.
Easy?
Easy how?
No one's better at dealing with
7-year-olds than we are!
You're right.
Come on. We can do it!
The reason I've gathered everyone here today
is to inform you of something.
The person sitting here
is not the Teacher Solar we know.
Now, he's Little Sun.
- Please take good care of him, everyone.
- Hello...
Little Sun, right?
Okay, Aunt.
Sure.
Sun, someone wants to talk to you.
Sun, Uncle Pobmek is a good person.
He can be trusted.
If you behave, Mom will hurry to pick you up.
Alright.
Kids, remember what I taught you
about getting into animal characters?
Our teacher Solar has to take on
the character of Little Sun on some days.
You're all his friends,
so please be kind to Little Sun.
- Okay?
- Okay!
It's kind of surreal, isn't it?
The whole thing
about Solar turning into a kid.
But at least when he's Sun,
he's pretty easy to handle.
He's way sweeter than some kids.
How?
He's probably the most chaotic in the school.
I think you're wrong, Pobmek.
[I'm sorry I was so bad
I made you sick, Uncle]
At least Sun stopped calling you Kidnapper.
Jee.
I said a lot of bad things to you today.
- Actually, I...
- Hey, no worries!
I don't like you.
Huh? What do you mean?
I mean, I used to not like you.
You're just perfect at everything.
And my mom kept praising you so much
all the time
that it annoyed me,
even though you did nothing wrong.
Perfect?
You know what?
I have to see a psychotherapist for my OCD.
I'm not perfect like you think.
But I...
I really want to be your friend, Pobmek.
Okay.
You already are.
You've been for a long time.
In the future,
you and that Jee guy might become friends.
Are you ready, Mr. Pobmek,
for this week's sponge bath?
My final exam score still sucks as always!
My mom won't stop praising that freaking Jee!
Damn it!
Who cares if he's top of the class?
I'm not him!
And I never wanted to study accounting
in the first place!
That's why my score sucks like this!
That's enough. That's enough.
You did great.
When you can't take it anymore,
you should let it out.
You might feel stressed or not okay now,
but I believe time will help you.
Who knows?
In the future,
you and that Jee guy might become friends.
No way!
I don't want to be friends with him!
Are you going to keep holding my hand
until tomorrow morning?
Hey, guys.
We know how to deal with Sun now,
but I wonder if Solar will come back.
I don't know either.
Alright, forget it.
Let's split up and head home.
Things might be better tomorrow.
I guess.
Come on.
Let's go home, guys.
Oh, but who's going
to wake him up, Teacher Jee?
Guys.
I think I have an idea
when the two will switch.
You startled me! Why are you up so early?
Are you Solar?
Of course I am.
Who else could I be?
I figured it out!
You switch between being yourself and Sun
every time you wake up.
Huh?
Am I still switching to a kid?
Yes.
Yesterday, you fell asleep during the day,
and woke up as Sun.
But don't worry.
I'm going to help you get better
no matter what.
So...
does this mean you'll always have
to take care of me like this?
Are you forcing yourself?
Don't force yourself.
If it gets too much,
you need to take a break.
Got it?
Yeah. I know.
Solar, that's enough.
What do you mean, enough?
You're too cute! I can't help it!
You usually just do things on your own.
Solar, that's enough. Come on, be shy!
It's fine.
We're all grown-ups here.
Teacher Solar just kissed you six times.
I was counting.
So please kiss him back that many times.
My OCD is asking.
Sponge bath?
Yeah.
You're the best!
You let others help you now, right?
Yeah.
Oh, come here!
Solar! That's enough! Be shy!
- Even though it seemed tough at first,
- Come here!
Because it was a challenge
I'd never faced before,
- That's enough!
- and I chose to carry it all by myself,
but now that I've finally gathered the courage
to ask for help,
everything feels a lot lighter.
It makes me realize
I'm not going through this alone anymore.
If you don't get back to your old self soon,
our room's going to
turn into a toy graveyard.
How old are you, Little Sun?
I'm 7.
Sun! What are you doing?
I'm tired of Sun!
[Plan to get Solar back]
We need to keep him as Solar
as long as possible.
And get Sun to bed as early as possible.
Deal!
Shit!
I hope we get to be together this Sunday.