=Eight Hundred=
Hui, look. We've reached Mr. Gao's home.
(Year 1976)
How come no Spring Couplets are posted?
I know, right?
Who is it?
It's me, Hongbing.
- You haven't even put up couplets.
- Happy Chinese New Year!
Come in.
What's going on?
Hey,
come out.
It's Hongbing and his family.
It's fine.
Mrs. Gao.
- Well...
- Mrs. Gao.
Where
did this child come from?
I found her.
Found her?
Early this morning,
I found her by the restroom entrance.
Let me see.
Come here.
Is it a boy or a girl?
It's a girl.
Look at her face.
Hongbing,
since Gao Ying is gone,
we have discussed it.
We plan to adopt this child.
Adopt?
Mr. Gao, for an adoption,
you have to notify the police station.
Of course.
You must
support us.
Yes, Hongbing.
If it's not against regulations,
I will help you.
Hui,
come and look at your sister.
Take a look.
Little girl.
What is her relationship
to the head of the household?
My granddaughter.
Grandfather and granddaughter, right?
Yes.
What is her name?
Mr. Gao,
let's call her Songge.
Gao Songge.
It's from Gao Ying's favorite essay,
"The Character of the Pine." How's that?
Gao Songge. That's a good name.
Let's go with Songge.
(Permanent Residence Registration: Gao Songge)
Gao Songge, then.
It's a fine name.
=Episode 2=
(Tube Popsicle)
These are
the empty bottles from last time.
Count them.
Hello?
My dad found out.
Stop the deal.
Understood.
I can't get the goods today.
Go back and wait for my word.
What's wrong?
Wait. Why can't we get the goods today?
Get out of the way.
- Don't.
- Move.
Just give me two bottles first, okay?
Just two.
I really can't take it anymore.
Are you hooked?
No.
I'm not.
Have you forgotten what the rules are?
I saw how energized
they were after drinking it,
so I couldn't resist having a bottle.
I'll never drink it again, okay?
You broke the rules.
There is no next time.
No way.
Give me two bottles.
Give them to me.
Give them to me!
Let go!
Stop!
A detonator?
Go ahead.
Light it.
Are you crazy?
I'm not afraid of doing this job.
If you dare come any closer,
we'll both be done together!
Just calm down first. Fine.
You're insane.
Crazy woman.
(Starlight Video Hall, Rose Ballroom)
Songge,
where are you?
Hui,
my vascular fistula ruptured.
I can't stop the bleeding.
Can you ride your motorcycle now?
I can make it now,
but I won't make it
to the municipal hospital.
Go to the mine hospital.
No,
go straight to my mom's.
Now!
What should I say when I see her?
Just say you were hit by a car.
Ditch your phone and your bag.
Hide the motorcycle
in the drainage ditch.
I'll meet you at my mom's place.
Hurry!
Okay.
(Ding Yue Clinic)
Yue,
Hui and Songge
grew up together.
In my views, nowadays when young people
get into a relationship,
they go all in like
there's no turning back.
Back then,
to marry Hongbing, you...
Wait.
We were talking about my son.
Why bring me into it?
I mean
it's not enough just to talk to Hui.
You have to discuss it with Songge.
That's not appropriate.
Don't be so blunt with her.
Xi,
give me some fruit.
Okay.
(Ding Yue Clinic)
What happened to her?
Songge!
What's going on?
Songge, what happened?
Why is there so much blood?
- Poor girl.
- Songge.
Songge, you're in bad state.
Why didn't you go to the hospital?
You know what kind of
conditions this clinic has.
Stop nagging.
She's my child.
If something's wrong,
who else would she turn to?
Quick, get the scissors!
Stop it.
I'll take a call.
Hello?
Hongbing.
Songge's vascular fistula ruptured.
Get a car over here immediately.
We need to get her
to the municipal hospital.
- It's okay, Songge.
- Hurry up!
I have to go.
Hand me the scissors, quick!
Coming.
Mom,
I bought some fruit for you.
What's happening?
- Songge.
- Her fistula ruptured.
Don't worry, Hui.
Your dad has already called for a car.
It'll be here soon.
Come on, quick!
- Hurry!
- The car is here.
Quick, the car is here!
She's lost so much blood.
Hurry up!
Hang in there, Songge.
- Come.
- Okay.
Open the car door.
Hui.
Hurry up!
Okay.
Go to the other side.
I'll handle this.
(Jiangbin Municipal People's Hospital)
Slow down.
Quick.
Mom, hold her.
I'm going to get a bag.
Okay.
Don't pull so hard.
Let me help you.
Look at you.
What's the big rush?
(Emergency Resuscitation Room)
You must be hungry.
Aren't you going in?
Songge fell asleep inside.
This poor child.
She has to get another vascular shunt.
Fortunately,
everything is fine now.
It breaks my heart to see her.
What's gonna happen
to her in the future?
I asked you to talk to Hui.
Did you?
Of course I did.
I told him this morning.
What did he say?
What could he say?
He has grown up, after all.
I feel like
we should stay out
of his business.
You're really something.
I asked you to talk to Hui,
but instead, he talked you out of it.
How can you be so useless?
You can't even handle him.
You're making me furious.
What are you doing?
Well,
if you're so capable, you go.
Why do you keep pressuring me?
Aren't you the head of the family?
Must I handle
every family crisis for you?
I've already told Hui.
What can I do if he won't break up?
Then talk to him again.
Until he agrees.
Stop it.
Others might see us.
What are you doing?
Hui went to buy water
and hasn't come back yet. I'll go check.
Hongbing,
why are you hiding?
The trunk is broken.
I'm sorry.
I've gotten so much blood in your car.
How much
for a cleaning?
Don't worry about it.
I can't do that.
You've taken good care
of me all these years.
But I really can't help
with Gao Ying's case.
That's a separate issue.
Here, take it. This is all I have.
I don't want your money.
I said I don't want it.
What happened to your trunk?
Ask Hui.
I told him not to pull it
and I'd open it.
But he wouldn't listen and
insist on that bag.
I don't know what his rush was.
Well.
Hui, hurry up!
Mom, hold her.
I'm going to get a bag.
Hui, hurry up!
I told him not to pull it,
and I'd open it.
But he wouldn't listen and
insist on that bag.
Dad,
where were you just now?
I just called Han Ning.
I told her not to open the shop tonight
and to go home to look after Grandpa.
Songge.
I...
I want to ask you something.
What is it?
All these years,
we
have been good to you, right?
If it weren't for you and Mr. Chen,
I would have died long ago.
Then, I'll just
speak plainly.
Can
you leave Hui?
You bought so many drinks.
Can you finish them all?
Songge is staying for a couple of days.
She doesn't drink much,
but I do.
This bag is so dirty.
Why is there blood on it?
It might be from
Songge's injury.
I didn't notice.
Songge,
it's really not
that I look down on you.
Mr. Chen and I
won't be with Hui forever.
If Hui has to carry
such a heavy burden alone,
we
won't be able
to rest in peace.
They say a parent's love
knows no bounds.
Can you please
try to understand
my feelings?
Songge.
Mom.
How is Songge?
How is she? Is she okay?
It's so dirty to leave the bag there.
Dad,
I'll take it.
What's inside?
You're so nervous.
Nothing.
Can I take a look?
No.
What are you hiding in there?
I'm not hiding anything.
Dad, why do you want to see my stuff?
What are you arguing about?
Songge is trying to rest.
What if I insist on seeing it?
No way.
You can't look at my things.
No, Dad.
Dad, you can't look. No.
- You can't, Dad.
- Stop it.
- Dad, you can't.
- What are you doing?
Dad!
(Condoms)
With so many things,
are you planning to open a shop?
Yue,
Yue.
What are you doing?
Why were you
snooping through his things?
I thought it was some adult tapes.
- You know?
- Hui is so disappointing.
She's in bad state
and I talked such things to her.
Am I ruthless?
Don't worry about them.
Just take it slow, okay?
What do you mean by slow?
How can we take it slow?
I have to go to the station.
Go home by yourself.
I haven't even finished talking.
Be safe on the road.
I haven't finished talking.
I'm sorry.
That scared me.
That was too dangerous.
From now on,
I'll handle deals.
What are you saying?
Didn't we agree on this?
I'll handle the deals,
and you're in charge
of getting the stock.
Isn't this the first time
something like this has happened?
You know
that I don't want to hide behind you.
Otherwise, I'd feel even more guilty.
But if this happens again,
- I...
- Don't think about it.
Isn't everything fine now?
We set the rules together.
No one is allowed to break them.
If you break them,
I won't continue the treatment anymore.
- But...
- No buts.
By the way,
where's the bag?
Didn't I tell you to throw it all away?
Why did you bring it back?
It was stained with my blood.
I was afraid something would happen.
Don't worry.
I hid it.
When there are fewer people outside,
I'll go get it back.
♪Forsaking my ideals♪
♪Anyone can do that♪
♪What's there to fear
if one day it's just you and me?♪
I hope you have a great time tonight.
- Hey, where are you from?
- Jiangbin.
What are you doing?
Trying to get my friend drunk
while I was away?
Move over.
I wasn't.
They came all the way to Fengyang,
so we have to treat them well.
- Enjoy it.
Nobody move.
Turn on the lights.
- Police inspection.
- Don't move!
Mr. Kang,
what's going on?
We received a report
that someone is using contraband here.
Why wasn't there a notice?
If I notified you,
what would I be inspecting?
You know the public security regulations.
Cooperate with us.
We'll cooperate, absolutely.
Men on the left.
Women on the right.
Each of you, take a cup.
Urine test.
No one's getting away.
Chief Liu,
I'm sorry.
Something delayed me.
It's fine.
We also received
a report about contraband.
We came to check
this place on short notice.
How is it? Is the search going smoothly?
It's okay.
Limin is inside organizing it.
By the way,
the composition report on the body
came out this afternoon.
(Welcome to Vienna)
On the victim's remains,
some strange things were found.
What was found?
There is carborundum,
as well as potassium manganate
and manganese dioxide.
I know what carborundum is.
It's an industrial abrasive.
What about the other two?
The report says they're
byproducts of potassium permanganate
decomposition at high temperatures.
Before the body was burned,
there was potassium permanganate
on the victim.
Potassium permanganate.
You're awake?
Where is Jiao Yuqin?
Who are you?
Why did you kidnap me?
Where is Jiao Yuqin?
I don't know Jiao Yuqin.
Let me go!
I'm asking you
if you sell the cough syrup?
What cough syrup?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Then what's in that bag
you hid in the alleyway?
The moment you
sneaked out of the hospital,
I had my eyes on you.
I followed you all the way to the alley.
Stop playing dumb with me.
Is it money you want?
I'll give you however much you want.
I don't want money.
I just want to know where Jiao Yuqin is.
I told you I don't know the person.
I don't even know who that is.
You won't talk?
What are you doing?
Where are you?
What are you pouring on me?
What do you want? Say something!
I'm asking you for the last time.
Where is Jiao Yuqin?
I really don't know her!
Then go to heck, you brat.
Potassium permanganate
and glycerol.
Get a taste of being burned.
Are you sick?
Are you crazy?
You have the wrong person.
This must be a mistake.
I don't know who this person
you're talking about is.
There's no way I have the wrong person.
You drug dealers
never tell a word of truth.
My wife
was destroyed and
deceived by you!
I'm going to burn you!
Huo Kaiming!
You said
you've been following me all day.
Aside from my parents,
you're the only one
who followed me today.
It's you, Huo Kaiming.
It's you!
Brat,
I'll give you one last chance.
Tell me
where Jiao Yuqin is?
Do you know her?
I don't!
If you burn me,
my dad won't let you get away with it.
By then, you'll be nothing but ash.
What could your dad possibly find?
I'm burning you right now.
You brat, trying to be clever
with me, huh?
You're done!
Mr. Huo.
Mr. Huo,
your wife is Jiao Yuqin, right?
Did she run off with a drug dealer?
Nonsense, impossible!
Yuqin isn't that kind of person.
The drug dealers
who coerced her!
Darn it!
In Fengyang,
only I am able
to help you find Jiao Yuqin.
Although I don't know her,
I know the person selling the drugs.
Mr. Huo,
let go of me.
Why should I believe you?
If I lie to you,
you can find me anytime.
I'll help you find her
if you let me go.
You brat.
Remember what you said today.
If you dare lie to me,
I'll kill you whenever I want.
That batch of goods
stays here with me for now.
Wait for me to find you
at the roller skating rink.
Chen Liang?
I'm here.
You can go.
Wang Sui?
That's me.
Tested positive for Kejianin.
Take her away.
I didn't do anything.
You must have made a mistake.
She's a university student.
She just arrived in Fengyang.
How could she have done anything wrong?
We won't make a mistake.
Do not obstruct us in duty.
Take her in.
- Xin Yu!
- This must be a misunderstanding.
Please check again.
- Why are you running?
- Get out of the way!
Don't move!
(Welcome to Vienna)
- Where do you think you're going?
- Where are you running?
- Stop!
- Get down!
Get down!
Where are you running to?
Where exactly do you think you're going?
Take them down.
Move!
(Emergency Department, Outpatient Department,
Jiangbin Municipal People's Hospital)
Where is Jiao Yuqin?
Do you know Jiao Yuqin?
Who's Jiao Yuqin?
Hui,
you're back.
Did I wake you?
I wasn't sleeping soundly.
I was worried about you.
How are you?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Everything's been handled.
Why did it take you so long?
Did something happen?
Nothing happened.
Go to sleep now.
You need to rest.
What happened to your neck?
It looks like you're hurt.
No,
it might be an allergy.
I scratched it.
Today,
did my mom say something to you?
You don't look very well.
No.
She just told me
to be more careful
when I go out in the future.
She was just worried about me.
She didn't say anything else?
No.
Just sleep.
Hui.
Tell me.
If we could go back
to when we were kids,
how wonderful would that be?
Happy birthday, Songge.
I hope I can eat cake every day.
Remember to do
your homework when you get home.
I know, Hui.
See you tomorrow.
♪So colorful and free♪
♪Yet popping at a single touch♪
Hui.
Hui,
where are you taking me?
I'm taking you
to the roller skating rink.
- Okay!
- Let's go.
♪Just like when we
were innocent children♪
I've learned!
I'm so smart!
Great job.
If you can manage to skate a whole lap,
come find me again.
In 30 minutes,
you'll see
an airplane right here.
Let's fly!
Songge.
Chen Hui.
♪The moonlight shines on the bed♪
Come on.
Let's go.
♪Just pretend
you're holding my hand again♪
Chen Hui,
why do you always like coming here?
Because I can stand high
and see far here.
This is the highest point in Fengyang.
What do you think? Isn't it cool?
Cool. And this torch.
At night,
when all the lights in Fengyang are out,
it will still be lit.
Chen Hui,
from now on, let's call it
the Light of Hope, okay?
The Light of Hope?
Okay.
You will have
the college entrance exam next year.
What school do you want to go to?
What school?
Whatever.
Anyway,
it has to be far away from my dad.
Then go to Haicheng.
Okay.
Haicheng it is.
I'm going to Haicheng!
I'm going to Haicheng too!
You two, get down from there!
You little brats!
Haicheng?
I'll make sure you never leave Fengyang!
What do we do?
We've been caught.
I'm going to take Songge
to the ends of the earth!
To the ends of the earth!
♪Back then, the distance was in sight♪
♪The road had no end♪
♪Say "see you tomorrow"♪
♪And there would surely be a future♪
(Advanced Unit)
(Fengyang Town Police Station,
Jiangbin Municipal PSB)
Don't worry.
- We'll work with the local station.
- Chief Liu.
Okay.
What is it, Director Chen?
Chief Liu, I need to check in with you.
Chief Liu, here's the thing.
This time,
we arrested 26 people
who tested positive for Kejianin.
These people are all buyers.
And they all bought their supply
from that missing person,
Lu Yuan.
Two of the sellers
lived in the village.
I had Limin
take his men
to make the arrests overnight.
But when they got there, they found
they had all fled.
Both sellers ran away?
Yes.
The villagers said
they've been gone for two days.
They vanished the same day as Lu Yuan.
They are slippery.
Of the buyers we caught,
has anyone seen the original bottles?
That's the strange part.
Among so many people,
no one has seen the bottle
for this cough syrup.
(Contraband, Peidun Cough Syrup)
That is strange.
We arrested all those people,
yet not a single seller
was from the town.
And the buyers all drank
refilled cough syrup.
No one has seen the original bottles.
This ring is tightly organized.
Chief Liu, does the municipal PSB
have any new findings?
Regarding the commemorative coin
from the scene,
the municipal PSB conducted
a city-wide investigation.
Only one set remains unaccounted for.
The applicant is the owner
of a motorcycle shop.
On the afternoon of October 1,
he used this set
of commemorative coins as a prize
for a lucky draw at his shop.
They were won by a middle-aged woman.
Her specific identity is unknown.
A middle-aged woman?
Aren't there way too many of them?
Right, did you check
the potassium permanganate?
Aside
from medical use,
(Potassium Permanganate, Glycerol)
it's generally a daily item
for women.
With retail sales like this,
it's very hard to track.
Let's keep investigating
the cough syrup then.
As long as we find one seller,
we can smoke out the whole ring.
Whatever you say.
Let's move.
The municipal PSB
is taking the discovery
of Peidun Cough Syrup in Fengyang Town
very seriously
as it's a prohibited drug.
This is also the first time
it's been found in our province.
Now, this cough syrup matter
is also closely related to
the Beimianling body-burning homicide.
So the municipal PSB
is preparing to launch
a major crackdown and night inspection
against Peidun Cough Syrup in Fengyang.
It will mainly target
public consumer venues,
such as video halls,
arcades,
roller skating rinks, and dance halls.
Whenever anyone is found
testing positive for Kejianin
during this operation,
interrogate them immediately
for the seller's whereabouts
and make the arrests.
In our Fengyang,
there are quite a lot of places,
large and small.
But in our entire station,
there are only about 20 people.
Even if we deploy everyone,
I'm afraid we won't have enough hands.
The municipal PSB has notified
the Criminal Police Squad One.
They will come to assist us
in carrying out this operation together.
That's great.
With the assistance
of the municipal PSB,
we will solve the case
as soon as possible.
Director Chen.
Sir.
Who are you?
My name is Xin Yu.
My friend's name is Wang Sui.
She was arrested by you yesterday.
She's innocent.
Who wronged her?
She was arrested despite doing nothing.
Doing nothing?
That's illegal consumption
of prohibited drugs.
She has to pay a fine
and stay in detention for five days.
Do you understand?
She couldn't have taken it on purpose.
Someone must have drugged her.
Please be flexible.
Don't detain her.
Everyone says it wasn't on purpose.
Who forced her?
Wang Sui is a college student.
She just came to Fengyang to visit me.
If you detain her,
the school will expel her
if they find out.
She has always been a good girl.
She wouldn't take it intentionally.
Please don't detain her.
I'll look into the situation further.
(Yingxiong Roller Skating Rink)
Hui, you're back.
- Mr. Wang.
What's wrong?
Lu Yuan is over there.
He found this place so quickly?
What should we do?
Should we hide for a bit?
We can run, but we can't hide forever.
Let's go ask him what he wants.
Let's go.
(Yingxiong Roller Skating Rink)
(Jackpot is Coming,
China Welfare Lottery)
- Morning, Cai.
- Morning.
Want some steamed buns?
No, thanks.
Why are you sleeping here?
Something came up, so I got back late.
You could have at least called.
Don't you know I was worried?
I'm going back to sleep for a bit, Mom.
Where's Sui?
Why didn't she come back with you?
Sui went to sleep at a hotel.
Why go to a hotel?
Yesterday,
she had a bit to drink and got sleepy.
I told her to come back,
but she didn't want to disturb you.
So I just took her to a hotel.
Listen.
Sui is a good kid.
Don't you go corrupting her.
I know.
Cai.
Hey, little beauty.
Why so early?
Give me
two lottery tickets.
Sure.
How's business been
at your roller skating rink lately?
It's been pretty good.
Good luck.
Mom, I'm heading back now.
Han Ning, wait a second.
Yeah?
I
remember you saying
your boss's father
works at the police station, right?
Yeah.
He's the Deputy Director.
Could I ask him for a favor?
What is it?
(Menu)
This is my boss.
Boss,
this is a neighbor of mine.
Her name is Xin Yu.
You're the one
who sings at the club, right?
That's right. Do you go there often?
Not often. Just occasionally.
Next time you come, look for me.
Drinks are on me.
Boss,
she said she has something
to discuss with you.
Why don't you two talk?
I'll head out first.
Go ahead.
I heard your father is the Director
of the police station.
Deputy.
Is that why you're looking for me?
Here is the thing.
A friend of mine was arrested
by the police yesterday.
She might even be detained.
Then you've got the wrong person.
Never mind your friend,
even if I were arrested,
he wouldn't lift a finger.
But she was framed.
She just got to Fengyang,
and she's still in university.
She just came to the dance hall
that day to see me.
She must have drunk something
she shouldn't have.
If she really gets detained,
and if her parents find out,
it'll worry them to death.
And
if the school finds out, it's over.
She won't even be able
to finish her studies.
(Yingxiong Roller Skating Rink)
I haven't finished yet.
Regarding my friend's situation...
I have a friend here. We'll talk later.
Mr. Huo.
What brings you here today?
I have some business with Chen Hui.
- Mr. Huo.
- You get back to work.
Let's talk inside. Come.
Mr. Huo,
what are you doing here?
How is the search
for Jiao Yuqin going?
I've already asked everyone under me.
Nobody knows Jiao Yuqin.
You have to give me some time.
I don't have time to give you.
Hurry up and find her for me.
Mr. Huo,
let's be reasonable here.
You only gave me a name
and one day.
Where am I supposed
to find someone that fast?
Do you have any other information?
You know her, right?
Mr. Huo,
I swear I really don't know her.
Who are you kidding?
You sold her the cough syrup,
and you don't know her?
I really don't.
I just supply the drug to the dealers.
How would I know who they sell it to?
Bring your dealers here.
I'll ask them myself.
I can't contact my dealers.
The police are checking
for cough syrup everywhere now.
What if they've been caught,
and if I contact them,
wouldn't I be turning myself in?
I don't care about that.
That's your problem.
I just want you to find Jiao Yuqin.
If you can't find her,
I'll report you to the police station.
Let's see how your father
deals with you then.
I don't think you'd dare to report me.
What do you mean?
Aren't you afraid of the police
investigation into Beimianling?
Did you take care
of the potassium permanganate
in your car?
Boy,
are you threatening me?
You want to go down together,
is that it?
Mr. Huo,
I gave you my word.
So I'll find her for you.
But you have to give me some time.
Besides, in all of Fengyang,
I'm the only one
who can help you find her.
I'll trust you this once.
Mr. Huo, are you leaving?
Take care.
Take care, Mr. Huo.
What's going on with you and Mr. Huo?
Why did you have
to talk in the warehouse?
It's nothing.
Remember when he and I
took you to the hospital?
I broke his trunk latch.
I promised to pay him back.
It's all settled now.
(Yingxiong Roller Skating Rink)
The one in the blue clothes.
I'm talking to you.
Yeah, you. Come here.
Go, quick.
Everyone, move inside.
Police inspection!
Turn on the lights. Turn off the music.
Stop.
Over here.
Men in one line, women in another.
Line up.
Li, take him.
Get him sorted out.
Move.
Men's line here, women's line there.
Spot check.
Take a paper cup.
You're doing urine tests in a moment.
Hurry up.
Men in one line, women in another.
Police inspection. Line up.
♪I always thought
once we see the full picture♪
♪We could understand
each other with empathy♪
♪I always thought
the path we never took♪
♪Must have had more beautiful scenery♪
♪Keep moving forward
and don't look back♪
♪The shore is only reached
by the road ahead♪
♪Too much debt has accumulated♪
♪In this short life♪
♪Between right and wrong,
how to choose♪
♪Regret is inevitable in the end♪
♪Even so-called love
is repaid with pain♪
♪I hear the laughter
and follow the crowd♪
♪Into the streets and alleys♪
♪On that brightly lit night♪
♪Unfortunately, the breeze in town♪
♪Can no longer catch up to the children♪
♪Times have changed♪
♪Now, everything♪
♪Is no longer what it used to be♪