[uplifting instrumental music playing]
[music swells]
[music continues]
[music speeds up]
[music swells]
-[music continues on computer]
-[girl] There we go!
-That dress!
-[boy 1] So beautiful. So many people…
-[music stops]
-[gasps]
No!
Why is there a lag?
[boy 1] Our Internet's that bad, huh?
Hey, don't let my uncle hear you.
He's only just bought the latest plan.
Is someone downloading?
Downloading?
-[boy 2] Uh, that's it.
-Hey, it's Ms. Berta. Hi, Ms. Berta.
-[Berta] Hi.
-[boys] You!
-[boy 2] It's him.
-[boy 3] There you go.
-[boy 4] Hey.
-What's that?
I'm trying to burn a CD.
-Oh, are you?
-Yeah.
-Try later.
-What?
Later. We're watching
the debut party for Mara San Andres.
-Uh, what do I care?
-What?
-Why should I care?
-This. This is why you should care.
-[boy 3] That did it!
-Ugh.
-[boy1] Rose.
-[boy 3] Come on, it's on.
-Come on. Hurry, here, hurry!
-Here we are.
-Almost…
-[Rose gasps]
[boy 2] There she is, there she is!
-[Rose] Look at her, she's beautiful!
-[boy 1] Wow!
-[boy 2] Oh!
-[all] Yeah!
-[boy 3] Oh!
-[music stops]
-[all gasp]
-Jeez!
No!
[uplifting instrumental music playing]
[music fades]
[woman] Hey, Jordan,
wipe that frown off your face.
[Jordan] Mom, I still don't understand
what the heck we're doing here.
New job! New opportunities!
Aunt Kakai has offered me
the chance to manage her resort.
-[Jordan exhales deeply] Yeah.
-[indistinct background chatter]
-Are we staying with Aunt Kakai?
-No.
We're renting a house near the resort.
Is there a computer there?
-Probably not.
-Mom, how am I supposed to contact Dad?
There might be a computer shop nearby.
And will you let those shades go?
The sun's gone.
Honestly.
[boy] Oh my God, girls!
I spy with my pretty eyes
a white chocolate wearing a black jacket!
-[girl] Who, where?
-[boy screams in excitement] Shocker!
-[screaming]
-[energetic music playing]
[boy] Baby boy.
-[woman] Jordan!
-[Jordan] Coming.
[music stops]
You're hot! Oh, yes, you are, you cutie.
You don't always dress up,
but you're pretty. Ah!
Darling.
That face of yours is staying the same.
So there's no point
looking at the mirror! [laughs]
Oh, you… You're ruining it.
Your pretty face won't change, all right?
You didn't even let me finish.
-Really? Good recovery!
-Yeah, you like that?
It's just your hair.
It's nice but it looks like
it could be stuck to your forehead.
-Looks greasy.
-Oh. No.
Maybe there's something
I can buy you that'll fix it.
When I'm in town, I can pick up
shampoo, conditioner, whatever.
Thanks, Dad.
I'm gonna buy them myself
'cause today I get paid.
Hang on. You told me
you were saving for your debut.
-Well, I am.
-So why don't you let me buy them?
-Huh?
-Promise?
-Sure! [laughs]
-Really? Oh, you're the best dad ever!
-Thank you, Dad. Thank you!
-I love you!
-You're welcome!
[upbeat music playing]
[upbeat music continues]
[people screaming excitedly]
[screaming continues]
[Rose] What's up?
-Great timing. Come on now. Quickly.
-[Rose] What? Why are we…?
-Move, move.
-What is going on here? Hey! Hey!
-[upbeat music continues]
-[screaming continues]
-Oh my… oh my God!
-[screaming]
What's happening? I can't see a thing.
What do they look like?
Just like Jack. Mm.
-[girl 2] So true.
-Who's Jack?
The one in the Titanic.
-Leonardo DiCaprio?
-Sure, babe.
-You know, I got a crush on that guy.
-Me too.
-Look, he's coming out.
-[boy] Oh my God!
-[screaming continues]
-Oh! Ugh!
[excited clamoring]
-[screaming continues]
-[woman screams]
[upbeat music playing]
-Oh! Hey! Hey, stop shouting. Stop!
-[screaming continues]
-Don't yell at Ms. Melai.
-[Ms. Melai screams]
-Ms. Melai…
-[screams]
-Hey, don't shout! Stop shouting!
-Go away!
-Ms. Melai, let's, um…
-What's happening?
[shakily] Have we had another
stabbing incident with a ballpoint?!
-Uh, no. Ms. Melai, it's more.
-Oh!
-You know the guy from the Titanic?
-What?
Leonardo DiCapri?
-Caprio. Caprio.
-Caprio? Oh!
-Ms. Melai.
-Caprio, Caprio. Uh!
-Come to the garden. Let's go.
-Okay!
-[girl 3] He's coming!
-Let's go…
-Oh my God!
-[boy] No, no…
-[all screaming]
What's your problem?
-You're my problem now.
-[screaming resumes]
[yelps] He's holding my hand.
I think I'm in love.
[all screaming]
[screaming continues]
[music stops]
[Rose] There you are! Camellia and Dahlia,
I've put you two together,
so that when you finally bloom,
you'll be so beautiful, okay?
I've also replaced your soil. [laughs]
Okay, that's it.
[Ms. Melai] Stop it.
They'll start talking back soon.
[laughs] My mother always said
to treat them like they were my own kids.
-[Ms. Melai] Mm!
-Talk to them and also, take care. Eh?
Do you have a lot of plants
at home as well?
Oh, of course.
Especially when Mom was still here.
She was always planting
and growing things, you see.
-So, you take after her?
-Oh yeah, I got her good looks as well!
Ugh! No! Oh, my amnesia.
And I forgot the fertilizer.
I should have brought it down.
-It's behind the tree.
-Ms. Melai.
-I'll go get it.
-Really?
-Calm down now.
-That'd be great.
It's… it's right there
in the jute sack. It's just there…
-Uh, I'll deal with it.
-Thank you. Thank you so much!
[blows raspberry]
[indistinct chatter]
Excuse me.
This is the computer room, right?
-Yes.
-Can I use them?
No, they're broken.
Uh… All of them?
That's not…
[sighs]
[poignant music playing]
[dramatic note plays]
[all] Hi, Jordan! [screaming]
Jesus.
[upbeat music playing]
Move. Get out of the way.
[growl]
Damn!
-[music builds]
-[screaming]
-[screaming in distance]
-[indistinct]
Stop it. Please!
Later. Yeah.
Jordan, Jordan. Jordan, where are you?
Girl, where is he?
-You go down that way.
-Okay.
And you guys go to the right.
-Should we use a secret code?
-Well, screaming is good.
And you'll be where?
-Yeah.
-Just here.
-You think? Come on.
-Okay, let's go.
-[screaming]
-[all] Jordan!
-Uh. Later. See ya!
-Later.
-[music fades]
-Damn it. Wow!
[screaming continues in distance]
[upbeat music resumes]
Ugh. Smells. [sniffs]
Oh, man. [panting]
[music builds]
[Rose] Hey!
[music continues]
-[music stops]
-[Jordan grunts]
[gasps, groans]
What? Oh my God! Shit!
Are you…?
-Gee.
-What is that?
[gags] What's that smell?
Shit?
Are you serious?
Why are you walking around with shit?
That's fertilizer.
That's for… That's for my…
-That's for my…
-For your what now, huh?
For my scholarship.
You know, community service.
So full of it.
[scoffs] Scholarship.
That is not fertilizer. This is shit.
You keep saying shit.
You're shit. It's fertilizer.
You think you're so great
but you're a jerk.
You bumped into me anyway.
-So it's my fault we both smell like shit?
-Uh…
-Yeah! Duh!
-You shouldn't have brought this.
-Duh!
-Don't be arrogant. I know everyone here.
If you wanna go for it,
I'll snap my fingers,
and they'll be waiting at the front gate.
If that's what you're after…
-Slow. Stop. Stop.
-My fingers snap and you're dead.
-I can't even understand you…
-Uh…
-Just say sorry…
-Speak clearly.
-Say sorry to me now.
-[screaming]
-You say sorry now.
-You want me to say sorry?
-[Jordan, frustrated] Oh my God!
-[screaming continues]
-What's going on?
-I don't know…
-[Jordan] It's your fault.
-Don't be so rude! You son of a…
-Hey, are you from around here?
-He's not listening to you.
-[keyboard clacking]
-[sniffs] Foreigners don't wash often.
-[boy 3] That's… That's body odor, right?
-No way.
[sniffs] Ugh!
-It's shit.
-Holy shit!
-Horrible!
-Smell like shit, huh?
-[boy 3] Uh-oh.
-Oh.
Come on, huh?
What, you thought I didn't understand?
Thought I didn't understand?
-Come on, come on! Say it to my face.
-[boy 1] Sorry.
-What? How is it you're still here?
-[boy 2] Rose, he's bullying us.
-So, what are you doing here?
-This girl's the reason I smell like shit.
Shit girl.
-Who are you calling "shit girl," huh?
-You got shat on too? You smell like shit.
Hey, that's not it.
He ran into me. I had fertilizer.
I dropped all the fertilizer.
I'd say that's his fault, is it not?
-Just tell them the truth.
-Oh, what truth?
You're just like everyone at that school.
Chasing me, following me…
Enough! Seriously, can't even
get an ounce of peace and quiet.
Oh, for someone who's so high and mighty,
there's a lot you should learn.
This is where I work.
Before you were even here,
I work here, you colonizer.
-[boys and Rose] Oh! Colonizer!
-Colonizer?
-Colonizer? What the fuck?
-Hey.
-[Jordan] Colonizer?
-No swearing in here, no more swearing.
You can't swear in here, so get lost.
-I'm not leaving.
-"I'm not leaving." Get out!
I paid for the hour,
so I'm finishing my hour.
Think you're a tough guy, do you?
Okay, that's it. This is gonna cost you.
You can't do that.
I'm a paying customer. Come on.
-What the hell?
-Go on.
Oh, big man crying over ten pesos.
Here's ten pesos.
I don't need your ten pesos.
-Get out.
-[boy 2] Go home, go on.
Where's your boss?
I'll talk to him right now.
-He wants the boss now?
-Boss?
-He wants the boss.
-Boss.
-Actually, I'm my own boss. I'm the boss!
-[boy 1] Oh! Yeah!
-[Rose] And that's that. So get out. Okay?
-[boy 2] Go! Go home!
-[boy 3] What an asshole.
-You stink.
[overlapping chatter]
Even the other customers think you smell.
-Can you smell yourself? I know you can…
-It's you. Just leave.
-I know you can smell yourself.
-It's you. You stink… like shit.
-See you. Stinky.
-Like shit!
[boy 3] Uh, gross.
[music stops]
I don't want to be here.
[grunts]
Why am I here? Why am I here?
Why am I here, Mom? Why?
[melancholic music playing]
-[Jordan] Mom.
-What?
-Can I have cereal?
-Huh?
Oh, no, we don't have any cereal.
I haven't got to the store yet.
Uh, there's only dried fish.
-Thank you so much.
-Thank you.
Mom, you know
I don't eat rice in the morning.
Oh? And why is that?
Mom, we've gone over this so many times.
Dad never ate rice. Americans don't.
Oh. But you're also Pinoy,
so eat your rice.
-No, I'm American.
-[sighs] You know what, Jordan?
If you keep acting like this,
how will you ever adjust?
You need to be more open,
or you'll never make new friends.
Mom, can't I just be with Dad?
[sighs]
Mom. Mom, fine.
Can… Can you please
just buy me a computer?
-What for?
-So I can email Dad.
He can get me out of here.
Has he replied?
When he writes back.
So, keep emailing him.
Mom, how can I keep emailing him
if we don't have a computer?
Please stop it, okay?
You'll be late for school.
Come on. Please, huh?
[melancholic music continues]
Jordan.
-Your lunch. Jordan!
-[loud music playing on headphones]
[music fades in the distance]
[indistinct chatter]
Hey! Would you be able
to help me get the chocolate drink?
I can't reach that high.
Hey, that drink's mine! Give it here.
What do you mean it's yours?
I'm already holding it.
Give it here.
I asked the shopkeeper for it
and that's why I hadn't already bought it.
-Let me have that.
-It's not my fault you're small.
Bully.
Think you're a model?
I think… Why would you say that?
Think I'm a model…
That's all you guys care about
in this place.
-Fucking looks.
-You…
You know, "fuck." You know "shit."
Do you know more words than that?
Where were your parents
when you were learning to talk?
[somber music playing]
I should have that!
[energetic rock music playing]
[slurps loudly]
Now it's wasted.
[rock music fades]
[indistinct chatter]
Okay.
Hey.
-One hour.
-Oh!
There's no available computers
for you today.
There's a computer right there.
I'm not blind.
Not that one.
Because that one cannot be hired.
Someone's using it. Too bad for you.
-Fine. I'll wait.
-Okay. You wait.
-I will.
-Good for you.
Okay. [scoffs] "I'll wait."
-Rose!
-Ah, Ms. Berta!
-You know why I'm here. I need an hour.
-Of course, Ms. Berta.
-That one's yours!
-Yes, my favorite.
-Thank you!
-Hey, okay! Have fun, Ms. Berta.
Hey. Hey!
That's mine. I waited.
You told me to wait. I waited.
She's a regular
and she made a reservation. Did you?
-No reservation, huh?
-Reserve?
I heard the whole conversation back there.
She did not reserve.
You want me to tell the barangay, huh?
I'll tell the barangay right now.
-Tell what?
-I'll tell the barangay right now.
And I'll have them close up the shop.
-Oh, where are you going?
-The barangay, you heard me.
[mockingly] Oh, barungey, okay.
Let's make a trip to the barungey.
And I'll report you to the barungey
'cause you stole my drink, didn't you?
-Huh? Remember, huh?
-One drink. One chocolate drink.
And you're not gonna
let me use your fricking computer?
-That's it. Okay, fine, I'll buy you ten.
-Uh-huh.
-You want ten?
-It's not about that.
-What?
-It's about my, um…
My…
principles.
[scoffs] Principles?
What are you talking about, principles?
That's none of your business.
-You're making fun of me? You wanna…?
-There, you see that?
You'll be beaten up if you don't leave.
Yeah, that's right, you'll be beaten up
if you don't leave right now.
-Oh!
-[Rose] Is that clear?
Oh my God, just go away.
Oh. Oh, I feel sorry for you. Just go.
-[Jordan grunts]
-Oh!
I'll beat you up, boy. Small little boy.
[energetic rock music playing]
[music continues]
[music stops]
Hey! Why are you all wet?
'Cause of some stupid girl.
You pick fights with girls now?
-Jordan, that's not right.
-Come on, of course I know that.
She picks fights with me.
She doesn't let me go
in the computer shop or use the computer.
Do you want me
to talk to whoever's in charge?
-Aunt Kakai knows the owner.
-No, I'm fine. I can handle it myself.
-Okay.
-I'm fine.
But, you know,
there's still a way that you can help,
if you really want to, Mom.
-Mmm?
-I've been asking about it all week.
Come on, Mom, can we please
just get a computer, that's all I need.
I'm sorry, son,
but it's just not in our budget.
I'm still new at the resort,
and hey, we have to save our money
for all the things we really need.
But Mom, I… I need it,
so I can message Dad.
-Has he emailed back?
-Why keep asking me if he's answered?
How am I supposed
to know if he's answered? I don't--
Your father hasn't replied,
and it's been ten years or more.
-Maybe it's time to give up.
-No.
I will not give up on my dad.
I will not do what you did.
[melancholic music playing]
I… Mom, he's going to answer me.
I know he will.
He will, because I am his son.
He's gonna answer me.
I know.
No computers available
even though you're just opening up shop.
Yeah.
No available computers for you.
I'll wait.
Even if I have to wait all day.
Then, wait.
[melancholic guitar music playing]
-Ah, Ms. Berta!
-Hi, Rose.
Baby time.
Wow! Looks like you're moving
to the next stage.
-You look good together.
-You think?
-Really good, Ms. Berta!
-Thank you!
-[computer game SFX]
-[Berta] She said we're a match.
Uh… I need you to finish up.
-Thirty minutes more.
-Okay, thirty minutes. You as well.
-No, wait. I'm just finishing up.
-Come on. Really?
Rose.
He's been here since this morning.
He said he'd wait,
that it didn't matter how long it took.
It's a long time.
See how long he lasts.
-Many thanks!
-They're all done.
Thank you.
[music continues]
[music fades]
Hey, Rose. Maybe it's important
what Mr. USA needs to do.
He's been waiting out there all day.
Come on, Rose.
Have some mercy. Poor thing.
Show some heart, Rose.
Uh, you three.
You changed your minds quickly.
Psst. Hey.
We're closing in 15 minutes.
Well, I'm not leaving.
Not until I've read my email.
I'll fix the Xerox machine.
I'll be there for five minutes.
What do I care?
I said, I'll be there for five minutes.
Dude, use this.
-Wait, wait.
-It's free. Sit down there.
Come on, go.
-[upbeat music playing]
-[machine rattling]
Come on.
[music turns melancholic]
Whoa! That was quick.
Less than five minutes, huh?
-Is he done?
-Weird. He left so quickly.
Are you okay?
I just got a bit weirded out
by that customer from America, Dad.
[father] Mm.
Tess's son.
Handsome boy, huh?
Hm?
-No.
-Mm? You think he's cute.
-You do! Look, your nostrils are flaring.
-No. No, no.
-Oh, come on. They're not. You're silly.
-[father laughs]
-Gotcha!
-Hey. Hey, no.
-Because Dad…
-Mm.
He keeps on pestering me
to get into Green Skies.
-Mmm.
-That's the truth.
But when he logs on,
all he does is check emails.
He doesn't do Friendster
or games or open YM.
That goes to show
he doesn't think those things matter.
Also… Maybe the thing that matters
is who's getting that email.
Could be his father.
You know? It can be really hard
being far away from those you love.
[melancholic music playing]
A bit like Mom and you, hey?
Hm? No. Your mom and I are different.
I know that she'll be back here.
I know at some point she'll come home.
But Jordan's dad? Who knows?
So, try to be a bit more sympathetic.
[melancholic music continues]
Uh!
Uh! Head back, head back.
I'll get some ice.
How come your nose is bleeding again?
Maybe I'm allergic
to being kind, Dad! [laughs]
[father] Head back. Head back. Head back.
-Head back! Where's… Where's that towel?
-[laughing]
[energetic rock music playing in distance]
-Rose, Rose.
-Oh, look, here comes Rose. Sit here.
[girl] Come sit here.
[indistinct chatter]
Hello?
[energetic rock music
playing through headphones]
Hello! Hi!
[volume increases]
[singing along with music on CD player]
Oh! Yeah.
[continues singing along with music]
[both sing along with music on CD player]
[Rose] Let's go!
[sings in menacing voice]
-[voice rises and stops]
-[song ends]
[applause breaks out]
Thank you! Thank you!
Thank you! And thank you!
-[cheering]
-Thank you! [laughs]
-You're awesome. Are you in a band?
-[music stops]
What? Being a singer, worth a try.
I… just listen to their music. That's it.
Interesting you can
sing a song in Tagalog.
I thought English
was your only language. [laughs]
So what if it's Tagalog?
I like their music.
Lots of people ask me
to burn GSK CDs at the shop.
So, I've memorized some of the songs.
But if I ever play them at the shop,
Dad will always blast me.
-I get killed! [laughs]
-[laughs] Me too!
-My mom…
-Yeah?
My mom is the same, she doesn't like it.
Maybe it's an old people thing?
[both laugh]
Huh. You know, my dad…
My dad, though, he likes this music.
He's really into heavy metal.
He likes GSK.
[whimsical music playing]
What's this?
-What?
-What are you doing?
Why are you acting all nice, huh?
Because you're by yourself,
I thought I'd sit with you.
I felt sorry for you.
I don't want your pity. I'm fine.
There, there, it's okay.
Oh. There, there. Really?
"There, there." That's four! Want this?
I'm fine.
[screams]
-Jordan, hi.
-Hi. Hi.
[Rose] Jordan!
-Are you going to Green Skies?
-[boy and girl] Bye. Bye.
Maybe.
Maybe? Just say if you are.
Look, why are you
being so nice to me, man?
I don't get it.
Don't be sorry for me. I'm fine.
You're joking. You're a drama queen.
-Actually, I want to say sorry.
-Sorry for what?
I'm sorry for not being nice.
Which you already know
because I'm apologizing now.
-I won't grovel.
-[laughs]
You can go to Green Skies.
You can email all you want.
[tender music playing]
Mm… My mom lives away for work.
So, I know what it feels like
to have someone living far away from you.
Mm. So you're spying on me. Huh?
-I know you've…
-I only just found out from Gibo.
Talk to Gibo.
-Spying. Who? Me?
-[laughs]
Um, yeah. Okay, I've been…
emailing my dad.
He's in the US.
I'm trying to make him get me out of here.
-Well, email him every day. Hm?
-Yeah.
Then he can look after you.
That'll get rid of one burden for me.
What'd you say? Huh?
-Nothing. I said nothing.
-Yeah?
-I thought so.
-Let's go.
I thought so!
[Rose] This is a lot.
You know, I'll hand it to you.
I really admire your persistence.
[laughs lightly] Yeah, it's…
It's been two years.
I've been emailing him for two years now.
And you know how I found his email…
two years ago?
I was just looking
through my mom's drawer.
That was the way I found his contact.
What? He still hasn't replied?
Perhaps it's not even
his actual email address.
-Maybe it belongs to someone else.
-No. I'm sure.
I'm sure it's him, sorry.
I lied.
He did reply.
But only to the first few emails.
What if he's busy?
Or he just forgot to reply?
Or maybe he got annoyed.
You have been sending a lot of emails.
Can you blame me?
I…
I just need my dad.
So it's been how long now?
Ten years.
It's been ten years.
I was seven years old.
That's terrible.
So long.
But you still want your dad to take you?
Why? What's there in the US?
Have you thought about that?
That you'll miss people.
Your friends in the old Philippines.
I don't have friends.
Ah… Of course not.
Of course not.
-[keyboard clacking]
-[music fades]
You know, I was thinking…
Could your dad not want you
because you're… a bit desperate?
-Well, I am desperate. Can't help that.
-Guess you can't.
But have a think about Gela
and the girls' behavior. You hate it.
They're desperate
for any attention from you.
And the last thing
you want to do is give them that.
-See? Get it now?
-Why are you comparing Gela to my dad?
You want me to run away?
You want me to avoid him?
-Ignore him? What are you…
-Well… No.
Uh… You have to make him want you. Get it?
Forget about how much
you have to talk to him.
You shouldn't make him feel responsible.
-Okay?
-But I am his responsibility. I'm his son.
Where… where are you going with this?
-You're so negative. I give up.
-Okay. Fine, fine. I'm listening.
-That's enough. Forget it.
-I'm listening.
Rose, I'm all ears.
Please. What do you suggest?
[Rose clears throat]
You have to make him see
that you have your life together, okay?
That you're always busy,
that you're achieving many things.
You have to be somebody. Huh?
And how am I supposed to do that? Here, I…
Very good question.
Good question. You're really coming along.
All right. Eyes here, eyes here.
Do you see that?
This picture here, do you know Mr. Chito?
-Obviously not.
-This… this… this is Mr. Chito, here.
This is Mr. Chito, who is now a councilor.
Mr. Chito is also my uncle.
He's the owner of Green Skies.
But… I'm the reason that he won.
He wouldn't have won, you see.
Except I designed him
a poster and a jingle.
Do you see? He became somebody.
Now I can do that too, for you.
You just have to pay me.
[Jordan laughs]
You sound and look
like a scammer at the moment.
Scammer, huh? Well, you get nothing.
It's not a scam.
And I don't charge high fees.
-Deal?
-What do you need the money for anyway?
You work here.
I'm saving up for my debut.
De-boo? De-boo. You mean debut?
Debut. De-boo,
whatever, it's all the same.
Sure.
So you wanna…
wear a dress, dance with boys.
-That's what you're saving money for?
-Hey.
It's not that superficial.
In fact, it's every Filipina's dream.
Maybe that's why Filipinas…
Filipinos don't have money. Hm?
Sounds impractical.
Very impractical if you ask me.
You and your mouth.
You should listen to yourself, man.
You act like you're too cool for school,
but you're an American living here. Oh.
Hey, how many times you gotta talk about…
-That's because my dad left and I don't--
-[blows raspberry]
Whatever. You talk too much.
So why don't you…
just help me with the costs for my de-boo,
and you'll get my help reaching Daddy-o.
Huh? Ah, ah!
I don't know.
Okay, money back
if it doesn't work. That's my offer.
Mmm? Uh? Yeah! Good, right! Give it here.
To quote that old saying,
"Are you in or out?"
Huh? Give it here!
-Fine. I'm in.
-Yeah! A good decision.
Smart choice. Have these. [laughs]
[music fades]
-If your head hurts, stop doing it.
-Dad?
Here, your daughter's home.
-Here, it's your mother. She wants a word.
-Ah, thanks.
Hey, Ma!
Hey, I miss you. I love you, Ma.
I love you so, so, so much!
Oh, honey, that's very nice to hear.
I love you too.
You sound in good spirits.
It's nothing, Ma.
I just found an extra racket.
Hey, I'm not working hard over here
just so you can take on more side hustles.
My debut's soon.
-Will you be here for that?
-Of course I will.
Oh, and do you have a list of men
that are going to dance with you?
Come on, a list?
And find someone handsome.
That shouldn't be hard.
Listen to her!
She thinks I should look for a male model.
This is our strategy if we're
going to get your dad to notice you.
1. GET RECOGNITION AT SCHOOL
-Here it is.
-Serious? I'm paying for this?
You know, I've been working on this a lot.
So, you better choose
your next words carefully.
Number three. All right, "Become famous."
-"And be seen on live TV. "
-Mm.
How are we supposed to do that?
You're such a downer all the time.
Why be a downer?
-Don't worry about that. I'll work it out.
-Fine.
I'll leave all the work to you,
Ms. Miracle Worker.
Yes! That's the spirit!
-I'm ready to get my money back.
-Say what?
Nothing! Nothing.
Come on. Where do we start?
Now, relax. Anyway, this plan's great.
You're gonna be
the next student body president.
Rose, I'm a transferee.
No one's going to vote for me.
Oh, really? That you can't ever know.
[upbeat pop music playing]
You smile. Big smile. Yeah!
Then you wave to them.
Just wave to them, go.
-Girls!
-[screams]
[screaming grows louder]
Ah! Now, you tell them, "Wow, I love you!"
-All right, now, why would I say that?
-[screaming continues]
Don't be a downer.
Say, "Wow, I love you!" Shout.
-[half-heartedly] Wow! I love you!
-[screaming intensifies]
-Oh!
-[all] We love you, Jordan!
-[gang yelling excitedly]
-[Rose laughs]
-[upbeat pop music continues]
-Oh! All right.
[Rose] Let's get to work.
Go easy on the orders, Rose.
We're not getting paid.
Damn right.
Oh. It sounds like
you want me to go and get Jordan.
Could that be what you're saying?
-No, no, I didn't say that.
-Jordan!
-Yeah. Just a sec. What's up?
-[Rose] Mm.
Jordan, what's that?
Is that dirt in your armpits?
Check them.
-[screams]
-[boy] Oh my God.
-[screaming continues]
-Oh my God!
[Gela] Now, we'll work, work, work.
-Vote for Jordan.
-Vote for me.
You have to vote for him.
Tell your friends.
-Casey! Oh, can you hold this?
-[girl] Vote for Jordan!
When the gang arrives,
can you give it to them?
And then, I'll let you know
what I want you to do.
-Just hold on. Thanks for this.
-Rose.
Yeah. Thank you. Take care.
What is it?
-I'm giving away flyers and balloons.
-Yeah, can't you do that next to me?
Why?
'Cause I need you.
Uh, I need my campaign manager. Hm?!
Sure.
-Jordan! Jordan! Jordan for president!
-[upbeat pop music continues]
[Jordan laughs]
-Submit it!
-[Jordan] I'm going to do it!
Um… Ma'am. Jordan Anderson.
Please. Can I please take the photo?
-One, two, three…
-[inaudible]
[upbeat pop music continues]
[pop music fades]
[rooster crows in distance]
-[inspiring music playing]
-Oh! Beautiful! [gasps]
Oh.
-That one's beautiful.
-[Rose] It is!
And I think it suits you.
But maybe you'd consider
offering a discount for friends?
Um, I'll see. I could ask my mother.
-Promise?
-Yes, of course.
By the way,
it's weird you're not here with Jordan.
Why? Because if he was,
you'd give that discount for sure?
-Who, me?
-[both chuckle]
But he'll need to be measured up
for what he's wearing
to the meeting about the election.
No, it's not hard to do.
-I can guess it and, anyway, he's busy.
-Ah.
Because right now,
he's practicing his speech.
-A speech, I see.
-A speech!
But… are you officially
going out with Jordan?
You two are always together, right?
-Yuck! No, that's silly.
-Yeah. [laughs]
-That's not a thing. That'd never happen.
-Really?
But anyway,
I just want to assist with the election.
-[Gela] Mmm.
-I don't know if… we're even friends.
You're only saying that.
Maybe you're just giving
false hope to us Jordan addicts.
[laughs] Jordan addicts.
Oh, and of course,
if it's the wrong size
or doesn't fit, just bring it back.
[music fades]
Anderson!
-Dimaguiba!
-[cheers]
-Anderson!
-[Jordan] It's close.
Dimaguiba!
-Why are you so nervous?
-[Ms. Melai] Anderson!
-Dimaguiba!
-I'm not.
-Rose, you're literally biting your nails.
-[Ms. Melai] Anderson!
What's up?
-[Ms. Melai] Dimaguiba!
-I'm okay. I'm just hungry.
[Ms. Melai] Anderson!
-Joke!
-[Ms. Melai] Dimaguiba!
[exhales] It's because
it's such a close fight, see?
I thought it was gonna be a landslide.
-[Ms. Melai] Anderson!
-I hope you win.
[Ms. Melai] Dimaguiba!
-[Ms. Melai] Anderson! Dimaguiba!
-Don't worry. I'll win.
-I'm sure about it.
-[Ms. Melai] Anderson!
What self-belief. Confident!
-Maybe we'll get knocked out?
-No. That's impossible.
-[Ms. Melai] Dimaguiba!
You know why? Because I have
the best campaign manager in the world.
-[poignant music playing]
-[Ms. Melai] Anderson!
[cheering]
-[Ms. Melai] Dimaguiba!
-[applause]
[Ms. Melai] There's five more,
just five more.
-Shh.
-Dimaguiba!
[cheers]
-[nervous chatter]
-Anderson!
-[all] Yes!
-Dimaguiba!
Anderson!
-[cheering]
-Yes!
[tense music playing]
-Anderson!
-[cheering]
[Ms. Melai] Okay!
We have a new student council president.
It's the transferee, Jordan Anderson!
[raucous cheering]
[upbeat pop music playing]
[all] Jordan!
[cheering continues]
[all] Jordan! Jordan! Jordan! Jordan!
Jordan! Jordan!
1. GET RECOGNITION AT SCHOOL
[all] Jordan! Jordan!
-Hey! Take it easy.
-[laughs]
People might think
you're losing your mind.
No, I… I just didn't know I could be
this happy from winning the election.
-Can we go to Green Skies?
-Now?
Yeah. I was thinking I want
to message my dad as soon as I can.
Well, the shop's closed today.
They're fixing the modem.
-Are you serious?
-Mm-hmm.
There's no way. Damn.
It's okay. Don't worry,
it'll be open again early tomorrow.
You'll be able to email your dad then.
-Wait. You'd do that for me?
-Mmm.
-You would do that for me?
-Yeah.
-You'll be able to email. It'll be fine.
-Best campaign manager ever!
-[Jordan laughing]
-Hey, quit it. If I punched you…
-Agh, oh…
-[clack]
-Oh, careful, you'll break it.
-Oh, damn!
-That's sore. Ugh, it's your fault.
-[music turns somber]
You don't look okay.
It's your fault I'm so dizzy.
[laughs] Sorry, oh… Well, you can't walk.
-Made me dizzy, spinning me round.
-I can carry you. Come on. One…
-Two…
-Don't overreact. I need to sit down.
-Okay.
-Okay?
-Ah, you're catching on fast!
-[both laugh]
You know, when Dad and I lived in Manila,
I thought I should
have started working earlier,
because I wanted to do
what they were doing on TV.
You know Star Circle Quest? Kids.
Kid's Quest. I could have done it.
If I'd done that,
then by now we'd be rich.
You think those kids are rich?
Don't you? Of course.
You're gonna be modeling Moose Gear.
Then you'll get deals for hot dogs. Oh!
Now, that'd be all right,
a lifetime supply of hot dogs!
[laughs] Maybe I should be an actor.
-You? That'd suit you!
-[laughs]
-Oh, yeah! You look like one!
-Yeah?
Seriously though,
Filipinas are into that stuff.
You know,
foreigners and looking like foreigners.
Sandara Park is a foreigner
and she won SCQ.
-Mm.
-You didn't know that before? Mm?
-Mm?
-No. [laughs]
Yeah, but why would
you want to be an actor?
Would you still work?
Your father lives in the US.
He'd probably send you lots of money.
-[poignant music playing]
-Huh.
-Hm.
-What?
Doesn't he?
Come to think of it, I…
I honestly wouldn't know.
Mom never talked about Dad sending money.
You've got a problem
if you want to follow this dude.
Why do you want to be over there?
Mmm… I don't know, I guess…
Ever since I was a kid,
my dad was my hero.
Just wanted to be like him. I idolized him
in every single way I could think of.
Whatever he did, I wanted to do.
Is that why you became a blonde, huh?
-And why the fake accent?
-What?
That blonde.
The blonde is fake. Yeah! [laughs]
-This is not… This is real.
-Oh!
-It's not. You can see here, it's fake.
-This is… [laughs]
Okay! Fine. Fine.
Fine. Yes, Okay. Fine, fine, fine.
Fake hair, fake Tagalog accent.
I can talk Tagalog pretty good, but…
I don't know. I guess I got used
to speaking English all my life 'cause…
Yeah, Dad spoke English.
Like I said, anything he did,
everything he did, I followed, I copied.
I faked it until…
it made me happy.
Well…
Yeah.
And are you happy now?
Hm?
[poignant music continues]
Now I am.
-Ah!
-A little.
-Hey, thanks to me. Thanks to me!
-Thanks to you.
And…
You're welcome.
[music stops]
Man, it's been two days. Still no reply.
Hey, face facts.
Maybe he's been busy with work.
It could be too busy to check emails.
You don't know.
-I knew this wouldn't work.
-Hey, come on. Calm down.
This is just the first plan.
We've got two more on the list, right?
Think positive, okay? All right?
-Sorry, you're right. Think positive.
-Mm.
-That's right.
-Attract positivity.
That's right. Now, because
you've been very good, have a treat.
That's it!
Ah! How come you and Putrid
are together so often?
I thought you were
just helping with the election.
Who's Putrid?
-You!
-Hey. He doesn't smell, you know.
-[Gibo laughing] Uh…
-[boy 1] She said he doesn't smell!
-Stop it, okay?
-[boys laughing]
-Hey, that's enough, guys.
-Come in, come in.
-[Gibo] So he doesn't smell anymore? Ugh.
You can help us out
instead of acting all stupid.
We've got a problem here.
We have to make this guy famous.
So maybe suggest something. An idea or…
Oh, I saw this on TV.
A guy opening a coconut with his teeth.
-I saw that!
-That'd be great.
What are you talking about, dude?
-You. Coconut.
-Ah, you take the coconut…
-Coconut mouth? Your ideas are stupid.
-[Gibo] Oh, come on, it'd be awesome.
-Enough now. Don't listen to them.
-[Gibo] Why don't you try that?
-Damn right! These suggestions are stupid.
-Tell me how that works out.
Uh, excuse me, is Bertha here?
-Uh, is this your dad?
-Bertha?
-No.
-We're under attack from white people!
Don't… don't mind them.
Jordan. How can I help you?
Yeah, I'm looking
for a woman named Bertha.
-[Jordan] I'm new here, so I don't know.
-[Rose] Uh, maybe…
-Who's Bertha?
-Do you have her address?
Well, this is the only
Internet café in town, right?
-Yeah, yeah.
-[Rose] Only this one.
Then I'm sure she's from here.
Sorry, sir, I didn't get your name.
Uh, I'm sorry, my name is Ewan.
-That's familiar to you?
-[Ewan] See this.
I always see this in the background
when we chat on Yahoo Messenger, so…
-She's got to be from here.
-Ah! You're the one she always speaks to!
You're Ms. Berta's baby.
-Berta! Yes, Berta!
-It's you.
-Ah, Berta!
-[Rose] I remember your face.
I'm here to surprise her.
Do you know where she lives?
I will take you to her.
-Great! Great, great!
-I got you.
-Okay, come on.
-Can you three look after the shop
-while I take this guy to Ms. Berta?
-[boys] Sure.
-Let's go.
-Hurry!
-[Ewan] There. There. Yeah.
-[Rose] It's here.
[exciting music playing]
RomblonPrettyGirl!
[music turns intriguing]
DaddyWhiteBoy19?!
-Bertha!
-Ewan!
Yes, it's me!
I came here to be with you, my love!
-Oh my God! Oh my… Oh my God.
-[music stops]
-Oh my God. Oh my God, oh my God…
-Wait there. Ms. Berta?
-What's going on?
-What the heck?
Oh my God, oh my God, oh my God! [whines]
[whimpers] Oh my God! Am I beautiful?
-Of course you are. So pretty.
-Really?
Look at me. Look at me, I'm hideous.
You're hideous, aren't you? You're awful.
-Come on, Ms. Berta.
-[cries]
[Rose] Have you forgotten?
You're the original jewel of Romblon.
Those days are gone.
But this is who I am now.
Oh, I've gotten so big, Rose.
Why? Why?
Why would she run away like that?
Am I… am I that ugly? Do I smell bad?
Hey, hey. Hey, hey.
Don't beat yourself up. Not just yet.
-[Ewan sighs]
-It's just, you know, women are…
weird, here. [laughs]
That's what I like about her.
She's… different.
I thought she would appreciate, uh…
-a crazy surprise like this.
-Uh-huh.
You know, because she's…
-Crazy!
-Yeah.
I just didn't think
she was going to be that crazy.
Hey, don't worry about it too much, okay?
Rose is in there.
She'll speak some… sense into her head.
Rose is the best.
Really? Rose is that good?
-Yeah.
-[dramatic note plays]
Shit, I'm so stressed.
I don't know what I should wear.
[sighs] Do you like this one?
-I think…
-No, it's ugly.
I look like an ex-convent girl.
-That will look so nice.
-Disgusting!
Not this one!
Don't worry. That man didn't
come here because of what you wear.
-He's here to see you.
-[dramatic note plays]
[melancholic music playing]
He's just so good-looking.
Well, Ewan… what's your plan now?
I don't know! [laughs nervously]
But I'm not giving up on her.
You don't give up on love.
Yeah.
Have you ever been in love?
[poignant music playing]
Good morning, Ms.
Where on earth have you been?
-Hey, hey, hey… how's Bertha?
-[Rose sighs] Uh…
She's just a bit overwhelmed.
-Uh.
-Because, you see…
She wasn't expecting at all that
you'd come all the way here, that's all.
-Yeah, because I want to be with her.
-Maybe she's just… confused.
I mean, we know
she loves the online version of you.
-Okay, well, what… what can I do?
-Simple!
We'll show her
and introduce to her the real you.
-Okay… how do we do that?
-Okay?
We'll do that
by getting you to sing harana to her.
-Harana? What, what, what is that?
-Yes, we'll do harana.
That's the traditional way
of courting here in the Philippines.
-Okay, Okay.
-Okay? We'll do it?
-Yes!
Am I a part of this?
-Yes, of course!
-Yeah, come on, I can't do this alone!
-[Rose] Yes!
-[Ewan] There you go!
You know… I can't believe
that Ewan is willing
to give up his whole life in the States.
-Whole life.
-[Rose] Mmm.
And turn everything around for Ms. Berta.
-Crazy.
-Really?
I don't think so. I get Ewan.
Because he really loves Ms. Berta.
And he's the sort of person
that, when he's in love,
he won't stop till he's tried everything.
Do you think that'd be your approach?
I don't know.
You don't know? Why?
Haven't you been in love?
[pensive music playing]
Ah, maybe you can't relate
because you've never felt love.
That's why. What a loser.
[scoffs] What? You're trying
to tell me you've been in love?
Of course! Twice!
-Twice?!
-Yeah!
Damn.
-Oh, yeah.
-Twice already, this early on in life?
You're trying to tell me
you've been in love twice.
Oh, what? You've never been in love.
You don't know. You've got no idea.
Someone falls in love easily. Mmm.
Ah… bu--bu--but…
[laughs] Careful.
You might fall in love with me!
-Hm?
-Uh… Oh, smooth!
-[laughs]
-You talk too much, you know! Okay.
There was one who was
a neighbor back in the day.
I was still in grade two.
But he moved to Manila.
And the other one's name was Jack.
-Jack?
-Of course, Jack.
Am I supposed to know who Jack is?
It's Jack. He's in the Titanic. [chuckles]
[Jordan laughs] Ah!
Spoiler alert… He died.
You're hopeless. Okay.
Why did he die then? Why did he die?
I don't know, the Titanic sank?
Hey. He sacrificed himself for Rose.
You get it?
And we've got the same name.
Damn! How's that?
[both laugh]
And, you know,
when Gela and the girls first saw you,
they said you looked
just like Leonardo DiCaprio.
Really? [groans, laughs]
-Ah! Da-da-da-da-da…
-What?
I understand it now.
You say I look like Leonardo DiCaprio.
Jack. Mm.
You're trying to tell me
you have a crush on me?
Uh, excuse me.
It was actually Gela who said that.
-Mmm.
-Oh, I don't see it.
-I don't see it. There or there!
-Oh… Oh, ah… Ah.
Really? Hm? Mmm?
[laughs]
What an idiot! Come on, let's go home.
Gotcha!
-Can you hold my coconut?
-[music fades]
[man] Two… three…
You're making corners,
move smoothly… Three… four.
Okay, and then you meet in the middle.
[indistinct chatter]
[teacher] Okay,
and after, you bow. Okay, go!
-Rose!
-Really?
-What are you doing?
-[laughs]
You don't need to surprise me.
-I'm fine with hello.
-I just felt like it. You're so serious.
What are you looking at? You're staring.
[Rose] That's Juana over there.
-[teacher] …four, five, six.
-She and her partner…
They're practicing
the dance for her debut.
Uh-huh… You're jealous.
[breathes deeply] No way, Jose.
I'm not jealous…
[laughs] Don't be jealous!
Uh… why don't you just
ask him to teach you the dance?
Uh, okay. Okay, why not?
But it'll look weird, won't it?
If it's just me doing the practice.
Well, you have… me.
Seriously?
-If you don't want to, you can just say…
-Hey, no taking it back!
[both laughing]
Okay. Okay, fine!
-Uh… Sir?
-Ask him.
Would we be able to learn to dance?
-Is that okay?
-Okay. Is he your escort?
Uh… um, friend.
-Friend.
-[teacher] Okay, just follow what we do.
-Stand there.
-[Rose] Okay.
-[Jordan] I'll go here, yeah.
-[teacher] Okay, ready? Two, nice.
-Waltz two, three, one, and turn around!
-[teacher] Three, around. And stop, okay.
-This is Gibo, playing the cajón.
-Okay. Gibo, hey.
-Yes. And that is Samgi.
-Nice. Hey, Samgi.
-He will be playing the guitar for us.
-Great.
While Tony will be playing the macarenas.
-Macarenas! Go, Tony!
-[Rose laughs] Macarenas.
And I will be teaching you the song.
-Let's do this. Okay?
-And Jordan will sing backup.
-Okay, great, great.
-Hey, I only sing heavy metal!
-What do you mean, "backup"?
-It'll be great.
Okay, the first line…
[sings lyrics in Filipino]
[in English] Hang on, just slower.
Can you break it down?
-Please, for me.
-You say… [recites lyrics in Filipino]
-[repeats lyrics in Filipino]
-[Rose in English] Yes!
-Hooray! Faster, that's the first line.
-First line!
After you finish learning it,
you have to rehearse it over and over.
I'll manage Ms. Berta.
I'll prepare her for the harana
so she doesn't disappear again.
-How're you going to do that?
-She loves salsa!
-Really?
-Yeah!
-Okay!
-Great!
[all laugh]
[Rose] Let's go!
Ewan made that.
He asked me to give it to you.
-Did he cook it all?
-For you. Because it's your favorite.
-It's yum! Mmm.
-Nice! Yes!
-She loved it?
-She loved it.
-Oh!
-She had a big smile when eating the meal.
She said the sauce was great!
Now I can't wait for the surprise.
Me too! I'm sure she's gonna love it.
Especially when she sees
you wearing that barong,
looking all handsome!
I'm sure she'll run to you in double time!
-Fingers crossed.
-Yes!
If you think I look handsome
in this barong, you should see Jordan!
Way better!
[intriguing music playing]
So… how do I look?
Handsome, sir.
[friends cheer mockingly]
-[Tony] Yeah! There she goes again!
-[Gibo] You two! Ah.
-Oh, to be young and in love!
-[Gibo squeals]
[Tony] She's totally into him.
Look, she's blushing!
[music stops]
[romantic guitar music playing]
Are you serious?
[sings a romantic song in Filipino]
[harmonizing in Filipino]
[in English] I got this.
-How do I look… okay? All right.
-You're beautiful.
-Berta.
-For me?
-Yes, of course!
-Oh. Thank you!
-To… RomblonPrettyGirl@skype.com!
-[Berta laughs]
-That's sweet.
-To the woman… who was there…
In my computer, every day.
You have saved me… from my sadness.
Even though we were countries apart,
I felt your love…
pass through our computer screens,
straight into my heart.
[laughs softly through tears]
[Berta] How do I look? Am I beautiful?
-[Rose] You are so beautiful.
-Okay.
[Rose] So, so beautiful.
-Berta…
-[gasps]
[crying]
Will you marry me?
Go!
Ewan… Ewan.
-Yes!
Yes! Absolutely, yes!
-Does it fit?
-Oh… perfect!
-Perfect. Oh, yeah!
-Perfect. Oh, my love!
[Jordan resumes singing in Filipino]
[harmonizing in Filipino]
[song ends]
-[boys cheering]
-[Gibo in English] Aw, guys! Go home!
[Jordan laughing]
[Jordan ] Uh…
-Rose.
-Jordan.
[both laugh lightly]
-[Jordan] You go first.
-No, uh…
Nothing. I just wanted to say that…
uh, I loved the way you sang.
For someone who's a heavy metal rocker,
you could be a balladeer.
-Really? [laughs]
-You could!
I honestly didn't think
I could sing like that.
-Oh! I told you you'd be great.
-Mm. [laughs]
You wouldn't believe it.
Thank you.
Thank you for what?
For always believing in me.
Oh, of course, because…
you're paying me, remember?
Is it really 'cause of the money?
[Jordan laughs nervously]
Um…
Hey. Get off the ground now.
You can't propose. I'm too young for that!
Oh, yeah, of course.
Of course I know that.
I am too! [laughs]
But, um…
I do have another proposal.
Proposal? What proposal?
Rose…
Can I be your escort at your debut?
-Are you sure?
-[laughs] Of course I'm sure!
-Of course. Yes.
-Mm.
But, um, if you have someone else in mind…
-Get up now, you're talking too much!
-Please…
I'll think about it first.
Think about? Really?
I mean, come on.
They say… I look like Jack.
Right?
You are Rose.
I'd say we're perfect together.
If you ask me!
[both laugh]
Fine, we can be Jack and Rose at my debut!
-Yeah?
-Yes, but…
I hope the ending's
not that tragic at my debut.
[laughs] I hope so! I hope so!
So, um, what now?
HHWW?
I'm sorry, what's that?
Holding hands while walking.
Schmaltzy.
-Huh? Schmaltzy! It's a good word.
-Ugh.
It's a good word.
Oh, come on. Okay. Hey, hey, hey.
-Bye-bye!
-Bye!
-Uh, what… what do I…
-Uh…
-Do I… What do I do?
-Uh… do?! Stay here. I'll go there.
-Right. Yeah.
-Okay, yeah!
Bye.
-Bye-bye.
-Bye.
[music swells]
[laughs nervously]
Bye!
[father] Mmm!
-Mmm…
-[Rose laughs]
-So this daughter of mine is all grown up?
-Dad!
[father] Huh?
[both laugh]
That guy from the Titanic
and your Jordan are almost the same!
[both laugh]
And you, my love? Huh?
Sorry, Dad. Sorry, Pop.
You're really very pretty! Huh?
Come on, Dad, cut me some slack.
Just this once…
-Okay?
-Mmm.
Okay.
But you… can't get pregnant,
you're far too young.
-Dad!
-Huh?
-I don't want… No, I won't… Why say it?
-[laughs]
-I'm joking! [laughs]
-Ugh.
-Hey, Rose…
-[high-pitched ringing]
I was joking.
Rose.
Rose?
[tense music playing]
-[thud]
-Hey, Rose! Hey, Rose?
[tense music continues]
[heavy metal music playing
through headphones]
Jordan! Jordan, Jordan, Jordan!
Look at this!
I… look at this.
Oh, you're gonna love this.
-Out of the way.
-Gela, be careful.
Look at this!
Everyone in town is talking
about the foreigner and Ms. Berta.
Then there's you and Rose.
You guys are like real-life Cupids.
-Mm!
-You're famous now!
[tense music playing]
Wait.
This was Rose's second plan.
What second plan?
2. BE FEATURED
IN THE LOCAL NEWSPAPER OF ROMBLON
Nothing. Um… thank you.
Thank you, Gela. Uh…
-You're welcome.
-Have you seen Rose, 'cause…
I haven't seen her all day.
I messaged but no reply.
Surely she's at Green Skies.
Most likely, yeah.
-Rose! Rose! Guys, Rose? Where's Rose?
-Huh?
-Gibo.
-Jordan.
Where's Rose?
-No Rose?
-She's not here.
[indistinct background chatter]
-Where is she?
-She's sick.
-Damn!
-Are you going to use a computer?
Yeah, one hour.
Um… and I need these scanned.
Uh, six is free.
Dad hasn't replied to you yet?
And Rose hasn't replied.
Rose?
Why is that? You have a tiff?
Did you?
[rooster crows outside]
Gibo says she's sick.
She's sick, but I…
Hey, Mom… last time I saw her,
I kissed her on the cheek.
[laughs]
Do you think I'm being overaggressive?
She's not answering.
Maybe she's actually sick.
Have you been by her place?
-[somber music playing]
-No.
Go over there.
[footsteps leaving]
-[indistinct background chatter]
-[computer game SFX in background]
[message pings]
[music turns tense]
[music turns poignant]
Oh my God!
Oh my God! Fuck, yeah! Fuck, yeah.
-Hey, enough with the "fuck." What's up?
-Sorry. Sorry, sorry.
[upbeat music continues]
Rose? Rose!
[panting]
[Rose] Jordan?
Gibo said you're sick. Are you sick?
I don't know what to tell you.
I wanted to tell you in person.
We did it!
My dad replied.
My dad replied!
[gasps] My dad replied, Rose.
[tearfully] My dad… My dad replied.
He… I didn't think it was possible, but…
After so long, he finally replied,
and it's all because of you.
Thank you so much.
[crying] Thank you, Rose. Thank you.
We did it! We… [laughs]
-[tearfully] Congrats!
-What? Why are you crying?
I'm happy for you.
[both laugh softly]
Thank you.
I… I couldn't have done it without you.
[father clears throat]
You're Jordan, right?
Yeah. Yes, sir.
Are you hungry?
Why don't you join us out back?
So you like eating kinilaw, huh?
-Dad, he's just being respectful.
-[father] Mm?
No! [laughs nervously]
-No, sir. Um, it's actually my first time.
-Mm.
But… I like it a lot. Thank you.
Suck up! [laughs]
[all laugh]
No! Look, look. Mmm.
He's just pretending, Dad.
Don't believe a thing.
Sir, where's the restroom?
Uh, you go in there and it's on the right.
Just through that door.
Thank you.
-[footsteps departing]
-[door opens]
Have you told him yet?
[somber music playing]
Now's the time to tell him.
[somber music continues]
-This CD's got the playlist for my debut.
-[Jordan] Mmm.
"My debut playlist."
Nice. Are there… any GSK songs on it?
What do you think? Of course there are.
I'm sure you know "Story."
Heard that one? Sure you have.
Oh! Makes sense. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Their…
That's their…
only ballad song on the album.
Yeah, right.
They're a heavy metal rock band
that records one ballad song. It sucks!
I actually call it their sellout era.
That's why I want it at the debut.
I can imagine every detail.
And then…
I see it all.
Everything's slo-mo…
And I'm dancing with my escort.
You mean… me. Right?
[melancholic music playing]
Rose. If you don't want me
to be your escort anymore,
it's… it's okay.
You can just tell me.
Is there something wrong?
[cries]
[hesitates]
I have brain cancer.
I…
I just wish there was
something I could do, you know.
Oh, come on.
It's all okay.
I can do it.
And survive too.
Rose.
Rose. Please, remember…
I'm always here if you need me.
Okay?
Promise?
Don't forget that, yeah? Promise.
-I'm all right.
-Okay. [sniffles]
-Yeah, okay. Sure, okay.
-Okay?
See you.
-Okay. See you.
-See you.
See you. [sniffs]
-[sobbing]
-[melancholic music playing]
[takes a deep breath]
[romantic pop ballad playing]
[music builds]
[music falls]
[music fades]
[indistinct chatter]
Look at you! All growing so well!
You give me strength.
And you're beautiful as well.
I want to bloom like you.
[Ms. Melai] Rose? Rose!
-Oh, Rose!
-Ms. Melai?
Rose! [groans]
I heard the news.
But I'm not going to cry.
Because you don't like drama, right?
That's fine!
So what's the word from the doctor?
Can they make you better?
[sighs] Uh, well, you know…
I have a booking next week.
That's so I can begin chemo.
Because they need to see
how I'll go with the treatment.
Know what? I am going to make sure
that all these flowers
get to you at the hospital.
-Not there, Ms. Melai.
-What?
The debut party… If I make it!
-Oh, no! Don't talk like that.
-[laughs]
You know you're going to get better.
And then, we'll bring
all these flowers to your debut, huh?
Give me those. They're mine.
Because I won't have you
working too hard and becoming exhausted.
Well, good morning, Star Seekers Company.
I'm Kevin Dimaguiba.
Ms. Melai, what's going on?
You wouldn't have heard about that.
It's people from Channel 3
looking for teenagers to audition.
-What?
-Those that want to be stars.
How long are they gonna be here,
Ms. Melai?
They're here until next week,
then they move to a different location.
Kevin Dimaguiba.
Vote for me on Star Seekers.
-[phone rings]
-Yeah, Rose. What's up?
Hello, Jordan. Is your class over?
Yeah, what's wrong?
I think we're ready
to action the third plan on our list.
[Rose] Your audition
is exactly a week from now, huh?
Yeah, and your chemo session's
exactly one week from now too.
[Rose] Hey. Don't worry about that.
As long as we're prepared, right?
Because then you'll get in.
And you'll be on TV.
Tell me,
why do you want to be a celebrity?
Uh, because I, um…
Hey, what are you saying?
You can't say "um." Don't give me "um."
Don't show them you're thinking.
This is the answer, okay?
"Because my friends tell me
that I am the Leonardo DiCaprio of Romblon
and I want to be a star!"
-Okay?
-I don't know why I'm saying that. I…
-Game!
-Ugh!
Because my friends tell me
I'm the Leonardo DiCaprio of Romblon,
and I want to be a star.
-[Rose] Happy! How do you show happy?
-Happy?
-There you go!
-Happier, okay. Happier!
-Woo! Yes!
-Yes, very good!
-Angry.
-Mad?
Oh, sure.
Get angry with the camera. That's it!
-Sadness?
-Sadness.
Is that the best you can do?
It should be…
We don't want it looking fake.
If you're feeling blue,
hit me with it. Okay?
-Sad.
-Okay.
Go. Tap into your emotions.
[music fades]
-Rose? Rose! Rose! Hey!
-[tense music playing]
[high-pitched ringing]
Hey, are you okay?
[music builds]
Oh… there.
That's sadness. See, I felt that.
Now you look incredibly sad.
Rose, this is stupid.
Why would you do that? Don't do that.
-[somber music playing]
-Sorry.
-How would you like your hair done today?
-I don't know.
-Hey, Berta, it'd be quicker to shave it.
-I could try…
-Just a bit.
-Like, bald?
-No. No, no, no. Come on, no way.
-You'd have some hair.
I don't think
I'd look good as a bald guy, okay?
It'd give you an awesome look.
Or, if you want, I could trim it a little.
-Or I could take it off the top.
-Yeah, I can do a trim.
-[Berta] You don't want a color?
-No. No, I'm happy with…
This is fine. Yeah, let's do a trim.
-A trim'll be fine.
-He's scared to shave, but I'll shave.
-What are you doing?
-What are you talking about?
I really want to go bald.
And why would you do that?
Well, it'll probably happen anyway.
Why not now?
Ready.
[razor buzzing]
[melancholic music playing]
[music builds]
[music fades]
Psst. So… how do you think I look?
What? No answer?
-Don't you like it? Is it bad?
-[laughs softly]
It's not that.
What now?
Why are you staring at me like that?
Well…
It's 'cause I want to remember this face.
Bald and perfect.
Have you eaten something weird?
-It's Rose!
-[laughs]
[Jordan] Rose.
Rose, can I please not do that audition?
What?
Why?
I want to be there with you.
In your chemo sessions.
-To do what? Wha--
-To… to be there with you.
To be there with you, to hold your hand.
Be next to you.
Be next to you through the whole process.
I want you to know
that I'm here through everything.
Jordan, that won't help me.
You can't do a thing. Okay?
Rose, why are you…
why are you pushing me away, Rose?
[waves lapping gently]
[melancholic music playing]
I'm afraid I won't be able
to survive this. [sobs]
-I don't want you to see me die.
-Don't say that, don't say that.
-But it can happen.
-Rose. It can happen, but it won't.
-But if I do…
-Don't, don't even bring it up, Rose.
It's not fair.
We're not going to talk about
you dying because you're not going to die.
-Shh. Jordan. Jordan!
-You have to hold on. God damn!
Shhh. [sobs]
If I do…
[shakily] If I do…
you have to continue our plans, huh?
You have to meet your dad.
You… you need to meet your dad,
and you have to get off this island.
-Okay? Okay?
-[feebly] Yeah.
[Jordan crying]
You know, Jordan, when… when I was young…
When I was young,
all I wanted was a simple life.
I just wanted to be alive.
Here on Romblon. [laughs through tears]
With my mother… and my dad.
Before long, when I started to hang out
at the computer shop day in, day out…
I saw that…
this earth was big and beautiful.
[breathes deeply]
And there were so many interesting places…
outside of this island.
So… I don't know whether
it seems superficial, but…
I'd like to have what Mara San Andres had.
[laughs softly] To be like her.
I'd like to have the chance
to be a princess. Just for one night.
I want a debut. I want a debut because…
I worked and I put my money away.
I saved and worked so hard…
because I wanted to have a fancy debut.
Then I hear all the people…
there are lots of people saying,
"Wow! Oh, wow! You are awesome, Rose.
Did you see Rose? Wasn't she great?!"
"She had a wonderful debut party.
She did all that, you know."
"And what about
the way she saved for that?"
"Because she dreamt about it."
I just wanted…
I just wanted everyone's attention.
So that… so that people…
people would look forward…
to what's next for me.
But…
there might be nothing next.
Maybe there won't be a next.
Rose, don't. Please don't say that.
Don't say that. Don't be like that.
[Rose continues crying]
Jordan…
If I do…
you will fulfill your plans, okay?
Because…
the moment your dream comes true,
it will be like my dream's come true.
[sobbing]
And always remember…
Don't you forget me, okay?
We did this together.
-We planned this, me and you.
-[both crying]
You'll do it, okay? You'll do it.
Okay. Listen to me.
Listen to me. Listen to me.
[Rose] Please.
I'll do it.
-[laughs through tears]
-I'll do it for you.
Promise. I promise.
Thank you.
[melancholic music continues]
[indistinct chatter]
Jordan Anderson.
-[Rose] Dad, you're sweating so much.
-[laughs]
Hungry?
I am, but I'm not allowed to eat.
Nice try, Dad.
[nurse] Uh, Ms. Rose? Follow me.
Hello, hello! [laughs nervously] Hello.
Ma'am, sir, hello.
My name is Jordan Anderson. 17 years old.
[melancholic music continues]
[scanner whirring]
[melancholic music builds]
[click]
-[Rose] Mom!
-[mother] Sweetheart!
-[Rose screaming in pain]
-What's happened? Where does it hurt?
-Honey? Rene quickly. Rose, Rose, hold on…
-[continues screaming]
[mother] The pain will go away.
Just hold on to Mom, okay?
-Rene! Nurse, please, Rose…
-Mommy!
-Mom's here by your side.
-What is it?
-It just hurts too much!
-[screaming]
[mother] Call the nurse! I'm here, honey.
[melancholic music continues]
-[melancholic music fades]
-Thank you, Mom.
I'm glad you could be here.
Thank you. Thank you.
Of course, darling,
I don't like working away from here.
Taking care of folks I'm not close to.
My baby needs me right here with her.
But, Mom… I haven't got any cash.
If you were to charge me, I couldn't pay.
[both laugh]
I can't afford you.
You know, Rose, you just get well.
That's more than enough for me.
-[TV show theme tune plays]
-Can you do that?
-Yum, thanks.
-Eat up.
Promise?
Oh, oh! Jordan, it's Jordan. Jordan's on.
-Is that your boyfriend?
-No, Mom. He's just my friend.
Wow!
[all laugh]
Dad!
-[theme tune continues on TV]
-[studio audience cheering]
We're back
and you're watching Star Seekers.
And now, we're down
to our last contestant for the night.
And this kid's popular support
has been off the charts.
[raucous cheering]
From the auditions
to here at regional finals,
his support has been amazing.
Even the text votes
have been record-breaking.
Let's not delay any longer.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the so-called "Jack of Romblon."
Jordan Anderson!
[cheering raucously]
-[theme tune continues]
-[raucous cheering]
-Look! Excited?
-I'm being supportive, that's all.
Do you think you are
the star we're searching for?
Of course. The one and only.
[TV host] Wow, confidence. I love that.
-Jordan's handsome. Well done, Jordan.
-I taught Jordan that. I did!
Your question will be coming
from the one and only,
-Ms. Mara San Andres.
-[cheering]
Hi, Jordan. You're so good-looking.
-Ah! Your idol! Your idol!
-Is she the one, the one that…
-That's who… that's who's on my mirror.
-Yeah. Oh…
-Of course, I know who that is.
-That's her face!
Could you be in a love team?
[Rose laughs uncomfortably]
-Kidding! [laughs]
-[audience woos]
-[audience chattering]
-[laughs nervously] Um…
-I'm sorry, but… I can't.
-[audience reacts with disappointment]
[host] Oh, wow.
This is the first time
I've ever heard anyone reject Ms. Mara.
Is someone waiting for you in Romblon?
Anyway, the question
on everyone's mind, Jordan.
Do you already have a girlfriend?
-[suspenseful music playing]
-No. No, he won't.
[suspenseful music continues]
Girlfriend? [laughs nervously] Um…
I don't have a girlfriend.
[TV audience reacts with shock]
But… someone very special to me
is waiting in Romblon.
-Oh!
-Mm?
[tender music playing]
She's actually a big fan of yours, Mara.
Oh? Well, she must be very special
for you to reject me
on national television.
But she says she's a fan of mine,
which suggests
she must have pretty good taste.
Well, anyway, Jordan,
here's my question for you.
Why do you want to become a star?
[tender music continues]
To fulfil a friend's dream.
I only realized recently
how short life can be.
You never know when it's your time.
And in this lifetime, if I have the means…
If there's a way
to make other people happy…
why wouldn't I?
[melancholic music playing]
If by becoming a star,
I'll help her realize her happiness…
then that's my dream… To make her happy.
[melancholic music builds]
And the regional winner for Cebu
is none other than…
-[audience cheering]
-[host] Jordan Anderson!
3. BECOME FAMOUS AND BE SEEN ON TV
[audience cheering]
-[cheering stops]
-[music fades]
[keyboard clacking]
[clack]
[message alert]
[phone ringing]
-Jordan?
-[Jordan laughs] Rose, hey!
Jordan! How is the Jack of Romblon?
[laughs] I'm good, I'm good.
How is Rose of Romblon? Did you watch?
-Oh, of course! Of course I did!
-[laughs]
You were looking great on TV.
[laughs] Really?
More handsome in person or on TV?
TV.
[melancholic music playing]
But…
I miss you in person.
Oh man, I miss you too much.
If only you knew.
What time is it?
You don't have to sleep yet?
What? Come on.
You just called me,
and you think I should go already?
Why?
When I'm knocked out,
you think the cancer's knocked out?
[both laugh]
You know, I pray for you every day.
I pray that you'll get better.
Don't get so serious. Everything's fine.
♪ I'm alive, alert
Awake, enthusiastic! ♪
[both laugh]
But thank you. Thank you, Jordan.
It's so nice to have this break.
How's your, um, chemo sessions going?
Okay!
-Yeah?
-Okay, so far.
It's all okay.
I'm down to my last session.
-Yeah.
Next week…
March 25th.
-On your birthday?
-Yes.
But… how about your debut?
Huh?
-Debut?
-Yeah.
Uh… On that subject…
Plans changed!
We'll just do something nice
at the hospital.
Uh, man, I wish I could be there for you.
But… you know that…
I… well… Now, don't worry about that.
The best birthday gift I could have
would be if you won Star Seekers.
-[both laugh]
-I will. I will, I promise.
Uh, but, hey, by the way,
my dad's been answering all my emails.
-He's so proud of me. Yeah!
-Really?
-Oh, good for you. Good job, Jordan.
-[laughs]
Oh, and what's he say?
Will he bring you over?
Yeah.
He said he'll be my manager if I win,
so we can be together.
Good job. I told you, right?
I was convinced that this plan would work.
And it did work, right?
Yeah.
Hey, you can never be too sure, huh?
I don't know, he might
have said that as a joke or something.
Boy. What's the matter with you?
What did I say to you?
Remember. I said you should…
never be negative, always be positive.
Concentrate on the positive side.
Yeah. I will, I will.
I promise it's all for you, Rose.
It's all because of you.
I'm so sorry
I can't make it to your birthday.
Hey… I feel so guilty.
Well, it's fine.
Don't think about it, it's nothing.
And I'll be able to watch you from the…
the hospital bed, so… that's fun.
And after, you can text.
-[Jordan crying]
-Send me a… picture message.
-Yeah. Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
-So…
So, you got to go because my dad's awake.
He'll probably scold me. Tell me…
Tell me I'm up too late.
Good night, I'm going now.
Good night.
You take care, okay? Good night.
Night.
[melancholic music continues]
-[nurse 1] See you. Happy birthday.
-Bye. Thank you.
-[nurse 2] Good morning. Happy birthday.
-Thank you, nurse.
So many people are greeting you.
-Happy birthday.
-Thank you, Mom.
-[guard] Goodbye.
-[mother] Bye-bye.
-[Tess] Rose! Happy birthday!
-Hi! Thank you, but…
-Hello!
-[Tess] Hey.
What are you doing here?
Um… giving you a ride.
[laughs] Tell me… where are we going?
Maybe just come along.
-Where?
-Rose, it's all right.
-This'll be all right?
-[Tess] Yes! Yes, come on!
[pensive music playing]
Ms. Berta, what's this about?
I'm sure I told you
that I'd be doing your makeup
before your debut.
Oh, Ms. Berta.
The celebration's
only going to be at the hospital.
-We're not going to let that happen.
-There's no way.
-Not a chance. [laughs]
-[indistinct]
-But--
-You're asking too many questions.
Just sit back
and let us make you look
like the most beautiful girl of Romblon.
Okay?
[uplifting music playing]
I look amazing, Ms. Berta!
-You're so beautiful, Rose.
-You're blooming just like a flower. Mm.
-[Gela] You're incredible, Ms. Berta.
-[Berta] This was so easy.
[uneasy music playing]
But… something's not right.
What's wrong? Are the eyebrows even?
They look fine.
[Berta] Mm.
[uneasy music fades]
[inspiring music playing]
Perfect.
Lovely.
It's all good now.
-Perfect.
-So lovely.
-Will my parents be here to see me?
-Of course they will be.
-Is my dress all right?
-It's fine. You look gorgeous.
-[Rose] Perfect?
-[Gela] Perfect.
[uplifting music playing]
[uplifting music continues]
Happy birthday, Rose.
I wasn't expecting to see you.
I said I would be your escort, right?
But…
What about the competition?
The dream and your…
Dreams can wait for another day.
But you only turn 18 once…
And I wouldn't miss that for the world.
Shall we?
-[Rose] We shall.
-We shall!
[uplifting music continues]
[uplifting music builds]
[Rose] Thank you so much
for organizing this.
Thank you so much for organizing my life.
[both laugh]
Schmaltzy!
Come on.
Can you let me be romantic just for once?
Okay, fine!
Well, my Rose…
I just wanted to say…
I found a home here in Romblon
because of you.
I look forward
to the slow Internet connection.
Countless days at Green Skies,
the sunsets, everything.
Because of you,
I've met some of the most amazing people
I've met in my whole life.
More than that…
You've made me realize that…
I love you so much more
than my American dream.
[in Filipino] I love you so much, Rose.
[Rose sobs]
-[in English] That's enough words for now.
-[laughs]
-May I talk?
-Of course. Of course.
I love you, my Jack.
-I love you.
[uplifting music continues]
[music fades]
[indistinct background chatter]
[melancholic music playing]
It'll be fine.
Mm?
[laughs softly]
Take care.
[melancholic music continues]
[music builds]
[music continues]
[melancholic music stops]
[uplifting music playing]
[music continues]
[music stops]