BOYD:
Previously on
From...
[SOBBING]
Come here, come here.
[SOBBING] Oh, no.
[SOBBING]
"Knowledge comes at a cost"?
They killed Jim because of us.
Anghkooey. It means...
"Remember."
BOYD:
These kids
keep calling you back
to help them.
How do we do it?
I'm working on it.
TABITHA: Julie and Ethan.
I don't know how,
but I'm going to find a way
to take care of them,
to keep them safe.
Hey!
[CRYING] I don't want
to be here anymore!
What did you do?
Why didn't he come home?
I did nothing!
You're lying!
I want Dad!
JIM: Ethan.
The night we arrived here,
you had a dream.
Lake of Tears?
It's here,
and I need you to find it.
JULIE:
Ethan called it Storywalking.
I need you to give me some time,
even if it looks bad.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
[LIGHT GASP]
[GASPS] Dad!
[SCREAMS, STRAINS] Randall!
[WHIMPERING]
[RANDALL] I got you.
[SCREAMING]
Look at me.
SOPHIA:
Lord, please protect us
in this dark place.
[MAN] Ahh!
Please stand by
my daddy's bedside
and let him wake
renewed in your love.
[MUFFLED WHIMPERING]
[SOBBING]
My father died.
KENNY:
I'll talk to Boyd
about a burial.
BOYD: If people find out
what you did...
Help!
No!
That's the kind of thing that
could tear this place apart.
You're gonna tell them
that you lost your eye
trying to help Fatima.
[ENGINE REVVING]
Hey, hey, whoa!
I'm a good person,
and I don't deserve to be here.
Get the strip.
What I'm doing is getting out.
There is no way out.
[METAL CLANKING]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
What the fuck is wrong with you?
I gave birth to one of them.
Dad, tell her that's not
what you're saying.
It's the one I killed.
I told all of you that
there was something inside me.
Sorry.
It's okay.
I'll get out your way.
No, you don't...
You don't need to go.
I just came
to get a glass of water.
Boyd said if people
find out what happened...
I know.
We should probably
get our story straight.
Are you okay?
I'm not really sure
I deserve to be.
Elgin, I don't want to hate you.
This place took advantage
of both of us.
None of us will ever
be the same again...
will we?
No.
We won't.
There's something
I need your help with.
[GUNSHOTS]
[SCREAMING]
BOYD:
Abby, stop!
No! Stop!
[GASPS]
[EXHALES]
Oh, fuck.
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS] Shit.
You want to tell me what
the hell that was yesterday?
Not really.
You're going to have to do
a little better than that.
What do you want me to say?
I want you to tell me
that you're not going
to lose your shit again
and put people's lives
in danger.
You got lucky yesterday,
you understand that?
If Kristi had gotten hurt,
you and me are having
a different conversation
right now.
Look, whoever that was
yesterday, that wasn't me,
all right?
[SIGHS]
I don't want to be here.
Well, good.
We're working on that.
[SIGHS]
You know, Kristi told me
yesterday that she's seen
dozens of people
with dozens of schemes
about how to leave this place.
There's only one thing
that they have in common.
You know what it is?
They all died.
Yeah.
Well...
Well, this time feels different.
Yeah. It's probably
what they thought.
Can you give me a bullet?
I only need one.
I'll go into the woods.
And look, don't worry.
You won't even have
to clean it up.
Sophia...
I brought you some things
from your dad's car.
Thank you.
We're going to take him down
to the service now.
Can I have a minute
to say goodbye?
Yeah, of course.
We'll be right outside
when you're ready, okay?
SOPHIA: Okay.
[DOOR OPENS]
[EXHALES]
[DOOR CLOSES]
You were fun.
I couldn't let you go
without something
to remember you by.
[GRUNTS]
[TOOTH SNAPS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
["QUE SERA, SERA" PLAYING]
♪ When I was just a little boy
♪ I asked my father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be handsome?"
♪ "Will I be rich?" ♪
♪ Here's what he said to me ♪
♪ Que sera, sera
♪ Whatever will be, will be
♪ The future's not ours to see
♪ Que sera, sera
♪ What will be, will be
♪ Now I have
children of my own ♪
♪ They ask their father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be pretty?"
♪ "Will I be rich?" ♪
♪ I tell them tenderly ♪
♪ Que sera, sera
♪ Whatever will be, will be
♪ The future's not ours to see
♪ Que sera, sera
♪ What will be, will be
[SONG CONCLUDES]
Fuck!
Fuck.
Jade.
What?
Tell me you got something.
Does it fucking look like
I have something?
I...
Okay.
It's all...
It's in here. It's in here.
I know it is.
There's more to this.
There's more to what we need
to know, and I just...
I can't...
Fuck it.
You don't have any acid,
do you?
What?
LSD.
What? Listen, Henry said
Miranda started seeing
this place
after an acid trip they took,
which kind of makes sense
given, you know,
how the brain stores memory.
If it worked for her,
it stands to reason
it could work for me.
Oh, okay. Um, uh...
Take a breath.
If you're right
and everything we need
is in your brain,
then the last thing we need
is for you to scramble it.
Just take a little time.
Get back to this
after the funeral.
[SCOFFS]
I'm not going to the funeral.
Trust me, I won't be missed.
Look, the best thing
I can do for Tabitha,
for everybody here...
is just find a way to unlock
whatever is locked in here.
How are you going to do that?
I don't know.
Hey, Jade.
Be careful.
The message on the barn wall
wasn't fucking around.
Whatever answers you may find,
we have no idea
what they're going to cost.
You okay?
Doesn't fit.
[SIGHS]
Honey, I'm sorry.
It was the only thing
I could find in the shed.
You don't have to wear it
if you don't want to.
ETHAN: Yes, I do.
At grandpa's funeral,
Dad said a man wears a suit
to show his respect.
You look very handsome.
Let's go.
[SOFT CHATTERING]
Days like today...
they're not easy.
I'm not gonna stand here
and try to tell you that--
[CAWING]
[CROWD MURMURING]
[CROWS CAWING]
[MURMURING]
Boyd.
Just...
[CAWING CONTINUES]
You need to eat.
I'm not hungry.
[CLEARS THROAT] Hello.
Hey, Victor.
Uh...
Oh, I... so...
When I was a boy,
I drew pictures
so that the pictures
will remember.
This is for you.
[CLEARS THROAT]
That's very sweet, Victor.
Thank you so much.
Can I go to the Colony House
with Victor?
No, not today.
Please.
I don't want to be here.
Is that okay with you?
Yeah.
Okay.
Be safe, okay?
I'll make sure that nothing
happens to him, I promise.
Okay.
KENNY: [SIGHS]
Here, you drink this,
and Bakta
is just whipping you up
something to eat.
Has anything like that
ever happened before?
With the... the crows?
No.
I mean, everybody sees them
when they see the trees,
but that's, uh...
that's-- that's new.
When did it get like this?
What do you mean?
Well, Sara,
the girl who helped me
with my glasses, she...
she said that after Sheriff Boyd
found the talismans, that
for a long time
people were safe.
When did that change?
KENNY: It was, um...
I guess it was around
the night that my dad died.
We had lost a family
the night before, the Pratts.
And then Jim and Tabitha,
the Matthews family,
they showed up with Jade.
They came all together?
Um, not in the same car,
just they got here
at the same time.
And ever since then,
things have been bad?
No, no,
that's not what I mean.
Hey, Kenny.
You mind if I borrow him
for a second?
I'll be back.
Come here a second.
[KENNY SIGHS]
Hey.
Uh, Sophia, right?
I'm Julie.
I know.
I just wanted to tell you
I'm really sorry
about what happened
to your dad.
How's she doing?
[SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
Honestly,
I don't really know.
I mean, she prays a lot.
Are you fucking kidding me?
I... I didn't mean
to upset you.
I'm sorry.
What the fuck did
you mean to do then?
Hey, Julie.
No, she thinks it's our fault.
Hey, okay, everybody,
let's take a breath.
Did you tell her that all of
the bad things started happening
because we came here?
No, no, that's--
No, I didn't say--
No, that's not what I meant.
Let's go home.
No, fuck this.
This is not our home.
I... [GASPS]
Julie.
Julie, stop!
Do you think it's true?
What?
That when we got here,
that all of the bad things
that have happened
since we got here,
do you think it's our fault?
No, honey. Of course not.
Why did it feel like
those crows were celebrating?
[INDISTINCT]
Sophia.
I'm sorry. I didn't...
It's okay.
We need to talk. Okay?
Okay.
Poor Julie.
Yeah.
It seems like a lifetime ago
that we made that little space
for her in her room.
Yeah.
Hey.
You know,
you haven't really talked much.
About what happened?
I'm trying to be okay.
I am. I just...
I'm trying to let go of this.
I just don't know how.
You know what? I have an idea.
Stay right there.
I gotta grab a few things.
Where are you going?
Stay right there.
I'll be right back.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
[MUSIC FADES]
Oh, look.
Uh, Ethan,
my dad is my roommate now.
It's... This is...
This is his bed right here.
Yeah, it's a good thing
that I threw all my stuff
out the window
because then it made
all this space.
[SIGHS]
It's nice having
a roommate now, too, be...
because you have
someone to talk to,
you know, if you're afraid.
[SIGHS] And you can talk to me,
you know, if you're ever...
if you're ever afraid.
Are there any lakes here?
What?
Lakes. Have you seen
any lakes here?
There's the...
There's The Brundles.
That's not very far from here.
Can we go see it?
What?
No, I don't like it there.
Water's creepy.
Please.
Why do you want
to go see The Brundles?
Never mind. I'll find it myself.
No, but you're supposed
to stay here with me.
I don't care.
Well, I do.
I just need to see the lake.Why?
Friends aren't supposed
to keep secrets, Ethan.
Fine.
If you take me to the lake,
I'll tell you.
[GROANING]
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
[DRAWER CLOSES]
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
What are you doing out here?
Saw you walk off alone.
Thought you might be
doing something stupid,
like going back to the ruins.
Go away.
Julie.
I'm not going
to the ruins, okay?
I need to get something
from our house.
Okay.
Our old house.
Wait...
the one that collapsed?
No. No fucking way.
I was inside that thing
when it came down, remember?
Okay.
It's too unstable.
No, look, look.
All right, stop, stop, stop.
What's in there
that's so important?
I told you that thing
that I can do.
My brother called it
Storywalking.
Mm.
I learned about it
from one of his books,
and all his books
are under the house now.
And I need to know
if there's anything in there
about how to control it
so I can go back and save my dad
without getting killed.
And maybe that is stupid, okay?
But I'm not asking
your permission. I'm going.
So you can help me,
or you can leave me alone.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Give me that.
[EXHALES]
You still want that bullet?
There's something I need you
to do for me first.
What's he doing?
I think he's sleeping.
Jade?
What?
Let's go.
We just got here.
It's not what I'm looking for.
How do you know that?
I just do.
Ethan, you-- you promised...
that if I brought you here,
you would tell me.
I need to find
the Lake of Tears.
It's a lake with magical powers.
What kind of magical powers?
It can make people better
when they're hurt.
I thought I made it up.
But my dad told me it's here.
I need to find it.
When did he tell you that?
Yesterday... out by the RV.
Maybe once I find it,
it can make him better.
Maybe he'll come back.
Maybe Jade can help.
Jade!
Oh, for Christ's sakes, what?
We need to find
the Lake of Tears.
The Lake of what?
It's a kid's book,
though, right?
It's stories made up
for little kids.
Before we got here, I thought
monsters were made up, too.
Fair point.
You good?
This is where I talked to my dad
the day the house collapsed.
He was still down there
when the sun was setting.
I was so scared that
we were just going to lose him
right then and there.
He...
He kept telling me
everything was going to be okay.
that I shouldn't be afraid.
Hey, um...
Why don't you let me do this?
What?
I can handle a couple of books.
Besides, someone's gonna
need to be up here
if something happens, right?
No. No. I should be the...
It's my thing.
I should be the one--
Hey, hey, hey.
Storywalker.
Why don't you let
someone else do the cool shit
for change, huh?
It's good for my self-esteem.
There's a--
There's a way in over here.
[SNIFFLING]
In the story,
Achan caused the whole
nation of Israel to suffer
because he offended God.
And that's what you told Julie.
I just thought that maybe
if somehow they brought
some sort of ill--
Okay, stop.
The people here...
they're always one bad day away
from giving up.
Giving up, losing hope.
I know, it was-- It was...
I know.
Look.
We need to figure out
where you're going to live
from now on.
Where do you live?
[SMACKS LIPS]
That big house up on the hill,
Colony House.
There's plenty of room there.
But there's
so many people there.
Yeah.
Can't I just stay at the clinic?
Well, there's no extra rooms
in the clinic, so...
Where does Sara live?
What?
She was really nice to me.
That's not a good idea.
Because of... of what she did?
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
How did you, um...
I've...
I've heard people talking.
Why-- Why would you--
Why would you want
to live with her?
Because I've...
Because I've seen her kindness.
And I don't-- I don't think
she's a bad person.
You have no idea
the kind of person she is.
[GRUNTS]
[MUSIC FADES]
JULIE: I--
I can't see you at all.
Are you okay?
[PANTING]
I'm fine. Just letting
my eyes adjust, that's all.
[EXHALES]
How many of these books
am I looking for, anyway?
He kept them all
in a little blue bag.
They should be together.
Little blue bag, huh?
Piece of cake.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SQUEAKING]
[WIND BLOWING]
[WOOD CREAKING]
[EXHALES]
Randall?
I'm fine.
What are we doing here?
[EXHALES]
We got storage sheds
around town.
Storage room in the diner.
They're filled
with clothes, tools,
everything we thought
would be useful.
This is everything else.
Okay.
I want you to treat this place
like a crime scene.
Like, these... these things,
they tell a story, right?
I want you
to develop a narrative.
Tell me everything
there is to know
about the people
this stuff belonged to.
Why?
Because I asked you to.
So why don't you do it?
You're a cop.
You were trained to do this.
I wasn't.
ACOSTA: Hm.
There... There might be
things we overlooked.
Something that'll help us
get out of here.
Tell me why we're really here.
I just did.
Bullshit.
Hey.
You better tell me
why we're really here.
Because you remind me
of someone.
All right?
You remind me...
of someone I could have helped
and I didn't.
I don't get to get that back.
But I'm not gonna
stand here and--
Look, I know you think
everything I said is bullshit.
And maybe it is.
Maybe it isn't. Right?
But if you... do this for me,
think about all the people
you might be helping.
The people you might be saving.
You think about the cop
who first put that badge on.
You do all that
and you still want
that bullet...
then yeah, we'll talk.
It's a promise.
[CROWD CHATTER IN THE DISTANCE]
Donna?
[FLOORBOARD CREAKS]
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
I think she went back to town.
[MUSIC FADES]
Oh...
You need something?
Uh, no. I'm-- I'm okay.
Are you?
Forty years, I sat in my house
after my family disappeared.
I was a lot of things.
"Okay" was never one of them.
I should go home.
Where are you headed?
Um, just going home. Mm.
Oh. Well, I'll walk with you.
Henry, no. It's okay.
I can go by myself.
But, Tabitha, I don't think
you should be alone right now.
So where are you really going?
I'm going home.
And where are you going
after that?
Henry, I don't know
what you're talking about.
Sure you do. You're good
at a lot of things, Tabitha.
Lying is definitely
not among them.
So we can play the whole charade
of me dropping you off
at your house and then waiting
to see where else you go.
Okay, I'm going to find
the lighthouse, okay?
[EXHALES]
I'm gonna find my way back
to the lighthouse.
I got out of here once.
If I find the lighthouse,
maybe, maybe,
hopefully I can do it again
and take my children with me.
I'm not gonna let them die here.
How? Donna said no one knows
where the lighthouse is.
No, they don't.
That's why I have
to do it again,
like I did the last time.
I have to go through
The Bottle Tree.
The-- The man in the pool,
Dale, right?
He died when he tried
going through.
Yeah, but...
Okay, what if it was...
What if it was
not meant for him?
only meant for me?
And what if you're wrong?
What if you end up
stuck in the side
of God-knows-what, somewhere...
Well, I don't know.
I don't know, Henry.
I have to try.
Okay.
I'm coming with you.
No, Henry.
You said you're going
to The Bottle Tree, right?
I want to see it.
I want to see the tree
my wife died trying to reach.
Henry, I have
to tell you something.
She was my wife.
Please.
Okay. Let's go.
Okay.
Yeah.
Where are we going?
Just a little further.
Why won't you tell me
what's in the bag?
You'll see.
Ever heard of a rage room?
They're really popular in Japan.
Sort of a way to lash out.
You know, let go
without hurting somebody
or breaking shit that you need.
[EXHALES]
[SCOFFS]
Ellis, this is really sweet,
but I don't know
how this is going to help.
When my mom died...
you were the one
that brought me back.
You didn't even
know me very well.
But you knew that
I was still in there,
underneath all the...
the dark, horrible shit
that I was going through.
And you never gave up on me.
Not until you finally
pulled me out.
It's my turn now.
Give it a shot.
[BAT THUDS]
So...
you want the crowbar?
Or the bat?
[EXHALES]
Definitely the bat.
That's my girl.
[GRUNTS]
[ELLIS CHUCKLES]
[LAUGHS]
It's all yours.
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
[CHUCKLES]
Okay, so let me
get this straight.
You made up this Lake of Tears
as part of a game
that you used to play
with finger puppets.
It wasn't a game.
It was a story.
Okay, so you told a story
about this lake,
some finger puppets,
and now...
Now what?
You think the lake is here
because your dad told you
that you need to find it?
Maybe I didn't make it up.
Maybe I just thought I did.
I'm confused.
Do you remember the red rocks
we found at the settlement?
Yeah.
My mom thought she made them up
because she used to have
nightmares about them.
But the reason
she saw those rocks
was because they were here.
Maybe it's the same
with the lake.
Maybe I used it in my story...
because it's real
and I just didn't know.
What were you doing
at The Brundles?
It's an old
meditation technique.
ETHAN:
Why were you meditating?
JADE: Because I...
[EXHALES]
I'm trying
to remember something.
I'm trying remember something
that I used to know.
Something that'll help us leave.
ETHAN: So we're both
looking for something
that can help everyone.
JADE:
Yeah, I guess we are.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
Hey, Victor,
we got a lake to find.
Victor?
Hey.
What is that?
Victor.
[CROW CAWING]
[EXHALES]
ETHAN: Victor!
Victor! Come on.
JADE: Victor!
ETHAN: Victor!
[MUSIC FADES]
RANDALL: Jesus!
Fuck!
What?
[GROANS]
Nothing. I'm good.
Oh, fuck.
I see the bag.
[SIGHS]
Kenny.
Is everything all right?
KENNY: Sophia and I
have been talking about
where she wants to live
from now on.
Okay.
And if it's all right,
she would like
to live here with you.
Oh.
Okay. Sure.
KENNY: Okay.
Okay. Come on.
Let's go.
Randall?
Randall, what's going on?
Ah, just give me a sec.
[GRUNTS]
I got the bag.
What are the titles?
Uh...
Grand Gooligog,
the Cromenockle.
Okay, that's them.
Get out of there.
Yeah, all right.
Just you and me, pal.
Aw, fuck.
[GRUNTS]
[SQUEAKING]
[YELPS] Fuck!
JULIE: Randall?
Randall?
I'm okay.
[GROANS]
Better?
A little, yeah.
Well, it's a start, right?
Yeah.
I'm gonna, um...
I'm gonna go take a nap.
Yeah, I told Donna
that I was going to start
getting things ready
for the food run tomorrow.
Okay.
And hey, um...
thank you for today.
You're welcome.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
It's me.
I did the best I could.
Think it's going to be enough?
It's a great start,
but I think we're going to need
a little bit more.
[MUSIC FADES]
Well...
Victor told me this is where
Miranda was going when...
when she died.
He took me to her grave,
but I...
I don't think he could bear
to take me here.
This looks just like the one
she made back home.
Except for this.
Go back to town, Henry.
Tabitha, you can't do this.
Henry, please, I...
Look, I was hoping
you'd realize it on your own
by the time we got here.
Henry, I told you.
The tree is the one
that's gonna let me go through.
Yes, the tree is meant
only for you.
And... And... And...
And what if it isn't?
What if you're wrong?
What if you end up stuck
in some walls somewhere,
gasping for air, alone?
What happens to Julie and Ethan?
I left a note for Donna.
[NERVOUS EXHALE]
She'll make sure
to take care of them.
You left a note?
Yes, I did.
Boy, well, I didn't realize
you'd left a note.
I'm sure they'll be just fine.
Am I supposed to do nothing?
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYS]
Finding the lighthouse could be
what gets everyone home.
And if it's not?
I don't know.
I'll try something else.
Not if you're dead!
Then what the fuck
am I supposed to do, Henry?
Move! Please.
I don't know!
I don't know.
I wish I did know.
But if you want to go
through this tree...
you're gonna have
to go through me first.
Henry, move.
Please, Henry.
Your kids need you.
Ethan and Julie.
Tabitha?
Here.
[INTRIGUING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Why are you here?
Why do you look so different?
Those are the wrong questions.
Will that tree take me
back to the lighthouse?
I don't think so.
Wait, you don't think so?
You told me
it was the only way.
It was, but that was before.
Yeah, but before--
Okay, you need to stop
talking in riddles.
You're getting so close now,
but I'm afraid
you're running out of time.
ETHAN: [IN THE DISTANCE]
Victor!
[MUSIC FADES]
Okay.
It came from over there.
Come on.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
Victor!
[VICTOR WHIMPERING]
What happened?
TABITHA: [IN THE DISTANCE]
Ethan?
We're over here!
Ethan!
Oh, honey.
[MURMURING]
Honey.
Victor.
Hey.
Hey, talk to me, son.
I told...
I told myself it wasn't real.
[WHIMPERING]
[HENRY] Shh. It's okay, buddy.
It's okay.
You're all right, son.
It's okay, son. It's okay.
It's all right.
You're all right.
It's all right. Hey, hey.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[WHISPERING] I'll be damned.
[MUSIC FADES]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Hey, Abs.
Been a while.
Things are...
Yeah, things are changing.
I am changing.
Done some things recently,
and said some things.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYS]
I don't know
if I like who I'm becoming.
But I don't know
who else to be.
Tabitha and... and Jade,
uh, if what they're saying,
what they remember,
if-- if it's true,
it feels like
for the first time,
we're close to something.
Yeah,
but none of it matters if...
if I can't hold
these people together.
If I lose these people
right now, I...
Yeah.
I could really use some help.
I... I...
I don't know if there's--
if there's anything
you can do, but...
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
...if you can hear me...
What the-- Hey!
[STRAINING, SCREAMING]
No, no, no! No!
Hey, hey! Hey, hey!
[GRUNTING]
[STRAINING]
[MUSIC STOPS]
[SHOUTS]
[GROANS]
[PANTING]
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
What the...
What the fuck is...
[MUSIC FADES]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC CONCLUDES]