[Episode 5:
Isn't this the kind of night I wanted?]
Chen Ke. What's wrong?
I... I got burned.
Chen Ke.
How could you be so careless?
Stop wasting time.
Let's go. We're going to the nurse's office.
How could you be so careless?
For the next few days,
let's keep you in the hospital
for observation.
Ke Ke.
What's wrong?
What on earth happened?
It's nothing.
I just accidentally kicked a thermos
when I got up in the night.
I got a little burned.
The doctor already treated it.
Don't worry.
But how could you just
happen to kick a thermos?
He Jin. You were the last one to go to bed.
And that thermos was yours.
How did it just happen
to be next to Chen Ke's bed?
It was pitch black.
I just put it down wherever.
How would I know
he'd get up in the middle of the night?
Then why didn't you put it somewhere else?
You just had to put it there.
I think you did it on purpose.
- Yu Lei.
- I think you did it on purpose.
- Enough.
- What did Chen Ke ever do to you?
Why would you treat him like this?
Yu Lei. Don't be rash.
It was just an accident.
See? Even Chen Ke says it was an accident.
What are you trying to do?
If you have something to say,
say it to my face.
Pulling these dirty tricks behind my back,
you're asking for a beating.
- Yu Lei, calm down.
- Yu Lei, forget it.
- Calm down.
- Enough.
It's so late. Stop making a scene.
The patient needs to rest.
Everyone, go back to your dorms.
You can come back
during visiting hours tomorrow.
Okay. Thank you, doctor.
Let's go. Go.
Today's the day the baseball team leaves.
It's also my birthday.
But I'm stuck in this hospital room alone.
I thought I'd be celebrating with Yu Lei.
Looks like I'll be spending it by myself.
Senior.
What are you doing here?
It must be boring being in the hospital.
I heard it's your birthday today.
I brought this for you.
Maybe it'll cheer you up.
Senior, you really shouldn't have.
You're injured, so don't move.
Actually, I was going to ask you
to help us out,
and play in the next
school orchestra concert.
But seeing you like this,
you should just focus on getting better.
I'll figure something else out.
It's okay.
I'll be sitting down for
the performance anyway, so it's no big deal.
That's true.
Ke Ke, happy birth...
Sis.
Lei Lei.
Yu Lei.
Aren't you supposed to be with
the baseball team for the game today?
You're still in the hospital.
How could I leave for the game
with a clear conscience?
I was worried you'd be lonely
spending your birthday in the hospital.
I didn't expect you to be here too, Sis.
Looks like we had the same idea.
That's great.
Now we have two cakes.
Then let's have the birthday boy
cut the cake and blow out the candles.
What are you waiting for?
Let's sing the birthday song.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Chen Ke ♪
Happy birthday.
I'll do it.
You're still a patient.
My hands aren't injured.
Stop fighting. Just let Lei Lei do it.
Birthday boy.
Here, Sis.
Thanks, Lei Lei.
I'm going to the restroom.
- Let me help you.
- I'll do it.
Sis. I'll do it.
Careful.
What are you doing?
Ke Ke, you said you needed the restroom.
I'm here to help you.
My foot is injured, not my hands.
Okay.
By the way, Yu Lei.
You don't seem very happy today.
Really?
I don't think so.
It's your birthday. Why wouldn't I be happy?
I can tell whether you're happy or not.
I was hoping we could celebrate alone.
Your cousin isn't a stranger.
Right, right.
Not a stranger.
Maybe she'll be family someday.
Yu Lei.
Lei Lei, Chen Ke, I'm leaving now.
I'll leave the cake here.
- You two can finish it.
- I'll walk my cousin out.
Lei Lei.
If you have something to say, just say it.
Following me quietly like this
is kind of creepy.
It's nothing.
It's just...
It's just that...
I...
Why are you stammering?
You're not usually like this.
Sis.
What's going on between you and Chen Ke?
What do you think is going on?
Sis, just tell me straight.
Do you like Chen Ke?
I can't tell you that.
It's a secret.
No way.
You're my cousin. He's my friend.
- You two...
- It's the 21st century.
If two people are really in love,
height is no barrier, age is not a problem,
and even gender...
No, it's not okay.
I won't allow it.
Yu Lei, you already picked me up
from the hospital.
I can handle the rest myself.
It's fine.
Didn't the doctor say
your injury hasn't fully healed?
You still need to change the dressing
and rest.
I'll do everything for you,
so you can get more rest.
Okay. It's clean enough.
You should get to class.
You don't have to stay here
just to keep me company.
It's fine.
A few people promised to take notes for me.
If I were you,
I'd just take a leave of absence and go home.
Right. I forgot.
You're so popular.
I shouldn't worry about things like that.
But don't you worry about my business either.
I know what I'm doing.
You're not so unpopular yourself.
Look how nice my cousin is to you.
Don't you two have your own little secrets?
You're right.
Your business is none of my business.
What little secrets do I have
with your cousin?
And to think I trusted you before.
I thought you didn't have feelings for her.
But now, you two are practically in love.
Then where does that leave me?
What are you talking about?
She and I barely said a few words
to each other this semester.
What makes you think we're into each other?
Besides, she's such a straightforward person.
If there really was something going on
between us,
do you really think she'd hide it from you?
Well... T-Then just don't worry about it.
Actually, she did talk to me a few days ago.
The school orchestra has a big performance
in June.
They're short-staffed,
so she asked me to help out.
But how is that some big secret?
Well, something like that...
Y-You never told me about it.
I just didn't want to owe her a favor.
It's that simple.
It's not that complicated.
So you're saying I'm overthinking it?
That I'm the one making things complicated?
Yu Lei. That's not what I meant.
That's exactly what you meant.
Aren't you always running around,
busy with all sorts of things?
Everyone's always around you,
flocking to you.
They all think you're so capable.
You said we were twin stars.
I only see you as my best friend.
But you?
You can so easily make all kinds of friends.
So shouldn't I be busy with my own things?
But you still should have told me!
I'm not that petty.
If you really care that much,
I'll cut off ties
with all my friends right now,
and make my world revolve only around you.
Would that make you happy?
Yu Lei.
If you really cared,
you should understand me.
You would trust me,
and know what I would do
and what I wouldn't do.
I...
Well... Cai Tian Yu and the others
brought you back a souvenir
from the competition.
I've put it over there for you.
Let's just not fight, okay?
Yu Lei.
I never wanted to fight with you.
Weren't you the one who started it?
Fine.
Then just go do your own thing.
Mr. Meng, what are you doing here?
These past few days,
I've often come to the office.
You've been practicing in the piano room.
I can hear you every day, you know.
Mr. Meng, have I been disturbing you?
Not at all.
Didn't I tell you before?
I love hearing you play.
It's almost noon.
You haven't had lunch, have you?
Want to have some with me?
Oh... I couldn't possibly.
It's okay.
This is just a little sandwich
I brought for myself.
Besides, for listening to you play,
I should offer our little pianist
some kind of compensation.
Gosh.
The tag-along is here again.
Why are you here every day lately?
Don't you get tired of it?
Brother Yu Lei asked me to hang out.
Besides, this isn't just your dorm room.
Why are you so nosy?
What's with you, are you an exhibitionist?
Taking your shirt off just like that,
without any warning?
It stinks! It stinks!
What?
It's not like you're the only one here.
Yu Lei didn't say anything.
Besides,
have you never seen a shirtless guy before?
If not, take a good look.
Take a good look!
Alright, you two, stop fighting.
Why do you bicker
every time you see each other?
Are you two betta fish or something?
Look at you.
You're built like a stick.
No wonder you're always clinging to people.
God, how annoying can a person be.
I have muscles too, you know.
Oh, really?
Let me see. Where are the muscles?
Let me see where the muscles are.
Let me see, let me see.
- Yu Lei!
- Oh, my God!
- Yu Lei.
- She saw everything!
Sis!
How can you walk into a guys' dorm
just like that?
Never you mind. Come on.
We need to talk.
Where are we going?
- Hey. What's wrong?
- Mind your own business.
Chen Ke, it's not my place to pry, but...
The kind of piano you play now
is not quite the same as before.
What's wrong?
Is something on your mind?
Actually, rather than practicing
for the performance,
the truth is,
I was just trying to avoid Yu Lei.
You two used to be thick as thieves,
and joined at the hip.
What happened?
Did you have a fight?
Yes.
But I still don't understand
how things between us ended up like this.
Silly child.
Since you two were so close,
it means you're drawn to each other.
Seeing you so troubled now,
that just means you really
don't want to lose such a good friend.
Between people,
a little friction and misunderstanding
is a common thing.
It's like a machine.
It needs a break-in period
and a little lubricant.
Otherwise, if you leave it for too long,
it will rust.
Right?
Mr. Meng, everything you're saying is right.
I know all that.
But maybe relationships between people
are just too complicated.
I don't know what counts as
working things out,
and what counts as crossing a line.
Maybe for me, solving problems on paper
is just simpler.
Young man, I can tell you're a child
who seeks purity.
But absolute light is the same as
absolute darkness.
You can't see anything when you're in it.
Only by seeing the imperfections
are we motivated to more actively
pursue what is good.
So-called best friends
also have their sharp disagreements,
their moments of distrust,
their possessiveness,
and their jealousy.
These things are all very normal.
Mr. Meng, are you saying that...
The closer people are,
the more they want to hear
each other's true feelings.
This kind of guessing game,
it inevitably leads you to assume the worst.
Now that the most heated moment has passed,
why don't you both try to
communicate a little more.
Once you've calmed down,
you can better understand
what the other is thinking.
But I already said what I said.
If I go to him now, is it too late?
As long as you're both still alive,
it's never too late.
If you still care about each other,
why not be the one to reach out?
Lei Lei.
I was just messing with you before.
Chen Ke and I are just friends, that's all.
I can apologize.
I shouldn't have joked like that.
But Lei Lei,
can you tell me
what's going on between you two?
Why this sudden cold shoulder?
I don't mind.
And I'm not giving him the cold shoulder.
Lei Lei.
When you were little,
you used to tell me everything.
I know you're grown up now.
You're an adult.
And I get that you have
your own private thoughts.
But what's really going on?
I thought you really liked Chen Ke.
Sis.
Why are you always taking his side?
You're totally biased.
Listen to yourself.
I'm your cousin.
He's your friend.
What is there to be jealous about?
Yeah. Who am I even jealous of?
Looking at the jacket Yu Lei left behind,
I felt like I was making
a mountain out of a molehill.
The truth is, there was never this huge wall
between us, was there?
All it would take is one step forward,
and a few simple words.
I've been so foolish.
Yu Lei, it feels like we haven't
really talked in a while.
The thing is,
there's a lot I want to tell you.
Lei Lei.
Can we just talk calmly, for once?
Please?
Okay.
I'll wait for you.
See you back at the dorm.
Wow, I never would've guessed.
Your Xiao Ming is pretty progressive.
What's it to you?
You're just jealous.
I have a girlfriend and you don't.
Jealous of what?
You're just a broke, ugly, horny gorilla.
Hey, you little...
Never mind. You guys keep talking.
I'm going to head back.
Chen Ke.
- Yu Lei.
- Wait.
They're having a conversation.
Why are you sticking your nose in it?
It's none of your business.
I...
Here. Careful, it's hot.
Thanks.
Your... How's your leg?
It healed a long time ago.
That jerk He Jin.
He did this to you on purpose.
We can't just let him get away with it.
It's okay.
There's no solid proof it was him anyway.
With people like that,
it's best to just stay away.
Are we really just going to let it go?
Yeah.
There's no need to waste energy
on people who don't matter.
Chen Ke.
When we talk about "caring",
are we talking about the same thing?
Yu Lei! Yu Lei, help me!
Li Ming's about to hit me!
Alright, that's enough!
Both of you, stop fighting.
It's all your fault.
Ouyang.
Can you turn your game down a little?
It's making it hard for Chen Ke to practice.
Okay.
Want any?
If you're bored,
you can head back to the dorm.
Not at all. I... I'm fine.
You just focus on your playing.
Don't worry about me.
Yu Lei. What are you two doing?
Where did you come from?
We're just taking a walk.
You two are taking a walk without me?
How about we all go play soccer?
They say the more the merrier, right?
But with Ouyang Han around,
I can't help but feel like
I'm the third wheel.
I think I just want to be with Yu Lei.
Is that too much to ask?
Thanks.
Here. Have this.
I-I'll do it myself.
Tomorrow's Yu Lei's birthday.
Should we do something to celebrate?
Tomorrow's June 1st.
Want to grab dinner together tomorrow night?
[Victoria Italian Restaurant]
You shouldn't have brought anything.
Just you coming here is enough.
Isn't it your birthday?
Yu Lei. Happy Birthday.
Thanks.
I was starting to think
you were so lost in the world of art,
that you'd forgotten all about my birthday.
How could I forget something like that?
By the way, today,
it's just the two of us, right?
Of course.
Yu Lei!
I can't believe you.
You invited Chen Ke but not me?
We're all friends.
Why are you playing favorites?
That's so not cool.
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm not playing favorites.
Exactly. We're all good friends.
Come on, let's go eat.
I'm starving.
Make a wish.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Alright. Let's eat.
Come on, let's eat.
L-Let me tell you guys.
Last winter break,
my family was planning a trip.
My mom said she wanted to go to the beach,
and my dad said he wanted to go hiking.
They couldn't agree, right?
So we ended up never going.
It dragged on until
I had to go back to school.
And then, somehow,
the whole thing got blamed on me.
They said it was because I was indecisive
that we didn't go.
- This is ridiculous.
- No, not at all.
I think your parents
have a great relationship.
Last time I was at your house,
I saw how loving your parents were.
What?
Do you go to Yu Lei's house often?
Yeah.
No, actually, he's just shameless
and insists on coming over.
You're talking nonsense.
I think your parents really like me.
Yu Lei. Didn't you say last time
that your parents saw our picture
from the old town,
and were suspicious about our relationship?
But to be fair,
I think your parents are pretty open-minded.
They said that whether Yu Lei
likes boys or girls,
they don't mind.
What's important is that Yu Lei is happy.
Enough.
- It's not as dramatic as you describe.
- Yes, it is.
Actually, my dad just saw him
coming over a lot,
and was just casually joking.
That's not it.
Give it a rest.
I can't even get a word in.
Actually, it's your birthday today.
You two should celebrate alone.
You'd be happier that way.
I was being inconsiderate.
Sorry about that.
I have something to do.
I'm leaving first.
Then we won't see you out.
Take care then. Bye-bye.
Let's eat.
June 1, 2001.
Rainy.
Getting close to the sun will get you burned.
I wanted to be the only one,
but I only made a fool of myself.
It's better to retreat
into a night of solitude.
Isn't this the kind of night I wanted?
Ke Ke. Ke Ke.
Are you there?
- Ke Ke.
- Enough already.
If you keep knocking,
security is going to show up.
This is crazy.
I've checked all the places he usually goes.
He's nowhere to be found.
I'm telling you,
he's doing this on purpose to upset you.
Ouyang Han.
Can you just be quiet for a second?
Where are you going now?
We can't find him anywhere.
His phone is turned off.
What should we do?
I have to go look for him again.
If I still can't find him,
I'm calling the police.
Ouyang Han.
If you don't want to come with me,
then just go home.
Stop causing trouble here, okay?
Chen Ke, Chen Ke.
All you ever think about is Chen Ke.
Can't you just open your eyes and see me?
S-See you?
What do you mean?
What do I mean?
Exactly what it sounds like.
What kind of time is this to be acting crazy?
How am I acting crazy?
Can't you tell that I like you?
I've liked you for a long time.
But you don't even see me.
Every day, you talk to me about Chen Ke.
But he doesn't feel
that way about you at all.
Can't you just open your eyes and see me?
Let me take his place in your heart.
Let me tell you something, Ouyang Han.
I can see you as a friend,
as a little brother,
but never as a lover.
Yu Lei.
Gorilla.
I'm out. Get me another one.
Who do you think you are, ordering me around?
I think we're done.
Stop drinking.
If you won't go... if you won't go, I will.
Slow down, slow down.
Hey. Go where? What are you talking about?
You're the one who insisted
on not going back to the dorm.
I was nice enough to get a room
to take you in.
Don't push your luck.
You hear me?
What's wrong?
- Are you crying?
- No.
There aren't even any tears.
Seriously.
Alright, alright. That's enough.
A real man doesn't cry easily.
Do you know what the next line is?
It's "only because the pain
hasn't hit him yet".
How did an uncultured idiot like you
get into Mingde University?
I...
Alright.
If you want to cry, just let it out.
Have a good cry.
Why should I do what you say?
Well...
if something's bothering you,
you have to talk about it.
If you keep it bottled up inside,
it'll just make you more miserable.
How would a gorilla like you understand?
I... What's wrong with me?
You want to cry?
I want to cry, too.
What's wrong with you?
Forget it.
It doesn't matter if I tell you.
It's just that...
Meng Yu broke up with me today.
She said I wasn't considerate enough.
That I didn't care about her enough.
I just don't get it.
I mean, what did I do to her?
Do I have to act like the male lead
in a romance drama
for things to work?
You?
What about me?
Do you know what it feels like
to pour your heart out and love someone?
to try everything you can,
just to get someone's attention?
Do you know what it feels like
when the person you adore
only has eyes for someone else?
You don't get it.
You don't get it at all.
S-So, you're the one who gets it?
- I do.
- As if you've ever really loved anyone.
I get it now.
You like Yu Lei, don't you?
You...
How did you know?
Even I can tell.
Yu Lei likes his Chen Ke.
You don't have a chance.
Li Ming, you...
I hit the nail on the head, didn't I?
Let me ask you something.
The way you dress up every day,
is it to imitate Chen Ke?
No, I'm not.
You're not?
Then why do you try to get close
to Yu Lei every day?
Is it to push Chen Ke away?
I'm not.
I just... I...
Go ahead and laugh if you want to.
Look.
Actually, the way you were before,
even though you were a bit of a pain,
you were pretty good.
You just need to be
the number one Ouyang Han.
Why do you have to be a second-rate Chen Ke?
If I'm the number one Ouyang Han,
will someone like me?
Of course, they will. What are you thinking?
Be more confident.
You talk big.
But you're scared to death when I kiss you.
So pathetic.
Who are you calling pathetic?
You wanna bet I'll take you right now?
[Next episode]
I just got a call from my mom.
She said... my dad suddenly collapsed.
I'm going to ask my advisor
for a leave of absence.
I'll book the next flight home.
But we've got final exams right now!
I can't worry about that now.
If I let you go alone,
how could I possibly rest easy?
I'm booking tickets for both of us right now.
Both of us?
I've made up my mind.
I'm skipping the exams too.
I'm going back with you.