QUEEN OF TEARS
Tell me this isn't true.
DIVORCE SETTLEMENT AGREEMENT
Say it.
Deny it.
- Hae-in...
- Say it.
Tell me it's not true.
Tell me it wasn't you.
No.
It was me.
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you.
When?
When…
When did you prepare this?
I have…
something to say.
Was it
that day?
The day I told you I was dying?
Yes.
Is that why
you kept
your mouth shut
and didn't tell me?
Because I was going to die soon anyway?
Yes.
So…
you lied all along?
What's wrong?
You've lied through your teeth.
So what's stopping you now?
I found it…
on my way here.
Our lock is still here.
Hae-in.
It's too late to go anywhere.
Stay here. I'll go.
Just…
let me be.
I don't even have
the energy to get mad.
Just hear me out.
I'll tell you why I did that,
what I was feeling,
and what my plan was.
No, forget it.
I'm not curious.
I love you, Hong Hae-in.
I love you.
Are you okay?
What are you doing here?
Don't you know you should be more careful?
Let's go inside.
I'll explain everything.
And then,
I'll do as you say.
- So...
- Hyun-woo.
If this ever happens again,
don't save me.
I'm so shocked.
Hyun-woo was normal.
What do you mean?
I thought he'd been out of his mind lately
since he seemed to truly love Hae-in.
But he was just like any other guy.
I was surprised too.
Who knew he was planning
to divorce her in secret?
- I wonder when it all began.
- What?
Someone must've encouraged him.
I've been suspecting someone too.
Who?
My aunt.
I see.
What?
She's been getting in my way
and talking nonsense lately
about Hyun-woo
being more handsome than me.
Recently, it seemed like
those two were sharing a secret.
I saw them last time.
The biggest priority of this business…
- What's going on?
- So why didn't you go?
Why did she go alone?
Why did you let her go alone?
- Send who alone?
- Why?
What? Why is she crying?
They were having a serious talk in secret.
Really?
I wonder what it's about.
Where are you going?
The treatment fell through, so what?
What he means is that we need time.
Let's go back to Korea,
raise your WBC, then return...
You're despicable.
I know you're happy that I'm dying
and have given up everything.
You've given up everything?
So you won't bother trying anymore?
What about a lawsuit?
I'd be grateful if you divorced me
without filing a suit.
- What?
- You know everything now.
So?
You wouldn't let me go that easily.
It was unbearable to live with you anyway.
Don't act like you had no idea, Hae-in.
You know what kind of person you are.
No wonder I chose to do so.
I could've lived
a comfortable and wealthy life,
so why did I want to run away?
Because I hated living with you
more than anything!
Hey.
- Baek Hyun-woo.
- Yes, you're right.
I'll be honest.
When I heard that you'd be dying soon,
I was relieved deep down.
We'd have a clean divorce
if I put up with you
for the next three months.
But I got caught.
Everything's ruined.
So if you choose
not to take any action at all
and just divorce me,
then honestly,
I'd be grateful.
Will you do that?
What should I do?
Should I pack up and leave once we return?
Or…
If I continue to grovel at your feet,
will you revise your will?
Are you sure you can handle this?
Do you think you can handle my rage?
Then bring it on!
What will you do?
Do something if you can!
Mr. Song has gone through
his first round of interrogations,
but our attorneys doubt
that the prosecution will stop here.
If that's how
the prosecution will proceed,
then it'll only be a matter of time
until they summon you.
Look at this mess we're in
thanks to Hyun-woo.
I'm worried about them summoning you.
You need to take your medications on time.
Then you can go instead.
- Sorry?
- What's wrong?
I was behind bars for ten months
when I was Soo-cheol's age.
Gosh.
If only I was as young as Soo-cheol.
Why are you looking at me?
This is an experience
that you can't even buy with money.
I'm not interested.
If you appear in his stead,
people will think you're the heir.
But if you don't,
they'll think you're terrible.
I have a family to protect.
And so do I.
Yes, that's me. You should protect me.
What are you saying?
Be quiet!
The problem is that we have
an important investment deal coming up.
If the investors find out,
the deal might fall through.
He's right, sir.
We should hasten the deal.
We have a whole feast
prepared in front of us
that could be taken by Chairman Yeom.
The reporters
will find out sooner or later.
Mr. Yoon will opt out immediately then.
And that's what Chairman Yeom wants.
First, we need to secure the deal.
Grandfather!
QUEENS MART ENTERS NEW RESORT BUSINESS
Once the construction begins,
we'll insinuate the licensing issue
related to altitude restrictions
to the investors.
Then the investors and stock firms
who gave out loans
will choose the pre-payment option.
Soo-cheol, that coward, will be shocked.
He might even cry.
That's when I'll offer
to invest the amount
that the investors have pulled out
and suggest convertible bonds.
And this is when
the prosecution will investigate?
Correct.
Once the embezzlement news gets out
and the Hong family goes to jail,
I'll use the convertible bonds
to purchase Queens' stocks.
Then I'll combine that with the 4.9%
that I previously purchased
and become the biggest shareholder.
Everything is panning out.
Even Hyun-woo is out of the picture now.
Who knew we'd find
the divorce papers at this perfect timing?
Did Hyun-woo admit to it?
Did he sign the divorce papers?
Why bother asking? Of course, it was him.
How could he do this?
Why do you even wonder?
They should just divorce.
He bugged your room
and gave the tapes to the prosecution.
But I can look past them.
Why would you?
Our family is awfully tolerant
of their parents' sufferings.
One thing I don't understand
is that the scumbag
wanted to divorce her first.
That's the one thing I understand.
I'm sure there's someone.
Perhaps, a mistress.
- Father, I'll look into it.
- No.
- The Audit Team will.
- They will?
He'll leave Queens after the divorce.
I need to find out before then.
I'll look through his computer,
financial documents, phone, and account.
I'll track his funds.
I'll find out whom he met
and what he's been up to.
The moment I find
any embezzlement or illegal act,
I will report him
and file a claim for damages.
- You'll go that far?
- Yes, I will.
I'll take care of it,
so please don't get in the way.
She sure is merciless.
I said I'd pick you up at the airport.
Are you okay?
Hey, are you hurt?
Can you hear me?
Your eardrums can pop when you get beaten.
It happens to many of my clients.
Can you hear me?
That's enough.
So you're okay. You're fine.
Gosh. Well done.
Come here. Let me give you a hug.
You should've feigned innocence
since you were acting anyway.
"The divorce papers are nothing.
I was just practicing
to become a divorce attorney."
Couldn't you have improvised?
She must be livid.
I bet she's even more terrifying now.
I bet you're dispirited.
AVAILABLE FOR MONTHLY RENT
You worked so hard
pretending to be in love.
You must feel hopeless now.
You're wrong.
- What do you mean?
- She wasn't mad.
- No?
- No.
And I don't feel hopeless.
- I'm upset.
- Hey.
You're in no position to feel that way.
Hae-in cried.
She did.
And it drove me insane
seeing her crying.
What in the world…
did I do to her?
What's with him?
I thought he couldn't stand
being next to her.
Does he have feelings for her or what?
So what's your next move?
- What move?
- Do you have no plan?
She's probably planning something.
Of course, she is.
You upset her big time,
so I bet she's thinking of the best way
to take revenge.
Exactly.
- She should.
- What do you mean?
She needs that motivation.
She needs to focus on something.
So you purposely let her focus
on ruining your life?
Are you a sacrifice?
Are you a soldier
running into a losing battle?
If this ever happens again,
don't save me.
This is the only way she'll live.
Hyun-woo.
Why did you do it?
I'm on my way to see your grandfather.
Let's talk later.
It'll be me anyway.
- What do you mean?
- Try all you want.
But the heir will always be me!
Do you still not get it?
Were you that jealous of me
that you'd bug his room?
Did you want to know
all the conversations that we were having?
No, I didn't.
- I didn't bug his room.
- I get it.
Get what?
I knew you were up to something
when you put up
with everything Hae-in did.
But what now? You got caught.
I was planning to give you something
once this resort deal became a success.
"I should set up a branch
in Yufuin or Cancún
and send him there.
No, Yufuin is too near.
Hae-in would just need to fly an hour.
He should go to Cancún
if he wants freedom."
That's how much I cared about you.
What?
You need to halt the resort construction.
The consulting firm
that Mr. Yoon introduced
predicted an annual profit of 500 billion,
but the actual figure was 89 billion won.
That's less than 20%. Isn't that odd?
You signed the contract
even before the validity test...
You're trying to get in the way again!
Stop worrying about my success.
Don't forget! It'll be me!
I'm sorry for worrying you.
Okay, do explain.
Why did you hide the divorce papers?
Were you going to surprise us
with it later on?
Is that why you've been nitpicking
my words and disobeying me?
Just because of those papers?
Sir, the chairman wants to see you.
Okay.
Please leave all your electronics outside.
Yes, do so.
You could be recording even now.
Come in.
What did Chairman Yeom promise you?
- Sorry?
- The divorce.
I couldn't care less about it.
You chose to ruin your luck.
I'm sorry.
But if you bugged my room
and Chairman Yeom handed it over
to the prosecution,
I won't allow that.
Did you scheme
Mr. Song's embezzlement too?
Were you targeting me?
It's true that the embezzlement
was targeted at you.
Are you playing smart with me?
I'm asking if you were behind it!
Director Jo Hyeon-myeong approved
Mr. Song's embezzlement files.
The man next to him has been in charge
of Queens' external audit.
He's Hwang Byeong-u
who has his own accounting firm.
- They went to the same university.
- So what?
He's been doing yearly audits,
so it's odd
that he found no issues until now.
Has his accounting firm
truly been unaware of Mr. Song's
embezzlement for the past five years?
So you're telling me
that Jo Hyeon-myeong schemed with his firm
and turned a blind eye
to the embezzlement?
So that I'd be investigated?
No, sir.
Director Jo didn't do this alone.
Someone ordered him.
I believe that individual bugged your room
and planted the transmitter in mine.
And who is this person?
I haven't found out yet.
What?
You're not even sure,
yet you want me to believe you
after what you did to my granddaughter?
Do you?
Director Jo.
You should hurry.
Why? Because Baek Hyun-woo is after you.
ESTIMATED ASSETS
2,386,690
Are you doing stocks again?
The market is a mess.
It doesn't matter how blue it gets
as long as my baby is red.
QUEENS DEPARTMENT STORE
- It's red.
- What is it?
- Who's your baby?
- No.
- Come on. Tell me.
No!
Stop that!
Are you crazy?
You bought Queens' stocks?
Mom will kill me, so be quiet!
Why would you buy them?
I had them in the past, but I sold them.
- When?
- When Hyun-woo mentioned the divorce.
I couldn't ignore the owner's risk.
Nothing good would've come out
of the media mentioning their divorce.
How sly of you.
Then you bought them again
when Hyun-woo decided not to divorce?
Right. Check this out.
- It's going up, right?
- Jeez.
Mom.
It's unlike you to take a nap.
I had a bad dream.
- Gosh.
- What was it about?
It was ambiguous.
What was it?
Maybe it was a conception dream.
Hyun-woo's a dad?
It wasn't anything cute like that.
MOM
- Hello?
Isn't this Mr. Baek Hyun-woo's phone?
Yes, it is.
I'm Hae-in's mother.
Hello, Ms. Kim. How have you been?
I guess Hyun-woo left his phone behind.
- But why are you...
- Yes.
He's speaking with my father-in-law.
I don't know if you know,
but Hyun-woo
turned our family upside down.
What? What happened?
My father-in-law's room was bugged…
Forget it.
Did you know Hyun-woo wanted a divorce?
He did mention it before.
But it's normal for a married couple
to go through rough patches.
I thought they had resolved it.
She knows about the divorce.
Look…
You should hear them out first.
You told me not to get in their way
on the day they got married.
But you see,
I will make sure they part ways.
So don't get in my way.
Mom, what did she say?
What do I do?
Goodness. What do I do?
Unbelievable.
Mom.
It must be a mess.
What if he really gets a divorce?
You bastard.
SELL
YOUR ORDER IS COMPLETE
I sold them.
It's nothing complicated.
Just do what they did with the apples.
Ms. Hong can take a bite
of your pear and say,
"Gosh, that's sweet."
That's all she needs to do.
I should ask her for help again?
She was supposed to help us.
They're the ones who took advantage of it.
What's your take on this?
It's already incredible
that she made time
to come down here and flex.
And you want to ask her for help again?
It won't be easy.
- Exactly.
- You'll lose face.
Right?
Then will you let
Park Seok-hun take everything?
You're always so extreme.
Are you an INFP?
What do you mean? I'm Park Chun-sik.
I'm talking about your goals.
Will you do anything to reach them?
Or does the process matter more?
INFP or ENFJ.
In that case…
I'm an INFP.
Then feed her some pears
and tell her to comment on it.
First, we need to remove
the video of her eating the apple.
If you don't want enemies
stealing your food,
- don't set the table in front of them.
- That does make sense.
Dad, why haven't you been picking up?
It's out of battery. I'm glad you're here.
Take down that video of Hae-in
eating the apple.
I already have.
That's not the issue. I have bad news.
What is it?
Gosh.
You'll all find out eventually.
Hyun-woo…
Goodness. What do we do?
They're getting a divorce?
Hyeon-tae, do you have any anxiety pills?
- Of course not.
- That's not the problem.
He should overcome it.
Damn it!
Is this entertaining for you?
You see, I'd like to use Dr. Oh's solution
in this situation.
It was Episode 58,
the one with Nancy Lang.
Dr. Oh mentioned three steps
to overcome hardships in life.
- I saw it but forgot.
- Step one.
Acknowledgement.
Accurately assess the current crisis.
Did they hand in the divorce papers?
I don't think so.
Step two. Self-awareness.
Find out how bad the situation is
and how much worse it could get.
Were there any articles or tabloids?
Not yet. But it'll only be
a matter of time, right?
Of course.
And lastly, sorting it out.
Decide what you'll give up on
and what you'll keep. Then act on it.
Who cares about the election anymore?
Forget it.
- Where are you going?
- Where's your mom?
She just left.
I don't know where she went.
Did you have to mention
the election right now?
Sorry.
I'm an INTP.
YONGDU-RI SUPERMARKET
What is he talking about?
Hyun-woo's mom knew everything
and lied to us.
How dare they upload that video
of Hae-in when she knew nothing?
Calm down.
Be calm as her mom.
Imagine how Hae-in must feel.
Seon-hwa!
What's going on?
Did Hyun-woo really do that?
You were always defending him.
What did I tell you?
You're such a poor judge of character.
No wonder you're always betrayed.
Don't blame me.
You'll always be duped
if someone is determined to trick you.
Why shouldn't I tell anyone?
That bitch has been deceiving us
for over 20 years!
Exactly.
That just proves how savage she is.
If you don't have proof,
she'll just deny it
and turn you into a fool.
Let's be patient. She has a son,
so she must be sending him money.
Let's find him first.
In the meantime,
keep your temper under control.
You must.
I wouldn't be able to relate
since I'm not a mom.
But then again,
I guess the same goes for you.
You don't need to be a mom to relate.
I can imagine how she must feel.
Still, think twice about the divorce.
I know times have changed,
but Hae-in will suffer
more than him if they divorce.
Take her for example.
Why are you looking at me?
Unlike her ex-husbands
who have all happily remarried,
Beom-ja is still single.
What do you mean?
I remarried right away too.
And you divorced just as quickly.
Seon-hwa, that's not
the problem right now.
Where's Hae-in? What's she doing?
Gosh, she's already struggling as is.
She's already struggling?
Is something going on with her?
No.
She's just a workaholic.
She needs to take a breather. Damn it.
Jeez.
What is she saying?
There. I signed it too.
But it's up to me
when I'll submit it and how.
Okay.
I can finally understand why
my aunt beat her ex-husbands
to a pulp before the divorce.
I'll hire much more competent attorneys
than she did.
You won't leave this house unscathed.
You will be kicked out mercilessly.
Okay.
I get it.
But please keep your distance
from Yoon Eun-sung.
What's it to you?
He was out of touch for a long time
then suddenly appeared.
Then he gifted Soo-cheol and you
a hefty investment
and the Hercyna deal.
He must have a motive.
- He's suspicious too.
- How so?
There was dashcam footage
of the hunting ground incident.
I gave the SD card
to a data restoring company.
Mr. Yoon visited them,
and the owner has disappeared.
So? How does that prove anything?
He could've simply been another client.
And even if he has
something up his sleeve,
he won't fool me that easily.
But I did.
Just don't make the same mistake.
We've prepared pine mushroom porridge
for breakfast.
- Would you like some?
- No.
I want beef.
Ms. Hong's diamond necklace blinded me.
We have a peacock at large.
- Brace yourselves.
- Yes, ma'am.
I'm sorry, but what peacock?
Right. You're a newbie here.
How did Ms. Hong look?
Gorgeous.
That's true.
Okay, just remember this.
The more upset she is,
the fancier she dresses.
She looked like a fabulous peacock today.
It means we're all dead meat.
Then what should we do?
There's…
no solution.
Natural disasters and Ms. Hong's moodiness
are two things humans can't control.
Gosh, I'm sorry!
I'll reprint these documents and...
It's okay.
Sorry?
What did you…
It's okay.
It's not a life-or-death situation.
Don't feel so bad about spilling.
It's okay. You may go.
Ms. Hong, are you very upset?
No, I have something
that enrages me much more.
This is nothing.
Look.
Even this sloppy report
doesn't enrage me.
She was so terrifying even when not mad.
I wonder what she's enraged about.
We're from the Audit Team.
We're conducting an investigation
after receiving a report
on the illegal use of expenses.
Please stand up.
Do not shred any documents.
Do not destroy or move anything.
Gosh, this is total bloodshed.
Has the Hong-Baek Battle begun once again?
This will be a disaster.
Let's go.
- All of them?
- Yes.
- You're going to reject them?
But you already confirmed them
before going to Germany.
I know.
- All of them?
- Yes.
She rejected them all.
It usually lasts a week.
The duration isn't the problem
this time around.
The intensity is on another level.
What in the world happened in Germany?
Let's share their schedules.
Don't let them run into each other.
What? The lunch meeting.
We're having sushi at J Hotel too.
Change it. I'll follow
your schedule for the elevator rides.
Okay.
BAEK HYUN-WOO
QUEENS DEPARTMENT STORE INC.
"We have already reviewed the contracts
for the soon-to-be-closed stores,
so you can proceed.
We have already discussed this,
so you cannot change it.
You'll have to pay triple
the penalty fee if you do.
Please approve it so we can proceed.
Goodbye then."
That's what he said.
"The Legal Team can take care
of penalty issues. I can't approve this.
Shouldn't you have come up
with different scenarios
regarding the possible issues,
run simulations,
and then reported them to me? Again."
That's what she said.
- How feisty.
- Sorry?
Never mind.
Aren't we having sushi at J Hotel today?
Let's go.
How about the Chinese restaurant instead?
Why?
It'd cost a lot for all of us
to have sushi omakase.
It's okay. It's my treat.
I know how hard you've been working.
Let's just have Chinese, sir.
Their sweet
and sour pork lunch set is delicious.
Why all of a sudden?
Is there another reason?
No, not at all.
They all prefer to have Chinese instead.
What's with Mr. Kim's face?
He's going to kill us if we choose sushi.
I bet it's because Ms. Hong
is going there.
I think Mr. Baek caught onto it.
I thought he loved jajangmyeon.
This is entertaining.
I don't care what we have.
I just want to watch the rich argue.
ME TOO
The Owl has switched to Chinese.
Okay. The Eagle is headed
to the elevator in Building A.
The Owl is headed to Building B.
It's running late. Let's go to Building B.
But it'll be here soon.
The Eagle has changed course.
Approaching Building B in three minutes.
Should we walk instead?
- It's very healthy to take the stairs.
- Not if you're going down.
Emergency.
Ms. Hong is coming this way! Help!
I'm in the chatroom too.
I'm sorry.
You guys must be eating out together.
You must not have much to do.
I'm treating them
since they have a lot of work.
Sure.
You should do better.
And while you're at it,
give me an analysis report
on the cases you've repeatedly lost
in the past three years
and find out how to improve.
Yes, ma'am.
But when you review it,
I hope you leave out
any personal feelings you have.
I guess you didn't know.
I'm pretty much an AI
when it comes to work,
so don't worry about that.
Is that so? I didn't know.
That ignorance of yours
is the reason
why you keep losing those cases.
Should we take the stairs?
- Sure.
- Let's go.
Did you read the news?
NSFA's new biotechnology was fabricated?
- We invested in them.
- Did you use your shares as collateral?
It was impossible
to get the money in cash.
I even signed
a foreclosure agreement with the bank.
Me too.
What if the bank confiscates our shares?
Can you reach Director Jo?
Gosh, it's sad to see you leave.
- People grow on me so easily.
- Stay healthy.
Your kids will be happy to see you.
Even more so since you're rich now.
I'm starting afresh,
so I'm going to do many good deeds
and help others.
Sure.
The statute of limitations
for financial fraud
of 100 million or more is 25 years.
You can't help others if you're in prison.
So don't get caught.
You bet. I'll stay far away
from Korean marts and restaurants.
I'll live well.
Goodbye then.
What a filthy scumbag.
How is he so brazen after sucking
his long-time colleagues dry?
Goodbye. Go on.
What a dirt bag.
SUNGMIN UNIVERSITY MEDICAL CENTER
BAEK HYUN-WOO
Hae-in.
Contact Sungmin Medical Center.
I need to check something.
Goodness, Mr. Baek.
How have you been? What brings you here?
I had a question.
Do you recognize this watch?
I see.
It's a limited edition
for Ronde de Frédic's 101st anniversary.
- Only 101 of them were made.
- I see.
But this one is preordered.
Do you see this yellow diamond?
This diamond was only added to the dials
of the ten preordered watches.
I know it's a lot to ask,
but may I know
who bought those ten watches?
Sure, I can help you.
You helped my mom resolve
the medical malpractice incident.
I'm close with HQ's team leader.
Don't worry.
Thank you.
I'll turn now.
Look far ahead.
- Slowly.
- Good.
Straighten your back.
Step on the pedal. That's it.
Good, turn. Yes, slowly.
Slowly. That was good.
Turn smoothly.
- Like this?
- Yes, that's right.
- You're doing great.
- Okay.
You're terrific.
Are you really a beginner?
I don't need these extra wheels,
but he kept insisting.
You know him, right?
He's a bronze medalist.
- Yes.
- I should listen to the pro.
Everyone uses
the training wheels at first.
I'd be flying without them.
Watch me.
- I'll go faster.
- Okay, but relax.
Slowly. That's it.
- Like this?
- That's right.
Go in a straight line.
Are you okay?
Goodness, my son! Soo-cheol!
Oh, dear!
You're bleeding!
Why didn't you guys stop him?
Why would they need to?
Can't you see all this dirt and cement?
Why would you ride here? It's dangerous.
- Don't ride this.
- Come on, Mom!
Skateboards, bicycles,
skis, rollerblades, and kick scooters.
I can't ride any of them because of you.
You didn't even let me ride steep slides,
so I've had no experience.
Because you might fall...
Exactly. I've never fallen before.
That's right.
Now, do you understand
how much I doted on you?
Why must you fall?
Mom.
As his dad,
I should at least teach Geon-u
how to ride a bicycle.
So it's just to teach
your son how to ride?
- That's why?
- Yes.
I'm going to teach him
how to ride bicycles,
rollerblades, kick scooters,
skateboards, and skis.
You can just hire someone to teach him.
Why would you
put yourself in danger like that?
Dads are supposed
to teach their kids these things.
I'll begin.
- All right.
- No, Soo-cheol. You'll fall.
- Soo-cheol...
- Mr. Kim, move the car!
- Mom, come on.
- Get off.
Move the car, or I'll crash into it.
Hello?
Hello, this is Kevin from Manhattan.
Hello.
It's about the Upper West Side apartment.
The owner wants to sell it.
That's great.
Then I'll proceed. The contract
will be valid until the end of the month.
Will you be here by then?
You need to sign it yourself.
I'll be there in two weeks.
Ma'am, there's something odd
I found out about Mr. Baek.
What is it?
He kept calling a woman's name
on the rooftop garden.
A woman's name?
Yeong-suk.
Yeong-suk?
Yeong...
Come out if you're here.
Her name is Yeong-suk.
Oh, that?
He keeps telling her to come out.
Forget it.
I recognize that name.
Yes, ma'am.
Did you find anything?
We've been keeping a close eye
on Mr. Baek around the clock lately.
This is what he's been doing every hour.
The places he went to weren't typical.
What has he been up to?
What? "Coin baseball"?
Yes, five balls for five hundred won.
He always goes there after work.
- With whom?
- Alone.
Forget it. Next.
What is "Grandma's Home Cooking"?
They sell home-cooked meals.
He has dinner there every day.
- With whom?
- Alone.
I tried their food for research purposes.
It was delicious. I'd go there alone too.
Why would he act pitifully and eat alone?
He can always eat at home.
What about two days ago?
He came home at midnight.
Right. He enjoyed some pork bulgogi
at Grandma's Home Cooking for dinner,
bought two water bottles
at a convenience store,
and went to an elementary school nearby.
At that hour? Was it a secret rendezvous?
No, he was alone.
- What did he do there by himself?
- He ran.
- He ran?
- Yes.
You know teachers punish their students
by making them do laps.
That's what he was doing.
- What for?
- Beats me.
It's not like he's an athlete,
but he even sang and shouted.
I was a bit spooked.
Would you like to see?
Don't ask me why I'm leaving
I was
Such a fool
What's wrong with him?
I told you, sir. He's not typical.
He met up with a stray cat
on his way home.
He said hello and gave it a snack.
I didn't expect a mistress,
but I did expect to see some tycoons.
Did you do your job properly?
I don't want to brag, but you see…
I'm so competent that I can locate
a target even in North Korea.
That's true. He's very tenacious.
As the legal director of Queens,
his only rendezvous was with a cat?
It's Aeong.
- What is?
- The cat's name.
It's the most ferocious cat
in this neighborhood.
But he named it, and it listens to him.
I also hired a former-CSI hacker
to hack his phone.
There were many photos of Aeong.
Strange, right? We thought the same thing.
What kind of man takes such pretty photos
of his woman whom he wants to divorce?
If you look closely,
this photo makes her legs look long.
This photo requires
a lot of concentration.
- This is true love.
- Totally.
I don't think he has a woman on the side.
This doesn't prove anything.
You've put a tail on him many times.
He knows to behave well
at times like this.
Do you think so?
The numbers will tell.
The audit results will come out soon.
They couldn't find anything at all.
They did a thorough check
from his consultation fee
to the litigation expenses
and found nothing.
I checked his card details and account,
and he surprisingly doesn't spend much.
He just often goes to the car wash.
- But…
- But what?
He'd withdraw millions in cash
every now and then.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Another odd thing is that
he'd always spend 300,000 won
at Moulin Rouge
on the day of his withdrawal.
Moulin Rouge?
- A bar?
- A flower shop.
He spent 300,000 won today
and sent the flowers to a Kim Min-ji.
That's a female name.
- I believe so.
- I see.
So he bought some flowers
and withdrew some cash
before meeting this Kim Min-ji?
Where?
Where is she right now?
KIM MIN-JI
GANGJU-GU, SEOUL
DAUGHTERS
KIM MIN-JI
CEO HONG HAE-IN OF QUEENS DEPARTMENT STORE
Ms. Hong.
Ms. Kim Min-ji?
Deal with our customers only.
The company already helped
with the funeral.
You personally sent us flowers
and gave us a lot of condolence money.
And you even made time to visit.
I don't know how to thank…
I guess Mr. Baek has been sending
condolence flowers under your name.
I'm a bit touched.
I like it.
Like what?
All funeral halls are the same.
But this place is clean and modern.
There aren't just chrysanthemums,
but dahlias and tulips as well.
It brightens up the room.
Are those angels?
Rococo style. I like it.
I also like how they
have halogen lamps here,
but pin lights over her photo.
Are you looking for a funeral hall?
What?
I mean, you're looking around so closely.
I was just looking around.
I see.
It's been a while
since we came to a funeral like this one.
Most of the funerals we go to
rarely have family members
weeping like them.
They're busy consulting
their attorneys or accountants
about their inheritance or gift tax.
Mom…
You're right.
They're genuinely mourning.
Why did you send flowers?
And the condolence money?
Stop playing. You disgust me.
Even if I lose my memory down the road,
I will never forget what you did to me.
You let go of my hand when I was
the most helpless.
I will never forgive you.
Try all you want,
but I will resent you
until my last breath.
So all you need to do
is stay still…
and get lost when I tell you to.
- That was quick.
- Of course, it was.
- What is it?
- It's nothing.
- I don't want to add fuel to the fire.
- No, let me hear it.
What is it?
Did you know that Secretary Kim
and I have become quite close?
We just spoke on the phone.
"How are they doing?
Do you think they reconciled?
Where are they going after work?
Don't let them cross paths."
- That's what secretaries...
- It's not just us.
All the workers are dying too.
They liked it better when you didn't care.
But you've been having
good and bad days lately.
Enough. It's best that I don't hear it.
You made me talk.
Anyway, there's one thing
you can do for us.
- Remaining amicable.
- Enough.
It'd be best if you went on a trip.
- Abroad if possible.
- Aren't you busy?
Of course, I am. I'm your secretary.
You're having dinner with Mr. Yoon.
You're seeing him often.
Isn't it great?
No split levels.
An entry fee of 8% is not bad.
But why does he want Hercyna
to hire their own employees?
That's his rule.
- The workers need to be 27 or younger.
- I know, but why?
He doesn't want old employees
to sell his products.
Unbelievable.
What's so terrible about aging?
It's actually a blessing.
It's great and something to vie for.
It's beautiful.
He's obnoxious.
So will you give up then?
He accepted almost all of our conditions.
"Our"?
Your conditions.
Yes, he accepted my conditions
for your sake.
So tell me.
What do you want?
I know I owe you one.
I feel uneasy
since you're not asking me for a favor.
If it's something I can do right now,
then I'll do it.
- Divorce him.
- What?
Divorce Baek Hyun-woo.
That's what I want.
He was planning to leave you.
Will you still keep him?
That's my business.
You're crossing the line again.
Should I really cross the line this time?
What if I…
replaced him?
I'd be crossing the line
if I really asked you that.
I can't eat.
I can't digest food well
when I'm offended.
He was adopted by a Korean family at 12.
The US may be vast,
but the Korean community is small.
Our new international attorney
used to live in his neighborhood.
They weren't close,
but his family was well-known.
- How so?
- It was soon after he was adopted.
His adoptive parents moved
to a bigger house.
Then they sent him
to the most expensive private school.
Hill Crawford Academy.
The annual tuition costs over $60,000.
But his parents weren't rich.
Can you reach his parents?
I did look into it.
They both passed away.
It was a drunk driving accident.
But people thought it was odd
since neither of them were drinkers.
You shouldn't be here.
How is this place?
It was empty for a long time.
You should go.
I feel reassured to know that my son
is living under the same roof as me.
I told you to leave.
- You need to be more careful, Ms. Moh.
- Don't call me that. Call me Mom.
You told me not to call you that,
so I held myself back all along.
Now, I can't even say it anymore.
Right.
We had quite a past.
But I don't regret it.
Really? When this is your life right now?
She's a housekeeper.
She's been here for a while.
You could say she's like
the head housekeeper
whom Grandfather relies on.
Don't mind her.
She's a nobody.
And over there…
Gosh, that's salty.
Ms. Moh has lost her touch.
Why is this so salty?
That's why
you should kick her out this instant.
I would've done that already
if it was up to me.
- Eat up. The other dishes are fine.
- Okay.
Don't you remember everything you've lost
in the past 30 years?
Of course, I do.
I wanted to keep my son close
and raise him myself.
But if I did, you wouldn't
have gotten nice birthday meals
or brand-new school uniforms.
We would've been dirt-poor.
I would've said,
"We're a family. Hang in there."
"Things will look up soon."
But that wouldn't have happened.
It's a nice house, isn't it?
Chairman Hong is very meticulous.
It took him five years
to build this house,
when it would've taken others one year.
He even chose which stones
to put in the garden.
But soon,
we'll kick them all out
and have this house to ourselves.
Don't think it's unfair.
We're just changing the order of things.
This family had everything
they ever wanted.
They were happy.
And now,
we will take over
and become happy.
You're more careless than I thought.
Do you think it'll be easy?
- I...
- No, there it goes.
Kick the ball to me.
I want to do it too.
It's over there.
Guys, have a drink.
Mommy brought drinks.
- Let's go.
- Can we have it now?
Can we really drink it?
Come here!
Goodness, my princess.
Are you up?
Goodness, you're so pretty.
Goodness.
Beom-jun, be careful.
Guys, look here.
- Carry me.
- Sure.
Chairman Hong enjoyed
his happiness before us,
and he still remembers those times.
We've yet to take them away.
You won't fall.
We shouldn't be
complacent like this.
- What is this?
- Use it however you want.
Where can I possibly use this?
Secretary Jang told me that you'll
be investigated for the secret fund.
Your son or grandson
can't go to prison for you
since they have a lot on their plate.
- So?
- I'll go instead.
Let's say I secretly embezzled
your secret fund
through the scholarship foundation.
I'm neither a board member
nor your family by law.
If I take responsibility, you won't have
to worry about the owner's risk.
Even if the media covers it,
I can take the fall alone.
There's no honor I need to keep,
so it's okay.
I'll be interrogated
and go to prison instead.
Don't you worry.
You're much better
than all my children combined.
Hae-in.
Why are you out in the cold?
Where's your car?
Where is it? Where's Mr. Oh?
I'm not sure.
How did I get here?
I keep finding myself
like this these days.
Time keeps slipping away
when I'm running out of time as is.
What about you?
How did you know I was here?
Did you recognize this umbrella?
Do you remember giving it to me?
I was really dumbfounded back then.
Hae-in.
Don't give me that look.
There's a 51% chance.
I can go to Germany and receive treatment.
Hae-in.
Why do you keep calling me?
Right. You know Ye-na, right?
She got into a car accident two days ago.
She fainted and went to the ER.
Then, her husband…
Then, her husband
and her attorney rushed over.
He caused a scene
and said she had to revise her will.
He was so noisy that she woke up.
Are you crying?
I'm sorry.
About what?
Are you that worried?
Don't you worry.
Baek Hyun-woo.
I love you.
- Her name is Yeong-suk.
- Forget it.
- I recognize that name.
- Yes, ma'am.
That was ages ago.
He's still calling for her?
QUEENS DEPARTMENT STORE
GUIDE MAP
Mr. Baek, did you know?
A raccoon lives on our rooftop garden.
That can't be.
There are no raccoons in Seoul.
I saw her.
Many times.
- Really?
- Yes.
She only comes out of hiding
when it's empty and you call her name.
She comes out?
That's impossible.
You must take me for a fool.
I'm serious.
Her name is Yeong-suk.
You're lying, aren't you?
Call out her name when no one's around.
But she only comes out when she wants to.
Come on. Don't lie.
You're lying.
She's so adorable.
You're fooling me again.
You're lying.
She has big, round eyes.
I know you'll love her too.
I'm sorry, but you're not fooling me.
He is a fool. He still believes it.
Does he believe everything I say?
No wonder he married me after I said
I'd make him happy.
Yeong-suk.
Come out if you're here.
Yeong-suk?
Yeong-suk!
I want to see you, Yeong-suk.
QUEEN OF TEARS
He ran laps, and had rice soup again.
Is this fun?
How could I possibly leave her?
Get out.
A reunion? A bar? There's only one answer.
A mistress.
Why are you still here
and letting them humiliate you?
That today will be
the best day of my life.
She'll choose me anyway.
You! Let her go!
And if you try to harm her,
I'll do the same to you.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim