Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.xyz or dramacool.club
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
♪That day♪
♪Nothing stays together forever♪
♪I've quit romance♪
♪Who hasn't failed again♪
♪Crying in death♪
♪And in life♪
♪Even now♪
♪We keep learning♪
♪It's no surprise♪
♪Being happy is so hard♪
♪Weirdly, I became a role model♪
♪On the day we met again, we said hi♪
♪It was a reminder,
a test, and a complaint♪
♪Who can do anything without regret♪
♪I am all right♪
♪May you live in peace♪
♪Let the world roar♪
♪Sounds like a carnival♪
♪Being alive is never dull♪
♪How wonderful to be free♪
♪I became even better without you♪
♪Nothing can be perfect♪
♪We bless each other in pain♪
♪We nod and smile♪
♪May we both be well♪
= Love's Ambition=
=Episode 9=
First, let's turn to
the latest on global markets.
(Host, Xu Yan)
Renewed confidence
fueled a global market rally yesterday.
(Nasdaq hits all-time high)
The Nasdaq index,
fueled by tech giants,
has surged to a new record high,
climbing over 1 percent.
I think
delivering it in a steadier pace
is better.
I don't agree.
I think it's great.
Moreover,
this suits her better
than food programs.
Yan.
A surprise for you.
Want to know?
We two
have been thinking about
giving you a special gift.
Here.
Congratulations!
Thank you, Mom, Dad.
Open it and check.
This is too expensive.
Do you like it?
I'm glad you like it.
Thank you.
Both of us think
now that you're an anchor,
your on-screen presence
should be more elegant.
Rubies are perfect.
Let me put them on you.
You're always thoughtful.
I'd only know
to buy bags,
which are useless here.
If you think in this way,
you must strive to
keep your wife satisfied.
Right?
Right.
Haoming.
I'll switch horses next Saturday.
Can you go with me?
Saturday?
Not Saturday.
He and I
have a meeting with Mr. Wu.
Fine.
I'm not important.
Haochen.
Maybe I'll go with you.
Do you know about horse switching?
This kid...
Alright.
Forget it.
Let me try these earrings on you.
Catch!
Go!
Pass it!
- Stop fighting!
- Stop!
Stop it!
Bu!
Throw it farther.
Bu.
Bu, come.
Come.
(Parents' Group)
What happened?
So annoying.
Ready, Bu?
Trouble again.
Mr. Wang.
What's up, Mom?
Haochen's teacher texted me.
He hit a classmate again
during P.E. class.
Not his first offense.
His parents insist me to go.
I'm so busy!
Hosting ten feasts
is easier than dealing
with his teacher's message.
Haochen always causes trouble.
I'd be lectured
by these young teachers.
We are all busy.
And I have
to handle these.
I'm overwhelmed. This is annoying.
Every time the teacher calls,
my heart aches.
You're more patient than I am.
I'll add you to the group,
and I'll exit.
Deal then.
Is it okay, Mom?
It's perfectly okay.
You married Haoming,
and we are family now.
You are also Haochen's guardian.
Deal then.
I'll tell his teacher.
Okay.
But, Mom.
It's my first time being a parent.
There's much I don't understand.
Please guide me.
No need. Just follow instructions.
Apologize when needed. Alright.
I've added you.
(Parents' Group)
I'm in.
(You've joined this group chat.)
The teacher...
Bu!
Bu, come.
I will play with you.
Here.
Babe.
Come here. Come.
(Haochen's parent,)
(Haochen got into another fight in P.E.)
(and hurt a classmate.)
(The school's talked to him,)
(but it's useless.)
(The injured child's parents are furious,)
(waiting in the office.)
(Come to the school now.)
Understood.
I'll talk to him when we get home.
Sorry, we'll take the blame.
When you get home, talk it out with him.
As his family,
you can't just dump him at school
and leave him alone.
This doesn't work.
Understood.
After we go back,
I'll talk to him.
Alright.
That's it.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Okay.
Next one.
Move to the center.
Want to tell me
what happened today?
Don't worry.
The kid's parents
won't pursue it further.
But I think
we need to talk it out.
Can you hear me?
Back?
Yan, how was it?
The kid's parents
won't pursue it further.
He really needs to control his temper.
He's only twelve.
When he's older,
we can't control him.
What we're providing him with
the best educational resources.
An excellent school.
Right?
Now we need
to focus on
solving the problem.
Maybe we should consider
sending him abroad.
Mom.
Haochen is only twelve.
Isn't it too early for him?
Ms. Sun's child
went abroad even younger than him.
Went to Australia at eight.
Wait, this varies case by case.
He just turned twelve.
If we send him abroad now,
he might
go astray,
and no one will
correct him then.
But he's a boy.
He could benefit from it.
I don't oppose it.
But we must
find the right timing.
It varies case by case.
Maybe it works
for other kids,
but not ours.
Listen, he's been spoiled...
The school isn't over yet.
I'll go check.
I think we should
discuss this with him.
Let's hear what Haochen thinks.
If he rejects,
don't force him.
Haoming.
In this entire family,
you spoil him the most.
You take the blame
for turning him this way.
Reflect on this.
Haochen.
I think
the school isn't over yet.
Why you...?
Let me ask you.
Did you tell my parents
to send me abroad?
Why would I do that?
Stop pretending.
You made my brother fall for you,
and then pleased my parents,
until everyone adored you.
But I didn't fall for your tricks.
Now trying to drive me away?
- Right?
- Right.
You guessed it right.
I do want to drive you away.
And then
make them all adore me.
How clever of me!
Shen Haochen.
Use that little brain of yours.
Does this make any sense?
Let me tell you.
I'm not going abroad.
No matter what tricks you pull,
I, Shen Haochen,
fight you to the end.
I don't know why
you're so hostile toward me,
but let me remind you,
I married your brother.
I'm your sister-in-law,
and we're family now.
I love you
how much they love you.
I won't hurt you,
so I don't need
to send you abroad.
Before you came,
my brother spent every day with me.
If you listen to me,
and no more
of today's incident,
I can make
Haoming spend more time with you.
I can guarantee
you would stay.
Deal?
What's this new trick?
We're in an advantageous position.
Have some tea.
What does this mean?
Jinda Group has agreed
to grant us exclusive coverage
of the New District development project.
This is an extraordinary opportunity!
Many media outlets are vying for this.
And you're the perfect candidate
for this.
I'm telling you.
Once this project launches,
it'll boost your career.
Of course,
your professional skills are excellent.
But this will
be the icing on the cake.
Thank you, Sir.
Not at all.
Come on. Have some tea.
Yan.
There's a Mr. Zhou
waiting for you downstairs.
Okay.
It's been so long.
Five or six years, I think?
How are you?
Not bad.
Seeing you on TV
after all these years,
you've fulfilled your dream
of becoming a news anchor.
I'm happy for you.
Thank you.
Remember?
Our first meeting
was also in a cafe.
(Five Years Ago)
Zhou, your project
is too theoretical for me.
Mr. Chen,
there are
very few experts
involved in this research
and not many people understand
its systems.
I believe in the upcoming future,
it will become
the prevailing trend in healthcare
and empower doctors
to better serve patients.
Alright.
I understand your point.
Let's stop here for today.
I have a meeting soon.
I'll consider it.
Fine.
Call me.
Mr. Chen,
the proposal.
No need.
Xu Yan.
I've reviewed your resume, impressive.
Finished the form?
Yes.
Here you go. Please.
The family members
and occupations section
is left blank here.
Why?
May I ask
this section is mandatory?
This top-tier media company
puts great emphasis
on employees' backgrounds.
Beyond education
and professional skills,
family background serves as
a part of background checks.
Understood.
I grew up with my grandma.
Then I'll...
May I ask
about your parents' occupations?
My family runs a barbershop.
Include that?
Then better not.
This could get you a bonus,
but filling it in
will be unfavorable.
But you can't leave it blank.
Here's my suggestion.
Overseas business operations.
Don't worry.
They usually
can't verify this.
It's safer.
I advise you not to listen to her.
Fabricating resumes
is equivalent to planting
a time bomb in your career.
One day,
it would suddenly explode.
Then all your credibility
and your previous efforts
would be completely wasted.
These despicable headhunters
are increasing.
What if they use this to threaten you?
Nonsense.
Miss.
You're eavesdropping us,
and now slandering me?
Just fill it in here.
- Here?
- Right.
(Family Members)
Miss.
I just graduated.
I want to be honest.
If it's really
as he said...
Then I can't handle
this case for you.
Okay?
I won't take the commission.
- Miss.
- Can't believe it.
Sorry.
No problem.
Hello. I'm Xu Yan.
I submitted my resume to your company.
Sorry, we're not interested.
Wait. Please hear me out.
For you.
You failed today,
but don't be discouraged.
Just like this sunflower,
thrive strongly and never give up.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Hello.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Now I need one too.
The investor
won't come.
Alright.
Then let's
thrive strongly together.
Keep going!
I-I want to ask
if you made this
from that proposal.
Exactly.
No one wants it.
Need this resume?
I can teach you.
No, thanks.
What's your name?
I'm Zhou Zeyuan.
And you?
I'm Xu Yan.
Xu Yan.
Now you've become
a genuinely successful woman.
Not really.
I just became a news anchor recently,
still waiting to see audience feedback.
It's too early to say so.
Enough about me.
What about you? What do you do?
Those investors
all doubted me,
but I always believed in myself.
When my company started,
there were only three.
And now we have
over 160 people
in the company.
We got three funding rounds,
and expanded
from domestic to overseas markets.
We established branches
in New York, London,
and Ottawa.
Mr. Zhou.
And we signed a contract
with a German institution.
My plan is to collaborate with
over 70 hospitals
in three years.
(He is radiant with vigor,)
(and full of ambitious spirit,)
(just like he was)
(when we first met.)
(The only difference)
(might be his current outfit.)
(It looks casual,)
(without flashy logos,)
(yet clearly expensive at first glance,)
(perfectly embodying the image)
(of a tech nouveau riche here.)
Moreover, I plan
to go public on NASDAQ
by next year's end.
- Have some water.
- Thanks.
When we first met,
we were all novices.
Now look at us.
I've believed
in the mysticism of persistence.
Persistence will get rewards.
We achieve what we're determined to do.
Xu Yan,
I know you married
Shen Haoming from Jinda Group.
Jinda Group is top-tier
in the construction field.
Their Investment Division
is also highly reputable.
Given our relationship,
I'll be direct.
To be honest,
I came to you
to connect through you
with your husband.
Collaborating with Jinda Group
would benefit
my company greatly.
I deeply respect the industry
and vision you've chosen.
By the way,
could you first send me
your company's
recent financial reports
and business plans?
Then I'll tell my husband.
No problem. I'll prepare it right away.
Thank you for your support.
Not really.
A worthwhile investment project
can be beneficial, for my husband
and the group.
A win-win situation
would be ideal.
Mr. Zhou.
Mr. Wang from Youkang Medical
is here again.
We agreed...
Zhou.
I've tried to schedule you,
but failed.
Reserve this batch of equipment for me.
The price is flexible.
Let's sign the contract today.
No, no.
Wang.
I've been so busy lately.
And I have a guest here today.
Another day.
Fine.
You go ahead. I'll wait here.
Then sorry.
Please wait here.
Wang, come with me.
Listen, I've tried to schedule you.
I've been overwhelmed.
Let's go.
(New Medical Innovation Competition,
First Prize)
Excuse me.
Where's the restroom?
Go straight and turn left.
Okay, thank you.
I haven't had my break yet.
Yes.
My current job is super easy.
Just sit there doing nothing.
Five hundred a day.
Much easier than the filming work.
Want to join me?
Let's come together.
Don't worry. No one notices you.
Just sit at the desk
and pretend to work.
Exactly.
It's just a shell company.
Doesn't matter.
They don't need skills.
Can you show me?
Of course.
I-It's simple.
Under maintenance.
Let me find Mr. Wang
over in Engineering.
Hello.
This is Shangze Xinhui
Medical Technology.
Hello. This is Shangze Xinhui
We've completed
comprehensive upgrades.
Rest assured about our services.
Our services are lifelong.
For any problem,
feel free to contact us anytime.
Liang.
About the financial report,
the CFO wants to see you.
What?
A payment from the 15th
needs verification.
A payment on the 15th?
(Sales Department Archives)
Xu Yan.
Sorry to let you wait.
Mr. Wang left.
Let's talk then.
I didn't tell you
I have plans tonight.
It's okay.
Call me.
Okay.
Honey, are you done?
Almost.
By the way,
is cousin still in Jingzhou?
Probably.
She found a job?
Selling cosmetics.
Thank you.
Let's treat her to a meal.
Okay.
However,
she's working at a mall now.
She might get off work late.
It's okay.
Let her know
I'll adjust to her schedule
to show my sincerity.
No problem.
I'll tell her.
Delicious.
This way, please.
So many koi fish here.
Mind your words.
Okay, okay.
I've ordered some dishes.
Let's see what else you'd like.
I eat anything. Thank you.
Any vegetable?
Golden mushroom shreds,
chrysanthemum moss,
baby bok choy,
braised shallots,
red peppers in sauce,
counterfeit dish,
and our signature stir-fry.
Cousin,
what do you want?
I... I...
Anything will do.
Well, any spinach?
Sorry, miss.
We don't have a fixed menu here.
Our menu changes daily based on
the freshest seasonal ingredients
available at the market.
Therefore, you can only order dishes
on the menu.
How about...?
She prefers spinach.
Go get some.
Thank you.
Yes, Mr. Shen.
Welcome.
Here.
Welcome to Jingzhou.
Thank you.
Are you settling in well here?
Very well.
Both the food and accommodations.
If you need any help,
tell me anytime.
I should be able to help.
No need.
Yan has been
caring for me.
My life now
is back on track.
Yan told me
you're busy with work.
Running such a large company,
I shouldn't bother you.
We're family.
It's okay.
You mentioned liking this dish,
so I reserved it.
I just mentioned it,
yet you remembered.
Try it?
No, you have it.
I'm glad to see you two like this.
Yan always
praises you to me,
saying you treat her so well.
Witnessing it with my own eyes today,
it's wonderful.
Thank you.
Cousin,
tell me more.
What else did she say about me?
She loves you deeply.
Yan had always been top of her class.
She studied hard,
excelled in academic.
And she's pretty.
Back in school,
she's a top student
and the campus belle.
Many boys wanted to pursue her.
But Yan
was only focused on
her studies
and ignored boys.
I used to wonder,
she is
with such high standards,
who could possibly win her heart?
You're so lucky.
You are her first love.
Really.
When we were in school,
she had zero interest in dating.
To her,
boys basically didn't exist.
If the town had a girls' school,
she would've transferred there.
Were you two
studying together?
I remember Yan told me
your hometown is Jincheng, Shanxi.
Well...
Good memory!
Yes.
I...
I wasn't good at studying.
In high school,
I repeated two grades
and transferred to
Yan's school
for remedial classes.
So we ended up studying together.
Excuse me,
allow me to serve.
She's exactly the same.
Back in school,
she'd always interrupt the teachers.
She still does it now.
Try the spinach.
Here.
Don't be shy.
We should
meet up more often.
I really enjoy hearing you
talk about Yan's past.
Sure, no problem.
(Mind your words.)
But I'm busy.
You two just go dating.
I'm glad that you two
get along well.
Here, have some more.
Yan isn't the type
to fall for anyone easily.
But once she does,
it's for a lifetime.
You better cherish her, okay?
Don't worry.
I will.
Good.
Here.
By the way,
any plans after the meal?
There is
a Sky Lounge here
where you can see
the Jingzhou's night view.
It's stunning.
I take her there often.
Why not mention it sooner?
We made plans
to go shopping.
But the Sky Lounge is amazing.
It's a must-see in Jingzhou.
Another day?
Sure.
Next time.
Excuse me.
Eat raw food?
Yes, okay.
Eat it.
Okay, thanks.
Here.
I'll do it.
Alright.
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.xyz or dramacool.club
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Thank you.
You talked quite a lot today.
Think I enjoy this?
Just to let him know
you love him deeply.
Why?
I consulted a lawyer.
The lawyer said
as long as your relationship
is genuine,
and the man believes
you love him,
while he loves you too,
and then even if the truth
comes out,
as long as he chooses
to stand by you,
you won't be put in jail.
Don't think this means
I approve of what you're doing.
Have any idea
what I felt today
hearing those dishes name?
I felt so worried.
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.xyz or dramacool.club
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
So scary!
You must've been scared too, right?
Why that look?
Nothing.
I just want to say that
you could join us for meals more often
to upgrade your dining.
Not afraid I'll reveal your secret
and cause you trouble?
It's okay. Not that bad.
That works.
Then I'll just keep brainwashing him,
and reminding him how much you love him.
No need.
He can feel
how much I love him.
Don't be that confident.
Men are oblivious.
Think he understands,
what if he
feels nothing at all?
Watched those TV commercials,
didn't you?
Remind him
again and again.
Even it means countless times.
To let him remember
how much you love him.
I saw you smiling.
What's funny?
You're quite adorable.
Talk less.
Well, I know
I'm adorable.
But listen.
You still need
to talk it out
to your husband, okay?
Feels like we haven't
walked like this in ages, right?
Cool!
Exactly. So cool!
What are you seeing?
Nothing.
Let's go home.
Qiao Yan.
Take it.
What's this about?
Keep it.
I don't want it.
Just take it.
You always came
to see this thing,
so I'll give you mine.
What about you?
My birthday is next month.
I'll have my parents buy me
a new MP4 player.
Alright, try it.
The sound is great.
Can you hear it?
No sound.
Impossible.
Can you hear it now?
There are
all my favorite songs in it.
You can download
your favorite songs.
Okay.
Do you like the music?
It's good.
The night view
is truly stunning.
Sky Lounge, right?
When do you take me there?
Anytime.
Sky Lounge.
I want to visit the museum,
anime expos,
water parks,
and that
aquarium.
Ruyi!
From now on, you're my horse.
I'll take good care of you.
Haochen.
Are you hot?
Haoming had things to do,
so I'm here.
Look!
This...
The cooling spray.
Feel cooler?
Switched horses already?
This horse is cool!
Cooler than the last one.
I just talked
with your coach.
He said
after switching horses,
take it slow
and gradually adapt
to the rhythm
and movement.
After you mount,
be careful.
And after that...
Go away.
Let's go.
Be careful, Haochen.
Haochen!
(Jingzhou Yuekang Hospital)
Haochen.
This bone broth
was simmered
for three hours.
It has Chinese herbs
to help your leg
recover soon.
Look at you.
Why were you so careless?
It wasn't his fault,
but that riding club's fault.
Understood?
The coaches' fault.
I'll find you a better club.
Their coaches
are all former professional racers
with medals.
You injured seriously.
Don't move around out of impatience.
It'd be terrible
if you don't recover, got it?
Hear that?
Mom, Dad.
Caregiver.
Good.
Hello.
I'm his mother.
He has a fracture.
Don't let him off his bed.
We're counting on you.
Trust me.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- One last sip.
Haochen.
Dad and I
have an engagement.
We'll come tomorrow.
We're leaving.
Dinner with Shifeng's executives.
Good boy.
Yan.
Thank you.
Okay.
I'll do it.
Here.
Let me feed you, okay?
Haoming.
I need...
I'm running late
for a dinner.
Talk later.
Here, take a sip.
Come on. Drink more.
Here.
Right.
Good.
No more drinking.
No more?
Then... how about some fruits?
Okay?
Look.
Pick something you like.
I don't eat fruits.
This...
What's up?
No!
Leave! I don't want you!
Just say it.
- Leave!
- Why hit me?
Outrageous!
What's up?
No.
Leave!
Stop talking to me!
Stop it!
- Leave!
- I quit!
I'm sorry.
So sorry.
I quit.
What about more money?
No way.
Never seen a child like this.
I can't do it.
I don't want to see you. Leave!
I refuse.
You!
Kick me out.
Come down here.
It hurts.
Can't get down.
Listen.
You'll stay in bed
for four weeks.
Your parents
and Haoming
entrust you to me.
During these four weeks,
behave yourself.
Otherwise,
you'll suffer.
Fine.
If you stay here,
get me some fruits.
Take those leftover ones.
I...
I-I want water.
Hurry up! I'm dying of thirst!
It's too cold.
I always drink
warm water.
Knock it off.
This is a hospital.
You don't know me.
I-I need food.
I can't reach the fruit.
Feed me one.
Feed me this meal too.
Your hands are hurt?
The doctor never said that.
Eat it.
When Haoming was here,
you treated me well.
Now that he's gone,
you're bullying me?
When Haoming was here,
you were like an angel.
Now that he's gone, you're bullying me?
I'm injured.
I-I'm a kid!
If you bully me,
my brother will punish you.
Alright.
Skip the meal.
Stop it.
What?
What's wrong?
I'll call the doctor.
Wait.
Hey,
I need to pee.
Just say it.
Don't you see
I'm clutching my stomach?
Is this okay?
I'll help.
No! I'll do it myself.
Watch me pee?
♪Like fireworks that loved♪
♪Rushing toward the stars♪
♪Undaunted by pain♪
♪Fearless of flames♪
♪Even if just a fleeting sparkle♪
♪We shed tears♪
♪Deep blue seas turn to foam♪
♪We regained freedom♪
♪If you remember me♪
♪Then I'm pleased♪
♪I just wanna take my time tonight♪
♪To do all the things I said I'd try♪
♪I go surfing, go diving, go driving,
and go flying to a different place♪
♪I go drink, go party, and go dance♪
♪Even if I'm lonely♪
♪Cause I just have been hurt
too many times♪
♪I'm giving it all to get nothing back♪
♪I was lost in the dark,
and it's too hurt to even see♪
♪See the world and how it flows.
We never let go♪
♪So I'll take my time♪
♪To reignite♪
♪The love I should deserve♪
♪When the time is right♪
♪You realize♪
♪It will all be alright♪
♪Cause I just have been hurt
too many times♪
♪I'm giving it all to get nothing back♪
♪I was lost in the dark,
and it's too hurt to even see♪
♪See the world and how it flows.
We never let go♪
♪So I'll take my time♪
♪To reignite♪
♪The love I should deserve♪
♪When the time is right♪
♪You realize♪
♪It will all be alright♪