Have you got it?
Of course.
I'm the Reception Envoy
appointed by my father.
They would naturally give me the pass.
Good.
Then let's depart immediately.
Go 30 li east
and then switch to waterways.
We should be able to reach
Qingluan Pass within 5 days.
Once at Qingluan Pass,
take Xiao Ran and the others
and continue east to Lincheng.
The rest of the envoy team turns south
and heads to Qiongzhou.
Guide Envoy Lord Zhan Ziyu has arrived.
Leave it to me.
Your Highness.
Her Majesty heard that you're going
to Qiongzhou with King Ximeng.
You hurriedly got the imperial pass
from the Ministry of Rites yesterday.
I didn't expect you to leave today.
I wonder why you're in such a hurry.
What are you talking about, Lord Zhan?
My royal parents gave me the grace
to be the Reception Envoy
and accompany King Ximeng on a tour.
How dare I slack off?
Your Highness, you're absolutely right.
But I find it very strange.
Qiongzhou is a long way off
and has no scenery.
King Ximeng came from afar,
so he should enjoy
the beautiful scenery of Biantang.
Why go all the way to Qiongzhou?
Could it be...
that there is something special
about Qiongzhou?
Don't ask, Lord Zhan.
I'm wondering too.
This old man from Ximeng is very weird.
He insists on going
to that damn Qiongzhou.
I'm very reluctant.
How did I end up with such a hard job?
Why speak such words, Your Highness?
Her Majesty has always loved you the most.
To show sympathy for your hard work,
she specially sent me as a Guide Envoy
to clear the way
for you and King Ximeng.
That's not necessary.
Going to Qiongzhou is a trivial matter.
How can I bother you, Lord Zhan?
You are wrong, Your Highness.
Receiving foreigners
is an important matter for the country.
How can you say it's a trivial matter?
What's more,
this is Her Majesty's decree.
Let alone me,
even you
should follow it carefully.
Your Highness.
Since Lord Zhan has conveyed
Her Majesty's gracious intention,
I can't naturally disappoint him.
Let's travel
with Lord Zhan.
[REBIRTH]
[Episode 14]
[Qingluan Pass]
Your Highness,
we have arrived at Qingluan Pass.
There are 2 forks ahead.
One to the east and one to the west.
Both can reach Qiongzhou Prefecture.
Go east. Set off immediately.
Wait, Your Highness.
To go to Qiongzhou Prefecture,
you should head west.
The terrain in the east is steep,
with many mountains and wild beasts.
The west is an official road.
There are post stations along the way,
which is much more convenient.
The road in the east is a bit rugged,
but there are shortcuts.
We can arrive
at Qiongzhou Prefecture earlier.
That's strange.
You don't take the flat official road
in the west,
but insists on going
to the deserted, dangerous mountains
in the east.
Could it be that the east
has something special?
Or is it that King Ximeng
and you have ulterior motives?
You are not
going to Qiongzhou at all,
but somewhere else, are you?
Lord Zhan, you're indeed smart.
You can tell at a glance
that I have ulterior motives.
To tell you the truth, Lord Zhan,
it's said that heading east
from here will pass by Yingchuan.
There is not only good wine and food
but also countless beauties.
I do have some selfish motives
and want to experience it.
But since you're the Guide Envoy,
I will listen to you.
By Lord Zhan's order,
take the official road in the west.
I'm tired.
Let's rest at the pavilion ahead.
Attendant,
come here.
Your Majesty,
what are your orders?
It's cold.
Go get me a blanket.
Yes.
Wait.
Step forward.
Hold your horses.
Tonight, we will rest
at the official post station
at Tianshui Ferry.
We'll travel at night.
So we can arrive
the night before Great Yong
and Great Yan exchange their prisoners.
Yes.
Your Majesty, do you have anything else?
If not,
I will take my leave.
My Lord.
Keep an eye on
King Ximeng's personal guards.
See if you can
find any clues from them.
Yes.
Welcome, Your Highness.
Come on.
Delicious, delicious.
This is also delicious.
I need more.
Come on, come on.
Eat some meat. Come on.
Come on. Eat some meat.
Eat some meat.
The meat is so delicious.
Delicious, delicious.
This meat is delicious.
Meat is much better.
Come on, eat.
Come on, come on.
-Eat the meat.
-Eat, eat.
Where's the wine?
Why do we get to eat
dry rations and cabbage,
while they get to eat a sumptuous meal
with delicacies?
Why do we get to eat this?
We want meat!
-Yeah!
-We want meat!
Come on, eat the meat!
Come on, drink!
Sirs,
I'm really sorry for the poor service.
You may not know this,
but it has been pouring rain for days,
and there are flash floods.
The merchants
transporting fresh vegetables
and meat to the post station
have been delayed.
So right now,
there's not enough food here.
I really can't arrange it.
-Sir, Sir!
-You think we can be fooled?
Not enough food?
Why do they get to eat a sumptuous meal
with delicacies?
Calm down, Sirs, please!
Lord Zhan arranged it this way.
I'm just following orders.
Please be understanding.
A sumptuous meal!
-Delicious!
-With delicacies!
-Fresh!
Sirs, you can't!
You can't!
Sirs!
Come on!
A sumptuous meal is bad for your health.
Yeah, yeah.
Simple fare is good
for your health instead.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's go, come on.
Come on, come on.
Simple fare,
-good health.
A sumptuous meal,
-choke to death!
Eat.
Eat. Let's eat ours.
Come on, let's eat ours.
What are you waiting for?
Eat and drink.
Let me see.
Nothing.
What is all this junk?
What did you do?
Why did you go through our bags?
Which eye saw us going through them?
Yeah, which eye?
You Ximeng people
are just like these beasts of burden,
poor and backward.
Tell me,
with your ragged bags,
what's there to go through?
Useless fool!
So it...
-is a little girl!
How dare you!
What are you doing?
What's going on?
Lord Zhan, it is a—
Lord Zhan, it is—
Lord Zhan, it is a little—
Lord Zhan.
You received Her Majesty's decree
to serve as the Guide Envoy for Ximeng,
yet you mistreated
Ximeng's soldiers like this,
damaging the relation
between Biantang and Ximeng.
Acting like this,
aren't you afraid
my mother will blame you?
Seems you're in a bad mood today,
Your Highness.
You reminded me
that damaging the relation
between Ximeng and Biantang
might incur Her Majesty's wrath.
But I feel that
you indiscriminately
killed Biantang's soldiers,
and it will enrage Her Majesty even more.
Your Highness, do not forget one thing.
The reason Her Majesty sent me here
is to prevent the Crown Prince
from doing absurd things
that disgrace Biantang.
Lord Zhan.
I only killed
2 troublemaking soldiers.
I didn't kill the Ceremonial Officer
and Guide Envoy, Lord Zhan.
How would that disgrace Biantang?
Why?
Lord Zhan, are you afraid?
It seems you remember
that I am the Crown Prince of Biantang.
And you,
a Ceremonial Officer or Guide Envoy,
in the end,
are nothing but... but...
a male favorite.
Your Highness,
whether I am a Guide Envoy
or a male favorite,
it's bestowed by Her Majesty.
It's not your place to judge.
But these troublemaking Biantang soldiers
have already been killed
by your own hands.
That Ximeng soldier
should also be taken away and interrogated
to find out what exactly is going on.
Guards,
arrest
this troublemaking Ximeng soldier.
-Yes.
Hold on.
Lord Zhan.
Since the soldier under my command
does not know Biantang's etiquette,
just let me handle it.
Take this troublemaker away
and deal with him by military law.
-Yes.
Let go!
Lord Zhan,
am I not allowed
to deal with my own soldier?
Let go!
Alright!
Go.
You just wait!
The imperial map.
The imperial pass.
Traveling from Tangjing,
we've already delayed
for a day on the road.
Qingluan Pass is just ahead.
You leave tonight.
If you ride fast, you can still make it.
Lincheng is an important pass
at the border
of Great Yong and Great Yan
and also an important military point
defended by Great Yong.
The prisoner of war camp here
holds important prisoners all year round.
It might not be that easy
for you guys to succeed.
Be very careful.
I know.
And,
you don't have to return
the same way after rescuing He Xiao.
You can circle back
to Biantang from the west.
It'll be safer this way.
According to the schedule,
you should be able to arrive
outside Tangjing in 15 days.
Li Ce will arrange someone
to meet you then.
Li Ce.
You killed the guards sent by the Empress.
You've already fallen out with Zhan Ziyu.
He will definitely
watch your every move in the future.
It might be trouble
if you return to Biantang.
My mother and I
have actually known what kind of person
each other is.
We've just put on a fake show
for over 10 years.
She's prepared.
So am I.
Qiao,
don't worry.
[Ninghui Hall]
Please inform His Majesty
that Prince of Luo, Li Yan, and his future
Princess Consort, Zhao Chun'er,
are here to seek an audience.
His Majesty is asleep
and hasn't left the bedchamber yet.
It's inconvenient to report.
It doesn't matter who you bring.
You two just wait here.
It's about to rain.
How much longer do we have to wait?
It shouldn't be too long.
It's almost noon.
His Majesty should wake up soon.
Your Majesty,
the Prince of Luo has brought his future
Princess Consort for an audience.
They've been waiting outside the hall
for a long time.
Prince of Luo?
When did I ever summon
his Princess Consort?
Go.
Go summon Beauty Han.
Yes.
Beauty Han,
you are finally here.
His Majesty has been talking about you
for the past two days.
He missed you so much.
His Majesty has been waiting
for you for a long time.
Let's go into the hall.
Chun'er,
let's go wait out of the way for a bit.
Wait!
Where are you going?
Didn't His Majesty tell you to wait here?
Here means here.
If you move,
how can you call it here?
Chief Fang,
why must you make things difficult for us?
Prince of Luo, what are you saying?
I am but a servant.
How would I dare?
A vole!
Quick! Catch it!
Beauty Han is terrified of voles!
Hurry!
Where? I...
Let's go.
Chief Fang, are you okay?
[Linrui Palace]
Chun'er,
why did you bring me here?
Isn't this Her Majesty's bedchamber?
We are not seeing His Majesty.
We are going to see Her Majesty.
Her Majesty is even less likely to see me.
I have a plan.
Please announce me.
I'm the Princess Consort of Luo,
bestowed by Her Majesty.
I have urgent matters
and must see Her Majesty.
The Prince of Luo is not married yet.
There is no Princess Consort of Luo.
Give this to Her Majesty.
She will see me.
She says
she is the Princess Consort of Luo?
Yes.
She came with the Prince of Luo.
They are waiting outside.
Then tell her to come in.
Just her.
Yes.
This jade pendant
was a gift from Biantang
when Noble Consort Wei
of Great Yong was pregnant.
This is carved from Tianshan ice jade.
It is extremely precious.
I picked it myself.
Since you have this jade,
you must be...
her executed daughter, right?
Your Majesty, you're indeed very wise.
My surname is Zhao,
and my first name is Chun.
I'm the daughter
of Noble Consort Wei of Great Yong.
Zhao Chun'er.
You said you are
my granted Princess Consort of Luo.
What do you mean?
Please forgive me, Your Majesty.
I took precautions for you
and took the liberty.
Please grant my wish, Your Majesty,
and arrange a marriage
for the Prince of Luo and me.
Although the Prince of Luo
has no power or influence,
he's still a member
of the Biantang royal family.
You are just a deposed princess,
who is still guilty.
Why do you think
I would allow you
to marry the Prince of Luo?
Because this matter
is a win-win situation
for both of us.
I'd like to hear it.
Stand up and speak.
Three years ago, I offended my father,
but now he is old and sick.
Today in Great Yong, my brother,
the Prince of Xiang, Zhao Che,
is in charge of the state.
He holds military power
and has the support of the people.
He'll surely be Great Yong's next king.
Although I am deposed,
my brother Zhao Che
has always loved me dearly.
Before I came to Biantang,
I had been living in the army.
If you're willing to ignore my past
and arrange a marriage
for the Prince of Luo and me,
I can write to my brother.
I will use this marriage as an excuse
to beg him to restore
my identity as a princess.
Why do you think
the Prince of Xiang
will agree to your request?
Just because he dotes on you?
Your Majesty, you hold a high position.
You should know better than me.
A princess married to Biantang,
compared to a dead deposed princess,
is more beneficial to both Great Yong
and the Prince of Xiang.
For you,
it should be the same.
How is it?
Her Majesty has arranged
a marriage for us.
Really, Chun'er?
It's scheduled for the 5th of next month.
Great!
Great, Chun'er!
Princess,
someone has been following us
since last night.
He's followed us for 40 li.
I guess
it's a tall young man,
and his martial arts skills aren't weak.
Ignore him.
Let's go.
Take a look. They are all fresh.
Beyond the Baichuan River lies Lincheng.
I see an inn over there.
Why don't we stay here
for the night?
Sir, you wear a blue robe.
Might your surname be Xi?
My surname is not Xi.
A female guest said your surname is Xi.
The appearance and temperament
she described
are exactly like yours.
Only the age doesn't match.
She said it was an old man.
That's right.
I am the old man.
What else did she say?
She has already arranged
your room and food.
The room is a bit small,
but she said you're old
and have mobility issues,
so she specifically informed me
to tell you to be careful on the stairs.
But you don't seem old to me.
Then just follow her arrangements.
Okay, please come this way.
Sorry, Sir.
The food was also arranged
by the female guest.
She said you are over 60
and have poor teeth,
so you should have some porridge.
Bring me a pot of aged wine.
Okay.
A pot of aged wine.
With the continuous wars
between Great Yan and Great Yong,
the leather business is getting harder.
That's all.
Just the transportation costs
have multiplied several times.
There's no money to be made.
With the wars every year,
my inn's business is also sluggish.
You know what?
Soon, Great Yan and Great Yong
are going to exchange prisoners of war,
so there are actually more travelers
passing through.
Haven't Great Yong and Great Yan
been at war all this time?
Why are they suddenly exchanging prisoners
at a time like this?
It is said that among these prisoners
are the former Xiuli Army.
Chu Qiao has gone missing.
In order to lure Chu Qiao out,
the King of Great Yan is said
to be willing to do whatever it takes
to exchange these prisoners.
Have you heard?
The King of Great Yan
is considered a young warlord
dominating the region.
But he is deeply in love
with the female general Chu Qiao.
That Chu Qiao
was killed by Great Yong's
general Zhuge Yue.
It is said that this Chu Qiao
was once a female slave
of the Zhuge family.
The Zhuge family
has kept slaves for generations.
Especially this Zhuge Yue,
who is the heir of their family.
Who knows how many female slaves
have been killed by them.
Life and death are at others' mercy.
How pathetic.
But God has eyes.
He also died in this frozen lake.
My Lord.
We've found out
General He's exact location.
But Lincheng is Great Yong's territory.
I'm afraid many in the Yong Army know you.
The Black Eagle Army
is also stationed nearby.
Our actions
will easily attract attention.
[Border between Great Yong and Great Yan]
[Prisoner of War Camp, Lincheng]
Tomorrow, Great Yong
will exchange prisoners of war
with Great Yan.
They definitely won't let anything happen
to He Xiao the night before.
Xiao Ran only needs to set a fire
in the corner of the prisoner of war camp.
He Xiao will definitely be relocated.
Go!
Hurry, go get water!
All right.
Let's go.
Follow them
and see where they'll move to.
In 4 hours, when the sky is gray,
people's minds will be least alert.
I will go in and rescue He Xiao then.
Xiao Ran,
you wait outside the city to back us up.
Fang Miaomiao,
go to Baichuan Ferry and find a boat.
We'll leave by water.
A fire broke out
in the middle of the night.
What the hell.
Who do you want?
If you want to live,
take me
to the Commander of the Xiuli Army,
He Xiao.
You...
Where exactly is he?
He's...
He's inside.
If you dare lie to me,
I will kill you on the spot.
Go.
Damn He Xiao.
You killed so many
of our Great Yong people
and still want to be exchanged?
In your dreams!
Even for a prisoner exchange,
I'll cripple you first.
When you return to Great Yan,
you'll be a cripple
for the rest of your life.
Inside.
Where is he?
He Xiao is inside.
He Xiao.
General Cheng,
thanks for your timely reminder.
Otherwise,
we would have lost the key prisoner today.
Put out the fire! Put out the fire!
[4 hours ago]
Lock all the prisoners
in the wooden cells!
Hurry!
Lord Liu.
Who's there?
I'm Cheng Yuan,
Commander of Great Yan's Black Eagle Army.
Coming!
The official report states
that the Great Yan general
escorting the prisoners is Shi Yan.
What is your purpose here, General Cheng?
Lord Liu, you have such great composure.
You can barely save yourself,
yet you still care about me.
What do you mean?
Do you think this fire is a coincidence?
If you move the prisoners now,
you will fall into the enemy's trap.
Chu Qiao,
you can die in peace.
Xing.
Zhuge Yue?
Kill Zhuge Yue for me!
Go.
Assassins!
Hurry! Keep searching!
Hurry!
What's wrong?
We have to split up.
Otherwise, it'll be too conspicuous.
You go that way.
I'll take the main road ahead
to distract them.
We'll meet outside Xicheng.
Okay.
Fang Miaomiao and the others
are at Baichuan Ferry.
If you can't wait for me,
we'll meet at the ferry.
Okay.
Don't worry.
Go.
Search carefully!
Don't miss any clues!
Find them for me!
-Yes!
Zhuge Yue!
You are poisoned?
There's movement over there.
Everyone, follow me.
Go.
Hurry up.
They are there.
Chase them!
Over there! Go!
They are over there!
Xing,
you...
Zhuge Yue,
we will live and die together.
Over there!
Stop!
Such a high cliff,
they won't survive.
Let's retreat.
Why are you alone?
Where is Princess Fu?
She didn't show up.
There's a curfew in the city.
The Great Yong soldiers
and the Black Eagle Army
are both searching for her.
Why is the Black Eagle Army here?
I don't know either.
We must find a way to save her now.
General Cheng.
Does your wound hurt?
I'll go get a physician for you.
No need, Lord Liu.
It's just a flesh wound.
It won't kill me.
I have some imperial medicine
from the Great Yong Palace.
Within 3 days of application,
the wound will heal naturally.
It's very precious.
Thank you, Lord Liu.
You're welcome.
Thanks to your great help today,
I didn't lose the key prisoner.
I am deeply grateful.
It's a pity
that they escaped.
Lord Liu.
If you live,
someone will know what happened tonight.
Then I
won't be able to live either.
Chu,
the law of the jungle
prevails in this world.
There is no justice or fairness.
Xing,
to the ends of the earth,
we live and die together.
To the new King of Great Yan!
Cheers!
You kept saying you liked me!
You liar!
Remember,
you are not allowed
to hide anything from me anymore.
Kill her.