♪
Rue: What if you could
go back to the beginning?
Jules.
(Echoing)
♪
I'm Rue.
I'm Jules.
♪
Rue: I had made a new best
friend for the first time
since getting
out of rehab.
I was feeling good
about the world.
Leslie:
Take your time.
You've come
a long way.
♪
Jules:
Oh, my God.
Rue:
What?
That's him.
Rue:
That's Nate's dad.
♪
Tyler?
Nate: Don't try to ruin my life,
and I won't have to ruin yours.
If anyone ever tried
to hurt you, I'd kill them.
Maddy: Nate's just, like,
totally ruined my confidence.
Love is super dark,
and no one talks about it.
Bitch, you're
my soulmate.
Both:
Thank you!
Lexi:
Rue seems really good.
It's because of you,
you know?
Does the way you feel about her
remind you of anything?
Rue: Every time I feel good,
I think it'll last forever.
But it doesn't.
What if we just
fuckin' left?
♪
We're good.
Come on.
She left you at
a train station?
Rue:
Yeah.
Faye:
Holy fucking shit.
♪
Rue: However hard
life was, it got harder.
♪
I relapsed.
If I were a genius, I'd figure
out a way to do drugs for free.
Rue, ready to do
some business?
♪
For the first time in my life,
I'm doing something for myself.
Fezco: (Over phone)
Of course I'ma be there.
I'ma be sittin'
in the front row.
♪
Maddy: I'm gonna get
back together with Nate.
Hey, Cass, how long have you
been fucking Nate Jacobs?
Open the door,
Cassie!
The longer you do drugs,
the more you're gonna lose.
Leslie:
Jules told me everything.
Rue:
What did you do with them?
Jules:
We flushed 'em down the toilet.
You are fuckin'
dead to me.
♪
This is the part where
the character never recovers.
When do you think you're
gonna come up with the cash?
Rue: This is the scene
that scars her forever.
Don't shoot,
don't shoot!
There's a kid in here!
(Gunshot)
I got faith in you.
♪
[Rue]
A lot of people ask
what I've been up to
since high school.
And honestly,
nothing good.
[people shouting in Spanish]
[shouting in Spanish continues]
[engine revving]
Más fuerte.
[shouting in Spanish continues]
Gracias, mi amigos!
[laughing]
- [engine revving]
- [all cheering]
[♪ "Ride Like the Wind"
by Christopher Cross playing]
- [volume increasing]
- Whoo!
♪ It is the night,
my body's weak ♪
♪ I'm on the run,
no time to sleep ♪
- ♪ I've got to ride,
ride like the wind ♪
- [Rue laughing]
[singing along]
♪ To be free again ♪
♪ And I've got such
a long way to go ♪
♪ Such a long way to go ♪
♪ To make it to the border
of Mexico ♪
♪ So I'll ride like the wind ♪
♪ Ride like the wind ♪
♪ Gonna ride like the wind ♪
Whoo! [laughing]
[singing melody]
- Whoo!
- [music stops abruptly]
[metal creaking, clanging]
[wind whooshing]
[motorcycle revving]
[♪ "Ride Like the Wind"
continues playing faintly]
[exhales sharply]
Andale.
[metal clunking]
Fuck.
- [metal clanging]
- Whoa! Fuck.
[metal scraping]
[creaking]
Whoa.
♪ To get to the border
of Mexico ♪
♪ So I'll ride like the wind ♪
Fuck!
- [music turning off]
- Okay.
Shit.
Go back.
[engine revving]
Alright.
- [grunting]
- [engine revving]
[tires scraping]
Come on.
[engine revving]
- [banging]
- [muttering indistinctly]
[turns off engine]
[Rue sighs]
Oh!
[glass breaking]
Ah. Fuck!
[grunting]
Put all my weight...
- [grunting]
- [horn honks]
Ah!
[softly] Oh, shit.
[metal creaking]
- [wind whooshing]
- [Rue breathing heavily]
[gasping, exclaiming]
Ah! Ah! Ah!
[♪ tense music playing]
[exhales sharply]
[metal creaking]
Oh, shit. Ah, ah!
Oh! Oh! Oh!
♪
There we go.
Okay. Whew.
[wind whistling]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[hawk screeching]
[whip cracks]
[♪ dramatic music
continues playing]
[rooster crowing]
- [pig grunting]
- [cow mooing]
[horse nickering]
You want a cup of milk?
[yawning] Sure.
Thank you.
That's the best fucking milk
I've ever had.
It's Dahlia's.
[Rue] Thank you, Dahlia.
[Dahlia mooing]
[Mr. Miller]
We wanna thank you,
Lord Jesus Christ,
for giving us our daily bread
and forgiving us our trespasses.
And Lord, please guide
our new friend Ruby
and her college newspaper
to help expose
the-- the pure evil that's
pouring across our border
and poisoning our great nation,
the United States of America.
Amen.
- [all] Amen.
- [Mr. Miller] Let's eat.
- Alright, pass the eggs.
- We're gonna help
with your plate, sweetie.
You know who
gets it first, Dad.
[Mr. Miller]
This is our address.
Will you be sure to send your
article when it's in the paper?
Yeah, as long as the commies
at college don't censor it.
[chuckles]
- You're doing the Lord's work.
- Thank you.
- Hope to see you again soon.
- Thank you so much.
- Good luck with everything.
- Yeah.
- Bye, guys.
- [all] Bye.
- Wish you well.
- Thank you.
- Aw.
- Safe travels.
- Thank you.
- God bless!
Bye.
[♪ whimsical vocalizing]
I just got my permit.
[car starting]
[Mr. Miller]
God bless, Ruby.
[Daisy] I've never been
on the internet.
[Rue] You know, Daisy,
I think you got it made.
[♪ "Love is Like Oxygen"
by Sweet playing on car radio]
But I can't help
but be curious.
All the people out there
living big, exciting lives.
I'd trade spots with you
in a heartbeat.
Why?
[radio volume increasing]
♪ You get too much,
you get too high ♪
♪ Not enough,
and you're gonna die ♪
[Rue] Thank you.
You ought to come back out
in the spring
and meet Dahlia's baby.
I just might.
- Oh, shit, qué pasó!
- [laughing] USA.
- Hey, USA, USA.
- USA.
[group]
USA! USA! USA! USA! USA!
[♪ hopeful music playing]
[♪ hopeful music
continues playing]
[rattlesnake rattling]
[metal fan rattling]
[wind whooshing]
[TV playing faintly]
[bird chirping]
[bird calling]
[bird babbling, whistling]
[squawking, calling]
[Laurie] Hello, Rue.
- [bird chirps]
- Hey, baby.
- Where's my car?
- [Rue] I had to leave it behind.
[Laurie]
Hm, I guess I'll just
add it to your tab then.
[Rue] A few years
after high school,
I was working
at a smoke shop.
[customer]
Could I just get
a raw cone, please?
[Rue] Yeah, for sure.
You can keep
the change actually, thanks.
Okay.
[chuckles] Laurie, hey.
- How are you?
- You owe me money.
No, I-- I know, yeah.
I was gonna pay you back.
- You were?
- Yeah.
Um, but then, you know,
you-- you moved.
[chuckles] I don't really have,
like, ten grand right now.
Oh, you don't owe me
ten grand, silly.
- I don't?
- No.
Um, you did 46 months ago,
and, um, now,
$10,000 at a 20%
monthly interest rate
over 46 months means that
you actually owe me, uh...
$43,887,000.
Uh, $43 million?
[Laurie]
I'll settle for 100,000.
But I bet you don't
have that either.
[Rue] And that is how
I became a drug mule.
[car horns honking]
[dogs barking]
[♪ dramatic Western music
playing]
[people chattering]
♪
[Uno] Swallow.
Um, I don't-- I don't really
think that's possible.
[Uno chuckles]
Claro que sí.
Disfruta.
[cigarette sizzling]
[Rue]
The most important thing...
is to make sure each balloon
is properly sealed.
[grunting]
[gulping]
[gagging, coughing]
[gagging]
After a few runs,
I decided to bring a friend.
[gulping, retching]
[Rue] Fuck.
[gagging]
[retching continues]
[coughing] Ugh.
The danger
of body packing is...
[sighs]
...if a balloon breaks,
you die.
[speaking Spanish]
[indistinct chatter]
[Rue] Faye, get your ass
in the car.
Okay, we gotta cross by 3:00.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[car horns honking]
[police radio chatter]
- [farting]
- Yo.
Sorry.
- Don't, man.
- I can only clench for so long.
Yeah, I know,
but you gotta keep that shit
up there, alright?
Breathe through it.
- [farting]
- Damn!
- Sorry.
- Faye, the fuck did you eat?
- [speaking Spanish]
- I'm good, thank you.
No, gracias.
[dog barking]
Turn the engine off, please.
- [engine stopping]
- Passports.
What were you ladies
doing in Mexico?
Uh... [chuckles]
I was just showing my girl
how the mamacitas
do it down here. [chuckles]
- Ruby Bennett?
- That's me.
Faye Valentine?
You have fun?
No.
[Ruby chuckles]
[dog barking]
[dog sniffing]
[♪ tense music playing]
♪
- Welcome to America.
- Thank you, sir.
[car starting]
- [birds squawking]
- [loud farting]
Laurie! Harley!
She's about ready to blow.
- [Rue] [straining] Oh yeah.
- Get the strainer.
It's in the dishwasher.
- [Rue panting]
- My bad.
- Come on, bro.
- [farting continues]
- [Rue] Oh, shit.
- Hang in there.
- Okay.
- Okay. Okay.
- Okay, I got you.
- [Rue groaning]
- The fuck are you doing?
- Just breathe.
- I had an accident.
- You better get the bucket.
- [Rue] Okay.
[TV playing faintly]
[bucket clanging]
[Rue] And that,
ladies and gentlemen...
- Damn!
- ...is how fentanyl
is smuggled
into the United States.
[indistinct chatter]
After Fezco's house
got raided,
Laurie left East Highland
and went into business
with her cousin Harley
and his son Wayne.
[indistinct chatter]
I'm not saying
they're inbred...
[babbling]
- ...but I have my suspicions.
- Appreciate it.
Looks good, Faye.
[Harley] Here's to Rue.
You haven't been killed
or caught yet.
[chuckles]
Praise the Lord.
[laughing]
[Rue] I'd done a dozen runs
over the course of two years
and somehow ended up
their number-one mule.
[Wayne]
Guess you finally found
something you're good at.
[rat squeaking]
You think Wayne
liked the spaghetti?
[Rue]
Mm, I think Wayne likes you.
[chuckles softly]
You know, he's trying to get
out of the drug business.
[Rue] Yeah,
I don't know about that.
He's been saving up.
That's why he's got
a lot of money in his safe.
What safe?
[Faye]
The big one in his basement.
He wants to get
into avocados,
and you can make
a lot of money with avocados.
What else does he have
in that safe?
Uh, I don't know.
Important stuff.
- Where's the key?
- On his belt.
What if there was a way to,
like, take off his belt?
[both laughing]
I think I can
figure that out.
[rooster crowing]
[Rue] In between runs,
I'd pick up extra cash
driving for Uber.
[engine starting]
[♪ "Sunset and Vine"
by Waylon Jennings playing]
♪ I left the old farm
down in Texas ♪
♪ And bummed
all around for a time ♪
♪ Then one day
I found myself staring ♪
♪ At a sign that read
Sunset and Vine ♪
♪ The big cars
and the view... ♪
[passenger]
This city is crumbling.
Crime is out of control.
Somebody's got to do something.
Yeah, totally.
♪ I decided to be
a great actor ♪
- Ooh, up here on the right.
- Oh, okay.
♪ On the corner
of Sunset and Vine ♪
Alright. Here you go.
- Stay out of trouble.
- Yeah, will do, Batman.
- [horns honking]
- [Batman sighs]
I don't know,
why are we still auditioning?
Boy Wonder.
Hey, babe, how are you?
[knocking]
[in low voice]
Yo, Howard!
It's Bennett, open up!
- Hey!
- [chuckles] Hey.
- How was Arizona?
- Um, yeah, no, it was great.
Uh, just got
to hang out with Gia,
and she's-- she's doing good.
She's, like, top of her class.
So was I.
I know.
[Rue]
Sometimes Lexi would
let me crash on her couch.
[teapot whistling]
But it always came
with a lecture.
[Lexi] What are your
long-term goals?
[Rue] And since
I couldn't be honest
about what I'd been up to...
Uh...
...I'd be vague.
Right now, it's kinda
just a day at a time.
You have to plan for the future,
because pretty soon
Uber drivers
are gonna be extinct.
It's all gonna be
automated, like AI.
They're not gonna need
people like you.
Right.
You know, I met these,
uh, these Christians
on a homestead in Texas.
Christians in Texas?
It was a drop-off.
But, yeah, the Miller family.
I can't stop thinking
about them.
There's like six kids,
and they lived on a farm
with like a bunch of animals.
And no technology.
No nothin'.
And I genuinely think that
they were the happiest people
I've ever met in my life.
'Cause they're in a cult.
Oh, well,
maybe that's the answer.
Christianity?
I just feel like
if I grew up religious,
maybe my life
would be better.
Well, I'm not gonna be
friends with a Christian.
[scoffs] Why?
'Cause they're judgmental.
You know,
you really should call Fez.
Yeah, I know.
I feel guilty,
but I just-- I haven't--
I haven't had any time,
I've been really busy.
Yeah, well,
you're free today.
This is rare. Like, I-- I work,
like, seven days a week.
Yeah, well, he misses you.
Did he say that?
- Multiple times.
- Mm.
I don't know,
my hours and his hours
don't really line up,
so it's hard.
No, just like, pick up
the phone and call him.
It's not like
he's going anywhere.
He's in prison for 30 years.
[Rue] Lexi was
working in Hollywood
on a nighttime soap.
Her boss, Patty Lance,
was an industry legend.
[Patty]
Writers are the engineers
of the human soul.
People underestimate
the power of entertainment.
What you see on television
directly impacts the way
we see one another.
The decisions we make
at home, in schools,
and more importantly,
what we do at the ballot box.
- [people snapping]
- Okay?
That means it's really important
that we get 712 together.
- [people snapping]
- [Rue] Lexi felt right at home.
She was surrounded
by smart, creative people
who cared about the world.
This election.
It's giving me
so much anxiety.
[Rue]
Unlike her sister,
who was living
in some right-wing
suburban bubble.
[♪ "(How Much is That)
Doggie in the Window"
by Patti Page playing]
♪ How much is that doggie
in the window ♪
[dog barking]
♪ The one with
the waggly tail ♪
[Rue]
She spent her free time
trying to become
TikTok famous.
- ♪ In the window ♪
- [panting]
- [dog barking]
- ♪ I do hope that doggie ♪
♪ Is for sale ♪
♪ How much is that doggie ♪
♪ In the window ♪
[housekeeper] Very nice,
Miss Cassie, very nice.
And wiggle, wiggle, wiggle.
♪ How much is that doggie ♪
- ♪ In the window ♪
- [dog barking]
[music stops abruptly]
- [Nate] So, I go
to work all day.
- [toy squeaking]
I come home,
and you're pretending
to be a puppy dog.
I'm just creating content.
There-- there are
dishes in the sink
from last night's dinner.
There are flies
buzzing around.
I am so sorry, Mr. Nate.
- Oh.
- [Cassie]
No, do not apologize, Juana.
- You work for the two of us.
- She is a housekeeper,
not a videographer.
- Well, she's good at both.
- I pay her to do one.
[snapping] Get to work.
Yes, Mr. Nate.
How many times do we have
to talk about this?
I am in the real world
making deals.
If an investor comes across
a video like this online,
- I'm a joke.
- People make money doing this.
[Nate] Think about
what you're saying.
What you're actually saying.
♪ How much is that
doggie in the window ♪
- Who's the doggie?
- I'm the doggie.
- Alright, so you're for sale?
- No.
No, but what you're saying is,
"You can buy me."
No, i-it's just a funny video.
Except you're not a doggy.
You're a grown woman.
So, that makes you a what?
A prostitute.
No, I am not a prostitute.
Then stop acting like one.
You are blowing this
way out of proportion.
I am growing my following.
This brand might sponsor me.
It's called monetization.
Mm-hmm.
Come. Tssh.
[whistling]
[bell softly jingling]
Sit.
You don't need to worry
about money.
I've got money.
Why haven't we remodeled
the living room?
- Or the kitchen
or the master en suite?
- Ohh.
Baby, we will.
But right now,
I'm investing in myself.
In the business.
It takes money
to make money.
- Then, let me chip in.
- No.
You've been a bad, bad dog.
Mm.
Woof, woof.
[Rue]
Nate had taken over
his dad's business.
How 'bout this?
Just turn 'em on and pretend.
- Pretend to do what?
- Work.
[knocking]
We gotta put on a show.
Alright, boss.
[Rue]
But what he didn't realize
is how fucking hard
it is to build
in Southern California.
Their wedding
was around the corner.
And Cassie
was dreaming big.
[Nate] Fuck.
[sighs]
[workers chattering]
- How's it going, buddy?
- Nate, how are you?
- Nice to see you.
- A lot going on.
- Thank you for coming out.
- Holy cow!
I know, it's busy.
It's all happening.
I got an A-plus-plus team
working around the clock
on this.
You sure do.
[Nate]
Do you know how many
baby boomers died today?
No.
- Six thousand.
- Jesus.
A boomer dies
every 15 seconds.
You fast-forward
ten years from now,
it's a tidal wave of death.
There's only two things
certain in this life,
and that's death and taxes.
Sun Settlers will be
the premier end-of-life
transitional facility
in California.
We're gonna offer
dignity and care
when these people
need it most.
You don't have to sell me.
I just need to make sure
things are moving smoothly
before I invest
in the second round.
- Smoothly?
- Yeah.
Take a look at what
we got going on here.
These guys have been here
since the crack of dawn.
Trust me, Kurt,
we're gonna make a killing.
[Heather]
If Fred ever tried to tell me
what I could
and could not post
on social media,
I'd castrate him.
He just doesn't get
the online world.
I mean, people make
so much money using it.
I don't want to have to fight
about the prices
of floral arrangements,
or a wedding cake, or ice luges.
I don't think you can
make money that fast.
I mean,
you can on OnlyFans.
Isn't that porn?
See, I used to think
the same thing,
but I started reading,
and it's actually
the biggest misconception.
I mean, the platform is used
to sell content, communicate.
- I'd be the one in charge.
- Wait.
Are you really
considering this?
I mean, I wasn't, not until Nate
started nickel-and-diming me.
So, what would you be posting?
I don't know,
probably the same stuff
that I post on Instagram.
So, why would people pay for it?
To form a deeper
connection with me.
Like, imagine all the unhappy
men in the world.
For just $50,
they could get a personalized
pic and text from me
saying, "Good morning, handsome.
Thinking about you today."
That's it?
People just want
to feel special.
Well, good luck with Nate.
Don't underestimate me.
[♪ upbeat music playing]
- Hey, Gillie.
- Hey.
[♪ upbeat music
continues playing]
[laundry machines rumbling]
Are you seeing anyone?
No.
- You?
- Nah, no.
You hear about Jules?
No.
Don't tell her I told you,
but Maddy told me
she's a sugar baby.
A sugar baby?
A hooker.
But there's a difference, right?
Sugar babies
don't have to have sex.
That's like hiring a chef
who doesn't cook.
You ready?
[Rue]
Maddy worked in management
representing influencers
and a few actors,
including Dylan Reid.
♪
The heartthrob of
L.A. Nights.
And action!
[pool cue clattering]
- You're drunk.
- I just had to build up
the courage.
- Cut!
- [crew member] Cut it!
- Gorgeous.
- [buzzer blaring]
What if he kisses her
and then says the line?
The kiss is the button.
Let's try it.
Spin her, kiss her,
then the line.
Okay.
And action!
You're drunk.
I just had to build up
the courage.
Good note.
And cut!
Where's my iced tea?
[Rue] That was the day
Lexi gained Dylan's respect.
Hey, Lisa.
[car door closes]
[fans cheering and shouting]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[Rue] Maddy's job appeared
more glamorous than it was.
Most days, she was stuck
behind a desk.
Ms. Penzler's office,
this is Maddy speaking.
Oh, hi.
Yeah, please hold.
I have Annie on line two.
I'll take it.
Darling, how are you?
How's Guatemala?
I was just about to call you.
[fans screaming and cheering]
[♪ dramatic music
continues playing]
[Rue] But she had good
relationships with the talent.
How long do I have
to stay at this thing?
Stop pouting, you're getting
paid $50,000 to watch a movie.
[Dylan]
Do I have to stay
for the whole thing?
[Maddy]
Give me a fucking break.
[Rue] A manager
takes 10% of everything.
Five grand for the night.
Good money...
if you're Maddy's boss.
- [Ali] Thank you, Miss Marsha.
- [Rue] Thank you.
The first step I get, right?
Like, I'm powerless
over my addiction.
My life is unmanageable.
Fine.
Step two, only a power
greater than myself
can restore my sanity.
Fine, I get it.
But step three,
I just... [exhales sharply]
That-- that's hard.
Why?
Because how am I supposed
to give my life
and will over
to the care of God?
Easy.
You believe in something
greater than yourself.
That something is God.
God is good. That is that.
You know I've never
been into the whole
believing in God thing,
you know?
- Yeah.
- But I did meet this family,
and, um, they were
super religious
and just, like, so happy.
And it just made me think
that maybe I'm the one
missing something.
Oh, religious people
are happier, that's a fact.
Okay, so what do I do,
just, like,
pick up a Bible
and start reading it?
- That'd be a start. [chuckles]
- Yeah, but isn't there a bunch
- of crazy shit in there?
- Like what?
Ali, I like girls.
What's that have to do
with anything?
Well, doesn't it say that, like,
gays should be put to death
or something?
[laughing] That was,
like, 3,000 years ago.
What, so 3,000 years ago
it was fine to, like,
- put the gays to death?
- Okay, look.
You're talking
about the Israelites.
They were on the run, that was
the main thing, alright?
There wasn't time
for any type of distractions.
- So being gay is a distraction?
- If you're running from
the Egyptian army,
fuck, yeah, it's a distraction.
Ain't no time for sex.
Yeah, but it specifically
calls out gay sex.
- They didn't want men
fucking men, alright?
- [chuckles]
- Okay.
- They didn't say
nothing about women.
But hold on,
it kinda makes sense, though,
because the men
had to focus back then, alright?
The survival of the people
was at stake.
Okay, so if two men
got caught kissing,
they just... killed.
Oh, my God, what are
you writing, a romance novel?
It says men who lay with men.
They're talking about butt sex.
Would you-- yo.
I don't know nothing
about butt sex.
But I do know that war
ain't the time for butt sex.
[laughing] Stop.
Dude. Okay.
This is before
the invention of soap.
Germ theory. Antibiotics.
- Gay, okay.
- Hey, look, I mean...
- I get it.
- You gotta-- you gotta
have ground rules, Rue.
- I get it.
- Okay, what I'm saying is,
you could spend all day
picking apart these books.
What about this?
What about that?
All kinds of mistranslations.
You know, just taking
everything out of context.
You either have faith
or you don't have faith.
Otherwise, you can argue
about this shit forever.
Okay, I'm sold.
I'm making the decision,
God be my witness,
that I'm gonna read
the Bible, okay?
And when I do,
I'm gonna read every word
as absolute fact.
God damn, you ain't gotta be
so extreme about it.
No, no, Ali,
you said it yourself.
Either you believe
or you don't believe, right?
So, I'm choosing to believe.
- The miracles have begun.
- [chuckles]
- [mugs clinking]
- Amen.
Hallelujah.
Alright.
[CD player whirring]
[narrator]
The first book of Moses,
called Genesis.
In the beginning,
God created the heavens
and the earth.
The earth
was without form and void,
and darkness was on
the face of the deep,
and the Spirit of God
was hovering
over the face of the waters.
Then God said,
"Let there be light."
[thunder rumbling]
- And there was light.
- [dog whimpering]
[phone ringing]
- Hello?
- [Wayne] Yo, retard.
Laurie needs you.
Uh, yeah,
I'll see you tomorrow.
[horse nickering]
Hey.
[♪ faint muffled music playing]
[♪ "Teufel" by
Schwarzer Engel playing]
Yo.
Hey, uh, I'm gonna need you
to drop off a package
to a real piece of shit.
- [Rue] M-Me? Really?
- Yeah, you.
- Are you sure?
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
- Yeah, and he's a big buyer,
so don't fuck it up.
[softly]
I'm making a chicken dinner.
- You know, for Faye.
- Mm.
- You know, just the two of us.
- Right.
- That's really sweet.
- Yeah.
Faye, hurry the fuck up!
Ta-da!
Good job.
- Wish me luck.
- [chuckles]
[chickens clucking]
[car door closes]
[♪ Western music playing]
[♪ Western music
continues playing]
[whispering] What the fuck?
- [whispering] Okay.
- [seat belt clicking]
Alright.
Hey, man, uh...
Alamo?
Is there anywhere
I could take a leak?
[bag zipping]
Inside, upstairs.
Take a right, then a left.
Okay.
And don't touch anything
you're not supposed to.
Yeah. Yeah, for sure.
- [♪ rap music playing]
- [people chattering]
[people continue chattering]
[bag unzipping]
[items rustling]
The probability of drawing
four of a kind...
is 0.17%.
I got lucky, man.
Is that what you call it?
- [♪ rap music playing]
- [people chattering]
[splashing]
Yo, uh, do you know
where the bathroom is?
Yeah, it's up the stairs
to the right.
[music and chatter continue]
[sighs]
[money ruffling]
Lucky.
Asshole.
[♪ rap music continues playing]
[partygoers] [chanting]
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Oh, shit, sorry.
Actually, could you help me?
O-Of course I can.
Yeah, no problem.
- Oh, thank you so much.
- [chuckles] Yeah.
I'm still sore from
my boob job, so it's...
- Oh, yeah?
- It's a little bit difficult.
Well...
if it's any consolation,
I think you look
fucking amazing.
- You think so?
- Hell, yeah!
Alright, there you go.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
So, how do you know Alamo?
[music and chatter continue]
- Marco! Marco!
- [laughing]
- Polo.
- Marco! Oh, hello.
- Marco!
- Polo.
[music and chatter continue]
[♪ "Trouble Man"
by Marvin Gaye playing]
[indistinct chatter, laughter]
♪ I come up hard, baby,
but that's okay ♪
♪ Trouble man,
don't get in my way ♪
♪ I come up hard, baby ♪
♪ I've been for real, baby ♪
♪ Gonna keep moving,
gonna roll to town ♪
♪ I come up hard,
I come up getting down ♪
♪ There's only three things,
that's for sure ♪
Oh!
- Oh, my God.
- Shit.
[Rue] Oh, hey.
I'll be right back.
Bishop.
She works for Laurie.
You walk up into my house,
dance with my girls,
and you don't even
introduce yourself.
I'm so sorry.
♪ Got me singin',
yeah, yeah ♪
That's mighty disrespectful,
little lady.
Got that new batch, babe.
Mm.
[whispering]
This'll hit the spot.
[scoffs]
[♪ "Who's That Girl"
by Eve playing]
[Rue]
I was beginning to believe
that I met Alamo Brown
for a reason.
This my little
slice of heaven.
Yeah, well,
some of these girls?
- Demons.
- [Alamo chuckles]
- That's 'cause
I hand select 'em.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
- What business are you in?
- Fuck is you, girl? FBI?
- [laughing]
No, I'm just curious.
[Alamo] Mm-hmm.
I collect the most
sought-after resource
on God's green earth.
More valuable than gold, oil,
uranium combined.
[partygoers laughing]
I'm in the business of pussy.
No shit. My man!
- [chuckles]
- Hell yeah.
See, I done peeped it
from a young age now.
I seen it.
Pussy...
that thing between your legs,
got a mystic power.
So, I figured I'd stand me
right by some pussy
with my cash register.
[both laughing]
Ka-ching. Ka-ching.
[Rue laughing]
Ka-motherfucking-ching.
- [chuckles]
- Yeah.
Oh, man, well, I came
to the right fucking house then.
That's right.
I'm the motherfucking
king of pussy. [chuckles]
I own and operate five
of the dirtiest,
most delectable strip clubs
in the state of California.
Fully nude, and always lewd.
Ain't that right, B?
- Yes.
- [Alamo chuckles]
Okay, I'm just
gonna, like, lay--
lay my cards out
on the table here.
That's, like, my dream job.
- Hoing?
- What?
[chuckles]
You wanna be a ho.
- No, man, no. No, no, no.
- [laughing] Shit.
I mean, like, h-helping out
in the club, you know.
Like, uh, troubleshooting.
Troubleshooting?
- Or troublemaking?
- [chuckles]
- Hm?
- I mean, a little bit of both.
I see you.
You a gay one, huh?
I'll bet you run them bitches
like a nigga, don't you?
[scoffs] What?
[laughing] You see, B?
We got a freak up in here.
- [Rue scoffs]
- [Alamo chuckles]
- I'm begging you.
- Oh.
Hire me. Come on, man.
Please.
Don't you work
for that cracker Laurie?
Yeah, but that's like the worst
fucking job in the world.
Mm-hmm.
Well, little lady,
that's the beauty
of this country we call America.
Anyone can reinvent themselves.
[chuckles]
That's right, babies.
That's right.
- [both giggling]
- That's right. That's right.
It's your daddy.
Is he always like this?
- Look away.
- Oh.
Okay.
[♪ faint pop ballad playing]
[chuckles]
How's the food?
[slurping] It's good.
Great.
Are you happy?
- Yeah.
- Good.
So, um, can we talk
about the wedding?
[gulps, sighs] What part?
- The florals?
- Jesus Christ.
[sighs] So, I have an idea.
I'm not spending $50,000
on floral arrangements.
- Will you just listen?
- $2,000, I understand.
$5,000, fine.
But $50,000 on something
that's gonna die
in a couple of days?
- That's insane.
- Well...
I might have a solution.
Is it less flowers?
- No.
- Is it less money?
- Then, there's no discussion.
- [clearing throat]
- [Cassie sighs]
- What if I paid for the flowers?
- [slurping]
You don't have any money.
I can make it.
Doing what?
[both chuckle]
So, I've kind of actually been
doing some research.
- Mm?
- And...
there is a way...
to make a lot of money
really fast.
How?
[chuckles] OnlyFans.
[both laughing]
The... [clearing throat]
the-- the porn website?
See, no, that's a common
misconception
- about the platform.
- Right.
- You actually just commun--
- You wanna do porn?
[chuckles] Well, if you would
just let me finish.
It's really fascinating.
You wanna sell your body
for floral arrangements?
I will if I have to.
[chuckles]
Absolutely not.
- [both laughing]
- No.
Well, then we have
a really big problem.
'Cause I didn't wait
my entire life
to have a ghetto wedding.
So...
- [utensil dropping]
- So, what-- what are you
trying to say?
That maybe we shouldn't
have a wedding
if you can't afford a wedding.
- I'm treading water right now.
- Mm-hmm.
I can't move forward
with Sun Settlers
till I get the fucking
environmental survey.
I got interest rates,
the regulations,
the Planning and Zoning
Commission is trying
to fuck me in the ass.
And Kurt.
Oh, Kurt's not sure if
now's the "right time"
to invest.
Mm, then maybe
it's not the "right time"
to get married.
- [chuckles]
- Baby.
Baby, I'm trying to give you
everything that you want.
- It doesn't feel that way.
- I ju...
I just need to get
to the starting line.
Starting line?
What about the finish line?
It's in view. I-It is in view.
We are so close.
We're so close.
This is gonna be our moment.
My moment is walking
down that aisle...
surrounded by my friends...
family...
and $50,000 worth of flowers.
What kind of pictures
are we talking about?
Pretty ones.
[clicking tongue]
[chuckles]
You promise me
you're not gonna show those
and your pretty face
at the same time.
- [muffled music playing]
- [people shouting, laughing]
[friend] Tish?
[friend gasps]
[screaming]
- [glass snapping]
- [liquid sloshing]
Shit's laced with fentanyl.
[rings clicking]
She send you?
Sabotage my shit?
Is that what she did?
She put your ass up to this?
I swear to God, I just--
I gave you what they gave me.
I-- I didn't pack it.
I didn't open it.
I-- I had no idea.
I mean, if I did,
why the fuck would I stay here?
You tell me.
[Rue] It's gonna sound
fucking stupid now, but...
[exhales sharply]
I just-- when we were talking...
I thought that, um...
I don't know,
maybe God brought us together.
- God?
- Yeah, I mean,
I don't wanna be
working for Laurie.
She's got me
swallowing balloons
the size of golf balls
and, like, packing my intestines
and going across the border.
It's fucking hell on earth,
and it's over some shit
I did in high school.
Wait, wait, how--
did she just say
fucking high school?
Nigga, she talking
about high school.
[Rue] Laurie fronted me
a suitcase in high school,
and then, like,
my mom found it
and she flushed it
down the toilet.
I mean, I'm not, like,
blaming my mom, obviously,
because I should have
hid it better.
But the point is,
Laurie came back and she said
that I owed her $100,000.
And I have been paying
for that single fucking
mistake ever since.
So...
you know, when you started
talking about how in America
you can reinvent yourself,
I thought, I don't know,
maybe this is God.
- [rings clicking]
- M-Maybe this is
the hand of God at work,
you know, giving me something
to look forward to,
or like, some kinda hope that...
one day, I-- I could...
you know, I could also have
my own little slice of heaven.
So, you believe in God?
Yes, sir.
Well, let's see
if He believes in you.
[wind whooshing]
[Alamo] Mm-hmm.
[♪ whistling music playing]
If I were you,
I'd stay real still.
[Rue inhales deeply]
[sighs]
[gun clicking]
[exhales sharply]
Ooh.
[inhales deeply]
- [gasps]
- [gunshot echoing]
[exclaiming]
[laughing nervously]
Whoo!
[laughing]
[chuckles softly]
[♪ "Little Green Apples"
by The Temptations playing]
Straight tweaker.
[Rue continues shouting]
♪ And if that's
not loving me ♪
♪ Then all I've gotta say ♪
♪ Mm ♪
♪ God didn't make
the little green apples ♪
♪ It don't rain in Indianapolis
in the summertime ♪
♪ There's no such thing
as Dr. Seuss ♪
♪ Disneyland, Mother Goose ♪
♪ Ain't no nursery rhyme ♪
♪ God didn't make
the little green apples ♪
♪ And it don't rain
in Indianapolis ♪
♪ In the summertime ♪
♪ Huh ♪
♪ And when myself
is feeling low ♪
♪ I look across
her face aglow ♪
♪ To ease my mind ♪
♪ Huh ♪