( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
[Episode 1]
[Ganglong Walled City]
Watch out.
Morning, Uncle Long.
Pay the rent. Hurry up.
- Drinking?
- Collecting rent!
- Chu San, you're back.
- Yeah, I'm back.
You haven't paid yet.
Pay up.
Bastard!
Don't run.
Stop right there.
You bastard, I'll chop you to death.
My name is He Chu San.
I'm a native of Ganglong Walled City.
Ganglong Walled City is
a lawless black zone in Hong Kong.
It's home to the poor,
gamblers, and prostitutes.
Big and small gangs
fight openly and secretly here.
They fight to the death,
with blood and flesh flying.
But there are also many people living here,
ordinary folks surviving amid the violence.
Some of us avoid the underworld at all costs,
while others flock to it eagerly.
Fei asked me to give this to you.
Thanks.
Uncle Bei, help yourself. It's on us.
Then I won't stand on ceremony.
Uncle Bei.
Do you know those guys
who were slashing people just now?
They looked so intimidating.
Of course I know them.
They're Xia Liu Yi's men.
The top enforcer in Ganglong Walled City,
raised by Qing Long, the boss of Xiaoqi Hall,
and personally trained as his top fighter.
Top fighter?
He's the best fighter in all of Xiaoqi Hall.
Six years ago,
to rescue Boss Qing Long, who was surrounded,
he went alone,
wielding two machetes by himself,
and kept slashing,
taking down more than 40 men.
He chased them for three whole blocks.
That battle is known in the underworld
as "Black Children's Day."
From then on, if someone offended him,
he would hold them at blade point
and invite them to celebrate Children's Day.
That's not right. Facing 40 enemies...
If each one had a 20 percent chance
of successfully striking back at Xia Liu Yi,
then the probability of him
knocking down all of them without injuries
would be 0.8 to the 40th power,
which is approximately...
Uncle Bei.
Even if Xia Liu Yi
has exceptional combat skills
and can knock down 40 people in a row,
the possibility of doing so
without being injured
is still infinitesimally close to zero.
So, now you're saying I'm old and senile, huh?
I was a member of Xiaoqi Hall back then.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Even brute force has to
follow the laws of science.
And gangsters usually
exaggerate their exploits to show off.
In reality, joining a gang is not only illegal
and punishable by law,
even in a small-scale brawl,
the fatality rate can be as high as 80 percent.
For the two of you,
it would probably be as high as 90 percent.
He Chu San!
Don't think that just because
you went to some university
you can act so self-righteous.
You two, don't listen to him.
He studied so much that
he's messed up his brain.
Uncle Bei, you might not believe it,
but I've been reading lately,
and I came across people
who recruit newcomers for gangs
and earn headcount commissions.
You're not making
that kind of money too, are you?
He Chu San, are you asking for a beating?
You damn foreign devil,
get the hell out of here!
Last time you came to my place,
you ate and drank for free.
You didn't pay a single cent.
And today you even want to bully Chu San.
I'll beat you to death.
- I'll kill you.
- Fei.
Get lost! Get out!
And you two as well.
You learn nothing good all day long.
What have you dyed your hair into?
- I was wrong.
- Your heads look like feather dusters.
Who do you think you are?
Do you even know who he is?
He's the first college student
from Ganglong Walled City.
He got into the University of Hong Kong
with the top score in the whole city.
If he teaches you anything,
you should go home
and burn incense in gratitude.
If you want to learn,
then learn from our Chu San.
Take your time reading.
Lai Quan!
Don't let me catch you.
If I catch you, it won't just be
about 20,000 bucks anymore.
That bastard.
Where is he?
Where did he go?
Brother Ma, we can't find him.
Can't find him? Then look!
Search! Hurry up!
Fei, I'm off to make deliveries.
Fei, I'm heading out.
Chu San, wait.
Come here.
Take these two portions of beef offal home
and have them with your dad.
Eat more offal. It's good for your health.
- Thank you, Fei.
- You're welcome.
Come on. Carry your backpack.
- Be careful on your way back.
- Okay.
There have been lots of gangsters
causing trouble lately.
Stay safe.
- Got it.
- All right, bye.
Chu San.
Help me take out the trash, thanks..
No problem, Uncle Shun. I'm off.
Are you blind?
I'm really sorry.
Hand over all your money.
- All your cash! Now!
- This isn't my money.
Don't run.
Run? Brat, trying to run?
Do you think you can outrun me?
Hand it over.
The money isn't mine.
Cash! Now!
I'll really kill you.
Give it to me.
Liu Yi.
I invited you to celebrate,
but you didn't come.
Yet, you're here buying others drinks?
Liu Yi.
It's just 20,000.
Liu Yi, you don't have to be so angry.
I'll definitely pay you back soon.
Go to hell.
Go ask around.
When I invite someone over,
no one gets to negotiate.
Liu Yi, I was wrong.
I was wrong, Liu Yi.
I chased you for nine blocks.
Rascal Quan, I finally caught you.
Sorry, I was wrong!
You can't see me, you can't see me...
You can't see me.
Boss.
Boss, why are you here?
Such a small matter
didn't need you to come personally.
I'll let this slide for now.
If you can't handle the other matter either,
don't bother coming back.
I was wrong.
Let's go, Lai Quan.
I'm inviting you to celebrate Children's Day.
Boss.
Boss, slow down.
Wait for us.
This is a year of bad luck.
My end is near.
Boss will definitely beat me to death.
Dad, Mom.
I'm sorry.
Ma here can't fulfill
his duties as your son anymore!
If only I had listened to you back then,
I wouldn't have ended up like this.
Do you need me to call a doctor?
Dad.
The University of Hong Kong?
Yes, Hong Kong.
You're that college student.
Good, good. Just what I needed.
I'm really lucky today.
I'll beat you to death.
So fucking annoying.
Xiao Ma.
Boss.
Where's the dubbing?
This film doesn't have dubbing.
It's just like this.
Get out.
Come back.
Boss.
Who is he?
The screenwriter.
A live one.
Boss.
Come closer.
Do you take me for a three-year-old?
B-Boss, I...
He's just a beef offal vendor.
No, Boss.
H-He's that college student.
The one who was
in the newspaper with fireworks.
Look.
See?
Thank you, thank you.
You're in the way of my boss.
Thank you, Director.
Our walled city finally has a college student.
The He family has produced a top scholar.
Boss, can I make up for my mistake with this?
I don't want to be beaten up.
Lai Quan is next door.
As for what to do,
I don't need to teach you, do I?
Understood.
Sit.
Sit over here.
What are they talking about in there?
"I'll give him an offer he can't refuse."
What about this?
"Leave the rest to me."
You've got some skills.
Eat.
No, thanks.
You little punk.
If he tells you to eat, then eat.
How many times have I told you
not to talk back?
Get lost.
That's enough.
Eat.
Your beef offal is pretty good.
Do you know why I asked you to come today?
To buy beef offal.
Did studying make you stupid?
Have you heard of screenwriters?
I want to make a movie.
Help me write a story.
I majored in finance.
- I can't do it.
- Boss!
Lai Quan is spineless.
He confessed after barely being beaten.
He said his would pay the money.
His is the woman of Fei Qi,
the boss of Hesheng Society.
Lai San Mei.
That Fei Qi treats his woman well...
Cars and houses...
All ten fingers covered in diamond rings.
That bastard has time to sleep with women,
but when Mr. Qing Long invites him to dinner...
What did Lai San Mei say?
Boss, do you know Lai San Mei?
Spit it out!
Fuck! I get even angrier
when I mention that woman!
I called her,
she said she's cut ties with her brother,
then hung up on me.
Damn her!
Bring him here.
Bring him over.
Move.
- Kneel.
- Kneel!
Liu Yi...
My refuses to acknowledge me.
There's nothing I can do.
Liu Yi, I'm begging you! Please let me go!
Pull out his fingernails.
No, Liu Yi.
Please let me go.
- Move.
- Move!
Hold him down.
Don't move.
Another one.
Think it over yourself.
One finger.
I'll help you think.
Three fingers.
Liu Yi, I'll go find my mom.
I'll find my mom.
Liu Yi, please spare me.
Please let me go.
One finger.
Liu Yi, no!
No! No, Liu Yi!
No, Liu Yi!
Wrap up the finger.
Send it to Lai San Mei.
Have her pass a message to Fei Qi.
Tonight at ten,
Qing Long will be
at Fengtai Nightclub waiting for him.
- Move!
Boss, you caught Lai Quan
just to get to Fei Qi, right?
Are you playing games with me here?
Boss, you're truly wise and brave.
You...
I know this kind of job.
I love doing this.
I'm going crazy staying at that film studio.
If I'm not sending you,
it's because I have
something else for you to do.
Who are we chopping down?
Just say the word.
What...
What did you just say?
I-I majored in finance.
And?
I can write scripts.
Good.
Go home.
Stop.
Take the money.
Work for me
and you'll be well paid.
A hundred thousand.
Dad works ten hours a day at the clinic,
charging 5 yuan per patient.
After deducting the cost of medicine,
his net income is about 40 yuan a day.
That's roughly 14,000 a year.
That means Dad alone, working rain or shine,
would have to slog seven years
to earn this much.
A hundred thousand.
Oh my God.
Chu San, you're back.
By the way, I left food on the table.
Why didn't you eat it?
Dad.
I already ate at Fei's place.
This brat made her spend money again.
That's really embarrassing.
Dad.
Dad, I'm sleepy.
I'm going to bed first.
Okay.
Go to bed early.
You should rest early too, Dad.
All right.
You little brat.
No.
I can't take money from the triads.
It would drag Dad into trouble.
Not to mention Dad said
Mom died because of the triads.
If I take their money,
I'm no different from them.
"One Hundred and One Loves."
They want a script.
Then I'll give them a script.
The rest has nothing to do with me.
Ladies, you're off work.
Liu Yi is hosting an important client tonight.
- Happy now?
- Let's go out and have some fun.
Let's go.
Boss, Fei Qi is here.
Lai San Mei is with him, too.
When will Qing Long arrive?
He went to Thailand.
I'm hosting tonight.
Qi.
I've long heard of your reputation.
Qing Long invited me, and he's late himself.
What's that supposed to mean?
You shithead...
Qi.
Qing Long specially prepared
a performance just for you.
But Uncle Yuan suddenly had a heart attack.
Everyone knows that Qing Long
is closest to Uncle Yuan.
As soon as he found out,
he rushed to the hospital.
But he didn't want you to miss
such a wonderful performance.
So, he asked me to host you here.
Even if Qing Long isn't here,
who do you think you are?
Come on, call them in.
Call them in.
Hello, sir.
Since you're already here,
sit down and have some fun.
All right, fine.
Go on.
Qi.
Our nightclub isn't bad, right?
Then about opening
a noodle stall on your turf...
Qi.
Liu Yi, you're here.
I saw the "Closed" sign outside.
I thought some underlings
were slacking off and having fun on their own.
Xu.
Fei Qi is here, too.
Liu Yi.
This is your mistake.
The boss has gone to Thailand.
Qi came to our nightclub.
I should be the one hosting him.
Right, Qi?
What's going on?
Qing Long isn't here.
Xiao Liu.
Are you messing with me?
If Qing Long isn't around,
do you think you can just summon me?
All right, calm down.
This is our turf.
Boss, do we make a move?
Qing Long is here!
- Boss!
- Move, move!
Boss!
- Boss.
- Qi, long time no see.
Something urgent came up before I left.
So, I asked my men to keep you company.
You don't think. I was
deliberately slighting you, do you?
Of course not.
Everyone has times they can't get away.
We're brothers, so don't say such things.
It has to be you...
So magnanimous as always.
Unlike me.
I can never gain weight.
Since you're so busy,
I'll keep it brief.
I asked you here today
to discuss the nightclub's matter.
Whatever you say, we'll do.
I heard recently
you got the top batch of goods from Thailand.
I can even make money lying down.
Of course I'm willing.
However, I have a brother-in-law
named Lai Quan.
Liu Yi told me that his men
grabbed the wrong person.
He was so anxious he didn't know what to do.
So, I told him to come in person
to apologize to you.
Qi, my men caught the wrong person.
That's on me.
I'll punish myself with a drink.
It's a small matter.
Nothing worth mentioning.
It matters.
The Hesheng nightclub business...
He'll be in charge of it in the future.
And the moment he shows up, he offends you.
What kind of start is that?
We're all in good spirits today.
Let's not talk about this nonsense, all right?
Liu Yi, pour Qi a drink.
Okay.
Pour it.
Qi, a great man overlooks petty faults.
I raise a toast to you.
I'll finish it.
Qi, it really was a misunderstanding today.
Work hard, buddy.
You've got a bigshot backing you.
Xiao Ma, see Qi out.
Kun, take the brothers to look around.
Let's go.
Okay.
This way.
Fuck you.
Are you kidding me?
That fatty can really drink.
He drained all my liquor.
Unbelievable.
Big Bro.
Why did you suddenly come back?
Is this nightclub really for me?
You're not doubting your brother, are you?
When have I ever lied to you?
If I hadn't come back early today,
I'd like to see how you'd have wrapped this up.
Big Bro!
I'm lucky, with you backing me up, right?
Besides, the film studio making movies,
the whole money-laundering thing,
should have been handled by Cui Dong Dong.
Bro, what am I?
A gang enforcer.
I should be the one
charging into battle for you.
All for taking over territories.
I get bored staying in the film studio all day.
Listen.
Although the nightclub is yours,
the film studio is your primary responsibility.
One month.
I'll give you a month.
Get the movie done.
Oversee it personally.
Also, spend some time with Xiao Man.
No, bro!
The studio is really boring.
Every time I'm in the studio, I feel like...
Big Bro!
Bro, are you okay?
I'm fine.
I've just been too busy.
Just a little tired.
You've worked hard.
Thanks, bro.
I just want what's best for you, too.
I've told you many times.
Always tie your tie properly
when wearing a suit.
You never listen.
You rebellious kid.
I'm leaving.
Bro, get some rest.
Goodbye.
Boss, do we still have to
go back to the film studio?
Are you stupid?
The movie must be made.
This is our big brother's order.
But...
With the director you found...
Can he finish filming in a month?
What does he do?
Has he won the Oscars or awards?
Got it!
We only need ten days to make the movie.
The rest of the time,
we can come to the nightclub
and continue partying.
Do you want to die?
- Boss!
- I'll kick you into your grave!
- Don't run!
- Boss!
Hao Cheng Qing.
For a pretty boy,
you've trampled on me,
your buddy who's been with you
through thick and thin.
♪ The midnight bell just rang ♪
♪ The neon lights are flickering ♪
♪ Who's seeking escape in a drink? ♪
♪ Who's causing trouble on the dance floor? ♪
♪ When the music plays, don't think too much ♪
♪ Your body starts moving uncontrollably ♪
♪ All your troubles are drowned out ♪
♪ Follow the rhythm, dance like crazy ♪
Awesome. You're awesome.
I'm not going to the nightclub.
I'm not going.
Let go of me, let go!
♪ Who cares about tomorrow at this moment? ♪
Boss.
Boss!
I brought this guy.
Any other orders?
Go have fun.
All right.
I'm here.
Let's have fun!
College student.
It's been three days.
Where's the script?
The Little Mermaid.
To see the human prince again,
she made a deal with the sea witch.
She painfully gave up her tail.
Fin.
You read.
She traded it for legs to walk on land.
When she stepped onto land,
every step felt like being cut by a knife.
Speak louder.
She still hoped to find the prince.
But she didn't know
the shadow over this port city
was ruled by a terrifying
dual-blade mafia boss.
The mafia boss controls
the city's underground dealings.
This boss also wields dual blades?
Isn't that impressive?
Why hide it?
Stop being sneaky with me.
Scheming behind my back.
College student.
Money isn't made this way.
Rewrite it.
- Got it.
- Now.
♪ The midnight bell just rang ♪
♪ The neon lights are flickering ♪
I'm studying finance.
I don't know how to write scripts.
♪ Who's seeking escape in a drink? ♪
♪ Who's causing trouble on the dance floor? ♪
♪ When the music plays, don't think too much ♪
♪ Your body starts moving uncontrollably ♪
♪ All your troubles are drowned out ♪
♪ Follow the rhythm, dance like crazy ♪
♪ Your heartbeat's about to explode ♪
♪ The alcohol burns it away ♪
♪ Who cares about tomorrow at this moment? ♪
Freaking hell.
Who is it?
Boss!
Qing Long is going
to the film studio to check in.
His wife is coming, too.
She's already on the way.
Hurry, wake them up.
Get up!
- Back to the studio.
- I have class.
Let's go. Ten minutes.
What class?
You've got 10 minutes. Write a new story.
Otherwise, I'll beat you up.
Wait a minute.
Hurry up!
Otherwise, I'll treat you to Children's Day.
Assistant director! Move it!
Hurry up, hurry up!
All departments, hurry up!
Get to work.
Be quick.
- This side too, be quick.
- Hurry up, hurry up.
Faster.
Everyone, move!
Boss.
- Boss.
- Assistant director.
Here, here, here.
Come on!
Xiao Ma, help me check my clothes.
Boss, Ma'am.
Boss.
- Boss.
- Come over here.
- Come on over.
Take Ma'am for makeup.
This way. We're going to take makeup photos.
Boss, this way.
Please have a seat.
Where's Liu Yi?
Liu Yi is taking the screenwriter
to get inspiration.
Write the script.
I heard he's been hanging out at Lan Kai Feng.
That's not true.
I'm grateful that Liu Yi
takes me everywhere for inspiration.
Otherwise, I couldn't have
written such a good story.
That's nothing.
Qing Long wants Liu Yi to make a movie.
It has to be an Oscar-worthy one.
Don't worry.
If you need anything
in the future, just tell me.
I will definitely help.
Bro! What are you doing here?
Dressed like Chow Yun Fat, too.
I came to check on your Oscar-winning movie.
How's the preparation going?
Very simple.
Xiao Man also wanted to go out for a walk, too.
Sis.
Don't scare her.
The doctor said she can't be frightened now.
What did the doctor say?
Same as before.
Her mind is getting more and more confused.
Medication doesn't help.
She often mistakes people.
Sometimes, she doesn't even recognize me.
Is he the screenwriter?
Let me introduce him.
A top student from HKU.
Known as a drama-loving genius.
He loves creating.
A drama-loving genius.
Talk about your script.
Read it.
A carefree and unruly gangster
falls in love with a fallen, beautiful woman.
After a romantic love
that moves heaven and earth...
The woman is taken by a rival gang.
The rival gang, who has long coveted her,
seizes the opportunity
while the gangster is off guard
and abducts her with overwhelming force,
intending to use her
as leverage and humiliation.
One man, dual blades, cuts down forty people.
This plot sounds like...
Liu Yi saving Qing Long.
In the end, the gangster
and the beautiful woman
live happily ever after.
Hey! Why are you making things up?
- Are you asking for trouble?
- I think it's great.
Let's film it this way.
After Xiao Man finishes the makeup photos,
I'll pick you up for dinner at the villa.
No, bro.
His script is so...
I've said it many times.
If you wear a suit and tie,
make sure it's done properly.
What? Did you expect me
to create something out of nothing?
Rebellious kid.
I'm leaving.
Take care, bro.
Xiao Ma.
Take him down for a check.
Got it.
If there's no fracture,
keep him writing the script.
Get up.
- Let's go.
- Get up.
Gangsters are all villains.
Xia Liu Yi is a villain among villains.
I've skipped class these past two days.
I bet my scholarship is gone, too.
Next year's tuition...
Am I supposed to ask Dad for it?
He works so hard...
You wrote this?
It's really well written.
What's wrong?
You okay?
I'm fine.
Who did this?
It was Xia Liu Yi.
Liu Yi's misbehaving again.
- I'll go talk to him for you.
- No, no, no.
Really, there's no need.
You have to tell me.
He's always like this.
He can't make any friends.
But don't blame him.
He just has no one to play with.
Back then, he was very pitiful.
It was just him and me.
Are you the female lead?
Why aren't you filming?
Filming?
What's so good about filming?
No matter how much I film,
he won't watch it.
I thought...
I love him.
And he loves me, too.
That's supposed to be what love between us is.
But...
I heard you're a drama-loving genius.
You're very good at writing about love, right?
A drama-loving genius?
He's just making it up.
Then can you tell me...
What is love?
Love...
Sis.
Time for the photos. We're waiting for you.
That's "Ma'am" for you.
Liu Yi.
You can't hit people.
That's not good.
Okay, fine.
I was wrong.
I won't do it again.
You're the best behaved boy.
All right. Let's go take photos.
We've been waiting for you.
Let's go.
Then next time...
Next time, tell me the answer.
I'm watching you closely.
Okay, fine.
Let's go take the photos.
Let's go.
[Children's Day]
I should go looking for inspiration.
Just like a dog.
Bark, bark, bark.
What is love?
Love is having someone
willing to risk everything for you,
even give up their life,
just to save you from danger.
Someone not afraid of getting hurt.
Not afraid of pain.
They might even risk their life.
They'll stand up for you when you're helpless,
and step forward bravely.
They'll hold you tight
when you're on the brink of despair.
Time to eat.
Let's eat.
Food's here!
Time to eat, boss.
Eat first, then play.
- Come eat.
- Time to eat.
Time to eat.
Time to eat!
He Chu San.
- Come eat, now.
- Okay, got it.
Boss!
Are you okay?
If one day,
someone like this appears in your life,
don't hesitate for a second.
Don't run away.
Use all your strength.
Hold onto them tightly.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Boss, how are you?
Boss, are you okay?
How about you?
Are you hurt?
Because their eyes will tell you one thing.
"I love you."
Boss, I'll shut them up.
Don't bother.
This is a happy moment.