So scary!
What just happened?
[eerie sound]
It looks like everyone
came back to life.
- Yeah.
- Crazy.
But we all resonated with
Haumea and chose despair,
so it's not like
we should be happy.
All we can do is
watch over her.
She still gets to make
her own choice.
EPISODE 25"HERO'S TALE"
[HAUMEA]
Why are you doing this?
It will happen all over again.
Despair will gather once more,
and another Great Cataclysm
will begin.
We fought so hard
to escape hell.
All you've done is cause
our suffering to continue.
No, it's not like that.
And what makes this time
any different?
As long as human life exists,
the fear of death
can never be escaped.
Our consciousness
creates despair.
That's how it will always be.
I can't disagree.
Then tell me why.
Because I changed things.
It's better now.
What do you mean?
What exactly did you change?
[HAJIKI] Something
feels kind of different.
Is it me?
Hajiki, you're back!
I'm so happy!
Oh, no!
You're way too big to just
glomp people out of nowhere.
Hold up, what happened to me?
Oh, you're freaking me out.
Oh, my arm grew back.
Now I'm freaking
myself out! [screaming]
What's going on?
This is madness.
Oh, jeez.
I guess there's only
one explanation.
Am I dead?
I don't remember.
Could you guys tell me
if I died or not?
Yes, and I'm the one
who killed you.
Uh-huh.
I think it's starting
to come back to me now.
When we first met, right?
Indeed.
I struck quickly.
I see.
It's fine.
I can't sweat the small
stuff, you know.
How is he so cute?
AND THEN?
- I'm Orochi.
- Yeah?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Hajiki.
Killing him isn't
a deal breaker, huh?
This is quite strange.
Last I remember,
I was being burned
to death by a black flame.
I got my life and arm back,
even if it doesn't stay on.
Hmm.
Oh, well.
Works for me.
[scream]
Captain!
Maki, what's wrong with me?
- Your neck!
- Oh, my.
It's, uh--
PEEL
When I came to, my neck felt
weak, but I didn't know why.
Try flexing it.
Hell, yeah!
Something isn't right.
Everyone is far too laid back.
For a second there, I thought
I was the only one who noticed.
Everything feels off.
The world has changed.
It's formed from
a whole new image.
Depending on your perspective,
this could be pure madness.
[HAUMEA] I don't understand.
What could you possibly have
done to conquer despair?
I resurrected the world,
but made one big change.
I made life just
a little less precious.
But what does
that accomplish?
You said that when the value of
each person's soul increased,
so did their fear of dying.
So I changed death.
Now, it's something
a little more familiar,
maybe even friendly.
[HAUMEA] And you think that
will bring an end to despair?
I'll let you decide
if you want to start over
in this world or not.
If you think it's that bad,
I'll turn everything here
to dust and do it over again.
But why don't you
try enjoying life?
She's going to choose
despair again.
Brother, it's like the tale
of when the sun hid in a cave.
Have a little faith.
What's this?
I'm here, it's Charon.
Do you still hear
the voices of despair?
I know the agony that
lives inside humanity's
collective unconscious.
I've felt their suffering
through you,
Haumea, many times.
But to tell you the truth,
that never troubled me,
no matter how much despair
they felt.
I didn't care about them
because the suffering
you went through hurt me
more than the suffering
of everyone else combined.
That's why I wanted to start
the Great Cataclysm so quickly,
not for mankind,
but to set you free
from all of that pain.
Or that's what I thought.
But even then,
there was one regret
I couldn't seem to shake.
I didn't want to die
because I had never once
seen you smile, Haumea.
Every day,
you were always crying
from the depths of your heart.
The world's end
may be the climax,
but that doesn't mean
you have to crymax too.
PFFT
That was a good one.
If you don't want to smile,
that's fine.
But please show me
your face at least.
[HAUMEA] This isn't fair.
Shinra Bansho,
using Charon against me?
You cheater.
She's too cute.
It's all right.
It's a new beginning
for us all.
It's a new world--
new me and new you.
There's absolutely
no such thing as absolutes.
But I absolutely swear
you won't regret this.
You'll be glad you were born
into the world of death.
Just trust me.
You want me to abandon
the collective unconscious
and enjoy my life?
It's as simple as that?
Simple as that.
But I can't.
There's still
so much despair left.
Where will it go?
It's never going
to catch on in this world.
Time for you to go.
Now get out there
and live again.
Who could have ever guessed
that Haumea would choose
to live after all?
So what's next?
All the despair
was washed away,
so I suppose I'll go with it.
- I think I'll choose oblivion.
- Amaterasu!
Going back to life after all
these years would feel wrong.
You don't mean that.
I'm the doppelganger.
I shouldn't get to stay alive
while you fade away.
That's nonsense.
No matter what happened,
your eyes were
always brimming with hope.
Even your decision
to choose death with us
was only
because of the sympathy
you had for me and Haumea.
Iris, please, choose life
and live on in my stead--
Or rather, live life enough
for me too.
Even though
I'm nothing but a fake?
What about you?
I lived through the time
before the Cataclysm
and through the world
of flames as well.
Now, in the world of death
and souls,
I can live once more?
I don't think anyone, even me,
needs to exist
across three realities.
Fair point.
Wait, before I go,
I want to thank you for shining
your light on all of us--
on the whole world.
You're not a fake, Iris.
In fact, you're the me
I always wanted to become.
I'm so glad you're OK.
Glad to be here.
I'm back too, you know.
Thanks for giving
this world a try.
Well, I tried death first,
but it wasn't much fun at all.
Good.
You've finally done it.
It was a hard-won victory.
No, this isn't over yet.
Your lives are
an abomination.
They cannot continue.
Death shall claim them.
Huh?
That's no fair.
We just came back to life.
Brother,
what is this creature?
It's the last piece of
the puzzle this world needs
if we want to survive.
He's our god.
It looks a bit creepy to me.
People make up gods and use
them as an excuse to be cruel.
So I beat 'em to it
and made a real one.
I wanted a god
that was irrefutable,
so I manifested this guy
into our world--
a god who rules over death.
It's a skull.
Yeah, it is.
All right, God, we're ready.
We will accept your judgment.
That is a fine attitude.
Now die.
I won't be
needing it anymore.
The powers that
you possess were far too great
for any human.
Therefore,
I retrieve them from you.
I can see seven powers
with you.
Are they the Adolla Bursts?
How can that be when there
are only five pillars present?
I'm God.
I can retrieve them from those
who are not here as well.
Some weird light
just came out of me.
Something bothering you?
Although I could not retrieve
the eighth one
since it's not on this planet.
Even God has his limits.
FOOLS
Ow!
Why'd you flick me?
Did you not predict that?
Hang on.
I didn't see it, no.
I don't have everyone's
thoughts going
through my head either.
I don't have ignition
powers anymore?
It's not just
all you pillars.
It seems as though
I've lost my powers as well.
So could that mean--
[ALL] There's no more
spontaneous human combustion
in our world?
Well, then, I suppose I'll
go ahead and disappear now.
Thanks for everything.
And just where
exactly will you go?
It'll be somewhere
you'd expect gods to be.
I'll create a place with
the appropriate vibe
and stay there.
But if anything happens,
summon me.
Reach me at 4242564.
Toodle-oo!
Wait!
Uh.
Why am I sensing this
overwhelmingly relaxed aura?
It's fun, don't you think?
Or not?
Well, I don't believe
it's a bad thing.
Both of you
have done so well.
I'm so proud of you.
She's still in that form.
I know.
I don't look very
motherly like this,
but the world is different now.
Appearances aren't the same
kind of issue, are they?
Excuse me,
are you Shinra's mother?
Yes, that'd be me.
I'm Inca,
and this little cutie is Iris.
We're Shinra's girlfriends.
Say what now?
What are you talking about?
You're dating both of them?
You've got the wrong idea.
[INCA]
Oh, it's all right, mama.
Shinra's the superhero who
saved the entire world.
He can have
a girlfriend or three.
I don't even care
which number I am.
Is that how you feel
about it too, Shinra?
Well, anyway, now that
things have settled down,
why don't we go meet up
with the rest of the 8th?
Sounds good to me.
[SHINRA]
Using knowledge from
people like Licht and Vulcan,
we rebuilt the world.
Almost.
I mean, a lot of things
are very different
from how they used to be.
But you've still got
a place to come home to.
I'll be waiting for you,
old buddy.
Special Fire Force Company 8,
fire soldier Shinra Kusakabe
reporting back from duty.
The flames of spontaneous
human combustion
have all been extinguished.
I don't know
when it started,
but instead of tension
forcing my smile,
now, I do it naturally.
No, I do know.
It's when the boy called
"devil" found hope.
The same day I joined the 8th.
And I'm still smiling.
FIRE FORCE
THE END
[Japanese music]
♪ ♪
FIRE FORCE
EPILOGUE
[TAKERU gasps]
[TAMAKI] It's kind of hard to
believe that there are cities
like this outside of Tokyo.
I guess this is how
the world used to be
before the Great Cataclysm.
No human combustion
now either.
It's so peaceful,
it feels unreal.
[TAKERU] Being on a date
with you feels unreal to me.
I've never been this happy.
I guess it's not that bad.
Oh, dear.
I wonder how everyone's
doing now that the Fire Force
has been disbanded.
From what I hear, they've
been doing expeditions.
Nobody has ignition
powers anymore.
But they say that some people
have gotten even stronger.
The ones with
crazy strong souls
are extra scary these days.
WORLD HERO FORCE,
COMMANDER-IN-CHIEF
OBI AKITARU
They say Captain
Commander Obi can practically
flip a mountain with one hand.
And that's not all.
The ones who are stronger than
him, those guys leveled up too.
AIDE TO
THE HIGH BATTLE COMMANDER
SAGAMIYA KONRO
WORLD HERO FORCE,
HIGH BATTLE COMMANDER
SHINMON BENIMARU
I wonder what they're doing.
Like, what's the point
of the expedition?
There's way more
to the new world than Tokyo,
so they're exploring.
Commander in Chief Obi,
we pinpointed the location
of that giant monster.
It's been wild
since that day.
So, of course, we're after
some huge 100-meter snake.
Shinra cooked up a doozy
when he remade this world.
Speaking of, where are
Shinra and the others?
They're scouting about
20 kilometers ahead.
Rekka.
Thanks, guys, for real.
You're off duty today,
so I appreciate this.
The main force has things
covered for us.
So you're actually
really going to go?
I'll be setting out
into our great big new world,
starting my journey
to master martial arts.
Shinra's doing it again, huh?
That's right.
He's gone out chasing
after her again.
Seeing my favorite
be so popular with the ladies
makes me feel so giddy inside.
Seriously?
Hold on a second.
Didn't you have a massive
crush on him too?
Shinra is my favorite
no matter what he does.
And as his hardcore fan,
I have to forgive him, right?
I'm not sure
it works like that.
He's the entire
world's hero now,
so I do realize that I can't
keep him all to myself forever.
At this point, it's not like
romance is everything to me.
So I'm not going to get jealous
and upset over small stuff.
That'd be silly.
Shinra really is
something special, though.
I hope he'll be
coming back home soon.
The monster is on the other
side of that mountain, huh?
From what I hear,
it's some kind of giant snake
that's over 100 meters long.
Sounds pretty crazy.
Well, you turned this
into a crazy world, didn't you?
It's a fun one, though.
Where's Arthur and Excalibur?
They're down at the foot
of the mountain.
Some quick thing
to take care of.
[SHINRA]
I guess we should go get him.
I don't think he can
find his own way back.
I mean, he was up
in space for a long time
before he finally made it home.
[adventurous music]
♪ ♪
Arthur, you about done here?
Yeah, I've paid my respects.
Good.
So I'll be facing
a hydra, will I?
Sounds exciting to me.
Well, somebody might
actually die this time.
Yeah, sounds rough to me.
Ain't that right, Excalibur?
You are going to die.
I see the shadow
of death following you
into the next world.
Man, shut up.
He somehow makes
Arthur seem normal.
Well, we better
wrap this up quick
and get Vice Commander
Hinawa back home.
I don't want Maki's pops
getting mad at me.
Her dad.
You know, those two are
pretty clingy these days.
No one really knows
what's going to happen next.
So you just gotta go
for what you want.
There's no time to waste.
What about you?
What did I just say?
Hey, it's the dimwit trio.
I was starting to worry.
I was kind of afraid that you
would stop chasing after me.
Inca?
I should have known
you're the one
who summoned that giant snake.
So tell me, Shinra, have you
thought about what I asked you?
There's no way in hell
that I'm going
to give you what you want.
But why?
It's not cool to be so stingy.
I just want your baby, Shinra.
- That's all.
- Bow-wow-wow.
Come on, you know
that I'm with Iris now.
Huh?
Listen, you are way too boring
for me to want
to be with you like that, OK?
Yucky.
[SHINRA] What do you mean?
I thought you loved me!
The only thing I want is
for you to put a baby in me!
Wh-- what are
you even saying?
That's like,
such an insane thing to say.
I'm not going to do
anything like that.
Why not?
All we need to do
is ask Licht,
and I'm sure
he could make it happen.
[SHINRA] That's not
exactly what I mean.
[INCA] I want to have
the child of the hero
who saved the world.
You'll have more, so what's the
harm of letting me have one?
You tell me.
Why do you want one anyway?
It's pretty simple, really.
These days, we're
in a world based on death.
And that means the value
of life is way different.
So I'm just hoping to have
something that really
connects me to the future.
He saved the world too.
I bet Arthur could
give you what you want.
Hey, now,
don't pawn this off on me.
No dummies, please.
Ha!
In your face, Shinra.
She's talking
about you, you dummy.
I've wanted to die
as long as I can remember.
But since
you changed the world,
I've actually
gotten into living.
So thank you for saving
me in every possible way.
And that's why
I want to continue
your legacy with the baby.
Can I, please?
Hmm.
I'm gonna say no.
Ugh.
After all this,
you're still no fun.
Fine, until you say it's OK,
I guess I'm going to keep
being a witch
and causing some mayhem.
Even though you're still such a
pill, this world you've created
has been a real blast.
So thanks for that, too, hero.
Yeah, of course.
[laughter]
25 YEARS LATER
[laughter fading]
[music playing]
WORLD HERO FORCE,
SUPREME LEADER KUSAKABE SHINRA
[42]
Good morning,
Supreme Commander.
There's a message for you.
President Obi has sent you
a congratulatory telegram.
I'm happy he found time
in his busy schedule.
And you've got family
joining the hero force.
I won't lie and say
I'm not worried,
but it's still very exciting.
Live life passionately,
and you won't have any regrets.
So death's not all
that big of a deal.
Life's truly a gift.
Let's be dumb
and have lots of fun.
And with that
as our motto,
our souls are going to burn
brighter than ever before.
Let's see here, a child of God
in human form.
How is this kid
going to turn out?
I know.
Let's start by making him
resemble the hero
who saved the world
from despair.
Yes!
Hey, there kid.
[Japanese singing]
♪ ♪
And so a new world
free from despair
was created for all of us.
[Japanese singing]
♪ ♪