Officail Website : kissasian.be  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
♪ Hold me tight,
let the darkness drown me ♪
♪ Even one second of truth is enough
to lose myself in it ♪
♪ Hold me tight,
let the darkness drown me ♪
♪ Even one second of truth is enough
to lose myself in it ♪
♪ Whether you're light or a lie,
I can't pull myself away ♪
♪ In this game,
truth or lie no longer matters ♪
[Queen of Darkness]
[Episode 4]
You're really playful.
Dad, don't drink too much.
Alright, let's eat first.
Sis.
Wait, what's going on?
An Ning.
You scheming woman.
How dare you set me up!
You and your son tried to hurt someone,
but it backfired.
You deserve it.
So desperate for attention, huh?
Today,
you'll be the star clown here.
You...
That's enough!
Everyone's watching.
Don't embarrass yourself here.
I'll...
You, a cheating, abusive mama's boy.
Dare to speak up?
People are picking on me.
But you're not gonna help, whatever.
Your sister even sent you deer whip
to insult you,
yet you're still eager to please her.
Are you really that incompetent?
So you're grateful to her.
I swear I'll end you!
I...
Inspector Huo.
She's my wife.
Why are you standing so close to her?
What exactly are you trying to do?
I didn't do anything.
But your wife seems a bit drunk.
Well
want me to help get her to her room?
Wait, she's my wife.
I'll take her myself.
I'll do it myself.
Let's go.
Go.
Steward.
Young Master.
I'll take Young Madam back to her room.
Come on.
To win me over,
Song Pa really went all out.
Since she's already a gift,
I might as well see
what's hidden
beneath the wrapping.
What are you trying to do?
That should be my question.
Lying in my bed
in the middle of the night.
What do you expect me to do?
That family flatters you so much.
They even offered their daughter-in-law
to please you.
It's disgusting.
Why blame me instead of
the one who sent you here?
You're all the same kind.
You're no better than them.
Since you said that,
if I don't act a little wild,
your anger would be wasted, huh?
After all, I'm your
your sister-in-law.
You can't do this.
Whether you're really my sister-in-law
remains to be seen.
But now,
you're a gift someone sent over.
So, should I accept it
or not?
♪ I'm losing myself. I'm losing ♪
♪ I'm losing myself tonight ♪
So the shares of Longxing Group
are also part of the gift?
Xiao.
You're the inspector here.
Only you
can resolve this issue.
Longxing Group
was also built from
your father's hard work.
Just do something.
You took over the company
from An Yuan back then.
And you treated Huo family quite well.
Don't worry.
I won't let my own interests be harmed.
Deleting it is useless.
I already have a backup.
If you don't want the truth to leak,
(Watch on www.kisskh.at to support Admin)
Then you'd better let me go.
Do you really think a recording
can threaten me?
I'm not sure if it can threaten you,
but it will definitely affect
what you're planning to do.
Dad, Mom.
Look what I found.
What is it?
Open it and see.
Isn't that An Ning?
But the outfit and her vibe...
Of course not.
This is
the recently returned young lady
of the Qingyun Gang.
The gang leader's daughter.
Ye Ying.
She looks exactly like
that scheming woman.
Yeah, totally.
Super fishy.
But what's even stranger is
that the Qingyun leader,
Ye Hong, was just killed,
and Ye Ying had a car accident the same
day An Ning did.
This is...
So
The one in our house
with her amnesia
and changed personality.
Could it be a different person now?
Auntie.
I made this little cake myself.
I wanted you to have some.
What I did before was wrong.
I'm here to apologize.
No need for that.
Just don't do it again next time.
What's going on here?
Auntie won't eat the cake.
She just refuses to forgive me.
An Ning, we're family.
Your nephew put so much effort into
making that cake.
At least have a bite.
Yeah.
It's really good.
An Ning is severely allergic
to strawberries.
If you're not allergic,
then you're not An Ning.
Put me down.
Huo Xiao.
You're getting way too bold.
Aren't you afraid I'll call everyone over
and expose you as the scumbag
forcing himself on his sister-in-law?
Do you really think
I wouldn't notice you swiping.
An Ning's file from my room?
You'd better not
play the fool with me anymore.
I'm tired of it.
[An Ning, Case History]
What does that prove?
I just want to understand my past.
Is it wrong to try to
recover my memories?
Of course it's not.
Then how do you explain
faking the allergy?
The facts are the explanation.
Fine.
Then let me see it with my own eyes.
Stare again and I'll gouge your eyes out.
Such a useless brat.
All you know is how to play around.
Good for nothing.
But I did as I was told.
I gave Auntie the cake with cherry jam.
You said cherry jam?
I told you to use strawberry jam.
But strawberry isn't as tasty as cherry.
I get it now.
That sneaky woman was just acting.
She was faking the allergy
in front of everyone.
But how did she know I was testing her?
Wait.
If you're Ye Ying,
then An Ning is missing.
That means
the 20% shares An Ning holds
will be inherited by Ti Cha.
Ye Ying.
I wonder if you'll be able to
keep your secret
when you return to the Qingyun Gang.
These clothes aren't my style.
And the shoes aren't even my size.
The underwear size is wrong too.
According to the records,
An Ning is a housewife.
Timid
and weak.
But I have a hot temper.
[An Ning's personal habits and likes]
and I know how to fight.
So,
I can't be her.
Longxing Group was taken from
the An family by Song Pa.
The cause of An Ning's father's death
was suspicious.
Song Pa must be involved somehow.
I hold shares in Longxing Group.
So they definitely won't let me go.
Huo Xiao also seems to
suspect my identity.
Officail Website : kissasian.be  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
So, who am I really?
What's really going on behind all this?
♪ Mist coils around the sleeping forest ♪
♪ Memories scattered
through cracks of darkness ♪
♪ How to escape this real-feeling dream ♪
♪ Lies reflect in water's gleam ♪
♪ Traces of existence
can never be erased ♪
♪ How to find the self I can't reclaim ♪
♪ Fly away, hear she says ♪
♪ She'll fly out from
thorns of woven lies ♪
♪ Pierce the fog,
shatter this dream tonight ♪
♪ Burn like fire ♪
♪ Just burn like fire ♪
♪ The maze in the abyss starts to clear ♪
♪ Yet night keep on whispering ♪
♪ Surrender to fate,
no clear direction ahead ♪
♪ She will rise as the dawn
that breaks the darkness ♪
♪ Never slowing down,
for tomorrow cannot be stopped ♪
♪ Surrender to love and find the way ♪
♪ Even if fate tries to forget her ♪
♪ Never despair,
for the heart burns with endless light ♪
♪ Waiting for dawn ♪
[Copyright of this short drama
belongs to]
[Shanghai Chuqi Weishi
Culture Media Co., Ltd.]
[and Youku Information Technology (Beijing)
[Co., Ltd.]
[Youku Information Technology (Beijing)
[holds exclusive global online
and broadcast rights]