Pardon?
Pi Han Ul?
Yes.
You don't seem to know yet.
You should never try to know more about him.
You might die.
- Pardon?
- When I say, "die,"
it's not figurative. It's literal.
Be careful.
Why did you want to see me?
[Study - Join if you want to study!]
[Hwang Min Hyun]
[Han Ji Eun]
[Cha Woo Min]
[Lee Jong Hyun]
[Shin Su Hyun]
[Yoon Sang Jung / Gong Do Yu]
[Study Group]
- This is it, right?
- Yes.
You're sure, right?
I'm telling you.
Do you want to do it?
It obviously has to be you.
No, you can go, too.
It's okay. Go before I change my mind.
Right. Before you change your mind.
By the way, what was the name again?
Ji Wu. Lee Ji Wu.
W-What are you doing?
I don't know what Lee Ji Wu looks like.
You can ask.
- Hurry. Go.
- Hold on. Hold on.
- A little later.
- That's enough.
Hey, Lee Ji Wu!
There. Someone called her.
Hey, let's give up on Lee Ji Wu.
Why?
She's Lee Hyeon Wu's twin sister.
F*** you.
There's no way she signed up for the study group.
Crazy bitch. You're so brave.
Did I tell you to put the lunch menu on my desk or not?
Why do you ignore me and ruin my mood?
What's this?
You printed the menu and didn't put it on my desk?
No, that's...
Midterm preparation plan?
You idiots are trying so f***ing hard.
Shit.
How dare you f***ing look at me like that?
I said you can only hit me.
Let go.
Let go, you f***ing bitch.
Let go, you bitch!
F***! You're pissing me off.
Hey.
I'll kill you if you don't put the lunch menu on my desk by the next period.
[Midterm preparation plan]
Why would you bitches bother studying?
What the heck?
When did he leave?
- What's with you?
- Wow, nicely planned.
What's with you, I asked.
She highlighted each subject.
- I should try that, too.
- What are you, you loser?
Why is it so noisy here?
Gyu Jin,
the thing is...
You're the prettiest when your mouth is kept shut, Mi Hee.
Aren't you Yun Ga Min, who knocked down Lee Hyeon Wu?
By the way,
what are you doing with my girlfriend?
Is she your girlfriend?
- I wanted to talk to her.
- I know.
She's my girlfriend.
I'm sorry.
- Let's go.
- Why?
This is about a study group-
- Let's go right now.
- Why?
Did you talk to another man, Ji Wu?
You should be scolded, then.
- Put your hands out.
- Get lost.
Why?
Are you embarrassed because of other kids?
Crazy bastard.
I told you not to stand out.
Just take three hits, Ji Wu.
Or do you want to do something cute?
I'll forgive you, then.
Just hit me.
Gum?
You said she's your girlfriend.
Cocky bastard.
You think you're somebody since you beat Lee Hyeon Wu?
Your neck will get snapped unless you duck.
Hey, Kim Gyu Jin!
What are you doing?
Didn't you hear the Disciplinary Committee is assembling?
Why don't you get your butt over here?
I'll see you again soon, 10th grader.
Do you even want to have a quiet school life?
Of course, I do.
Yet you threw gum at the disciplinary committee member's face?
Are you crazy?
I didn't know he was on the disciplinary committee.
He's in front of the gate every morning.
You didn't know that?
And I couldn't just let a study group member get beaten.
Is she already a member?
I don't know. Anyway, we're in trouble.
Our lives will be difficult since we messed with the disciplinary committee.
The application for the study group...
I submitted it under Ji Wu's name.
- Why?
- The thing is...
Ji Wu is being bullied.
Hey, isn't Gyu Jin so f***ing handsome?
F***! He's so my type.
Handsome, my foot.
He looks just like the MacArthur statue in the park.
That's how I became a target within my first week at this school.
I'll pay you back soon.
- Hey, what do you want to do?
- Karaoke. Let's go to a karaoke.
Karaoke?
Shit, let go!
Geez, it f***ing hurts. Shit.
Hey, Lee Ji Wu!
Is Ji Wu being bullied because she defended me?
Huh?
I didn't ask that yet.
Could you ask me?
Yes.
Is Ji Wu being bullied because she defended you?
No.
Isn't that unexpected?
Y-Yes.
No one could challenge Ji Wu.
Thanks to that, I stopped being bullied, too. Yes.
Is that it?
Something happened soon after.
I don't know the details.
Ji Wu's brother, Hyeon Wu, was on the job delivering something important.
But I guess there was an accident.
You want to borrow money?
Yes.
Okay.
Under one condition.
Kim Gyu Jin started threatening Ji Wu using that video of Hyeon Wu.
She normally hates her brother,
but he's still the only family member she has left.
That's when she started getting bullied, too.
And I've been receiving help from Ji Wu all this time.
So, I want to be helpful to her this time.
Before I transfer.
- Transfer?
- Yes.
I couldn't tell Ji Wu yet.
I'm moving because of my dad's job.
Oh, okay.
So, I know I'm shameless, but let me ask you just one favor.
Please delete that video.
And study with Ji Wu instead of me from now on.
Would that be okay?
You said our lives would get difficult.
What? Why are you pushing responsibility now?
Excuse me.
I beg you.
Okay. Our lives are already difficult.
- Okay.
Let's help Ji Wu only focus on studying.
- Really?
- Yes.
By the way, where's that video?
What video is it that Lee Ji Wu became powerless?
It must be something big since it made Lee Ji Wu submit.
Huh?
- Isn't this it?
- Hey, let me see.
Let me see. Let me see.
This is it.
I saw them waving this in front of Lee Ji Wu.
Play it now!
Hurry up and play it.
Hold on. What is it, anyway?
[Lee Ji Wu]
Look at you, bastards.
Not the Disciplinary Committee room.
Why not?
Because it's the Disciplinary Committee room.
So, what about it?
Right.
The Disciplinary Committee room is a bit...
Right?
Why?
Because the Disciplinary Committee is a gang approved by the school.
A gang approved by the school?
They're officially allowed to act like thugs
while controlling the bad kids.
That's why most kids don't even go near the Disciplinary Committee room.
Gosh, bastards.
Are you that curious about this?
Do you want to watch it?
The thing is...
I do, but...
- Go ahead.
- Really?
Watch it yourselves, you bastards.
I'll upload it on GoTube.
GoTube? I thought you promised not to release it.
Why don't you pay back the money you borrowed from losers?
Why would I pay them back?
Right. Only losers keep promises.
And think about it, you bastard.
If Ji Wu's last family member goes to the juvenile hall,
she'd be so sad.
You'll attack her while she's vulnerable?
Her boyfriend would be the only one to rely on.
And I didn't even give him a loan with my money.
Whose is it, then?
It's his.
What do you mean by that?
You don't have to know.
Seriously, Han Ul is a genius.
Why do you ask me where Hyeon Wu is?
I heard you were close to him.
I'm not.
I'm not close to anyone.
I heard he borrowed money from Kim Gyu Jin and never paid him back.
- Maybe he ran away?
- He borrowed that money because of you, too.
Because of me?
Who says that?
Didn't he end up that way because he got into an accident
while running an errand for you?
What would I get by doing that?
If you tell him to,
he even breaks into his homeroom teacher's house, destroys things, and threatens me.
He became that desperate.
Han Ul,
you used him enough.
Let Hyeon Wu go now.
Is that all?
Is that the only reason you wanted to see me?
I heard you were starting a study group at a school like this.
I thought you'd be a very interesting person.
But you aren't.
Ms. Lee,
if Lee Hyeon Wu doesn't come to school,
just ignore it.
It's much easier to give up on the low lives.
Han Ul.
It's f***ing stupid that she's doing that for her brother.
She should give up on a piece of trash like him.
Some people might seem hopeless,
but that doesn't mean you can give up on them.
What's that?
What was that noise?
Shit, you scared me. What's this psycho doing?
Wow, were you hiding in there?
Oh, I see.
Lee Ji Wu told you to steal the USB drive, right?
That f***ing cunning thing used a man?
Wait...
by chance,
do you have a crush on her?
How dare you ambush like a coward?
Why does this loser keep getting in the way?
Did he do this to steal the USB drive?
You don't know how scary the disciplinary committee is.
How will you deal with the aftermath?
What the f***?
Sunbaenim!
Shit, he's in trouble. Three more went in.
My gosh.
This is no good. Let's fight.
- What?
- The two of us will fight.
The disciplinary committee comes in whenever there's a commotion.
We'll pretend to be fighting so Yun Ga Min gets to escape.
Oh, okay.
If I go there,
yell at me, saying, "Hey, you f***er."
What? Me?
Why? What's wrong?
Well, the thing is...
By chance, you've never cursed?
- No.
- Well...
but you should do that so it looks like we're fighting.
- Right.
- Choi Hee Won?
Okay, done. It's yours, bastard.
I already saved it on the computer. It was ready to be uploaded on GoTube.
Lee Hyeon Wu's life would be over after a click.
Lee Ji Wu will be doomed, too.
Don't!
[Uploading the video]
You f***ers went too far.
How embarrassing.
Well, the thing is-
I'm sorry, Ji Wu.
I wasn't trying to keep it a secret-
No, it's not that.
I should've f***ed them up sooner.
It's annoying that I put you guys through this.
It's nothing...
Ji Wu, are you going to the Disciplinary Committee room?
Watch closely.
I might get hurt later, but I can at least throw a punch.
But you shouldn't do that now, Ji Wu.
You're dead.
What?
Hey! You crazy bastard!
Why is he taking all that?
Why is it so noisy?
That bastard...
Hey, what's that?
I'll destroy it.
If this is destroyed, you'd no longer-
- What?
- Get the computer!
Did I need help from a loser like that?
Se Hyeon, the video is on there. The video.
You bastard! Wait right there.
Sons of bitches!
Se Hyeon, hurry! Take it with you now!
- You son of a bitch. You'd better not run.
- I don't know. I don't know.
You son of a bitch. I'll kill you.
You f***ing losers!
Kim Se Hyeon.
Where are you going?
It's too heavy.
Geez, seriously.
Son of a bitch!
Are you all f***ers high or something?
Hey, you f***er!
I'm so f***ing tired. You f***er.
You know I'm in the Disciplinary Committee, right?
Bring it here while I'm being nice, you f***er.
Why are you suddenly causing trouble together? You f***er.
Keep acting like a loser-
There are no pedestrians here.
You f***er.
I'll throw you, too, you son of a bitch!
Peekaboo, you f***er.
I finally understood what the four-eyed psycho meant.
I can kill you once that thing is destroyed.
Do you want to act cute, then, Gyu Jin?
You crazy bitch!
I'll kill you if you mess with us siblings again.
It doesn't mean you can give up on them?
I haven't met someone so interesting in a while.
You say that after what you went through?
I'll take it as a compliment.
It wasn't a compliment.
What is it, then?
A word of pity?
You'll be disappointed soon.
Follow me, you bastard.
It's gone.
Hee Won! That thing!
Huh? What's this?
It's that thing Gyu Jin is obsessed with.
Hey, loser, did something happen here?
No, the thing is...
I suppose you know nothing.
Gyu Jin would be thrilled if I brought this to him.
Thank you.
Watch closely.
I might get hurt later, but I can at least throw a punch.
Hey, you f***ing bitch!
Did you just call me...
You crazy bitch.
You crazy bitch!
Wow.
What did I just see?
Ji Wu, I just...
Hee Won,
you're finally a Yuseong Tech High student.
That idiot.
Hey, Lee Hyeon Wu.
Hyeon Wu,
I heard you've been robbed.
The thing is, I...
You should've told me.
I found out that the robber...
was Kim Gyu Jin.
He gave you a loan with that money.
Using the video you took as a collateral,
he threatened your sister, too.
Die!
Hyeon Wu? I know.
The siblings have no parents, but they rely on each other.
I'm proud of them.
[Student Transcript - Lee Hyeon Wu]
[Dream occupation: Filthy rich]
What will you do once you quit the sport?
I don't know.
Study?
You can't study with your brain.
What did you say? Huh?
I'm your older sister.
I'm telling you to keep playing sports.
No thanks.
It's tough and costly.
I can try making money.
You're too little. You can't make money.
Just focus on your studies.
You called me little?
You're much smaller than me.
You keep picking a fight with your older sister.
Do you want to be pinned on the ground?
Go ahead if you can.
Hey!
Hyeon Wu.
Look at me, Lee Hyeon Wu.
Don't give up.
I'll help you.
Ms. Lee, please...
- Ms. Lee!
- My gosh.
Ms. Lee.
[In Operation]
I peel fruits at home often.
Hee Won.
Ji Wu!
You must be Ji Wu.
Pardon?
Welcome.
Ms. Lee, how are you feeling...
Me? As you can see, I'm totally fine.
She was amazingly lucky.
She just needs to be hospitalized for two weeks.
I'm so sorry, Ms. Lee.
Lee Hyeon Wu, that bastard. I'll make him pay for this.
As for the treatment fee, give me some time...
- I'll try my best to-
- You're joining us, right?
- Pardon?
- Well...
Hee Won is joining our study group, too.
Study group?
Yes. I'm moving, but I won't transfer.
It turns out it's an hour-and-a-half bus ride.
I think I could commute.
I want to study with you guys here.
Ji Wu, you'll join us, right?
Join us.
Okay?
Well, I'm so sorry, but...
I...
want to join the study group.
Great.
[Yuseong Technical High School]
We're studying here for now.
What's he doing?
Wow.
[Yuseong High Study Group Members]
Why is he doing this?
He gets poor grades, doesn't he?
You prepared all this?
It's so cool.
It's nothing. It's the study group leader's job.
He only hears what he wants to hear, right?
Yes. I think you're right.
I'm nervous.
What is it now?
It will be filled soon, too.
Yes. Me, too.
- Fighting.
- Did you buy this, too?
- Yes.
When did you take that photo?
Isn't it cute?
By the way, did you guys hear?
Pi Han Ul got arrested, too.
Hey.
You're Pi Han Ul, right?
Can we talk for a second?
- I am-
- Detective Na Tae Man, right?
Let's go.
Yes, everyone's talking about it.
Why did he get arrested?
If Lee Hyeon Wu is being investigated and Pi Han Ul got arrested,
he might go to the juvenile hall like Lee Hyeon Wu...
Of course, they should. They're thugs.
By the way, Pi Han Ul came to school today.
- What?
Yun Ga Min!
Come down immediately!
- Why?
Why? F***. He asks why. What do we do?
Shit. I knew it.
What do you mean?
You might not be interested,
but you're at the center of attention at Yuseong Tech High right now, Yun Ga Min.
What's wrong, Gyu Jin?
Are you okay? Who did this to you?
Was it Yun Ga Min again?
Yun Ga Min, that son of a bitch.
Hey, Yun Ga Min beat up Kim Gyu Jin, too.
- Really?
- Kim Gyu Jin?
That Disciplinary Committee member who does Judo?
Isn't he on the 11th grade?
That evil bastard. He skipped to the 11th grade.
What would happen to Kang Tae Oh, then?
What are those bastards saying?
I know Yuseong Tech High is a mess,
but different grades don't fight each other by a rule.
But you broke that rule.
I think he's scared.
He can't do anything because he's scared.
So, who is he?
Kang Tae Oh. The No. 1 of the 11th grade.
Come down, you f***er!
Let's decide who's above whom!
Decide!
You can be above me.
Did you see that?
He's running away scared.
What?
Is he looking down on me, by chance?
Yes, he is. You've been looked down on, Tae Oh.
He looked down on you big time.
Not just big time. Big f***ing time.
Big f***ing time?
Hey, you son of a bitch!
You look down on me?
Yun Ga Min, you won't come down?
Where's Jun?
Let go, you bastards!
There you are, you son of a bitch.
What's this now? Huh?
Stay put, you bastard.
You said you'd conquer Yuseong Tech High.
I thought you were an ambitious bastard.
But you were holding this disgusting thing.
What's this?
Study Group Application?
Study group...
Hey, Yun Ga Min. You influenced him and turned him into a f***ing loser.
Give me that.
This?
F***!
Cute bastard.
I'll kill whoever is holding this from now on, okay?
F***. What the hell...
- Hey!
- Yun Ga Min!
Wow. F***.
Wow.
[Study Group]