( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
Your new condo is freaking luxurious.
I got a discount.
- How much?
- 70%.
Do you know that where you're
sleeping is right on top of where I died?
I can do anything to you.
Open the door for me.
If you don't, I'll puke
right in front of your room.
Time to wake up.
I'm serious.
I feel like Meen didn't kill me.
If it wasn't me, then who was it?
Who else do you think saw
what happened besides...?
Can you help me talk
to the ghost in the room?
No.
Hey, wait.
Hey.
I heard you locked
P'Arthit in the bathroom.
And you even shut the door in his face?
Shit.
Help me out, will you?
- Help me talk to the ghost in the room.
- No.
Hey, wait.
North.
Your friend is so unbelievable.
Yeah.
Last night he made me
sleep in the bathroom.
Damn it, I haven't even
settled the score with him yet.
And today he did it again.
He shut the door in my face.
He really left you
sleeping in the bathroom?
That's bold.
That's my friend.
You think that's funny?
So what do you want from him?
I just want him to help me with something.
Why don't you at least hear
him out about what he's asking?
It seems like his friend wasn't
killed by her boyfriend after all.
If she didn't do it but
still has to go to prison,
that's pretty pitiful.
Why do you think your
girlfriend didn't kill you?
girlfriend didn't do it?
Even though she had a motive.
A motive?
We had a big fight before that, but
it was a misunderstanding.
What were you fighting about?
She thought I was cheating on her.
It really was a misunderstanding.
I never cheated on her.
Then why do you think P'Meen didn't do it?
Even though Meen can be hot-tempered,
and kind of mean,
sharp-tongued. We fought almost
every day when she was in a bad mood.
Lately, we argued because she
misunderstood and thought I was cheating.
And that night, she was drunk.
But she wouldn't kill me, right?
I don't know.
You don't remember
anything from that night?
Not at all.
By the time I realized I was
dead, several days had passed.
Why don't you try asking
the other ghosts in the room?
Do you think I haven't tried?
P'Praw.
About that night...
When I was killed,
did you see anything, P'Earng?
P'Cream.
You're my last hope.
Dao.
Be careful.
P'Cream is the scariest one.
Dao.
Aren't you scared?
No.
Do you want to stay with me?
Why?
Why don't you want to stay with me?
Why did you kill me?
Why did you have someone else?
This isn't a concert.
Why are you screaming?
I want to go.
Huh?
I want to go to a concert.
You like going to concerts?
I like them too.
Are you a fan too?
Not that hardcore.
But I follow quite a few bands.
I'm a pro at getting concert tickets.
Dao's pretty impressive.
You even managed to calm P'Cream down.
She's the scariest one here.
Everyone has their exceptions.
Um, P'Cream.
Hmm?
The night P'Donut was killed,
did you see anything, P'Cream?
I didn't see anything.
I was in the bathroom.
But the sound of arguing
was really loud.
Was it P'Donut and P'Meen arguing?
No.
It was Donut and someone else.
Whose voice was it?
I don't know.
It didn't sound familiar at all.
Was it a woman or a man?
A woman.
Alright, alright. I get it.
Are you trying to knock
the door down or what...
P'Cream said
that on the night P'Donut was killed,
she heard him arguing with another woman,
not P'Meen.
That's all she said.
I haven't seen the others yet,
so I haven't asked them.
Wait.
So you're going to help me, right?
I'm helping P'Donut, not you.
Isn't that basically the same thing?
No, it's not.
Damn, he's actually a good person.
Yeah. Unlike you, Thit.
You little
jerk.
- Damn it.
- I'm just kidding.
Stop floating around like that, you creep.
Or maybe he was arguing with another woman.
But there aren't any other women around Do.
True.
I only have Meen. I love only Meen.
Shit.
Or did he actually have a side chick?
Watch your mouth.
I doubt it. Do's way too shy.
Or maybe it was someone around Meen.
Yeah, I think so too.
I can't even read this properly.
Just keep reading.
So pretty. That lipstick color is gorgeous.
So, are you going tonight, Meen?
I think I'll pass.
Do will bring me to a buffet.
Fine, go be with your husband.
O-lin isn't going either.
I don't drink, so it wouldn't be fun for me.
Drink for me, then.
Guess I'll just go alone.
I'd rather read a book.
I seriously don't get you, Meen.
So many guys are into you,
and you chose that bland guy.
I'm delusional, I guess.
I'm heading out.
- Bye.
See you.
That's how it is once you've got a man.
You should just break up. I
see you two arguing every day.
But I love him.
I know you do. If you argue
over trivial things, that's one thing.
But cheating? I can't accept that.
You weren't raised to be
betrayed like this, Meen.
I've been with him for four or five years.
How can I just break up that easily, Mind?
That's not love. You're just attached.
So many guys are into you,
yet you picked that bland guy.
It's not love. You're just attached.
How can I break up that easily, Mind?
Hey.
Any updates?
I haven't seen P'Praw or P'Earng yet.
Didn't you ask Do?
P'Do doesn't remember
anything from that night.
And his memories from before that
are blurry too.
Damn it.
How can he not even remember his own case?
But last night, P'Do
didn't go back to his room.
So where could he have gone?
As for the women around them,
there are probably just Meen's friends,
Meen's sister,
Meen's mom,
and Do's mom.
Ok.
Alright, I've gotta go. I have class.
Meen thinks she killed him.
She woke up next to the body
with a knife in her hand,
so she confessed to the police.
So right now, you suspect
her friends and her older sister?
Yeah.
I've ruled out the other possibilities.
That's all that's left.
Wait a second.
You told me the condo's security
cameras were broken that day, right?
Yeah, the condo was
under renovation at the time.
Have you checked any
other security cameras yet?
Around the condo,
or on the nearby streets?
Oh shit, you're right.
Damn, Fah, you're a genius.
I'm off. Clean this up for me.
See you.
This is CCTV footage from
the building across the street.
I asked for it.
Not sure if it'll help, though.
Yeah, that's it.
Damn, that was slick.
We should totally form
an e-sports team, Daotok.
It's rare to find someone as good as you.
Michael.
What?
P'Praw is here.
Okay.
Hey, who are you talking to?
P'Praw is about to jump.
Hurry and talk to her, Michael.
I know.
Damn it, who are you talking to?
Let's stop here for today, North.
I need to talk to someone.
Who?
The ghost in the room.
Excuse me.
Can I ask you something?
On the night P'Donut was killed,
did you see anyone in that room?
Did you see anyone in P'Donut's room?
Was that person the one who killed P'Donut?
Who was it?
P'Praw said someone else
walked into the room that night.
Do you know who it was?
I don't know her.
Do you remember what she looked like?
A woman.
Long hair.
A black shirt.
A woman.
Long hair.
A black shirt.
I didn't understand a
thing in class just now.
I even dozed off.
You fell asleep in class?
That's bad.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
She feels
irritated.
fed up.
She feels
sad,
hurt,
afraid,
anxious,
and confused.
Guilty.
Hello?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Thank you.
What happened to your face?
You look like a dog that got stung by bees.
Yeah.
Just a bit.
What do you mean “just a bit”?
Last night, a gang leader in
prison picked a fight with me.
Damn.
Whatever.
So why are you here?
Any progress?
- Detective Conan.
- Detective your ass.
Idiot.
I had him talk to the ghost in the room.
He said you didn't kill him.
See? Damn it.
He said on the night it happened,
a woman went into your room
and argued with Do.
Who the hell was that?
She killed my husband
and got me thrown in jail.
I'm so damn pissed.
Hey, do you remember?
Back then, the condo's security
cameras were broken, right?
So I asked P'Pae
to get CCTV footage from nearby buildings.
Smart as hell.
I got the idea from Fah.
- You idiot.
- Hey, asshole.
I just called you smart. And you
should told Fah to come visit me instead.
As for you, get out of my sight.
Fine, I'm leaving. I'm
not helping you anymore.
Hey, hey.
I'm kidding.
On the night it happened,
the CCTV actually caught something.
That someone dropped you off.
Could it really be her?
O-lin is quiet as hell.
The CCTV even caught
her walking out of the condo.
Exactly at the same time Do died.
Can you give it to the police?
Yeah.
I think it could be used as evidence.
I'll handle the rest. Don't worry.
- Thanks.
- Mm.
And...
You seriously don't remember
a damn thing about that night?
No.
My memory's gone since I was at the bar.
See? That's what you get for
going drinking without inviting me.
Idiot.
Yeah.
When I get out, I'll buy
you drinks for three months.
You said it.
The moment it's about
alcohol, your ears perk right up.
Hey.
So...
What are you going to do next?
If you get out, I mean.
It won't be easy, right?
You were with Do for so long.
I don't know.
Isn't it like in novels
where
the truth is he's not dead?
Or like
- he's in a coma and wakes up...
- That's enough, Meen.
I stood there and watched him
being cremated with my own eyes.
I saw his face before they cremated him.
His funeral
I didn't even get to go.
We were together for so long.
I didn't even get to see him one last time.
You know
nothing's sadder than
the person you love dying.
Yeah.
That's how it is.
I just
I can't picture myself with anyone else.
When I was with him,
I even daydreamed about
our wedding, like a kid.
Like
wearing a wedding dress,
having kids with him and all that.
Why are you bringing this up?
I'm about to cry.
Then cry.
It's not weak.
You bastard, Do.
Kwai ngaen. (You idiot.)
Why the hell did you leave me?
It'd be better if you left me for
someone else than left me by dying.
You're even flirt with me first.
How am I supposed to live?
Uh...
Meen.
What the hell is a “kwai ngaen”?
There's nothing sadder than
the person you love dying, damn it.
Damn it, I'm trying to sleep here.
What is it?
I can't sleep.
Do I look like a sleeping pill to you? Huh?
You can't sleep so you
call me whining like a kid.
You're a grown-ass adult.
I miss you, Direk.
What happened?
Do you remember Do,
the one who was murdered?
Yeah.
He's...
He's already dead.
But he's still lingering in the room, Direk.
Do you think
my mom might still be around?
Your mom… she's not here anymore.
Emma's gone.
Michael.
Where did you go, P'Do?
I went to clear my head.
I remember now.
What happened that night.
Babe.
You're back?
I didn't cheat on you, Meen.
There's only you.
What does she have that I don't?
Why can't you like me?
Meen.
I love you, Meen.
I really do like you.
I've liked you for a long time.
Lin.
I told you already,
I don't like you.
And I'll never like you either.
Lin.
You're Meen's friend.
Why are you doing this?
Hey, Lin.
Lin.
Calm down. What are you doing?
Put the knife down, Lin.
No.
I'll put it down only if
you accept my feeling.
Lin.
Nothing's going to change.
Don't come any closer.
Lin.
Lin, calm down.
- Lin.
- Let go.
- Do.
- Lin.
Let go.
I thought Arthit came to visit.
Who's this?
My name's Daotok.
I'm the one living in your old room.
The one next to Arthit's room?
The kid who can see ghosts?
Yes.
So.
Why did you come see me?
I think I know who the killer is.
Hey...
Wait.
Let me brace myself first.
Who?
P'O-lin.
Your friend.
Are you sure?
It might sound a bit unbelievable,
but I can read people's feelings.
When I met P'O-lin,
her heart was filled with guilt,
sorrow,
self-disappointment,
and fear.
You're not here to ask
me to forgive her, right?
No.
I believe P'O-lin will turn herself in.
Because her feelings
are too heavy for one person to bear.
She just needs a little push,
and it'll all explode.
A push?
Why the hell did you kill my friend?
- I'm sorry.
- Go apologize to Meen.
She's in prison because of you.
I didn't mean to.
Stop crying already.
I've got evidence against you.
Are you going to confess
to the police yourself,
or do I have to drag you there?
I'll turn myself in.
I'll go apologize to Meen.
I truly feel guilty.
I didn't mean to.
Wait...
So his girlfriend wasn't the killer?
So she went to jail for nothing?
That's messed up.
And they were best friends too, right?
Damn it.
Turns out the trigger was Arthit.
That sucks for you, Lin.
And
how's Do?
P'Do
he's still waiting for
you at the same place.
Damn.
He's pathetic as hell.
Without me, he can't do shit.
P'Donut feels really guilty
for making you unable to trust him.
That he truly had only you.
Why the hell should he feel guilty?
I'm the one
who should feel guilty
for not trusting him,
for thinking he had someone else,
when someone like him
has absolutely nothing
worth being jealous over.
I told you already,
I can read people's feelings.
So if you're sad,
please let yourself cry.
Welcome back, buddy.
My dear friend.
Damn.
You're that happy I'm out?
Of course I am.
I get free drinks for three months.
Damn, all you think about is booze.
If it weren't for you getting me out of jail,
- I'd pinch your balls black and blue.
- You asshole, Meen. Damn it.
That tickles, man. I jumped. I'm serious.
- Hey, I'm serious too. Come here, let me grab them.
- Don't, you bastard. No way.
Don't you want to try?
Try what, you idiot?
You said it—three months.
Yeah.
Seriously though, thanks.
For handling everything for me.
That damn case
it was a mess.
So?
What did O-lin say?
Damn.
She cried her eyes out.
Told me she hasn't slept
since she caused Do's death.
She wants to confess to what she did.
Damn it.
Took her months to come to her senses.
Look at me—covered in scars,
almost the queen of the prison.
Good thing
my face isn't ruined. Still gorgeous.
Damn it.
Hey.
Where are you dropping me off?
I've got class.
Is our old condo floor still empty?
Seriously?
Of course it's empty. The whole floor is.
Who the hell would dare stay there?
Yeah.
Then drop me at the condo.
Okay.
Didn't you tell me you were going to
investigate some major national case?
So what did you get?
The case is closed, Papa.
It ended so simply. I thought
it'd be some huge case,
involving some underground
secret organization or something.
Turns out,
it was that simple.
You even left a message asking
us to take care of Khun John.
Me and Daddy were so shocked.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. We're just glad
you're safe. I was worried.
I'll bring Khun John to you this Friday.
Alright, Papa.
I'll be waiting.
See you.
Yes.
I'm sorry I just got murdered, that's all.
Sorry my case wasn't exciting enough.
I'm scared, Dao.
Hm?
I'm scared I'll disappear.
Even I'm already a ghost, after all.
How can a ghost and a human be in love?
Yeah.
You could at least comfort me a little.
Hey, Dao, someone's coming.
Someone's coming, Dao.
Someone's coming.
Hey.
Is Do still here?
He's not here anymore.
Has he been reborn?
I know you're still here.
Show yourself.
Hurry up.
I miss you.
I
I miss you too.
I miss you.
You
why did you leave me?
As for me,
I didn't want to trouble Dao
and make him move out,
so I rented the room across instead.
So?
Pretty cool, right?
That way we can stay close.
On the way here, I
had Arthit stop to buy pad kra
pao from the place we used to eat.
It's not as good as Aunt
Joom's, your favorite, though.
But just eat it anyway.
You know,
I've never wanted to see ghosts.
But today,
I really wish I could see you.
What's up, Grandma's boy?
Hello, Khun Phuangthong.
Is there a way for a normal person
to talk to a spirit?
Why would you want
to? It goes against nature.
I've talked to him many times
already, Khun Phuangthong.
We're practically close now.
There is a way, though.
Will it really work, Dao?
I'm not sure either.
You have to wear a dead
person's shirt and hold your breath.
Then you'll see the
spirit of the shirt's owner.
You bastard.
You still look stupid as ever.
Yeah, like you're any prettier.
How've you been?
What about you? You doing okay?
I'm good.
Michael still misses her.
Even if we're touched by
P'Meen and P'Do's love,
I won't go back to missing him.
Really?
Mm.
Really.
Does it still hurt, Michael?
Not anymore.
Even though he just texted
you, you don't feel anything?
I'll be back in Thailand in two months.
Don't block me.
Even if you do, I'll just
make a new account.
How much for a cigarette?
A hundred each.
Put it on my tab. My cash is in the room.
Fine.
Nice lighter.
How much?
Are you seriously going to buy everything?
Yeah.
How much?
Two thousand.
Didn't you say you quit smoking?
Sorry.
You always like this whenever you miss him.
No.
I don't miss him.
Emma, stop nagging.
Since when did you become such a nag?
I'm not talking to you anymore.
What is it?
Direk.
What's wrong? Why are you freaking out?
It's Emma, Direk.
I heard that kid next door
who can talk to ghosts.
I heard him talking to Emma, Direk.
I heard him call Emma's name.
What are you talking
about? This isn't funny.
Emma's still here, Direk.
Mom's still here, Direk.
Mom's still here.
That kid can talk to ghosts.
He can see them and
communicate with spirits.
Are you thinking of asking
him to help find Emma?
Hey, North. Can I get
your friend's Line ID?
Are you trying to hit on my friend?
Hey.
You've already helped me,
can you help me a little more?
What made you dye your hair that color?