(Previously)
Kant.
I'm done running.
Five years behind bars…
That's still better than
running all our lives.
We have one day together.
I want to make the most out of it.
Let's do something that
will become good memories.
What you want to do,
where to go, what to eat,
just let me know.
YEAR 1
What's wrong?
No energy?
Yeah.
How'd I have any
when I barely got any sleep last night?
The guy next to me kept
putting his leg on me all night.
We have to be here for five years.
Get used to it.
If he puts his leg on you,
just do the same to him.
Easier said than done.
Dude looks super scary.
Just exhaust yourself with exercises.
It'll help you sleep at night.
Hey.
That's my place.
Come on.
The equipment is for everyone, isn't it?
What, pretty boy?
You wanna get in trouble?
It's my workout time.
It's not like you can book this in advance,
can you?
I don't see anyone's name on these things.
Or did your daddy book it ahead for you?
Hey, newbie.
You run your mouth.
Just watch your back.
A petite pretty boy
like you is just my type.
You should be my plaything.
Let's stay out of each other's way.
You can exercise here all you want.
Why'd you let him have it?
It'll just get to his
head that he's all that.
It's not worth it.
We have to be here for another five years.
Don't get yourself an enemy so fast.
How are you?
You have bags under your eyes.
Do you get any sleep at all?
Hardly.
I can't really sleep much.
I'm worried about you…
Are you sure you got this?
Of course.
Don't worry about me.
I'm just not used to it yet.
It'll take some time.
What about you?
How are you?
I'm so-so.
Some TV star got a tattoo
from me and posted it online.
People showed up at my studio after that.
So I've been busy lately.
But that's good.
It's making really good money.
You're a celebrity tattoo artist now.
Don't forget me when you're famous.
I won't.
How could I?
You have my heart and my body…
Penguin.
Babe asked me to give you a book.
He said it'll keep you
company when you're bored.
Thank him for me.
How are you?
I'm okay.
It's not that bad here.
I'll get by.
Really?
You sure you're not saying
that just to make me happy?
I've seen some interviews,
and the people who have
been here said it was awful.
It's not that bad.
I really miss you, though.
When you do, just come visit.
How's the garage?
It's been busy.
Dad's pretty much retired,
so I'm taking over everything.
Do you know how my burger joint is?
The landlord sold the place.
But it's still a burger joint.
Not a thing has changed.
Except the name, though.
I'll find a way to buy it
back when I'm out of here.
We can deal with that later.
If you can't get the place back,
I'll help you find another location.
Is there anything you want?
I'll leave it with the warden.
I don't want anything.
Just seeing your face
will last me a whole month.
What did they feed you in there?
You're way too sweet.
If you say such sweet things,
it'll only make me want to hold you
and kiss you even more, you know?
Kant, I can't do this.
Who'd be able to just watch
their boyfriend go to jail, really?
The worst part is only getting
a few minutes to talk to him.
I see him but I can't touch him.
We're so close but it feels so far.
I get your drift.
I wanna break through
the bars just to get to him.
It makes me feel bad just
seeing the look in his eyes.
Is there no way we could
hold them in our arms again?
There's a special visit
day, but only once a year.
Once a year is hardly enough.
I think I have an idea
that will give us more than just a hug.
What are you thinking?
"The Heart Killers"
(Episode 12)
Hey, pretty boy.
Where are you off to?
Let's have a little chat.
What do you wanna chat about now?
I gave you back your dumbbells, didn't I?
They're all yours.
I'm done lifting weights.
I want a different kind of exercise,
something strenuous and sexy.
Will you just leave me alone?
Be my baby,
and I'll take you under my wing.
I promise you your life
here will be damn comfy.
Not interested.
I have a boyfriend,
and he's waiting for me out there.
He already takes good care of me.
How lovely.
Whatever your boyfriend can't do,
I'll do it.
Hey.
Let go of me!
Don't think you can just make me your baby!
If you want a lover, then be
nice and don't force it on them!
I know I'm cute, but I
can't be messed with!
Hey, what's going on here?
What are you doing?
He was trying to force
me, but I wouldn't let him.
They'll leave you alone
from now on, I take it?
Being smashed by a dipper
repeatedly did the job, I guess.
You're lucky the warden was understanding.
Or else you'd have been locked up alone.
As if a man like me would
let just anyone have me,
and he ain't even good-looking.
Hey, you two.
I heard you worked in a
restaurant when you were outside.
Yes.
I worked at a burger joint.
The kitchen is short-staffed right now.
Can you cook Thai food?
Yes.
I can make the basics like
stir fried dishes and soups.
Good.
Go help out in the kitchen, then.
Of course.
Can I bring my brother with me?
I think I'll need an extra pair of hands.
Fine.
Don't let me see you two slacking off.
If you don't do your job,
I'm putting you on crap-cleaning duty.
Oh, I won't slack off at all, sir.
I'll be the perfect sous chef.
Yes, chef!
Good.
Before you go to the kitchen,
make sure the floor's clean.
Yes.
Of course.
Yes, chef.
Do your job.
What?
You want me to put you in jail?
Yes, Cap.
We want to go to jail.
You dimwits.
What do you want to go there for?
I wanna see my boyfriend.
You two are crazy.
Can't you just visit them?
It's not enough.
All we can do is talk to
them through a glass window.
I want to touch him,
to feel him,
to hold him,
to kiss him.
And I want to…
You're one lovesick bastard.
So?
You're gonna steal, kill, and
sell drugs just to get locked up?
Think about it.
I literally just helped
you wipe your slate clean.
That's not what I have in mind.
I have a better way.
I just need you to pull
some strings for us.
Do you know someone on the inside?
A few.
Don't tell me you want me to
help you reenact Prison Break?
Do you have a tattoo of a map or something?
You watch too much TV, Cap.
My plan is even better than that.
It's so much better in the
kitchen, don't you think?
I can easily get through five
years if we're here all the time.
At least it's something I'm good at.
You're right.
I miss your cooking.
The last guy was too
heavy-handed on the salt.
Thought I'd have to get my
kidney replaced when I'm out.
Am I right?
Get your hands busy, not your mouth.
The prisoners will be here soon.
And don't get too giddy,
'cause you won't get to
be in the kitchen all day.
You're taking vocational training, too.
What kind of vocational training?
All sorts of kinds.
There's carving, fortune
telling, drawing, fixing cars.
All sorts of things for you to choose from.
Hurry up and finish it.
Yes.
I think I'll go for drawing.
You wanna join me?
I don't like drawing.
You go for it.
What will you do?
Just sit around being bored?
Don't worry about me.
I'll find something to do.
[VOCATIONAL TRAINING FOR PRISONERS: ART]
Hey, is this seat taken?
Nah.
You can sit.
Hey.
Where's the teacher?
Are we allowed to just
paint whatever we want?
He went to get more supply.
He'll be back soon.
Sorry, guys.
I had to get us more supply.
Kant?
We'll draw some flowers and vases today.
We'll learn about light and shadow.
Has anyone taken an art course before?
So everyone has, except you.
Why did you want to study art now?
I think I'm too rough around the edges
and too brutish.
I think art might be able to soften me up.
Alright.
I guess I'll have to pay attention to
you especially so you know all the basics.
[THE INSIDE OF AN ENGINE]
…It's pretty exciting.
It makes you feel energetic and happy.
I'll be teaching you the basics
of auto repair today, though.
Let's save dancing for later.
Oh, hey.
Don't just stand there.
You wanna join this class or what?
I do want to join.
Is it okay if I don't know the
first thing about fixing cars?
It's alright.
You'll get to learn all about it.
If you want to, that is.
I'll show you every
nook and cranny of a car.
You'll definitely find some
use for what you learn from me.
But if you still can't fix cars after that,
I'll fix them for you.
You said you didn't know the basics,
but you nailed this
light and shadow lesson.
I have a gift for it, I guess.
There's something you're
just good at without learning.
I guess I have nothing to teach you, then?
Do teach me.
I still need some advice from a pro.
Follow me.
You seriously broke your pencil?
Oh…
Yes.
I must have used too much
strength when I was drawing.
It's quite okay.
But we're out of pencils right now.
I'll go get some from
behind the meeting room.
Sir.
I'm going to get some
pencils for the students.
Yes.
Thanks.
Warden, may I go to the toilet, please?
I'll be back to finish my drawing.
Told you I'd never stay away, didn't I?
I thought you'd do something
illegal just to get in here.
This is way better.
I get to be close to you
and to touch you just like I wanted to.
Style!
You'll be in trouble if the guard sees you.
So?
Why would I come here if I don't
get to do anything with you at all?
I can't help you.
You said you'd be patient,
and you're already losing it?
A guy has wants and needs, you know?
Guys.
Do you mind putting the tools
back in place when you're done?
That's all for today.
I'll see you again next week.
I'll make sure you can
all run a garage one day.
Kant.
How'd you get here?
Let's say I have some strings I could pull.
But you won't get into any
trouble for this, will you?
I'm worried about you.
Don't be.
Captain talked to some people for me.
We just can't be too obvious about this.
I'll be coming here to teach from now on.
But... won't it be a waste of time for you?
Seeing you will make me happy.
I'll get to meet you,
and touch you just like this.
I've been dying to do that
since the moment I saw you.
You're crazy.
Love will make people do crazy things.
Save your sweet words.
How did you get in here?
It's thanks to Kant's connections.
I'll be teaching here regularly.
So I'll see you every week.
You know…
You don't have to do this.
I don't mind seeing you once a month
or once every three months.
I did everything I could
to be with you, you know?
You don't appreciate that?
Or did you already find someone here?
I'd expect it of a popular guy like you.
Come here.
No matter where I am,
you're the only one for me.
Once you're done cleaning that,
put it back where it comes from.
Yes, sir.
I'll see you again next week.
I'm counting on ya.
YEAR 2
YEAR 3
What are you reading?
It's the book Babe gave me.
It's got a way to escape prison, you know?
And what are you gonna do with it?
Break out of jail?
I've been thinking about it.
Maybe I'll escape through the
toilet sewage on a rainy night,
like in a movie.
What do you think?
That's positively unhygienic.
Don't count me in if
you're serious about that.
You're on your own.
I want to barf just thinking about it.
Happy birthday.
Whoa, Fadel.
I can't make you an actual cake,
so you're only getting a banana muffin.
It's alright.
I've been in here so long that
the days blur into each other.
Birthdays no longer matter.
But it feels great when
someone remembers, though.
Thanks.
You're really…
The best brother ever.
That's enough.
I'm going to go work out.
Wash my clothes, will you?
Oh, you jerk.
Were you being nice just to use me?
Don't forget to hang them out to dry.
Sis. Big sis.
Hmm?
Are you seeing what I'm seeing?
See what?
Behind the clothes line.
Oh, it's all normal around here.
We gotta be discreet about doing it.
I'm keeping watch, actually.
And I was nice enough to ask for
only a pack of cigarettes in return.
Really?
Yeah.
It kinda feels like you're
a dingy motel owner,
like a small business kind of thing.
It kinda feels fulfilling, really,
to see people have fun and be happy.
I've been here forever
and I never have anyone.
What about you?
You're very pretty.
Don't you have anyone?
Of course I do.
He's outside.
There are other people outside,
as there are inside.
Who'd wait for you when
your sentence is so long?
I'm sure he has someone
else who gets his needs met.
Don't stare at them so much.
I can see the look in your eyes.
Don't make fun of me.
We're painting outside
today for a change of scenery.
Maybe it'll give you guys
some new ideas, am I right?
Yes.
Happy birthday to you.
You remember?
Of course.
I remember everything about you.
Too bad.
If we were outside,
I might have surprised you
with a northern light hunting trip.
I don't dream much.
Just seeing your face today is already
a happy birthday to me.
I'll give you your present
once you get out of here.
Hey.
Can I… ask you something?
When you…
get…
get that kind of feeling,
what do you do?
What do you mean by “that kind of feeling”?
Well, you know…
This.
What do you mean?
Well…
Oh, you mean that kind of feeling.
I have myself to count on, don't I?
Does it always work?
I wouldn't mind if you
find someone, you know?
It's physical-only, of course.
Don't you get your heart involved.
No.
I belong to you, with
my whole heart and body.
Hey.
Harassing a prisoner is illegal, you know?
Alright.
I'll go to court and defend myself that
the prisoner is simply too irresistible.
Hey.
Listen.
I know what I want.
You can give it to me
right here and right now.
Sis.
I'm counting on you.
Is this how things are done around here?
Yeah.
When an urge arises, it's gotta
be done behind the clothes line.
Well, what are we doing that needs hiding?
I want my birthday present.
What birthday present?
Didn't you say you were
happy just seeing me?
Come on.
You know that won't be
enough for someone like me.
Didn't you threaten me with a trip
to the court just for a kiss just now?
If I do anything more than that,
you sure I won't be sentenced for life?
Why, you scared?
YEAR 4
This is called a breaker bar.
It comes with different size sockets.
There's the 17mm, 21mm, 23mm, and 19mm.
There's also…
Are you here for class?
No.
Babe.
They told me someone is here to visit you.
Thanks.
Sure, babe.
What were you doing?
Took you forever.
I went to see you at the
garage but you weren't there.
I'm sorry.
I've been super busy these days.
I might not be able to
come here so often now.
Why?
I told you.
Since Dad's been retired,
I have to take care of
everything by myself.
I'm also thinking of
expanding the business.
I've got a lot of projects going on,
and I got to meet so
many people in the industry.
It's been eye-opening.
That's good.
It's alright.
I understand.
You don't have to come
here to teach, you know?
Don't worry.
I'll make time for it.
But if I can't, I'll just
come visit you instead.
Is that okay?
What's wrong?
Are you mad at me?
No.
I understand you have to live your life.
I'm in here so there's
nothing I can do but wait.
Style, I think…
Our timing just wasn't right at all.
What are you talking about?
I think you should focus on your future.
Coming here to see me,
with such a long way to travel,
it's just a waste of your time.
Working here doesn't
pay you a dime, does it?
It doesn't compare to fixing
some expensive cars, you know?
You shouldn't waste your time on me.
It's not a waste of time.
You're my boyfriend.
I will always make time for you.
Work is important, but
you're also important to me.
Before you went to jail,
you told me to focus on my own life.
Now that I'm doing exactly that,
are you sulking?
I'm not sulking.
Just do what you want.
Don't take me into account.
Hey, Fadel.
Wait.
I have work in the kitchen.
Don't want these prisoners to starve.
Thank you.
Think of Style Auto
when your car is in trouble.
Thank you.
You always only fixed a few cars a month.
What's going on?
Are you in need of money or what?
Not really.
I just want to save up some, is all.
What for?
You buying a new car?
Why would I want a new one?
I just finished upgrading
the one I have, didn't I?
Wait. Don't tell me…
You're thinking of buying a love nest?
Are you getting married?
I'm not.
You're jumping to conclusions.
Aren't you glad I work hard?
Where's Fadel been, though?
He's… going to culinary school abroad.
He'll be back.
Good.
I'm rooting for him.
You need a lot of trust when it
comes to long distance relationships.
Be patient, son.
You'll be back together soon.
What's that you're eating?
Pad kaprao.
You want some?
Nah. All yours.
Kant.
I want a tattoo.
Will you do it for me?
What gave you that idea?
Well, life has been memorable lately.
Well said.
What kind of tattoo do you want?
I want a tattoo of your name.
No way.
People will make fun of you for that.
People have their parents'
names tattooed all the time.
Why can't I have the name of the
most important person in my life tattooed?
Fair warning…
Once you get your first tatt,
one won't be enough.
Don't you want a tattoo anymore?
Follow me.
Sit still.
But it hurts.
You sure you're not messing it up?
I've been doing this
for years, come on now.
You sure the spelling is correct?
Yeah.
As if I'd misspell my own name.
You're funny.
You complain a lot, don't you?
And you're prissy.
Other artists never take as
long as you for one tattoo.
You wanna finish the rest yourself?
I don't know how.
Then keep quiet.
Won't you go and see Style?
He's here twice a week
and you refuse to go to class.
You refuse his visit when he's here, too.
I'm busy.
I don't have time.
“Don't have time,” my foot.
You're in here only during mealtimes.
What do you even do the rest of the day?
I don't want to learn
how to fix cars anymore.
I want to try my hand at massaging.
Massage?
You, learning how to massage?
You'll break someone's bones.
You'll be my first client,
and I'll do it with my foot.
Shut your trap
or I'll tell the guard you
want to be on toilet duty.
Fine. Fine.
I'll leave you alone.
Style asked me to give you this, though.
He said he got it from someone
who takes origami training.
I'm gone.
Chop the rest of the pork, will you?
Thought you'd never see me again.
What do you want?
What are you mad at me about?
I'm not mad at you.
I told you
I don't like expectations because
I don't want to be disappointed.
But I didn't do anything to disappoint you.
Coming to see me regularly,
getting me used to seeing you,
making me miss you,
and suddenly disappearing…
How do you think that made me feel?
If you can't do it, don't
promise me anything.
Do you know how easy it is
to overthink when I'm here?
If you have something
important to do, just focus on it.
I don't want to slow you down.
You're the most important thing to me.
I'm doing something
for both of our futures.
What are you doing?
Can you tell me?
Can you wait a little longer?
I want to be certain about it first.
I want to make sure I really can do it.
You really love surprising me, don't you?
Come back to class.
I've been taking the course for years,
and I still don't know how to fix anything.
All you do is yap.
But that's exactly what
you love about me, isn't it?
This…
It's cute.
Help me clean the blackboard.
And now you're ordering me around.
YEAR 5
I've missed you.
I see you so often, and you still miss me?
Of course.
Even one minute away
from you makes me miss you.
Hear that?
He said he missed him and all that.
Did you miss me at all?
I'm not saying it.
Come on, Fadel.
Easy, man.
I'm showing it.
What do you want to do now?
Go straight home or do
you wanna go somewhere?
I don't have a home to go back to.
There's always my place.
Let's do that later.
I want to go out and about.
Savor this freedom.
If you want.
Hey, can you guys drop
me off near my place first?
Of course.
What do you mean, “your place”?
The garage?
You'll know soon.
Let's get in.
Please.
Hey, watch my leg.
You alright?
Is this how fast you can go?
Oh, dang.
Take that!
Is it getting familiar now?
Are we there yet?
Yes.
Ready?
In three, two… one.
You said it was sold to someone.
I bought it back.
You didn't have to.
I worked my ass off to
buy this place back for you.
That means…
When you weren't coming to see me,
you were…
Yeah.
I wasn't sure I could
do it so I didn't tell you.
But the image of you
being back in this restaurant
gave me this great strength
to fix at least a hundred cars.
Thank you for doing this
for me and for waiting for me.
Well, I love you.
Of course I can wait.
Whether it's five, ten, or twenty years,
I'll wait for you.
I'll work hard to pay you back.
No.
This place isn't mine alone.
It's ours.
I'm here to support you in all your dreams.
I sure am a lucky guy.
I've been doing bad things my entire life,
but I have the best boyfriend in the world.
It's all thanks to Kant
for daring me to take you out.
From now on,
everything is yours.
Let's go.
Freedom sure smells so fresh.
I doubt it.
I checked and it said
the pollution is bad today.
Come on.
Cut me some slack.
I've been in prison for years, you know?
It smelled depressing there.
What are you going to do now?
The house you and Fadel used
to live in was seized by the police.
I don't know.
I guess…
I'm starting over from zero.
It's not zero.
You have me.
With me by your side,
you're starting from five.
We'll build the rest together
until we're back to ten.
How about that?
Move in with me.
No way.
I can't do that.
I can't impose on Babe like that.
Babe won't be there for you to impose on.
He just won a scholarship to study abroad.
Once he's there, I'm all alone.
I'll be super lonely.
You must make me pay rent.
How much rent is due?
It won't be too costly.
How about some…
hugs and kisses every day?
Sure thing.
Move in with me.
Alright.
But only till I'm back on my feet.
I don't want to depend so much on you
or Fadel, for that matter.
He should be focusing on his restaurant.
As for someone who doesn't
know what he wants, like me,
I'll just be looking for it for a while.
Alright.
But if you ever need my
help, you gotta let me know.
I'm here for you.
Thank you.
Oh, the fish are gigantic.
The door's unlocked.
Babe, you know you left the door unlocked?
What happened?
Why is the place all messy?
Babe!
Maybe he's with some friends?
Hey, Knot.
It's Kant.
Is Babe with you?
Okay.
If you see Babe, can you call me?
This doesn't seem right.
Dad.
Dad, Fadel's here to see you.
Oh, where's my dad?
I haven't seen him, sir.
By the way…
Someone left this for you.
Who?
A woman with long hair.
She looked really fierce.
I think she's loaded. She
was driving a Mercedes.
She's probably some bigshot.
“Dinner with Mom.”
Whose Mom?
I think I know.
Give up your guns.
Babe.
Kant, help me!
Dad.
Tyle.
What's going on?
What is this all about?
I'll tell you soon.
Guys, why don't you sit down?
You probably don't know,
but your son,
and your brother,
together with my sons,
threw me in jail.
They probably thought
I'd be in there for life.
They must have forgotten that
money can buy even freedom.
What the hell do you want now?
Is that how you talk to your mother, Fadel?
I lost everything because of you.
My reputation, the trust I built,
my connection,
even my employees…
Everything was ruined because of you.
As it should be.
You don't deserve anything.
Let them go and deal with me!
What satisfaction would that give me?
It was me who exposed you.
I masterminded the whole thing.
If you want to kill someone,
kill me.
Just let my brother go.
Kant was right.
Let my Dad go.
He doesn't know anything.
I don't care what you do to me.
So it was your hero complex
that made Fadel and Bison
fall head over heels for you.
Don't worry.
I prepared some drinks for everyone.
You will all…
die here together.
Don't be afraid, Babe.
Dad.
I'm sorry.
If you're being tricky,
I don't guarantee these
two will walk free afterwards.
Please.
Give us another chance
to help you build back what's yours.
Just please let them go.
I'll kill for you again, Mother.
I'll listen to everything you say.
But please let them go.
Mother.
Of course.
But after you give these two the drink.
I'll let you, and your boyfriends, go.
Can you do that?
Yes.
Hey.
Bison.
Take your pick.
A drink
or a bullet.
Hey.
Kill me.
End it here.
Oh, I will.
No question.
Don't, Bison.
You did your time in prison.
Don't go back there.
I'm calling the cops right now.
She won't get away this time.
Style.
Don't.
She'll die by my hand today.
If it doesn't end like this,
she's only coming back again later.
Don't you worry.
I won't kill you now.
Your death will be slow, torturing,
and all alone.
Bison.
Drink.
Drink it.
Drink it all!
You know, in prison,
this was the image I always dreamed of.
What image?
Being in your arms like this.
I just hope there's nothing
more for us to worry about.
Don't worry.
I even made my way to you
when you were in prison, didn't I?
I know you're great and all that.
But I can't take that anymore.
I don't want to be away from you anymore.
You won't have to.
If anyone hurts you from now on,
I'll shoot them all in the face.
Pew, pew, pew!
You watch too many films.
Oh, hey.
What is it?
What?
Plane tickets to Iceland?
Really?
Yeah.
When did you buy these?
Just before you got out.
We'll finally get to be there together.
You spoil me too much, you know?
I won't ever want to leave.
Well, then, don't leave.
Stay with me right here.
I'll make all your dreams come true.
Wait, let me say that again…
I'll make all our dreams come true.
Thank you, Kant.
We're going to Iceland!
Iceland!
Hey!
Should I change the name of the restaurant?
Why?
The name Heart Burger is fine.
It's our restaurant now.
I want you to be a part of it.
I don't think it needs much change.
Just add an S and a heart.
That'll make a better version.
With another heart, that is.
Good.
That sounds like a good idea.
What's that?
Kant's car key.
It's mine now.
Because you took me out?
It was a deal, after all.
If I could make you fall
crazy in love with me,
I'd get his car.
Then you should give the key back to Kant.
I'm not in love with you like that.
Are you sure
that you're not head
over heels in love with me?
How much do you love me?
Only 30%.
60% now.
How much do you love me?
100%.
You know what?
Having you is worth
more than winning that car.
Let me know if you get sleepy or tired,
we'll switch.
It's alright.
I love driving.
You can take a nap if you want.
Nah. I'd rather keep you company.
You've been driving for hours, after all.
I won't get sleepy.
Your playlist really keeps me entertained.
I've put so much thought into it, you know?
There's a playlist for just chilling,
for when you're sleepy,
even for when we're fighting.
Why would we fight?
Who knows?
Maybe I get hungry and moody,
or I give you wrong directions.
They said travelling is when you
really can tell if a couple will make it.
It tests how much we
can tolerate each other.
I see.
But we got through
wanting to kill each other.
You don't think we'd make
it after something like that?
Hey.
We've been driving a long time,
and still haven't seen the northern lights.
I think we need to keep driving.
Go somewhere out of
town with no light pollution.
I think it'll be better
around where we camp.
Let's just hope we find it.
Hey, look.
It's below freezing out there.
I think we're going to get
frozen instantly if we go outside.
Let's just cuddle to keep warm.
Are you going to be sad if we
don't see the northern lights?
A little.
But if we don't see
them here, I'll keep going.
If we don't see them in
Iceland, I'll go to Sweden,
Greenland, and Alaska.
I'll go anywhere in the
world until I find them.
I guess I'll be there with
you every step of the way.
Hey.
What?
Hey, come out and see!
It's gorgeous.
It's worth all the miles
we've come, don't you think?
Yeah.
You know, each culture has their
own myth of the northern lights.
Do they?
Tell me.
Eskimo believes the northern lights are
a path of connection to their ancestors.
Finnish believe the northern lights occur
because a fox runs across the sky,
and his tail grazes the mountains,
making sparks that
become the northern lights.
You know…
This is so different from what I imagined.
How so?
In my head,
I'd be standing here watching
the northern lights all by myself.
But now you're here.
Getting to share my
dreams with someone I love,
it feels even better than
anything I ever imagined.
I made your dream come true.
But do you know that you've fulfilled
the meaning of life for me as well?
What do you mean?
Well…
Kant means “the beloved,” right?
Now I have someone
who calls me his “beloved,”
and I also freaking love him.
Are you warm?
It's Style.
Take the call.
Hey, bud. What's up?
Hey.
You guys seen the northern lights yet?
Yeah.
Look.
It's beautiful.
We wish you were here.
What are you doing?
Taking your car for a little drive.
Rubbing it in my face, aren't you?
Style.
Hey.
Where's Fadel?
Say hello to your brother.
Hey.
Have fun and be careful on your trip.
Don't worry about me.
I've got a boyfriend to take care of me.
Hey, I have to go.
Let's talk later.
Take lots of photos for us.
Of course.
See you.
Bye.
You wanna take a long trip like them?
Of course.
I usually travel with my Dad.
Never done it with my boyfriend before.
Let's plan something later, then.
Now that your father knows
about my being a former hitman,
and a locked up criminal,
is he alright with it?
He sure is.
He said I need someone with
a past like yours to tie me down.
You know,
I still remember what I promised
your dad before I went to jail.
What did you promise?
I told him I'd go talk
to him after five years.
You're serious?
I am.
I never go back on my words.
I'll do it after the
restaurant is back to normal.
No need to hurry.
I think the pace we're
going is already good.
No need to push yourself.
After everything that we've been through,
still staying together is already
beyond anything we expected.
You're right.
I thought I'd die alone.
We'll die one day,
but we'll die together of old age.
You're so cheesy.
Fadel, I'm driving!
Hey, I'm driving!
Cuddling you is really warm.
Clearly.
You really are something, huh?