[A Splendid Match]
[Episode 15]
[Memorial]
My mother
asked me to pass along a few words
to Miss Gu.
Rong,
Lan,
[Memorial]
come with me.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry your mother is gone.
Miss Gu, I hope you
accept my condolences,
and take care of yourself.
That is the best way
to honor your late mother.
I know.
I heard the Old Madam came as well.
She arrived yesterday.
She wasn't feeling well last night,
and today
she couldn't get out of bed.
Did you send for a physician?
Yes.
It's nothing serious.
She's just overwhelmed with grief.
When will the funeral be held?
Not yet.
My mother's last wish was
to be buried in the Ji family
ancestral ground in Tongzhou.
Did the Gu family
agree to that?
That's not for them to decide.
I've sent people to look for Yuping.
There should be news soon.
Thank you, Third Master.
If you hadn't brought Yuping here,
Mother would still be alive!
It's my fault too
for believing your nonsense!
You said you were craving
Li's sugar-roasted chestnuts,
because I told you
Yuping's family
owned that shop, right?
So you knew that finding Li's shop
would lead you to Yuping, didn't you?
I did want to find Yuping,
but I never thought
Mother would take her own life.
I see.
No wonder you've been
acting so strangely lately.
So it was you
who helped find Yuping.
Zhao!
I was wrong. I didn't know
things would end up like this.
I deserve to die.
I really do!
This has nothing to do with Rong.
I lied to him.
He had no idea
I was using him to get information.
If you want to punish someone,
just come at me.
Stop putting on that act in front of me.
I always treated you
as my closest family,
yet you used me
and got my mother killed!
Rong.
I'm your sister, so listen to me.
What kind of sister are you?
I don't want a sister like you anymore!
Rong.
I've decided to go
to the Shuntian Prefecture
and accuse Gu Dezhao
of driving his wife to suicide.
Have you lost your mind?
He's the real culprit.
But do you realize
accusing your own father is a felony?
Before the case begins,
you'll take 40 strokes of the cane first!
So what?
I have to
seek justice for her.
Even if you are not afraid
of physical pain,
once you do this,
the Gu family's reputation
will be totally ruined.
Don't you want to get married someday?
And what about Rong's future?
Don't you care about
Rong's future either?
I'm not here to discuss it with you.
I just came here
to inform you.
Let me sue him!
I'm also responsible for Mother's death,
and I deserve no forgiveness.
Let me file the accusation instead.
I'll take the 40 strokes myself.
Fine.
Once I finish writing the petition,
I'll have you sign it with me.
Crazy.
They're all crazy.
My Lady.
I was just about to look for you.
A letter from Guard Chen says
Yuping has been found.
You are...
Miss Gu.
Miss Gu!
I was wrong.
I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry.
Back then,
I was the one who swapped
the labor-inducing medicine
that Yun drank.
It had nothing to do with Madam Ji Han.
I'm willing to confess
and take the punishment.
I only beg you
to spare my
two children.
Please.
I beg you.
Why did you harm Yun Xiang?
Years ago,
Madam Ji Han wanted to promote someone
to divide Master's affection away
from Madam Song,
so I...
harbored thoughts I never should have,
and even begged Madam to choose me.
But Madam Ji Han
chose Yun Xiang instead
and assigned me to serve her.
Yun Xiang relied
on her pregnancy
to boss me around
every single day.
I couldn't bear the humiliation anymore...
so I gave her
the labor-inducing soup
and told her it could prevent miscarriage.
Just because Madam chose Yun Xiang,
instead of you,
and you decided to harm her?
I'm guilty!
I deserve death.
I have no idea
what came over me at the time.
It was as if I were possessed.
So...
you had feelings for Master as well?
No, no, no. It wasn't like that.
I didn't understand
what love even was.
At the time,
I simply thought
that as Madam's dowry maid,
I was meant
to become Master's concubine.
Unexpectedly,
Madam chose Yun Xiang instead,
and said my temperament was unsuitable.
She told me
to choose a servant
from the outer courtyard
and get married off.
I didn't want to marry a servant.
So I...
You committed murder,
yet you were only expelled
from the mansion—
you should consider yourself lucky.
Then why did you suddenly come back
to frame Mrs. Gu?
I didn't come back
to frame her on purpose.
Miss Lan and Madam Song
came to question me
about the incident from years ago.
They asked
whether Madam had switched the medicine.
I couldn't admit
that it was my doing,
so I went along with their story.
Then Madam Song promised me
a reward of two hundred taels of silver,
if I was willing to testify against Madam
in front of Master.
I couldn't resist the money,
so I...
I'm so sorry.
I made a terrible mistake.
How would you like
to handle this matter?
Could you give me Yuping's
wrriten confession?
I was going to give it to you anyway.
What do you want to do with it?
If I take this to the Shuntian Prefecture,
will he be stripped of his position?
I can have him stripped of his post.
Then let's expose everything.
I was already planning
to take him to court anyway.
Are you sure you want
to sue your own father?
Do you think I've lost my mind?
I know
that my mother
wasn't directly killed by my father.
And I also know
the odds of winning this case
are slim.
But I never expected to win.
I just want to
ruin his reputation.
But do you realize
that if a child accuses their own father,
regardless of right or wrong,
they must first
endure 40 strokes of the cane?
I know.
But I'm willing to take it.
My mother was driven to this end
all because of him.
I refuse to let him walk away with it.
Fine.
What's wrong?
You helped Miss Gu today,
but you still seem troubled.
She wants to go to the Shuntian Prefecture
to accuse Gu Dezhao.
And you agreed to it?
I mean...
for a child to accuse their own father,
it's a serious violation of filial piety!
She can't possibly win.
Why are you letting her have her way?
She is filled with anger,
and that anger must be released.
Otherwise,
it will consume her.
But she'll have
to endure 40 strokes of the cane.
Can you bear to watch Miss Gu be beaten?
That is exactly
why I need your help.
[Case Precedents]
In the 17th year of Jingning,
a scholar from Zhending Prefecture
named Zhu Zhengrong
accsued his own father—
because his father was later found guilty
of unforgivable crimes,
Zhu Zhengrong was exempted
from the strokes of the cane.
Find a few more
similar cases for me.
I'll bring them to Yao Ping.
Are you planning
to change the law for this?
The law is based on human nature.
Besides, Gu Dezhao is guilty
to begin with.
By the way.
Find a few censors
to impeach Gu Dezhao—
charge him with favoring his concubine
and driving his wife to death.
Let's shape the narrative first.
Since she insists on accusing him,
I should at least
pave the way for her.
[Immersed in the Classics and History]
But shouldn't you
be dissuading Miss Gu instead?
You wouldn't understand.
Third Master.
A message has just arrived.
[Immersed in the Classics and History]
[Wenyuan Pavilion]
Greetings, Lord Fan.
That old fool Fan Chuan
has always been so stubborn!
He refuses to acknowledge
the advantages of sea transport,
and insists
on opening canal routes instead.
Today, the Imperial Board of Astronomy
said that this year's climate
is different from previous years—
the summer floods may arrive early.
If the summer flood comes early,
won't the banks of the Yellow River
and Huai River overflow again?
The imperial court must prepare
for disaster relief immediately.
Disaster relief is actually
a secondary concern.
Come with me.
Let me explain it to you.
Once the Yellow River bursts its banks
and the water changes its course,
[Pei County] [Xuzhou]
the water levels in Pei County,
Xuzhou,
[Suqian] [Huai'an]
Suqian, and Huai'an
will inevitably drop.
By then, the silting in the watercourse
will only become even worse.
In other words,
forget this year—
even next year and the year after,
the canal routes just won't recover.
The moment Fan Chuan hears
that the canal routes cannot recover,
he will have no reason left
to oppose sea transport.
Wouldn't you say
God is helping me?
What do you want to see me about?
Mentor, do you remember
when I was attacked in Tongzhou,
I mentioned that
Prince Ruichang's heir
had been selling
military weapons to the commoners.
I followed this lead and discovered
that recently a shipment of weapons
bypassed the
Ministry of War's allocation process
and was smuggled out through Ninghaiwei.
It seems
they're being transported back
to the capital.
You're thinking...
I think
this matter is still
related to Prince Ruichang.
I'd like to follow the trail,
let them in, and catch them red-handed.
You may play along,
but you can't actually
let them into the capital.
The capital
cannot be put at risk.
Then we should lure them to Tongzhou.
The weapons are large.
If they travel by land,
they'll have to face many checkpoints,
making it impossible to stay hidden.
They must be taking the water route.
And if they travel by water,
they'll inevitably pass through Tongzhou.
Then you should head to Tongzhou yourself.
Come up with a proper excuse.
My ancestral home is in Tongzhou.
I was just thinking of returning there
to pay respects to my ancestors.
Third Master,
all the legal precedents of children
accusing their fathers and being exempted
from punishment are right here.
Go to Shandong again.
Deliver this letter to
Pan Yuncheng
of the River Conservancy Office.
Why reach out to him all of a sudden?
The summer flood will be early this year.
But
the court will likely be unable to do much
regarding river repairs
and disaster relief.
Why?
Isn't it true
that after the land tax reform,
the Ministry of Revenue collected
way more silver than usual?
Is it because of the sea route project?
Those are two separate matters.
Surely no one would deliberately
neglect river repairs
just to push forward sea transport, right?
What did the Grand Secretary say?
I just came from the Wenyuan Pavilion.
I can't bypass my mentor
and make a direct request
to Ministry of Revenue.
Lord Pan and I
have worked together for many years.
Tell him
to prepare well.
He'll know what to do.
How did it come to this?
Early tomorrow morning,
you will escort the coffin
back to Tongzhou—
on foot the entire way.
How can you not eat more?
That's more like it.
Tomorrow morning,
I will come check on you again.
Yao.
I heard from Rong
that before Aunt passed away,
she begged you to call her Mother.
But you didn't say it.
Now that she's gone,
you must regret it deeply.
But actually,
you did call her Mother before.
Not just Mother,
you even called her Mom.
Before you turned four,
Aunt would return
to Tongzhou to visit you every year.
And every time,
you would run to her from far away,
calling her Mom,
and throwing yourself into her arms.
Then again,
even if you never called her Mother—
does that really mean
you never thought of her as your mother?
I don't think so.
Because if that were true,
why would you be this sad now?
I'm not very good at comforting people,
but I want to say this to you.
It's okay to be sad.
It's okay to cry if you need to.
But don't
let grief ruin your health.
More importantly,
don't hurt yourself just to punish people
who aren't worth it.
Because you are not alone in this world.
Think about Grandmother.
Think about Rong.
And think about me.
There are already more than ten memorials
impeaching you for favoring your concubine
and driving your lawful wife to death.
Some of the more aggressive officials
are even demanding
that you be stripped of your post
and brought to justice.
[Misty Waves in Serenity]
I'm here to let you know
and give you time
to prepare yourself.
For now,
things haven't gotten that bad yet.
But once those censors
get their hands on hard evidence,
you'll truly be doomed.
I plan to go to the Shuntian Prefecture
and accuse Gu Dezhao
of driving his wife to suicide.
I'm not here to discuss it with you.
I just came over
to inform you.
I'm finished.
Do you also think
I shouldn't sue Master?
I...
I just think
Master deserves to be punished.
But suing him
at the cost of your reputation,
Rong's future,
and enduring that 40 strokes of the cane—
I just think...
it's not worth it.
My future
is all ruined!
My Lady.
Master.
[Written Confession]
It's my fault.
It's all my fault.
I wrongly blamed Han.
I caused Han's death.
It's all my fault!
I planned to go to the Shuntian Prefecture
to sue you.
Oh...
I've changed my mind.
I've thought it through.
If I sue you,
the worst you'll face is
a ruined reputation,
a demotion,
or being stripped of your post.
And you
deserve much worse than this.
Tell me,
why did Madam Ji Han take her own life?
She... she was
too hard on herself.
She fell ill from depression.
She was trapped by you,
trapped by this mansion—
with no way out.
I want you to suffer
the same as she did.
What do you want?
I want three things from you.
First,
from now on,
whether you remarry
or take another concubine,
you must have my approval.
What?
Second,
you have no right to interfere
in my marriage or Rong's.
How is that even possible?
Third...
Qingpu.
What is this?
[Letter of Amicable Separation]
This is a letter of amicable separation.
You want me to divorce your mother?
-Your mother is already gone.
-You can still divorce her.
My mo-
my mother's last wish
was not to be buried
in the Gu family burial grounds,
but to be buried
with the Ji family in Tongzhou.
Sign this letter,
and the two of you
will be completely severed.
This...
[Letter of Amicable Separation]
Zhao,
why must you do this?
I know you resent me
because of what happened to your mother.
But your mother is already gone.
Divorcing her now
won't benefit you
or Rong
in any way.
As for Rong and me,
you don't need to concern about us.
Just sign it.
I'm still your biological father.
Why must you force me this far?
If you refuse to sign,
I'll sue you.
At worst,
we'll drag each other down together.
No, no, please don't.
I'll sign it.
[Signed by: Gu Dezhao]
[Memorial]
[Blessings Passed Down for Generations]
Mother!
[Spirit Tablet of the Beloved Mother, Ji Han Yuan Zhen]
Yao,
we are about to leave the town.
You should head back first.
Grandmother is still unwell.
The shop business
can't run itself.
They all need you
to go back and take care of things.
But it's a bit chaotic outside these days.
I...
[Ye]
[Divine Mission, Eternal Prosperity:
The Legacy of the Ji Family]
[The Coffin of Ji Han, Virtuous
Eldest Daughter and Honored Matriarch]
Get up.
Why are you here?
Why didn't you tell me
you were returning to Tongzhou?
Were you planning to leave
without saying goodbye?
After all we've been through,
couldn't you at least let me know?
Never mind.
These are my men.
I'll have them
escort you back to Tongzhou later.
This...
They are my personal guards.
The Yellow River
and Huai River have flooded.
The grain shipments can't get through,
and many areas have suffered disasters.
Lately, in the capital,
the number of refugees
has visibly increased.
With this many carriages
and so few guards,
you'll be an obvious target.
With them escorting you,
I'll feel more at ease.
Okay.
Thank you.
Rong.
Thank you, Your Highness.
With your men accompanying her,
I feel much more reassured.
Together with our own guards
escorting my sister
all the way to Tongzhou,
I suppose it should be safe for her.
Then I'll head back to Tongzhou first.
I'll wait for you to come back.
Yao,
take more men with you as well.
Please be careful on the road.
Thank you.
For what?
This isn't a gift.
Remember to give me
enough silver as a reward later.
This is the kitten we rescued last time.
It's grown this big already.
Alright, alright, alright.
Since Baopu likes you so much,
I'll let you
take care of it for a few days.
Me?
I guess it's fine.
But
I'm only looking after it temporarily.
This cat is still yours.
You're responsible for it.
When you come back,
you have to take it back.
Got it?
Remember what you said.
The weather looks
like it's getting worse.
Hurry up and leave.
She has a sharp tongue,
but a soft heart.
She's clearly suffering inside,
but she insists
on pretending nothing is wrong.
Forget it.
Three years, right?
In three years, I'll protect you.
I won't let anyone bully you.
Young Master?
She's already long out of sight.
Of course I can see that.
[Luhe Coaching Inn]
I told you
to set out earlier,
but you insisted
on leaving in the afternoon.
And now look,
you've been caught in this heavy rain.
Mother, have some tea first.
Calm down.
Out of nowhere,
you said you wanted
to pay respects to the ancestors.
You didn't ask your brother
and sister-in-law to return,
nor did you bring your sister.
Who knows
what you're really up to?
Never mind.
Since you said so,
I'll just go along with it.
I'll accompany you back to Tongzhou.
You are so eloquent, Mother.
I don't even know how to respond.
I heard
Zhao's mother
was driven to death by Gu Dezhao.
Is it true?
Of course it's not true.
Mrs. Gu passed away because
her long-term illness became terminal;
no medicine could have saved her.
Mother, given your friendship
with Old Madam Ji,
you shouldn't spread rumors like that.
Oh, look at you!
I was just chatting with you,
and you started lecturing me.
When you arrive in Tongzhou,
you should visit the Ji family often—
offer some comfort to Old Madam Ji
and Miss Gu.
Of course.
Wait.
Is Zhao
going back to Tongzhou too?
Mrs. Gu's last wish
was to be buried in Tongzhou.
So
Miss Gu is escorting the coffin home.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
We could have traveled together.
But...
it's probably for the best
that I didn't know.
It saves a lot of trouble.
After all,
she's traveling with a coffin,
and at my age,
I can't bear to see such things.
Third Master,
Madam.
Is it here?
Yes.
Who's here?
The Ji family's
funeral procession is here.
Mother,
I'll take my leave now.
Let's go.
You...
It's raining.
Hurry up.
No matter how many rooms they have,
we'll book them all.
Then ask the people at the inn
to clear out the woodshed
so we can place the coffin there.
If that doesn't work,
we'll have to build a shelter.
Right.
And regarding the Marquis's ten guards,
please let them know—whatever they need,
they should feel free to ask.
Understood.
My Lady.
It's the Third Master.
Third Master.
We came across
the memorial shed
that Chen family made along the road.
Thank you for your trouble.
Our families have been close for years.
There's no need to be so formal.
Since the Old Madam's here,
I should've gone to pay my respects.
But since I'm in mourning,
I was afraid it might not be appropriate.
It's fine.
My mother knows you're coming.
She specifically asked me to tell you
not to stand on ceremony,
and you should take care of yourself.
Greetings, Third Master.
Many people are heading
to the capital recently.
Only six rooms in the West Wing are left.
I'm afraid it might not be enough.
We'd rather have our people squeeze in
than slight the Marquis's guards.
Yes, My Lady.
Guards?
Ye Xian sent guards for you?
Yes.
He said it might
not be safe on the way.
How many guards are there?
Ten.
Chen Yi.
Yes, Third Master.
Tell our people
to clear out some rooms
enough for ten people to stay.
Yes, Master.
Thank you, Third Master.
Thank you, Guard Chen.
You're welcome.
Follow me.
[Inn]
Hurry up.
Yes, ma'am.
Get it up there.
Okay.
Hurry, over here too.
Yes, ma'am.
Over here.
The rain is so heavy.
Everyone, be careful not to get hurt.
Don't worry, My Lady.
Hurry, be careful.
-Over here.
-Here.
Go find something
to put another two layers underneath this.
I'll go find some wood.
Still not asleep?
I can't sleep either.
I'm used to it.
I can't fall asleep
before the second watch.
Are you cold?
I'm not going to sue him anymore.
I've made so many mistakes.
When I first returned to the capital,
I never wanted anything
to do with the Gu family.
All I thought about was revenge.
Sure enough,
I quickly found
Nanny Zhou's fault,
and had her beaten.
Later,
at Lord Lin's birthday celebration...
I humiliated my father in public.
Alhough I was forced by circumstance,
I also intended
to make a fool of him.
Later,
when the Liu family came
with a marriage proposal,
I found a way to reject them as well.
Until I found rhubarb
in my mother's medicine.
I thought
I still had everything under control.
things would always go my way.
So I didn't hesitate
to expose the truth.
I claimed to investigate
and cornered my opponent.
I had nothing left to lose,
so I gambled everything.
Then my mother died.
These past few days, I've been thinking...
if I hadn't been
so impulsive back then,
if I had just quietly
treating my mother's illness,
would she still be alive?
It's all my fault.
Is there
a song you'd like to hear?
[A Splendid Match]