( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(Previously)
I told you Run is just a friend.
Stop being so petty!
I'm going to celebrate Jim's birthday.
Want to surprise him?
You'll get a surprise yourself.
Do you know where Jimmy is?
Make up...
What the hell am I to you?!
Do you think I love you that much?
We're through.
Once we're done, never
show your face to me again.
Not even as friends.
Am I gonna be the fool again?
Why didn't you go sleep
in your room properly?
P'Toh.
Hey,
why are you burning up?
"Love Alert" (Episode 7)
From the look of it,
they've really broken up this time.
My friend said Jimmy was
drinking non-stop last night.
They must have had a massive fight.
Always drowns his sorrows
when there's a problem.
Heaven,
make his liver the
only part that gets hard.
What a piece of work, moron.
Poor P'Toh.
This time must've hit him really hard.
What can I do?
He never listens to me
but his own heart.
That's why he hurts like this.
But I hope this is the last time, brother.
When you're better,
just be done with someone like him.
Finally, you showed up, bastard.
What did you do to my brother?!
He's not your toy!
What did I even do?
He made a scene and started a fight.
Because you're a scumbag!
You left him to suffer
with a high fever at home!
It's all your fault, you jerk!
Huh?!
What happened to P'Toh?
Let go! I won't punch him.
So now you're worried?
You left him to go home
alone in the pouring rain.
No matter how bad the fight was,
you should've never let him go like that!
Teh, enough.
You helped your brother.
It's my turn to finish Jimmy off.
Listen up, everyone.
I want you all to know…
that Teh and I are dating.
And I know about the
"deal" Jimmy made with Teh.
As you can see,
both sides have broken the rules.
Teh is dating me, and you're dating P'Toh.
But do you know the difference?
What?
Teh…
actually loves me.
It's not about winning
or fun.
Unlike what you're doing to P'Toh.
So,
stay away from P'Toh.
A man like him is too good for you.
Teh.
What exactly am I to you?
What the hell am I to you?!
Am I your partner…
or just someone you keep around for sex?
Try being in my shoes, Jim.
Just try being me for once.
Do you think I love you that much?
Aren't you the one who's been chasing me?
Aren't you the one who's in love?
Let's see who gets hurt more.
P'Toh!
Congratulations!
Thank you.
Congratulations on the café, P'Toh.
I hope it's a huge success!
You can afford to spoil me forever!
Is that a blessing for me or for you?
Go grab a seat. I'll bring you some coffee.
- Give me a sec.
- Sure.
It's good that he's busy,
It'll keep his mind off Jimmy.
I think I'll help him post
photos on Instagram.
Great idea.
He looks really happy.
We're taking photos for
fun, not for an ID card.
I'm not a model, duh.
Having a photographer
as a boyfriend is so hard.
You're wrong.
You're perfect to me.
Smile.
Big smile.
- Smile more.
- Ugh, get a room, you two.
Dear customers, I have
cookies for you to try.
Have a taste and let me
know if they're any good.
Will do.
But first.
Teh,
take a photo of me and P'Toh.
Yes.
Alright.
Smile.
Big smile.
Smile!
Enough.
Another one, P'Toh.
Gimme a sec.
Is this necessary?
Okay.
Right.
Smile.
Okay.
Let me take a selfie.
Come.
One… two…
And a video clip.
Ready?
Spin.
Spin, spin, spin, spin, spin.
Spin, spin, spin again.
Another spin, spin, spin, spin.
This angle.
Down here.
There.
Teh,
that's enough.
I need to go back to my customers.
Thanks a lot.
Let's take a selfie.
He didn't tell me about the opening.
Well, your Mama started it.
I'm not gonna die over something like this.
We're through.
I don't give a damn anyway.
If I didn't have class,
I'd stay and help you until closing time.
It's okay. You've done more
than enough. Thanks a lot.
Fah and I will get those
photos up on the page ASAP.
I've already posted them on my IG.
Alright.
Get going. See you both this evening.
I'm so sorry.
It's alright.
P'Toh. Are you okay?
I'm fine. Don't worry.
You can go.
I'm truly sorry about that.
Don't worry about it.
Are you here for some coffee?
Yes.
We give a 30% discount on all
drinks today. Please, come on in.
Thank you.
Jimmy, right.
I'm Bank from Engineering.
Can I…
get your socials?
I've heard you're single now.
Of course. News sure travels fast.
I'm single and ready to mingle.
P'Toh is such a magnet.
Did you see those customers today?
It's like they focused only on him.
Yeah,
the guy who bumped into him this morning.
He was top-tier.
Yeah,
he looked so warm,
friendly, and sophisticated.
Anyway,
are you free tonight?
Want to play some games at my place?
Send me your location.
I'll be there.
Catch you later.
Is he running a café or a dating agency?
This cup is an apology for my clumsiness.
Woah,
do you want me to stay
awake all night, Mr. Toh?
Oh, I heard someone…
maybe your brother, called you earlier.
Ah.
Yes, that was my brother.
I'm Doctor Freeze.
Oh,
foce of habit.
You can just call me P'Freeze.
Sure.
You can just call me Toh.
So, you're a doctor?
Yes, I'm a dentist at the hospital nearby.
Feel free to stop by
for a check-up anytime.
You drew this yourself?
You're talented. It's so cute.
Yes, I planned to draw for every customer.
But since it's my first day,
It's been a bit chaotic.
So yours is the very first one I've done.
Wow, I'm honored then.
And the coffee's excellent.
Thank you.
Please let me know if
you have any feedback.
Of course.
Mr, Toh, we're almost out of ice.
How do I order more?
I think I wrote the number down somewhere.
Please excuse me, Mr. Freeze.
Take your time.
Have a seat.
Right here?
But I like it… it's exciting.
Bank,
your cologne is too strong.
I'm not in the mood today.
Don't call me over if
you're not in the mood.
You wasting my time.
I'm usually not like this. I'm sorry.
You're the "hotshot?" What a joke.
Saensee,
let me tell you something.
If Mama begs me, I'm
ready to take him back.
Are you saying it's my fault?
Listen to me.
I'm never wrong. I never beg anyone first.
You're my son.
You must be on my side.
What are you looking for?
Creamy treats.
Fresh out.
I totally forgot to buy them.
Don't worry, I'll buy some for you.
Recently, you only love Saensee, huh?
I must love the boy as well as his Papa.
I don't believe you.
I still don't believe you.
What about now?
No.
Believe me.
You win.
This is a bonus.
If I want to stop the pain, I must end it.
I'm sorry, Saensee.
P'Toh is such a magnet.
Did you see those customers today?
The guy who bumped into him this morning.
He was top-tier.
He looked so warm,
friendly, and sophisticated.
Must be that four-eyes.
What should I do?
Oh, Toh. One of my patients gave me
a bunch of these art exhibition flyers.
So I thought I'd bring some
for you and your sibling.
An art exhibition?
I think I saw this online.
If you're free to go, let me know.
I'm looking for someone to go with.
But I'm not sure if
I'll have any free time.
I understand. It's always hectic
when you first open a shop.
Can I…
have your contact info?
If our schedules align,
we can head there together.
Sure.
Here.
- Done.
- Thank you.
What did you find out?
The guy talking to the owner
is Freeze. He's a dentist.
They've exchanged numbers.
They're already at that stage?
You can see it from
Mars—he's hitting on him.
He made some excuse about
flyers just to ask him out.
And the owner just gave in that easily?
Fine. Show me your QR code.
I'll transfer the payment.
Hey.
Did the owner draw this?
Yeah, why?
- Can I have it?
- Hey. You said you'd pay for the whole tab.
I'm transferring your fee right now.
It's enough to buy ten more cups.
I'm taking this.
Is that all you need?
Thank you.
The guy talking to the owner
is Freeze. He's a dentist.
They've exchanged numbers.
You can see it from
Mars—he's hitting on him.
He made some excuse about
flyers just to ask him out.
Someone's hitting on your Mama today.
He's a dentist, no less.
Can your Dad even compete with that?
Once we're done,
never show your face to me again.
Not even as friends.
Remember what you just said!
I'm rooting for this guy with all I've got.
Me too! He's polite, warm,
and has a stable career.
I'm sure he can take good care of you.
Enough, both of you.
P'Freeze hasn't even done anything.
I know that right away,
that "using flyers
just to ask you out" move.
It's such a classic.
Oh.
You're way too naïve.
If he's not interested, he wouldn't
show up two days in a row like this.
Mark my words, he'll be back tomorrow.
He's just a customer stopping by for coffee.
There are hundreds of cafes
around here. Why specifically mine?
Am I right?
Exactly.
You should open your heart a little.
Or are you waiting for Jimmy?
What is it about Jimmy that
makes you head over heels for him?
Alright, that's enough.
I'm going back to work.
I need to spend time with Mr. Freeze.
I'll ask to tutor him.
P'Toh will surely give in then.
More like give in to Jimmy
if he comes back to beg.
No way. When P'Toh
says it's over, it's over.
He looks kind, but he can be very stubborn.
You might be right.
When I mentioned Jimmy earlier,
he just shut me down.
Maybe there's no return this time.
If that's true, I'll be so satisfied.
I'm just waiting for the
day P'Toh dates Dr. Freeze.
I'll post a photo and
rub it in Jimmy's face!
You're pretty savage.
Plaifah!
P'Toh will see us.
Don't worry. It's kinda exciting.
Don't be too loud, okay?
It's too lonely to drink alone.
Wanna hang out with me?
No.
I have a boyfriend.
Oh, you have one?
But he broke up with me.
He's not coming back.
I have to fix this…
Then I hope you can win him back.
Stealing my girl like that?
You think you're hot?
You want some, punks?!
- Come at me!
- I'll get you.
So much for Mr. Hotshot.
God, you're so damn huge.
And heavy as hell.
You'd better be grateful when you sober up.
P'Toh.
Did you see that?
I didn't go with another guy.
Am I a good boy?
Good boy, your ass!
You wouldn't hurt my brother
if you were actually good!
Teh!
My best buddy.
Can you please tell your
brother that… I'm sorry?
I was wrong.
Please.
Too late for that. Serves you right.
Move it, I'm taking you home.
I'm not going back!
I want to beg P'Toh.
Since I've broken up with him,
I've always missed him.
I miss him every single night.
If I could've turned back time,
I would've done everything better.
I wouldn't have disappointed him.
You must help me.
I'm begging you.
Just get in the car.
If I could've turned back time,
I wouldn't have loved you like this.
P'Toh.
I'm so sorry for bringing him here.
He was wasted.
And almost got his ass kicked.
When he wakes up, tell him to leave.
I don't want to see his face.
P'Toh.
I've never seen him this broken before.
I'm going to bed.
I have to open the café early.
If P'Toh is mad at me, you're dead, moron.
P'Toh.
Feeling better?
I promise.
I won't hurt you ever again.
It's too late for that, Jimmy.
P'Toh.
P'Toh!
Well, your Mama started it.
I'm not gonna die over something like this.
We're through.
I don't give a damn anyway.
Mama hasn't stopped loving me, right?
(Next Episode) Please help
me get back with your brother.
P'Toh!
I'm so sorry.
Please give me one more chance.
I really like you.
Would you like to try dating me?