I used to always pick a bad hand.
Crap...
Bring Mom.
When a couple fights,
the husband should reach out first.
Oh, it's working.
Do you need anything?
I'll get it for you.
My dad was hard-working
but struggled to make ends meet.
I always felt sad and bad for him.
Just get a new car.
This one sounds like
a 100-year-old grandpa coughing.
She can hear you!
Don't be so heartless.
I'm afraid it's dangerous.
This baby won't put me in danger.
You'll be alone without me.
Drive safe.
Are you coming at night?
I'll be pretty late.
Check the doors before bed!
Who would steal anything from us?
There you go.
Go on now.
Bye.
She's pretty. Just like her mom.
So what? Her mom ran away.
Mr. Kang shouldn't have married her
for her pretty face.
-I feel sorry for that poor kid.
-Stop it.
The poor kid whose mom ran away.
In this tiny little neighborhood,
people talked about us to pass the time.
And it hurt me more
because I was going through puberty.
Dad...
Where's he going?
It's raining. Shall we rent a video?
-Shall we have some ramyeon too?
-Sounds great.
I'll go rent it.
-Hurry back.
-Okay.
Mom?
To carry on,
I had to accept that it was just my life.
That my life was just one
of the awful ones.
That there was no reason
that I shouldn't be
one of the unlucky ones.
It's 1,200 won.
Did you lose your wallet?
Goodness. You make it so obvious
that your mother ran away.
Because of your mother,
you must act smart
so others won't find fault with you.
You know that, right?
Don't be so nosy.
Here.
Is it yours?
So anything was good.
I was desperate to feel a hand
reaching out to me.
JEONG SU-MIN
What?
Those brats...
I'll punish you!
Too desperate to judge
whether it was land or swamp.
But
I was determined not to do it again
with my second chance.
I was going to fight, grow,
and become happier than anyone else.
It was finally my turn
to pick a good hand.
I picked a good hand this time.
I believed I'd be happy.
I called to talk,
but you wouldn't pick up.
I thought about coming back later.
But you might keep dodging my calls,
so I waited to see you.
Ji-won.
I can explain this.
I was wrong. I still only pick bad hands.
EPISODE 12
BASED ON THE NAVER SERIES WEBNOVEL
MARRY MY HUSBAND BY SUNGSOJAK
Hui-yeon, I'm sorry...
Ms. Kang, what do we do?
Just now,
I called Ms. Yang
because she didn't show up.
What do we do?
Ms. Yang has stomach cancer.
That's why life's hard.
The future's a mystery.
I thought I'd knew everything
at this age when I was a kid.
No, you're doing great.
I read your column in the company paper
about that unfortunate incident.
The staff could've been shaken.
It was the appropriate response.
I was proud.
And I felt bad for asking you
to clean up my employee's mess.
We're like family.
It's the least I could do.
My father always told me
not to forget that U&amp;K was my family.
I've never thought differently.
Gang-cheol's so lucky.
He's raised you well.
If you feel that way, I shouldn't have
broken off the engagement.
We got engaged because of our parents,
and Ji-hyuk was so apathetic.
And I never liked him as a man.
That's why I agreed
to break off the engagement.
But he's become charming.
What's happened?
So I'm going to stay in Korea
for quite a while.
Can I do that?
I'll come and see you often.
How would it feel to have my boyfriend
marry my best friend?
Would I feel lucky
since I got a new rich boyfriend?
It's like a soap, isn't it?
You bought a car
to take me to the hospital.
How long since you last drove?
How were the test results?
It's not going to be easy.
I have to wait long
because the doctor's schedule is full.
Still, medicine's gotten
so much better, so...
I hate this.
I get weak if I'm with you.
I can endure it if I'm alone.
That's exactly why I follow you around.
You can't be mentally healthy
when you're in pain.
Cry.
Don't hold it back. Just cry in my arms.
You have to cry.
Why are you so good to me?
It's my fault.
My fate went to her.
But why?
This doesn't end with Min-hwan's marriage?
Hey.
Stop glaring.
You should've told my mom
if you hated this place.
How can I tell her?
You should've told her for me.
Why would I?
I think my mom's right.
It's dangerous
for a pregnant woman to fly.
All right. Fine.
The honeymoon isn't important.
Min-hwan.
Let's live a good life, okay?
You're the head of our house now.
-The baby--
-Hey!
Why am I the head?
Ji-won never said that.
Su-min.
You're great and all,
but you don't know marriage.
Listen carefully.
Marriages work well
when each spouse does their own job.
What?
You didn't like the wedding invitation,
didn't understand Mom,
and hated the honeymoon destination,
You keep complaining to me.
That's because
you only think about yourself.
Look at me.
Did I say anything
about your friends who caused a scene
at our wedding?
You were upset and threw your phone at me.
Hey!
Are they the same thing?
There's no use talking to you...
Forget it.
Damn it.
Congratulations
on picking up my trash.
No.
Hey, Sang-jong. Has it been rented out?
Yeah, I just wired the money.
-Thank you.
-Bye.
Okay.
But is it really okay to tell your mom
you were scammed?
Even if she falls for it,
won't your wife throw a fit about it?
I'm her only son. She won't kill me.
And it wasn't my wife's money,
so what can she do?
Hold on.
YU SANG-JONG: 360 MILLION WON
Okay, I got the money!
Debts are assets too. It'll be okay.
Okay, thanks. Bye!
Oh, my God!
What were you talking about?
What?
What do you mean? What did you hear?
What did you mean?
You said it wasn't my money!
Well...
It'll be released soon.
This puts us in a spot.
They even checked the draft.
How could they back out now?
You can't do this before the launch.
This is insane.
Wait! Wait a second!
What is it, Hui-yeon?
Are things not going well
with the project the respected Ms. Yang
and Ms. Kang are working on?
-Tae-hyeong.
-Yes?
Don't hold onto a hopeless project.
Let's go smoke, okay?
Yeah, let's go.
Keep working, okay?
It's 1:45 p.m.
You took three and a half days off,
and you show up to work now?
You act so meticulous at work,
but you're more meticulous
about your free time.
Mr. Kim?
Yes, Ms. Kang?
You must be going somewhere far
to smoke during work hours.
Since Ms. Yang is away,
you should help with the meal kit,
but you don't review the data.
Oh, that?
I don't need to review it. That's why.
Tae-hyeong, let's go.
The chefs suddenly
canceled their contracts? Why?
What?
What's with Chef Lee Gwang-min?
We're about to release. Why postpone?
He says the product's of poor quality.
Honestly, it's ridiculous.
I think something's up. Kim Gyeong-uk...
I mean, Mr. Kim is good at politics.
He has connections.
I think he did something.
What about Ms. Yang?
I took her home.
I think she should take time off.
Time off...
It's not time for me to be angry.
But you won't hear me out,
and you made me
call you like this at work.
I'm sorry.
I needed time to sort my thoughts.
I was confused.
I was given another chance,
and I thought I just had to get
Min-hwan and Su-min to marry.
While I was doing it, you were...
like a gift to me.
Did you ever hear that I was married?
It gets sorted out in a few years anyway.
I just sped up the process.
Yu-ra's a family friend
since we were kids.
I thought I could marry her
without any feelings.
But that wasn't the case,
so I ended it with her.
You can marry someone
without any feelings?
Such relationships exist.
To be honest,
I didn't know how I felt about you
before your funeral.
So I ended it when I got back.
That's all.
I don't know.
Everything you say
just sounds like an excuse to me.
Ji-won.
I'm not trying to blame you.
I just...
I realized I dreamed of something
too happy.
At the lake,
you told me
having a family was a good thing.
Do you know what it means
to not have a family?
I wanted to start a family.
Yes, I made a mistake.
My mom...
left home when I was 14.
She found love.
She endured for 14 years
because of me, but...
No matter how long you endure,
those left behind...
get hurt.
No matter what the relationship is,
once it's started,
I don't think it's right for one person
to end it one-sidedly.
I recruited Dr. Lee to our cancer ward
from the States.
She specializes in stomach cancer.
YUIL MEDICAL CENTER
DR. LEE HYEON-JI
I spent half a year on this.
Ms. Yang will receive
surgery as soon as possible.
Hello?
I hate clichés like this,
but I guess I can't help it.
Thanks for coming.
I thought it was only right
to talk to you, so I came.
There's nothing to worry--
That's not for you to decide, is it?
It bothers me.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know he was engaged.
And I'm going to stop seeing him.
In life, there are times
when you accidently stab someone.
But saying you didn't know
and will never do it again
doesn't cut it.
What do you want me to do?
I liked him.
I didn't mean to, but I fell for him.
So I had a happy dream for a moment.
However, after I found out about you,
I ended it.
I didn't know how I felt...
So I ended it when I got back.
That's interesting that you fell for him.
Didn't you have a boyfriend
of seven years?
You were practically married to him.
Why did you suddenly fall for your boss?
After seven years of working.
Because Ji-hyuk's U&amp;K's successor?
-It's not like that.
-Then you didn't know?
My grandfather knew...
...promoted to CEO...
...that I just
didn't want anything.
My life was decided since birth.
So I studied and worked only for U&amp;K.
So you knew.
I think we're done.
If you'll excuse me.
What I hate the most
are people like you.
Self-righteous nobodies.
You were greedy but say you weren't.
You know everything but pretend you don't.
You're not dumb enough to not know
he could change your life.
How predictable.
You're the type of person I hate as well.
Do you think everyone's like you?
You think it was important to me
that he was U&amp;K's successor?
It didn't matter to me at all.
Because...
my life changed without him.
I need to get a grip.
If the cancer went to Yang Ju-ran...
Wait...
What happens now?
-Open the door.
-Okay.
Say bye to your mom.
Say bye. Bye.
Princess.
Don't come here anymore. Rest at home.
Okay? Go on now.
I'm Lee Jae-won, Ju-ran's husband.
I have stomach cancer.
What am I doing right now?
Let's go.
Are you cold?
Go inside first.
-What?
-Your lips.
Husband...
What if the fate has something to do
with the husband, not marrying Min-hwan?
I went to see Dr. Lee.
I made treatment appointments.
I can get surgery soon too.
I don't know why,
but she always left one spot open.
She specializes in stomach cancer.
I spent half a year on this.
What? A scam?
-I'll kill that real estate agent.
-No, Mom!
I took care of it. I spoke to her, Mom.
What did you take care of?
Why are you on your knees here if you did?
When I think about it, Su-min is
different from me.
Right.
If you think about it,
this is all your fault.
What does a man know?
This is why a good woman
needs to join the family.
I shouldn't have been so hasty.
I felt strangely hesitant about this.
It felt wrong.
Although she married Min-hwan like me,
would she just let them
walk all over her like me?
Mother.
You should get the facts straight.
You picked the house
and gave him money to sign the contract.
Why are you blaming me?
I mean, after I let it slide that he was
renting a house, not buying one.
Goodness.
Listen to you! I've been nice to you
since you're pregnant.
You didn't bring anything,
but what? You let it slide?
I have money.
He said to not bring anything.
I guess it's because
he wanted to move in here...
Hey.
You're a contract employee. What money?
Contract employee?
You said she'd work after giving birth.
She will.
She's a competent contract employee.
I did stocks.
-What?
-I earned quite a lot.
What?
I'm not excited about this at all either.
And let's be honest. I did everything
you wanted for the wedding.
And during the honeymoon,
I learned of his--
Hush!
In any case, stop hitting Min-hwan.
He's the head of the household
and our baby's dad.
Or shall I just leave
with our baby general?
Our baby...
Here it is.
Marriage isn't all that bad, right?
I gained an ally.
Don't worry.
My mom can be harsh,
but she's cool.
Once our baby's born,
she'll buy us a house!
Once she hears the baby crying,
she can't withstand it.
There's no baby.
What? No what? What did you say?
My God!
I'll be home later.
Make sure the house is clean.
I can't believe this is my life.
I have two more mouths to feed at my age.
God, such nuisances.
Darn it...
What do you mean?
There's no what?
I...
had a miscarriage.
When you threw your phone at me,
my stomach started to hurt.
I was so scared.
And I didn't know what to do.
I didn't want to disappoint your mom,
so I couldn't tell you.
Our baby.
By the way...
You said you craved beef
during our honeymoon because of the baby.
But didn't you not have the baby then?
Didn't you say you had a house
when you didn't too?
What?
But our baby...
Ms. Kang!
You scared me.
Didn't you leave earlier?
I thought of you.
Since last Christmas,
I've been trying to eat healthy.
This is rich in protein and so crunchy!
It's my favorite lately.
Really?
It is good.
But for some reason...
Does it remind you of something?
It's probably this!
It's perfect. I desperately needed it.
To tell the truth, my brother bought
all this saying you'd need it.
What?
He's been hesitant
and walking on eggshells lately.
Is it because of Yu-ra?
Yes, well...
She's been seeing my grandpa.
But Ms. Kang,
whether he called off the engagement
for you or because he came to his senses,
I'm totally in favor.
To tell you the truth,
he got engaged because of me.
He said we should make a family
firm enough to stand on like land.
Also, my brother had no interest
in dating.
He just seemed emotionless.
He always suppressed his emotions.
Like some robot.
He's so different lately.
He wasn't like this.
The weather is chilly.
-Go inside.
-I'm okay.
-Hey.
-I'm back.
I'll escort Yu-ra now.
Yeah, okay. Bye.
-I'll come again.
-Okay, come often.
-Okay.
-Bye.
What are you doing?
I've been meaning to tell you this.
You've changed a lot.
You didn't just change your appearance.
You're a man now.
I came to see your grandfather.
No matter how our relationship is,
he and I are still close.
That's interesting.
I think you two suddenly got closer.
You came to Korea on the 8th
and visited him three times.
It never happened
in our five-year engagement.
Things like this.
You didn't care about anything but work.
You're so detailed now.
Is it because of her?
Didn't you accept my decision?
That was before I knew there was a woman.
I don't like anyone touching
what's mine.
Also, Yu-ra may seem normal,
but she's a total whack job.
Get out.
How much longer will you do this?
You know we're not anything.
It's her fault. Why covet what's mine?
I don't like anyone touching what's mine.
Enough.
Ms. Kang.
I know Mr. Yu's a good person.
This is my fault.
So let's stop talking about this.
Ms. Kang.
I'm not actually his real little sister.
My brother was hurt badly
because of me and my mom.
So...
He could never cheat on anyone.
I realized it again.
Yu-ra's a great kid.
You don't think she visits you
with good intentions, do you?
That's why I like her.
She's greedy enough
to be lady of the U&amp;K household.
I like those who obsess
over what's theirs.
A man should meet the right woman.
A woman needs spite to protect her family.
You're right. You said that.
That's why I thought it'd be okay.
Grandfather.
When my mother was alive,
how did you feel
about Father meeting Ms. Cha?
Did Ms. Cha have more spite and greed
than my mother?
I liked Ms. Cha.
Mother was always sick,
and I relied more on her as a kid.
Before I learned that Hui-yeon was
only five years younger than me.
After learning that,
I felt bad for Hui-yeon.
So after I got engaged to Yu-ra,
I held it in
even when I couldn't stand it.
I vowed that I'd never become
like my father.
But I only learned
things didn't work that way
when I saw the end.
But...
What should I have done, Grandfather?
It's too hard.
So he's the bastard that cheated on
his girlfriend with her bestie.
And she's the bitch that married
her bestie's boyfriend.
Because they don't know who Ji-hyuk is?
Yes.
Those fools.
What if they find out?
There's laundry to do today.
Don't just do what's in the basket.
Organize the closet
and wash the old clothes too.
By myself? Where are you going?
I'm the secretary of the Women's Center.
I have a luncheon.
Oh, right.
Since you're alone, take it easy
while listening to it.
Isn't your life so sweet?
You're so lucky.
Your grandmother will be back later,
our little general.
Darn it...
Seriously?
Is this really right?
Is this married life?
What's this?
U&amp;K STOCKHOLDER'S LIST
Yu Ji-hyuk...
YU JI-HYUK
YU HUI-YEON
What is this?
No way.
Did she really...
Su-min.
I have some trash to throw away.
Will you do it for me?
Congratulations
on picking up my trash.
She dumps Min-hwan on me
and goes for a rich man?
No way. No.
I stole him.
I did it.
I did!
No!
Why is...
the house like this?
Why are you asking me?
Your wife did this to the house,
locked the door, and won't come out.
What?
Damn it...
All that tall jerk did
was be born into the right family.
What the hell have my parents done
their entire lives?
I can fly much higher
with a little support.
Are you jealous of Yu Ji-hyuk right now?
Kang Ji-won dumped you on me.
So what will you do about it now?
So it wasn't just trash.
I picked up trash with no pride.
You little...
Not just that. You're stupid too.
Have you paid off your debt?
My mom can hear you. Stop bring that up.
How much is left?
Is 100 million won enough?
What?
We deserve compensation.
Why does Ji-won get all the good stuff?
Are you out of your mind?
Do you think she'll give it to you?
I'll make her.
I know everything about her.
Even what she doesn't know.
Happy you beat me?
You're my other half.
We can't just end things like this.
Ji-won, I can't reach you.
How have you been?
I heard about you by chance.
It's your mom.
Ji-won.
You grew up so well.
You really did.
You're still beautiful.
You were always
the prettiest in our neighborhood.
I'm all old now.
Time can't help but pass.
You're pretty too.
I'm glad you take after me.
I know it's in the past now,
but I never liked your father much.
I was young and struggling,
and he liked me so much.
I thought I could like him too.
Everyone got married like that back then.
So I didn't like you either.
I mean, I did.
You're my kid. How could I not?
Anyway, I'm sorry.
I was immature.
I had you when I wasn't ready.
Still...
I missed you so much.
Then why didn't you come to see me?
Forget my dad,
you could've come to see me.
I did.
He didn't let me.
Do you not know
how much he cared about you?
I know he was a good father to you.
He was sweet.
But he was so stubborn.
He wasn't considerate.
It was hard for me too.
I was only able to come to see you
after I heard your father had passed.
It took me courage.
My father tried his best to raise me.
Of course, your absence was big for me.
I was just an adolescent girl.
That's why I became attached
to the wrong people.
I didn't know how to express myself.
No...
Actually, I didn't know how I felt.
There was no one to teach me.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
I was a bad mother,
and it made you suffer.
How can I make it up to you?
How can I do it?
What are you doing tomorrow?
What?
If you're free,
would you like to spend time with me?
Did you get home okay yesterday?
Did you sleep well?
Yes, what about you, Mom?
Is it because I met you?
I couldn't sleep at all.
Are you craving anything?
Pork gukbap.
Do you know how to do this?
This is my first time.
This is pretty.
Where do we look?
Here?
I LOVE YOU
WITH MOM
Heart?
One, two, three.
This is so pretty.
They don't sell this in Busan.
Does it look good on me?
We'll take this.
No, don't!
That's okay.
This is so expensive.
Show us this.
It's too expensive.
Still, shall I just try it on?
-Can we?
-Yes.
How does it look?
-It looks good.
-Does it?
I wanted to buy something like this.
My friends brag
about their daughters so much.
How does it look?
It looks good on you.
What about the black?
The size is...
Are you that happy?
Of course.
I'm so lucky to have a daughter like you.
Since you date a rich man,
you know how to spend...
I knew it.
Even when I went to a good college and
joined a big company, you never called.
Ji-won, what I just said--
If you're talking about Yu Ji-hyuk,
I'm not seeing him. We broke up.
What?
Why on earth?
Are you lying to me right now?
Why did you do it?
Why?
Then why did you run away?
I didn't want to believe it.
Goodness. Look who called.
How have you been?
-It's been so long--
-I heard you needed money.
Did you know everything?
Then what is this?
I wanted to try it once.
A date with my mom.
A loved daughter, a good daughter.
Happy mother and daughter.
I wanted to try it once.
Now I've done it.
Have a safe trip back.
Do you have any money?
A good college and a good company.
Do you have 100 million won?
I'll never come see you again.
Do you think I wanted to?
You should understand me!
Who else would understand your mom?
I have no money. I have no mother either.
I didn't before,
and I won't in the future.
You chose to live as a woman
instead of a mother,
so live the rest of your life
that way quietly.
Don't be greedy.
You wench.
No wonder they live like that.
Why do I always have to do it myself
to get things done properly?
I said I was going to a funeral.
No one died!
I can't stay at home.
Try a married life. Can you come out now?
Damn it...
What was that?
What?
Park Min-hwan?
Yes?
I flipped him!
For the first time. Finally!
Yes, I've still got it!
The reserve for the national...
KANG HYEON-MO
Dad.
The gift you gave me...
I wanted to use it really well this time.
But why is the world so hard on me?
I hurt someone precious to me again.
It's all too difficult for me.
I really wanted to do well this time.
What do I do?
What do I do in this case?
I'm sorry I'm such a fool.
Yes.
Okay. In three minutes?
I understand.
Kang Ji-won stole my fiancé.
You punish the woman who betrayed you,
and change your life with a fortune.
What do I have to do to make that happen?
Kill Kang Ji-won.
I'll clean up the mess.
Do as you're told,
and this shitty life is over.
Say it again.
Stop lying.
Why are you doing this to me?
I can't protect you forever.
I like you so much.
Don't blame yourself.
The inevitable just happened.