( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(Lee Na Young)
(Jung Eun Chae)
(Lee Chung Ah)
(Honour)
(Supported by the Culture Ministry
and Korea's Creative Content Agency)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and animals were
filmed under production guidelines.)
(From an old friend, Park Ju Hwan)
It's been a while.
I missed you, Ra Young.
What's with that look? It's
like you've seen a ghost.
I heard the news. About
your tenth anniversary.
So I stopped by to congratulate
you, even if I'm a little late.
(From an old friend, Park Ju Hwan)
Where are Shin Jae and
Hyun Jin? Are they inside?
They're not here right now.
Really?
That's a shame. I hoped to
see them while I was here.
Let's go out. We can grab a coffee.
(Hankuk University
College of Law Newsletter)
By any chance,
what about the male
student that went missing?
Was his body ever found?
You mean Ju Hwan?
Ju Hwan didn't die.
He was found in a
hospital a few days later.
A passerby found him
and took him to the hospital,
but I guess they couldn't identify him.
If he's alive, why couldn't
they find the culprit?
Because Ju Hwan lost his memory.
Due to a cerebral haemorrhage,
he lost all memory of the accident.
I hear the after-effects were
severe. He took leave for rehab,
and went abroad. I haven't
heard from him since then.
Park Ju Hwan.
Spyware?
The Connect In app. They
were hacking our phones.
- They were watching our every move.
- That's insane.
Wait, how did they even know it was us?
They could've just been
collecting data from all users.
(Trainer)
Or we might have gotten flagged
by one of their security filters.
(Voice detected does not match VIP 0911.)
Or it could be both.
Gosh, I can't believe the
lengths these guys go to.
You need AI technology to do
this kind of real-time monitoring.
But to run an AI with this
level of deep learning...
This is no normal trafficking ring.
It's not amateurs who slapped an app,
and a website together, running
it as a gambling operation.
These guys are total pros.
Where's Attorney Yoon?
She stepped out to meet a friend.
The one who sent the flowers...
A friend? Who?
(From an old friend, Park Ju Hwan)
Which way did Attorney Yoon go?
So when did you get back
- to Korea?
- That's ancient history.
I was at a provincial office. I
just moved to Seoul recently.
I thought I'd say hello,
so I just dropped by for a minute.
(Park Je Yeol, Seoul Mujin
Regional Prosecutors' Office)
You changed your name?
You know how it is.
Victims often change their
names after an accident.
Because they want to put it behind them.
I guess that's why I became a prosecutor.
Because I know all too well
that until the culprit is caught,
the victim can never escape
their own personal hell.
A victim?
My head was crushed in. I
wasn't the perpetrator, was I?
I'm sorry about what happened.
That they never caught the culprit,
and that you lost your memory.
Considering you were so sorry,
you had no problem dumping me.
You never even visited me
in the hospital once after that.
And on top of all that, you
broke up with me over a text.
Can you imagine how hurt I was?
But I get it.
Complications from a
cerebral haemorrhage.
I'm still suffering from them.
I guess you were just too
pretty to stick by a sick boyfriend.
But of course,
you still are
just as beautiful.
And look what we have
here. Another welcome face.
How could I ignore a
friend I've missed so dearly?
That wouldn't be right.
It's hot.
It's been a while.
It has. What's it been, 20 years?
I heard you moved abroad, so
I didn't think I'd see you again.
But I guess life is full of surprises.
Why's that? Was there a reason
- you didn't want to see me again?
- Because I've always hated you.
I was against it from the start,
when Ra Young started dating you.
(Park Je Yeol, Seoul Mujin
Regional Prosecutors' Office)
Goodness, you became a prosecutor?
And you changed your name.
What, did you commit a crime?
That's usually what ex-cons do.
- Your name's still the same.
- That's because.
I have nothing to be ashamed of.
That's a relief. I'd hate to
see a friend as a suspect.
Let's wrap up this little reunion.
- We'll be seeing each other again.
- We will?
I'm planning to reinvestigate
what happened back then.
And since it happened so long
ago, I might need all of your help.
See you around.
Ra Young.
Yoon Ra Young!
Look at me.
It's okay.
Okay, breathe.
Again.
Good.
One more time.
That jerk. How dare he come here?
(Found the Connect In app.
(Call me before you come.)
Is the pain that bad? Should
I ask for more painkillers?
It's Brahms.
Brahms and Dvorak.
Mahler, Bruckner, Shostakovich.
In painting, Baroque.
Caravaggio, Rubens, and van Dyck.
I've read everything by
Stendhal and Flaubert.
And I loved John Steinbeck,
Emile Zola, and Victor Hugo.
For wine, Burgundy. On special
occasions, Domaine Leroy.
For whiskey, a Speyside single malt.
You have excellent taste.
You taught me everything.
Everything I love.
If I take away everything
I learned from you,
what would even be left of me?
I found the Connect In app.
On your phone.
Don't tell me you're going to deny it.
I'm not sure.
I'm afraid I don't know
what you're talking about.
I also found proof. On your phone.
And what exactly is this
"proof" you're talking about?
Why don't you check again?
You seem to have caused this scene over it,
but that's a shame.
And another thing.
Even if what you're claiming is true,
what's the big deal?
What did you just say?
You need to grow up, Shin Jae.
Before you leap without looking,
you need to weigh the consequences.
What you stand to gain from this,
and what you stand to lose.
I can't believe what I'm
hearing. Was that a threat?
Either way, you only have one choice.
Join me, or
spend the rest of your life being
pushed around by your mother.
Think it over if you
want to protect I and J.
There's no point in
discussing this further.
Leave.
How could you do this?
I should be asking you the same thing.
Did I teach you to be like this?
To invade someone's privacy like this?
What's going on? Why is the app gone?
We'll talk about that later.
A bombshell just dropped.
Park Ju Hwan.
What are you talking about? Park Ju Hwan?
He came to the office. And get
this. That jerk is a prosecutor now.
How's Ra Young?
I'm fine. I'm not in my 20s anymore.
I tell our clients that
everything will be okay,
so I can't afford to fall apart, can I?
I'm going to eat something spicy.
Something mind-numbingly spicy.
That's what we need today.
All right, let's hurry. I'm starving.
So what do you need us to do?
When did he get back to Korea?
Seems like a while ago.
We should've kept better tabs on him.
Before he could just pop up like this.
How were we to know he'd changed his name?
So how did he seem?
Did it look like he's really
gotten his memory back?
It's hard to say.
I'm not sure he's testing the
waters, saying he'll reinvestigate,
or if he remembers something.
I almost hope he hasn't
gotten his memory back.
If he's acting that brazen
knowing what he did to me,
it's just too
agonizing for me.
I could never forgive him.
Attorney Yoon?
Min Seo.
Something I ate isn't sitting right.
I'm okay.
Don't worry about me. You get some rest.
(Mujin Police Station)
- Hey, sunshine. Chief wants you.
- Right.
- Seung Jin.
- Yes?
Do you recognise this person?
Hey, he looks really familiar. What?
Isn't this Prosecutor Park Je Yeol?
Right? It's him, isn't it?
Yes, I think you're right.
Looks like he was a classmate of your wife.
Then again, the cream of
the crop all stick together.
Why would he change his name?
Hey, you'd better get to the
Chief. He'll flip out if you're late.
- All right. I'll be right back.
- Okay.
- You wanted to see me, sir?
- Yes.
(Seoul Mujin Police Station)
How many cases are
you working on right now?
The Samyang-dong serial theft case...
You can handle one more file then, right?
It's a 20-year-old case. I
need you to handle it with care.
The victim is a sitting prosecutor.
(Witness statement)
(2005 Hankuk University
student murder attempt)
Is the victim...
- Prosecutor Park Je Yeol?
- Yes, he is.
He specifically asked for you.
Do you two know each other?
(2005 Hankuk University
student murder attempt)
(Park Je Yeol, Seoul Mujin
Regional Prosecutors' Office)
Doesn't something seem off?
So that jerk Park Ju Hwan was
the prosecutor on Yoo Jeong's case?
And on top of that, he had
the case reassigned to him.
- So he took her case on purpose?
- Most likely.
But you know what's even stranger?
Park Ju Hwan had met
Jo Yoo Jeong a year ago.
She was a suspect in
an aggravated theft case.
You think this is a coincidence?
There's one way to find out.
I'll go meet Yoo Jeong's sister.
Yoo Jeong wasn't
actually trying to steal it.
At the shop where she worked part-time,
she accidentally spilled a
drink on a customer's bag.
She must have panicked.
So she and a friend from work
took the bag to try and clean it.
But they ended up getting accused of theft.
The customer refused to
settle, so we were really worried,
but luckily, the prosecutor
decided to suspend the indictment.
For aggravated theft, with no settlement,
he just suspended the indictment?
Min Seo, have you, by any chance,
ever met a prosecutor named Park Je Yeol?
No, I've never met him.
Min Seo, how did you end
up working for Connect?
You know Lee Seon Hwa, right?
- It was because of her.
- Lee Seon Hwa?
She took out a loan in my name,
and she said part of it
was transferred to them.
I was told I had to work
at Connect to pay it off.
(Case report)
(Habitual drug use)
- Hey, where's Lee Seon Hwa?
- Seon Hwa? She skipped town.
You have no idea where?
Kidding? If I knew, I'd have gone
after her. She ripped me off too.
That witch would squeeze
blood from a stone.
This is her stuff. I was hoping
I'd find something valuable,
but it's all just junk. Gosh.
It's a trial summons.
That's probably why she ran. She
got her indictment suspended last time,
- but she must've been caught again.
- A suspended indictment?
Yes, that junkie. She'll
actually do time for this, right?
It's her fourth offence now.
- Darn! My money.
- Wait.
She was a three-time offender,
and she still got a suspended indictment?
You said you'd kill them
next time, so that's a threat.
And since you were holding a
stick with nails in it, it's "aggravated."
While you're serving seven
years for aggravated threats,
have you decided which orphanage
to send your little brother to?
I did it because I was so angry
they bullied my little brother.
Sir, please let me off
the hook just this once.
Let you off the hook?
Shall I?
You really want me to do that?
Yes, please.
All right, then. Maybe I will.
Really?
That's up to you.
(Jo Yoo Jeong, Prosecutor
Park Je Yeol, Lee Seon Hwa)
Check this out.
Both women, after being
handled by Park Ju Hwan...
No.
Through Prosecutor Park Je Yeol,
they received suspended indictments,
and were then exploited by Connect.
In Lee Seon Hwa's case,
Min Seo had to take her place.
It's clear that some of the victims
were likely supplied to the app
through Park Je Yeol.
By using his authority to indict people.
So Park Je Yeol is part of Connect?
Even a prosecutor is
part of this whole scheme?
If that's true, then all
the pieces fall into place.
Including who's been using
our pasts to attack us all this time.
But right now, the only evidence we have
is all circumstantial.
If only that darn app
hadn't been taken down...
So, have you decided?
What you're going to
do about Attorney Kwon?
What's there to decide?
Now that I know who's behind this darn app.
(Jo Yoo Jeong, Prosecutor
Park Je Yeol, Lee Seon Hwa)
(Aggravated theft,
suspension of indictment?)
(Drug use, suspension of indictment?)
This just arrived by courier.
It's from Attorney Kang Shin Jae.
(The laws in the Republic of
Korea don't call what you did...)
(Managing Partner Kang Shin Jae)
The laws in the Republic of
Korea don't call what you did
a matter of privacy. They call it a crime.
When the wind blows, I will sway.
And yet, the flowers still bloom.
All the attorneys who resigned
are waiting at the meeting place.
What are your orders?
If they've come to a consensus,
then we must pave the way.
Let's go.
Welcome.
Mind if I join you?
- It's been a while.
- I heard you came looking for me,
so I thought we should at least say hello.
How did you find me here?
Around here, if I put my mind to
it, there isn't much I can't find out.
You're looking good.
I'm great.
I endure the searing pain in
my right arm several times a day,
and I have to choke down a
fistful of painkillers every day,
but I'm doing just great.
So,
are you trying to get your revenge now?
Why? You're only scared now?
- So you've regained your memory.
- Is that all?
I also got my hands on the evidence.
The DNA sample you
guys tried to sneak out...
It just so happens to match the
suspect's DNA from the scene.
Then I guess you also remember
what you did to Ra Young that night.
What difference does
that make now, Shin Jae?
It's not like you can prove it, anyway.
- What?
- Yoon Ra Young and I were dating.
We were just in love,
like any other couple.
People really can't stand you guys.
They say you're shrill and exhausting.
If I just add a little fuel to that fire,
who do you think will get
burned? Me, or you guys?
What do you want?
Back off from Connect.
And if I won't?
Are you really prepared to be broken?
I can be.
The one who'll be hurt
the most by this fight
will be Yoon Ra Young.
My apologies for being late.
Why are you just standing there?
Go on and do what you came here to do.
It seemed you were all just
waiting for a chance to turn on me.
So why the silence?
- Madam Chair...
- Fine.
Allow me to start.
I understand your intentions perfectly,
and I will process them all immediately.
(Letter of resignation)
Thank you, Attorney Kwon.
I've been meaning to separate
the wheat from the chaff,
and you've just picked
out all the chaff for me.
It seems you're all under
a serious misapprehension.
You are not the ones who
built Haeil into what it is today.
Haeil made you who you are today.
Anyone who defies me.
I cut them out.
When it comes to traitors,
I've never failed to remove
them from the industry.
Please forgive me, ma'am. I was foolish.
I was wrong.
- Please forgive me.
Back when we were young,
you used to say you were sick
of only attending law lectures,
so we used to sneak into
classes in other departments.
Remember that?
Yes.
Wasn't it an Intro to
Literature class we sat in on?
I really disliked King
Lear, Hamlet, and Macbeth.
The kings all lose their
thrones. So foolishly.
Jung Hyeon.
When a child is acting up,
you're supposed to correct them.
Not play along with them.
I have no excuse.
That's right.
You shouldn't have one.
I knew it.
The reason Park Je Yeol showed up.
He's using our past to stop
us from pursuing Connect.
But what if Park Je Yeol
really goes public with it?
Hyun Jin would be in the most danger.
But we can't just surrender.
Especially not to that jerk.
- Worst-case scenario, you could...
- Get arrested?
You think the lawyers here would
just stand by and let that happen?
And we would probably
lose everything.
Everything we've worked so hard to build.
But if we're prepared to
fight this to the very end,
your opinion is what matters
most to Hyun Jin and me.
Can you handle what's coming?
About that DNA sample from
before, the one Seon Kyu took.
It ended up in Park Je Yeol's hands.
- What are you talking about?
- So, does that ring any bells?
But do you even know who my husband is?
He's a sitting prosecutor.
Ju Hwan.
Park Ju Hwan.
Ju Hwan, I've been
looking all over for you.
I told you not to smile at other guys.
I'm sorry. Let's go. Everyone's waiting.
You don't love me at all.
You just say you do.
Then what do you want me to do?
What do I have to do
to make you believe me?
Prove it.
Are you crazy?
Let go. Don't!
No!
Why give me the cold shoulder
just because you got a few wrong?
Because I changed my
scantron answer and got it wrong!
This is so frustrating.
If you keep that up,
you're going to regret it.
Here.
(Super concert!)
No way! Dad, how did you get these?
What do you mean? I bought them, of course.
I'm practically an expert
at nabbing tickets now.
Thanks, Dad.
- Dad, come on. Mom's waiting.
- Right, let's go in.
(Family Registry)
(Hong Yeon Hui, Spouse:
Park Je Yeol, Child: Park Sang A)
- Having indigestion?
- No, it's my lower abdomen.
Are you sure it's not cramps?
Want some painkillers?
What's this?
What do you think you're doing?
Well...
- Orders came from above...
- What orders?
(Managing Partner Kang Shin Jae)
I'm Kwon Jung Hyeon, the new head of LnJ.
I look forward to working with you all.
(Managing Partner Kwon Jung Hyeon)
What do you think you're doing?
Consider this my response to your message.
You shouldn't have one.
- I trust you're ready to pay.
- About Shin Jae.
I will take responsibility
and send her to Haeil.
I'll resign from all my positions.
Just send me to LnJ.
You have to be able to
weather a storm like this.
Drop all your current cases.
I'm changing the firm's direction.
Women aren't the only vulnerable.
You can't just do this out of the blue.
We've been using our
own free time to take
a ton of pro bono cases. If
you make us drop them all
I also saw some cases
that were getting bad press.
Why should your volunteer
work tarnish the firm's name?
Who do you all think signs your paychecks?
From now on, no cases or
assignments without my approval.
When the steering
committee meets next year,
I don't want to be torn apart
for being an incompetent leader.
Like you were, Shin Jae.
This is all because of Connect, isn't it?
You're trying to stop us from
exposing what Connect did.
- Am I wrong?
- Well
I don't know what you
mean, but what I do know is
that the Jo Yoo Jeong case
is closed due to her suicide.
This is no playground to waste
time writing some ridiculous fantasy.
The person you are
calling is unavailable...
(Mom)
(Lee Seon Hwa)
I know everything you did to me.
Call me.
You've been giving me
a lot to worry about lately.
Mark my words.
If you keep acting up, Yoon
Ra Young is going to get hurt.
Min Seo.
I'm at the hotel.
Where are you?
In the government's national
pilot smart city project,
The Prime is being mentioned
as the most promising candidate.
That predictive defence
system you mentioned
- would ultimately...
- You're here.
We need to talk.
We need to talk about Attorney Kwon.
How could you, without telling me?
That would be unavoidable.
You also went behind my back,
scheming something interesting of your own.
That concern was our starting point.
Technology shouldn't surveil
people. It should protect them.
Our system doesn't track who is dangerous.
It simply determines which
situations are dangerous.
All data from the smart city project
will be encrypted using block chain.
No identifiable personal
information will be stored,
and it's designed so that no
admin can access the source data.
Why are the reporters taking our picture?
- Didn't you see the news?
- What news?
Redesigning the relationship...
Corruption by the powerful, a
system free from human prejudice...
You were outmanoeuvred.
("Prime CEO Baek Tae Joo
Engaged to Haeil's Successor?")
For even the most vulnerable...
Was this your doing?
I've let you off the leash for too long.
- So I've learned my lesson.
- Our technology will be the tool...
And him?
Is he okay with articles like this?
That is the one and only goal
The Prime aims to achieve.
(The Prime: Technology,
Setting a New Standard)
Quiet. People are watching.
Excuse me, sir, but a report about
your engagement just came out.
Is there any truth to the article?
The engagement rumour
is not true.
However, it is true that
I have feelings for her.
(The Prime: Technology,
Setting a New Standard)
Pardon the intrusion.
This is the only place we
can talk without being seen.
What do you think you're doing?
What do you mean?
Why are you siding with my
mother? And making things up, no less.
I wasn't lying.
I corrected the engagement rumour,
and as for my feelings
for you, Attorney Kang...
That part is true.
Do you realise we've only
met a handful of times?
Even before we ever met.
I've been interested
from the very beginning.
What deal did you make with my mother?
Or what do you want from me?
Is that always how you approach people?
As a transaction, not a relationship.
Profit over trust.
And what's wrong with that?
I happen to think we could be a great team.
- And not as business partners.
- What's that supposed to mean?
Try a different perspective.
I'm not an enemy siding with your mother.
I could be an ally who
empowers you, Attorney Kang.
Why would you choose me over my mother?
Because the one I find impressive
is you, Attorney Kang.
Not CEO Seong.
Oh, right.
I won't bother issuing a retraction
for that engagement story.
You never know, it might just come true.
See you around.
Here. Drink this.
I was so hungry, so I
stole my neighbour's milk.
When I was six.
I hadn't eaten in three days.
As punishment, I was locked
out on the balcony for two days.
In just my underwear.
And it was January.
When I was in elementary school,
I ran an errand and messed up the change.
And my entire body
became black with bruises.
My parents were always like that.
They said if you do something
bad, you get punished.
Is it because I'm a bad person
that this is happening to me?
Min Seo.
Could you ever stab someone with a knife?
You couldn't, could you?
Then why would you do that to yourself?
I used to do that to myself too.
"Why did I go there? Why
couldn't I see who he truly was?"
"Something this awful happened to
me because I was naive and stupid."
The kind of cruel blame I
would never put on anyone else,
I'd turn it on myself hundreds,
even thousands of times.
And do you know why?
Because I was my own easiest target.
I should've been mad at my
tormentor, at this unjust world.
But I didn't have the
courage to fight back,
so I was just taking it out
on someone weak.
Myself, the easiest person,
for me to hurt.
Blaming yourself
is the most convenient way
to be a coward. That's what I realised.
I
Want you to break up
with yesterday, Min Seo.
And I want you to start
showing some respect
to yourself.
Someone from Connect came to see me.
They said if I keep helping LnJ,
they're going to come after you.
- From now on, you must never...
- When things like this happen,
it feels like confirmation
of who I really am.
That I can never be
normal like everyone else.
And that I'll never be able to escape it.
I don't want much. I just
want to get back the things I've lost.
Can I get it all back?
Even after I've ruined everything?
You're up?
I figured a proper meal
would be better for breakfast.
How are you feeling? Are you okay?
Yes.
Did you make all this just for me?
You said you don't eat breakfast.
Have a seat.
A while back, when I
was having a hard time,
I couldn't eat anything for a while.
I couldn't get a single bite down.
While I wasn't eating, my
friends refused to eat too.
For them, I forced down
one bite, then another.
And slowly, I started to get up,
to walk, and even go outside again.
That's when I realised.
Surviving isn't all that complicated.
I felt like I was going to die,
but once I ate, I found
myself able to live again.
To live, you have to eat.
And to save someone,
you have to feed them.
I'm not going to lie to you.
In the end,
I never fully recovered.
Some wounds heal
without a trace, but others
leave scars that last forever.
Mine was one of those.
But maybe that's
because I never got an apology
from the person who hurt me.
"I'm sorry. I was wrong."
If I get an apology like that,
do you think I might be
a little more okay then?
To find that out, we first need to
eat and get our strength back.
This is from my emergency stash.
It's delicious. It has a nice nutty flavour.
Try some.
Also, Attorney Kwon Jung
Hyeon will be joining LnJ.
The VIP?
Yes.
It's best not to come to the
office for a while, Min Seo.
So you don't have to run into him.
Have you been busy?
I feel like I barely see you anymore.
I just got a new case.
What kind of case?
Attempted murder of a
Hankuk University Law student
from 20 years ago.
What?
The victim's a prosecutor now.
You know him, right?
You two were classmates.
Park Ju Hwan. No, I mean,
Prosecutor Park Je Yeol.
You were ordered to reinvestigate? By who?
By Prosecutor Park Je Yeol himself.
Sorry, I have to head out first.
Can you clean up after me?
(Prosecutor Park Je Yeol)
Yes, Park Je Yeol speaking.
So this is how you're going to pressure us?
How dare you drag my husband into this?
"Drag him?"
I'm just trying to help him score a win.
Besides, I thought it would be interesting.
To have your own husband
be the one to arrest you.
Are you trying to pick
a dirty fight? Is that it?
Detective Gu Seon Kyu seems
like a dedicated, by-the-book guy.
When he learns his wife is a
suspect in an attempted murder case,
I wonder how he'll
react. Aren't you curious?
You stay right where you are.
Yes, come on in.
I'm Detective Gu Seon Kyu
from the Mujin Violent Crimes Unit.
What to do? I seem to
have a prior engagement.
Just use your imagination.
The conversation we're about to have.
Please have a seat.
I've been expecting you.
Have you had a chance
to look into the case?
I have,
but the first investigation was botched,
so there are hardly any leads.
Are you reopening the investigation
because you've regained your memory?
Like you recalled a clue
to the culprit or something.
To be honest, I haven't
fully recovered my memory.
The fragments of memory I do have
I doubt they would even hold up in court.
Then why?
Let's just say I have a hunch.
That you, Detective Gu,
might be the one who can find the culprit.
Is it because I'm Hyun Jin's husband?
So you already knew
about my past with Hyun Jin.
You could say that.
Because you, Detective Gu,
are in a much better
position to get statements
from Yoon Ra Young, Hwang
Hyun Jin, and Kang Shin Jae.
And their memories
should still be perfectly clear.
Really?
Is that all there is to it?
Why do you ask?
Do you have some reason
to suspect there's more to it?
I don't know if this will help,
but Yoon Ra Young and
I were dating at the time.
And on the day of the incident,
all three were there with me.
But the reason they were
never considered suspects
was because they
provided alibis for each other.
Sometimes, I let my imagination run wild.
Were their testimonies actually true?
Then what happened
with Ra Young after that?
We broke up.
More accurately, she's the
one who broke up with me.
Aren't you curious why?
Every now and then, I
find myself wondering.
So you're really going to do
what your mom says again?
I'm thinking about what the best move is.
I'm
done running away.
Hiding it just makes it fester.
Just when I think it's healed,
it always splits open again.
If telling the world is the
price I pay to keep fighting,
I'm willing to pay it, Shin Jae.
Are you sure you'll be okay?
For once,
we should have fought for ourselves.
Connect.
I'm going to see this through to the end.
I can't stop now.
What's wrong?
But the reason they were
never considered suspects
was because they
provided alibis for each other.
Sometimes, I let my imagination run wild.
Were their testimonies actually true?
You know what this reminds me of?
Accomplices.
Their fates are tied together.
If one of them goes down,
the other is bound to go down with them.
I took another one. It's the same.
He doesn't know yet. I haven't told him.
For now, you're the only ones who know.
As for telling him...
Shouldn't I wait until I'm more sure?
- I'm home.
- Hey.
You're back?
What now?
What?
Something else you're hiding from me.
What on earth is it now?
What are you talking about all of a sudden?
What are you hiding behind your back?
What am I hiding?
No. We can't. Things have changed.
You know how long Hyun
Jin has wanted a baby.
If what we did gets out,
Hyun Jin will be in the most danger.
Protecting Hyun Jin has to come first.
You're right. It's too reckless
to just charge ahead like this.
Here's the information you asked for.
Thank you.
Is this for real?
I was going to tell you
once I was more certain.
I was afraid you'd be disappointed
if something went wrong...
How can you say that?
We're going to be parents?
Really?
- Why are you crying, silly?
- I'm not crying.
I'm just so happy.
There might be a way.
Park Je Yeol. We take him down first.
So he can't breathe a word about us.
Hong Yeon Hui, age 42.
Spouse, a prosecutor, Mujin
Prosecutors' Office, Division Three,
Park Je Yeol.
You.
What's your real reason for approaching me?
It was you, wasn't it?
You're the one who tried to
kill my husband 20 years ago.
It was a mistake.
I should have finished him off back then.
(Honour)
Attempted murder of a male student
at Hankuk University College of Law.
If this happens to Hyun Jin
again, I swear I won't let it slide.
You're telling me this
is Jun Hyeok's laptop?
I'll give you an exclusive,
and I'll even do an interview.
Attorney Kwon is involved. As a user.
I said I would help you.
That was our deal, wasn't it?
I've laid all my cards on the
table. So, what do you want?
- Mission complete.
- Jun Hyeok's laptop is gone.
If there's someone who
hasn't paid their due,
It's you.