(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
He's so attractivve.
Kaji-san is the top
salesman again this month.
I heard that every client he works with
has nothing but good things to say.
A capable man is just so charming.
(Sales Dept. Top Salesman: Kaji Akihiro)
Good work today.
Oh, I've got the promotional items.
- Thank you.
- Here, let me help you with those.
There we go.
Kaji-san,
the rest of us are going out for dinner.
Would you like to join us?
Ah...
I'm sorry.
I'm in a rush to finish a presentation.
I won't crash your girls' night out today.
Enjoy your dinner!
Perfect! He's absolutely the best!
Me, perfect?
That's just...
the persona I show the world.
There's no way I'd show my true self.
It's too much trouble.
In the end...
everyone is alone anyway.
Trying to build a deep relationship
is a total waste of energy.
If that's the case,
I'd rather just play the part,
and only take the best parts of life.
I wonder if he has a girlfriend?
He must! I heard they've been
together since college.
Apparently, she's a gorgeous model.
A girlfriend?
I'm 100% gay, okay?
A 20.
A 30.
A... 10.
Not a single decent one.
Alright.
Hair and clothes.
Expression.
Perfect.
Where on earth is he?
Someone who's actually worthy of me.
A guy who's a perfect ten.
"Unexpectedly Naughty Fukami"
(Episode 1)
Ugh.
A guy I hooked up with is texting me.
I'll just leave him on read.
Kaji-kun.
Sorry, did I startle you?
No, I'm fine. What's up?
Well, here's the thing.
There was a system error,
and a client complained.
One of our younger guys
has to go apologize in person.
Could you go with him?
Oh.
I mean, I could.
But wouldn't just the engineer be enough?
Well...
I'm a little worried about him.
Fukami, from our department.
Hello.
His technical skills are great,
but he doesn't have the best people skills.
What's with this guy?
He's so plain.
And gloomy.
(Average SE: Fukami Yuu)
His clothes are way too big, too.
The client really likes you,
so I was hoping you could help.
Sure, if I can be of any help.
That's a huge lifesaver.
A 5.
No.
He's a zero.
We are truly...
very sorry.
Please accept our apologies.
Alright, alright, you can look up now.
You guys were very
proactive about fixing it.
I'm relieved to hear that.
Come by again sometime.
Just don't let it happen again, okay?
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much.
Smile a little, will you?
Well then,
- we'll be going now.
- Take care.
This guy...
He's here to apologize,
but he's not even wearing a suit jacket.
Could he at least try to look professional?
I'm glad that's settled.
Ugh.
He's so unappealing.
Just terrible.
Even if we were the
last two people on Earth,
nothing would ever happen between us.
It's the office.
Hello?
What?!
I see.
About the hotel for tonight...
Apparently, they could
only get one twin room.
Wow, that's a problem.
The tourist rush is insane.
I don't mind, though.
Fukami,
should we try looking for another place?
It's fine with me too.
Sharing a room?
With this zero-point guy?
Whatever.
I'll just find a hookup
and stay out drinking until the morning.
Where can I find a guy
who's actually my type?
Nowhere, apparently.
But why is it...
that in the gay scene,
scruffy muscle guys are so popular?
Guys like me who want a clean-cut,
pretty boy are such a rarity.
I mean, look at all the idols and actors!
The bright, cheerful ones
are clearly the majority!
There's really no one for me.
The bathroom's
all yours.
Yeah.
Tha...
Who is that?
He's actually hot without his glasses.
What is this, some cliché rom-com?
And this guy...
is so sexy.
You dropped it.
Your phone.
This is bad.
You saw it, didn't you?
You...
No.
That's just who I am.
Right.
I'm sure you don't like...
sharing a room with a gay guy.
I'll go find somewhere else to stay.
It's fine.
Actually,
so am I.
Gay.
No, you don't have to say that for my sake.
I'm not just saying it.
Then...
Are you serious?
Gay?
What are the odds?
By the way, Fukami,
are you a top or a bottom?
If I had to say...
a bottom,
I guess.
So, want to hook up to
commemorate the occasion?
What are you talking about?
I could sue you for that.
Sorry.
Just forget it.
I'm down.
For some reason, today I'm...
really in the
mood.
Why...
am I...
making a move
on a zero-point guy?
No.
Don't touch yourself yet.
Don't.
Right there...
I'm gonna cum.
You're amazing.
So naughty.
Fukami.
No.
Don't just do it from behind...
Stop.
Why am I more turned on than usual?
I...
It's been so long since I felt like this.
My head is spinning.
This is bad.
What is this?
Incredible.
Look at that slutty face you're making.
Damn it.
You just came, didn't you?
Ah...
That felt so good.
This guy...
He's not a zero.
He's a perfect ten!
Our chemistry is the
best I've had all year.
Since we're so compatible,
maybe we should make this a regular thing.
He's so cold this morning.
He was moaning so much last night,
so it's not like he didn't enjoy it.
Could it be...
he's falling for me?
With my skills,
- it's definitely within my power.
- Well then...
I'll be going now.
Huh?
Ah...
Is he just overwhelmed
because he's not used to this?
You're hopeless.
I guess...
I'll have to give you a little push.
Hey, Fukami.
Let's go for a drink later.
We can finish what we
started yesterday, too.
Oh, no thanks.
I'll take my leave now.
Wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
I can't believe
I just got pumped and dumped.
No matter how you
look at him, he's a loser.
His hair is a mess.
He's just some loser nerd.
By all rights,
you should be the one
begging me!
What is your deal,
you zero-point guy?!
(Next Episode)
Fukami, you got a minute?
I'm definitely going to make you
obsessed with my body.
If you say you can
satisfy me a second time,
then prove it.
Go slower.
Like, with kissing.