(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
It happened so suddenly.
We were not prepared,
so we had to bury Master like this.
Ever since he took the poison
given by His Majesty,
he had been terminally ill
and lost all his martial arts skills.
And with this surge of anger,
he passed away.
Master has passed away.
Young Master,
whether you stay or go,
no one will interfere anymore.
Just as you said,
Master...
had no choice.
[REBIRTH]
[Episode 33]
[In Memory of My Grandfather,
Zhuge Muqing]
Young Master!
It's really you.
You really are alive.
Yue Da,
after I left,
have you been well?
Young Master.
We...
we've all been very well.
Yue Liu,
you are terrible at lying.
Young Master,
please leave Qingshan Manor.
As the Moon Guards,
we have accepted our fate
the moment we entered Qingshan Manor.
We have to be responsible for our choices.
Young Master,
please go your own way.
You don't have to stay for us.
Please leave.
Young Master!
You cannot leave Qingshan Manor!
The Master is dead!
Let go of me!
Young Master,
you have become King Ximeng.
Qingshan Manor
will fall into the hands
of the third branch of the Zhuge family.
Their master, Zhuge Xi,
was beaten to death by Chu Qiao.
The third branch hates you to the core.
If we Moon Guards stay here,
death would be a mercy.
I'm afraid by then,
we will be tortured to the point
where we'd rather be dead!
The Master is gone,
but Qingshan Manor is still here!
Yue Ming,
you fled without permission.
According to the rules of Qingshan Manor,
you will be executed!
Yes!
-Go!
-Let him go!
Young Master,
this is the rule of Qingshan Manor.
Zhan Fu.
I will return to Zhenhuangcheng with you.
Qingshan Manor
will not be given to the third branch.
Welcome back, Young Master!
Hurry!
This is the military camp of Ximeng.
Please leave, King of Great Yan.
He Xiao, look carefully.
I am unarmed now.
You can kill me anytime.
But I will not leave Chu's side
until she wakes up.
Chu.
Chu, hang on.
She fainted from losing too much blood.
Chu.
You'll be fine.
How is she?
The wounds have been treated.
But Chu still has a fever.
Lady Chu has two knife wounds.
Although they are not fatal,
she lost a lot of blood.
It is normal that she won't wake up
for a while.
We just need to take turns
watching her here.
She will be fine once she safely
gets through these couple of days.
What are you doing here?
Tell me!
What right do you have
to come to the military camp to see Chu?
If it weren't for you and Zhuge Muqing,
she wouldn't be hurt like this!
There are wounds on her left arm
and abdomen.
Although they are not deep,
they were caused
by Qingshan Manor's glazed iron.
Even if her meridians are not hurt,
they are hard to heal.
Have Xiao Ran
make some medicinal wine
with Yinlin snake blood and Huaying grass.
It can remove putrefaction
and promote tissue regeneration.
In 2 days,
she will wake up.
How do you know the details so well?
I thought I was the one who saved Chu.
It seems I was one step behind you again.
Today in the Yong Army's camp,
you offered yourself as the price
in exchange for Zhuge Muqing
to release them, right?
Tomorrow morning,
I will leave with my grandfather
and the people of Qingshan Manor.
The Yong Army will still be here,
but without a commander,
they won't do anything to Ximeng
anytime soon.
Ever since I've known you,
you have always been this self-righteous,
thinking you bear the burden
of the country
and its people.
But you are just a mortal too.
I don't care what promises
or deals you have made.
Zhuge Muqing is already dead.
You should stay
and help Chu through this.
In this world,
not everyone
can follow their heart
and do whatever they want to do.
We grew up together
and understand each other best.
I have my reasons.
Before I return,
take good care of Xing for me.
Zhuge Yue,
I don't understand you anymore.
And you didn't treat Chu like this before.
-Bravo!
-Good shot!
Bravo!
Thanks!
Zhuge Yue.
I've taken a liking
to a maid in your manor.
How about you give her to me?
I will certainly grant what you ask,
Your Highness.
But which branch
does she belong to?
She said she's from the Nonexistent Yard,
and her name is Nobody.
She makes clay figures under Mrs. Dou.
There is no such person in Qingshan Manor.
How can that be?
Her name is Nobody,
and she's from the Nonexistent Yard,
making clay figures under Mrs. Dou.
Doesn't that mean she doesn't exist?
She was messing with you.
How dare she lie to me?
I'll go find her.
Nobody from the Nonexistent Yard?
I can't believe she came up with that.
Zhuge Yue,
this Xing in your courtyard
has quite the nerve.
She even dared to lie to a prince.
I like her.
She's too bold.
She needs strict discipline.
No need for that.
Just give her to me.
If you keep disciplining her,
she will turn into
a block of ice like you.
No.
If I give her to you,
the Thirteenth Prince
will definitely fall out with me.
Pick another maid.
Wait.
Zhuge Yue.
We grew up together.
I've never seen you afraid of anyone.
Could it be
that you can't bear to part with her
and want to keep her by your side?
Zhuge Yue!
Yan Xun,
I will trust you one last time.
Take good care of Xing.
Keep her safe
until I return.
Xing.
Since the establishment
of the new government in Ximeng,
crises have been emerging everywhere.
You and I have faced death together
several times.
We should face the enemy side by side.
But my identity has now been exposed.
The bloody conflicts in both lands
all stem from this.
With my grandfather's sudden passing,
the wolves in Great Yong who are in power
will only grow more covetous of Ximeng.
On this journey,
I must first quell the unrest
in Qingshan Manor,
then eradicate
the deep-rooted ills of Great Yong.
Only then can Ximeng enjoy lasting peace.
Upon my return,
I will keep my promise
and reunite with you.
Chu, you're awake.
And your fever is gone.
You should be fine now.
Lady Chu, please calm down.
You've been unconscious for days.
Your body is very weak.
I'll ask Minglu to help you.
Where is Minglu?
What exactly happened?
Before Minglu left,
did she say anything?
She said nothing.
She stopped breathing
just as she arrived at the camp.
Except for these two pieces of clothing,
she left nothing behind.
Impossible.
She can't be dead.
It's impossible.
I'll go find her!
Chu!
I'll go find her! Let me go!
Minglu is already dead.
I'm going to find Minglu!
She's already dead!
She's not dead!
-She's dead!
-She's not!
Minglu is not dead!
She's not dead!
Minglu...
Minglu died for me.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Minglu!
Minglu!
I saw him that night.
I wanted to ask him clearly,
but when I caught up with him,
he had already left.
He only left this behind.
Zhuge Yue said
he wouldn't leave me
without saying goodbye.
He has made his choice.
Don't you understand?
What is that supposed to mean?
He was born into the Zhuge family
of Great Yong.
Zhuge Muqing
had always treated him
as the heir to Qingshan Manor.
Yan Xun.
What exactly are you trying to say?
He is different from us.
We don't have family,
but he does.
Qingshan Manor is his home.
Zhuge Muqing is his family.
Even if he can momentarily
give up his family and Great Yong
for you,
can he really do it forever?
Would his family allow him to do so?
No matter what you say,
I believe him.
You believe him?
Is he worthy of your trust?
Zhuge Muqing came to Ximengcheng before.
Did he ever tell you that?
Zhuge Muqing came to Ximengcheng
to look for him?
He and I grew up together.
We were like brothers.
I know him better than you do.
Born in the Zhuge family
and bearing the responsibility
of Qingshan Manor,
he has many things beyond his control.
For so many years,
at critical moments,
he would always abandon what he wanted
and make the advantageous choice.
Just like when he chose to stand
by the Emperor of Great Yong
and watch the entire Yan family perish.
Enough, Yan Xun!
I'm tired.
I don't want to listen to you anymore.
Fine.
If you don't believe me,
I'll take you to find him.
[Capital of Great Yan]
My Lady!
Bad news!
The elder of Lanchuan Tribe has rebelled!
As we speak,
the Lanchuan cavalry
has already reached Lexian!
Let's hurry out and hide somewhere!
What?
Why did the elder of Lanchuan Tribe rebel?
I have no idea.
But the nobles in the Capital of Great Yan
who heard the news
have all fled.
The Lanchuan Tribe and the Pale Tribe
have always had ulterior motives
toward Yan Xun.
This time they were forced
to show their full hand.
It must be...
Your Highness,
don't worry about this for now.
His Majesty is not in Great Yan now.
There are hardly
any Black Eagle Army soldiers left
stationed in the Capital of Great Yan.
If the Lanchuan cavalry
reaches the city gate,
we'll be in trouble.
Your Highness,
let's go now!
Search the whole city
for Yan Xun's remnants!
Kill them all!
Yes!
What happened?
Are you okay?
Su?
Su! Su!
Su!
You guys, go over there!
-Hurry!
-Let's go!
Check over here!
Yes!
Come.
Why are you here?
Something happened at the military camp
in the Capital of Great Yan too?
Spies from the Lanchuan Tribe
have infiltrated the camp.
They tried to kill me
before breaching the city.
I barely escaped.
But don't worry.
I've sent people to Yanming Pass
to inform General Huan.
They should have arrived by now.
From Yanming Pass
to the Capital of Great Yan,
it takes at least a day and a night.
The cavalry of the Lanchuan Tribe
has already occupied the palace.
Now their people are everywhere
in the Capital of Great Yan.
What should we do?
Don't worry.
They are busy burning and looting
and have no time
to deal with us for the moment.
You are His Majesty's Chief General,
and I am his Consort.
Elder Lanchuan
hates His Majesty to the core.
I'm afraid the first thing he'll do
is kill us to boost their troops' morale.
Hide here for now.
I'll go and see
if there's a way out of the city.
Cheng Yuan!
Don't worry.
It's safe here.
Let's go together.
You guys! Go over there!
Let's go!
Hurry!
They are over there!
My Lady! General Cheng!
We are here to escort you as ordered!
They are from the Snowy Region!
My Lady, General Cheng.
Thank you for your help, General Huan.
Thankfullly, you arrived in time,
so General Cheng and I are safe.
General,
the rebels of Lanchuan Tribe
have been captured.
Elder Lanchuan has escaped from
the Capital of Great Yan.
We have sent men to capture him.
Okay, I got it.
General Huan.
There is one more thing.
Among the captured rebels,
a small group...
are cavalrymen from the Helian Tribe.
Search carefully!
Detain everyone in the mansion!
Yes!
Go!
What's wrong?
What is going on here?
General Huan?
In the middle of the night,
you brought so many people to my mansion
and disturbed my sweet dreams.
What are you trying to do?
The Lanchuan Tribe rebelled
and has been burning, killing,
and looting in the capital,
ruining ordinary people's families.
It's a wonder you could still sleep
so soundly
and dream sweet dreams.
The Lanchuan Tribe rebelled?
How dare they?
Is the situation in the city
under control now?
Elder Helian, you don't need to worry.
I have led troops to quell the rebellion
in the city,
and captured more than 2,000 rebels.
Then I can rest assured.
Such a relief.
Since that's the case,
thank you for your hard work,
General Huan.
Please go back.
If the Lanchuan Tribe alone
could have successfully rebelled,
then it must have been Heaven's will
that Great Yan be destroyed.
Wait.
The Lanchuan Tribe has rebelled.
Instead of going to the Lanchuan Tribe
to arrest the rebels,
what are you doing here
in the Helian Tribe?
Among these 2,000 rebels,
300 are from the Helian Tribe.
Guards!
Elder Helian has just woken up.
I'm afraid he isn't seeing things clearly.
Consort Helian,
do you recognize these two rebels?
These two
are my brother's trusted subordinates.
They have followed him for many years.
Ling,
this is a grave crime of rebellion.
You must not talk nonsense.
Our Helian Tribe
is related to the royal family
and already holds noble status
with everything we need.
Why would we rebel?
I remember now.
The day before yesterday,
Elder Lanchuan said
he wanted to go winter hunting
in the mountains.
Because he didn't have enough men,
I lent him these few people.
That old bastard.
He actually dared to rebel?
Winter hunting in the mountains?
Then what about the 1,000 Helian cavalry
my men intercepted in Wuxian
outside the Capital?
How many troops did Elder Lanchuan want
to take for winter hunting?
What does it matter to me?
It's her!
She must have been the one
plotting behind the scenes.
Ask everyone in the Helian Tribe.
Ever since she became the Consort,
no one in the Helian Tribe
has taken me seriously.
And now?
Something has happened
to the Helian family,
and now you all come to ask me.
Why don't you ask the real leader?
Say something!
Since Elder Helian won't admit it,
it must be that these people have secretly
colluded with the rebels.
According to the laws of Great Yan,
rebels
and their entire clan must be executed!
General Huan, spare me!
It was Master Helian.
He told us to follow
the orders of Elder Lanchuan.
How dare you frame me!
You... I...
Ling,
save me.
I was deceived.
I was deceived by Elder Lanchuan.
I was really wrong.
Save me just this last time.
Save me, Ling.
Great Yan has its own laws.
General Huan,
I am just a consort.
Who dares to kill me?
I am the master of the Helian family!
Helian Ling!
You are not just Yan Xun's Consort.
You are one of the Helian family.
You are my sister!
Today,
if you let them kill me,
your hands
will be stained
with your own brother's blood!
And you will be the one
who destroys the Helian family!
You will be a sinner to the Helian family!
Besides you, the Helian family
has 4 younger brothers.
Although they are young,
if they are raised well,
they can surely take on
the role of Master.
If they cannot,
there are still 6 girls.
They are all of the same clan as us.
Every one of them
has better character than you.
They might also take on
the role of Master.
The king's law applies
not only to subordinates,
but also to superiors.
General Huan,
let the punishment fit the crime.
You will always be a sinner
to the Helian family!
Since you dared to come back,
you must have prepared an explanation.
Speak.
Let me hear
what excuses you have
to get yourself out of this.
I didn't plan to get myself out of this.
Ever since I fell into the frozen lake
during the battle at Meilin Pass,
I have been a dead man.
I was lucky enough to be saved
by the people of Ximeng,
but I was forced
to take Ximeng's deadly poison,
and have been controlled
like a walking corpse,
able to live only in the shadows.
This was left to me by my grandfather
before he passed away.
I have failed Great Yong.
I am no longer fit
for this great responsibility.
Your Majesty, please take back this seal
and punish me according to the law.
Back then, that old man Zhuge,
in order to make me believe
you were already dead,
drank
poisoned wine
that destroyed all his martial arts skills
as atonement.
Since you yourself said you're guilty...
I know I am guilty,
and I am willing
to drink this poisoned wine.
But I have one request.
I hope you can grant it, Your Majesty.
I know that
during my absence from Qingshan Manor,
Lord Muhe Lie of the Muhe family
has trained a group of loyal men
for Your Majesty
who are skilled in assassination
and intelligence gathering.
Qingshan Manor has had no successor
in recent years.
My grandfather has passed away.
I lack both virtue and ability
and am a criminal.
I can no longer bear
such heavy responsibilities.
Your Majesty, please issue an edict
to disband Qingshan Manor
and let its spies retire to their homes
to spend the rest of their lives in peace.
Do you want me
to abolish Qingshan Manor?
Yes.
Zhuge Yue,
let me tell you.
Qingshan Manor can be abolished,
but none of its people
will be allowed to leave alive.
Please don't be angry, Father.
I have a good idea.
Yang?
What are you doing here?
Yang,
don't mess around.
Father,
Young Master Zhuge is not only capable,
surviving death time and again,
but also skilled in governing the country.
Even when his own life is at stake,
he still tries to find a way out
for his subordinates.
Since that's the case,
Father, you might as well grant his wish.
What do you mean by that?
Bring him in!
Shiyi!
Young Master...
Young Master Zhuge,
you know the rules of Qingshan Manor.
Once you join, you can never leave.
But your willingness
to risk your life for them
truly moved me.
How about this?
Let him drink this poisoned wine
as an apology
on your behalf,
and I will plead with Father for you
to let all these people
from Qingshan Manor retire.
What do you say?
Shiyi!
Shiyi, don't!
What do you say?
Shiyi!
Are you willing to drink this cup of wine
for your Young Master?
Yue Shiyi, no!
Young Master,
you are a man destined for great things.
I hope you won't think
that I'm useless
and will still let me keep following you.
Yue Shiyi, no!
Don't!
Give it to me! Give it to me!
What a deep bond
between master and servant.
I'm so touched.
But this cup of wine
is different from the one
old Master Zhuge had.
It is a rare poison I specially obtained.
After drinking it,
you will feel as if venomous insects
are biting through your veins,
and you will scream
until your last breath.
Young Master Zhuge,
the stakes have changed.
You,
or him—
how will you choose?
I'll drink it!
Shiyi!
Yue Shiyi!
I'll drink it!
Your Majesty!
I've heard
that you dote on the Thirteenth Prince
and intend to entrust him with
the great responsibility of Great Yong.
In my opinion,
you should teach him
how to govern a country properly,
rather than treating the slaughter
of loyal subjects as child's play!
Zhuge Yue,
I hate the way you always look the most.
Now I want to see whether,
after you drink this cup of poisoned wine,
you can still remain
as calm as you are now.
Shiyi!
Shiyi...
Enough.
Your Majesty,
I have drunk the poisoned wine
for Young Master.
Your word is as good as gold.
Please let everyone in Qingshan Manor go.
Zhuge Yue,
for the sake of the late Zhuge Muqing,
I'll let bygones be bygones.
But if you don't know what's good for you,
I...
will destroy Qingshan Manor.
Every one of your subordinates
will be buried
with it.
Shiyi!
In my next life,
I will still follow you.
[Qingshan Manor]
Young Master.
These are the Moon Guard tags
of Yue Sheng, Yue Bo, and Yue Shijiu.
They were taken away with Shiyi.
The Thirteenth Prince
handed them over to the Muhe family...
and let the Muhe family
interrogate them about you.
To avoid dragging you down...
they all killed themselves.
These tags
were sent by the Muhe family.
Young Master.
The Muhe family has wanted to uproot
Qingshan Manor for a long time.
Now that they have attached themselves
to Zhao Yang,
they will definitely use him
to wipe us out.
Everyone, don't lose your spirit!
Now that the Young Master is back,
he will definitely protect Qingshan Manor.
Young Master.
You know the rules.
Yue Shiyi was your Moon Guard
and also a spy from Qingshan Manor.
His body...
cannot be kept.
I am the Chief of Qingshan Manor.
I will handle Yue Shiyi's body personally.
Lord Zhan came by during the day.
He took the files
of Yue Shiyi and the others.
Young Master, don't go!
It's pointless.
Once a spy of Qingshan Manor
is convicted,
none of their family members will survive.
Do you know
where Yue Shiyi's family lives?
What was his real name
Where is his family?
Young Master...
It's too late.
Lord Zhan has already been there.
You can't save them.
How is it?
How does it feel
to be betrayed by everyone?
So,
this was all your plan.
General Huan,
are you making decisions for me?
Helian!
I have no way back,
do I?