Here's the plan...
No helpers, no drivers, nothing.
To avoid gossip.
So, if you don't have
any better suggestions,
let's just stick to the plan.
Do whatever you want.
For now, we have to
follow what they say.
- Okay, game. Game!
- Cheers!
I’m good.
Sam…
- Hey, Sam.
- Sam!
Hi!
Who are you?
Here is my friend—also
he’s my ex-crush.
You are so kind and generous.
Why are you and
Summer still awake?
She’s waiting for her mom.
Mom?
I’m now your dog’s mom?
Yes.
It’s because
my dogs have grown fond of you.
I see.
Of course he didn’t mean
anything by that.
You waited for me, baby?
Yes.
I mean, we waited for you.
Your mom said
you didn't stay for dinner.
Is he worried about me?
Next time, if you're
going to be home late,
let me know.
So I’ll know what
to tell your mom and dad
if they ask me where you are.
I understand.
I’m sorry for not messaging you.
Have you eaten yet?
What now?
Is he genuinely being nice
or he’s just making sure
my parents can’t say
that he’s not taking care of me?
No,
I’m not hungry yet.
I think I’ll just sleep.
Well,
at least eat something
before you sleep.
It’s not good to sleep
on an empty stomach.
And
if you need
ointment for your back,
I have one upstairs.
Thank you, Clyden.
No worries.
If you suddenly feel hungry
and want a proper meal,
just tell me.
I can order.
Are you doing
an all-nighter again?
Okay.
How about you?
Did you eat dinner already?
If you want,
I can prepare for you.
What would you like?
It’s okay. I already ate,
but
thanks for asking.
Maybe it’s possible
that we can be
genuinely nice to each other.
Why are we always fighting?
Come on.
Let’s go inside.
It’s raining.
Let's go, baby!
Come here.
Good morning, Clyden.
Morning, Sam.
Your eyes look so puffy.
You haven’t slept yet, have you?
I’m just eating breakfast,
and then I’ll sleep afterward.
Sit down, let’s eat.
He’s still being nice to me.
I wonder what changed.
You cooked breakfast for me?
Yes.
The pancakes
were about to expire,
so I cooked them already.
Wouldn’t want them
to go to waste.
There he goes again,
keeping my hopes up!
What did I even expect?
Why?
You don’t like
almost-expired pancakes?
I could just give
them to the dogs.
No, I’ll eat them.
And too many pancakes
aren’t good for the dogs either.
It’s bad for them.
You can give them as a treat,
but you can’t put toppings
like butter, honey,
sugar, especially chocolates!
Did you have a dog before?
You seem to know a lot.
I did my research.
After all, I'm now
the mom of these dogs.
No,
Let’s swap that.
That one’s burnt.
Here.
This one’s better.
No. He’s actually being nice.
By the way,
Dad’s asking me to
come over for dinner.
It’s at your place.
Let’s go together?
Okay. I’ll go with you.
But you should sleep first.
I’ll just wake you up later.
So,
goodnight.
I’ll handle that, don’t worry.
And don’t worry about
the dogs, I’ll feed them.
You sure?
- Sure.
- Okay.
Thanks.
All right, your turn, babies!
Time for breakfast!
Let's go eat now,
my beautiful kids!
Hail!
No! You’re next. Share, please?
Summer, come here!
Eat your food now.
Eat your food.
You know what?
You guys are so lucky
that you have such
a beautiful and kind mom!
Right? Unlike your dad,
who’s always grumpy.
- Come eat, Summer. Here!
- Grumpy?
But you know what?
He is not that grumpy lately.
I actually
like this side of him.
I hope we can get along.
We could actually be friends,
if we just keep being nice
and kind to each other.
Right, babies?
You guys have good appetites.
But you know what?
I promise. I promise!
I’ll try my best
to not be grumpy
to your dad, too.
Yummy.
My look is serving today.
Yanna will love this ‘fit.
Maureen, you have to
win the approval
of your future in-laws, okay?
Dress to impress and
be on your best behavior.
Don’t disappoint me.
Clyden? Are you awake?
Is he still asleep?
Clyden, I’m letting
myself in, okay?
Wow, he's so
dedicated to his studies.
I wonder how it feels to be
this passionate about something.
Clyden?
How can someone as grumpy as him
look so innocent while asleep?
He looks tired, though.
Clyden?
I’m sorry I had to wake you up.
It’s just that it’s almost six,
and they’re
expecting us at 7:30.
Sorry, I just went
inside your room
‘cause you weren’t answering.
Are you okay?
You look good.
Thanks.
All right, I’ll get ready.
Okay.
I’ll wait for you outside.
They said there’s traffic
on the main highway.
I’ll just check
where the fastest route is.
We’re both wearing green.
Did he do it on purpose?
Or is it just a coincidence?
Well, if it was intentional,
I’m sure it’s just to make us
look like a real couple.
That color suits you.
Thanks.
Why is he so quiet?
This is so awkward.
I can’t stand it!
Do you mind if
I play some music?
It’s looking for...
I’m asking for your phone.
Oh my god.
I’m so sorry.
What the fuck was I thinking?
That was so embarrassing.
He’ll keep teasing me
about this, I’m sure!
You didn’t tell me that you
just wanted us to hold hands.
Cris, I heard you’re
expanding the hospital.
You’re adding a new wing?
You know that's impressive.
Yes! We recently acquired
the latest MRI machines,
the first in the country.
That’s why we’re getting
swarmed by VIP patients.
But you know how it is,
there’s a lot that needs fixing,
like permits and
government approvals.
Nothing moves without
the right connection.
I know what you mean, bro.
It’s just like politics.
You need the proper connections.
That way, you know
what you’re getting.
But,
you know?
I’m really glad we’ll
soon be a family.
Absolutely.
We can do great things
for this country.
- Yes.
Cheers to that.
- Cheers.
- Yeah, right.
At the expense of Clyden and me.
Wow. So fun.
Sam, your legs.
So, how’s living together?
It’s been great, Auntie.
I actually love
living with Clyden.
Yes, Mom.
It’s like the best thing that’s
ever happened in my life.
Well, that’s great.
I was really worried you
might be fighting every day
because you know Clyden,
he can be tactless sometimes.
If I'm forced to live
in a house with you...
might as well make sure
the house is nice.
Just a consolation.
I hate your dad. Actually,
I hate your whole family.
It’s fucking pathetic
to be honest.
And how am I your type?
You’re so full of yourself!
I’m leaving tomorrow,
just to get away from you.
I didn’t ask.
Clyden is actually really…
soft-spoken.
- Soft-spoken?
Really?
Yes, he’s not judgmental.
Not judgmental at all.
- Wow.
My son must
really like you, huh?
Who else would
he get it from, right?
Come on, Jaida.
I’m actually the
one who’s worried.
Because my daughter,
everyone knows
she’s a social butterfly,
and I’m afraid she might be
distracting Clyden.
She just loves to party.
She’s always in demand.
You’re so loud.
I can manage.
I take care of everyone
but no one takes care of me.
I can handle myself. Okay?
You can’t.
You know what,
you’re right, Auntie.
Sam can be really loud.
Sometimes she even
gets home late
because of all her activities.
The fuck?
This guy can’t even lie!
Did he really just rat me out?
But I found out that
the orgs Sam joins
are actually for charity.
She’s always busy
helping other people,
so I can’t help but
root for her, you know.
And she’s
the most caring person
I’ve ever met.
She even takes care of my dogs.
So,
it's really not hard
to love someone
like Sam.
That’s good.
If I didn’t know
we were just pretending,
I think I would’ve fallen
for those words.
Oh my gosh!
I’m sorry.
I didn’t see you there.
No worries.
Sorry for startling you.
No, it's okay.
So,
you’re graduating soon?
What’s with
the sudden small talk?
Yes. It’s my last year.
Nice. So,
after that,
you’ll get married
to my brother.
That’s the plan.
You know what?
If only I had done
great in college,
I’d be the one marrying you.
Such a shame!
You’re exactly my type, too.
So,
if ever you get
bored with Clyden...
feel free to approach me.
Does he think
I’m some kind of property
they can just pass around?
Excuse me, I think Clyden
is already looking for me.
Hold on.
Let’s talk some more.
Get your hands off her.
Okay!
Chill!
Clyden, it’s getting late.
I want to go home now.
Okay.
Let’s go home.
Why didn’t you
tell Charles off earlier?
He was clearly insulting you.
Are you afraid of him?
No.
I was afraid
I might cause a scene,
so I just let it go.
Are you…
always like that?
Like what?
Scared of conflict.
That’s why you stay quiet
even when you're the one
who's actually right.
No one has ever
pointed that out before.
It’s a disservice
to yourself if you don’t,
you know, speak up.
I hope one day you can
somehow find the courage
to defend yourself...
‘cause no one’s allowed
to talk to you like that.
Thank you, Clyden.
I appreciate that.
You can do it.
You’re able to show
your annoyance with me
when I tease you,
so how much more
with other people?
You’re different.
It’s just so easy
to be mad at you.
Okay, I’ll take that
as a compliment.
But he’s right.
Why is it that
I can be transparent
with my emotions with him?
How about you?
Did you always have a difficult
relationship with your brothers?
We used to be close.
But when we got older,
Dad would always compare us.
I feel like that's when their
resentment towards me started.
Do you hate your brothers?
Sometimes I do.
But what I feel more
is pity for them.
They’re always being
shamed by Dad.
How about my parents?
You hate them?
Sorry,
but I really don’t feel any
compassion towards your dad
because I witnessed firsthand
how his corruption has
affected hospital patients.
I was a premed
student back then.
There was a mother and her son
who had just come out
of the hospital.
Because they didn’t have money,
they weren’t admitted.
And that’s when
I saw how fucked up
our healthcare system really is.
It was during the term
of Senator Vera
at the Health Department.
Apparently, the mother didn’t
have enough for medication.
They were asking for help
from the government,
but the aid they
received was insufficient.
I used to think that money
always comes back.
But the lives
of our loved ones...
don’t.
That’s why I used
to get angry at people
who go to the hospital
only when it’s too late.
Life is priceless.
Even if you have
to borrow money,
as long as
you can get treatment.
That’s what matters.
That’s when I realized that
you can only have that
mindset if you’re privileged.
Unlike that mother and her son,
who had nothing at all.
So when they needed
help the most,
where was the government?
After that incident,
I immersed myself
in the public hospital system
and saw firsthand how corrupt
the management is.
No wonder the mother and
her son didn’t get any help.
Medical supplies and
equipment were overpriced.
So the hospital subsidy
funds were drained.
You know,
when I did my research,
it turned out your dad was
the one in charge
of the procurement
for all of these.
I didn’t know it was this bad.
No wonder he hates my dad.
I know my apology won’t undo
anything my dad did.
But,
I’m sorry for the victims
and...
thank you for
telling me this, Clyden.
I appreciate your honesty.
That’s one thing
I can promise to you, Sam.
I’ll always be honest with you.
Obviously.
You never filter
your words with me.
Sometimes it borders on rude,
and I just want to
smack you in the face.
But...
really, I appreciate
your honesty.
See?
You’re able to voice out
your frustration with me.
Just needs a little more
practice with other people.
Good morning!
He woke up in a good mood.
I’ll sit with you.
It’s not filling at all
when you eat alone.
He looks so neat.
Being a future doctor
really suits him.
What time is your class?
Won’t you hit traffic
on the way there?
My first class is at 10AM,
but I should get there by 9AM,
so I can review
and avoid traffic.
You still study
even before class?
So my readings don’t pile up.
I even review during break time.
Wow, your schedule seems hectic.
Wait, do you still
have time for lunch?
Sometimes,
when I remember.
You’re a future doctor.
I don’t need to tell you the
negative effects on your health
if you skip meals.
I’ll remember
to eat lunch today.
Thanks.
How about you?
Don’t you have class at ten?
How did you know?
I’ve noticed that...
you leave around 8:30 to 9AM.
I didn't know
he’s this observant.
My class schedule isn’t hectic.
I just get busy after classes
because I have
org meetings every day.
At least you don’t
forget to eat lunch.
He’s a bit chatty today, huh?
And this small talk
feels pleasant.
So, we can actually talk
without arguing.
Oh?
You’re wearing our
engagement ring today?
I always do.
Does he want people
to know he’s taken?
Taken by me?
I'm scared to take it off.
It might get lost.
And Dad might make me pay
for it if it does.
Of course! Why did I even
think it was because of me?
What the fuck is wrong with me?
People might think you're taken.
So?
I’m sure pretty girls from your
school will be disappointed.
Why?
Do you think others
find me likeable?
Wow, this guy is unaware
of how attractive he is.
If you smile at them often
and talk to them softly, then...
probably yes.
Like how I said good morning
to you earlier?
Huh?
Nothing.
Hurry up. You might
get stuck in traffic.
I convinced my uncle to book the
whole bar for the org meeting,
free of charge, when I told him
it’s for the fundraising event.
We only need to pay
for the food and drinks.
And they serve
good cocktails too, right?
I’m pretty sure a lot
will show up at the party.
I think we should do
something new too,
to attract more people.
What do you think, Sam?
Sam, are you okay?
Yes.
I'm sorry, just thinking
about something.
What is it? Is it a boy problem?
No!
Girls, I have a question.
What does it mean when someone
who's usually grumpy to you
suddenly becomes nice?
Are you talking about
a specific person here?
No, okay?
I’m just referring to a scene
from a Korean drama I watched.
It’s not that deep.
Well, it could mean nothing,
or it could mean everything.
Nothing, because
maybe he’s just being nice
now and wants to make up for
being grumpy to you.
And everything, because it
could be the start of something
romantic!
You’re right.
Why is it so hard to read him?
Girls, wait a minute, okay?
Okay.
Hey, guys!
What’s up?
Thanks for bringing me
home the other night.
Of course!
You guys are the best!
Are you guys together?
Huh?
Clyden.
I...
It’s...
You don’t have to worry.
You’re in good hands.
He’s a nice guy,
and I think he’s really wise.
You’ll learn a lot.
Wise?
He’s not a professor.
What’s so wise about him?
What’s there to learn from him?
Such a dumbass.
But, thank you! Thank you
for coming to the party.
I’ll invite you guys
again next time.
- Of course.
- I’ll message you...
and don’t ditch, okay?
In the next event,
can I have a free drink?
It’s for charity, you know.
For a good cause.
Maybe at the next event,
you’ll be...
I’m not like that.
Was I like that?
No hangover next time. Yeah?
I promise.
Thank you.
Hey, Giselle!
- Samantha!
- Hi!
Oh my god.
- It’s so good to see you.
- Nice to see you here.
What’s up? I heard you're
getting busy these days.
Not really.
My schedule is manageable.
More relaxed since
we're seniors now, right?
Yes.
You know what? I saw your
billboard, you looked so good.
Really, you saw it?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
Isn’t it hard being a model?
It can be hard.
I mean, it's a real job.
Long days on set.
Sometimes the photographer
can be intimidating.
But you know what,
I just love that
there’s a control
over the freedom of my time.
Definitely makes it exciting.
Plus, I get the
opportunity to travel.
The pay is pretty good, too.
It sounds like
a dream job to me,
especially about having freedom
and control over your time.
Yes. You know what?
Should I start modelling?
You know what?
You definitely have
the look and the vibe.
Let me look at you. Spin around.
How tall are you? 5’8”?
- Yes.
- With heels,
you could totally
rock that runway.
I mean, you have such an aura,
you have a beautiful neckline.
It would be so fun,
we could even model together.
Imagine we’re jetsetting,
the people that you meet…
You get to go to places you
wouldn’t even plan on going to.
You should
definitely think about it.
I can help you.
I have such a good agent,
and they’re always
looking for people.
I’m just kidding, Giselle,
but thank you for the offer.
Hey, think about it.
If you change your mind,
just give me a call.
Okay.
- Thank you!
- See you soon!
I’ll see you!
Me? A model?
I want to try but I feel like
I’m not fit for it.
Hey.
I was buying dinner earlier,
so I bought some for you too.
I hope you like ramen and gyoza.
You didn’t have to,
but thank you.
Okay.
I’ll just get water.
You can like, you know,
get the food already.
Nice.
We ran out of these earlier?
Did you buy these?
Yup.
I stopped by the grocery,
so I grabbed some.
You didn’t have to,
but thank you.
At what age did you decide
you wanted to be a doctor?
Because...
I saw in your room that
there's a photo of you
wearing a doctor's costume.
Just curious.
When was it…
That was at
my 6th birthday party.
Actually, I don’t remember
the exact age, but
since I was young, I’ve always
been at our hospital.
I also saw how my parents
took care of the patients.
That’s why.
I wanted to be like them.
It's good that at a young age,
you already knew what
you wanted to do in life.
How about you?
I don't know what I really want,
even though I'll be
graduating next year.
I took Communications,
not because it’s my passion.
I just did it because
I wanted to go against my dad.
Because I know that after this,
he’ll just dictate everything
he wants me to do with my life.
Your life is yours, Sam.
But if there
were no limitations,
what would you want to do?
Don’t laugh, okay?
You’re already laughing.
No. No, I’m not.
- Okay.
- Well?
I was thinking…
if I could…
model?
Don’t laugh.
I’m not laughing, I swear.
Okay.
What?
That’s a good idea.
It suits you.
I mean,
objectively speaking,
you have the physique,
you have the height.
Looks? Do you have it?
Yes, you have the looks,
and the personality of a model.
Really now…
Just say that I’m beautiful.
That’s it!
That confidence of yours,
you’ll need that if you
want to be a model.
Thanks.
For?
For saying that
I could be a model.
Your words boost my confidence.
But, yeah...
I still need to think about it.
You don’t have to hurry.
Samantha Maureen Vera.
- Yes?
- Maureen.
Maui.
Can I call you, Maui?
Only my family
gets to call me that.
Why? Am I not family?
I’m your future husband,
to be exact.
Is he serious, or
is he just teasing me again?
Nice try.
But I think you’re
forgetting our agreement.
We won’t last a day
until our wedding.
Are you sure?
Why? Do you...
like me now?
Do you?
No! I don’t like you.
Good.
Then the feeling is mutual.
I don’t like you
that way as well.
Okay.
It’s settled then.
We both don’t like each other.
But at least,
we don't hate each other.
We can manage to live
in this house peacefully.
Right.
Anyway, I need to
go back to studying.
Thanks for the food, Mau...
I mean, Sam.
Yes, no problem.
It’s still too early for him
to call me, Maui.
It's too risky.
Maybe in the future.
Are you eating well, Yanna?
Don’t forget to eat
fruits and veggies, okay?
And avoid coffee and soda.
As much as possible,
try to eat more fiber.
Grandma already mentioned that.
Also, avoid doing
heavy chores, okay?
Just rest,
you might hurt yourself.
Yes, Sam!
I'm already being nagged
by Mom and Grandma,
and now you're adding to it?
I can't see this pregnancy
getting into any trouble
with all these
naggers around me.
Jeez!
What about you?
How’s everything
with your fiancé?
Is he still grumpy?
Lately, we’re okay.
We’ve been nice to each other,
and we’re having
a lot of good conversations.
Surprisingly,
he’s fun to talk to.
So he's being nice to you now?
Are you ready for a taste?
Bitch! No!
There is no tasting
happening because
we're not in that
kind of relationship.
Besides, we’re breaking the
engagement in the near future,
remember?
You could still go for it.
You're both single,
and you guys
do look good together.
Give it a chance! Who knows?
No. We talked about it
a while ago.
We made it clear that
we don’t like each other.
Then why do
you look disappointed?
No, I’m not.
I'm just happy that we're
already in friendly territory.
And that’s as far as it can go.
Okay, if you say so.
You need to fix it. Like this...
Okay...
Hey!
Did you just take a photo of us?
I was fixing my bra.
No, I’m not.
Did she just roll her eyes?
So rude.
Hey, let it go.
No, Sam. She took our picture
without our consent.
That is not right,
especially because
she's invading our privacy.
You better not upload that.
Right! What if she’s going to
use it for other purposes?
Like what?
You think I’m gonna take your
photo, make a fake account,
and start chatting with old men
using your face?
Thanks for the idea, by the way!
Oh my god. Why is she so rude?
Girls, just let it go.
I’ll handle it. It’s fine.
Naomi, can we talk? Please?
You know her, Sam?
Kind of, she's...
She’s my friend.
All right. We’re just
going to buy food.
Do you want anything?
It’s okay, girls. You can go.
Naomi,
I’m sorry about what happened.
Can you just delete the photo?
I did not take a photo!
See it for yourself.
You really have to check, huh?
Of course,
you believe your friends.
You can’t even tell them
I’m your sister.
I’m sorry. I thought
you wanted us to treat each
other like strangers in school.
I didn’t know...
Yeah, you’re right.
Maybe we should treat each other
like strangers here in school.
You couldn’t even
defend me from them.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Yes. I’m okay.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yes.
What do you want for dinner?
I'm buying.
I’m not hungry.
But thank you for offering.
By the way, I have an
org party this Friday.
It’s a fundraising event.
Do you want to attend?
I can’t.
I still need to finish
my readings.
But I’ll just buy a ticket
to help out.
Okay.
Thank you, Clyden.
I’ll go to sleep now.
- Goodnight.
Let’s have a family
dinner tomorrow.
Don’t be late.
I have no energy for
a family dinner tomorrow.
I don’t even know how Naomi
will react when she sees me.
Summer! Hi!
Are you here to comfort me? Huh?
Babies!
So cute! Thank you.
Where’s Clyden?
You didn’t tell me
I should bring him,
so I didn’t invite him.
And I think he’s also
busy with his studies.
Well, you should
always bring him.
Besides, he's your
future husband.
And you should
get to know him more.
You should force yourself
to get to know him.
Maui,
make sure he doesn’t back out
of this engagement.
You need him.
No, I don’t.
Yes, Mom.
I’ll bring him next time.
Good.
Naomi, do you have plans
for your birthday?
It’s your 18th birthday.
Well…
Nothing grand.
She’s gonna have a little
get-together with her friends.
Mom, it’s her 18th birthday.
It should be grand
if she wants it to be.
Honey, just because your
18th birthday was grand
doesn’t mean hers has to be too.
Besides, we talked
about it already.
A little get-together with
her friends will do.
Can you stop talking
about my birthday?
Stop acting like
you care about me.
You don’t know anything
about me. It’s annoying.
Naomi!
You’re such an ungrateful kid,
you know that?
You should be thankful
your sister even remembered your
birthday when no one else did.
Mom!
Don’t raise your
voice at me, Maureen.
You.
I’m so disappointed in you.
You’re grounded.
Go to your room!
Yeah.
Like it would even
make a difference.
I’m used to it anyway.
God!
Mom, don’t do that to her.
Don’t jail her in her room.
Maui, she needs
to be disciplined.
And you,
don’t disappoint me too.
Hey.
How’s dinner?
It was okay.
Did something happen?
I’ve noticed since yesterday
that you’re not okay.
I’m having problems
with my sister.
Do you need a hug?
Can you give me a hug?
Come here.
You smell nice.
You just took a shower,
didn’t you?
Sorry.
I just came from a jog.
From jogging? But you still
smell like baby powder?
Wow.
I can feel your heartbeat.
But I’ll just pretend
that I can’t.
I hope things will
get better soon, Sam.
Thanks, Cy.
I really needed that.
And you know what?
You can call me Maui,
if you like.
Sure, Maui.
Thanks for buying tickets
for the fundraising party.
I hope you can still make it.
I can’t promise,
but I’ll try.
Okay, thanks.
Hey!
Luna’s getting nervous.
Don’t worry. Kalix is not going.
- Just enjoy the night.
- Okay.
Let’s go! Let’s go!
All right.
Come on, guys. Energy!
Wow! She’s got energy.
You’re full of energy, girl!
What’s up? Got some good news?
Not really. I’m just
in the mood to party.
Really?
Our friend here is really happy.
Let’s dance!
Like this.
Go, Sevi.
Hey, Sam? What the...
- Come on!
- Are you drunk?
I’m not drunk, Sevi.
Come on, dance with me.
Let’s go, Luna.
This is fun.
Oh, god.
That color suits you.
Thanks.
You know what,
let’s take a break.
Let’s have dinner for a bit?
Yes, I’m starving.
Cy, ikaw?
Pass. I need to finish
everything by 7PM.
Why? What’s up?
There’s an important event
I need to go to.
What event?
You know, Eva,
you’re such a gossip, huh?
Don’t worry about it!
You know what?
Let’s just eat. Okay?
My brain can’t handle any
more medical terms right now.
- Come on.
- You’re treating, right?
No promises.
This is the first time
I’ll meet your fiancée.
I still can’t believe
you’re actually engaged.
Wow!
Sir, flowers for sale. Only 150.
Should I buy?
This is really cheap, sir.
A small one should be fine.
- How much?
- 150.
Thank you, boss. Thank you!
That’s good enough.
No.
- How much is this?
- 350, boss.
You can just add 200.
200...
- All right, then.
- Thank you, boss.
- Thanks.
- Let’s go.
Shit! No— Not enough.
How much is this?
600, boss.
Are you sure about this?
Yes.
Here you go, just add 400.
Keep the change.
Hey! Thanks, boss.
You might as well
buy everything.
Let’s go.
Hey!
Hey, what’s up, mamacita?
Are you new here?
Damn, this is some
real party, bro.
Your bouquet looks
out of place, though.
I thought it was a formal event.
How can it be a formal event
when it’s literally at a bar?
Sure, Cy. Sure.
Where’s Maui?
If you stopped ignoring
my messages and calls,
then maybe you would know.
I’m sorry, I didn’t answer
your calls earlier.
Here’s the playboy!
I think it’s really time
to go now.
No. So cute! One more!
Let’s go now.
Do you guys know
how wild the party was?
Sam here was so hyper!
She was even giving
Sevi a sexy dance!
While Sevi was just standing
there like a statue.
It’s been a while since
we all went out together.
What do you expect?
Yanna hasn’t been around.
Do you know
what happened to her?
Yes, where is she anyway?
Hi, girls!
- Hi!
- Hi, Eva!
They’re my friends.
So nice to meet you.
What’s your problem?
Nothing!
Go, drive Eva home.
What’s your problem?
Are you jealous?