(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
SUMMER OF 2020
PLEASE WEAR A FACE MASK
TOGETHER, WE CAN OVERCOME THIS!
COVID-19 PCR TESTING STATION
SEJEONG PARK BEHIND HEALTH CENTER
GOOD LANDLORD CAMPAIGN!
30% DISCOUNT ON RENT!
SEJEONG-RO
COMMERCIAL BUILDING ASSOC. 11
PHOTO ALBUM
YOU'RE A ROLE MODEL FOR LANDLORDS
YOU'RE A MAN OF CHARACTER, MR. GI!
Mr. Gi.
- Have a nice, cold coffee.
- Mr. Oh.
Thank you.
- Why does it taste so good?
- Right?
You didn't know our latte
ranked second in the whole world?
Who came first, then?
We got first place
but I'm trying to be humble.
I'm so sorry the pandemic broke out
just when you opened your café.
I'll do my best to get through it.
I was lucky enough
to meet a great landlord
who reduced the rent,
and that was a huge help.
You're helping me out, actually.
I found a great tenant like you
and your café helps
Se-yoon Building center itself.
I feel so reassured.
- Honestly.
- I'll give a discount
to all the tenants in this building.
Thank you so much.
- You saw our basement storage.
- Yes.
You can use that space freely.
If any facilities cause a problem
or get in the way of your business
you can come to me at any time.
I'll take care of it for you
before you can even take a breath.
Man, our landlord is the best.
Let's go, Se-yoon Building!
Let's go.
- How about a commemorative photo?
- Should we?
Let's see.
You're a handsome guy.
Okay. One, two, three.
- We look nice.
- I'll send it to you.
- Okay.
- Should we hang it on the café wall?
- Should we?
- As a souvenir?
Do you think the banner is too small?
Should I have made it bigger?
No, it's big enough.
No one would be
stupid enough to miss it.
- Right?
- Yes.
- I hope it becomes a centerpiece.
- It will.
Your building will be
the center of this neighborhood.
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
EPISODE 5
I'm using this on Mr. Oh now.
This shot will put him to sleep
for a few hours.
It's your turn now.
I'm done.
Okay.
- It was so good.
- Enjoy your meal.
- Cheers, everyone.
- Cheers.
- Let me pour you one.
- Thanks.
- You should wash your hands.
- Okay.
Will Dong-ki be okay?
He didn't bleed for long
and the wound isn't that deep,
so he'll be fine.
Why do things only go haywire for me?
What now?
What if he knows everything?
Like what?
About kidnapping Yi-gyeong.
Let's take some time
to think about this.
And talk.
Talk about what?
Why don't you pay him to keep quiet?
What if he starts talking
after taking the money?
Should we make him sign
a non-disclosure agreement?
I'll see if I can think of a way
to talk about this
calmly and quietly.
You're like a whole other person.
Were you like this
when you slept with Hwal-sung?
You don't remember
what we talked about, do you?
We'll discuss that later.
The timing's off right now.
What a grand excuse.
What do you want to do, then?
Get divorced?
Let's get out of here.
Come on. Let's go.
VCU TEAM 1
CAFÉ JINSIM, ROBUSTA, BRAZIL,
YONGDAEMUN-GU SEJEONG-RO 52
CASE REPORT
JEON YI-GYEONG'S KIDNAPPING
SEOUL YONGDAEMUN POLICE STATION
NOTES
PERSONAL DETAILS
"Jung Chang-su."
PREVIOUSLY OWNED CAR MS. JEON WAS IN,
OWNED CHANGSHIM BUILDING
"Changshim Building."
CASE KN-260315AT
SURVEILLANCE &amp; DASHCAM FOOTAGE
SURVEILLANCE FOOTAGE KN-260315AT
SEJEONG-RO REDEVELOPMENT AREA 4
CHANGSHIM BUILDING SITE
CHANGSHIM BUILDING
SEJEONG-RO 247, YONGDAEMUN-GU, SEOUL
APPLICATION TO VIEW OR PRINT
PROPERTY REGISTRY
ADDRESS: SEJEONG-RO 247
"Real Capital."
OWNER
REAL CAPITAL AND GLOBAL PARTNERS
Sign next to your name, please.
RECEIPT OF PERSONAL BELONGINGS
TRANSFERRED FROM KOH JU-RAN
TRANSFERRED TO JEON YI-GYEONG
PERSONAL BELONGINGS
PHONE, CAR KEY, MIN HWAL-SUNG
I'm sorry about last time.
Pardon?
When you questioned Su-jong.
You were just doing your job.
I think I overreacted.
Not at all.
I jumped to conclusions.
You can catch
the culprit, right?
We'll do our best,
but in cases like this
if we can't catch the culprit
within 48 hours
the case is likely to go unsolved.
Oh, gosh. Hello.
You came in pretty early.
Okay, so...
How is Mr. Min doing?
- He's just the same.
- I see.
Why don't you get her
some tea or coffee?
No, thanks. I should go.
My mother is eating out
with the police commissioner today.
Yes, I heard about that.
- The three billion won.
- What?
My mom hasn't given up on that.
She's not someone
who can live with a loss.
SEOUL YONGDAEMUN POLICE STATION
PERSONAL BELONGINGS
PHONE, MIN HWAL-SUNG
Hello?
LOAN RECOMMENDATION
URGENT LOANS OK, LOAN HEAVEN
"Loan Heaven"?
Hello?
Is that Loan Heaven?
We don't take general customers.
We only take private clients.
Are there certain requirements?
- I'd like a consult. Where is...
- Come on.
Miss.
We only take clients
via recommendations.
Call somewhere else.
Min Hwal-sung.
I got this number from Mr. Min.
That changes everything.
Will you come to us?
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
JUNG CHANG-SU
POLICY DEPUTY NAM SANG-HO
"Nam Sang-ho"?
I guess he was still inside
when the place was torn down.
He must've had a drink or two.
Sergeant.
The ownership of Chang-su's building
was transferred to Real Capital.
Around the time we think he died.
If you get me a search warrant...
Hey.
You're relying on your gut again,
aren't you?
Is it about Gyun?
You're adding to my plate
when I have a lot on my mind.
Hey.
Just close the case as an accident.
You told me to bring
Jung Chang-su's body, so I did.
Why won't you let me investigate?
Do you still have a grudge against me
because I reported you
- to Internal Affairs?
- You punk! That's...
- That was ages ago!
- What is it, then?
Ju-ran.
Let's go with the flow.
You need to close some cases
and get promoted.
Whatever.
Forget about that.
Do you know Deputy Nam Sang-ho?
POLICY DEPUTY NAM SANG-HO
He works at City Hall.
No.
Who's he?
I found that on Jung Chang-su's body.
Hey, come here.
Take a look.
Look at the business cards I got
from politicians, big and small.
See this?
A policy researcher.
An inspector.
I'll say this out of concern for you.
Don't go after a politician.
You might get into a lot of trouble.
Goodness.
Come and eat.
Okay.
(Is something wrong, Dad?)
Not at all.
(The steamed egg tastes great.)
I seasoned it just right today.
Seon.
I don't feel like eating.
Da-rae, I'm going to work.
(Why not eat first?)
No, there's someone in our building
waiting desperately to see me.
Sorry.
(What's up with him?)
Don't mind him.
Your dad.
His blood is Type O, right?
(Dad's Type O,
you're Type B, and I'm Type B.)
(Why do you ask?)
Okay.
Here's your iced Americano.
- Why did it take so long today?
- Sorry.
- Hello.
- Two iced Americanos.
Two?
Aren't you taking my order?
Just a moment, please.
I don't have much time to spare.
Can I have a chocolate latte?
Yes, sorry. Just a moment.
Where the heck is my boss?
Did the moron get drunk again?
THE BOSS
PART-TIMER 7
Poor guy.
What on earth are you doing?
What landlord stabs his tenant
with a knife and locks him up?
Is that even right?
I'm really sorry, Mr. Oh.
It was an accident. I swear.
Mr. Gi, right now...
I'm cold and dizzy.
I really need to go to the ER.
Okay.
Are you hungry? I brought food.
Do you know I wet my pants?
Oh, dear.
It's fine. It dried out.
If you untie me now
I'll pretend it never happened
and forget about it.
Mr. Oh.
Have a piece of a sandwich.
Bread might be too hard to eat
since you're on your back
so have the ham and egg filling.
Go on and eat.
Here.
Be careful.
And I used scissors, not a knife.
Oh, no.
Have some water.
Hold your head up a bit.
Slowly. Take your time.
What you just fed me.
Did you get it from my café?
Yes, I did.
How are things over there?
Well, your part-timer's doing
the best he can.
Darn it.
What will you do with me?
You won't kill me, will you?
Come on now.
How could you
say something so dreadful?
Don't go any further.
Let me go to a hospital.
Okay, hang in there
just a bit longer.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
- You'll let me go?
In that case
I won't tell anyone
that your wife had an affair
with your friend.
Where did you hear about that?
You talked about it yesterday
after you tied me up.
No, wait. I'm still chewing...
LOAN HEAVEN
Ma'am.
We met, haven't we?
I can't say.
You're Mr. Min's wife.
Yes.
Is he still in the hospital?
He is.
Oh, dear. I hope he gets well soon.
So he can pay me back.
Your husband has poor credit.
Credit is everything.
Don't you agree?
How much does he owe?
Including the interest
and all that he owes
800 million won.
He only borrowed cash?
What does that mean?
Did you lend or sell him a car?
I'm a money-lender.
I don't handle secondhand cars.
What about unregistered cars?
Unregistered cars?
What should we do with you?
Miss. It's illegal to deal
with unregistered cars.
Money-lending is legal.
Can you pay back the money?
I hadn't heard from Mr. Min
so I was going to seize his assets.
- Account number.
- What?
Your account number.
Don't you want my money?
94028-119-572-38.
Nara Bank.
Check the balance.
NARA BANK DEPOSIT
800,000,000 WON
What the heck? I like your style.
Ma'am.
If you need anything
do give us a call.
YEON HWA-JIN INTERNAL MEDICINE
Ae-su.
What? Do you want one?
Like the old times?
No, thanks.
You used to chew me out
for selling meds.
What are you doing here?
Things came up.
Are you sure this is safe?
Yes.
The doctor is near death
and doesn't care about anything.
How is life treating you?
Awesomely great.
Don't get caught.
Don't worry.
- The money...
- Forget it.
We go too far back to owe each other.
Thanks.
Light it up.
I can't believe I gave blood.
I feel so dizzy.
What's that?
I'm handcuffing him instead.
I need him to be comfortable
if we're to reach an agreement.
He should be able to eat
and relieve himself at will.
Here's the key.
You keep it.
Where did you get the handcuffs?
Where do you think?
I bought them from a store.
A place that sells toys for adults?
Did you use that with Hwal-sung?
That punk is a pervert.
Did he use that
to provoke and excite...
Damn it.
Are you insane?
Is that what you want to say now?
Aren't you the crazy one?
How could you do that with my friend?
I'm really sorry.
Divorce me if you can't forgive me.
But let's sort out
the problem we're facing first.
I want to sort out our problem first.
You don't care how I feel, do you?
Scenes from that video
still float around in my head.
I'm sorry.
It won't happen again.
Seon.
Cheating is different
for a woman than for a man.
Women cheat with men
they truly have feelings for.
It wasn't like that.
I made a mistake, and so did you.
We found out now, and that's that.
I never cheated on you, though.
It's done.
How was he this morning
when you talked to him?
If I let him go,
he said he'd let it go.
Did you believe him?
How could I?
I can't even believe my wife.
Let's do our best to persuade.
If that fails...
If that fails?
We must choose.
Will it be our family or him?
Hwal-sung.
Is there anything else?
MADAM JUNG
I'VE BEEN SO OUT OF IT LATELY
COME FOR A DRINK
AND I'LL CHEER YOU UP
ARE YOU SEDUCING ME?
I'M NOT SEDUCING, I'M SERIOUS
YEON HWA-JIN INTERNAL MEDICINE
NURSE JOO
DID YOU WIRE THE MONEY?
CASH DEPOSITED
What is this, Hwal-sung?
You cheated on me?
What the...
NO POSTS
I HAD A GOOD TIME TODAY.
ARE YOU FREE NEXT WEEK?
I FEEL ALIVE WHEN I'M WITH YOU.
MY WIFE WHINES AND HAS NO CHARM
SHE'S AN AIRHEAD
BUT YOU'RE FULL
Hello?
Yes, where are you?
I'm at the hospital.
Why? Is something going on?
No, I was just feeling tired.
When will you put together
that meeting I mentioned
with Se-yoon Building's owner?
Give me some more time, Mom.
We don't have to drag this on.
Handle it quickly.
Okay.
I got it, so enough is enough.
HOW TO KILL A PERSON
HOW THE MAFIA KILLS
HOW TO KILL SOMEONE
WITHOUT CAUSING PAIN
PAINLESS, NATURAL DEATH,
I'M TRYING TO WRITE A NOVEL...
We must choose.
Will it be our family or him?
No.
This is kind of heavy.
(What are you doing?)
Something broke down in my building.
(You seem broken, Dad.)
Come on.
I'm doing great. Totally fine.
Da-rae.
Never mind.
(How silly. You've been odd lately.
You need to pull yourself together!)
Yes, right. I just remembered.
Dad loves you, Da-rae.
Thank you.
Did you bring him?
Hand them over.
It's right here.
Jeez, how unsightly.
Zip it up already.
I thought he was with me
but he went around
doing odd things behind my back.
Anyway.
Great work handling him.
It wasn't a big deal.
Are you joking...
That was a funny comeback.
How youthful.
Wait.
What happened to that vice president?
He returned to the States.
Without saying goodbye?
He's quite rude.
Excellent.
He always showed off
but never did his job.
I never liked him.
What was your name again?
Jonah, sir.
A Korean from overseas?
It's something like that.
Something like that?
So?
Are you some kind of troubleshooter?
Well, whatever you are,
do a good job from now on.
I'm not the type who cares
about people's age or gender.
All I care about is one's competence.
You can trust me.
How feisty and youthful.
Morgan?
I prefer you to that sly punk.
Anyway.
Handle him quietly, okay?
Are you going to keep working
with that tteokbokki guy?
Just until we get everything
from Nouveau City.
What about him?
We'll mix him in there.
In a way that nobody notices.
How thorough you are.
Does your wife do this often?
When will you let me go?
People in my life will think
something is weird.
Yes, so I wanted to discuss
that matter with you today.
I need you to guarantee
that you will not say anything
once you leave this place.
Yes.
I'd like to do that as well.
You saw the money, didn't you?
I did.
And you tried to take it.
Be honest with me.
Yes, so I put it in my bag.
Do you know what that money is?
You have to be frank with me today.
It's the abduction ransom.
So that's what you think.
Remember that time
when I helped you carry the suitcase?
I carried it from the bottom
just like this, right?
Down there.
That was a person, right?
I was just honest with you.
I swear that I'll keep the secret.
Why would I share this with anyone?
How is that going to benefit me?
Wouldn't it benefit me
if I didn't talk about this?
I'll shut my mouth if you pay me.
Wait.
How much?
I don't know. A billion won?
Don't throw out a random number.
Be more realistic.
I don't have that kind of money.
You do!
I can tell that much by looking.
Okay, let's say I do have that money.
Even if I give it to you
you still won't keep your promise.
I will...
Sure, you can think that way.
But in this situation,
we have to have faith in each other.
Are you going to kill me?
You aren't, right?
I'm talking to you right now
because I know you aren't like that.
One second, Mr. Oh.
One second.
- Hello?
- Hey, I'm on my way
to the building right now.
Yi-gyeong is coming over
with her mother.
She wants to seal the deal.
- Right now?
- Yes, she's in a hurry.
You must've been right
about the redevelopment project.
Yes, I told you many times.
I told you time and time again
that we shouldn't sell this.
All right. I'll be there soon.
I'll be right back, Mr. Oh.
You said you wanted to talk...
Think of your daughter!
Think of your daughter's future.
Will you turn into a murderer?
Think of Da-rae.
What would she say if she saw this?
Right?
We should talk!
Da-rae!
COMMERCIAL PROPERTY SALES AGREEMENT
I won't beat around the bush.
I gave you 30% more
than the current market price.
Why?
- What do you mean?
- Why are you
paying me more than the market price?
So you must know.
Yes, many people have been
interested in this building lately.
This is too big for you to handle.
You should step out of this.
I'll give you a good price.
Mom, what are you doing?
I'm always grateful for how you care
for my daughter and her husband.
I'll continue to watch your back
so give me the building.
COMMERCIAL PROPERTY SALES AGREEMENT
SELLER: GI SU-JONG
BUYER: JEON YI-GYEONG
We don't have much time.
Sign it so that we can wrap up.
- You know about Hwal-sung.
- Yes?
Did you know that he was
after this building?
I wish
to hold on to this building
a little longer.
There must be a reason
why people are after this.
How dare you disregard
the goodwill I'm providing?
You have no idea
how this world works.
I just told you.
This is not something you can handle.
Mom.
Yes, I understand what you mean.
But first, I must talk to my wife.
You're pushing me
a little too hard today
which I find disconcerting.
Pushing who?
I gave you 30% more
than what it's worth.
I never asked you for it.
You'll regret this.
You really can't handle this.
I'll do my best.
Well...
Let's talk again next time.
We also need time to think.
Yes, Mom. You were too rushed today.
You don't even know your place.
I'm sorry. I'll have a talk with her.
- It's okay.
It's all right.
Mom!
Mom.
We should think about it.
Mom, please!
You need to think
in other people's shoes.
Do you have to go this far?
You dimwit.
That's why people
only take advantage of you.
What?
You paid back your husband's debt.
How did you know?
What an idiot.
Wait, you knew, yet you didn't help?
Why would I help him?
He's my...
Darn it.
Yes.
I need to see you tonight.
I have a favor to ask you.
Yes.
Bye.
What?
You ruined me.
Later on
you'll realize
that I had been right all along.
No.
I'll never be like you.
Is this really enough?
Do you have another idea?
No, not really.
Why don't we lower the cost a bit?
No.
Let's just give him what he wants.
All right. Let's do that.
Right here.
"I, Oh Dong-ki, have participated
in Jeon Yi-gyeong's abduction
with Kim Seon and Gi Su-jong.
In return,
I received monetary compensation.
I hereby promise
not to leak out this information
to any third parties in any format
and I swear to keep this confidential
with my life."
All right.
Thank you.
If you break this promise,
we'll all go down together.
I'll keep it with my life.
One stab with a knife
and two days of confinement
exchanged for a billion won
is pretty nice, actually.
- Can you...
- Hello, Yi-gyeong.
Why?
I came back to talk to you and all.
You're in the basement, right?
She came to see us.
You should go upstairs.
I'll be there.
Bye.
- I'll go.
- Okay.
Wrap up everything here.
- Help!
- Hey!
Why are you doing this, Mr. Oh?
Do you really want to die?
Mr. Oh, I got a nosebleed. Darn it.
Yi-gyeong.
Do you hear something?
Hear what?
I thought I heard someone screaming.
Since this building is old
you can sometimes hear sounds
from the first floor.
Anyway, what brings you here?
Well...
Can we talk in private?
Sure.
- Should we go to the rooftop?
- Okay.
I'm so sorry. Can you free me?
Why won't this open? Darn it.
It won't open?
You're dead, you punk.
What do you mean dead, Mr. Oh?
You need to talk more nicely.
I have the key to your handcuffs.
This one.
What?
Wait.
- Where is it?
- It's not there?
You don't have it.
First of all
let me apologize
on behalf of my mom, Seon.
It wasn't your fault.
But still, I called that meeting.
I'm so sorry, and I feel really bad.
That's family.
They might seem
embarrassing and frustrating
but you continue to go on with them.
I have no idea
how my life turned out like this.
No one is living
a better life than you, Yi-gyeong.
Hwal-sung has a woman on the side.
A married woman with a kid.
And he...
badmouthed me with that woman.
He said I was an airhead
without charm or maturity.
He probably married me
for my family's money, right?
I was young, rich, and dumb
so he must've thought I was so easy.
Don't say that, Yi-gyeong.
You're such a beautiful person.
Yi-gyeong.
Would you like to grab a beer?
Yes.
Let go, darn it.
Let go!
Let go. Darn it.
Darn it.
Hey, let go of me.
Let go.
- Let go of me, Oh Dong-ki!
- Su-jong seems like the real deal.
What? What do you mean?
He's an honest man.
Oh, I see.
Who do you think
he had an affair with?
I thought I'd never be curious
but now that I'm in this situation
I'm dying to find out
who she is
and what in the world she's like
for him to have an affair
with a married woman who has a kid.
I'm dying to know.
Is she pretty?
Is she sexy? Or intelligent?
It's nothing like that.
What?
It's just that
he doesn't know
how precious what he already has is.
When someone is
unsatisfied with their reality
people covet what isn't theirs.
People are like that.
It's not a matter
of who's better and who's worse.
I don't think
that's what's important.
It's not your problem, Yi-gyeong.
It's Hwal-sung's.
Seon.
What book do I have to read
to speak with such eloquence?
Tell me.
Stop it. I'm not eloquent.
- Mr. Oh.
- I let go.
- Okay.
- I let go of you!
Take a break, then. Take a five.
Let's take a five.
Hey, do you remember?
Remember what?
The good landlord.
During COVID-19?
Yes, when I had
just opened my business.
Those were the good days.
You made the best latte back then.
Back then
you did that to receive
the tax benefit, right?
What are you talking about?
That's just how the law works.
What are you doing?
Law, my ass.
Your frugal tactic went a long way.
I got you, didn't I?
Hey, Mr. Oh. Stop it.
Let go of me.
Thank you
for taking the time to talk to me.
Don't worry about it.
Talk to me whenever you need to.
Let's meet often from now on.
Okay.
Die.
Die!
What? He hasn't come out?
COLD STORAGE
What's with the door?
What did I do so wrong?
Su-jong!
All you had to do was pay me.
But you left me here
until I wet my pants. Die!
Don't do this, Mr. Oh.
Su-jong, let's leave.
Oh, my.
Darn it.
HANMAEUM BUILDING
I'm saying we should do
what we did back then just once more.
You want to go to Se-yoon Building
and make it defective?
It's not that hard.
You just need to pop a few pipes.
Don't you think
we're too old
to do something like that?
We're much better
than those young ones.
Do you have to take things this far?
You wouldn't be able to say that
if you knew the kind of humiliation
I had to suffer from today.
HE THAT FINDETH HIS LIFE
SHALL LOSE IT
AND HE THAT LOSETH HIS LIFE
FOR MY SAKE SHALL FIND IT
MATTHEW 10:39
I can let you use the equipment.
But that's about it.
You won't get your hands dirty?
I'm acquainted with that landlord.
I also have principles to live by.
Fine.
I'd feel much more comfortable
getting this done myself, anyway.
I had to do the dirty,
unpleasant, and dangerous work
all by myself
to get to this place today.
And why?
Because you must never trust humans.
You'll regret this.
I've already lived in regret
for a very long time.
It must sting.
Do you think Dong-ki will be fine?
Yes, he must be a bit hurt, though.
All done.
What now?
I don't know.
Let's keep an eye on him.
I should've turned it down
when Hwal-sung mentioned
the abduction scheme.
I must've been out of my mind.
My only thought then
was to protect this building.
Don't say that.
You did your best.
And you did it for us.
If I get locked up,
will you send me money for snacks?
You won't be the only one there.
I'll get locked up as well.
You can't get locked up.
You have to look after Da-rae.
She has to get the surgery done,
go to college, and even get married.
We can do all that
as long as we keep the money safe.
Let's do this together until the end
no matter where it leads us.
Let's do this together to the end.
We'll be fine, right?
Yes.
MANAGEMENT OFFICE
Die! You asshole.
I'm sorry.
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
Is this all you have?
We've been using security cameras
since last night.
We didn't use them before
because we had some issues.
Don't you find it strange?
Everything that's happening
inside this building.
Wake up!
Are you scared that
I'll get caught and start talking?
Bring me money
before I spill the beans!
Wasn't there something you said
about the place I was locked up
when I got kidnapped?
Yi-gyeong asked
about the cold storage?
You're good at finding people, right?
Find that person.
We do anything as long as we're paid.
- Get him!
- By any chance, are we the suspects?
If only you hadn't made that offer
I wouldn't have come this far.
Subtitles by Eunsook Youn
and Jennifer Lim