WHEN THE PHONE RINGS
EPISODE 8
Thank you…
for all your hard work, 406.
You…
knew everything?
Since when? No…
If you knew, why didn't you…
Why didn't I what?
Why didn't you hate me?
Tell me,
Hong Hee-joo.
Tell me how to hate you.
Tell me how to not love you.
Eat slowly.
It's good.
I've been wondering for a while,
but why are you such a good cook?
Cooking's about sincerity.
To tell the truth,
as long as the kimchi's good,
this dish is a success.
It's really good.
From now on,
let's eat together often.
At home.
So it'll feel more like a home
and not feel like a jail.
When did I call it a jail?
That's what you said.
- I did?
- You just feel guilty.
No, I don't.
Was the three years
we lived together normal?
There were nothing but cold vibes
in this house.
We didn't speak or make eye contact.
We didn't eat or sleep together…
Do you want that?
If you hated sleeping in separate rooms,
you should've told me.
No, that's not what I'm saying.
To me,
this home was warm.
When I returned home
and saw the lights in the window,
it made me feel good
to know you were there.
When I looked at you,
the noisy world around me
became quiet…
and peaceful.
You should've told me sooner.
Do you remember
what I said to you before?
I told you
not to have any feelings for me.
Don't try to have any feelings for me.
Let it all go.
You don't need to act like a puppet
in front of me.
How could I forget that?
You didn't have to be so harsh.
I was scared.
If I didn't draw the line like that,
I was scared
I'd end up giving you my heart,
and before I knew it,
I'd think living like this with you
might actually be okay.
That I'd give up everything
and just cave in.
Let me be clear.
You weren't part of my plan.
So from now on,
if you interfere or get in my way,
I won't let it slide.
What was the plan
you mentioned back then?
I'll tell you when the time comes.
Actually…
I have something to tell you too.
UNKNOWN CALLER
Relax.
Don't worry anymore.
I will track him down soon.
Also, about this phone,
only you and I know about it.
It's not going to the police.
That'll never happen.
Are you worried it'll be revealed
that I'm involved?
I'm prepared for it.
Let's reveal everything and--
I'm going to take care of things
one by one.
You just wait.
Don't think about doing anything.
And for the time being,
don't speak in front of anyone
but me.
Why not?
The accomplice is someone close to us.
I'm sure of it.
Until we know exactly who it is,
we must be careful.
Okay.
To tell you the truth,
I'm sad to end these calls.
It was fun.
The fiery Hong Hee-joo that only shows up
when she's 406.
Wait, where was that lingerie again?
Why? No, wait.
Why?
It's just…
hard to believe.
That you accepted me just as I am
and forgave me.
Could you do the same
when you know everything about me?
MASTER
DID YOU GET THE PHONE BACK?
No.
WHY NOT?
What the hell?
Damn it.
Just a moment!
Goodness.
Good grief.
- Goodness.
- What floor?
Thank you. I'm going to B4.
I see.
Thank you.
Goodness.
Aren't you Spokesperson Paik Sa-eon?
Yes.
It's an honor to meet you.
I saw the news. Are you okay?
The world's so chaotic
that all sorts of crazy people dare
to do things like that to you.
Thank you for your concern.
Take care of yourself.
Such a bad guy should be caught…
Did you know?
Paik Sa-eon
smells really good.
What I want to get back
isn't that stupid phone.
I'm going to take it all.
Even the scent coming from him.
The screen beside me shows
the composite sketch of the suspect.
According to police,
the suspect is around 185 cm tall
with a solid build
and in his early to mid-thirties.
And he is odd-eyed, and one eye
appears light brown in different lighting.
He has also been reported
to have anger management issues,
acting impulsively
due to a lack of control.
Sir. Ma'am.
HBC has reached out to confirm if
the interview will proceed as scheduled.
- Cancel it.
- Say we'll do it.
Yes, ma'am.
Mr. Min.
Yes, sir?
The number you dialed doesn't exist.
Please check the number and try again.
Please check…
The number you dialed doesn't exist.
Did you sleep well?
Aren't you going to work?
Not today.
I won't move an inch today.
I took the day off.
You did?
As you know,
for the past three years,
I've worked without any days off,
even on holidays and weekends.
I can take a day off.
Then…
what will you do today?
Is there something you want to do?
Well…
There is.
Things that I never imagined
we could do together.
I know it's ridiculous,
but I imagined it sometimes.
Us being…
completely ordinary
just like everyone else.
Funny, right?
Even though I wanted to get a divorce
and to escape this house every day.
Since when?
What?
When did you
start imagining that?
I don't know.
Probably…
She is…
my wife.
Did you fall for me then?
Fall for you? Me?
It's just that I'd never thought
you'd do something like that.
For me,
it was way before that.
Way before.
When?
Well…
CHIEF KANG YOUNG-WOO
- Yes?
- Mr. Paik?
- Sorry for disturbing you on your day off.
- What is it?
I'm really sorry, but I think
you need to come here right away.
A car's coming!
He's here!
- Wait.
- Move out of the way.
Wait a moment.
Move. Just a moment.
- Please move.
- Move.
Move out of the way.
Why was Paik Sa-eon being threatened?
Who do you think is
the mastermind behind them?
Paik Sa-eon's statement
was completely different from your claims.
Could you comment on that?
Why do you think that is?
The spokesperson
drew a clear line to avoid causing
any trouble to his father's future.
He didn't want
to make a fuss over a political issue.
Then, do you still think
those trying to harm you
are the ones who attacked
the spokesperson?
Wait. What's that?
Move out of the way.
- What are you doing?
- Move.
Stop. Don't go inside.
- Hey.
- You can't go inside.
PAIK JANG-HO'S GRANDSON,
PAIK UI-YONG'S SON
I KNOW WHAT PAIK SA-EON DID
Share a few words!
YOU GOT THIS!
WE'RE IN THIS TOGETHER!
THIS TOO SHALL PASS!
After thinking about how to offer
our support and comfort,
we prepared this.
Do you like it?
Mr. Kang.
Yes?
Did you ask me
to hurry to the office for this?
When I took my first day off
in three years?
Yes.
You took your first day off
in three years.
We imagined how you felt,
how difficult it must've been.
Since we prepared this anyway,
should we take a commemorative photo?
By the way, where's Mr. Park?
Sir!
You've found his location?
Yes, the reverse tracking is complete.
Hajeong, Gyeonggi-do?
Does the location ring a bell?
Are you going right now?
- Then I'll come with--
- I'll go alone.
Don't tell the police.
Sir.
Be careful.
Great work.
CHILDREN'S WELFARE CENTER
Enjoy!
- Okay!
We're still eating what you bought before.
I appreciate it.
That reminds me.
Did you find out anything more
about what you asked me last time?
That? No.
I've been asking his peers
to try to find the twin brother,
but no one knows anything.
By the way, what about the newscaster
who came with you before?
She didn't come today.
Oh, her.
She's probably working.
She's not your girlfriend?
Not at all. She's just a colleague.
Then again…
I remember your first love.
She was nothing like her, right?
My first love?
Her name was…
Hong Hee-joo, right?
Yeah, well…
You've got a great memory.
Of course.
She came to our center regularly
to volunteer for years.
She even taught the kids to sign.
I haven't seen her in so long.
I wonder how she's doing.
The chairman said
to bring you home for now,
but no, you need to hold out.
The moment you leave this house,
you can't come back.
Also,
I know who the culprit is.
Who else would threaten Sa-eon
and talk about your marriage?
Hong In-a. Who else?
That brat…
I could tell she was trying
to break you two apart.
She must regret her choice now.
What great timing, right?
The election's soon, things are
going well, and she's trying to ruin it.
Hey.
Did you know she was back?
What did she say? Does she want
everything back? You told her no, right?
Don't see her again.
Don't listen to anything she says, got it?
Sis, remember what I said before?
You don't know anything about Paik Sa-eon.
You can't even eat what's handfed to you.
- Don't you want to know?
- How could you only
- take after your father?
- Are you curious?
Get it together,
or you'll end up like your father.
Hey, I'm leaving.
What is this?
HBC JANG HYEOK-JIN
- Hello?
- This was just posted.
Take a look at what I sent.
I KNOW WHAT PAIK SA-EON DID
Do you think the culprit sent this?
What's wrong with him?
What grudge does he have against you?
- I'm on my way to find out.
- What?
Where?
Nothing!
CALLS
PAIK SA-EON
Hee-joo, how are you doing?
HEE-JOO, HOW ARE YOU DOING?
ARE YOU OKAY?
I CAN'T REACH YOU, SO I'M WORRIED.
It's been a while, Sang-woo.
Hee-joo, have you been well?
Sang-woo, can you meet me right now?
Right now?
WILL PAIK SA-EON BLACKMAIL CASE AFFECT
PAIK UI-YONG'S ELECTION?
How are you going to handle this?
There's a limit to what I can stop.
The person to handle this
isn't me or the spokesperson,
it's you.
- Take responsibility and fix it.
- What?
What kind of absurd nonsense is this?
Didn't all of this happen
because of your daughters?
If it'd gone as originally agreed,
this wouldn't be happening!
Why give them the chance to find fault?
It's all in the past,
but since you brought it up,
let me ask you something.
Your family's Achilles' heel,
are you sure it was taken care of
by Chairman Paik?
No?
Is there something left
that hasn't been cleared away?
Of course not.
If, and I mean if,
that thing shows up now
and holds you or me back,
this time,
I'll chop it
into tiny pieces
from head to tail myself
and neatly scatter them in your yard.
So, either look forward to it
or prepare for it.
I advise you to do something,
Candidate Paik.
I advise you to repay me first.
Shouldn't you at least pretend
to repay the debt you owe me
from three years ago?
I'm talking about your eldest daughter.
I'm glad nothing happened.
So many incidents happened
after you started working there.
I felt a little troubled.
Thanks for your concern.
But what's going on?
What brings you here?
The case you're investigating
on the program you're appearing on,
didn't you say it was about a case
of missing orphans?
Yeah, that's right.
Can you tell me more about it?
Help yourself!
Eat it before it cools.
You don't like it? Those were good too.
The meat was bursting out.
It wasn't just like a sausage or ham.
Yeah. That's right.
What's it like?
What Korean food does it resemble?
Nothing!
If this is how it's going to be,
don't call it a seminar.
YOU DID IT
YOU'RE THE KILLER
PAIK SA-EON
The meat was bursting out.
It wasn't just like a sausage or ham.
Yeah. That's right.
What's it like?
What Korean food does it resemble?
Nothing!
MISSING ORPHAN CASE
CONTACT US IF YOU KNOW ANYTHING
This house is where the orphanage kids
went in and never came out.
Why is the door open?
Does someone live here now?
No.
I don't think so.
Did you go in?
Yeah. Last time I came here.
Hee-joo, why do you ask about the case?
Do you know something about it?
You're asking about it.
And the spokesperson asked before.
You're both very interested.
We're coming back from covering a site.
You know that we're doing a show together.
You-ri told me you asked her about me.
What's the story about?
It's too late tonight.
So let's come back during the day.
PAIK SA-EON
Is there someone that calls you?
Take it.
You can take it.
How could I?
I guess there's someone
who knows besides me.
Know what?
That you can speak.
What's that?
HONG HEE-JOO
What are they doing?
Is he crazy?
Don't get out.
- Open it.
- Don't.
We don't know why he's acting like this.
Hee-joo.
Hee-joo!
What are you doing?
Let go.
I'm warning you,
don't ever come near Hong Hee-joo again.
Who are you to say that?
What exactly is your relationship
with Hee-joo?
You answer me first.
How much do you know
about the Sinil Childcare Center incident?
Have you found the culprit?
Why do you ask--
There'd be an investigation if they had!
Do you already know who the culprit is?
So, you're seeking revenge?
"Revenge"?
I don't know if I'm having
reasonable doubts about you
or if it's just a misunderstanding,
but stop here.
Stop…
digging into this case.
Why do you care so much about it?
What does it have to do with you?
What bothers me isn't the case, it's you.
From the moment you appeared,
the threats, kidnapping,
and explosions started.
Is that really a coincidence?
What?
Why did you come here?
Because of this.
It was sent to me.
…a sausage or ham.
Yeah. That's right.
- What Korean food does it resemble?
- Nothing!
UNKNOWN CALLER
YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT PAIK SA-EON.
So did you go
to ask Ji Sang-woo?
I asked about the case.
Why didn't you ask me?
Were you scared to ask?
Answer me, Hong Hee-joo.
You're right.
I was scared.
Why?
Are you scared and anxious
that you might find…
something shocking about me?
Is that it?
I've been scared,
anxious,
and wanted to run away many times.
I was afraid you'd find out
that I was 406,
that you wouldn't forgive me,
or that you'd never want to see me again.
I wanted to run away
before you found out about everything.
So I am scared and anxious.
That you might run away
if I find out your secret,
just like I wanted to.
So I couldn't ask you.
Because…
I know what that's like.
That's not the only thing I'm scared of.
Today, I…
I've felt anxious ever since I woke up.
I was scared last night
was just a dream.
The kind of dream
that makes me break down in tears
when I wake up,
feeling empty and sad.
This kind of happiness
would never happen to me.
No one would love me this easily.
That's never happened to me before,
so how could I?
How can I make you believe it?
What can I do
to ease your mind?
Don't hide anything from me.
Show me everything.
I can handle anything.
Don't be so sure of that.
Why not?
You knew I was 406,
yet you didn't abandon me.
Let us
show each other our worst
and make it even.
Hong Hee-joo.
If…
something happens to me
and the Paik Sa-eon you've known
disappears from this world,
even if I throw away the title
of Paik Jang-ho's grandson,
Paik Ui-yong's son, and the spokesperson,
just remember this.
The only Paik Sa-eon I want to leave
behind in this world is the one…
that belongs to Hong Hee-joo.
In-a, why did you come back
without me knowing?
When I said I couldn't marry him,
I thought you'd force me to.
But you let me go easily,
so I was grateful
yet a bit surprised.
Was it all part of your plan?
Were you the one who sent me those papers?
PAIK UI-YONG AND PAIK SA-EON
DNA NOT MATCHED
When I think about it,
you didn't look so surprised.
As if you already knew.
No.
There was no reason for you
to send it anonymously.
You could've just told me.
Stop talking nonsense.
What was the reason?
Why did you make me
run away from that marriage?
What's the contract you signed
with Chairman Paik?
What did you just say?
Your second daughter?
Sir.
Hundreds of wedding invitations
went out under In-a's name.
Everyone knows that Paik Ui-yong's son
is engaged to Chungwoon family's eldest.
Now you want to send your second daughter
down the aisle?
This is a soap opera.
Have you lost your mind
since your daughter ran off?
Also, why should we take
your second daughter?
Do you think she's on the same level
as Sa-eon?
There's nothing more to discuss.
- Let's prepare a statement.
- No one will know.
Let's just fill the empty slot.
You've done it before, so you know.
It's easier than you think.
Our two families…
have a long-standing agreement.
Chairman Paik kneeled before me
and made this promise.
He promised to grant me
anything I wanted,
whenever and whatever it may be.
IF THE CONFIDENTIALITY CLAUSE IS UPHELD,
PARTY B MUST ACCOMMODATE ANY REQUEST
MADE BY PARTY A, WHENEVER, WHEREVER.
PAIK JANG-HO
HONG IL-GYEONG
I heard it from her.
Who is all ears and loose-tongued.
But I'm sure you wouldn't just tell me,
so I thought about it.
The car accident when I was young.
After that,
you were mad for a while.
You had the police and prosecutors
investigate and dig everything up.
As if you'd make a culprit
if there wasn't one.
But…
why did you stop?
No.
Who made you stop?
Don't bring up the rotten past.
Do you want to know
what you should be focusing on now?
Did you hear
that Paik Sa-eon is being threatened?
The culprit
knows everything about Hee-joo.
Hee-joo?
That means…
they know
what happened to you,
Sa-eon, and Hee-joo.
How are you so sweet?
What's your secret to maintaining
such a happy marriage?
Well, there's nothing special.
We just fill each other with what we lack
and share what we have in excess.
While doing that, we've become like one.
I can't live without her now.
In such a harmonious home,
I hear there have been some troubling
and worrying issues lately.
It's about your son,
Spokesperson Paik Sa-eon.
Yes, about that…
"The threats and acts of terror were
crimes of vengeance."
"The victim provided the reason
for the threats."
I hear there are various rumors.
Yes.
However, some insist
that that isn't the case
and urge caution
against reckless speculation.
I apologize for causing concern
to our supporters and the public
who have trusted and watched over us.
We promise to resolve this matter swiftly.
However,
to my son Sa-eon,
who must be suffering more than anyone,
as his mother,
I want to say something.
Goodness. That would be great.
Now, look at the camera
and say what you have to say, please.
Okay.
Sa-eon.
Do you remember?
Remember…
what I always said to you?
I'm…
not locking you up.
I'm protecting you.
I will…
still protect you.
I'll protect you,
Sa-eon.
I'm sorry for the worry I've caused.
I'll work really hard.
Don't be sorry.
You did great.
But I think you lost weight.
How are you feeling?
I'm okay.
Now.
To welcome you back to work,
we've prepared a gift for you.
A gift?
You'll be the interpreter
for the spokesperson's speech
at this year's
Environmental Climate Day event.
See. I told you she'd be happy.
You're right.
I was worried it might be too much
since you just got back,
but your face says otherwise.
Let us know if it's too much for you.
It's not at all!
Just leave it to me,
and I'll do my best to prepare!
Through this visit to France,
our government aims
to strengthen the trust and friendship
between the two nations
and establish a stepping stone
into a cooperative partnership.
Furthermore, we expect this visit
to contribute to the expansion
and diversification
of our diplomatic outreach.
That is all.
All right.
We will take questions from now on.
- Spokesperson.
- Over here.
I have a question.
- There's so much enthusiasm.
However, we'll only take questions
related to today's issues.
How about a back briefing?
- A back briefing?
- I'll take questions on any topic.
- Sir?
- I have a question!
- Over here!
- Spokesperson, I have a question.
- Sir!
- Here!
Please.
What did the blackmailer demand?
And why didn't you report it
after the first threat?
Well…
Another question.
"I know what you did, Paik Sa-eon."
What do you think this means?
Yes, any more?
Go ahead.
You firmly said
it was not political terrorism.
How are you so sure?
Surprisingly, it seems
you're all being careful around me.
You can ask bolder questions.
Let's be honest,
you're all curious about one thing.
You've all dug into me
and never found any dirt.
So, what could be
Paik Sa-eon's deadly weakness?
A woman?
Gambling?
Drugs?
He's out of his mind.
- Sir…
- I'm going to show you something,
and I want you all to make use
of your information
and investigative skills
to solve this quiz.
The meat was bursting out.
It wasn't just like a sausage or ham.
Yeah. That's right.
What's it like?
- What Korean food does it resemble?
- Nothing!
The video I just showed you is
what I received from the blackmailer
just yesterday.
But you can't tell what it's about,
can you?
What does he want?
What's he threatening me with?
It's the same for me.
So I need your help.
So,
what if we figure it out?
The one who figures it out
will get an exclusive interview.
Stop it.
Why are you treating us
and even grilling the meat?
It's all done. Please, eat.
- Let's eat!
- Thank you.
It's so good.
Right? Eat your fill.
Why aren't you eating?
No, I am.
What is it?
Are you crying?
I'm not crying.
The smoke got in my eye.
There's no smoke here.
I mean…
It feels like just yesterday
you were practicing sign language
with those tiny, delicate hands,
fumbling this way and that.
When did you grow up like this?
Now you're the interpreter
for the presidential office
and are treating us to galbi.
I'm so touched.
I need to pull it together.
What's this?
Why is it so good?
You said your department
are regulars here.
I can see why.
I wanted to come here with you.
Thanks.
You're the only one who thinks of me.
By the way, Hee-joo,
you've gotten so much prettier.
I thought the same.
- Me too.
- Right?
You look more radiant.
There's definitely something different.
Wait.
Did you get work done?
Laser? Fillers?
Come on.
No.
I'm just kidding.
Hey.
You got hired by the presidential office,
and you get to work right next
to the respected spokesperson.
Of course, you look good.
But…
the atmosphere at the presidential office
has been chaotic lately.
Is the spokesperson okay?
Right.
Are the threats for real?
There was the accident
at the company retreat too.
How would Hee-joo know?
Look here.
Just eat some galbi.
What is this? It's so good!
This is perilla pesto.
A quiz?
I mean, why has our spokesperson
become so high-maintenance lately?
Why does he keep causing trouble
without consulting us?
See?
There it is.
It must be an answer to the quiz!
Spokesperson's office.
Is this…
the presidential spokesperson's office?
Yes, it is. How can I help you?
I have
something I need to tell
Spokesperson Paik Sa-eon.
FISHING SUPPLIES
Second floor.
Getting off.
Hello.
Did you have…
lunch?
Interpreter.
Hong.
Hee.
Joo.
I did. What about you?
So did I.
Your sign language has improved.
I've been practicing hard.
Am I
good?
Yes, it's rewarding to have taught you.
I'll see you later.
Okay, see you at home.
I won't be late.
Sir?
A call came in a moment ago.
This…
Come in.
I have something to pass along.
HE'S ALIVE
Is this all?
He hung up after saying this.
So I immediately looked up
the caller's number,
and a business came up.
A business?
JUAN FISHING
Hey. Pictures from the retreat
have been posted.
Really? I want to see.
Did they turn out well?
- Let's see.
- Wow.
Everyone looks great.
Mr. Jeong, you came out great.
Wait for me.
He's alive.
He's alive?
Could it be him?
Help!
Please help!
Help…
I told you not to come out.
Go inside.
PAIK SA-EON
Will you be late?
This feels so strange.
This house was supposed to be
my newlywed house.
I have something to ask you.
Go ahead.
Why did you come back?
If you're trying to reclaim what's yours…
Shouldn't you ask first
why I left in the first place?
JUAN FISHING
Father told me
that Sa-eon's blackmailer knows everything
about you and this marriage.
Then you should also know
why I refused this marriage.
The reason…
you had to marry him in my place.
Wake up!
There's more to Paik Sa-eon
than you think.
Did you know already?
It doesn't matter?
Hong Hee-joo.
If…
something happens to me
and the Paik Sa-eon you've known
disappears from this world,
even if I throw away the title
of Paik Jang-ho's grandson,
Paik Ui-yong's son, and the spokesperson,
just remember this.
The only Paik Sa-eon I want to leave
behind in this world is the one…
that belongs to Hong Hee-joo.
WHEN THE PHONE RINGS
Did they turn out well?
Yes.
WHEN THE PHONE RINGS
What is this?
What in the world happened?
There's one thing I'm sure of.
He wasn't hiding you
but protecting you.
I've been curious about this.
Who does Spokesperson Paik take after?
I wonder what his real name is.
Even if I'm not
the Paik Sa-eon you knew,
does it not matter?
It didn't matter to you either.
It's my turn now.
It's my turn to protect you.
Subtitle translation by: Sue Mounce