( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
From now on,
can I do as I please?
Well, I…
What are you two doing over there?
Come in, Kyeong-nam!
Let's go inside.
How could you not remember what you drew?
Episode 17, Si-woo and Na-ra's first kiss.
Ms. Jang comes over and slaps her.
Don't you remember?
Why do you have my work memorized?
That's creepy.
I hate it so much that I can't look away.
You're dissing my work, aren't you?
You can't even draw.
Being an author
is not only about drawing well.
It's about diligence and originality.
Just memorize that.
Hey, anyone can talk about diligence,
but not you.
I heard that Park and Seo here
are working overtime every Friday.
Aren't I the only author on Fridays?
I always send in my work early.
Yeah…
The thing is…
He must be working late all the time
because your files are a mess.
No, they're not.
I do have rather high standards, so…
-Huh?
-That's why.
I bet you want to work with someone
who can actually draw, right?
But I think he draws well.
What? Who draws well?
That piece. Wasn't it done by you?
What? Was that how you originally drew?
That's not my work.
Right? I knew it was so good.
Who's the artist?
-This guy.
-Huh?
He gave it to me
when I moved into this studio.
Whoa, how are you so good?
You guys didn't know?
Kyeong-nam was my art instructor
when I was preparing for college.
Really?
Well, it was just a part-time gig
when I was in college.
You should do this for a living.
Such a waste of talent.
Right?
See? Others see things the way I do.
Stop.
Plenty of people can draw like me.
Come on. That's not true.
Just worry about yourself.
I'll handle it myself.
This is the next episode.
If I do this,
don't you think it would be good?
-It's nice.
-Right?
Hwany, can I use your charger?
There's one next to the sofa. Yes.
Is he asleep?
From now on, can I do as I please?
What did he even mean by that?
Are you doing okay?
What? What do you mean?
That.
"That"?
This.
It's gotten a lot better.
I'm screwed.
EPISODE 8
THE ODD OR EVEN GAME
Are you doing okay?
Damn it!
I miss you.
From now on,
can I do as I please?
Let's go!
Hello?
Hey, where are you?
I'm near your place right now.
What are you doing here?
I was feeling down, so I went for a run.
In this weather?
Can I come over?
I even bought some bungeo-ppang.
You should have told me sooner!
I'm at the department store.
Huh?
You're shopping again?
No, my vacuum cleaner broke down,
so I have to buy a new one.
Hey, that's still shopping.
Is it?
A lot of newlyweds frequent our store,
so the package discounts…
Holy!
…explained in detail.
-Physical stores are our strength.
-Hello?
-What is it?
-God, that scared me.
It's the guy from my blind date.
He works here. I remember now.
What do I do?
I really need to buy a vacuum cleaner.
Hey, that's great. Ask him for a discount.
Are you insane?
I ghosted him after that day.
Whatever! I'll call you back.
So be prepared for that,
and the high-discount items…
I'm running out of places to go
because of all the dates.
Talk about karma.
This is a place where any romance
you desire becomes reality.
There are 900 themes just for you.
So, who will you be dating today?
Hello.
-Doors opening.
-Hi.
Doors closing.
So I can get on with you.
Hi.
Hey, what's up?
Come on, focus.
What is it?
Did you come here looking for me?
I came here for this.
I see. Right!
You can take it.
Okay.
Drink this while you work.
You got that for me?
Yes. I had to come anyway, so…
Come to think of it,
they are gone already.
What do you mean?
Your bangs.
Looked good on you.
Bye now.
Okay.
Stop being conscious of him.
Don't show that you're losing composure!
Get a grip!
Ms. Seo.
Here. This is yours.
This is…
I picked it up here in the lobby.
I thought I had lost it. Thank you.
That was
my gift, by the way.
I'm the one who put it in there
for the gift draw.
You are the one who bought this? This?
Yes. I bought this one for no reason
and put it in the box.
-I didn't know that.
-Naturally. It was an anonymous draw.
Anyway, thank you.
Sure. See you tomorrow.
Ms. Seo?
Will you be putting it on again?
Do whatever you'd like.
This is driving me crazy.
Good night.
What was that?
PRODUCER PARK
GOOD NIGHT
Wait, did he just send me
a private message?
This is crazy.
Good night.
This really is crazy.
Huh?
Why do I look so tired?
None of this is working.
Come to think of it,
they are gone already.
Your bangs.
Looked good on you.
Gotcha.
What?
You have makeup on,
so why are you wearing a cap?
What?
I don't know. I just put it on.
You worked all night?
So you can reclaim the top spot for TMTK?
Don't push yourself too hard.
Ms. Seo, you look really exhausted.
Yeah.
I do?
-Let's eat something nice today, okay?
-Love it.
The platform and genre
will remain the same.
Even for them, making a game
out of a series that's just started…
I guess Kyeong-nam really is taking off.
As if dethroning TMTK wasn't enough,
they're planning a game based on PlanC.
A game? What kind of game?
It seems he's in serious talks
with DU right now.
What is it with everything
Park Kyeong-nam touches?
At this rate, he's going to turn Hwany
into the undisputed champion.
Look at Mr. Hwang
grinning from ear to ear.
You know, Kyeong-nam scares me
more than anyone else.
Such a solid guy, isn't he?
Hey.
Hello?
Hello!
Oh, yes?
You are not listening to me.
Why are you zoning out like that?
Sorry. What did you say?
I got a hand X-ray taken.
The inflammation's so bad
that I have to eat with my left hand.
But I can't use chopsticks with it, can I?
Right.
So stop ordering noodles for lunch.
Okay. Understood.
As if dethroning TMTK wasn't enough,
they're planning a game based on PlanC.
At this rate, he's going to turn Hwany
into the undisputed champion.
Ms. Yun!
Don't you realize
how bad things are right now?
We really need our heads in the game.
The gap between PlanC and us
keeps widening.
It's great that you're dating,
but are you just going to give up on TMTK?
Why are you being so serious
all of a sudden?
All I did was text my boyfriend.
How would men
make any meaningful contribution
to our lives?
-Huh?
-Think about it!
Is it okay to let our relationships
affect our livelihoods?
No, Ms. Yun. It's not okay.
Where is this coming from?
-Can't you just let me handle it myself?
-Absolutely not.
You take the subway, right?
I was thinking of taking the subway too.
We can go together.
By the way,
did you wear a cap
so you wouldn't look pretty for me?
What?
Oh, this? Nope, not at all.
I thought maybe.
Oh, I just remembered.
I have to take the bus today.
Huh? You're taking the bus now?
Yes. Have a safe trip home.
Wait!
But that bus is…
Fasten your seatbelts.
We're approaching the highway.
The highway?
Wait, excuse me.
Where is this bus headed right now?
Incheon.
Incheon?
You should sit back down. It's dangerous!
He could have told me.
The one who set us up told me
that this will be your last blind date,
regardless of how it turns out.
That's right.
May I ask why?
I've just grown really tired.
I feel the same way.
It's really hard to find someone you like.
I agree.
Do you have a type?
I like
men who are full of contradictions.
-Full of contradictions?
-Yes.
Someone who's neat but sexy,
gentle but bad,
and smart but sloppy.
He should have a steady job
but be a free spirit,
love books
without looking like a bookworm,
have hard muscles but a soft heart,
and finally,
be the kind of man
who says he'd never fall for me
but loves me more than anyone else.
-I see.
-Should I keep going?
Excuse me. I need to take this call.
Huh?
The first song goes to
the lady who asks for too much
but is beautiful enough to be forgiven.
Is it over between you and that man?
Well, yes, I suppose…
I want you to forget about him.
A story just for two of us
The moon is shining on us
My destiny, I'll hold you tight
You're the one
I sing this song for you
I love you, I love you
Now I confess my whole heart
To you
Congratulations, Ms. Lee Ji-yeon,
on meeting your first date!
Awesome.
The tree sure is bare this year,
with how busy Director Hwang is.
I know. He used to gather us up
and decorate it, like it was a tradition.
It's kind of sad.
What do you mean?
You know, a Christmas tree
is supposed to be all shiny and stuff.
So the holidays have a way of making
even Seo Mi-rae sentimental.
What are you all doing tomorrow?
I'll probably watch dramas at home.
I'm going on a staycation with friends.
What about you?
-I'm going to church with my mom.
-I have it better.
How about we go for a drink after work?
Oh, the bars might be packed
since it's Christmas Eve.
-I can't go.
-Why not?
Christmas Eve or not,
today's just a TMTK update day for me.
Oh well, let's go without her.
Kyeong-nam.
Are you also working late today?
Yes.
You poor things.
Tell Hwany to take it easy.
He should pace himself while he's young.
So, what about that place
we went to last time?
Aren't I the only author on Fridays?
I always send in my work early.
The thing is…
Mr. Park.
I guess Hwany is also late
with his submission today.
No.
Sorry?
He already sent it.
Then why are you still…
Because I want to be here.
Oh, I see. All right!
YUN SONG
UPLOAD COMPLETE
What?
What's going on?
Is it a blackout?
You said it made you sad, so…
It's kind of sad.
What do you mean?
You know, a Christmas tree
is supposed to be all shiny and stuff.
Ms. Seo.
Are you taking the bus again?
No.
Thank you.
I felt the Christmas spirit thanks to you.
It was nice.
I enjoyed it.
I heard about the PlanC game coming out.
Congratulations.
It hasn't even been confirmed yet.
How are you so good at everything you do?
I get the impression that
you wouldn't have much to worry about.
You do everything so easily.
Did I come across that way?
I'm not like that.
LEE KYU-TAE SOLO EXHIBITION
Do you know this artist?
I buy their illustrated calendars
every year.
Come to think of it, I get similar vibes
from their pieces as yours.
I used to like this artist too.
I see.
The exhibition is going to end soon.
It seems so.
Wanna go with me?
Did that come off too casually?
Take your time and let me know.
Aren't you hungry?
It seemed like you were skipping dinner.
By the way, why did you stop drawing?
You seemed to have a lot of talent.
I didn't feel it anymore.
Huh?
Drawing used to mean everything to me,
but suddenly it just felt different.
I felt bad about changing,
but at the same time, I was excited
to find something else I liked as much.
That's why I quit.
So did you find something
you liked as much?
Turns out it wasn't easy
to like something that much,
that consistently.
-See you, then.
-Bye.
Oh, wait.
Read it later.
Okay.
Bye.
Let's eat together next time.
Just the two of us.
I wanted to tell you that I like you.
Did you get home okay?
YES
GU YEONG-IL
How much longer should I wait?
I WANTED TO TELL YOU THAT I LIKE YOU
How did I end up like this?
You're here.
-Hey--
-I got a bite.
It seems they are only biting
whenever I try to say something.
Seems so.
How odd.
What's wrong?
I confessed my feelings to you,
and now you're talking to me seriously
with a serious look.
I'm scared.
That I might say no?
Are you going to?
I can't catch a thing today.
Let's go.
Want me to draw you?
Just act natural.
Okay.
Ms. Seo.
I like you.
From now on…
can I do as I please?
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
What?
Well,
I won't be coming back here anymore.
Why is that?
You wouldn't understand
even if I told you,
but the more I meet you,
the more I keep falling for someone.
And that feels
as though that person is having it easy.
Do you mean that,
even when you're with me,
another man keeps coming to mind?
Do you like him?
I don't know.
How do you not know your own feelings?
It's frustrating for me too.
How about you?
Do you know what it is to like someone?
You don't know what it's like
to truly like someone.
I know.
It's knowing you won't change,
even if the person you're with does.
I never changed.
Mi-rae.
We all change.
You've also changed.
What you said about your drawings…
Why are you so obsessed
with what changes and what doesn't?
Is it such a big deal?
Why are you so obsessed with it?
Could there be any other reason?
That's the way I am. I can't help it.
The way you are?
There is a reason for everything.
Because it was me
who made you.
Ms. Seo Mi-rae.
I'm sure you know what I want…
Even if you don't like me anymore…
…and what I fear…
…I won't ever change.
…as well as I do.
Because that's my way of liking someone.
No. Perhaps even better than I do.
Did he tell you
that he won't change?
I didn't feel it anymore.
Turns out it wasn't easy
to like something that much,
that consistently.
When his feelings for you change,
are you certain you won't get hurt?
As for me…
I won't ever hurt you.
So,
don't go.
Ms. Seo.
-It's the final evaluations already.
-So it is.
Fantasy was super competitive this year.
How about you guys?
Ours was intense as well.
Kyeong-nam and Mi-rae would keep going
back and forth about who was right.
All right.
Mr. Hwang can't make it today,
so let's get started.
-Okay.
-Sure.
This one's well-balanced,
but isn't it a bit too old-fashioned?
A bit lacking in that regard,
but at least it's a safe choice.
It's not bad, but it's not great.
It's smooth, but it lacks an edge.
Put it on hold for now?
Okay.
Who needs to use the restroom?
-I do.
-Me too.
I think every piece needs to pack a punch.
The references…
Oh, I left my phone behind.
Make me a coffee.
Go ahead. I'm not going to use it.
Ms. Seo.
Are you sick?
No.
You just don't look too good.
Anyway, so…
What you said about doing as you please,
I get what you meant by that now.
But whatever it is,
I'd appreciate it
if you could stop doing it at work.
At work?
I didn't phrase that correctly.
Just stop doing it altogether,
wherever it may be.
Please.
Huh? I said I wanted some coffee.
You want one, yeah?
-Move on to the next piece?
-Okay.
A-606. Crimson-Eyed Elena.
What do we have here?
I love the style. Who picked this one?
Actually, we had mixed opinions
about this piece.
So…
I'm the one who approved of it.
Kyeong-nam and Mi-rae
never saw eye to eye on this one.
I think this piece is fully qualified.
And Mi-rae? Are you still against it?
Yes.
I don't like it.
It is a little rough around the edges.
-What don't you like exactly?
-Huh?
I think I've already told you
several times.
This is a contest for rookies.
Director Hwang told us to focus
on the potential, and I saw the potential.
Well, I didn't see it.
You almost changed your mind at one point.
From start to finish, did you really
hate all of it?
Yes.
And I don't think…
that will ever change.
Yes! Now that's what I call a meeting!
Why don't we call it for today
and finish talking about it tomorrow?
-Sounds good.
-Good work, everyone.
We worked too hard today, huh?
-Good work.
-I'm tired.
Let's go.
Good work, everyone.
I just remembered
why I was so adamant
about not dating anyone.
But
seeing how scared I am
of Kyeong-nam changing…
I guess he really was the person
I truly liked.
I used to think that you were the reason
Kyeong-nam made my heart race,
but I think I must have…
actually liked him.
That's why I held onto you.
I didn't wanna see you suffer.
It's bound to end someday,
and you will have to deal with it alone.
Ending up alone again,
you hate it more than anything.
I wanted to forget.
Are you okay?
Goodness, you fool.
MI-RAE, SE-JUNE
Here's the shrimp ball.
-You're not gonna let me have that?
-No way.
-You're the best.
-Thank you, ma'am.
-Here.
-Okay.
Your legs are very tight, ma'am.
Your hair's so damaged, ma'am.
Easy. Do it from a distance.
Right. I'm sorry.
Look.
It's hilarious. Look.
What had always been part of a pair
was suddenly alone.
When it dawned upon me
that he was never coming back,
it hurt so much.
And you're afraid
that it might happen.
The man I created…
keeps weakening my resolve,
over and over again.
You did well.
It's the right thing.
I buy their illustrated calendars
every year.
Wanna go with me?
If it's going to end anyway,
it's better not to start it at all.
Jeong-hyu wrapped up this episode nicely.
When should I pay off the setups?
Hold on. I need to take this call.
Hey, Mom.
I'm sorry, but I guess…
Three cups of coffee, three treats.
What are you getting at here?
Well, since there are three of us--
Again with the three!
Are you putting it out there
that TMTK is in third place?
…I'm not brave enough.
Anyway, you all worked so hard last year.
-Here's to us!
-Great work, everyone!
It's time for me to share some good news.
Oh well, I guess for you guys,
it might come across as somewhat sad news.
Starting this year,
we have decided to really jump into
the American webtoon platform race.
And that's why we are going to send
Korea's finest over there.
Who might that be?
It's me.
I'm leaving. For the States. As the CEO.
Director Hwang! No, CEO Hwang!
-Oh please!
-Congratulations!
Come on, how are we supposed to manage
if you just leave us like that?
Hey now, I still have a few months left.
Don't be like that.
I'm a bit torn up
about having to leave you guys behind.
We should start preparing
a farewell party, right?
Of course.
A grand celebration that befits him.
True.
Hey! That was on me!
-Thanks!
-I told you I was buying.
-You're the best!
-Thank you.
I'm spending it all before I leave!
-Let's join him today.
-Director Hwang!
-Where to?
-Let's go!
-Awesome!
-Where is she going? Hey!
It's so cold.
Seo Mi-rae!
Let's share this one.
Okay.
Thanks.
I'll get out first, then you,
and Kyeong-nam will get out last.
Rest up, guys.
-Thank you, sir.
-Sure. Have a good night.
Weather update.
Snowfall centered over the central region
has continued since this evening.
It is falling at a rate
of about 1 cm per hour in Seoul,
Northern Gyeonggi-do,
and Yeongseo, Gangwon-do.
Around the city…
Sir, you can drop me off here.
Sure thing.
I'll be going now. Happy holidays.
Wait.
Take this. It's snowing a lot.
It's fine.
We're right in front of my place.
Goodbye, then.
Ms. Seo!
Take this.
But I…
I said I was okay.
You won't accept anything from me?
What?
Just use it.
How are you going to get home?
You can't hail a cab right now.
I'll manage.
Hey.
Mr. Park.
Take this back.
I don't want to accept this.
I just don't want you to get snowed on.
Does a small favor really bother you?
Did I ever
ask you to like me?
Don't you think
you're being too inconsiderate?
Do you only care about your own feelings?
I mean, have you considered
how I might feel about things?
This is
hard for me too.
I hate myself for how much I sway
every time you stir my heart.
This is difficult for me too.
But so what if I get swayed?
What are you suggesting?
That we start dating right away?
Why can't we?
Are you being serious?
What are you so afraid of?
We haven't even begun yet.
If there's a beginning…
there will be an end too.
I…
don't think about the end right now.
For now, sure,
but you'll change eventually.
Do you hate change that much?
Is change really that bad?
Ever since…
I fell for you, Seo Mi-rae…
I've changed.
Subtitle translation by: Daham Yoon