(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
Kill everyone but the children.
Don't go there!
Don't go there.
Mother!
Stop!
You wear painted skins?
You're not from the Shilin Sect.
Who are you exactly?
What are you after?
The Frost Spell. The Formless Moon Sect.
Wu Wangyan?
You always wanted to know
what secret I was hiding.
Now you have your answer.
The Star Stone…
Give it back!
Dream on.
The sachet…
Oh no!
Threatening me with him won't work.
I can't undo the petrification.
I can't do it.
Then I'll kill him!
The stone thorn has my runes on it.
If I cast the spell…
you'll die instantly.
Do you choose death,
or do you help me free my people?
Qing Yi!
The Dragon Deity's Power.
You have it,
so why no dragon birthmark?
The Dragon clan…
Birthmark…
Your birthmark is so interesting.
It looks like a heart
made of flowing water.
How did I never see it?
You're not Wu Wangyan.
You're not her!
You're looking for a child
with a dragon birthmark.
Then I know who you are.
That's right.
She's Jiu Ying.
Little Nine.
Or maybe…
I should call you by your true name…
Jiu Ying.
Who sent you here?
Why pretend to be a Shilin Sect member?
It… It's Jiu Ying.
You know of me?
The first time I saw
those nine spots on you,
I suspected it was you.
Those nine markings on your head
are quite pretty.
So I'll call you Little Nine.
Later, you found out
we weren't the real Man Man and Di Zhu.
If you were dead,
those two demons
who possess Man Man and Di Zhu
would never get the Star Stone.
The only one who could stay by us
and eavesdrop on our every word
was Little Nine.
But Little Nine
was just an ordinary, harmless snake.
Relax. The blood didn't turn dark.
So, I had to wait for you to slip up,
to reveal your true form.
I failed twice…
but in the end, I caught you.
Just a bit too late,
since you've grown your third head.
I don't quite understand
what you're saying.
But it sounds like you know me well,
like an old friend.
Indeed.
Very well.
All your scheming,
just to get a look at my true form?
Because in the end,
you'll become the Demon King,
destroying the whole world,
yet no one knows your origin.
So, I wanted to find out
what exactly you are.
In the beginning,
I was just a snake egg
buried in this earth
for millions of years, unable to hatch.
The egg was filled with deadly venom.
The Aodeng people migrated here
and were poisoned one after another.
They thought it was a plague.
Then the Star Stone fell from the sky,
bringing heavenly fire.
The heat of the flames hatched you.
I broke out of my shell,
absorbed the Star Stone's power,
and became a demon.
The egg disappeared.
The Aodeng people
stopped getting poisoned.
They thought it was a blessing
from the Star Stone.
After I hatched,
the first person I saw was Di Zhu.
But I was newly born, my power weak.
I could only take Di Zhu's blood
and briefly possess her.
That way, I could go
into the cave every night
to absorb the Star Stone's power
and grow stronger.
To keep others from getting the Stone,
you started killing.
The Star Stone's power
gave me a second venomous head.
I smeared venom on a hairpin
to kill those who coveted the Stone.
But the venom couldn't kill demons.
So…
I could only frame you.
Too bad you didn't succeed.
True.
But I got something unexpected.
I found a power source
even stronger than the Star Stone.
Killing.
No, not killing. It's fear.
I realized, the more people died,
the more the Aodeng people feared,
the stronger I became.
In just a few days,
I've already grown my third head.
Even without the Star Stone,
as long as the world
is filled with despair,
fear, and hatred,
I'll have an endless supply of power.
Soon enough,
all nine of my heads will be fully grown.
With all nine heads,
Jiu Ying can break each head
into nine spirit fragments.
Eighty-one pieces
scattered across the world.
That's why this land
is overrun with people
controlled by Jiu Ying.
The Six-Eyed Butterflies under Jiu Ying
planted pupae inside us.
We have no choice but to obey.
Wu Zhiqi was already going
to give the Star Stone to Jiu Ying,
to bring it to the battlefield
and destroy humanity.
Why control you
and arrange for us to steal it?
Because… the Star Stone
wasn't meant to destroy humanity.
It was to make humans
and demons destroy each other.
What?
The Yuan Clay Incident,
which sparked the war,
seemed like an accident,
but it was also schemed by Jiu Ying.
You mean Yuan's death
wasn't an accident?
It wasn't just him.
There are countless others
you'd never suspect
possessed by Jiu Ying's spirit.
They walk among us,
constantly stirring conflict
between our races, igniting battles.
And all this strife and hatred
makes Jiu Ying stronger.
She even slaughtered the nine Dragons.
No wonder they say
Jiu Ying can't be killed.
Turns out, even sealed
by the nine dragon sons,
you're still causing chaos.
They thought sealing my nine heads
would destroy me for good.
Too bad
I'd already scattered countless
spirit fragments across the world.
Each piece can attach to a living being.
Once it attaches,
it waits for a moment
when the host's mind wavers,
then takes control.
As long as one piece remains,
Jiu Ying cannot die.
You might as well give up.
No. You're wrong.
The Dragon Deity
will defeat Jiu Ying in the end.
All 81 spirit fragments
will be destroyed one by one.
That annoying Shilin Sect
has been hunting for my spirit fragments.
I have to kill Chi Wen,
break the seal,
and get my heads back.
So you've been searching
for the dragon's descendants.
Because only a dragon…
Can kill a dragon.
The Six-Eyed Butterflies
gave us the glowing worm.
Once it's inside the Star Stone,
it will devour his insides,
make him lose control,
and cause an explosion.
Where's the Star Stone?
What do we do now?
Where are we taking him?
We can't go anywhere.
The Six-Eyed Butterfly…
is actually two people.
That's right.
Unlike you, we're inseparable,
loving brothers.
Watch out!
You've got it wrong. We're not with him.
Threatening us with him won't work.
You should just kill him.
Are you sure?
The look on the person
behind you says otherwise.
If you don't want him dead, come with us.
Don't forget he imprisoned you
for all those years.
You said earlier he secretly helped us
by letting me go.
All these years,
in that tiny space, he was my only friend.
If you no longer care
about the Star Stone,
then why did you attack me at the wedding?
- Kiss!
Come out, Little Nine!
I simply wanted you dead.
Tian Di!
Let Wu Zhiqi go! Stop!
You're covered in wounds,
yet you can't bear to hurt her.
How devoted.
Let's see how long you can last.
Don't be rash!
Oh no. He's losing control of his power!
Tian Di… No!
Yuan Xizai!
So this is the Star Stone
exit Master Bai Ze mentioned?
This stone tablet?
It's Wu Shiguang's master's grave.
Stop bickering. Quick, smear the blood.
Okay. Got it.
Wu Shiguang would be surprised
that the keepsake of our friendship I kept
would save his life years later.
Why isn't it working?
That liar Bai Ze!
Are they really going to die
in the disasters?
Master… What's happening?
Father!
Mother!
Shiguang!
Quick, take him and go!
I won't! I have to save my parents!
Father!
What are you waiting for? Go after them!
Lu Wuyi!
- Oh no.
- What's happening to Wu Zhiqi?
The third head, the head of frenzy.
It drives a person mad,
making their demon power run wild.
If Wu Zhiqi loses control,
it'll cause the Hurricane Catastrophe.
I've figured out Jiu Ying's origin.
Let's go. We'll use
the Star Stone to leave.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Where's the Star Stone?
You go first.
You can turn into sand and leave.
Let's go together!
Once we get the Star Stone,
we can use our power
to leave the illusion.
You…
He…
He's Yuan Wuhuo, the butterfly demon.
He went in too?
When the Star Stone's pull
was strongest earlier,
I almost got sucked in.
The butterfly demon hiding
in the shadows pushed me away.
But he got pulled in himself.
So, in the past they're living in,
who is the true owner of that time?
That past was shared by the two brothers.
They are both the owners
and witnesses to each other.
You're not that Yuan Wuhuo.
You're the butterfly demon, Yuan Wuhuo.
That's right.
So you've been acting this whole time.
How else could I make you
lower your guard,
help me get the Star Stone,
and leave this place?
So you were behind it before too.
Exactly.
I tried to kill Tian Di
to turn him back into the Star Stone.
But it didn't work.
All that struggling was pointless.
Did you really think
I was your brother?
Aren't you?
No.
Then why do you look exactly like me?
You're wrong.
Know your place.
You look like me.
I…
Who am I?
You'll never know.
Stay here forever.
Yuan Xizai!
Why did I lose my power?
Quick, heal him!
Hurry!
Xizai! Xizai!
Save him! Save him!
I can't hold it together much longer.
The Star Stone must not shatter.
I still need it to save my people.
Is there any way?
Yes.
What is it?
The Dragon Deity's Power.
It can restore anything
and bring the dead back to life.
Dragon hearts as one,
all to source return,
all barriers break!
Dragon hearts as one,
all to source return,
all barriers break!
Master Jiu Ying truly has
flawless foresight.
I infused my demonic energy
into a fragment of the Star Stone.
Once it joins with the piece Wu Zhiqi has,
the entire Star Stone
will shatter completely.
Wu Zhiqi will surely sacrifice himself,
releasing
the Dragon Deity's Power to fix it.
Then you'll have your chance
to seize his power.
Give up.
Take after Xiaowei,
and you'll share her fate.
Bai Ze, you already gave 70% of your power
to that false Dragon Deity.
And you used another 20%
to fix the Star Stone.
With the 10% left,
you want to break my barrier?
What a joke.
Or maybe…
you could try using
the Dragon Deity's Power.
Now we're really trapped here.
It's all my fault.
It's all my fault. I'm sorry.
At least we know Jiu Ying's origin,
that's something.
And we found out something else,
even better.
What's it?
Jiu Ying's weakness.
What's his weakness?
The same weakness as mine.
Look out!
Ji Ling! Ji Ling!
Ji Ling! Hold on to me! Don't let go!
Lu Wuyi!
What are you doing?
A spike will help…
When disaster strikes,
lovers stay together.
"Live together, die together"?
That's just a story to fool girls.
I don't like him enough to die for him.
The Star Stone!
Let go!
No!
Let go of the other hand!
Take out the spike! Trust me!
Let's take a gamble.
If we lose, we just stay here.
And I'll marry you!
You're here.