Hey, you.
Hm?
So, about you dating Hia Sorn…
Does the whole office really know?
Yeah, they all know. Hia Sorn went and told Korn,
even though I told him again and again not to.
That's good, though. You've been with him so long better to make
it official so people stop bothering both of you and besides.
I don't know how anyone couldn't see it.
You and Hia Sorn are glued together.
No way that's just “brothers.”
Ugh…
But at the office…
Hia Sorn and I…
We barely even talk.
Mostly just argue.
You guys have been together
a while. Has it been a year yet?
Since he asked me out?
Next week will be a year.
Whoa.
That's pretty fast.
You're his boyfriend, and
you even moved in with him.
Hia Sorn should be
proposing to you already, right?
What the hell are you even saying?
Alking nonsense.
I'm just saying what I see.
Marriage is important, you know.
The law's passed too.
If he's serious about
you, he'll have to propose.
Honestly, I feel like Sorn and I are happy with our life
right now. I don't see why we need to rush to that step.
Or maybe he's not serious about you?
Maybe he's tired of taking care of you.
I mean, you're living in his house.
Do you actually do anything for him?
I do plenty. Housework, helping him with
work, splitting utilities I pull my weight.
I mean, like… other
stuff. Taking care of him.
Did you get it done?
Take care of him how?
Like when he comes home tired, I
massage his shoulders and cook for him…
Or just little things like that.
You sound like an expert.
Where'd you learn this?
I watch too many dramas.
Damn.
You really just talk nonsense.
No, I'm serious.
Stuff like this matters.
If you do it
I guarantee…
Hia Sorn will be head over heels for you.
Who knows…
On your anniversary…
He might even propose.
You're talking impossible.
Order food.
You're the one who won't stop talking.
What?
Hmph.
Hey.
Hm?
The person behind you.
Doesn't their face look familiar?
Feels like I've seen them somewhere before.
I don't know.
No, I really recognize them.
You're imagining things.
Is he following you?
I saw him secretly
staring at you over there.
Maybe he likes you?
Damn it, how do you even come up with that?
Talking nonsense.
Hmph.
Well, you've gotten better-looking.
Not weird if someone likes you.
What the hell are you saying, huh?
Say it again and I won't
talk to you anymore.
Are you ordering food or not?
Scolding me again. Are you mad?
There, there. Don't be mad, okay?
If you pout, I won't let you see.
I mean it I won't let you see.
Are you making it up to me yet?
Then I won't let you eat.
You're paying, right?
Yeah, sure.
Really?
Really.
Then let's do it, my dear friend.
But don't stay mad at me.
Yeah.
When you stayed at my place, did you
ever do anything for me… like cooking?
Mmm.
Hmm?
Is it good?
Mm-hmm.
Want another bite?
It's good.
This dipping sauce is so tasty.
You ate so messy.
Should I add anything else, Hia?
Want me to add something?
What's wrong with you?
Nothing's wrong.
Don't you like me taking
care of you like this?
There's no way I wouldn't like that, Jun.
I'm just afraid that…
you'll get bored of me.
I'll never get bored of your weirdness.
Feed me one more bite.
It's hot.
Blow on it for me.
See the steam?
Whoa, you blew too
hard now it's all your spit.
Mmm.
Nom nom. If you want it,
you have to eat it yourself.
No way I'm feeding you.
Why not?
Feed me, will you.
Pleeease.
Who should this piece
of pork go to, I wonder?
Who would it belong to…?
Come on, act cute for me.
Whoever acts cute gets to eat it.
Can I have this piece of pork, please?
I don't see you being cute at all.
Can you be even cuter for me?
May I have a bite of the pork?
Please.
Pleeeease.
Promise me first you
won't ever get bored of me.
What are you cooking?
Just trying it out.
Yeah?
But I'm hungry. Can I have some first?
Looks delicious. I'm starving.
Hey Hia, no, it's burnt!
It looks so good, let me try it first.
I'm hungry.
Please?
But it's burnt.
Still edible.
Whoa.
My baby here…
You made it look delicious.
You're exaggerating.
Want to eat?
You eat it, Hia Sorn.
Come on, just a bite.
Hmph.
Is it good?
It's really good.
You've got to eat it like this too.
Tasty, huh?
Since you're living with him now,
do you even do anything for him?
P'Sorn.
Hm?
Come here.
Why?
Dress properly, will you?
Stop showing off your muscles.
Why, is it so hard to dress like this?
I'm jealous.
And also the office sign.
Here you go.
I like this scent.
Smells good now.
The other side too.
There, now you look handsome.
Now go get yourself dressed.
Go on, my wife.
Get dressed.
Okay.
See you.
I don't come out here often.
The weather's amazing.
Hmm.
Since you're living with him now,
do you even do anything for him?
Yeah.
What are you looking at?
Is it good?
It's good.
Not eating?
Better than before?
It's insanely good.
How was it?
You're amazing.
How's it going?
You're crazy good.
Why are you so good?
Who taught you?
Taught me what?
You were the one who taught me.
Do it again next time.
I'm done.
That's all I've got.
Don't call it “just that.”
Call it damn good.
You know what?
The only reason I managed that is…
Win told me.
Did he teach you?
No, he didn't.
He just...
Did Win teach you this?
Gave me some advice and...
Told me to do whatever it
takes to make you like me more.
Anniversary…
What?
Did you forget?
I didn't forget.
I remember.
How could I ever forget?
Next week we're going
to the beach, remember?
Do you want to go?
Hm
I've never been on a yacht before.
It'd be nice if we had the chance.
But don't go buying or
renting a yacht. It's expensive.
Then I'll buy you seven of them.
What do you mean, seven yachts?
Everyone's here, right?
Who's that?
This is my friend, Aun. He
owns a resort down south.
Oh.
But hey… his face looks familiar.
You've met him before, actually.
Really?
Yeah, back when I wasn't around.
I asked him to keep an eye on you.
Seriously, you go that far?
In case you had someone else.
I get jealous.
Jealous, huh… yeah, jealous.
Can you guys wait a sec?
My stomach hurts.
I need to hit the bathroom.
Didn't you already say that a while ago?
Yeah, I'll be quick.
How many places did
you follow me to, anyway?
Just a few.
Eh, forget it. So, what
should we bring to the beach?
Just myself and my heart… though
my heart's in the bathroom right now.
All I've got is a ball.
How can we go without music, man?
Hey.
Oh, shit!
That's the porn clip I
sent you this morning!
Whoa…
Don't tell me he's in the bathroom and…
Damn, P' Sorn…
Not bad at all, huh.
Ehh.
That voice sounds familiar, Sorn.
Feeling better after just now?
Oh!
I thought the video didn't have sound.
Did you like it?
I was just watching, that's all.
Anyway, let's head to the beach. (Watch on
www.kisskh.ovh or www.kisskh.la to support Admin)
Can you still drive?
You worn out yet?
Not yet.
Still got plenty left in me
good for a few more rounds.
About what you asked…
You can go. I already called and told them.
You and Hia Sorn are glued together.
Don't worry, Thanu will be there, dumb-ass.
Won't he get suspicious?
Me suddenly disappearing
on my own like that?
No one's gonna suspect anything.
Let the kid breathe a little.
You two are glued together way too much.
I love what's mine.
Yeah, Mr. Lover Boy.
Come on, P' Thanu.
Let me.
Thanu, look at your brother totally whipped.
His whole heart belongs to the kid now.
I just swallowed a big gulp.
He kept saying he doesn't
like kids, doesn't like kids…
Yeah right, look at him now.
So sweet it gives me chills.
You guys talk like I'm not even here.
Oh, so you can get embarrassed?
Jun.
They're teasing me.
Don't join in with them.
They're troublemakers.
Hmph. Idiot.
Hey P'Sorn, where did P'Aun and P'Thanu go?
The moment we got to the beach,
they ran straight into the bedroom.
Guess we can't hang out with them then.
Hmm… but it's actually nice, right? Getting to
spend the holiday at the beach together like this.
Do you like it?
Yeah… I do.
You like the beach?
Mm-hmm.
But if I had to choose what I like more…
It'd be the beach with you in it.
Which angle looks good?
Wanna try?
Okay.
You choose the spot then.
Alright.
Mm.
Whoa.
Legs that long you must
be at least 180 cm tall.
Here.
Does it look good?
Pretty. Can I try standing too, bro?
Sure.
Come here.
Mm, mm, mm.
Okay.
Alright.
I'll send it to you. I'll send it.
Uh… P' Thanu
where did P'Sorn go?
Uh… he'll come soon.
You look suspicious.
Suspicious?
You're talking nonsense.
Go post over there, the light's better.
Babe, put it on faster. Just putting it
there won't protect from the sun, you know?
Honey, just stay still.
It'll be done in a sec.
But you're so slow.
Mhm, here too.
Send it to me too, okay?
No problem.
Okay.
Hey, babe.
Yes?
I ran into Sorn today.
Mm.
But he was with another boy who looked a lot like
Jun. Same build, same face… almost Jun, but not Jun.
Don't tell me… Sorn broke up with Jun?
What? No way.
So, what were they doing?
That's the strange part
they were picking out rings.
Friends don't normally do that, right?
What if… Sorn's living a double
life? Babe, we should tell Jun.
But maybe it's their private
matter. We shouldn't interfere.
Do you think P'Sorn really loves me?
My brother really loves you, Jun.
Even Mom knows about you two.
He's even planned the
future with you. I'm telling you.
He's not messing around
with your feelings this time.
But P'Sorn's been gone the whole day.
He didn't answer my calls.
Didn't even read my texts, let alone reply.
Yeah, he went to take
care of some business.
He'll come pick you up for dinner later.
What business?
So important that he
has to vanish like this?
Just gone without a trace?
If you want answers…
Ask my brother yourself this evening.
He's got all the answers you need.
Not eating?
Do you have something you want to tell me?
What's wrong with you?
I'm just asking if there's
something you want to tell me.
If you're suspicious of something,
just ask me directly, Jun.
Well… someone told me you
went to buy a ring with another guy.
Shit.
Are you cheating on me?
Listen to me first.
I love you so much.
I would never cheat on you.
I did go to buy a ring.
I heard you say...
The other day that our
anniversary is coming up.
But I'm no good at choosing.
If I chose on my own, you'd
probably end up with some plain ring.
So I asked Aun's boyfriend
to help me pick one.
So you could have a beautiful ring to wear.
So you won't be
embarrassed in front of others.
Listen to me.
Hia loves Jun.
You've been mine for so long.
I've raised you since you were little.
But now…
My wife's gorgeous.
I'd never cheat on you, Jun.
Why are you being so sweet?
Can't I be sweet to you?
Mm.
I'm blushing.
Since you already bought it…
Then put it on me.
Which finger do you want me to put it on?
Hmm…
You chose it,
so you decide which finger.
You're letting me choose?
Well hello, hello!
Oh wow.
That's really sweet.
Mind if I join? Mind if I sit down?
Oh.
Aun.
There's another pair, you know.
Whoa.
Sit here.
This is Nice.
Aun's boyfriend.
His family's in the jewelry business.
So I asked him to help pick out the ring.
Hello, my name's Nice.
He's my boyfriend.
Whoa, the whole table already
knows, you're always showing off.
Well my boyfriend's this cute.
How could I not show him off?
Well, since we're all here congrats to
my brother and my future brother-in-law.
Thanks.
Let's eat.
I need another plate first.
No kiss before the meal?
What?
Oh, acting all shy now,
huh? My dear brother-in-law.
I feel like staying in the bathroom all day.
I believe you.
I could do this for you forever, you know.
Hey, P'Sorn… don't tell
me this boat is yours.
It is.
Why?
Whoa…
Why did you buy it?
You're that rich?
Buying random stuff like this…
Calm down. Let me explain.
Do you remember when my dad got shot?
Yeah…what about it?
When I went back to handle things at home.
My mom gave the money
to me and Thanu to manage.
My mom probably didn't want to
use the money from Dad's death.
So I took the money I got,
and invested it.
Became a partner in Fan's shop.
Bought a house.
Bought a car.
And this boat.
Aun recommended it.
I barely use it myself.
Mostly.
I rent it out for income.
You're incredible, P'Sorn.
I'm just doing what I should.
And besides…
Now I have you in my life.
And I already promised Go-Nung
that I'd take care of you the best I can.
So I have to make enough money.
Especially since you eat so much.
Hey.
Well, it's tasty.
Want some?
You wanna eat?
Is it good?
Hey, I wanna ask you something.
If you're already this rich, why
do you still work at the company?
If it were me
I'd just sail around the world.
Why though?
Back when I was studying…
Mm.
Uncle Long really helped me out.
He sent me and Champ
to finish school overseas.
Even though life's easier for me now.
I still have to help with the company.
Make sure it's stable first.
And when that day really comes.
I'll probably go live with
my mom down south.
Will you come live with me, Jun?
No matter what you do or where you live
I'll stay with you.
Always by your side.
You'll stay too, right?
I'll stay forever.
You said it yourself.
Mm.
Eat.
I'll get drunk.
Don't you have any beer, bro?
The weather's so nice.
Really?
Do you like it?
I do.
Cheers.
Tastes good.
What do you mean?
Champagne.
Well, it really is good.
Do you wanna come again?
Do you want me to?
You're gonna come anyway, right?
Then let's do this more often.
Okay.
Do I have to feed you?
Here.
Why are you so cute today?
I'm cute every day.
You just noticed today.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, what's this?
What's what?
Give me a kiss first.
Then why are you so cute today?
Mmm.
I'm cute every day, aren't I?
Really?
Yeah.
Then stay cute forever, okay?
What are you looking at?
Can't I look at the driver?
We're at the beach, look at the sea.
Pretty, right?
You?
The sea.
You're prettier.
Come up.
Right here.
Was that easy?
Yeah.
This one's straight, this
one's straight I remember.