ADAPTED FROM THE NOVEL
HIDDEN LOVE BY ZHU YI
BROTHER NO. 2
Do you like the gift?
He has really thick skin.
He took such a picture
and even asked if I like it.
Why is this picture there?
SANG ZHI
It's not clear at all.
This gift is a defect.
BROTHER NO. 2
If you agree to let me pursue you,
I'll send you an HD version immediately.
SANG ZHI
You wish.
I had wanted to use this
to speed up the courting process.
I didn't expect you
to reject me right off the bat.
I can only resort to this
to win a chance for myself.
You crafty old thing.
SANG ZHI
Old man.
YOU CRAFTY OLD MAN.
DUAN JIAXU
I have to be one step ahead
to deal with a young fox like you.
I'm going to sleep now.
Good night.
BROTHER NO. 2
EDIT CONTACT DETAILS
SUITOR
SILLY DOG
Little demon, buy whatever you want.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
The pool table will be blocked
if you move it there.
Do you see that?
Okay, boss.
Sang Yan, I might be dating soon.
SANG ZHI
SILLY DOG
Are you attending university
to study or to date?
Isn't it common to date
during university?
SILLY DOG
Suit yourself.
Be careful. Don't get cheated.
Yes, place the stool over there.
That's right. Over there.
Yes.
He's a bit old.
-Hello?
-Don't tell me he's older than me!
Lower your voice.
Where did you meet him?
He…
He's a postgraduate student here.
Listen.
You should study hard at your age.
Forget about dating.
He can't be even one day older than me.
I can't accept being addressed formally
by someone older.
Even if he's one day older than you…
You should feel respected
to be addressed formally.
CHAPTER 16, FEELINGS
WAITING FOR YOU TO DATE ME
Is that from your crush?
Have you decided
when you will accept him?
Do I need to think about that?
Of course.
Since he wants to pursue you,
you need to decide for how long.
How long should it be then?
That depends.
I accepted Chen Qiang
not long after he started pursuing me.
But it's up to you.
The right time for you is the best time.
I think right now is perfect.
You're something else.
But listen, Sangsang.
You have to protect yourself.
Do you understand?
Weiwei.
I'm actually a little worried.
Worried about what?
I'm afraid that he's doing it on a whim.
What if he loses interest after a while?
I don't think that is very likely.
You two have known each other for years.
Since he has decided to pursue you,
that means he must be determined.
What do you think?
You have a point.
It's okay.
If you're worried about that,
you can test him.
I'm going to sleep now.
Don't give in yet.
-Here is your favorite.
-Thank you.
-Your Americano.
-Here it is.
Thank you, Wangwang.
-Here is your latte.
-Thank you.
Did you buy a new bracelet?
It's pretty.
What are you saying?
It's a gift from her crush.
-A gift from her crush?
-Really?
Come on. Let me take a look.
It's pretty nice.
-What is this?
-Is it a mouse?
It's a fox.
-A fox? I couldn't tell.
-A mouse?
-Sorry.
He has good taste.
This one.
Are you free tomorrow?
Did your crush text you?
Wait.
What will you reply?
Let me reply for you.
Didn't we say that we would test him?
It will be fine. Trust me.
"No."
Send!
Stop messing around.
What do you know?
Sangsang and I talked about this before.
Right, Sangsang?
What did you two talk about?
No.
SANG ZHI
Did he reply?
"What about the day after tomorrow?"
I might not
be free either.
I might not be free either.
But what if he fails the test?
That's impossible.
He will pass the test.
He definitely will.
Listen, these relationship tests
can go either way.
Sangsang, you had better think twice.
Let me ask you guys something.
If you asked someone out
and she replied
that she might not be free,
is she free or not?
"Might not be free" means
it depends on your performance.
Why don't I call him?
You don't get it.
This is the appeal of love.
Do you understand?
-Okay.
-What do you know?
Just reply like that.
Just wait. Hold back a little longer.
Eat something first.
Don't meddle when you don't know anything.
Does that mean she's free?
Jiaxu, look into my eyes.
Who is it?
Who might not be free?
Eat your food.
Don't be nosy.
Something is up.
Here it is! See?
I told you. I knew he would reply.
-What did he say?
-Let me see.
How about Thursday night?
"How about Thursday night?"
Fine.
Since he has tried three times, he passes.
Hurry up. Stop being pretentious.
I'm free.
SANG ZHI
Do I look okay?
Yes, you look beautiful.
There is a new noodle shop
right off campus.
I heard that it's good.
-Really?
-Let's go together.
-Sure.
-You guys can go.
Today, I…
Sure.
We'll try it out for you.
What noodles do you guys want?
I heard from Yuting that their shrimp…
Sang Zhi.
I'm sorry.
What's the matter?
Why did you start with an apology?
It's like this.
We just found a bug in our system,
so we're all rushing to fix it.
I think
I won't be able to have dinner with you.
Okay. Will you be working very late?
Will you have dinner?
Should I get something for you?
Why is there another error, Jiaxu?
Jiaxu, save us.
Lower your voice.
Hello?
You should get back to work.
It's fine. Don't worry about me.
Sorry about this.
Remember to eat dinner, okay?
Okay.
Bye.
It's done.
I guess I'm having noodles today.
Where is the shop?
-Just to the right of the entrance.
-You're so dressed up.
Are you going like this?
Can't I eat noodles like this?
I guess so.
-Come on.
-Let's go.
Let's go.
-Bye.
-See you.
She's so pretty.
-Hello, Jiaxu.
-What should we eat later?
-Sorry.
-Pork hock with rice?
Sure. Or the noodles we had last time.
You're apologizing again.
This time,
a colleague suddenly ran into some issues.
We have to change the requirements
and add functions.
There's no helping it.
Well,
call me when you're free.
You're not upset, are you?
Once things settle down here,
I'll take you out for a nice meal.
That's all for now.
Hurry up.
-Right?
-Right.
Didn't he say
that he was going to pursue me?
Is he even trying?
I don't want it!
Wait for me!
I'll stop.
-What happened?
-Why are you back?
You…
What are you doing here?
I thought you were going on a date.
-That's right.
-You scared me.
He canceled it.
Didn't he say he wanted to pursue you?
How many times has he canceled?
It doesn't look like he's trying.
He's busy with work.
He didn't do it on purpose.
So what?
Can't he spare a few minutes?
He should have time before and after work.
He can see you if he wants to.
-Precisely.
-But he really is busy.
He's so busy
that he doesn't have time to sleep.
It would already be our curfew
by the time he gets here after work.
Why are you still defending him, Sangsang?
Don't you blame him?
It's fine.
I'm utterly speechless.
Don't tell me I have to teach him
how to pursue you.
Sangsang.
Have you not had dinner yet?
-Are you hungry?
-That's right.
Where are our leftovers?
-They're delicious leftovers.
-That's right.
-There is fruit too.
-They're delicious.
Here, take it.
You haven't eaten, right?
Smell it. It's nice.
Don't eat that yet.
Eat the hamburger.
I'll have some fruit first.
No, you can't have the fruit first.
Why?
Well, the hamburger will spoil
by tomorrow.
Eat this first. It's very filling.
Eat this.
Take a sniff. It smells great.
Currently, the character modeling
is basically completed.
Regarding this,
we actually optimized the fluidity
of the characters' techniques.
Currently,
we have basically completed
all optimizations.
There are no issues for now.
Yes.
I'm sure everyone has seen
how much Jia Yang has improved.
You flatter me.
This has been tough on you guys.
Our optimization
has proved to be effective.
So
I want to congratulate you guys.
No overtime today!
-Go home and rest.
-At long last!
We can finally leave on time.
-Yes.
-Let's go.
NURSING HOME
Drawing it like this won't do.
What are you drawing?
Sangsang, why are you back again?
Did he cancel again?
I was stood up again.
-No way!
-Wait, what?
How many times has it been now?
-Was it work again?
-Don't cry.
It's not work this time.
But I didn't ask him about it.
I couldn't be bothered.
Is he pursuing her if he doesn't date her?
Of course not.
What is he doing?
All right. It will be fine.
Even without him, we are here for you.
-We'll take you out for coffee.
-Yes.
-No.
-Let's go.
I don't
feel like going out today.
-Come on.
-Let's go.
-Let's go. You have to go.
-No.
-Come.
-No, thank you.
-I'm not going.
-You have to go.
-No, thank you.
-You're coming right now.
C&amp;D YIBAI ELDERLY CARE CENTER
Mr. Duan.
Your dad hasn't been doing well lately.
I see. Thank you, Dr. Yang.
He has been bedridden for nine years.
His health and immunity are subpar.
His pulmonary edema has worsened lately.
I suggest taking him
to the hospital for surgery
to remove the excess water in his lungs.
Otherwise, an infection might occur.
It will be even more severe by then.
Do you think
he will wake up?
Miracles will happen
as long as he is still alive.
Dr. Yang, I'll let you handle
the hospital transfer procedure.
I'll be going then.
Okay.
Jiaxu.
Mom, look.
It's snowing today.
Call your dad. Why isn't he back yet?
We were going to celebrate
your first place
in the city's physics contest.
I'll ask him.
Don't eat it yet.
-Well?
-He didn't pick up.
Call him again.
-Dad.
-There you are.
What's the matter?
Did you drink?
I'm done for.
-What do you mean?
-I'm done for.
What do you mean?
Dad, what's the matter?
I ran someone over.
Where did it happen?
At the burger shop on Renmin Road.
How is that person doing?
Well…
No one saw it.
I drank. I couldn't call the cops.
Duan Zhicheng, have you lost your mind?
How could you drive after drinking?
Are you mad? What were you thinking?
Jiaxu!
Jiaxu, don't call the cops.
-Don't call them.
-Dad, listen to me!
We have to save that person!
It will be worse
if something happens to them!
Dad, you can't escape from this.
Zhicheng, go and turn yourself in.
We'll figure something out.
-I don't want to go to jail.
-Zhicheng, turn yourself in.
Jiaxu!
-Zhicheng!
-Jiaxu!
There was a car accident
outside the burger shop on Renmin Road!
-Send medical help!
-Turn yourself in!
Dad!
-Dad!
-Zhicheng!
Zhicheng!
You're back.
Why are you still up?
You're making that again.
You're back late from work too.
Look at the time.
Did you skip dinner again?
I'm not hungry. I was waiting for you.
I brought noodles back for you.
Put that down for now.
Let's have dinner together.
You're wasting money again.
These?
-They're inexpensive.
-Let me finish this first.
-Let's eat first.
-Okay.
Try this.
I heard that this restaurant is good.
Here.
Other kids are enjoying themselves
after the college entrance exam.
But my son
took on two jobs right after the exam,
working from morning until night.
It's because I'm young.
Young people should endure more hardships.
By the way, Mom,
I asked my boss
for an advance.
But he can only give me
half a month's advance
since I'm a newcomer.
But that's fine.
I'll think of something else.
Just let me handle this.
I'll try to borrow money
from our relatives.
Stop borrowing money from them.
I'm serious.
Mom, I have something to tell you.
What is it?
After giving it some thought,
I won't attend university in Nanwu.
Earning money is more important now.
Absolutely not.
You have to attend university.
Our family is in huge debt.
I don't have to go to university.
I will work in the morning
and do part-time jobs at night.
We'll pay off the debt eventually.
You mustn't let our mistakes
affect your future.
But you know that--
No buts.
You have to finish university.
If not,
don't call me your mom.
Mom, what's wrong?
I'm fine.
Maybe it's because I skipped dinner.
My tummy is protesting.
How many times have I told you?
You can't skip meals.
I'll get you some water.
Mom, it's time to eat.
Have you done the discharge paperwork?
You're not leaving.
What are you doing?
Sit down and rest.
Mom.
You don't need to be discharged.
I borrowed 30,000 yuan
from my university friend.
You can stay here and recuperate.
Jiaxu.
I feel much better now.
I feel like going home.
I'm serious.
Return the money.
I already borrowed it.
Your health matters the most.
Rest well.
My son.
Aren't you tired of owing people money?
We cannot stand with our heads up high
until the day we pay off all our debt.
I don't want you to be burdened by this.
Mom, don't worry.
I can earn back the money in the future.
Don't overthink it.
Now, have something to eat, okay?
I brought you some--
I'm begging you!
Will you please return the money?
We haven't paid off our existing debt yet.
We still need to take care
of Xiaoying and her mom.
We can't afford to take on more debts!
What if I die one day
and the debt isn't paid off yet?
What will you do then?
Mom, you won't die. What are you saying?
What are you doing?
SANG ZHI
DUAN JIAXU
I just got home.
Hello, Jiaxu.
What is it?
What are you doing?
I'm at my dorm.
I'll go and see you.
Right now?
It's 8:30 p.m.
That's three and a half hours left
until your curfew.
Okay then.
I'll take you out for supper.
What do you want to have?
I'm fine with anything. I'm not hungry.
I'll be right there. Wait.
Don't wait.
-Wait, I--
-Hurry up.
What have you been busy with lately?
Plenty of things.
I have lectures to attend,
assignments to finish,
also,
a drawing exhibition,
my school club,
and wait for someone to ask me out.
Lately…
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to keep canceling.
I've just been deluged
with too many miscellaneous things lately.
Miscellaneous things?
They're just trivial matters.
They're not important.
If that's the case,
why didn't you ask me out?
I had no idea
you wanted me to ask you out so badly.
Are you upset?
No.
I feel
that you're unhappy.
Are you burned out from work?
No. How can that be?
I'm finally having a meal with you.
I'm over the moon.
I'm serious.
If so,
give me a smile.
Wait here.
-Where are you going?
-Wait here.
Hello.
Can I make one?
Hi. Do you want to make one?
I would like to have a try.
Thank you.
It's pretty difficult.
Do I do it like this?
Cut it for me.
Okay.
Take your time.
Bring it lower.
Is this okay?
Yes.
Do you want cotton candy?
-I'll pay you in a bit.
-Okay.
This is for you.
For me?
It's as if you're cheering a child up.
Yes, an old child.
When I was unhappy in the past,
eating sweets would cheer me up.
Do you want to try it?
I'll try it.
Is it sweet?
It's very sweet.
Thank you.
It's my first time
being comforted like this.
Do you want to try it?
Is it sweet?
It's sweet.
You're pretty good at making cotton candy.
Have you made it for someone else before?
No.
So I'm the first person to try
the cotton candy you made.
Yes.
I understand what you mean now.
What do you mean?
I understand.
What do you understand?
Haven't you agreed
to be my girlfriend?
When did I agree to that?
Why would someone make cotton candy
for an ordinary friend?
-Ordinary--
-That's not all.
You're wearing the bracelet.
Jiaxu, you…
Stop being so devious.
You won't win me over like this.
Then how can I win you over?
You can
search online
or ask other people.
Ask other people how to pursue a girl.
How do I pursue a girl?
Must you ask me?
Can you teach me?
Anyway, listen up.
At this rate,
if we're only texting,
occasionally calling,
and meeting up once in a long while,
it definitely won't work.
It's not online dating.
Online dating at your age?
Speaking of online dating,
I suddenly recall something.
-A certain kiddo had--
-Okay, that's enough.
That's enough. Great job.
Don't bring it up again.
I was just joking with you.
I'm serious.
Today,
I've realized my mistakes.
From today on,
I will be serious
and work hard to pursue you.
I'm serious.
Great.
I will look forward
to your performance.
Are you free tomorrow?
Tomorrow morning?
Not in the morning.
I need to be at school.
Do you have classes on the weekend?
It's not a class.
An alumnus is giving a sharing seminar.
But…
-My afternoon--
-I see.
-I'll just work overtime tomorrow then.
It's fine.
I will keep at it.
I said "but" very loudly.
Don't tell me he didn't hear me.
I'm excited about this sharing session.
We should tell them to come.
All right. I'll text them right now.
Let's sit here.
Okay.
Text them right now.
I'll ask them on WeChat.
Sangsang,
I can't see the blackboard from here.
I'm going to sit closer.
Good morning.
What's the matter?
Who is that next to Sang Zhi?
Is that her boyfriend?
I don't know.
What are you doing here?
Didn't you say that
there is a sharing session today?
Yes.
So I inquired about the time and location.
Don't you have work today?
I took time off.
So…
Are you here to keep me company?
What do you mean?
I just happened to run into you.
Sure.
You graduated from university
almost two years ago
and just happened
to run into a freshman like me.
And look at your getup.
Do I look young?
It's not bad.
I'll dress like this from now on.
Sang Zhi's boyfriend keeps gazing at her.
He's so gentle.
Why does he keep staring at me?
Maybe I should pretend to sleep.
I'm sleepy all of a sudden.
It hasn't started yet. I'll take a nap.
Why are you sleepy now that I'm here?
No, I would be sleepy
even if you weren't here.
Take a nap then.
Go to sleep.
This kiddo is pretending to be asleep.
SANG YAN
I think my sister is seeing someone.
She's alone out there.
Help me look out for her.
Make sure she doesn't get tricked.
Okay.