ADAPTED FROM THE NOVEL
HIDDEN LOVE BY ZHU YI
Sangsang, help me take a look.
Does this long, wide-angle shot
look out of place?
It makes this spot look weird.
This spot isn't good.
The next static shot seems off.
What if I put the subtitle above it?
-Yes, swap them.
-Swap them? Okay.
Do you want a drink?
-No.
-No?
Fruit.
Swap the two.
Okay.
-Apple?
-Thank you.
-Take a look inside.
-Okay.
This used to be an event venue
for a company.
It will be perfect as a workspace.
And is the balcony back there included?
Yes, it's included.
This space is around
200 square meters in total.
Jiaxu, this office is smaller
than the previous one.
It is 150 square meters.
-150 square meters?
-It is closer to your expectation.
It's ready to go
once your employees relocate.
-Is this a conference room?
-Yes.
Is the price negotiable?
Yes, because the landlord wants
to support young entrepreneurs.
That's wonderful.
How about this?
It works.
-It can work.
-Look at this.
This is so cute!
I'll use this angle then.
Don't criticize me.
I didn't!
-Sorry!
-Enough!
-Sorry.
-Okay, that's enough.
-Come on. Continue.
-Fine, I'll let it go for you.
Good job.
-Have some water.
-Thank you, sir.
Where do I put this, sir?
Put that in the room first.
Okay, thank you.
It's all set, right?
Liu Yu, right?
-Yes, that's me.
-Hi.
-Have a seat.
-Okay.
Thank you for waiting.
No problem.
This is my resume.
Please have a look.
-It looks so formal.
-Yes.
Have you played A Dream of Jianghu before?
Yes.
I'm really impressed
with the optimized version.
You flatter me.
This is my start-up's early stage.
Let's learn from each other.
Try it.
CONGRATULATIONS,
YOUR SUBMISSION WAS SUCCESSFUL
It's done. You can rest now.
I'm free.
CHAPTER 25, RUN TOWARDS YOU
SECRETLY, UNABLE TO HIDE IT
Put it on my tab.
Sang Yan's bar has quite the ambiance.
The bar called Syria is nice too.
Here, have some cola.
I'll sit with you, Qian Fei.
Why?
We should keep some distance,
so my girlfriend doesn't get
the wrong idea.
Screw you.
There you are.
Yes, at long last! I am exhausted.
You even have your luggage.
I'm dead tired.
Slow down. Are you that hungry?
I rushed here after I got off the plane.
I'll faint from hunger.
I appreciate it, Junwen.
Thank you for coming to be
my chief programmer.
Order whatever you want.
It's your welcoming party.
We have the boss here anyway.
-I'll go all out then.
-Order away.
Scan the code.
Speaking of which,
I came to help you with your start-up,
but you didn't even come to pick me up.
Excuse me?
They were your college roommates too.
They didn't pick you up.
Don't just blame me.
He's right. You two didn't pick me up.
Why is that?
I…
Sorry.
Sang Yan.
I would like
to visit your parents
in the next few days.
Are you so eager
to meet her parents already?
That's not it.
I finally have some free time
after being busy with my studio.
I think I should visit them.
I want to discuss something with them.
He's not like you.
He dates with marriage as the goal.
He doesn't string girls along.
You even tell them,
"All the girls chase after me."
You are 125 kg of bull crap.
Shut it.
Who is 125kg?
Who? Me?
Duan Jiaxu, you have changed.
You're no longer
the Duan Jiaxu who liked me.
Listen, my circumstances have changed.
My brother-in-law
is sitting across from me.
I have to take his side.
Right, darling brother?
-Darling brother!
Wait. After dating my sister,
you're as dumb as her.
My brother is so mean.
How mean!
-Yes!
-He's so harsh!
SANG ZHI
Do you mind?
-Yes.
Hello?
Hello. Are you still out?
Yes.
Chen Junwen arrived today.
Sang Yan, Qian Fei, and I
threw him a welcoming party.
Are you back at your dorm?
Yes, I'm back.
Call me when you get home later.
Okay, I'll call you when I'm home.
By the way,
don't worry.
Nothing is going on
between me and those three.
Are they next to you?
Yes.
Then tell them that I'm jealous.
Bye.
Now I know why you two are going
to be family.
You two are just the same.
Don't drag me into this.
I seem to remember
that someone told his sister
that every girl in our school
was obsessed with him.
Who could possibly be this narcissistic?
Who is so shameless?
Yes, who are you talking about?
Indeed.
That's on you, darling brother.
-Darling brother!
Enough. Shut up.
When are you coming?
Pick a time when your parents are free.
Why?
I'll join in on the fun.
Me too.
Count me in.
Get lost!
Don't be nosy, you two.
Why can't I come?
I'll come if I want to.
Let's not tease them. Eat this.
You're punctual.
You were serious about coming.
Of course.
Because Sang Zhi said
that our parents don't like you,
so I'm here to see if that's true.
Then I can mock you.
You are all dressed up.
Just sit by the side and watch.
Don't say anything.
I'm staying out of it.
I wouldn't be here
if Sang Zhi hadn't asked me to help.
Come in.
Xiaoduan, hello.
It has been a while, Mrs. Sang.
I bought you and Mr. Sang some food.
Why? No need for that.
-Keep it.
-No.
Please accept it. I insist.
Take it.
He can bring it in.
-I've got it.
-Then I'll get it.
Mom, I'll get it.
My husband is cooking.
It will be ready soon. Take a seat.
-Okay.
-Go ahead.
It's delicious.
Xiaoduan.
Have you found a place for your studio?
Yes.
It's in our headquarters' technology park.
I've already assembled my team.
That's a nice environment.
It's perfect for a start-up.
Yes.
We will head into full operation soon.
Good.
Eat some more.
Sure.
Mr. and Mrs. Sang,
I have to use the restroom.
Enjoy the meal.
It's upstairs.
Here, have some fruit.
-Thank you.
-Xiaoduan, are you full?
Yes.
You didn't eat a lot.
Was the meal not to your liking?
No, it was very delicious.
I'm glad to hear that.
Try this amazing tea.
-Thank you, Mr. Sang.
-Do you want any?
No, thank you.
Just drink it.
Ignore him. Enjoy the tea.
Mr. Sang.
I have thought a lot about the concerns
that you mentioned last time.
I understand
why you have misgivings
about my relationship with Zhizhi.
You are afraid she will be hurt.
But I'm here to tell you
that I'm very serious about Sang Zhi.
You see,
after my dad's car accident,
the victim's family
did come to pester us.
However, it has been fully dealt with now.
You need not worry about it anymore.
Sang Zhi will graduate in two years.
Before that, I will work here
for my future and hers.
Are you sure
you want to start over in Nanwu?
Yes.
Mr. and Mrs. Sang.
I would be a different person
if I had never met Sang Zhi.
I heard from Sang Yan that you work.
Then I see you working today.
I wanted to say
that you don't have to treat me
if you're short on cash.
Jiaxu.
Don't panic.
Once I grow up
and start making money,
I'll help you pay it off.
She always puts me first
in everything she does.
Jiang Ying!
Does it hurt?
It's not a major surgery.
-It's okay.
-I'll wait for you.
She is clearly much younger than me.
I should be the one protecting her,
yet she always wants to shield me.
As long as I am here,
I won't let anyone bully Duan Jiaxu again.
He has me
and many others who love him.
We all love you.
She helped me overcome my past,
and I will
safeguard her future.
Mr. and Mrs. Sang.
I don't have a lot in my possession.
But I will give my all
to treat Zhizhi well for a lifetime.
Jiaxu.
We see your sincerity.
Zhizhi has mentioned
her relationship with you
to us many times.
As it was only her side of the story,
we were unsure about the whole thing.
Previously,
we said that we were worried
about your family.
That was because we didn't want Zhizhi
to get hurt.
If you say that you can protect her,
that's all we want to hear
as her parents.
Xiaoduan.
My husband and I really want…
In fact,
it all boils down
to her happiness.
Yes.
The rest isn't an issue.
I know.
Now I finally understand
why Zhizhi is so amazing.
She is so lucky
to have the two of you as her parents.
Did you forget
about her awesome brother?
What?
Don't be narcissistic.
I'm part of the family too.
Have tea, Xiaoduan.
-I'm her brother.
-Thank you, Mrs. Sang.
Does the little demon know
that you met the parents?
I haven't told her yet.
Listen, as a man,
you need to toughen up.
Did you hear what you said earlier?
What's wrong?
If you spoil her like that,
I can envision your future.
She will be the death of you.
And if you spoil her rotten,
she'll take it for granted
and feel entitled.
I don't mind it.
One more thing.
From now on,
don't take everything on yourself.
It's so unreasonable.
You can
make your life easier.
Thank you, buddy.
I'm serious.
Thank you
for all you've done.
You're crazy.
I remember the first time I met Sang Zhi.
We were walking on this street
to take out the trash.
Your sister should be quite obedient.
Obedient?
She's in her rebellious phase.
She won't listen to me.
You've seen how my parents spoil her.
She's in middle school,
but acts like
an elementary school student.
Is that so?
I have something to tell you.
Your sister's teacher wants
to see your parents.
She kept asking me
if I could see the teacher for her.
Jiaxu, are you coming or not tomorrow?
I've told you everything.
Why don't you ask Sang Yan?
No way!
I framed him just now.
So Sang Zhi.
You know when we'll meet next time, right?
Bye.
Close the gate when you leave.
Go and see her teacher tomorrow.
So that's why she insisted
on inviting you to dinner.
She had a secret agenda.
It's probably nothing serious.
It's always the same problem
when the teacher wants to see us.
She needs to learn her lesson.
I won't indulge her this time.
Ignore her.
No, I just promised her.
I can go with you tomorrow.
It's just a simple meeting.
You promised her. I didn't.
Go on your own.
She followed me to the front door
just to secretly confirm
if I'll see the teacher for her.
I forgot about it already.
Slow down, darling brother.
Aren't I punctual?
Are you not in your dorm?
I went home
because I have no classes
tomorrow morning.
I figured
I could come here to snack.
And tomorrow, I can sleep in.
Who is this?
What happened?
You seem extra chirpy today.
I am quite happy.
Happy about what?
Tell me.
Well, here's the thing.
I went to see your parents today.
And then
they gave their approval.
How did you convince them?
What did they say?
Did they say they support us now?
Really?
Are you happy?
I'm very happy.
Me too.
Listen.
From now on,
you must be even more certain
that you're the best.
You, Duan Jiaxu,
are the best in the world.
And no one can tell you otherwise.
Got it?
I miss you so much.
I miss you too.
That's right.
Are you free at the end of the month?
The end of the month?
Why?
My design won an award.
The award ceremony is
at the end of the month.
That's amazing!
Will you come?
When did you say it is?
The end of the month.
That might be a bit hard to arrange.
You see,
I have a new project at the moment,
so I have a lot of meetings to attend.
The end of the month is…
I'm sorry.
It's okay. Focus on your work.
Well…
The next time I win an award,
you have to be there.
Pinky promise?
Pinky promise.
Whoever breaks the promise
is a big, fat dummy.
Has the ceremony started?
Is your boyfriend not coming today?
He's busy.
That's true. I can imagine.
Don't forget about me, future CEO's wife.
Show me the previous one.
This one?
No, this one.
Why are you ignoring me?
Do it like this.
Who is that?
He's so handsome.
Who is he? He's a hunk.
He's so cute.
Miss.
Why did you ignore your boyfriend's text?
Is this seat taken?
No.
Sit down.
It has been a while.
It certainly has been.
Why are you here?
DUAN JIAXU
Why do you react like this?
It feels like you don't miss me at all.
When did you get here?
SANG ZHI
My flight was this morning.
So why are you here?
SANG ZHI
DUAN JIAXU
I know you're coming
to this award ceremony.
The A Dream of Jianghu team
was also invited.
I came in Siyun's place.
Then why did you say
that you weren't coming?
I wanted
to give you a surprise.
I saw it in your guide.
Frequent surprises are necessary
in maintaining
a long-distance relationship.
I thought you forgot.
How is that possible?
It's my phone wallpaper.
When you said you weren't coming,
I…
Were you disappointed?
Unhappy?
-Don't tell me you cried.
-No.
I am very happy that you could come.
Why am I sitting here?
They're sickeningly sweet!
Is it Sangsang and her boyfriend?
I want to see!
Should we sit in the back?
Sorry to bother you.
Let's go.
Sorry to disturb you, miss.
Sorry, miss.
Hurry up.
-Excuse me.
-Hurry up.
Did you change into a suit for this?
How does it look?
Does this tie go with this suit?
But today,
the tie feels a little tight.
It's strangling me.
You have to button this…
-What are--
-What are you doing?
If you want to kiss me, just say so.
No need for these little tricks.
I…
What's wrong?
Was I too shameless?
So you know.
Sorry.
I just haven't seen you for too long.
I really miss you.
What?
What does that mean?
That means
that I miss you too.
Mr. Duan, may I trouble you for a second?
I'm going to sign in.
Wait a moment.
Wait for me.
Next up, we will award
the final prize
of the competition.
Let's welcome the award presenter,
the representative of A Dream of Jianghu,
Mr. Duan Jiaxu,
onto the stage.
Applause, please.
Hello, everyone. I am Duan Jiaxu.
It's my great honor to represent
the production team of A Dream of Jianghu
and present awards to everyone today.
You're so handsome!
Man, the new game is so much fun!
Boss, are you still single?
Sorry, everyone.
My girlfriend is taking a photo of me.
She has a clearer view now.
He's so sweet!
Goodness!
Let's get back to business.
I will be presenting
the last award of this competition.
The Character Image Design Award.
Please take a look at the screen.
THE FIFTH DESIGN COMPETITION
OF YIHE UNIVERSITY
So cute.
"MY SECRET" BY SANG ZHI
Then let's keep at it
and work hard together.
I will find my dream.
You will also realize your dream soon.
I hope
that all unhappy things
can stay away from you.
I hope that someone can accompany you.
I hope that someone is me.
It's very creative.
It's so good.
Now our dreams
have come true.
Now,
let's invite this award-winning student,
Sang Zhi, to come to the stage
to accept the award.
Great job, Sang Zhi!
Awesome!
Great!
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Next up,
let's invite the winners
and the dean of Yihe University
onto the stage
to take a group photo
with Mr. Duan Jiaxu.
Please come up.
Hello. Thank you.
Everyone on stage,
please face the camera in the center.
Get ready for a big group photo.
Get ready.
Three, two,
one.
AWARD CERTIFICATE
TWO YEARS LATER
-Happy graduation!
-Graduation dance!
-Okay!
-I'll help you take pictures.
-Who?
-Come at me!
Over there.
Let's take photos of them.
Four years went by so fast.
We've graduated.
Stop right there.
I don't want to cry today.
Don't tell me what to do.
Normally, I would argue with you.
But today,
we'll go our separate ways soon.
I'll shut up.
What am I going to do
without you bickering with me?
Isn't Chen Qiang also good
at talking back?
Would he dare?
I might not get used to it either.
I want to cry even more now!
Don't cry!
I can't take it!
All right, it's fine.
Although we have graduated,
we were only together for four years,
and
it was fleeting,
our friendship won't disappear.
Always together.
Weiwei.
Your makeup is really messed up.
If you want to take pictures later,
you should…
-Where?
-She's right.
Go and fix it.
-I'm going!
-We'll take more photos later.
-Go with her.
-Find a bathroom.
I'll go with you.
-Okay, let's go.
-Did you bring your makeup bag?
-I did.
-Hurry up.
-Fill in your brows now.
-Okay.
-Do you want water?
-Yes, later.
-Later.
-Thank you.
-I'm going to fix my makeup.
-Okay.
Help yourself to water.
-I have it here.
-This way.
-Come on.
-Hurry up.
-Okay.
Let's do it right here.
-Chen Qiang.
-Here.
Do you remember what you're going to say?
-Right.
-Roses!
-Yes, go and get them.
-Go get them.
-Let's make a heart here.
-Give it to me.
Then pile it up.
After it's piled up,
we'll scatter a ring of roses around it.
-Where do we start?
-From here.
Pile it up, right?
Come on.
-I'll help you.
-Okay.
There's too much here.
-Change it.
-It's okay.
This is okay.
We can pile it up now.
Hurry up.
-How should we pile it?
-Like this.
Take it all like this.
-Pile it up, right?
-Yes.
Make a heart
and roses.
So? What do you think?
-It works.
-She will like it.
I hope it works out.
Don't open your eyes.
-What?
-Don't open your eyes.
I just fixed my makeup. Don't mess it up.
That won't happen. I won't touch it.
-Be careful.
Follow our steps.
Be careful.
Are we there yet?
-We're almost there. Come.
-Come.
-Get ready.
-Take a step.
-Your right foot.
Which foot?
-This is confusing!
-Be careful.
Okay.
Stand up.
Come here.
Are you ready?
-Ready.
-Okay.
-Three.
Two!
-One!
Sorry, this is a bit abrupt.
I thought of many different ways.
Sang Zhi.
In the past, I always felt
that being alone forever
wouldn't matter much to me.
That was until I met you.
You made me realize
that loving someone and being loved
is such a happy thing.
Thank you for giving me so much love.
Because of you,
I found out
that I'm such a great person too.
It turns out
that I deserve to be loved too.
You made me suddenly want to try.
To love someone no matter what.
I don't have anything else I can give you.
Only six words.
Only one person for a lifetime.
I hope you can be a witness
to these six words.
But it will take
a little longer to witness.
I want to use a lifetime
to live up to this promise.
Will you marry me?
-Say yes!
-Marry him!
Sangsang!
Kiss!
-Kiss!
I am quite envious of you.
You secretly liked me for so long.
The feeling of having a person in my heart
is quite nice.
I'll tell you a secret.
Before I told you that I liked you,
I already secretly liked you.
Really?
Do you still remember
the first snowfall in your freshman year?
That was when it started.
Our story started
when he was 22 years old.
I used to secretly hide
my feelings for him.
I didn't dare to let anyone find out.
I strived to become a better person
and catch up to him.
When I made it to his side,
I found out
that I was never running alone.
He was also running towards me.
It was five full years.
I healed the wounds of his youth.
He fulfilled my young first love.
Our story started
when he was 22 years old
and ended when I was 22 years old.
Why did you secretly hide one?
You didn't hide it well either.
Do you want to know what was written?
MY DREAM IS TO GET INTO YIHE UNIVERSITY
Okay, get ready to roll.
Action!