=Eight Hundred=
(Body-burning homicide day)
That woman.
She ran off just six months
after marrying me.
And she was carrying your child.
She's my wife.
How could she have married you?
Is this the woman you're talking about?
How is this Jiao Yuqin?
This is Jiao Yuqin.
The Liugou you're heading to
is an illegal coal pit, right?
You're a local and you don't even know?
There are only a few legitimate
small coal pits in Fengyang.
I was just asking casually.
If you want to chat,
say something proper.
Speaking in half measures,
I can't even be bothered with you.
So you
are from the Liugou pit.
Then let me ask you something.
I heard that in these illegal pits now,
there are many women
who are Death Benefit Brides.
Is that true?
Of course it's true.
What kind of place
is an illegal coal pit?
A life there is worth less than coal.
Have you seen it?
Seen people die, and their wives
take the money and run.
But whether they
are Death Benefit Brides,
no one would say.
Then that kind of deal
sounds pretty good.
No work, no effort.
It's not as simple as you think.
You know,
someone has to scout things out.
Looking for those
with no family and no ties,
who want to live a proper life.
But if you can't get
a marriage certificate,
you won't get a single cent.
By the way,
when you get a marriage certificate,
you can't use your real name.
If others find out,
your life won't be safe.
You seem to know quite a lot.
So,
you did it before?
Of course not.
I just heard it from
those illegal pit workers.
When they have nothing to do,
they like to talk about
frightening things.
It's quite strange
when you think about it.
You say these women
don't even go down the shaft,
so how did they manage to
kill those men?
Drugging them.
Making them take medicine?
Doesn't the medicine
taste
bitter to them?
Bitter?
Once a woman undresses,
any man would lose his senses.
Bitter?
Forget bitter.
Even if you fed him something foul,
he would think it was fine.
Why are you turning?
Where are we going?
Are you out of your mind?
It's this.
You used this
to make your husband
drink himself to death, didn't you?
That's none of your business.
You're out of your mind.
Stop.
Stop right there!
Let go!
I know you.
You're Jiao Yuqin, right?
Who are you?
Who is she?
Where is she now?
I don't know who you're talking about.
Was she using your ID card? Speak.
I don't know.
Help.
Help!
Help, let go!
Let go!
Speak. Where is she?
Where is my wife?
Where is she?
Speak!
=Episode 7=
(Before the Rain)
(Stop)
Only I can help you now.
Listen to me, otherwise you won't get
out of this.
And you won't escape either.
You darn drug dealer.
You're no different
from a murderer like me.
You won't escape.
How can you prove I sell drugs?
I saw it.
Where's the evidence?
Don't forget,
your phone is still with me.
Right.
The phone is with you.
But I forgot to tell you something.
In the future, after making a call,
remember to wipe off your fingerprints.
The goods I gave you
were for you to give to Lu Yuan.
Since you killed him,
those goods must be at your house, right?
Along with that phone
with your fingerprints...
But none of that matters now anyway.
After all,
they can't execute you twice.
You rascal.
From the very beginning,
you were framing me, right?
I'll kill you right now!
Chen Hui!
I will kill you, believe it or not!
Listen to me,
and the three of us can all live.
The police are about to track us down.
I have a suggestion.
Let's wipe the slate clean
on everything that happened before.
Put the knife down.
After we get back,
I will help you find
the person you're looking for.
That way, it's a win for both of us.
Mr. Huo,
the police will be here any moment.
Right now,
your only choice is to trust us.
Otherwise, kill me,
and we all go down together.
- Kill me first.
- Shut up.
- Kill me.
- Kill me first.
- Kill me first!
- Shut up!
- Kill me!
Kill me!
Shut up!
Everyone go. Hurry.
That red car, come over.
Quick, throw the stuff away.
Throw it away.
The police are here.
Why are you stopping here?
The cars ahead have all moved on.
Go, hurry.
Go.
Mr. Huo.
Limin.
Hui and Songge?
Where are you going?
I'm taking Songge
to the city for dialysis.
Wait a moment.
We need to conduct an inspection.
Mr. Huo, vehicle registration
and driver's license.
Then turn off the engine and step out.
And the keys.
Mr. Huo, that's a lot of medicine.
My stomach hasn't been well.
How is it?
Everything okay?
It's fine.
All good, right?
Alright.
Thank you for your trouble, Mr. Huo.
It's nothing.
Limin, there's blood on this seat.
What about the blood?
Maybe
it was left by a previous passenger.
I'm not sure.
Remove the seat cushion
and the seat cover,
and check everything again.
There is a large amount of blood
under the back seat.
What about the blood in the back?
This
might also be
from some passenger.
Take him back to the station.
You...
Hui,
don't just stand there.
Say something.
Hui,
does this blood
have anything to do with you?
This blood
belongs to Songge.
It belongs to Songge?
That day, her fistula ruptured,
and I took her to the city hospital.
My father knows about this too.
He can testify.
(People's Public Security)
Kaiming.
I owe you an apology for this.
It was a misunderstanding.
It's fine.
About Songge that day,
I haven't had the chance
to thank you yet.
No need.
By the way, the inspections
on the national highway
have been very strict
these past few days.
You'd better not go out.
Otherwise,
I'll end up following behind you
and explaining things for you every day.
Alright.
I'll get going.
Drive safely.
Dad, if everything's fine,
we'll leave first.
Alright.
Take good care of Songge.
Go on.
Let's go.
Chen Hui,
I think
Huo Kaiming won't let us off.
If he comes again,
what should we do?
We need to seriously think
about who he's actually looking for.
How would we know who he's looking for?
That's true,
but he's already lost his mind.
There's no use reasoning with him.
Did he ever tell you
any characteristics about that person?
He said that last year
he drank cough syrup,
and it was a full bottle.
But last year, we never sold
whole bottles at all.
I really can't figure out
who gave it to him.
What's wrong?
At the end of last year,
the one cooking at the illegal coal pit,
Ma Heping.
What about him?
He said his son
broke 16 bottles.
Sixteen?
Why didn't you tell me?
Didn't we agree
that anyone who breaks
the rules has to be out?
I felt sorry for him.
He's disabled
and has a child with him.
So I...
So now, only Ma Heping's bottles
are missing and haven't been returned.
Then his bottles must have gone
to the person Huo Kaiming
is looking for.
I need to go home
and see if my dad
has any information.
You...
You little rascal,
you got me all dirty.
Whose kid are you?
Why are you so naughty?
Oh my, what are you doing?
Dad, don't...
Hongbing!
Quick, look.
This child is covered from head to toe.
I'll get some water.
- What's wrong with you?
- Take a bath.
Who told you to mess
around like that?
- Come here!
- I don't want to take a bath.
Stop right there.
Don't come over here.
Hui, grab him.
Catch him.
Whose child is this?
A friend's child.
- How did he end up here?
- Come here, don't move.
I'm helping someone
take care of him for a while.
Don't move. Be good.
Come on.
The water's ready.
Coming.
Let's go.
Mom.
Hui, you're back.
- Grandpa.
- Sit down, quick.
Have a piece of watermelon.
Oh my.
What a commotion.
Hui,
I'm telling you,
your dad's
just pretending to be
a good guy in front of others.
When you were little,
he never once bathed you.
That's exactly what Hongbing's mother
used to say when she was alive.
So that means
you learned it from him, right?
Ma Kai,
who gave this to you?
Dad.
Your dad gave it to you?
Then who gave it to your dad?
Mom gave it to him.
Your mom?
Where is your mom?
Dad said Mom is dead.
If your mom were dead,
how could she have given
this to your dad?
It's another mom.
Another mom?
Have you seen her?
Ma Kai,
look at me.
Have you seen this other mom?
Dad won't let me say.
So you have seen her,
right?
Where did you see her?
In Dad's car.
He pointed at a lady and said
that was Mom.
What did she look like?
She had red lipstick on
and curly hair.
What is her name?
I don't know.
Dad,
I really can't eat anymore.
Hui, hurry and take the child
to wash up.
I'm going out for a bit.
What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
What happened?
He took the necklace
my mom gave me.
He took my necklace.
Why did he take your necklace?
He said he wanted to look at it,
and then he took it.
I hadn't even agreed yet.
Alright.
Don't cry.
Tomorrow,
I will help you get it back, okay?
Okay.
Come on, let me help you wash up.
Tell me,
what's your name?
Ma Kai.
What?
What's your dad's name?
Ma Heping.
Ma Kai,
what did the uncle ask you just now?
He asked who my mom is.
Then, who is your mom?
I don't know!
Why does everyone
keep asking about my mom?
My necklace is gone!
- Chief Liu.
- Who is it?
It's me.
Coming.
Director Chen.
Chief Liu.
Take a look at this.
I found it on Ma Heping's son.
This is not the same one
as the one we saw
at the body-burning homicide scene.
I think
this is another piece from the same set.
Who gave it to him?
The child said
Ma Heping brought it home.
He said his mother gave it to him.
It's the woman from the motorcycle shop
who won the prize draw.
That's what I thought too.
But the child
couldn't clearly describe
what the woman looks like.
So I was thinking
of discussing it with you.
Can we bring Ma Heping in
for questioning immediately?
Wait for me. I'll get my coat.
Alright.
(Interrogation Room 2)
Where did this come from?
Answer.
I picked it up.
Ma Kai said
his mother gave it to him.
That was just to comfort the child.
He's too young to understand anything.
He keeps crying for his mother.
Listen carefully.
This item, no one here
has reported losing it,
and no one in the city has either.
Tell me where you picked it up.
Where did you pick it up?
Did you pick it up out of town?
Speak!
Where did it come from?
I picked it up.
I really picked it up.
Ma Heping,
this set of commemorative coins
is connected to a homicide case.
If you explain this clearly,
it will count as
a major meritorious contribution.
You could also go home sooner
and see your son.
I picked it up.
Don't you want to go home anymore?
(Yingxiong Roller Skating Rink)
Songge.
Songge!
Song...
Songge.
Huo Kaiming, what are you trying to do?
Just like you said,
I wiped off all the fingerprints.
Where is the person I want?
I've already found
the person you want for you.
We can talk this through.
Let Songge go first.
I'm not here to negotiate with you.
I've already killed someone for you.
You owe me a life.
If you can't hand the person over,
I'll take hers instead.
But I've found the person.
I've already tracked them down.
Where?
Who is it?
All along,
there has only been one person
who lost our bottles,
and his name is
Ma Heping.
Ma Heping, the one
who cooks at Huang Liang's pit?
Yes.
That's him.
I know him.
He's just a coward.
He doesn't have
the nerve to kill anyone.
I know, I know him too.
But he's the only one
who lost the bottles.
If you don't believe me,
I can show you the records.
Alright.
Take me to him now.
He...
He was taken by the police.
Are you playing me, Chen Hui?
Playing me again?
I trusted you again and again,
and you lied to me every time!
Do you really think
I wouldn't dare kill?
Mr. Huo,
calm down.
Calm down.
Think about it.
I believe Ma Heping
will confess very soon.
Once the police catch her,
she's finished.
That would still count
as revenge for you.
No!
You must find her
before your father does.
I've ended up like this
because of people like you.
I will kill all of you myself!
Speak.
When can you find her?
Three days. Give me three days.
I will bring the person to you.
No.
How many days?
- How many days?
- One day.
One day!
One day.
Alright.
By this time tomorrow,
if you don't bring her,
both of you
will be buried with me.
Master,
this Ma Heping,
could he be the killer
in the body-burning homicide?
Do you think so?
Chief Liu and I
both believe he is not.
Then why does he refuse
to say a single word about where
the commemorative coin came from?
Whether he says it or not,
as long as we find the evidence,
we can convict him.
Chief Liu,
let me ask you something.
When you encounter
someone like this
who refuses to confess,
how do you usually handle it?
Step up the interrogation
and find the weak point
in his mental defenses.
Then why didn't we
keep questioning him earlier?
Ask Director Chen.
When it comes to Fengyang,
he knows it best.
Chief Liu, you're being modest.
Master, teach me.
Ever since we brought in Ma Heping,
he has been completely cooperative
about the cough syrup.
But when it comes
to the commemorative coin,
he refuses to say a word.
Why is that?
Because he's protecting someone.
A man like Ma Heping
is usually quiet and submissive.
He has lived that way
for most of his life.
If you glare at him,
he would not even dare look back.
But with people like him,
once they decide to stand their ground,
it means they are prepared
to never give in.
So,
Limin,
what we need to do now
is secure solid evidence
and find a way
to make him talk.
Most importantly,
we need to identify
the person he is protecting.
Master, this place doesn't look like
a woman has ever lived here.
Look more carefully.
Ma Heping
is keeping his mouth shut tight,
which means his relationship
with that woman
is far from ordinary.
We are bound to find some clue.
(Ding Yue Clinic)
Ma Kai,
stop playing for now.
Let me treat the patient first,
then you can play.
It's nothing serious.
Try to drink less,
go to bed earlier,
and don't stay up so late.
Alright.
Thank you, Dr. Ding.
You're welcome.
Mom.
What brings you here?
We were worried
the child might trouble you here.
Since we had nothing to do,
we thought we'd take him
to the roller skating rink for a bit.
Sure.
Go ahead.
Ma Kai.
Hui,
you
don't look well.
I probably didn't sleep well last night.
Mom, what time did Dad leave this morning?
This morning?
A little after seven, I think.
Mrs. Chen,
we'll take the child and head out first.
Alright, go on.
Okay.
Let's go, Ma Kai.
Hui,
bring
the child back earlier this afternoon.
People from the Civil Affairs Bureau
will be here tomorrow
to take him to the welfare home.
I want to take him
to buy a couple of outfits.
I can go instead.
I'm free anyway.
Alright.
You're just like me,
soft-hearted.
Get some rest.
Got it, Mom. I'm heading out.
Go on.
Let's go, Ma Kai.
I'll take you to buy some candy.
Ma Kai,
my mom just told me
that people from the Civil Affairs Bureau
will come tomorrow to take you away.
Is that a place for orphans?
Yes.
I don't want to go.
I don't want to go!
I have a mom and dad.
I'm not an orphan.
It's okay.
I know.
I know. Don't cry.
There are lots of children there.
I'm not an orphan.
I don't want to go.
- I know.
- Ma Kai,
I know you're not an orphan.
Don't you have a mom?
We'll take you to your mom,
and then you won't have
to go to the welfare home.
But
I don't know where my mom is.
Then what do you remember?
Tell me.
I might recognize it.
I only remember
there is a drink shop
across from my mom's place.
Last time I wanted a drink,
Mom bought me a bottle.
If you see her,
will you recognize her?
Yes.
Ma Kai,
I'll take you around first.
If you recognize her,
tell me right away, alright?
Okay.
Let me see.
Don't cry now.
There aren't that many
drink shops in Fengyang.
We will find her.
Hongbing,
what's going on?
Director Tong,
Ma Heping's son
also had a commemorative coin on him.
With the one from Beimianling
that the victim was carrying,
they complete the set.
The child said
a woman gave it to his father.
But Ma Heping denies it.
So
we brought back
all his belongings
to see if we could find
any clues related to that woman.
Any new findings?
Not so far.
Keep looking.
Thanks for the hard work.
Mom.
(China Welfare Lottery)
Kid,
can't find your mom?
Sorry, he got the wrong person.
Chief Liu.
- What's wrong?
- Look.
A lottery ticket.
From October 2.
Look at the time it was printed.
3:10 AM.
What lottery shop
would be open at that hour?
Limin,
go
check which lottery shop it was.
Find the exact
address.
Got it.
Everyone, keep checking.
See if there are any other clues.
China Welfare Lottery, right?
Fengyang Police Station.
Help me check
the address of a lottery shop.
Hui.
Songge.
Mr. Xing,
I brought over
the Terra-Cotta Warrior
costume you wanted.
It should be over there.
It will look...
Mr. Xing, we have something to do.
- Songge.
- My mom is over there.
Make sure you come take photos.
Master,
we found it.
(No. 9-16, Guanghui Road, Fengyang Town)
I know who it is.
Hui,
over there.
That's my mom's place.
(China Welfare Lottery)
Wait.
Mom.
I want to go find my mom.
Let go of me!
Let go.
(Yingxiong Roller Skating Rink)
By this time tomorrow,
if you don't bring her,
both of you
will be buried with me.
I'll kill you right now,
believe it or not.
I'll kill you, believe it or not!
How dare you lie to me?
I can take your life anytime.
I'll go cook.
You should change your clothes first.
Where's my notebook?
Where did my cooking notebook go?
Where is it?
Chen Hui, what are you looking for?
Where's my notebook?
Chen Hui, do you want me
to help you look?
Where is it?
Where's my notebook?
I can't even find a notebook.
I'm useless.
Chen Hui,
Who can I protect?
I'm useless.
Useless!
Who can I still protect?
Chen Hui.
Calm down, please.
Chen Hui, don't do this.
Don't hurt yourself.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
Don't do this.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Songge.
I scared you.
No.
Chen Hui,
I'm the one who should be sorry.
It's all because of me
that things turned out like this.
Songge,
let's go take the photos tomorrow.
Okay.
(Shiguang Photo Studio)
(Glycerol)
Does it look good?
Yes.
Come on.
Alright.
Change your pose.
Come on.
You two look great together.
This setup works.
I'll switch to another one.
Okay.
Come, give it to me.