You dare mess with my boy, asshole?
Who the hell is your boy?
Right here—he's mine.
Get in the car.
Ouch!
You started it first.
How was I supposed to know that guy already had a boyfriend?
Next time, open your damn eyes and look properly.
What now? Tried to beat me, huh?
All you got was a kick in return.
Can you stop complaining already?
If you keep nagging, then stay out of it.
I’m leaving.
Why did you suddenly decide to help me?
When I got punched, I saw you just standing there doing nothing.
It’s good for you to get some sense knocked in.
So you’ll know to listen when an adult speaks.
When did you told me?
I told you your kissing sucks, which means you shouldn’t be kissing anyone yet.
Since you don’t listen, better let you taste some kicks instead.
I only stepped in because that bastard was out to kill you.
I don’t even have clothes for your funeral.
You kiss like crap, you know?
Was I really that bad?
From what I saw—yeah.
Why?
Are you that bothered?
If you think kissing is just putting your mouth over someone else's and sucking like a starving
suckerfish, then yeah, it’s terrible.
I’m so embarrassed.
Want me to teach you how to kiss?
Sure. Why not?
Didn’t you say you already used what I taught you on someone else?
Stop talking so much. Are we starting or not?
No. Not right now.
Why not?
It’s just a kiss, right?
Your breath smells like alcohol and you’ve got blood on you—totally kills the mood.
Go take a shower first.
Where are you rushing off to, Jun?
You seriously forgot everything I taught you?
Who could remember all that?
Then how do you usually do it?
Show me.
That’s it?
I just don’t want to use my tongue.
Why not?
Because when I use my tongue, you get turned on.
And if you don’t use your tongue, how are you going to arouse someone?
If you can make me feel something without that, then you’ll prove me wrong, Jun.
You have to take it slow. Don’t rush.
Was it really that bad?
Don’t worry.
I’ll teach you. You’ll be amazing after I’m done.
Have you ever done this kind of thing with anyone else?
What do you mean?
Like this... the way you're helping me...
Just remember—you’re my student, Jun.
Huh?
Until I finish training you, don’t you go doing this with anyone else, okay?
So I’m really your student?
I’m serious.
Fine, alright.
I’ll master it then use it all at once—flawlessly.
So they’ll fall head over heels.
Hey, you can’t tell anyone about this. Seriously, don’t tell a soul.
Have I ever broken a promise to you?
No, but you love to mess with me.
Well, you’re just too fun to tease.
Ugh, what should I do with you?
You really sleep like you’re ruling the world—just like your dad said you would.
Sure, my place is near the office, but that doesn’t mean you get to sleep in like a log.
Hurry up. I’ll be late for work.
Why do you keep nagging?
And why didn’t you wear the shirt I hung up for you?
Didn’t want to.
Why?
Because people might realize it’s yours.
Student uniforms may look the same, but your smell... not so much.
That’s not funny.
Spit it out. What are you holding it in for—waiting for your dad?
I was savoring it.
You wanna recover faster or not?
Yeah.
Let me kiss you.
Whoa, what are you saying?
Give me your LINE.
I gave it to you before but you never added me.
Not giving it now.
Last time you weren’t around. Now you are.
So we can talk about steamy stuff at night.
What are you on about?
I’m hurt, you know.
Just sit down.
You’re always being so suggestive.
And about what I asked you to teach—it was just for that.
Not to satisfy your urges.
I was just messing with you—unless you actually want me to.
Maybe I do.
Give me your LINE—just LINE.
I’m not robbing you or anything.
Why do you have three and I only get two?
That’s it.
Ugh, I’m so full.
What?
For snacking during the day.
Thanks.
Hey, what’s up, Win?
You disappeared, bastard. How many rounds did you finish?
I’m heading to the office.
That’s a dodge. Not answering means something happened...
You’re silent now, huh? Jun, I’m telling Tai you’ve gone wild.
Yeah, I’ve been wild for a while now. Go ahead, tell him.
I heard there was a fight at the club last night—someone almost got stabbed. Did you see it?
Oh, and your boy Pop or whatever was with another guy too.
So... did you get someone new?
Yeah, I got someone new. Forget about Pop.
Dude, I’m telling you—it was a whole new experience. I met him by the bathroom.
So damn good. First time I’ve felt this way.
I’m just worried you’ll mess with the wrong person and get yourself killed before graduation.
Why are you so worried about me?
I feel bad for your dad and your sister.
Damn you.
For stuff like this, talk to Hia Sorn. That guy’s a pro.
Everyone says his moves in bed are unmatched.
Anyway, I gotta get to work. We’ll talk later.
What’s spicy-hot now?
The sausage just now—he asked what I ate.
Right, whatever.
So how was last night? Did Jun tell you what happened?
Nope, he said it wasn’t that Pop guy.
But he found someone new—outside the bathroom.
I really worry about him. He’s not as hardened as Sorn.
Why’s that?
Back when Sorn was abroad, he changed partners constantly.
Almost got his ass beat so many times.
No joke. Lucky for him, he’s good at dodging trouble.
Man, I really wanna be his student.
Win!
Just kidding, Hia. Like I’d actually dare.
Don’t let me catch you, though.
When did I say you could eat that?
During the day.
And what time is it now?
Still the day!
You’re not gonna thank me for last night?
Already claiming that? You helped me once, that’s it.
But you finished twice.
Sorn, you jerk.
Watch how you call me. I’ll smack that mouth of yours.
Alright, thanks for the help.
Do you have a mask in your car? I forgot my lip is busted.
It’s in the back. Grab it.
What’s with you?
Isn’t Win tired? Driving between your house and the factory every day?
Probably. He’s always complaining about it.
He should rent a condo near the factory. Better to rest than waste time driving.
Exactly. It’s risky to drive when you’re exhausted.
Yeah.
Hey, that’s Jun. Why’s he with Sorn? Don’t they not get along?
Yeah, I gotta go ask.
Why are you with Jun?
Saw him get off a bus and walking alone. Felt bad, so I picked him up.
Jun, why are you wearing a mask? Are you sick?
Yeah.
You okay, Jun? If not, just say so—I’ll write you a sick leave.
Do you have a fever?
Why’re you blocking me? Let me check on him.
I asked him already. He said he’s sick.
Then what’re you doing just standing here, Jun? Get inside! You won’t pass the internship like this!
Pae, Aei—I’m coming too.
I’ll head in first, Hia. See you.
So you’re not picking on the kid anymore?
Nope. Let him stop acting like a kid first—then I’ll treat him better.
Go to work.
Hey P’ Phut, good morning.
Yeah, morning.
What’s wrong with you? Why are you wearing a mask?
I’m not feeling well. Don’t want to spread anything to others.
Why’re you here so early today?
Had some errands to run, so I left home early.
Those errands wouldn’t happen to involve that fingerprint on your face? That hurt?
Hurt like hell.
Still not as bad as getting dumped.
Hey, you can’t cry here. People will see.
I really loved her, you know? But no matter what I said, she never listened.
Alright, let me ask you one thing.
That person you’re talking about… is it the one you kissed by the fire escape?
You saw that!?
Don’t worry, I just happened to see it. Wasn’t snooping.
Alright, just don’t tell anyone.
Their name’s Vee.
And yeah… I cheated before.
But I’ve stopped now. For real.
You believe me, right?
Yeah, I do.
What should I do now?
Honestly, I don’t know either.
Help me out, will you?
Hold on, just a sec.
“You done talking to Phut yet?”
I gotta go now. Work’s piling up.
Hey, don’t leave yet. And thanks—for listening to me.
But… please don’t tell anyone, yeah?
Okay, I won’t. But you better sort yourself out.
No one meant for it to end like that.
Keep this between us, alright?
Jun, stay quiet about it, okay?
What were you talking to Phut about for so long?
Well, hey...
Someone’s going to notice those marks.
I just wanted to check your wound.
Why keep checking? You already saw it earlier.
Fine then. Get to work.
You’re here as an intern but always slacking off. I swear I’ll—
Old man, stop whining so much.
Why do kids always slack off these days?
Exactly. Slackers! Bleh!
I’m going.
Jun.
What now?
Come kiss me.
What the hell!?
What kind of crap are you saying!?
If you want to be an expert, you gotta practice often.
No. It’s work hours.
No one’s watching.
Yeah yeah, just pretend it’s practice.
I’m going to work.
“Why didn’t you come down for lunch?”
“How’d you know?”
“Because I’m smart.”
“Still working. I’ll go down later.”
“What do you want to eat?”
“Noodles.”
Why’d we come out in this heat? Why not just order delivery?
Because the Tokyo place I wanted doesn’t deliver.
It’s tough being your senior.
That’s Jae Tai and Jae Champ. Should we go say hi?
So what exactly do you want to eat?
Anything’s fine. Up to you. What do you want?
We’re standing in front of a chicken rice place. You want me to get basil pork or what?
Then just get chicken rice.
James said this place is pretty good.
“Pretty good” equals...?
Equals good, obviously.
Whoa, calm down. I was just teasing.
So are we eating or not?
Yes, we’re eating!
Alright then, let’s go. Don’t take your hangry out on me.
Hey Jun, getting a coffee too?
Yeah.
Don’t forget to add a little heart for me.
Geez, always teasing.
What’s a little flirting gonna hurt?
Hey, look over there.
You think P’ Sorn’s really seeing her?
Of course. Look at how tight they are.
They’re practically glued to each other these days.
To get in bed with P’ Sorn, you’ve got to be hot, pretty, and have a killer body.
If you’re not top-notch, there’s no way he’d sleep with you.
Alright, alright, back to work!
Come on, hurry up!
Hey! You eating or what?
What’s wrong with you?
This is like... an indirect kiss between you and me, huh?
You asshole.
What the hell are you even saying? Just eat already.
Hey Jun, your documents are done. I took care of it.
Thanks.
Delivery here!
Sorry!
It’s alright.
Just be careful next time, or you’ll crush everything.
Hello, food delivery.
Thanks!
Everything’s here.
Get together already. Just don’t break up, alright?
Ugh, my back hurts.
Hey guys.
You look wiped out.
Starving like hell.
Wanna hit convenient store? Fastest option. I’m craving snacks too.
Yeah, looks like we’ll have to.
I’m starving to death. Haven’t eaten since lunch.
If you’re that hungry, why didn’t you go grab something downstairs?
Still replying to emails.
Same here. Been running between the meeting room and the copy room all day.
Stop complaining or you’ll get fired.
Being an intern is so damn exhausting.
Hi, P’Penny.
Hello!
Hi there! What are you all up to?
We’re heading to get food with Jun. He hasn’t eaten since noon.
Alright then, enjoy. Just don’t come back too late.
Got it!
Let’s go
Let’s go?
Jun!
Why do you look so down?
I’m just hungry...
Okay, Let’s go!
I’m very hungry
Sorry, Jun. You’re soaked.
Thanks... for the umbrella.
No worries. It’s nothing.
Ooh my god, Jun’s actually kinda hot, huh?
Not even half as hot as me though, right?
We’re equal, bro.
Jun, you’re soaking wet. This ain’t “a little damp.”
What the hell did you do? You look like a drowned puppy.
What, does your convenient store have a leaky roof or something?
And you, Korn—how about finishing that task as fast as your eyes chase guys?
Well, P’ Sorn, Jun’s this hot—how could I not look?
Jun’s all wet—want me to help dry him off?
Great job drying, P’ Korn.
Korn!
I’ll get back to work, okay?
Let’s go, Phut, Aei, Pae. Follow me.
I’ll take you to dry—oops! I mean, get to work!
Bye for now~
Hey, let me have some too.
Here, take this shirt.
And this one’s for the office. It’s cold in there.
Thanks, Hia.
You done with your own work? Then quit poking into my brother’s business and get to yours.
You overthink too much.
I’m not messing with your brother, alright?
I need to piss—I swear I’ll do it in a bottle right here.
Dude, chill.
P’ Sorn, pass the shirt.
Why the hell did you let yourself get this soaked?
Lunch break was already over.
Wait, you really haven’t eaten since noon?
Why do you care? Just give it.
Answer me.
Why do you even care? It’s none of your business.
I never said I was gonna buy it for you.
Well, I wasn’t counting on you either.
There’s too much work. No time to eat.
I’ll treat you to dinner tonight to make it up—so stop sulking.
Who’s sulking? I’m not mad at you.
Then what’s with that sour face and pouty lips?
Why are you always touching my lips? God knows where those hands have been.
On you, obviously.
P’ Sorn, you jerk.
Why do you always slap “jerk” in front of my name? Learn to show me some respect, like Tai and Champ do.
Then act like someone worthy of respect! You always tease and take advantage.
Take advantage? I told you—more kisses equals more practice.
Aren’t we kissing too often? My lips are going numb. Once a day is enough.
If we do it too much, I’ll get bored of you.
And if I end up using these skills on someone else, won’t it go dull?
On who?
Why are you raising your voice?
You just said you’d use it on someone else. I told you—don’t.
Or you’ll embarrass yourself out there.
If you haven’t finished training, I’m not letting you go flirt with others.
I was just joking. Why so serious?
Even joking—don’t. I don’t like it.
And tonight—wait for me at the car after work. Don’t forget.
Oh hey, Jun.
Where’ve you been? Hey, I brought donuts for you.
Donuts may have holes, but my care for you is whole—P’ Korn’s always here ❤️
Thanks.
Dude, I’m blushing.
Hey Jun, what happened to your face?
Oh no! What happened? Does it hurt?
Let me see.
It’s nothing, Hia.
Don’t lie to me.
What did you do? Does it hurt?
It’s just...
Let’s go to Police station with me —now.
It’s fine, Hia. Just a small wound—it’ll heal soon.
Small or not, you still have to report it.
Was he trying to kill you or what?
What’s with Sorn? He knew about this and didn’t tell me?
Sorn! Come here.
You, get back to work upstairs. I’ll handle this.
So you knew about this?
You didn’t think to tell me? You disappeared yesterday—got into a fight, didn’t you?
What if something had happened to Jun? Could you take responsibility?
Calm down, will you? What are you getting so worked up for?
It’s over now. I helped your boy, didn’t I?
He didn’t get gutted. He’s back at work, safe and sound.
Are you two... something?
It’s Sorn—last night Jun got into a fight at the club. Sorn knew, but didn’t say a word to me.
Whoa, really? Is he okay?
Jun’s still just a kid.
But he’s not a toddler anymore. He’s got his own life to live.
Let him learn things on his own a bit.
But his dad entrusted him to me!
Don’t you trust me to look after him?
If you look after him, you’ll just keep teasing him. He’ll end up hating you.
I’m not that much of a jerk, am I?
Sorn...
You’re a jerk.
You asshole.
Once you’re done, send it to me.
Got it. See you.
Bye.
You done?
I’m staying at the condo tonight.
Why?
Because I have to be at the factory tomorrow.
Oh right, I forgot.
How you getting back?
Probably just take a taxi.
A taxi? Nah, I’ll give you a ride. Easier that way.
You’ll be dead tired driving around like that and get home super late.
Don’t worry, I’m off tomorrow. I’ll drop you off. Chill.
Alright, up to you.
You act like a total sneak, you know that?
I just don’t wanna deal with Hia Champ and Hia Tai’s questions.
Why’s that?
You and I don’t get along, yet we’re hanging out—don’t you think that’s weird?
If they start asking questions, ugh, I’m too lazy to answer.
So what are you gonna say if they ask?
I dunno. Haven’t thought about it.
Just tell them you’re my boy. If you’re mine, you’ve got nothing to worry about.
If they have questions, they can come ask me directly.
You’re just spouting nonsense.
Hey, what are you doing?
It’s hot! Hia Tai gave me two shirts, I’m wearing the short-sleeve one.
Asshole
Cheers?
Name’s Penny.
Ugh, I’m so full. I can barely walk now.
Hey, I’m just stopping to check out some clothes real quick.
Whoa, this one’s really nice!
How much?
2,500 baht.
not buying?.
It’s expensive. I need to save up. Don’t want to burden Jae Poy.
Jae Poy? Your sister, right?
Yeah.
If you like it, I’ll get it for you.
No thanks. Too pricey.
Won’t make me go broke or anything.
Don’t come collecting later—I’ve got nothing to pay you back with.
You talk too much. I’ll just shut you up with a kiss.
Here you go, customer. Thank you!
Can I grab one more?
Go ahead, but I’m not paying for that one. Let’s go.
Let’s go
Jun.
Jun!
We’re here.
Thanks, bro.
Jun, don’t forget to take your meds. You still feel warm.
I’m heading out now.
“Win...”
“If someone you don’t like acts like they care about you... would your heart still skip a beat?”
“No one gets butterflies for someone they don’t like, man.”
“It only happens when you actually like them.”
Thanks a lot for the ride.
No big deal.
Wanna come up, grab a bite before heading back?
Sure, why not?
Let’s go.
This is all I’ve got—just something to fill you up for now.
It’s delicious already.
Wait... what are you doing?