I…
think I know.
Sorry?
The person who came to my place that day,
I think I know who it was.
Yes, Young-bin.
What?
Mr. Choi, can you hear me?
If you can, blink once.
- Jae-hee!
- Jae-hee.
Are you starting to come around?
Jae-hee.
La-ik.
Yes.
Why am I here?
Where's Hye-joo?
I'm sorry,
but the patient needs rest.
Please step outside.
Why would he ask for Hye-joo?
What happened that night?
Yeah, what happened?
Do you know something?
It's a relief that Jae-hee woke up.
About that accessory,
that…
was something Hye-joo and I got together.
What's this?
These are our matching piercings.
Cute, right?
So beautiful.
I worked so hard to get these!
She ordered them herself.
I heard only two existed
in the whole country.
Let's wear these every day.
When we broke up,
I took mine off and locked it in my safe.
Then the one the police seized
wasn't yours.
We can't be certain yet, but…
if Hye-joo entered your house that night,
it could be connected
to the door-lock sound we heard.
La-ik.
I think we should tell the police.
Yeah. We have to.
I don't have time to waver now.
We came this far
to find the truth.
It's late. You should go in.
Go ahead.
Okay. Get home safe.
Bye.
Yes, Chung-jae.
If you're still up,
could you come down for a minute?
There's something I want to show you.
What is it?
You told me to check
with the residents last time,
so I looked into it.
Turns out the first floor
is pretty close to the garden.
And I remembered Jae-hee
saying he heard something outside.
So I kept digging.
I found a house with a security camera
facing that direction.
So I pulled the footage.
Did you see it? This part.
If that's a person, it's weird
they're walking around
in heavy rain with no umbrella.
Comparing with the structure beside them,
height is maybe low-160s.
Pretty small build.
If it's a man, he's very small.
And if it's a woman?
Hye-joo may have been
at La-ik's house that night.
Hye-joo?
But didn't she say
she met La-ik outside that night?
And earlier, when Jae-hee woke up,
the first person he asked for was Hye-joo.
It's not definitive yet,
but this could also
be circumstantial evidence.
Given everything, I'll dig further.
Thank you.
I just don't like him, okay?
La-ik needs to be cleared fast
so he can disappear from your life.
Then maybe I can…
What?
Anyway, I'll tell you if I find more.
I backed up the footage.
Share it with the investigation team.
We actually thought it was strange too,
the way he asked for Hye-joo
the moment he woke up.
And with this footage
and the accessory you found,
we should look into that angle.
But Prosecutor Kwak
is still insisting on indicting La-ik.
He says Jae-hee's statement alone
isn't enough to change the suspect.
And even if Hye-joo
is connected to Jae-hee's case,
it doesn't directly tie her
to Woo-seong's murder.
But wasn't Do La-ik indicted
because he believed
La-ik was involved in Jae-hee's case?
Exactly.
But…
Prosecutor Kwak keeps pushing
this forced indictment.
No idea if it's pride or what,
but he won't back down.
Excuse me.
Hello.
Jae-hee?
Yeah.
You're here.
Where's Choi Jae-hee?
He's waiting for you inside.
He keeps insisting
he'll only give his statement to you.
Open the door.
CHOI JAE-HEE
It's just…
I don't really remember
what happened.
I don't even know
why I woke up here.
So please, just leave me alone.
That night…
Stop coming after me!
After I hung up with Director Geum,
Hye-joo contacted me.
Out of nowhere, she wanted to meet me.
It's been a while.
Three years?
Yeah. I got back to Korea not long ago.
But what's going on?
Woo-seong's death was shocking enough.
Then you and La-ik.
It's all over the news.
I was really worried.
Are you okay?
What happened?
What's going on?
Tell me.
It's complicated.
I don't know what's going on either.
Is that why you came out here?
This place is near
where you guys had your first show.
Right.
I just really missed Woo-seong.
And I didn't have anywhere else to go.
The prosecutors keep treating me
like I'm the culprit.
That's ridiculous.
There's no way.
You're too soft-hearted for that.
But still, it feels like
everyone suspects me.
I'm really not.
I know. You'd never do it.
But that night, you went to La-ik's place.
I think that's
why people are misunderstanding.
But it will clear up.
They'll see you're innocent.
How do you know
that I went to his place that night?
What do you mean? It was on the news.
The news?
Of course. How else would I know?
Jae-hee.
You probably haven't eaten, right?
Let's get dinner.
Okay.
You go first, I'll follow.
Let's get something nice.
I'll treat you.
Something felt wrong…
that night.
Woo-seong said
he was going to meet La-ik,
so I waited at the hospital.
STILL TALKING?
But he never called, so…
I went by La-ik's place for a moment.
Woo-seong!
But I never told anyone that.
I was afraid people would suspect me.
But I'm not sure how Hye-joo knows that.
I'm in a situation, and I need some help.
Yeah, so…
Aren't you leaving?
I'll go.
After that,
I don't remember anything.
But thinking about it,
the fact that she suddenly asked to meet,
me waking up here afterward,
none of it makes sense.
Prosecutor,
do you know why I'm telling you all this?
You once told me
that even if someone's innocent,
everything depends
on how you choose to see it.
There is no such thing
as an absolute truth.
The truth is always relative.
Depending on your perspective,
it can change.
You said there's no absolute truth.
But you're wrong.
Truth is singular.
And I never wrote a suicide note.
I never attempted suicide.
That is the truth.
So please,
look at what's real.
Don't turn innocent people…
into criminals.
I looked into Hong Hye-joo.
It's not directly related to the case,
but I think you should see this.
PATIENT MARKED EMOTIONALLY UNSTABLE
Yes, La-ik.
I'm at the hospital right now.
The police and the prosecutor are here,
so I wanted to check if you knew.
I heard that
at the police station earlier.
They said he's giving his statement now.
Since I'm involved in the case,
I guess I'm not allowed to see him.
But Young-bin's here,
so I thought I'd check in on him.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
But…
if Hye-joo really has
something to do with Jae-hee,
shouldn't we tell the prosecution?
She said she was leaving the country soon.
Young-bin's here.
I'll call you back later.
Okay. Call me later.
MEDICAL REPORT
The doctor said
we don't have to worry too much.
He's fully conscious now,
and he's slowly recovering.
I'm sorry.
Why would you be sorry?
I just…
feel like all of this is my fault.
I've done nothing but hurt you guys.
I had no idea how hard it was for Jae-hee
or what you all were going through.
Not knowing any of that.
Don't say that.
We didn't understand
what you were feeling either.
And Jae-hee's probably feeling
sorry toward you too, deep down.
But seriously, what did happen that night?
If only we had Woo-seong's phone…
He used to record everything out of habit.
If anything was saved on there,
we'd finally know the truth.
Prosecutor,
I've told you everything I know.
Please investigate
Hong Hye-joo properly,
so the truth can come out.
Sir.
Attorney Maeng Se-na is here.
This is all circumstantial.
Nothing here objectively proves anything.
- It's just speculation…
- I heard you met Jae-hee.
He testified that he met
Hong Hye-joo right before the accident.
And these,
the sound from the last call
between Director Geum and Woo-seong,
the silhouette caught near the scene,
the trace evidence,
and this piercing…
don't these strike you as strange?
Not to me. I don't see anything unusual.
No. You do know.
You know the path you're choosing
might be the wrong one.
If the truth gets buried like this,
someone innocent will live
their whole life carrying a crime.
And I…
I know exactly what that life is.
A life where all you can do…
is endure.
Byung-gyun.
Can you…
really live with yourself
after pushing someone
into that kind of misery?
Can you carry that weight
for the rest of your life?
Hye-joo is leaving the country soon.
We don't have much time.
Kwak Byung-gyun.
You…
don't have to live the way
your father did.
MEDICAL REPORT
Woo-seong used to record
everything out of habit.
If anything was saved on there,
we'd finally know the truth.
I'm leaving now.
Take care.
MEDICAL REPORT
Byung-gyun, you know
I once dealt with something a lot like
what you're facing now.
There was a suspect.
No hard evidence, but a damn clear motive.
But he wouldn't confess.
No matter how hard we pressed,
he kept claiming he was innocent.
And then one day…
that guy…
went and hung himself in prison.
Hey, wasn't that girl so pretty?
- Come on.
- Hey.
My father is not a murderer.
- What?
- And your father knew that,
but he still drove mine off a cliff.
- What are you talking about?
- You want to be a prosecutor?
I hope you make it.
Because I want you to watch me
set everything right.
Kwak Byung-gyun.
You…
don't have to live the way
your father did.
Yes, Detective Yu. It's me.
Hello, La-ik.
I saw your text message.
Are you flying out today?
Yeah. I'm leaving in a bit.
I called because I need
to ask you one last thing.
Something to ask?
What is it?
That night…
The night Woo-seong died,
did you come to my place?
Just tell me the truth.
Were you at my place?
No. I wasn't.
I don't know what you heard
or who said what,
but just remember this.
Whatever people are saying,
none of it is true.
You know that, right?
Hong Hye-joo!
I couldn't reach you at all,
I got worried…
What's wrong? Did something happen?
No.
I just…
missed you so much.
And then you showed up.
That's all.
What's wrong?
You said you'd call me back,
but then you wouldn't answer.
You were on the phone the whole time.
Come in.
There's something I want to show you.
So you're saying Woo-seong's phone
might have been automatically synced
with this cloud storage?
Woo-seong used to record everything.
And the more I thought about it,
if someone took his phone,
maybe there was something on it.
So I've been trying to get into this. But…
WRONG PASSWORD
I can't crack his password.
I thought I knew him better than anyone,
so I tried everything I could think of.
But nothing works.
I told you to answer clearly!
Where exactly were you on the night
Choi Jae-hee had the accident?
I already told you.
I attended a company event
and went straight home.
You can check the CCTV.
Oh, right.
Did you fail to secure that?
We secured something better than CCTV.
Choi Jae-hee's statement.
He woke up.
Yesterday.
Did he?
That's good to hear.
According to him,
he met you that night,
right before the crash.
And…
these.
A figure passing near the scene
whose build matches yours.
A piercing found at the site
that belongs to you.
All of this is pointing straight at you.
How do you explain that?
Are you shaken by that kind of evidence?
- What?
- Jae-hee named me
because he knows I gave a statement
that wasn't in his favor.
And that piercing?
I gave it to La-ik myself that night.
We argued, and I was furious.
Prosecutor…
I didn't do it.
And honestly…
you're better off if I'm not the culprit.
Wouldn't you agree?
Wow, she's no ordinary one.
If we could get a confession,
we might get something.
What do you think you're doing?
Release Hye-joo. Right now.
I can't do that.
She's a prime suspect.
And we have evidence.
It's not decisive evidence!
I told you.
Cases aren't won with evidence.
They're won by pushing through with power.
Release her immediately--
Father.
Is this how you've lived your entire life?
Suppressing the truth with force?
Then teach me.
Teach me how to pretend
I don't see the truth.
How to look the truth in the eye
and still act like I know nothing.
Please teach me.
She will be released soon.
There weren't even enough grounds
for an emergency arrest.
What you're doing isn't an investigation,
it's a tantrum.
And no matter what it takes,
I will stop
this stupid mistake you're making.
So you're saying you'd block your own son
if it meant protecting your success.
I see. Thank you.
That last little bit of doubt I had,
you just erased it completely.
What?
You walk your path, Father.
And from here on, I'm going to walk mine.
And I'll fight you.
For the first time in my life.
KANG WOO-SEONG
The secret in Woo-seong's song.
Do you know where that post about
Woo-seong's hidden secret is?
LIKE
Like, can I ask you one thing?
Hey! Why'd you disappear?
You even deleted your account!
What's going on?
I'm sorry.
Sorry to bother you out of nowhere,
but about that hidden message you said
was in Woo-seong's song,
can you tell me more about it?
Oh, that?
It's only in the album.
The album?
Yeah, it's only on the CD.
Yes, La-ik, can you come over
for a moment?
I think I might've found something.
Yes.
My friend said
Woo-seong hid a secret message
in one of the songs he composed.
- A message?
- Yes.
It's not in the streaming version.
You can find it if you listen to the CD.
If you pay attention,
there are tracks where a high-frequency
tone repeats at the end.
And when you run that tone
through a decoding app…
PLAY
…a hidden message appears.
SECOND FULL ALBUM
These are the messages I've found so far.
But these are way too long
to be passwords.
Right?
Still, I'll check every track,
just in case.
It feels kind of weird,
listening to our song like this together.
Why? It's my favorite song.
I had no idea
Woo-seong hid anything in his music.
And the fact that fans figured it out,
that's insane.
Fans want to know everything.
Even the tiniest little things.
Every shade of meaning in a lyric,
every tremble in a voice,
every look onstage.
Because all of it is him.
- Did you hear that?
- Yes.
PLAY
Aren't these album titles?
Look! The first letters.
- It's the name of the first full album!
- Right.
And here.
That's the second album, Forward.
And this one.
It's the third album, Lonely.
No, not that kind of thing.
Our next full album
is our 10th anniversary one.
We should do something really fresh.
I heard that cyberpunk is the trend.
Not that, since it's our 10th anniversary,
I want something with a message.
A message?
Like what?
It worked!
These are the files uploaded
on the day of the incident.
VOICE RECORDING
I think the time is almost the same
as the estimated time of the event.
VOICE RECORDING
Since things have turned out this way,
I'll take responsibility
for what I've done.
And no matter what it takes,
I'm going to break free from you.
Only then can we live the way we want.
- Kang Woo-seong?
- Why are you here?
What are you doing?! Why are you…
Isn't it obvious? I'm here to see La-ik.
La-ik!
He's really drunk. He's asleep right now.
La-ik.
Why are you acting like this?
Move.
You haven't changed at all.
Look who's talking.
Drinking with him, pretending to listen,
pretending to care.
You're still leeching off him, huh?
What?
La-ik!
I said stop it!
Why? Who do you think you are?
I want to see him,
who do you think you are, stopping me?
This is why I said stop, because of you!
Do you know how much he has suffered
because of you?
How much pain you put him through?
Hye-joo, you push people until they break.
No matter how much love he gives you,
you want more and more.
Because you never got any love growing up.
It's over.
And like I told you before,
he has moved on.
He doesn't love you anymore.
Hye-joo, you need to…
You…
What are you doing?
You said it's over.
Without him,
maybe it's better
if everything ends here too.
Hey!
Drop the knife! Drop it!
Woo-seong.
Woo-seong!
No, Woo-seong!
Maybe we should stop here?
Woo-seong!
CHOI JAE-HEE
La-ik.
I kind of…
expected it.
I hoped I was wrong.
If this recording is released,
the truth about you and Hye-joo
will become public too.
Are you okay with that?
No.
But I'll face it.
I'm done running.
No matter how painful the truth is,
we agreed to bring it to light.
Because that's the only thing I can do
for the people who loved me,
and for the people who loved Woo-seong.
This morning, prosecutors sought
life imprisonment
for the defendant, Ms. Hong,
who has been indicted for murder
and attempted murder.
It has been confirmed
that she is the illegitimate daughter
of Chairman Hong of the Imhwa Group.
Hong Hye-joo keeps insisting
it wasn't premeditated.
But when it comes to Choi Jae-hee,
it's pretty clear.
She'd been getting sedatives
from her hospital,
and it looks like
she slipped them to Jae-hee.
She probably wanted
to frame him as the culprit.
Thank you.
I know you were under a lot of pressure
pushing this case forward
and getting her into court.
And when I asked you for help,
you made the call before it was too late,
so we could catch the real culprit.
So, really. Thank you.
I should be the one thanking you.
Honestly,
this case tormented me the whole time.
I couldn't admit I might be wrong,
but if an innocent person
could end up paying for my mistake,
I didn't know how I'd ever live with that.
It scared me.
But thanks to you, we caught the real one.
And I'm on the news too.
I'm a hotshot prosecutor, thanks to you.
I'm sorry.
Your father's case,
I really hope the truth comes out soon.
Really.
Anyway, I've said what I needed to say.
I'm leaving. Take care.
KANG WOO-SEONG
YOUR TIME LIVES ON IN YOUR SONG
Why are you here?
Did you come to watch me fall apart?
No.
I came to ask you why.
Why did you do that?
I wanted to hear it from you.
And you think I owe you an answer?
Fine. I'll answer it.
You want to know why?
Because of you.
All of this…
is because of you.
I didn't go abroad after we broke up.
I was in a hospital.
A psych ward.
I tried to take my life more than once
after we broke up.
But…
you were smiling.
So brightly.
I just…
wanted you back.
If you hadn't pushed me away so coldly,
I never would've gone to that house.
And if Kang Woo-seong…
hadn't made such a big deal out of it,
none of this would've happened.
This is all because of you.
I hope you never forget me.
I hope you dream of me every night
and can't sleep.
I want you to hate me
and yourself…
forever.
No.
I won't waste my time hating you.
There's one thing
I could never wrap my head around.
Why did you take that knife?
If you'd just left it there,
I would've taken the fall.
It would have ended clean and easy.
So why didn't you?
If you want to say you did it
because you loved me,
I want to tell you you're wrong.
That's why I came here.
That wasn't love.
Real love is
cheering someone on
no matter where they are
or who they become. Believing in them.
Wishing them well with your whole heart.
Wanting their happiness.
ONE YEAR LATER
No, no.
To meet the Gold Boys,
who are too busy with their world tour,
I've flown all the way to New York.
Gold Boys, it's great to see you!
- Two, three.
- Hello, we're Gold Boys.
First of all, congratulations.
I heard every show on your world tour
has completely sold out,
and thanks to the overwhelming response,
the tour has even been extended.
Before we dive in, could you say
a few words to your Korean fans, Goldy,
who've been eagerly waiting for Gold Boys?
Everyone.
I hope you're all doing well.
Even when we're not there, I believe
you'll take good care of yourselves.
We're working hard so we can come back
to you as soon as possible.
So until then, make sure you eat well,
don't get sick,
and stay healthy.
I'm sorry I can't be there with you.
I miss you.
I like La-ik on stage too.
I thought I had no choice
but to not back down then.
That's why we won,
because we caught the real culprit.
Lies can't beat the truth.
As the bereaved family of Maeng Ji-yong,
I earnestly request
that you order a retrial.
Subtitle translation by: Soyeon Kim