RTNNJ
GLORY
YEONHWADANG
What a sunset.
She is enchanting.
To ste kupili mojim novcem?
No, but my own.
Would you like some?
Do you like to gamble?
Jedanput sam se kockala svojim životom.
Successfully?
I'm counting on it.
Do you live nearby?
Više sam vas puta vidio u klubu.
And you?
Not far.
Do you work close by?
Why don't you eat?
Ne jedete hranu iz trgovine?
I just watch my carb intake.
You didn't answer me.
Otherwise you have many questions?
I'm usually quiet, believe it or not.
Why do you like him?
I like it
that we fight to the death in silence.
I like it and what to win
I have to destroy houses
which the opponent carefully built.
Why don't we play together?
Now I know what you eat and how you play.
JAEPYONG BUILDING
HA DO-YEONG
My name is Ha Do-yeong.
Bring more money next time.
You won't eat this?
Is that your breakfast?
You are here every morning.
Don't you cook?
Have you eaten yet?
Work at Semyeong School?
I saw the sticker on the car.
You have a good job.
May I ask you something?
Are you the owner of Semyeong Real Estate?
I saw you there
when I was looking for an apartment.
I was there.
I realized that it was my apartment
cheaper than other apartments in the area.
Why did you do that?
Good thing it's cheap. Why do you ask?
Teachers have a small salary.
You didn't know I was a teacher then.
Sorry to ask you this,
but i have to know.
Is the apartment haunted?
Until now I thought you were
cold as stone. I prefer you like this.
Please do not leave trash here.
Take it down.
These are bills for parking, fuel
and other expenses this month.
I'm sorry. Revenge is obviously very expensive.
MONEY FOR PARKING
MONEY FOR FUEL
I taught in the 20s
so I could spend now.
I saved money. No worries.
Following them, I discovered
that Hye-jeong is the most predictable.
And he's always on his cell phone.
I could steal it from her.
I think I am very gifted...
I THINK I AM VERY GIFTED
Can you do it?
No worries.
Have you met Park Yeon-jin?
Everything went well?
Shall we meet?
You weren't scared or intimidated?
You should have killed her.
I did the latter.
That's good.
I'm proud of you.
I was worried.
Do you know Park Yeon-jin's mother?
The photo is a little blurry.
She was with the shaman again.
It goes every other week.
With that guy again.
I thought they were seeing each other
but they went separately.
And they came separately.
There must be a reason for such behavior.
Let me know if you find out.
Are you by any chance
followed this man?
Followed?
Don't follow him.
I didn't tell you that to scare you.
He's a policeman.
He was the head of the station, now he is something more.
Assistant Chief of Police
in Bukbu Province.
His colleagues are deputy governors,
and roses don't bloom for him.
How do you know?
Didn't see the soup receipts?
I took four soups
and waited in front of the agency.
When you initially threatened me,
I didn't know there was no banter with you.
Take care.
I will.
Look at me.
Let's pretend it has to do with work.
Wait, I…
What was it? are you ok
I'm sorry.
I'm good at photography
flowers and birds,
but my hands are sweating
when I photograph people.
It's okay.
One more time.
I'll try one more time.
Dear mother!
Your first Gucci shirt, Ye-sol!
Do you like grandma's gift?
"Babies don't know what they're wearing.
It will grow by next month."
Isn't it?
Please?
You live like that because you think like that.
A different beginning
leads to a different destination.
- Find a new babysitter.
-Good.
We will make a payment to your account
honorarium and other fees.
Thanks for your help.
Keep these clothes.
Let him wear it on important days.
It will remind her to try
like the day she was born.
And Do-yeong got it.
I'll take care of her.
Dear mother!
Ye-sol!
Say: "Grandma."
"Grandmother."
Ye-sol will never have to work hard
like when she was born.
How are you, Mr. Director?
Can we see each other?
Yes, now.
Miss Moon Dong-eun?
Mr. Kim recommended her.
We were in an awkward position
after Mr. Yang abruptly left…
Wait.
You're saying Dong-eun knows the director?
How is that?
I'm not sure.
Does that mean she wasn't qualified?
It's not like that.
We investigated it. He has an excellent resume.
But it is rare that someone from a public school
transferred to a private school.
I understand.
May I see her resume?
Well, you know…
We have to be careful
with personal information.
Yes, of course, I understand.
You can upload her resume,
and I'll take a look.
Is that possible?
You're doing it wrong!
You can't paint like that!
Miss Moon, cherry blossoms
it must be colored pink.
They are my flowers, I can do what I want.
My cherry blossoms are transparent.
That doesn't exist.
Miss Moon, Ye-sol is wrong, isn't he?
Seung-ae's tulips look beautiful
because they are full of color,
and Ye-sola's cherry blossoms are beautiful
because they are empty.
Both pictures are beautiful.
And now let's finish our pictures.
How much?
Cut this crap and ask for the money.
I'll give you as much as you want.
I will compensate you
for all mental and physical injuries.
You just got rich.
Shall I write you something?
"I will never appear before you again
as long as I live."
I want you to write it down and sign it.
And your mom signed it
form for you to print.
Why people like you
they are lashing out at the wrong person
when did your parents hurt you?
Don't save your reputation now.
Tell me how much you want.
Wait.
You're not doing this, are you?
to get a sincere apology?
You're about to turn 40.
You're too old for fairy tales.
That's a long time ago!
I can't do anything. Do you agree?
Yes, I don't want an apology.
Don't apologize.
I didn't waste my adolescence,
20s and 30s to apologize.
You must be punished.
By legal punishment if God is with you,
divine if he is with me.
God?
Have you now moved from fairy tales to the Holy Scriptures?
Which God?
Not my God.
You're holding my daughter hostage.
And you think God will be on your side?
As a hostage?
I?
What did I do?
Did I choke Ye-sol? She hit her chest?
She slapped?
Or did I fry it with something hot?
What did I do Ye-sol?
I tried to encourage someone
who lives in the world
where the rainbow does not have seven colors
and where it is not known when the fruit is ripe.
In my classroom, colors don't matter.
But that's why they could be
a little awkward for you.
How...
How did you find out?
I won't do anything to Ye-sol.
I can do something else.
For example, at parent meetings.
As you know, mother is not the only person
which goes to parental leave.
Don't tempt me anymore
to see what I'm ready to do
and how much I can make your life miserable.
I want you to land slowly and long.
Let's land and die together, Yeon-jin.
I'm really looking forward to it.
An interesting scene.
What is it about?
Hi, Bixby.
Call Gad.
I call Gad.
BASTARD
The person you called is not available.
Leave a message after the signal.
Has that cunt gone completely wrong?
Mr. Jeon, a package has arrived for you.
-Here?
- Yes, sir.
In this street?
Like in Avengers?
HA YE-SOL
What is this?
The secretary is really incompetent.
No one was allowed to enter.
Did you earn a lot?
I like it when you're dressed as a construction worker,
even more than when you're in a suit.
It's sexier.
Because of you, Zegna and Versace will fail.
Do-yeong, let's send Ye-sol
to school abroad?
What are you saying?
Ye-sol is only eight years old.
We'll give it to the guardians.
Mnogi se školuju vani kao djeca.
Where did that come from?
Would you like to go abroad?
Oh no.
Then it's even weirder.
Škola je blizu, ima dadilju, vozača.
Would you send her out?
Do-yeong, često si igrao golf
s direktorom Kimom, zar ne?
Možeš li srediti da ga upoznam?
Ye-sol ima novu učiteljicu.
The woman is crazy.
How crazy is she?
Dovoljno da se ravnatelj uplete?
Moraš mi reći više o tome.
Forget it. It doesn't matter.
Umorna sam, pa sam emotivna.
Ići ću na posao od mame. I'll call you.
Investigate her finances, boyfriends, family,
friends, colleagues and distant relatives.
Find out all about her.
Bravo!
Your mother turned 90 yesterday.
Moon Dong-eun. Who is she?
That's what I want you to find out.
What I know is no longer valid.
Effervescent vitamin pills?
That.
Bubbles appear
when you insert the tablet into the water.
That sound calms me down.
Why do you think that sound helps you?
to keep calm?
It sounds like the rustling of ginkgo leaves
in the breeze.
Sounds like raindrops on a go board.
When I listen to that, I feel lonely.
Kind of like that.
Tijelo ti je sve zdravije,
but your heart is lonely.
Mogao bi promijeniti svoje okruženje.
Move or go on a trip.
I'll think about it.
I have patients.
You must be a good doctor.
You're always late for our meetings.
I pay you by the hour.
It's good for you that I'm late.
You need a tomography,
but if it's so hard,
it is probably an osteoma.
It doesn't hurt me. Will I really need surgery?
You may not have symptoms now,
but you might be sore afterwards.
I understand.
If I decide to have surgery,
how long will i be in the hospital?
I'm a teacher. I arrive during the holidays?
For examinations and surgery
it will take us seven days.
- Are you a teacher?
- I did.
In which school? How do you like it?
Vlogs say that teachers are eating poorly
because they have to eat with the children.
What about the children? Are they listening to you?
Are you a parent?
I'm not, I'm not interested in children,
but what it is like to be a teacher.
What?
SHANGHAI
Did you lose weight?
I did, a little.
I told you that your weight
it must match mine.
My clothes won't fit!
- You want a bad grade?
- I'm sorry.
Give it back. The next one.
Good, Hye-jeong.
Gain weight before the next flight.
If you lose weight again...
What the hell is this?
What about the cell phone?
Is that a passenger's cell phone?
How should I know?
Ask the airport
did they find the cell phone!
Good.
You must be joking!
Seriously?
It was a cat's cough.
What else do you need? Just say it.
All the best. See you next time.
Wait a minute.
You are so cool every time.
Eat something.
I thought we'd be out.
I loved it last time. A little picnic.
This is... You know.
Something important.
"The bird breaks out of the egg.
The egg is the world."
From Raemian.
Sun-a read it.
That bird won't break through.
You boiled an egg.
And Raemian is a residential complex.
The book is Demian.
I didn't cook it. I baked it!
You can't give in to feelings
because you seek revenge?
I have a bruise there!
I'm going to get sick again.
Beloved,
don't take revenge
but give place to the wrath of God.
It is written: "My retribution is,
I will bring her back,” said the Lord.
Amen.
Let us pray and remember His words
from the Epistle to the Romans.
Let's pray.
Beloved Father, I thank You from the bottom of my heart.
You always embrace us with love,
even though we are not worthy of it.
Let us thank You again for Your mercy.
Lord, you always told us
to love our enemies.
But how many times have we tried to love them
and take care of them?
Contrary to Your word,
we hated and resented them.
We ask that you forgive us for that.
What's a rag like you doing
in such a distinguished place?
Sa-ra, I'm interested in something, so I'll ask you.
Do you believe in God?
Really?
That's sacrilege.
Repent if you don't want to be punished.
-Seriously?
-That.
Yes, I prayed
and made an agreement with God.
He agrees.
Crazy bitch, you've gone too far.
Now that we are adults, does everything hurt your dick?
How do you say that?
We are in God's house.
Just a moment.
Oh, no.
Your God is furious now.
He says you're going to hell.
Watch out!
Are you crazy? Are you high?
You do drugs. And a lot of it.
And often.
What is this fucking scumbag talking about?
I'll give you 15 days.
Fill this with money and wait for the call.
Make it dollars.
Listen.
That's a threat, you fucking bastard.
Do you know how many policemen?
comes to this church?
Has anyone ever threatened you before?
Let me go!
Shit!
I haven't even started threatening you yet.
Sa-ra.
Turn left at the intersection
at Gyodae Park.
GYODAE PARK
YEO-JEONG
Did you save my number?
I make it easy for you if you haven't.
My name is Joo Yeo-jeong.
Today will be a heat wave. How are you?
It is snowing heavily today.
Walk carefully like a baby so you don't fall.
Take care.
Did you see the sky today? It is completely clear.
I hope you are healthy.
CIALIS
FOR SEOUL JOO GENERAL HOSPITAL
JOO YEO-JEONG
BY KANG YEONG-CHEON
Yeo-jeong, you got a message.
MESSAGE FROM DONG! EUN!
My cell phone must be broken!
She answered after eight years!
Although, we met once.
And now she answered?
Maybe I was beautiful.
I get it now. Yes, I was beautiful that day.
Is Dong-eun married?
Don't read that!
Why? What does it say?
He's inviting me to the wedding? Is he getting married? For whom?
Then he gets a divorce? Or is he remarrying?
That?
She is interested in what Cialis is.
What kind of medicine is this?
DONG! EUN!
- Let's talk live. Where are you?
- What's wrong with you?
- The professor is coming.
- I can't now.
Where will you be after 7 pm?
Sorry if you're in a rush.
I had to change my schedule
after your call.
Did you play it?
I win some money here and there.
Are you still in Seoul? Or to Semyeong?
How do you know that?
You said you don't work in Semyeong "yet".
Are you there now?
I work at a school in Semyeong.
Are you close to that person?
- With the one who takes that medicine.
- I haven't yet.
So, that also falls under "not yet".
I'll say this just once.
Cialis contains tadalafil.
It has a long-lasting effect.
And?
That's convenient.
Viagra works similarly.
I know that.
Is it used for any other purpose?
What two purposes do you mean?
It might be used in another case.
Some people take it
due to altitude sickness.
From a medical point of view,
it is a drug for erectile dysfunction.
Does he live in Semyeong?
Those are different stories.
Find a guy who doesn't need pills.
As a doctor, it worries me.
As a man, it makes me think.
You're wrong, kid.
You've become rude since the last time.
How can you say I'm wrong?
But you already knew
that the pill was an excuse.
I am.
You could have looked up what Cialis is for.
On the other hand,
I didn't know what your excuse would be.
I had fun.
Although I don't know who he is,
I wondered if he was sick.
I hoped every part of his body hurt.
That's what I meant.
I wanted to apologize.
Tell?
I don't know what era you had to go through,
but I am at that time
was rude.
I'm sorry if I hurt you.
I have a question.
Why your excuse sounds
like saying goodbye to me?
Are you saying goodbye?
You're telling me to stop texting you.
But why?
You don't answer me anyway.
Am I that unattractive?
Yeah, I don't like you.
You're not my type.
Yes, exactly.
I don't know what you're doing.
I don't know why you do that.
But do it.
Do whatever you want.
But you should also see me.
I will make you happy.
There are certain moments
when you are allowed to feel something
to another person.
If that means I'm alive,
how many days do you think I am
actually lived, Yeon-jin?
Why are you smiling?
I think I'm happy now.
But Yeo-jeong…
I'm not looking for a king.
I don't need a king.
I need an executioner to join me
in my sword dance.
What?
She didn't pass out for eight seconds.
- Hit her in the plexus.
-What?
You have to hit her hard.
If he doesn't pass out, you hit poorly.
Do you know who set the record?
on an impact device?
I.
Tell me if it hurts.
I will pray for you.
Look at me.
Dong-eun, stand up.
If I miss, I'll hit you in the tits.
You invited me to tteokbokki
and a serious conversation,
but you haven't ordered yet.
Sorry! Tteokbokki,
fries and ice cream.
It's coming.
Are you eating ice cream?
- You don't cover the tattoo?
- My tattoo?
Yes, on the neck.
They don't bother me anymore because of her.
Do you remember Spanish lessons at school?
I hated Spanish.
But I got him because of your tattoo
fell in love again.
You're going! You're dumber than you look.
It's not Spanish, it's Latin.
"Memento mori."
"Remember you're going to die."
But with a pain relief patch
you covered one part.
And that's how he got the Spanish phrase.
What phrase?
IT'S BORING ME
I'm eating ice cream.
- Were you in the hospital?
- I did.
You discovered something important.
So-hee's corpse is indeed there.
You're going! I don't even know how much money I would ask for.
Who did it?
The amount depends on who killed her.
- What if I tell you?
-Tell me, who?
The rest is easy.
I will torture that person day and night.
He won't be able to eat or sleep.
I'll beat her
and hand it over to you.
I know I'm not.
Are any of them four?
Sa-ra? Did she kill her while she was high?
Yeon-jin?
She is the scariest of them all.
Hye-jeong?
She killed So-hee if she exposed her
and physical education teacher.
Jae-jun? The bastard killed So-hee
if she mentioned his eyes.
Now we are in the same mess.
Which one of them killed So-hee?
Dong-eun asked you for money? How much?
I don't know. She threw the bag
and told me to fill it.
Fuck it! The bag is huge!
- Why don't you answer me?
- When did you call me?
- Not you.
- He's talking to you.
She didn't visit you?
He doesn't want money.
I offered her money. She refused.
Why can't I get Myeong-o?
You fired him?
He won't know he's fired
because it doesn't answer me.
Neither does she.
Do you remember high school well?
How is Ye-sol?
Who is guarding her?
What exactly did we do Dong-eun?
Was it bad?
She didn't throw her bag in front of you?
Hell! She must have seen a lot of movies.
Crazy woman wants dollars!
Ye-sol is already in elementary school?
Which one? The one in Semyeong?
If he wants us to suffer,
what would you do to us?
I didn't buy her a bag.
What class is it?
Tell me where you're going
and do you want a return ticket.
I've always wanted to try this.
I didn't think I would see it.
To Vladivostok, in one direction.
I think about you all day.
Shall we meet?
Fuck off.
Do you want to see me alone? Why?
Why do you want to meet me?
Who? Son Myeong-o?
You cunt, where are you?
And Yeon-jin? Did you arrange a meeting with her?
Me...
I...
Mori.
I'm dead.
IT'S BORING ME
Subtitle translation: Davor Fröbe