Will she come?
- I don't know.
How much is this bike?
Dad bought it for me.
Sir, she is here.
Hi.
- Hi.
What is this, Joji?
You're looking really smart.
Love your outfit.
- Really?
Thank you.
Okay, enough of your shyness.
Someone might see us.
Start the bike quickly.
Shall we go?
- Let's go.
Shall I sit?
Will you ride it?
Do you remember what I said?
You didn't forget, right?
I remember it very well.
- Ride carefully.
Sir.. Compliment her dress.
Say that her dress is good.
- What?
Compliment her outfit.
- Oh..
Padma.
Your dress is beautiful.
Okay.
- Looking marvellous.
Okay, thank you. Start the bike
first. Someone might see us.
Okay, hold on tight.
Bye.
- Bye. - Bye..
I think your father is next.
- Run now. I might lash out.
How many days
will he eat by himself?
He will deal with that.
In his old days..
Will you shut up for a while?
Always talking non-stop.
If you keep talking,
I'll get really mad.
I have already given
the bike trusting you.
If anything happens to my bike..
Move.
It's good if they're happy.
Riya, I have taken many
wrong decisions in your life.
Not only that, I have
not saved you from that.
Dad, you..
Tell me, dear,
what are you thinking?
If I speak from my heart,
I will start crying.
All these days,
I have cried enough.
Correct, I am also saying the same.
You have cried enough.
Hereafter, you should not cry.
You should be happy.
As the owner of such a big resort,
I feared people might judge
my daughter being a divorcee.
That's what was on my mind.
But hereafter, only your
happiness is important to me.
Nothing else is important
to me other than you.
I am not worried about what
society and others might think.
I am telling you now.
Just divorce Deepak.
He has been so toxic!
I'm sorry, dear.
I am responsible
for everything. Sorry.
Dad, I am also sorry.
For not telling you
that I'm pregnant.
I should have told you, but..
- It's okay.
Hereafter, you should
not worry about anything.
You should believe that
I am here to take care of you.
I am there, dear. I will take
care of you and the baby.
Come with me.
No, Dad, it's okay.
What, dear?
What are you saying? Come on.
Sir, I'm sorry.
I spoke harshly
in the meeting the other day.
I should not have spoken like that.
- What is this, Nedumaran?
Don't I know about you?
I've been seeing you
since your training period.
If you are angry,
it is justified.
No, sir, you are not talking to me
since you came. - No..
I got to know
that Riya is pregnant
only at the party.
I felt very bad
when she hid it from me.
I got to know it
like a third person at the party.
So what place do I hold
in Riya's heart?
How much does Riya love me?
I've been thinking about it.
Sir, please don't think like that.
I have known Riya
since her childhood.
Only she knows what she is facing.
Excuse me, sir.
You've got to control yourself, sir.
- I'll take this.
I can't.
That's why I asked them
to reduce the sugar.
Cut it totally, sir.
Sir, don't eat it.
Sir, there is a lot of sugar in it.
No, sir, it's very high..
How did you know this?
Sir, when you opened it,
I smelled a strong scent of sugar.
I told you based on that.
Okay.
Sir, but I swear I didn't taste it.
- No..
I didn't think
you would have done that.
But, I was wondering if you can tell
the amount of sugar
just from the smell.
Maran, is it possible?
Actually you can't smell
sugar, sir. You can't.
But, you can smell caramel. Yeah.
I think he smelt
the caramel and he..
It's not possible
to smell sugar, sir..
Very few people can do it.
He is..
Maran.
Are you okay?
- Yeah..
I am okay, sir, I am okay.
You've served it, right? Take this
and clear it. - Okay, sir.
Ask the person who prepared
it to wait in my room. - Okay, sir.
Get out.
Good guy. He was the one-day
chef, right? - Yes, sir, yes.
Maran, why don't you add him
to the kitchen team and train him?
Sir, it doesn't work like that.
You need basic book knowledge to
follow a recipe and work as a chef.
He is not educated, sir. No.
Maran, how did
our Chidambaram come to us?
What was his education?
What was his book knowledge?
You don't want me to remind you
about Chidambaram's cooking, right?
Sir, Chidambaram..
You know what
Chidambaram did to us, sir.
Why are you talking about it now?
- Okay..
That's your wish.
You have to take a call on that.
I told you what I wanted to tell.
But, I lost an ice cream.
Nedumaran, you have to prepare
an ice cream for me.
Yeah, sure, sir.
Hey, what is this?
Why have you charged me
for the dishes that I didn't eat?
I'm already angry about the
price increase at your resort.
Now, you have wrongly
charged me Rs. 550.
What are you glaring at?
You ate the Chicken Burrito
and charged it to my bill?
Why would I do that, bro?
- Bro?
Who is your bro?
Am I your bro?
Sorry, sir.
Such issues are normal in billing.
Just give me 10 minutes,
I will sort this out.
Do you think you're a big shot?
You talk in English
as if you're a hotshot.
Did I speak to you in English?
I spoke to you in Tamil, right?
Similarly, you should
talk to me in Tamil, right?
Sorry, sir.
Forgive me, sir.
Give me 10 minutes. I will
change the bill and come. - Go..
I feel bad thinking about him.
Even I feel bad.
But, when I talk to him,
he talks in a way that I feel worse.
Poor guy.
He is short-tempered. If we
control that, he will be fine.
Believe in something impossible.
- No, Aishu.
Once he comes to the kitchen after
the punishment, he will be fine.
But, when he works in room service,
the guests will treat him badly.
I don't know how
he is going to handle that.
Why are you thinking about that?
Don't think about it.
I can't stop thinking about it.
Something is
constantly bothering me.
Don't get tense.
He should understand all this.
- No, Aishu. - Let's see.
Who billed for room number 210?
I did. What happened?
What are you thinking, Veni?
Haven't I had enough?
You have added a Chicken Burrito
that he did not order, to his bill.
He is talking as if I am a thief.
Humiliate me all you want.
What are you thinking?
Mistakes do happen while billing.
You are talking as if you never
made a mistake while billing.
Yes, Sous chef.
Why are you getting
involved in such cheap things?
Go and mind your own business.
-That's exactly what I'm doing.
Why are you shouting like this?
Are you happy to see me
shouting like a dog?
Don't talk like a fool, Vicky.
I can't even enter
the kitchen in this shirt.
I'll look like a fool indeed.
Take this.
Make someone else deal with this.
He is here.
He must have faced many issues.
So, make him deal with it.
What happened?
Joji has been
admitted to a hospital.
What are you saying?
Wait, I will be back. Stay here.
- Okay.
Come fast.
- Grace..
An emergency.
Can you give me your bike key?
I am going to the entrance.
- Bike key? - Bike Key.
I am coming, you go.
- Here you go.
There is an old man named Joji..
- Go straight and take right.
Here? How..
- Thank you.
Hey, Vetri, come in.
- What happened, sir?
Nothing.
- What happened, Doctor?
Sudden spike in blood sugar.
Because of that,
his BP also fluctuated.
So, please don't give him sugar.
So, don't worry.
Nothing to panic about.
He needs proper diet
control and rest. - Okay, Doctor.
Phew.
Don't allow him to eat
any sugary food.
That's the reason for all this.
- Oh, no..
What did you find out now?
I got to know that he has diabetes.
You were listening
as if you understood everything.
He was putting in effort
to explain. That's why..
His blood sugar had hiked
after eating something. Ask him.
What happened, sir?
Tell me now.
- Nothing, Vetri. - Nothing?
Did you faint for no reason?
- Leave that.
I won't. Tell me.
That is..
Padma said she likes brownies.
I bought it for her.
- Okay.
I didn't ask her.
She fed it to me.
I had it under control
for so many years.
When she fed me,
I couldn't control myself.
So, I ate it.
I got to know when I saw it.
There was a lot of sugar in it.
I didn't want to eat it.
- Okay.
Then, the things that shouldn't
have happened, happened.
No, Vetri, it's the first time..
When she gave it to me,
it did not seem nice to say
that I am diabetic, right?
Of course..
- Think about it.
Hey, my bike is fine, right?
I'm admitted here for poor health.
But, you're worried about
what happened to your bike?
You've brought the right person.
- Sorry, sir.
She's bothersome.
Sir.
Where is she?
She has gone to pay the bill.
Oh..
- Sir, don't worry.
How can I not worry?
It was our first date.
And it went like this.
I was happy since morning.
But, I am in the hospital now.
Don't cry, the day is not over yet.
Shall we do one thing?
You leave first.
We will follow you, okay?
But, maintain some privacy, man.
My ill luck!
Is everything okay?
- I am okay.
You are smiling happily,
but I am scared.
It's okay, I am fine.
- Can you ride?
Yes.
- Shall I ride? - No.
I will ride.
- Are you sure? - Yes.
We are their love gurus.
Come on, pose.
- Hey, no.
I want my bike back safe and sound.
If not, I will tell my dad
and deduct it from your salary.
Hey, don't do that.
Why are you doing this?
They're leaving.. Start the bike.
- Get on.
Go fast.
- I am going. - Accelerate..
Hey, go.
- I am hungry.
Please go.
You are doing too much.
- Go.
I went inside.
It's okay
even if he had scolded me.
He insulted me
by showing some actions.
Don't feel bad.
You just want to get
scolded, right? You little..
You were waiting for the chance?
- Yes.
Wearing the chef's coat makes you
feel like scolding someone. - Hello.
Enough.
I can't believe I had to witness
this, and in this heat.
Show this.
- What material is this?
What other colours are available?
Show that. What material is that?
- Hey.
Why are you looking here?
Get lost..
This is superb, right?
- Good, very nice.
I like this colour too.
- Very nice, wait..
Is it good? You like it?
- Oh, God.
I don't know
what else I have to see.
Hey, isn't it fun to watch them?
- Yes, it'll be.
Do you know what you are doing?
You just keep watching.
I am leaving.
Hello, wait.
No, it's okay.
- Sir, is it done?
Hey, wait, don't disturb us.
- Oh, God..
Okay, carry on.
Give them a minute.
Okay..
- Nice.
Really?
- They're done, let's go.
Okay, sir.
- Thank you. - Sit.
Hey, sit properly.
I loved riding the bike
and exploring all day.
I went on a bike after many days.
That too with you.
I enjoyed a lot.
- Actually..
It's been a long time
since I felt happy.
Thank you very much.
Did I help you?
You are thanking me.
We went outing,
we enjoyed together, that's it.
I can't forget this day.
Not only that.
I'll never forget meeting
and talking to you in college.
You could have told me
all this back then.
The only question on my mind
all day today..
was that one.
I still regret
not doing that, Padma.
Anyway, it's not too late.
Actually, Joji, that is..
- Mom.
What are you doing?
Nothing, Shruthi.
We were just talking.
Aren't you ashamed?
How old are you?
What are you doing here?
You told me that you were
going to a Siddha doctor.
I have been calling you
repeatedly for three hours.
You are not answering the phone.
Shruthi, just listen to me.
I've run out of patience.
I might end up yelling at you.
You better go to your room.
Poor guy, Pandi.
He became sad
when she spoke like that.
I feel so bad.
If a man is unlucky
throughout his life..
what will he do?
Her daughter said
such unpleasant things.
It's true
that rich people lack peace.
How long has it been since
I asked for a full boiled egg?
He is making an omelette.
What the heck are you doing?
Hey, this is not for you.
Do you see with your eyes closed?
Here is the full boiled egg.
Pandi, give it to me.
Here you go.
- Hey.
Why are you
talking disrespectfully?
Won't I get angry then?
You won't respect us,
but should we respect you?
That's right.
Hey, I'm speaking very politely.
Yes, he is very decent.
Congratulations.
Hey, don't mess with me.
Then I'll be a different person.
- Will he be decent at least?
Or is he also a drunkard like you?
- Hey!
Are you laughing?
Hey.
You don't know who I am.
I will destroy this shop.
- Oh.
As if he is a magic man,
he'll change the shop by magic.
Hey..
- Hey, take your hands off him!
Why are you being disrespectful?
- Take your hands off.
Hey, leave.
Why are you pushing me?
Take your hands off.
Hey.
Why are you raising your hand
when we're talking?
I will kill you.
Hey, don't..
Don't..
- Hey, you are drunk. Go away.
Hey.
- Go away. - Hey.
You hit me, right?
Tomorrow, the shop won't be there.
Tomorrow, you will know
who I am. - Yes, I'll know.
I will see you tomorrow.
The shop won't be there tomorrow.
- Sir, wait..
Hey..
Why did you fight with him?
He hit me and tried to strangle me.
He is a drunkard.
- Hey.
He works in the corporation office.
He comes to the shop often
and creates problems.
So, I avoid
any kind of trouble with him.
If he gets tense,
he will wreck the shop.
Oh, no.
I shouldn't have left the shop.
Hey.
His actions have already caused
two-three shops to change places.
It's been a year and still
they can't reopen their shops.
And you've caused
problems with him.
Over! Everything is over!
Hey, he will make us
remove the shop.