♪Shrugging off past burdens♪
♪Beneath the mask, who am I?♪
♪Release and find wider shores♪
♪Love's a riddle, and rain pours heavy♪
♪Crossed paths, now downward fall♪
♪From dust arises starlight's spark♪
♪Tearing through
the night's dense blockade♪
♪Heart's flame illuminates all solitude♪
♪Let time's sails drift endlessly♪
♪Through wandering exile♪
♪Breaking free from the cocoon,
I start anew♪
♪Moon as song, life as flame♪
♪Nameless heart clings fiercely♪
♪Let me♪
♪Charge toward the next raging river♪
♪Moon darts, snow falls♪
♪We tread rugged paths to reunite♪
♪Hands held tight♪
♪We forever live for love's sake♪
♪Shadow's spear burns fiercely♪
=Legend of The Female General=
=Episode 19=
Good morning.
Commander Xiao.
Miss He.
Let's have breakfast together.
Please.
Actually,
I've known for a while
you're not my elder brother's son.
Your act
was quite convincing.
Since Her Highness knew
you came to Jiyang
and yet did nothing,
she must have her plans.
In that case,
I had to play the fool.
You're a master of disguise.
I'm impressed.
To become Princess Mengji's right hand,
you must be
exceptionally clever.
Not as astute as you.
Let's have breakfast together.
Please.
Mr. Chu.
Mr. He, good morning.
Good morning.
But now I should call you Miss He.
You're still mistaken.
Currently,
you should call her Mrs. Qiao.
We have a visit to make, right?
Let's go.
Go.
Don't miss the time.
Mr. Chu.
I'll take my leave.
Speak your mind.
How did you know
I was visiting an elder?
You dressed formally this morning,
obviously to meet someone.
In all of Jiyang,
the only one worthy of such formality
would be your master.
My master once told me
that if needed,
I could find him in Jiyang.
I assumed
he was merely enjoying nature
but never imagined
there was a hidden story.
What story?
If it's hidden,
it can't be revealed.
Commander,
please don't press me.
Fine.
I don't care to know.
Thank you.
Thank you, Master.
Master Yunlin.
When did you arrive here?
Around each Water God Festival,
I return to Jiyang City.
This time,
I discovered Wutuo spies
disguised as civilians.
So,
I tracked them secretly
and indeed,
these Wutuo spies
used the festival crowds
to kidnap the young princess
to blackmail Princess Mengji.
The kidnapping
is just the first step.
Now, Wutuo agents
move freely through Jiyang,
like water eroding stone.
This was long planned.
Her Highness
dislikes
our interference
but has enhanced
security checks.
Let's hope it helps.
It feels like a storm
is brewing in Jiyang City.
Something major approaches.
You continue.
I need fresh air.
Ask what you wish.
Master.
Did you stay in Jiyang
for Princess Mengji?
Or is there another reason?
Even if she weren't Princess Mengji,
I won't stand idly by
and see the people
in Jiyang suffer.
Isn't it the same between you
and General Fengyun?
You're right.
I was small-minded.
But Master,
you...
Do you truly have no wish to see
Princess Mengji again?
You have much work to attend to.
I won't keep you longer.
Your master
seems burdened.
Even you noticed.
I don't know
Master Yunlin well,
but
this melody clearly reveals deep sorrow.
You truly are a master of music.
People may conceal truths,
but instruments never lie.
If I recall correctly,
Princess Mengji also played
this melody before?
They truly share a profound connection.
(Peaceful Land)
Commander,
Mr. Cui needs you
for urgent matters.
I'll take my leave.
And you?
You should return.
I'll walk around
and secretly inspect
the defenses.
(South Gate)
Next.
Go.
Princess Mengji is decisive.
A masterful defender.
Next.
I truly hope Jiyang City
can maintain this peace
and harmony forever.
Mr. Chu?
Why is it you?
I'm sorry.
I startled you?
It's nothing.
These are turbulent times.
Caution is only natural.
Please don't take offense.
Actually,
I want to apologize to you.
Apologize?
Why?
Last time, it was I who invited you
to admire the moon over Mount Baiyue.
But urgent matters arose,
and I left.
Nothing.
Don't take it seriously.
Moreover,
I did gain something else that night.
You hold no grudge
due to your magnanimity.
I cannot pretend
it never happened.
I must apologize.
By the way,
let me give you a gift, Miss He.
What?
Last time we met,
I noticed
you wore a purple whip
at your waist.
By chance,
I obtained this tassel.
I think it suits you perfectly.
Try it on.
See if it's better.
Mr. Chu,
I can't accept it.
Forget it.
Besides,
this tassel appears
quite valuable.
You call me Mr. Chu.
We're friends.
Between friends,
exchanging gifts is natural.
Besides,
this tassel isn't costly,
so feel no obligation.
Okay.
I'll accept it.
Thank you, Mr. Chu.
Perfect match.
In return,
I should give you something, Mr. Chu.
- Sir.
- Miss.
Which is the priciest one
here?
The floral basket.
Would you like one?
Yes, give me one.
Alright.
May I draw it myself?
Certainly.
Here you go.
Done.
How's this?
Do you like it?
Zilan
means fragrant orchid.
The person who named you
loved you certainly.
They surely wished you noble virtues
and a good future,
so you got this elegant name.
This is
my reciprocal gift.
Mr. Chu,
don't mock my clumsy handwriting.
How could I?
I'm deeply honored.
Burn him!
- Burn him!
Mr. Chu.
It's okay.
Are you
afraid of fire?
Thank goodness
this isn't ruined.
(Mengji Mansion)
Jiyang's defenses
remain well-fortified.
Let's hope so.
Commander.
Where are you going?
Just walking.
Then I'll join you.
This is a gift from Mr. Chu.
Miss He also gave me a gift.
I like it very much.
She once sent me osmanthus candies,
a whole handful,
more than I could eat.
The characters "Zilan"
on this sugar painting
were written by Miss He herself.
This food is fragile.
You should keep it carefully
in case you
end up with nothing.
Thank you for the advice.
I'll preserve it with utmost care.
If you both enjoy sweets so much,
I'll buy more in the future.
Commander.
Several crucial granaries
are ablaze.
Very fiercely.
It's the Wutuo's doing.
Assist Mr. Cui
in it.
Yes.
Let's discuss it
with Princess Mengji.
Agreed.
Fire! The granary's on fire!
It's the Wutuo people.
They've made their move.
Quite the spectacle.
Those Wutuo people
grow more audacious by the day.
Doesn't this situation feel
all too familiar?
Mingshui
and Que City
both witnessed similar things.
The Wutuo people
breached the defenses easily
and launched attacks.
This time, Chancellor Xu aided them.
As for the previous two...
After this,
Xiao Jue won't let this slide.
Go take a look.
Skip the formalities.
You've come.
Lou,
they're your life savers.
Have you forgotten
your manners?
How could you act like this?
Commander Xiao.
I was just about to see you.
As you observed,
Wutuo is watching hungrily.
The situation in Jiyang City
grows more dire by the day.
Though I've dispatched troops
and increased security,
the Wutuo people
are moving faster.
How many men
are stationed here?
Under 20,000.
We've captured
some Wutuo infiltrators,
but it won't turn the tide.
Wutuo has already launched its attack.
This will be a bitter struggle.
Though Jiyang lacks manpower,
we'll never retreat.
I'll hold my position here
and stand with Jiyang
to the last breath.
I'd like
to offer my assistance.
Leaving your post at Yezhou
is a breach of military law.
Commanding troops now
would bring
graver consequences.
Do you truly
risk such repercussions
for Jiyang's sake?
As a Wei general,
it's my duty
to protect the people.
I'll contribute my efforts, too.
Good.
From this moment,
all Jiyang troops
will obey Commander Xiao's orders.
Our people's safety
rests in your hands, Commander.
I'll spare no effort
to defend Jiyang to the last.
Your Highness,
the war looms imminent.
Perhaps
the young princess
should be sent away.
I'm staying here.
I remain with Mother
and our people
no matter what.
So be it.
You'll stay by my side, Lou.
I'll keep you safe,
whatever the cost.
(Self-Revealing Virtue)
The troops here in Jiyang
are far too few.
And they lack recent combat experience.
You show true leadership.
Unflinching in crisis.
Aren't you
aspiring to be a female general?
20,000 men.
Far better than that
in Que City.
Whether 20,000
or 2,000,
when enemies are outside,
we fight to the death.
Prove those words true.
These 20,000 men
will follow your command.
Wise choice, Commander.
None could lead but me.
Thrust.
Stab.
Down. Chop.
After years without combat,
they look slack.
Such bold claims.
You make our army
sound like brittle clay.
Just a mere woman.
How can you teach us men
battle tactics?
You're gambling
with our lives.
Well?
Care to test me?
Don't waste time.
All ten of you
attack her at once.
You mock us?
I would like to see
how you'll face ten opponents alone.
Commander.
You honor me excessively.
Do you know?
I hear
Mrs. Qiao is challenging
the Jiyang army single-handedly
at the training field.
Is she crazy?
Any more challengers?
- Great!
Now you see
how formidable she is.
Truly the best of Yezhou Garrison.
This scene
looks eerily familiar to me.
Here.
Thank you.
- Amazing!
- Awesome!
Yes.
Incredible!
Didn't I tell you the truth?
Women
are never inferior to men.
Through the ages,
people have claimed
women belong at embroidery frames
and housewifery.
But must we women
be confined to domestic roles
or limited to needlework?
We can write and fight.
We can write literary masterpieces.
We can charge into battle
and earn glory.
We're not just waiting to be saved.
We can save ourselves.
Of course
I won't force you
to fight on battlefields.
But beyond combat,
you can do other things.
Even the tiniest dust
can fill mountains and seas.
The faintest glow
can rival the sun and moon.
I prided myself on noble birth
but remained trapped in stagnation.
I can sell unwanted jewels
to buy
weapons and provisions.
- Me too!
I'll donate.
Those who are poor can learn
medicine from us.
Countless soldiers will need care
later.
Rich or poor, all can learn.
Well?
Am I impressive?
You know why I let you
lead them?
Because
I'm unquestionably capable.
Miss He is so skilled
in martial arts.
She
always defies convention.
Young Master,
Princess Mengji began
evacuating the civilians today.
Shouldn't you join them?
My goal is unfinished.
How can I leave now?
But Jiyang is too dangerous.
Only by staying
can I uncover
Master's true intentions.
Yingxiang,
two paths lie before me.
Either
die in this city
or survive
to confirm my suspicions.
A life of complacency
would be meaningless
even if I return.
Understand?
Keep up.
Everyone, follow me.
Stay close.
Jiyang has become
half-deserted overnight.
Shops stand shuttered.
Only the able-bodied
and those strong enough
could flee.
The old, weak, and ill
can't even join the exodus.
Miss Song.
I know what you'll say.
Save your breath.
As a healer,
I won't abandon people
in crisis.
What are you thinking?
Don't you want me to leave?
Come on!
You haven't conceded defeat yet.
And you want to escape?
Cheng Lisu.
Besides,
you aim to heal the world
and reform medical texts.
No one should obstruct your path.
Cheng Lisu.
This time,
let's see who saves more.
It's also part of the contest.
If you lose,
you'll have to wash
my socks for a year.
You're destined to lose.
There won't be
many women for you to rescue
in combat.
I won't lose.
Then we'll see about that.
If the heavens don't favor us
on the day of battle,
what then?
Every inch of Jiyang's land
can become our burial ground.
This is the conviction
every soldier should possess.
Rather die with shattered wings
than endure separation
amidst the clouds.
Today,
the weather is clear.
What's your plan?
They've suddenly forced their march.
If we want to win with fewer people,
holding fortresses is crucial.
Go.
Be careful.
Hurry.
Go.
Let's go there.
Hurry.
Go.
Young Master,
as the Military Inspector,
you've done more than enough.
You can't fight.
For your safety,
please leave the city.
Leave this to me.
I took on from Her Highness
the evacuation
and resettlement.
I must finish it.
I can't abandon the people
to save myself.
Moreover,
Chai Anxi isn't found.
If I leave alone,
how will I face my master?
But...
I've decided.
Over here.
Move aside!
Thank you, sir.
Anyone else disrupting order
will be executed.
Are you alright, sir?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Thank you.
There's an empty house
ahead sheltering
lost elders and children.
You can
stay there temporarily
for shelter.
Okay, thank you.
Yingxiang.
Escort the elder.
Yes.
Thank you.
Mr. Chu.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Thank you.
When I bought the sugar painting,
I noticed you seemed
uneasy around fire.
Mr. Chu, are you afraid of fire?
(Smoke him out to cleanse)
(bad luck!)
- Yes!
Do it.
Smoke him out.
Your mother eloped.
Serves you right.
You fatherless boy.
Illegitimate.
Don't insult my mother!
Mother.
It's okay.
Mr. Chu.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't ask you.
It's okay.
Thank you.
Mr. Chu.
You've already thanked me.
I just remembered it.
I have a garment
made of mermaid silk fabric.
The merchant claimed
clothes crafted from this material
are swordproof
and resistant to fire.
I'll have it sent
to you later, Mr. Chu.
This way,
you won't fear flames.
It's settled then.
Mr. Chu, I'll go patrol.
Stay cautious.
Be careful.
Let's go.
We just got news.
The Wutuo Army
suddenly sped up.
They're 20 li
outside
the south gate.
I suspect
they've got news
about you being in Jiyang.
They've always feared you.
Knowing you're here,
they'll surely exploit
the lack of coordination
between you and the troops
to strike swiftly.
For us to overcome their numbers,
speed will be crucial.
So,
this is our opportunity.
True.
Our troops' morale is high.
Civilians are encouraged.
Both united
to strike.
This is our moment to repel Wutuo.
But
Jiyang's limited forces
remain our critical weakness.
We need unusual ideas
to reverse our fortunes.
This time,
the Wutuo commander
is Huyate.
Courageous in combat
but stubbornly self-assured,
with limited skill
in formations.
Disrupting his formation
is key to victory.
I've heard of Huyate.
His heavy-armored troops
are tough.
But it decides the battle.
You seem well-informed
about Huyate.
Commander,
after all,
I aspire to be a general.
It's my duty
to study
potential adversaries.
See?
This knowledge proves useful now.
Commander.
During the evacuation today,
my men stationed
at checkpoints
didn't find
Chai Anxi.
He likely
hasn't fled the city yet.
In that case,
he probably plans
to escape
once the battle begins.
But by then,
the city will be surrounded,
and we'll be stretched too thin.
Continue the checks.
Stay vigilant.
If war truly breaks out,
our priority
is to defend Jiyang.
Yes.
(I've guarded)
(this city for over two decades.)
(This time,)
(I will surely protect it again.)
(Master.)
The Mengji throne
doesn't require marriage alliances.
Through generations
of rulers' diligence,
they won over the people.
Diligent governance is crucial,
but through history,
no woman has ever inherited the throne.
Hongjin is Prince Mengji's sole child.
Legitimate.
(Taoist Yunji)
A brave and smart woman
rivals any man.
These are just your personal views.
Though laws never stipulated
only men can inherit the throne,
some traditions
have become unspoken rules
in the public's mind.
Her gender alone
gives opponents ground to challenge her.
Hongjin will prove to the world
she surpasses her ancestors.
I'll stand by her side.
The nobles in Jiyang
won't grant her that time.
Now,
only marriage
can stabilize the situation
and her position swiftly.
I believe
heaven never seals all doors.
We can defy our destiny.
You two might challenge fate,
but victory demands sacrifice.
Don't tell me
you fear no hardship.
The suffering
won't just burden you two.
When turmoil erupts,
countless Jiyang citizens
will inevitably
endure hardships because of you.
Even so,
please let me go down
and see her.
Let me tell her.
She's still waiting.
I can't break my promise.
Master.
Master!
Confine him under strict watch.
Prevent him from descending.
Master.
Her Highness
will get married in three days.
It's all over.
Abandon your stubbornness.
♪Through endless nights, I walk alone♪
♪Heartache swirls like ceaseless winds♪
♪Yet I yearn to stand opposed to you♪
Since you didn't come then,
why seek meeting
right now?
♪Upon towering fortress walls♪
♪Brooding over lamented pasts♪
♪Where shall light be found♪
♪Once♪
♪I had an unbreakable faith♪
♪If given another life♪
♪Never yield♪
♪I'm shrouded in darkness♪
♪Resent old dreams like drifting clouds♪
♪Heartache♪
♪Resenting the lonely years♪
♪Why persist♪
♪Tears crystallize to frost♪
♪Clutching stubborn obsessions♪
♪Yet falling into folly♪
♪Fading into oblivion♪
♪Yet memories surge everywhere♪
♪After the separation♪
♪My heart feels adrift♪
We'll go
to the camp with Her Highness later
to await our victory.
Young Master,
what's in this package?
Is it important?
Miss He gave me
this protective gear.
This is war,
not child's play.
Why are you going?
Go join
Ms. Wei's group.
I'm serious.
Our soldiers bleed outside.
As a healer,
I must contribute.
You're a doctor
who just treats women.
You should go join them.
Stop hindering me.
I...
I'm in.
We can watch
each other's backs.
(Huyate, Wutuo Commander)
Attack!
Commander,
let me lead the elites
to draw away Huyate
and the heavy armor units.
He Yan, listen!
Come back alive.
Yes!
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪I've seen the mountains♪
♪And trodden through ice♪
♪Day after day, I venture alone♪
♪Destiny is my creed♪
♪Ideals surge beneath the surface♪
♪Igniting the flame against the winds♪
♪A restless yearning in my soul♪
♪Gazing through the mire♪
♪Who cares about this boundless void♪
♪Charge ahead with blazing fervor♪
♪Stubbornly fighting with my life♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪