(All characters, places,
and organizations are fictional.)
(Children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
(Restricted Area)
(Episode 12)
Is he busy?
Or does he just not care at all?
I was rushed to the ER after that.
(Yong Joong)
The person you're calling is unavailable.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Maybe he uses two phones like I do.
Be well.
I'll be back soon.
(Las Vegas, Landed)
Are you hungry?
I'm okay.
Did you have bibimbap
or the Western meal on the plane?
I slept the whole way.
I just had cup noodles before we landed.
Did you go to any Korean restaurants?
No.
You said you craved the gimbap James made
when you were abroad,
so I made some for you.
You shouldn't have.
It was no trouble at all.
Were you okay while I was gone?
- Aren't you going to change?
- After I shower.
You said gimbap is best on its own,
so I didn't make any soup.
It's delicious. Thank you.
- Aren't you having any?
- I ate the end pieces while making it.
Did you text Mr. Ha?
I'll stop by later. He knows I'm back.
How's Pickles?
She had some diarrhea,
but she's fine since I changed her food.
Hello?
Hello.
I'll take a taxi.
I can just drop you off on my way.
It's seasoned even better
than when James makes it.
That's a relief.
His cooking is getting saltier
with his age.
- Are you done eating?
- No.
- I hope you like it.
- Goodness.
But you bought me that necklace last time.
It's not designer.
When have I ever cared
about designer brands?
It would've been nice
if you could've come with me.
- Were there a lot of high-tech gadgets?
- Yes.
The jet lag must be tough
for the next few days.
It's not as bad on the way back,
flying west from the east.
Anything happen while I was gone?
I learned to drive and shopped with Momo.
She's all better now?
She says she still gets a little dizzy.
It's really lingering.
Thank you.
You can relax and let me drive now.
My instructor showered me with praise.
He said I was ready to hit the road.
- I'll leave the keys for you.
- No, this car is too much for me.
I'm getting a call.
It's been a while.
Yes, I got your message.
I'll come up for a bit.
Bottled water or barley tea?
Either is fine. The barley tea.
(Park Seong Cheol, Marketing Team Manager)
Just pretend it's champagne and drink up.
Let's set a wedding date.
I've been thinking,
and...
I think it'd be best if we stopped
seeing each other for a few months.
To me, you've always been...
that little kid I first met.
I need to get past that image of you.
Do you understand?
It's just...
so I can think of you only as you are now.
I need some time.
Because I keep...
feeling like I'm doing something wrong.
Don't think that.
You don't have to think that way.
Aren't you...
repulsed by me?
Am I a burden to you?
It's different from burden.
Let's completely erase our past feelings
and start over.
It won't even take a year.
Please, trust me and wait a little.
Okay?
I need time.
You must be a little confused too, right?
Can't you...
just accept it?
Is the past more important
than the present?
First impressions last a lifetime.
Not once have I ever looked at you...
with any ill intentions.
Was what we did that night...
wrong?
A little impulsive.
I'm sorry. It's my fault.
No, I'm the one
who should've known better.
Anyway, we're getting married.
We are, but what I'm saying is
that I need a little time.
How should I put this...
My feelings for you
have only grown deeper.
We can text every now and then.
- I'll leave the car.
- No, don't.
Please, don't get the wrong idea.
It might not even take
as long as you think.
(Jaeil Apartments)
Going down to the first floor.
The doors are closing.
(Ba Ra)
Hello?
Yong Joong.
Yes.
Thank you.
To be honest,
I felt a little weird about it too.
Let's just forget it ever happened.
We're only human. We all make mistakes.
We just made the same mistake.
We were drinking that night, too.
Are you listening?
Yes.
If we don't see each other
for a few months,
it still might be impossible
to go back to how we were.
Then we just shouldn't see each other.
- And just act like we never met.
- Is that even possible?
And if it's not?
People date, break up, get divorced...
Why should we be any different?
That's all just a part of life.
I'll just...
think of all of this as a memory.
That's what I'll do.
Just give me time.
It'll be even more awkward
if we see each other in a month or two.
Then I'll take back what I said yesterday.
No.
Your decision is the right one.
- I would've done the same...
- Are you home?
Let's meet and talk.
Don't worry about me.
Geum Ba Ra...
We're going back to how things were
before the interview.
- How can I live without you?
- I'll be just fine without you.
- I hate feeling stuck in limbo like this.
- Just one month.
I promise I'll come around.
Forcing it won't feel natural.
It's pointless to force things.
It's pointless...
But, I...
No, this is wrong. It can't end like this.
I'm going to go to Boston for a while.
For how long?
I'll see when I get there.
Remember I told you about
the missionary in Boston?
Yes. I remember.
You really don't have to worry.
Then...
If anything happens, call me right away.
Okay.
Promise.
I promise.
You hang up first.
I'm at a loss for words.
That won't solve anything.
Whether it's Boston or anywhere else,
you need to recover first before you go.
I'm fine now.
I guess I just got a little worked up.
That's what you're telling yourself,
but your heart hasn't accepted it yet.
I'll go grab you something.
Are you craving anything?
Don't you feel betrayed?
More than betrayal,
I don't think I can treat
psychiatric patients anymore.
I never would have guessed
or could have imagined it.
I couldn't bring myself...
to express it and say it out loud.
You held it together well on your own.
If you hadn't let it all out like this,
you would've gotten sicker.
(Nua General Hospital)
He must have seen my missed call.
Is he sick or something?
(She is eating well.)
Madam, just three kilograms.
All right.
Your brother stopped by.
He left this since you were in a fitting.
I don't need things.
But when he travels,
he has to buy me something.
Even if it's just for a couple of days.
- You won't find another brother like him.
- Tell me about it.
Is it toner? Or cologne?
I can't get discharged
because I don't have my phone on me.
Could you cover the hospital bill for now?
Go on up and wait.
(Nua General Hospital, Neurology Center)
(Nua General Hospital)
Are you really planning to never see
Yong Joong again?
Yes.
How can you do that?
Then you don't really have to leave.
I want to clear my head.
To sort out my feelings.
- You need to recover first.
- He could call me...
or come looking for me.
Then just stay here.
I only come up for a few hours
of sleep anyway.
If that makes you uncomfortable,
I can just stay at my parents' house.
What if I end up losing them both?
I can't let that happen.
Not I, Kim Jin Ju... No...
I mean, Momo.
Especially now that Ba Ra's gone.
Did you sleep well, Pickles?
Pickles!
What do I do?
(James)
- Hey.
- What do I do?
Reporter Geum isn't answering either.
- Why? What's wrong?
- Goodness, it's Pickles...
I woke up, and Pickles wasn't breathing.
The person you have called is unavailable.
Leave a message after the tone.
Call charges may...
(Nua General Hospital)
Excuse me.
Could I speak to someone from HR?
What is this about?
I promised myself when I was released,
I'd make time for volunteer work...
as a way to atone.
Whether it's directing cars
or cleaning the restrooms,
- I'll do whatever you ask...
- Really? For no pay?
Yes. All I ask for is
one meal from the cafeteria.
I saw there were many patients
in wheelchairs.
I could help them get around and in cars.
I'm physically fit.
I could work on a construction site,
but I made a promise to volunteer
to the Blessed Virgin Mary.
Why did Reporter Geum
suddenly go to the US?
To get away from Ju Shin?
He must have been clinging to her
like a stalker.
Director Shin doesn't seem like the type,
though.
You need to eat something.
I made some side dishes for you.
I don't have an appetite.
Reporter Geum is
going to blame me for this.
I never should have brought her here.
Maybe she wouldn't have died
if you had just kept her.
It was just her time to go.
I should probably go see
a shaman or something.
First Oiji, and now Pickles.
We're definitely jinxed.
You can't expect only good things
to happen in life.
But she was perfectly fine
without even being sick.
She was even being playful last night.
Try calling her again.
She might have her phone on
now that she's landed.
- Later.
- Is it early morning there?
Oh, Pickles.
(Jaeil Apartments)
Are you not eating?
I already ate.
You could at least come sit with me then.
My mom used to make a heart
with the ketchup.
I'll make you a heart next time.
Just drink room-temperature water.
Am I making you uncomfortable?
Why would I be?
Don't go to so much trouble
starting tomorrow.
Who said you had to earn your keep?
It's no trouble.
And I can afford to pay for my room.
Don't force yourself to eat it
if you don't like it.
I'm not forcing myself.
I don't think I've had omelet rice
in over ten years.
Let me know if there's anything else
you're craving.
My mom always made a full spread
with at least five side dishes.
You're not up for that, are you?
I'll give it a shot.
I was just teasing you.
I'll do it from the heart,
not out of obligation.
You need to stay healthy.
What do you mean, from the heart?
Like you're my mother?
(Momo)
- Hello?
- Hi, Yong Joong.
Hey.
I heard you got out of the hospital.
Yes.
You can get in touch with Ba Ra, right?
No.
Don't you think something happened to her?
She even made her account private.
She probably just wants some time
to herself.
- I hope that's all it is.
- How's your vertigo?
Took you long enough to ask.
It's pretty much all better now.
Since Ba Ra isn't here,
I don't think
I'll have a birthday party this year.
It's your birthday? When?
My birthday is this Sunday,
but I'm telling everyone
it's next Wednesday.
If you invite me, I'll come.
I can at least be there.
Are you free on Sunday evening?
Yes.
I'll text you.
Okay.
(Nua General Hospital)
- Is this the main Orthopedics building?
- Yes.
Thank you.
Please sit here.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Watch your step. Goodness.
- Have a good day.
- Thank you.
(Surgery time, Current time,
Anesthesia time)
(Nua General Hospital)
Cardiothoracic Surgery these days...
The dialysis patients from Cardio Med...
Am I too early?
No.
I used to always...
spend my actual birthday with just my mom,
so the thought
of eating my birthday meal alone...
was just too sad.
So please, join me.
Of course.
The housekeeper left food,
but I told her to skip the short ribs.
I'm sick of them.
I see.
Do you like seaweed soup?
I'm not picky about soups.
Even fermented skate liver soup?
You know what that is, right?
Yes.
That one might be a bit much...
Thank you.
I almost had to eat
my birthday dinner all alone.
No text from Ju Shin?
Not a single word.
Oh, right!
- When's your birthday?
- In the winter.
When in the winter?
It was the day after
last year's engagement party.
Oh, my.
What kind of jinx?
The kind that makes you want to dance.
If only music were playing now...
I have the sudden urge to waltz right now.
With me?
Yes.
With anyone.
I feel like I could even dance
with a snowman.
You don't dance anymore?
Not even by yourself?
Pardon?
No.
It might help lift your spirits.
Maybe I should take up dancing?
I've even forgotten the steps.
I see.
Have you ever seen Ba Ra dance?
No, why?
Apparently, in college,
she was in the dance club.
I see...
Who's he trying to impress, seduce?
What about you?
Have you ever seen her dance?
Not really...
Still no word from him today?
Nothing.
Looks like he wants to cut all ties.
It's not like you're naked or anything.
Here, eat this.
Okay.
It's melting.
It's gelato.
I used to wonder what the big deal was,
but this is pretty good.
It's actually pretty good.
What shampoo do you use?
It smells nice.
It's from my conditioner.
You don't use conditioner?
Who has time for all that?
Go get some more.
There's a box in the freezer.
Okay.
What do you like about Yong Joong?
I just do.
There's no such thing as "just because."
For me, I fell for Momo
after seeing her act.
I thought you already had dinner.
I had a late snack at the clubhouse.
Everyone's fighting
a battle of the bulge these days.
What did you have?
Jajangmyeon.
It wasn't as good as yours, though.
I'm serious.
It wasn't so much that I liked him...
I just lived my life
with my heart set on him.
Hoping to marry him?
My goal was just to see him again.
But the human heart is a fickle thing.
I shouldn't have gotten greedy.
Now I can't even see him anymore.
- Just see him anyway.
- How can I?
It's all in how you look at it, isn't it?
Could you do it if you were me?
The fact that we're here together
proves I can.
I wanted to marry you,
even while knowing everything.
Look, I know Yong Joong,
and he's more responsible
than anyone I know.
He'll come around and decide to marry you.
A forced decision means nothing.
It has to come from the heart.
- I'm not the one he truly loves.
- Who is?
Is there someone else?
I don't know.
I can tell you know.
What is there to hide at a time like this?
It can't be Momo, can it?
Is it?
I didn't say anything.
What's Yong Joong's appeal, anyway?
He seems pretty average to me.
Do women go for faces like that?
It's not his face.
It's his heart.
- What about his heart?
- His humanity.
And what am I, a wolf?
A monkey? A tiger?
The kind that soothes a person's soul.
He just has that quality about him.
If that's something you can learn,
I'd like to.
How does he soothe you?
If you feel like crying, just cry.
- Don't hold it in.
- You wouldn't understand.
You think you know me so well?
When you were a kid,
were you ever called anything
other than your name?
Like a term of endearment...
from your parents...
My mom would sometimes call me "Son,"
and as cringey as it sounds,
but sometimes "my prince."
I was only ever called Geum Ba Ra,
a name I don't even know who gave me.
It's not a bad name.
But...
he was the first person to ever call me,
"kiddo."
That's what he called me.
It was the first time in my life
I'd ever been called that.
No one had ever held me so tenderly,
and I had no memory
of being held in a warm embrace.
The first time we met at the supermarket,
he said, "Hey, kiddo,"
and he hugged me.
He said I was so small
that he thought I was a preschooler.
That feeling was seared into my soul.
I can never forget it.
That memory is what kept me going
all this time.
I endured
the world's scorn and prejudice...
to become worthy,
and when I appeared before him,
he just...
saw me as Ba Ra,
that little kid from the past.
He could.
How am I supposed to live now?
My purpose is gone, and I've lost my way.
I have no one to live for anymore.
What about me?
Won't I do?
Seriously...
We should just have a baby.
We'll have a son or a daughter,
and we'll live for our child.
Lately,
I've found myself wanting a child
of my own.
There's nothing else I want for,
but especially
after my father passed away,
I feel this void every now and then.
And I don't hate myself
for feeling this way.
Feeling lonely is part of being human,
isn't it?
Creating life is...
a magnificent thing.
Doesn't it make you feel
like humans are like deities?
Just think of it
as settling for second best.
Me.
I'll be your second best.
That's not who you are.
Who am I then?
I know that if you wanted to,
you could marry the only daughter...
of the Mihwa Group in a heartbeat.
I told you, I don't want for anything.
- I'd have to marry into her family.
- Someone socially prominent...
If I really wanted to,
I could achieve worldwide recognition.
Good for you.
The kind of feeling
you had for Yong Joong was...
the way people blindly fall for a deity.
- It wasn't real love.
- You just don't understand.
In time, you'll realize it.
For almost ten years, I've lived
thinking of and longing for only him.
Everything comes to an end.
Besides, have you never heard
of a mother's love?
I was abandoned by my own parents
the moment I was born.
But my mother told me herself...
that in her heart,
I was her number one priority.
My father was second.
She said it was our secret.
You'll understand
once you become a mother.
What kind of people must our parents be...
to have abandoned
their incredibly precious children?
When you feel an outburst coming,
just let it all out.
I'm not trying to force you,
but just think about it.
I don't understand.
After everything I've told you,
you still won't change your mind?
If we're keeping score,
Momo was even pregnant with my child.
If you only judge Momo by her looks,
most people would
probably be disappointed.
In the end, Yong Joong is no different.
You've had a first love, haven't you?
Of course you have.
The reason I ask is...
that I'm about to tell you
something that no one else knows.
Before my mom met my dad,
I heard she had a daughter
when she was 20.
To everyone else, she was the perfect mom,
who was completely devoted to me.
But she was always haunted by the daughter
she'd had but couldn't raise.
So the truth is, she took it out on me.
As she got older, it seemed
to weigh on her even more.
She agonized over the guilt,
making my life miserable.
And in the end,
that's the choice she made.
I had no choice but to get engaged to
Director Ju Shin because of her.
It was because of my mom.
Not even my agency knows.
She would either keep it all bottled up...
or sometimes, she'd just unload.
After that, I was just
her emotional dumping ground.
"Because of me..."
"If I'd understood her better,
maybe she wouldn't have made that choice?"
"Is it all my fault? Am I to blame?"
The guilt was...
unbearable.
For my mom's sake, I got engaged
and pretended to be happy,
but I just couldn't bring myself
to get married.
So...
my mom's first love wasn't my dad.
It all makes sense now.
Like I've said before,
I've been so envious of Ba Ra at times.
She always had you to lean on.
This might sound weird,
but from now on, you can lean on me.
Then one day,
when I started to wake up in the morning,
the first person I'd think of was you.
That's how I start my day now.
The heart wants what it wants, you know?
It's not a matter of willpower.
I know you might avoid me after this,
but I just had to be honest.
Just like Ba Ra, I...
Of all people, why me?
"Of all people?"
That's a strange way to put it.
You barged in and made yourself at home.
Tomorrow...
No, I'll pack my things
and leave right now.
I meant you barged into my heart
and made yourself at home.
I think I want to have a baby.
Good thinking.
But marry someone else.
What?
That's not fair to the child.
And I don't want to.
I'm the absolute worst.
Do you have a fraud conviction
or something?
Are you drowning in debt?
If you have debt, I'll pay it off.
You have a decent job,
and no offense,
but you're also quite presentable.
- It's not like you've had much work done.
- My heart is the problem.
Being with you is making me
understand Yong Joong.
Anyway, people's hearts are fickle.
- Feelings are intangible.
- Does it really not bother you?
It doesn't.
I'm just not uncomfortable
when we're together.
Just because you're not uncomfortable?
Do you want a confession of love?
No, that's not what I meant.
Fine, then.
That's important to me.
Even though we're living
in the same house,
it's crucial that we don't feel
like we're in each other's way.
I'd say we're compatible.
Don't overthink it.
Once you start, there's no end to it.
If you're curious not about what I am,
but about me as a man,
feel free to find out right now.
I'm ready to go whenever you are.
If anything, I'm better than Yong Joong.
Mr. Ha?
Hey!
Are you a member here?
I switched over since the King Hotel
is being renovated.
You're not worried
about something, are you?
The kids left, and so did Pickles.
Oh no.
And I still can't get a hold
of Reporter Geum.
Tell me about it.
I'm sure she's fine.
And with your birthday coming up,
I haven't heard a thing.
So I was wondering if I was left out.
I was planning on skipping it this year.
That makes sense.
Yesterday, Yong Joong and I...
just had a simple birthday dinner at home.
You did?
So you two decided to just be friends?
You haven't heard?
Heard what?
Come on, you can tell me.
I told Yong Joong...
honestly how I felt about him.
What in the world...
What's up?
I ran into Momo at the pool last night.
Is it true?
Is it?
- I'm thinking about it.
- What is there to think about?
We need to talk before you leave for work.
Momo is out of the question.
You should've told her that yourself,
then.
You came this morning just for that?
I stopped myself from coming last night.
Ha Yong Joong. Please don't disappoint me.
Where does that little fox get off,
going after you of all people?
If you actually get to know her,
Momo's had it rough.
What are you talking about? She blew it.
She's carrying a pain no one knows about.
Did something happen with another guy?
Besides Ju Shin?
She has...
an older sister from a different father.
I'll tell you more once I find my child.
Is she someone I might know?
Could it be Hyun Ran Hee?
It doesn't add up.
Paul Kim only found out
about this recently...
after he returned to Korea.
Do you have any lunch plans today?
- Just you tonight?
- Yes.
Just make me something.
Not from my bottle.
You got it.
You don't marry someone out of pity.
It's not pity.
Don’t end up as a laughingstock.
(The Mind)
(Nua General Hospital)
(Ju Shin)
Have a seat.
I didn't buy these myself.
A patient gave it to me as a thank-you
when they were discharged.
You look well.
That's a relief.
(Ba Ra: You look well. That's a relief.)
We must be flexible.
- Did you check it?
- They're on loan from that department.
We'll support them until next week...
I haven't seen you in a while.
I stopped by last time,
but they said you were in Paris.
Right. I was there for a hair show.
Oh my gosh.
Momo's wedding announcement
just hit the news.
With Director Shin Ju Shin?
The game developer, Ha Yong Joong?
Oh, I know him.
The guy who made 100 million from a game.
One hundred million dollars?
So that must be why
she broke up with Director Shin.
You didn't know either?
I know you're not happy about this,
but I need you to trust my decision.
If Mom and Dad were still here,
you wouldn't have made this decision.
- Am I wrong?
- It's fate.
I think we were meant to be.
Meant to be? It's still not too late...
It's better to call it off now
than a breakup once you're attached.
You know me better than that.
What did Ju Shin say?
I haven't yet. I wanted to tell you first.
You'll regret this. Mark my words.
- You know how right my hunches are.
- Even if they do, I can't help it.
This is what's best for now.
It's only what's best for Momo.
Momo has plenty of guys lined up.
She could have anyone she wants.
Ha Yong Joong.
I'm begging you.
That's why I should just do
whatever it takes to break them up.
My brother could do so much better.
Do you have any idea
how much Choi Hye Ri begged for an intro?
I guess you'll have to design the dress.
How can I design a dress
when I feel like this?
But you'll design one for me, right?
For which embassy party?
My wedding dress.
With Director Shin?
Yes.
Congratulations.
Did you hear from Ju Shin?
Reporter Geum is getting married
after all.
He proposed with this ring.
How could I say no?
Isn't it a little big?
Maybe a little.
It's not like he could ask for my size.
Besides, I'll probably gain weight
after we have kids anyway.
You're happy for me, right?
Of course.
She's just forcing a smile.
She probably wants to break down and cry.
You should move into my place.
No point in leaving that big house empty.
Why would I do that?
Have the housekeeper stop by to clean.
It was just a polite offer.
Be my bridesmaid.
Your actress friends are closer to you.
You could ask Jang Ma Ri, Cecilia,
or An Ri.
I'm sure they'd all say yes.
- May I clear your plates?
- Yes.
You barely touched your food.
I'm the one who should be on a diet.
I had a salad for lunch.
You had your phone off,
and your account set to private.
I was worried about you.
I just wanted some time
completely to myself.
I'm sorry.
I'm a huge fan.
This reminds me of when we first met.
I guess it wasn't the very first time.
We saw each other at the press conference.
Here is the sea bass ceviche.
I should've asked her sooner...
about how they met.
(Yong Joong)
Hello?
Can you meet me at your complex
in about 30 minutes?
You're coming here?
Okay.
I haven't let on until now,
or I should say, I couldn't.
The truth is,
I've had similar feelings for you, Momo.
But you're not just anyone.
Really?
I don't even have flowers...
I know this isn't the right way
to do this, but...
I'm asking you to marry me.
No way!
Thank you, Director Ju Shin.
For making me Momo
and for slapping some sense into me.
What about Ba Ra? Does she know?
No.
I have one condition.
I don't want any other woman
being that familiar with you.
Not even Ba Ra.
When you took care of her more
than you would a real sister,
I started to wonder...
if you had other feelings
for her several times.
Does Ba Ra come before me?
Is she your priority?
I understand.
I get what you're saying.
The world is so big,
and it's got so much delicious food.
Are you giving up on your diet?
I have to eat well to have a healthy baby.
We're going to start trying
as soon as we're married.
Just to rub it in Director Shin's face.
We'll start trying once we're married,
just to rub it in Director Shin's face.
I've decided to just get married too.
To Director Shin.
So that's what you decided
while you disappeared.
We're going to do it quietly,
without starting rumors.
How can there not be rumors?
He's my ex-fiancé.
I'm pretty close with
most of the entertainment reporters.
It's to be considerate of Director Shin.
So he's your consolation prize?
Director Shin instead of Yong Joong?
Wealth instead of love?
Geum Ba Ra,
you're just a materialist after all.
I'm having my dress made by James.
You're more shrewd than I thought.
After he proposed to you,
you disappeared, pretending to be torn up.
I didn't just disappear.
I was with Director Shin.
It's an easy situation to misunderstand.
I'll be the one to clear it up.
I've packed everything.
Without announcing it publicly,
I'd like to have a small, simple wedding.
I know I'm not in a position to ask,
but please, just grant me this.
It's not improper at all.
Any news articles about me...
won't do you any good.
This isn't a marriage of convenience.
When you find someone you just want
to spend your life with,
that's when you make up your mind.
I will do my best...
so I don't disappoint you.
Don't try to clear things up.
It'll just make things weirder.
I heard everything from Ba Ra.
What are your thoughts...
about Ba Ra?
There's a foreign poem.
I don't remember the poet,
but there's a line that goes,
"A thought once spoken is a lie."
That's just a poem, not reality.
Don't try to dodge the question.
It's pointless and improper...
to share what I think
without her presence.
Then you two should talk it out properly.
You said you heard it all, didn't you?
It's not that I don't trust you,
but if you'll use this against her
and stress her out, call it off now.
What if I call it off?
Will you cancel your wedding too?
What you think you know
might not be the truth.
- It could be a misunderstanding.
- What misunderstanding?
I don't know.
Maybe this is just how it's meant to be.
You believe in fate now?
Since when?
Depends on the situation.
I'm asking you again,
don't treat Ba Ra
the way you treated Momo.
You have no right to say that to me.
Think about it from Ba Ra's point of view.
What did she say to you?
Was she hurt?
It's not as simple...
as getting hurt or hurting someone.
Stop beating around the bush.
Get to the point with facts.
(Doctor Shin)
Be wary of Jin Ju.
Once she stabs you in the back,
she's bound to do it again.
You've figured it out, haven't you?
Kim Gwang Cheol was right.
He said she'd never kill herself.
If I spill everything,
people are going to lose their minds.
If I wear makeup, I'll outshine the groom.
Reporter Geum, are we at the same table?
I'm not sure.
I might not let you see the baby
when it's born.
You'd better treat me right.
The wedding ceremony of Ha Yong Joong
and Momo will begin shortly.
- Did you have lunch?
- A little while ago.
- What about you?
- I'll starve a little to fit into a tux.
I knew it.
Momo, you'd never do that to me.
If you're going to become Momo,
Yong Joong can't find out.
This might be the last chance you get.
Excuse me! Wait!
I've pulled it off both times,
so don't worry about a thing.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)