[1927]
Are you done?
Please stay still, Miss. I'm almost done.
All done.
Wow! I'm quite a pretty girl.
So pretty. My girl is the prettiest.
What is the point of getting dolled up when nobody can see me?
I've never left my house.
Who is here, Lang? Let's go and have a look.
Please don't go! Your dad could scold you.
This way, sir.
Lang, who is he?
He is Lord Sampanpanich, he works for the ministry.
Why did you ask?
I'm visiting your place quite often.
But I've never asked if you're annoyed by my company.
How could I be?
You're talking about business with my dad.
I've done talking about business with him a while ago.
I keep visiting your place because of something else.
What is this tree called? I like its fruits.
This is pomegranate tree, a lucky tree.
Its fruits produce many seeds.
We believe that planting this tree
will bring plenty of children to house owners.
If that so,
I think I should plant the tree at my house.
Will it be alright if I ask for the seed from your house to plant at mine?
Well…
I'm not sure.
The pomegranate tree belongs to my dad.
You should ask him.
If he allows it,
will the expert of pomegranate come to live at my house?
I wish both of you to grow old together and live happily.
When you marry my son,
you need to love him dearly.
I've never known anything about love.
What does it like?
I will teach you, Shen.
This painting is called…
Make Love.'
Make Love?'
Make love...
is an action of affirmation to show true love among two people.
Don't be scared.
Just follow my lead.
I will take it slow.
Thank you
for teaching me about love.
I think I will miss you so much.
We just got married
and next week we will be apart.
I really don't want to go to Penang.
Don't say that.
It's the government work and you can't avoid it.
One more thing, we haven't been apart yet.
My mom used to tell me that
we need to spend every moment as memorable
as possible before we are deemed to part.
You're right.
In that case,
before I leave,
I will love you every day.
And we…
will be happy together.
Please wait for me,
I will come back and make love to you every night.
I've told you a million times that you can't make sound when you eat.
When you were at your house,
was it necessary to eat like you were starving your whole life?
Watch your manners.
I'm sorry, Mother.
It's been three months already and there is no sign for Perm to return.
You must be so lonely.
You can come and hang out with me if you like.
You can talk to me about anything.
Try some Massaman curry.
I can get it for you.
Term, didn't you forget?
Shen doesn't eat soup curry.
She is worried that it could upset her stomach.
Am I right, Shen?
- I…
- What?
You've been living in this house for so long
and you haven't tried curry?
This is a Thai family household.
If you don't eat curry, what can you eat?
We won't cook you the food that you're familiar with
because we are not fond of Chinese food.
Why don't you try spicy shrimp paste?
If my brother comes home and he sees you getting slimmer,
he would be mad at us for not taking good care of you.
Thank you.
But…
actually I can eat some curry and coconut milk soup.
Well, isn't it great?
Let me give you some.
Oh my!
Rayrai!
Thank you.
Watch out, it could burn.
Look at that, you just made a couple get mad at each other.
But I didn't do anything.
Don't talk back to me.
My elder brother is not around.
I need to take care of his wife for him.
What is wrong with you? Why are you getting jealous?
Should I get jealous?
Shen just moved in
and you were trying to please her more than
pleasing me for a whole year.
Women are so overthinking. This is so annoying.
Where are you going?
To hang out with Shen,
isn't it great?
Term! She is your sister-in-law.
You need to behave. Don't be so gross.
Rayrai!
You need to lower your jealousy with me.
I think I keep you full all the time.
Or your desire is higher than others?
If you want some,
I can give it to you.
Or you don't want it anymore?
Aunt Somsong prepared you a bigger bowl today.
But I can feed you only little bites, please don't get bored before I'm done.
Should I
feed you bigger bites instead?
I'm joking.
Little bite.
Hello, this is Pipatratsada residence.
You've learned how to prepare fruits for months,
and you still haven't done it properly.
I pushed the knife too deep?
When your mom was still around,
hasn't she passed on any knowledge about homemaking skills?
Or your kind only know about slaughtering ducks and chickens?
You don't eat fruits so you don't know how to prepare them properly?
So you don't want it anymore?
I can share it with kitchen staffers.
Khunying.
Someone from the ministry just called to inform you that
your son will come home in two days.
- Really?
- That's right.
Perm, my dear.
You need to go to the kitchen
and tell them to prepare Perm's favorite dishes.
Okay.
Where are you rushing to?
To the kitchen.
Are you really lonely lately?
What are you talking about?
I saw you sneak up on us last night.
If that is what you really want,
I can give it to you.
Term,
I am your sister-in-law.
Stop saying something disgusting like this already.
Why's that?
My brother has been away for three months now.
It's fine if you get lonely.
Even if I get lonely, I wouldn't trouble you with that for sure.
Besides, someone at the ministry called to let us know that
your brother will be home in two days.
Hello, honey.
Your favorite steamed rice dumplings.
I learned to make it when you were away.
So tasty.
Do you remember Tone, Soi's son, who used to work here?
Sure, I do.
I heard that her whole family moved to Penang.
Did you get to meet him?
I did, he seemed like a hard-working guy.
So I recruited him to work here.
- He will be here next week.
- What position?
We don't have any job for him at the moment.
I hired him to be Shen's personal driver.
Hey, I ordered a car from Italy, just for you.
Honey?
Shen is not that busy, she doesn't need her own car.
I think it's way too much for her
- to have her own personal driver.
- That's right.
I still need to ride a tricycle taxi to work every day.
Since you bought the car already,
I think we should use it as a family car.
I can use it in the morning for work,
and Tone can drive Mom and Rayrai
for some errands later.
- What do you think, Mom?
- Great idea.
I bought this car with my own money.
I also paid Tone from my own pocket.
Shen will be the one who can use these.
What? Can't you share the car with me? I'm your brother.
Share?
I'm an eldest son.
I've shared everything with you my whole life,
but not this time, I won't.
On the other hand, have you ever shared anything with me?
Am I right, Little Nualnoy?
Father?
Look who's here with me?
Hello, Father.
I heard that my wife was the one feeding you every day.
Do you like her?
I'm glad to see both of you get along really well.
A penny for your thoughts?
Nothing in particular, dear.
About the car,
I think it'd be a great idea to share it with the family.
I don't normally need it to go anywhere.
I bought you a car and you denied it?
You don't really need it but you can still have it.
You're Lord Sampanpanich's wife and you need something to show, okay?
Your return
is the greatest gift that I could ask for.
I missed y…
Are you alright?
I was just worried about work tomorrow.
I haven't been to the ministry for three months.
I'm not sure about how it will go.
You should go to bed first.
- But I…
- I told you to go to bed.
Please wait for me,
I will come back and make love to you every night.
[Chanting.]
Tone! You're here!
Hello, sir.
How are you? Are you exhausted?
Not at all, sir. I slept all the way
from Hat Yai to Hua Lamphong.
Good. What about the car? Any trouble at all?
It's in good shape. The mechanic checked it already.
Good.
- Come here.
- Yes, sir.
This is Shen, my wife. She will be your new boss.
Nice to meet you, Ms. Shen.
No need to be formal. We're around the same age.
This is Tone. He will be your personal driver.
See? Isn't my wife so pretty?
Yes, sir.
You're all grown up now, Tone. So big.
Let me see your face closer.
You're as good-looking as your dad.
How are your parents?
Mom has some medical conditions.
Other than that, she's doing well.
Good. I'm glad you're working for us.
Even though, you're not working for me directly.
- Shen is such a lucky girl.
- Mom!
I can guarantee you that she won't recognize you for sure.
Auntie, look who's here with me?
Who?
Hello, Aunt Somsong.
You look so familiar but I can't recall.
I'm Tone, Soi's son.
What? You're Tone? You're all grown up now.
And you're handsome just like an actor from a live soap opera.
I see.
Tone will be living with us.
Mr. Perm hired him to be Ms. Shen's personal driver.
That's great.
The more the merrier, kid.
Tone, this is Duang. He is Mr. Perm's personal driver.
They are Noy and Prapai.
Hello, nice to meet you.
Tone, can you tell us more about Penang?
Did you live close to the beach?
He is exhausted from all the traveling. Let him rest.
Let's go. I'll take you to our room, you're sharing it with me.
- Nice.
- Let's go.
Tone, when you're done, please come here and hang out with me.
Let's go.
Thank you.
I've never thought that I would get a gift this huge.
It's just a car.
Well..
should we ride around the city?
You can test the new car.
I'm busy tomorrow.
Or…
should we go to Bang Saen next week?
Just like when we first got married…
You should go there by yourself if you want to.
I gave you a car, I hired a personal driver for you.
What more do you want?
- I…
- I'm going to bed. I'm tired.
Nothing has changed in the past 10 years.
Except us, we are growing.
I still remember us
skinny dipping and jumping in the river.
Tone, do you want to reenact my memory?
Should we jump in the river to cool us down?
You crazy? No way.
People can see us, that would be so embarrassing.
You lived abroad for more than 10 years.
You must have used only foreign language.
When you speak Thai, it sounds weird.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Hey, Tone!
- What do you mean by that?
- Huh?
It's not like that. You got it all wrong.
- Are you sure?
- Yup.
Hey, Shin.
Can I ask you something?
- Shoot.
- About Ms. Shen.
What is she like?
I will work for her so I know how to behave.
Well, at first glance,
she looked so pitiful.
Then I took a second glance, I saw her eyes
and she was like that woman who hides her stubbornness.
And…
what's the deal between Mr. Perm and Ms. Sern?
Deal? Like what?
- They're married couple.
- I know, but…
Do they really love each other?
Or is it just an arranged marriage?
Nope, not arranged marriage for sure.
Mr. Perm chose his own wife.
Ms. Shen is a daughter of a Chinese businessman.
Mr. Perm fell in love with her when he visited her dad's house.
He really loves his wife.
- Don't you dare doing something nasty to her.
- Come on!
Who would dare? She is my boss' wife.
Why do you have to be be so mad about it?
Let's go to sleep.
What?
Then she grabbed Laothong's arm,
Khunpaen yelled to stop, and raised his hands to protect.
Shen,
where are you going?
I think I will visit my place for a bit.
I haven't been to my home for a while.
This is your place.
You're married to this family. What other places are you going to visit?
I need to talk to my dad.
Khunphra was fed already.
It won't be long. I will be back soon.
I know that you don't have to run errands.
You just want to show off your new car to people.
I won't allow you to go.
Don't you hear it? You can't go.
Go back to the kitchen.
Help Erb prepare for lunch. Go!
Okay.
Tone.
Yes, ma'am.
- Can you give me a ride to my house?
- Sure.
Where is it, ma'am?
Talat Noi. I'll tell you where.
Sure, ma'am.
If you love yourself and you feel embarrassed, then you need to stop.
Don't cause a scene or you will be mortified.
If you don't listen…
Right.
Is that a car?
I think so.
Who told you that you could read this romance novel?
Why can't I?
It's nothing but love story. Why are you reading it?
- I…
- I will burn it.
If I find out that
you continue reading it,
I will flog you so bad.
Dad!
Miss?
My teacher said that it was just a book about young people's love.
Why didn't my dad forbid me from reading it?
Can't I know anything about love?
If you dad won't let you read it,
then you should listen to him.
If you want to know about love,
someone will teach you all about it one day.
Thank you.
- Ms. Shen!
- Lang!
You can park the car over there.
Okay.
Sir, look who is here?
Shen? Why are you here?
I'm visiting you, Dad.
I've been away for months,
you're not going to ask me how I am doing?
You look fine to me.
Are you behaving well?
Did you cook for them?
I did. But they don't eat Chinese food.
So I need to learn to cook Thai food.
Good. Just learn whatever they want you to.
Don't cross them
or it could affect my business.
All you care about is your business?
That's right. What else should I care about?
People in that place hurt your feeling again, didn't they?
My poor baby.
Your dad never shows his love to you
and your new family keeps pushing you.
But your husband is home now, it will get better, right?
I thought it would be like that
but since he got back
he hasn't been the same.
What? What is going on?
He bought me so many things,
including the car and my personal driver.
Still, he hasn't been the same.
Well…
I mean…
did you fulfill your duty as a wife?
That could be the reason if you didn't.
Please don't be shy.
This is totally normal.
On the contrary, when I tried to be closer to him,
he kept pushing me away.
What?
I tried to make us be happy together
like before he was sent off to Penang.
We were so happy on daily basis back then.
He taught me about love.
When he was back,
it seemed like he didn't want it anymore.
This is weird.
When the man just got married,
his desire would occur so often.
What about you?
What about your drive?
This is completely normal.
Of course, I want to do it.
Can you get me this set?
Please wait.
Just try the recipe.
You boiled it for your dad all the time.
If your husband's blood and pressure flows better,
things will get better eventually.
You think it's because of his exhaustion from work, right?
It's not because he isn't in love with me anymore, right?
Don't say that.
Why would be stop loving you?
Let me carry it, ma'am.
Thank you.
Are you hungry? I can hear your stomach.
Nope.
I saw a noodles shop over there. It looked good.
If you're hungry, you should get something to eat.
It's fine.
If you don't eat when it's time, it will hurt your stomach.
Gastritis is hard to cure.
I'll wait for you there.
You're not hungry?
I…
You can sit with me and eat, I don't mind.
Okay.
Why are you smiling?
It's nothing, ma'am.
I also slurp like this at home.
You should try, it makes the food taste better.
You're right. It does taste better.
So you're close to Perm since you were young?
I was born in this house.
Mr. Perm and Mr. Term are a little bit older than me.
We played together since we were kids.
But I'm closer to Mr. Perm.
Mr. Term liked to tease me.
Khunphra and Khunying adored me as well.
They raised you? That's why you are so polite and neat.
Actually, I'm not that neat.
I was a stubborn kid growing up.
Were you?
One time,
Mr. Perm and I played in the rice field.
We played in mud and it was all over our bodies.
When we went home, his mom whipped me so bad.
What is wrong with you?
Why did you play in mud like that?
How could you let Perm play with you like this?
- She whipped you?
- That's right.
You must be a stubborn kid for sure.
Like a little monkey, ma'am.
Do you know a place where I can boil some soup for my husband?
I think Mother will make a big fuss
if I try to cook it at home.
And my dad will get suspicious
if I go back to his house.
What type of soup is that?
It's for nourishing his body.
He seems a little tired lately.
It's Chinese herbal remedy and I can't cook it at home.
Mother will get so mad.
I think I know a place.
Whose cottage is this?
Can we use it?
Khunphra owns this land and he rents it for farmers to plant rice.
Nobody is living in the cottage.
They will be here during harvesting and planting seasons.
I ran around this place when I was a kid.
This way, ma'am.
The kitchen is in the back.
Here it is.
I will take you to the temple next time.
Good, let's go.
Shen hasn't come back yet?
Ms. Shen, please drink some water.
Thanks.
You seem so happy to live with Mr. Perm.
Why did you move?
My dad worked for the store that imported products from Penang.
When I was 11 years old, his boss wanted to move back.
So he took my mom and I along to Penang.
You must be so good at speaking English since you were there for years.
I spoke English at school every day.
But I spoke Thai when I was home.
Is it hard? To speak English.
Can you teach me later?
I want to…
speak English.
Really? It's not that hard.
I can teach you.
It seems like it's going to be hard for me.
Ms. Shen, are you okay?
Ms. Shen?
This is nothing, it will get better.
Okay.
I think I will walk around a little bit.
Can you watch it for me?
If the water is lower to half the pot, then you can stop.
Got it, ma'am.
Where were you?
I told you not to go anywhere.
What is in the pot?
I went outside and cooked soup for my husband.
He seems a little tired lately.
I won't let my son eat any Chinese food.
Shin, throw it away.
I said to throw it way.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm sorry.
Follow me.
Hey, you need to park it properly.
Let's go.
I know that I disobeyed you.
But I didn't do anything wrong.
Let me decide if it was right or wrong.
I am a master of this house.
If one of you won't listen to me,
how can I control the rest of the house.
You disobeyed me and you will be punished.
Turn around.
Khunying.
I am the one who drove her around.
It's my fault.
Please punish me instead.
Your boss ordered you to driver her around.
You followed her order.
I won't punish you, just go.
If that's the case, I am her personal driver,
- please punish me instead.
- Tone!
Leave!
I told you to leave.
Yes, ma'am.
If you wish to whip me, just do so. Let's get it over with.
Don't challenge me.
You're home, sir.
I'm home?
Watch out, sir.
Mother? What is going on?
Why did you punish my wife like this?
She disobeyed me and left the house.
I expected her to help me in the kitchen and she was gone.
Mother.
Shen is one of your help.
She is my wife. If she doesn't want to be in the kitchen,
then you can't make her go to the kitchen.
Perm?
Hey!
You can't behave like this to me when you're drunk.
Mother.
I bought her car and I hired a driver for her,
because she can go anywhere that she likes.
Why did you stop her?
Everyone.
- Yes, sir.
You all need to leave Shen alone, you hear me?
Shen is my wife.
And I want her to be the happiest girl in this house.
Perm?
Why are you so rude to me?
You're too obsessed with your wife and you're ignoring me?
Perm?
You can go anywhere that you want.
Don't listen to her.
Let Tone take you.
You're too drunk.
I..
I will get some damp cloth to clean you.
It's too hot.
Shen.
Do you miss me?
Of course, I do.
I've always missed you.
What are you trying to do?
What are you doing?
- I..I was just…
- Don't do it again next time.
- But I..
- I said don't do it!
Make love...
is an action of affirmation to show true love among two people.
You are the one who taught me this.
- When you came back…
- Listen to me!
I will do it with you
whenever I want to.
And we will not talk about this anymore.
There will be a party at my boss' palace.
I will take you to the party.
Is it the gown?
I can guarantee you that Ms. Shen will be the prettiest girl in the party.
But I think it can be more beautiful.
If there is anything I can do on behalf of Mr. Perm,
please let me know.
Sir, I heard that
you just came back from Penang, didn't you?