[speaking Cypriot Greek]
[Fisk] This is a terrorist attack.
Orchestrated and executed
by the vigilante of Hell's Kitchen.
[Karen] I can't go with you.
No, I know. I...
-I didn't come to get you.
-Fucking great minds, huh?
[Daredevil] He's gonna prosecute you
and humiliate you,
and make everyone cheer for it.
-[Karen] That means there'll be cameras.
-Exactly.
[Kirsten] Can you tell me
about those scars?
I got these in a firefight
with Daredevil and Frank Castle.
-[Kirsten] Was the defendant there?
-I was told she drove the getaway vehicle.
You were told?
What else did Officer Powell tell you?
-[gun fires]
-[crowd screams]
Did he tell you to kill Hector Ayala?
[Daredevil] You wanted
one good deed, right?
[choking]
[Dex] You know I can't make any promises.
[Buck] Where is she?
[Daniel] She's not coming.
-[groans]
-Where, Daniel?
How long till you're on the floor
with a gun pointed at your head?
[♪ theme music playing]
[♪ pensive music playing]
[chattering indistinctly]
-[judge] Miss McDuffie?
-[gavel bangs]
[dial tone sounding]
-Anything?
-Nope. No answer again.
Shit.
Is everything all right, Miss McDuffie?
Will Mr. Murdock be joining us today?
We're fine, Your Honor.
Please don't wait on us.
Uh, Matt is tied up,
but he should be along shortly.
[groans] God damn it, Jessica.
-Oh, knock it off.
-[Matt winces]
And you're not even that bad.
[sighs] That's easy for you to say.
I'm not built like you.
You've never tried childbirth.
[chuckles]
[winces]
-You good?
-Yeah, I'm fine. I'm-- I'll be fine.
Just need some...
medication, some rest.
Maybe a total knee replacement.
You came back, huh?
Thought you were done with Fisk.
With New York.
This shit has gotten so far outta hand.
I know.
Can you stop him?
Not alone.
Well, that was kind of the idea.
[Matt] I don't think
he's gonna kill Karen.
At least,
not until he gets me in his sights.
Which is exactly where I need to be.
[knocking on door, door opens]
Buck.
Sir.
Did Daniel deliver Miss Urich as promised?
No.
I think I'm only now understanding
the responsibility of someone
who's elected by millions...
chosen... by millions of New Yorkers.
I hear the whispers.
They think that my grief has clouded
my judgment. Do you believe that?
No, sir.
It seems Murdock has survived the night.
[Buck] You really wanna do this?
I will make arrangements.
Thank you, Buck.
[Heather] Her demeanor is combative.
She exhibits the classic hallmarks
of antisocial personality disorder.
Antisocial personality disorder.
What we used to refer to as a sociopath?
-Exactly.
-[door opens]
Miss Page continues to unravel.
In our interview last night,
she demonstrated hostility, duplicity--
[Matt] Objection. It's prejudicial.
Sidesteps any objective diagnosis
with conjecture.
Mr. Hochberg, you know better.
Mr. Murdock, are you okay?
I am outstanding. Thank you, Your Honor.
Mr. Hochberg, please continue.
-Sorry I'm late.
-[whispers] Late?
I thought you were dead.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, I'm fine.
-Just got shot in the leg.
-[Hochberg] Dr. Glenn...
I was wondering if you would
read to us a passage
from your latest book, Men in Masks.
"The Psychology of Vigilantes."
Especially interested
in Chapter 2, page 35.
Of course.
"The vigilante's mask
does not hide his public face,
"in fact, it reveals his private face.
"The real mask is the one
that he wears in his public life.
"The dutiful boyfriend,
the responsible boss...
"the loyal son."
Thank you so much. No further questions.
Your witness.
So, let me get this straight.
You said, "The real mask is the face
the vigilante wears in public," right?
The son, the boss, the boyfriend...
Maybe even the clinical professional?
Is that a question?
Dr. Glenn, did you strike Miss Page
during your evaluation last night?
-[Hochberg] Objection.
-Absolutely not.
-Sustained.
-No further questions.
[scoffs]
Actually, I have a question.
Dr. Glenn, does...
does a vigilante need a mask?
-How do you mean, specifically?
-In your professional opinion,
would my client qualify as a vigilante
if she never cultivated an alter ego?
-Or, as you call it, a mask?
-Sure.
She didn't need a mask.
She hid behind Daredevil's.
In the same way that you're hiding
behind the Fisk administration.
-[Hochberg] Objection.
-[judge] Sustained.
I see. Thank you. No further questions.
[judge] The court is recessed for lunch.
When we return,
-the defense can call its first witness.
-[gavel bangs]
[man chattering indistinctly
over radio]
[camera beeping]
[Judge Grimes] Mmm-hmm.
And the prosecution has no objections?
Oh, far from it, Your Honors.
We welcome Mr. Murdock's self-sabotage.
-I'll allow it.
-Thank you, Your Honor.
Call your witness.
The defense calls Mayor Wilson Fisk.
[audience murmuring indistinctly]
[♪ dramatic opera music playing]
[bailiff] Raise your right hand.
Do you swear to tell the truth,
the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth,
so help you God?
[heart thumping]
I do.
State your full name.
Wilson Grant Fisk.
[whispering indistinctly]
You know, when I was a boy...
I was taught to find
the biggest man, and...
bring him down.
But as I grew, I realized
that no man stands as tall
as this courthouse,
these institutions.
[clears throat]
That was lovely, Mr. Mayor.
Thank you for joining us today.
Not at all. I consider it my civic duty,
and I welcome the opportunity
to see my Safer Streets Initiative
in action, to see justice prevail.
[Matt] I was a little surprised
you, uh, showed up.
I could say the same for you.
Thank you. I'll live.
[screams, grunts]
[screams]
[breathing heavily]
[chuckles softly]
Argh!
God!
Fuck!
[groans]
[Bullseye chuckles]
Poseur.
The Safer Streets Initiative
was born out of necessity.
It was created to save lives,
lives destroyed by vigilante violence.
It's too late for Foggy Nelson. It's...
too late for Muse's victims,
for Officer Saunders.
And, uh, my wife, Vanessa.
But we can bring these criminals,
like Karen Page and Daredevil, to justice.
People we lost deserve that.
People of New York...
deserve that.
I'm sorry, was that an answer
or a speech, Mr. Mayor?
You asked me why I enacted
the Safer Streets Initiative.
You, of all people, should know.
You were there.
Ah, I see. Yes.
When Bullseye took a shot at you--
Actually, you called me a hero
that night, didn't you?
Objection. Can we have
a little relevance, please?
Sustained. Get to the point, Counselor.
My point is that,
as the mayor stated before,
the statute that my client
is being charged under
was supposedly created to protect the city
from criminal vigilantes.
-Is that a fair assessment, Mr. Mayor?
-It is.
And are the streets safer?
Statistics say they are, yes.
But there is still lawlessness...
Of course.
I mean, some might say, rounding people up
and throwing them into detention
without due process is lawless.
Objection. Immaterial. Invites conjecture.
Sustained.
-Your Honor, I'll rephrase.
-Thank you.
Mr. Mayor, your policies,
as harsh as they may be,
did not prevent
a criminal from taking a shot at you
and, ultimately, murdering your wife.
An assassin, actually,
who I believe was once in your employ.
Objection. This is contemptible,
even for Counselor Murdock.
Sustained. This kitchen sink approach
is getting tedious.
Your Honor, there is a point to all this.
Please remember what my colleague
asked at the beginning of this trial.
"What is a vigilante? What is a criminal?"
Please.
You really wanna do this, Mr. Murdock?
Oh, absolutely, sir.
Karen Page is charged with,
among many other crimes,
aiding Daredevil in the sinking
of the Northern Star,
resulting in the death of its crew.
Mister Fisk, were you aware
that the Northern Star
is smuggling illegal arms into
New York City via the free port
that is owned
by the Fisk Industries Trust?
Objection. Assumes evidence
not on the record.
Sustained.
[chuckles] Yeah.
Mr. Mayor,
did Daredevil sink the Northern Star?
The evidence says yes.
No, it doesn't.
The evidence does not suggest that.
The only thing that's been presented
is testimony from Officer Powell,
who is in your employ,
who takes his orders from you.
It is the allegation
of the District Attorney,
who, guess what, is in your employ,
takes his orders from you.
-[Hochberg] Objection.
-Overruled.
Your Honor, at this point, I would like to
introduce evidence regarding
the Northern Star.
Video testimony from the ship's
first mate, Christofi Savva.
-[Hochberg] Objection. Video testimony?
-Overruled.
Mr. Savva was duly deposed
by Miss McDuffie before he "disappeared."
Considering the flexible standards
of this court,
such evidence should be admissible.
-Christ, this is turning into a circus.
-Mr. Hochberg,
I think we've been
under the big top for a while now.
I'd like to see counselors in chambers.
Mr. Savva's testimony is substantial
and relevant in and of itself.
-The man's not even present in court.
-It doesn't matter that he's not present.
-And relevant to what?
-It-- What--
[Fisk] Murdock...
There are things I can say in here
that will ruin your life.
With the complete support
of the legal system,
I can have you thrown in a cell forever.
I could say the same about you.
-Excuse me?
-Hmm?
No, about relevance, Your Honor.
Karen Page is charged with
providing support to terrorist attacks.
It's the definition of relevance
that the defense provide
exculpatory evidence
about one such attack.
And a basis for appeal
if such evidence is suppressed.
There's not going to be any appeal.
[chuckles] You're saying that out loud
in front of the judges?
You wanna just hand Fisk
the robes and gavel?
We'll allow it.
Thank you.
My name is Christofi Savva.
I was the first mate on the Northern Star.
We were under orders to sink the ship
if it was ever boarded.
[McDuffie] Why was that?
[Christofi] Because the Northern Star
was carrying weapons,
military grade, very illegal.
[McDuffie] Who sank the Northern Star,
Mr. Savva?
[Christofi] My captain,
Achilleo Kyriaco.
[McDuffie] Not Daredevil?
[Christofi] Not Daredevil.
[McDuffie] But he was there?
Yes. He found the weapons.
[McDuffie] And who is was the one
who ordered you to scuttle the ship?
[Christofi] Achilleo has called him...
[speaking Cypriot Greek]
[in English] ...the Kingpin...
but we knew it was the Mayor.
-Wilson Fisk.
-[gavel bangs]
-[Justice Waters] Order! Order!
-[Hochberg] Your Honors,
the witness we just heard from
is not in court.
As such, his testimony remains immaterial,
unless it can be corroborated by someone
who was actually on the Northern Star.
And that is exactly
what I intend to do, Your Honors.
Then please, by all means, do so.
Mr. Mayor, through evidence testimony
in your own statements,
we have determined that Daredevil
was on the Northern Star, correct?
It's safe to say.
So, if only we could ask him
what he witnessed that night.
I welcome going down this road
with you, Mr. Murdock.
As do I.
Is it safe to say
you don't really like Daredevil?
Safe to say, yes.
But what if the people of New York
disagree with you, sir?
What if the public actually think
that Daredevil is a hero?
[laughs] The people know better.
Do they?
I mean, I guess it depends
on how you define a hero.
Take me, for example.
I took a bullet for you, didn't I?
Would that make me a hero?
[audience murmuring indistinctly]
[cameras snapping]
It's a simple yes or no question, sir.
Am I a hero?
[Hochberg] I'm sorry, Your Honors,
what does any of this nonsense
have to do with Karen Page?
Who, I remind you, is the only person,
as of now, on trial here today.
My client's being tried in a court
created by one man,
who has an obsession with one vigilante
a vigilante who sent him to prison
on more than one occasion.
[Justice Waters] Mister Murdock,
we allowed you
admission of the video testimony.
-Use it or lose it. Please. Now.
-[Matt] With pleasure.
Mister Fisk, did you or did you not
orchestrate the sale
of military-grade weapons
through the official use of your office,
and then order the Northern Star
to be scuttled when your plan was exposed?
-Do not answer that, sir.
-Why not answer it?
-Do not answer it.
-Answer it, sir.
[yells] I will answer it!
[audience gasps, murmurs]
You don't get to know
what comes through our port.
All you need to know is that
I'm running this city and it's thriving.
Anything else is
above your paygrade, little man.
Your... Your video proves no wrongdoing
by the mayor, Murdock. It's all hearsay.
Correct, but we have established there was
another witness on that boat, haven't we?
A witness who, in fact,
is in this courtroom today.
-Isn't that right, Mr. Mayor?
-[audience gasps, murmurs]
You and I both know who Daredevil is.
He's the man who knows exactly
what happened on the Northern Star.
He knows exactly
what happened in my apartment,
and he knows exactly who the real criminal
in this courtroom is. Isn't that right?
[grunts]
You are a fool.
No, I'm not.
-I am Daredevil.
-[audience gasps, murmurs]
[Hochberg] But-- Objection.
-Objection!
-[Justice Waters] Order!
-[Hochberg] Your Honors, this is insane.
-[Justice Waters] Order! Order.
-[gavel banging]
-Order, please!
-[Hochberg] Representing a criminal?
What is this?
Are you, honestly,
going to tell this court
-that Daredevil is a blind man?
-[audience gasps]
Order. Order!
A blind lawyer who can fight.
-[Justice Waters] Order, please!
-[Hochberg] This is an absolute farce!
The Northern Star
smuggled weapons into the city
-under orders from Mayor Fisk. I was--
-Objection!
-I was there and can testify to this.
-Overruled!
Miss Jones and myself then
witnessed Fisk arm his private militia,
A.K.A. the task force, with said weapons.
Which we then destroyed
in the interest of public safety.
Fisk's smuggling is a criminal act.
Arming the task force with
smuggled weapons is a criminal act.
Enough evidence has been provided
to charge Fisk with these crimes.
-But first-- I'm not finished!
-Are you really--
-Overruled.
-Your Honor, this court was formed
to adjudicate
the Safer Streets Initiative,
an initiative created
by this man, Mayor Fisk,
in furtherance of his criminal agenda!
Which means, this court has
neither the ability nor the mandate
-to decide justice!
-[audience cheers]
-[gavel bangs]
-[Justice Waters] Order. Order! Please!
Daredevil or not, Mr. Murdock is right.
In light of the evidence,
the corroborated testimony,
Miss Page's crimes,
if they even are crimes,
cannot be judged by this court.
Thank you, Your Honor.
I move for dismissal.
Granted. This case is dismissed
with prejudice.
Miss Page, you're free to go.
Mr. Murdock,
please remain in the courthouse.
[applauding and cheering]
Oh, thank God.
You've won nothing, Mr. Murdock.
Nothing.
Mr. Fisk, the attorney general
has filed charges against you,
for racketeering, smuggling, corruption...
at this point, it's a dictionary.
Your assets have been frozen,
and the free port
is under government control.
On the word of a deluded lawyer?
None of it will stand up.
Oh, then there's attempted murder
against a government official.
Your assassin lived. He has a lot to say.
This is the part where you resign.
[Fisk] There's a process
for what you propose.
I suggest you start that up.
If you'll excuse me...
Interesting to see who you've
aligned yourself with, Miss Jones.
Watch yourself, Kingpin.
[reporters chattering indistinctly]
Where are you going, Daredevil?
You're going to hide?
Accept defeat gracefully, old man.
Matthew Murdock, Daredevil...
[Fisk] Defeat?
You've only weakened yourself.
[Matt] It's over. You lost the city.
-I've lost nothing.
-Murdock's coming out. Prepare the shot.
-Repeat, prepare to take the shot.
-[Bullseye] Sorry, pal. Wrong Bullseye.
-[Powell] Sir, it's a trap!
-No-- Wait!
You don't, you don't wanna do that!
You don't--
-[gun fires]
-[Powell] Outta here!
-Get him the fuck outta here! Go, go, go!
-[crowd gasps]
Get the mayor out of here
and don't let Murdock leave the building!
Get fire in that top right window!
Go! Move!
[all screaming]
-Here.
-[Buck panting]
[officer] Secure the doors.
As you can see behind me,
a surreal scene is unfolding
outside the courthouse as Mayor Fisk
has locked down the building
in the wake of the explosive end
to the trial of Karen Page.
Defense attorney Matt Murdock
shocked the courtroom with his admission
that he is the vigilante known
as Daredevil.
[Kirsten] What is he waiting for?
I don't know. We can't just hold up here.
I mean, we're sitting ducks.
Yes. God bless jurisprudence.
Task force or not, at this point,
he just wants to tear it all down.
-I'm calling in the National Guard.
-Wait.
There's more.
New York is in a state of emergency.
Following today's miscarriage of justice,
we were once again
attacked by a vigilante.
My aide has been wounded.
[grunts]
Right now, we are under siege.
As we speak, our enemies are assembling.
Masked,
hidden, and they're coming for all of us.
I want to make myself clear to you.
I will not abandon you.
I swore an oath,
and I intend to honor it.
I will stand and fight.
Will you?
Jesus Christ. He's asking for a war.
See, that's my concern.
You call in the National Guard,
you're giving him exactly what he wants.
Yeah, then, that'll take hours. I mean,
we, we have to stop this now.
-Hold on one second.
-[Karen] What?
-[♪ fanfare playing]
-Hello. It's me again.
We are under siege. By me.
[giggles]
-[tape distorts]
-[BB] The mayor's right.
We are under siege.
-[man] Stop!
-[officer] Push them back!
[BB] By the task force.
By the people
who kill our family, and our friends,
and lock us up.
[echoing] It's our city, not his.
It's time...
to take it back.
-[woman 1] Slide through. Come on.
-[woman 2] Come on!
[man] Move out, move out.
[group] Go. Quiet, quiet.
[woman] He's going down.
The city's picking sides.
[Jess] Trick or treat.
[crowd clamoring]
Whatever happens tonight,
to them, to me, to you...
Matt Murdock and Karen Page
never leave this building alive.
Now, go do your jobs.
Sir, Murdock's not alone.
Ah.
[Fisk] Well, if you're feeling challenged
by your responsibilities...
feel free to tender your resignations.
[officer] We'll take care of it, sir.
-[crowd clamoring in distance]
-Can you hear it?
Pretty soon everyone out there
will be in here.
[sirens echoing,
men speaking indistinctly]
[officer 1] Team Two, clear the hallways.
-[officer 2] You heard him.
-[officer 1] Move out.
The Task Force is coming.
This is it.
-[Karen] We'll be right here.
-[Kirsten] Mmm-hmm.
Stay safe.
You, too.
-You ready?
-Finally.
-[all chattering indistinctly]
-[sirens wailing]
Make a hole. Make a-- Come on!
Get out of the way! Make a hole!
All right, let's not do anything
that we're gonna regret later, all right?
Put the guns down.
Sir, it's the attorney general.
He'd like to speak with you.
Cherry, aren't you supposed to be upstate
playing bingo or some shit?
-You don't fucking belong here.
-Yeah, we do.
Or maybe you forgot, we serve the people,
not the other way around.
Take one more step
and we'll shoot you right in the face.
I'll be back.
-Oh, Heather--
-Give me your jacket.
Uh, oh, it's a Canali.
He's shivering. Give it to me.
It's just madness.
Look, we... we are both reasonable people.
There's no reason we should burn with him.
-Ease up.
-[Cole] Just back up.
-Everybody just back the fuck up!
-Shoot them.
-Whoa, whoa.
-Tell him!
Tell him about Hector Ayala!
Hector Ayala was a fucking cop killer.
-I said shoot that bastard.
-No! My husband wouldn't kill police.
You told me Ayala
pushed men off the platform.
I told you to shoot that guy.
-[Cole] He's one of ours.
-He's not one of ours. He's one of them.
The fuck happened to you?
You lose your balls in that fire, too?
I gave you a direct fucking order.
-No.
-Fine. You won't do it. I will.
-I'll just fucking do-- [grunts]
-[crowd gasps]
Get him outta here.
Let them in.
-All right!
-[Cole] Let them in. Move!
Move! Let them in!
Why don't you and I get out of here?
[choking]
Don't you ever touch me.
Kill Fisk!
[man] We're coming for you, Fisk!
Take down Fisk! Take down Fisk!
[crowd chanting] Bring us Fisk!
-[grunts]
-[groans]
-[officer groaning]
-[crowd] Bring us Fisk!
Bring us Fisk!
I'm here.
Okay.
It's the office of the AG again.
Final offer, he says, tender
your resignation and leave the city.
Leave New York?
And there I thought
I had your support, Sheila.
The office of the mayor has my support.
[crowd chanting]
Bring us Fisk! Bring us Fisk!
Renounce your citizenship, go into exile,
and the AG promises not to prosecute.
No! I won't leave this!
[Sheila] Speak to him. This is
the best offer you are going to get.
Open that door.
[Sheila] There are lives at stake.
Take the deal!
Open it!
Open that door!
Boo!
[grunts]
[all screaming]
[officers groaning]
[screaming]
No, no, no. No, no, no. No! No!
[Fisk] Come on!
[woman screams]
[grunting]
-[screams]
-Shh!
[groans]
[screaming]
-[man groaning]
-[exhales]
[groaning]
[all chattering indistinctly]
[people screaming in distance]
[grunting]
[crowd booing]
You're wrong about me!
You're wrong!
I have done everything for you!
I've given you my heart and my soul!
Liar!
-You're a liar!
-[crowd clamoring]
I've fought for you, and I stand here now!
And I still fight...
No! No! Stop!
[Daredevil] Listen! Listen!
And I just wanted a better New York!
[screams]
[Daredevil] Stop!
No! Stop!
We're better than this!
-Stay down, Fisk. Stay down!
-[Fisk grunting]
No! [grunts]
Listen. Listen to me.
It's over.
It's over for both of us.
[Fisk panting manically]
Take the deal.
I will not.
You go to prison,
you die locked away from her memory,
or you do what you do,
and this whole thing starts over again.
The poison, the fight, the death.
This is your so-called retribution?
It means nothing to me.
What...
What about grace?
No, no, no, no.
You are not allowed to offer that to me!
I believe you love this city. Same as me.
We have the opportunity to give it peace.
Even if we have none.
That's grace.
[Fisk gasps]
No.
Please.
I, uh...
I accept--
You'll understand if I don't...
shake your hand?
Yeah, Wilson.
I understand.
[♪ melancholy music playing]
[Karen] I don't know,
it's just kind of...
hard to believe it's really over.
Yeah, I know.
I know.
This normal life thing is...
No more running,
no more being hunted, no more...
-[Karen] It's gonna be hard.
-It's really hard.
-So hard.
-[Matt] Why is it so hard?
-Because we're really messed up.
-[laughs]
-[Karen] Are we really that messed up?
-What does that say about us?
[Karen] My God.
If I'm honest,
I'm not sure I know how to do it.
Well, that's okay. Neither do I.
I'd still like to take a shot at it.
Yeah, me too.
[sirens wailing]
[Karen] I thought we'd have more time.
[♪ ominous music playing]
[officers chattering indistinctly]
-Matthew Murdock?
-[Matt] Yes, sir.
You're under arrest for assault,
attempted murder. And it's a long list.
Daredevil's crimes?
-[officer] You have the right to--
-Waive the advisement, not the rights.
I used to be a lawyer.
I love you.
I love you too.
[♪ melancholy rock playing,
Radiohead "Pyramid Song"]
[vocalizing]
♪ I jumped in the river, what did I see? ♪
♪ Black-eyed angels swam with me ♪
Daddy!
♪ A moon full of stars and astral cars ♪
Oh, I missed you so much.
♪ And all the figures I used to see ♪
[man] BB.
I thought you should have this.
-What's this?
-Welcome to the Bulletin.
♪ All my past and futures ♪
♪ And we all went to heaven
in a little row boat ♪
♪ There was nothing to fear
and nothing to doubt ♪
Are you okay?
Yeah.
The work was...
different over there.
And you're done?
Yeah.
I heard he found someone else.
[woman] Mr. Robertson,
I just wanted to congratulate you
on becoming a million miler.
-Welcome to the club.
-Oh, wow.
♪ Jumped into the river ♪
♪ Black-eyed angels swam with me ♪
[inmates chattering indistinctly]
♪ A moon full of stars and astral cars ♪
♪ And all the figures I used to see ♪
♪ All my lovers were there with me ♪
♪ All my past and futures ♪
♪ And we all went to heaven
in a little row boat ♪
♪ There was nothing to fear
and nothing to doubt ♪
[inmates chattering indistinctly]