WHEN THE PHONE RINGS
No.
Get him!
No…
Oh, no…
What do I do?
Hello?
What?
From the Barun Cultural Foundation…
You didn't know either?
No, I didn't.
Where's it being held?
I'm on my way now.
No, don't come here.
There are a lot of reporters here.
What's important is that he's not here.
Former Presidential Spokesperson
Paik Sa-eon announced
he'd donate all the assets he inherited
from the late Chairman Paik Jang-ho
to society this morning.
And that all legal procedures
will only be carried out
through his legal representative.
Meanwhile, the Presidential Office
has accepted Paik's resignation
and is seeking a replacement.
LETTER OF APPOINTMENT
He…
disappeared.
FINAL EPISODE
Let's eat!
Hurry and take a seat.
Be careful.
That's nice.
Eat up.
Is it okay to eat more?
Of course.
You have to eat to grow.
I'm going to be taller than Sang-woo!
I'll be cooler too.
So, you can't marry Sang-woo, okay?
- "Marry"?
- Here.
Don't grow up so fast.
Being cute is the best.
Why compete with a kid?
Compete…
Whatever.
Have you heard?
Paik Sa-eon donated all his assets.
I heard.
How could I not know? It was huge.
The director here said
the Nuri Dream Center
is also getting a donation.
From Sa-eon?
It's from an anonymous donor.
Who else could it be?
He donated his assets,
resigned as spokesperson,
and is unreachable.
No one knows where he is.
It feels like Paik Sa-eon
has completely disappeared from the world.
He has.
Paik Sa-eon's dead.
That's right.
He died.
Breaking news.
It has been confirmed that Hong Hee-joo,
the wife of Spokesperson Paik Sa-eon…
1 MONTH AGO
…has safely returned to her family
after being missing for four days.
Police have charged Shim Kyu-jin,
the wife of Liberty and Justice Party
candidate Paik Ui-yong,
with kidnapping and inciting murder
in connection with Hong Hee-joo's case.
Min was also taken into custody
and is being investigated
for carrying out the crime.
Min confessed that he was instructed
to push the vehicle into the river
to stage a fall
and to scatter Hong Hee-joo's belongings,
such as her shoes and cell phone,
to obstruct the police investigation.
Meanwhile, the suspect
who kidnapped Hong Hee-joo
repeatedly threatened the victim
with a firearm despite repeated warnings
and ultimately was shot to death
by the police at the scene.
Mom!
You're there, aren't you?
I know you're out there!
Why did you lock me in here?
How long will you keep me locked up?
I told you.
Son, I…
I never want to lose you again.
I regretted it so much.
If only
I had protected you back then,
I wouldn't have lost you like that.
Sa-eon,
listen to me carefully.
Listen.
I'm not locking you up,
I'm protecting you.
KIDNAPPING SUSPECT SHOT TO DEATH
All this time,
I've always believed
that I lived a luckier life than others.
With a prestigious political family
and a father respected…
by the entire nation.
But it was all a lie.
The truth about my father
was the complete opposite
of what I had believed.
It was an illusion.
The son I had thought to be dead returned
and made it more miserable.
So, I am leaving behind
my family and background,
and I will stand again as Paik Ui-yong,
an ordinary man.
Honorable citizens,
if you can generously embrace…
my shortcomings and mistakes,
I, Paik Ui-yong,
promise to be reborn…
as a better version of myself for you.
Paik Ui-yong came in third
with 3.4% of the vote.
In the end,
the Paik family
never produced a president.
The defendant murdered her father-in-law
and, showing no signs of remorse,
once again incited murder,
ultimately repeating a crime
that led to casualties.
JUDGE
This court holds the defendant
accountable for this,
and sentences Shim Kyu-jin
to life in prison.
In the end, the mother,
who failed twice to protect her son,
appealed.
She asked for the maximum sentence,
the death penalty.
The butler, who had been loyal
to the Paik family his whole life,
acknowledged his crime
and showed deep remorse.
Considering that the victim
did not wish to punish him,
he was sentenced to five years in prison.
The Paik family's scandal,
which had caused such an uproar,
came to an end.
As for him,
he disappeared from the world,
letting go of everything he had.
You're back.
Have you been well?
Why do you keep coming here?
You know very well…
that I betrayed the spokesperson.
Before he realized your betrayal,
he called you the most
and talked to you the most.
Yes, he did.
Anything is fine.
Does anything from your conversations
with him come to mind? Anything.
Please, tell me.
He said…
he'd disappear like dust.
Once the revenge was over
and with everything
that had driven his life,
his goals and targets, gone,
he said he would self-destruct.
Originally.
"Originally"?
Yes, but…
What about now?
Did you change your mind?
Of course.
I'm going to live a life
after taking revenge.
With the person
I want to be with for the rest of my life.
So I don't think he disappeared
just because the revenge was over.
I'm sure…
there's another reason.
- Hee-joo.
- Mr. Kang.
How long has it been?
Have you been well…
It's been a while.
Are you here to see Mr. Park?
Yeah, I come by often.
It frustrates me
when I think of the spokesperson,
but I was taught to hate sin
and not people.
See you later.
He used to ask me quite often.
He asked what married couples talk about
and how they show affection.
And how to be a good husband.
In your marriage,
do you hide anything
or deceive each other?
Sometimes it's necessary to pretend
not to know and let things slide.
Marriage takes effort, don't you think?
Effort?
How do you do that?
- Excuse me?
- "I love you,
ultimate love in the universe."
He may have been clumsy,
but he tried really hard.
I want to hear more.
The spokesperson…
learned how to do this.
Can you believe it?
We were going to the retreat.
On the bus,
he asked me how to show affection.
So I taught him this.
But I guess…
that was all for you.
I never imagined that.
I miss him too.
How handsome. It looks great on you.
Dad, do you remember?
When I was little,
you bought me tonkatsu every Christmas.
Tonkatsu is yummy.
I ate all sorts of delicious food
every Christmas at Chairman Hong's house,
but the tonkatsu we shared together
was the best.
I like tonkatsu.
That's why I asked to come here.
It was my idea to come here.
Your food's ready.
Thank you.
You're back again.
Enjoy your meal.
It's good.
- But, Dad?
- Yeah.
Have you been here before?
On my birthday.
I asked to come here.
Asked who?
My son-in-law.
What?
When was that?
If it was your birthday, was it July?
Has he come back since? Have you seen him?
Let's go.
It's almost Christmas.
Don't stay alone in an empty house.
Come with me.
If you don't want to see Mom and Dad,
let's go on a trip.
How long are you going to stay here?
How many times do I have to tell you?
I'm not leaving this house.
You'll keep waiting here?
It's been six months already.
What if I leave this house,
and he comes back?
What if he comes,
but I'm not here, and we miss each other?
In-a…
I still can't believe he's gone.
After I was rescued
and woke up in the hospital, I'm sure…
he was right next to me.
When I slept for days from exhaustion,
every time I woke up,
he was right next to me,
as if he'd always be there.
And…
on the last night I could remember…
Hee-joo.
It's okay.
It was just a dream, okay?
I'm so relieved.
I had a dream that you got shot.
No.
I'm right here.
So go back to sleep.
I still remember his warm touch
that lulled me to sleep so vividly.
I feel like he'll come right back.
How could I leave this house?
He's not coming back.
What?
I thought you'd give up and move on
after some time.
But how is it…
that you can't forget, not for a moment?
Do you know?
Do you know why he left
and isn't coming back?
Do you know the reason?
This is the only thing I can tell you.
Forget him.
He…
will never come back.
So why?
Why would you say that?
In-a, tell me.
Please.
Hee-joo.
No matter what I say,
I know you won't listen.
But now, I just want you
to hurt less and be happier.
No.
I can only hurt less and be happier
if he's here.
I need him so badly.
I miss him so much.
PAIK SA-EON
Can we meet up for a moment?
MEMORIAL OF PEACE AND HOPE
WHERE YOUR LOVED ONES
WILL BE REMEMBERED FOREVER
Why here?
The number you called is not in service.
Please check the number and try again.
PAIK SA-EON
INCOMING CALL
INTERNATIONAL CALL
Hello?
CALLS
SEARCH HERE
COUNTRY CODE 604
ARGAN
Argan?
What?
You got a call from Argan?
Not just a call.
Ms. Hong Hee-joo?
Yes, that's me.
Here you go.
It's international mail.
Can you sign this for me?
Thank you.
In my name?
"Buiben International School
of Sign Language."
How much did you donate?
Two billion won.
Two billion won?
Wait, were you that loaded?
It wasn't me.
I don't have that kind of money.
Then who…
Didn't you work as a war correspondent
in Argan with him?
Do you know of any places
he might be in Argan?
What are you talking about?
Paik Sa-eon!
Are you saying he did this?
Who else would do this?
The call from Argan,
the amount of two billion won,
406, and 604…
Is this just a coincidence?
I don't know what you're saying.
So, what if I know some places in Argan?
Will you go--
If you have any ideas, tell me.
Come on, Hee-joo.
Don't you know Argan's a war zone?
Not only is it restricted
to certain people,
but you'll die if you go!
It doesn't matter if I die here
waiting for him
or get shot over there.
It's all the same to me.
So, please tell me.
I'm not leaving before you tell me.
Sunset.
Sunset?
Haven't you seen his phone's lock screen?
He's crazy about them.
He's obsessed with sunsets.
When we were in Argan,
he'd rush over at sundown.
There's an incredible spot
to watch the sunset.
He'd take photo after photo
of the sunset sky there.
It's red, like your swollen cheek.
BUIBEN INTERNATIONAL SCHOOL
OF SIGN LANGUAGE, ARGAN
I told you to wait
until I come to find you.
So, why?
Why are you here?
Because of you…
do you know how many times
my plans have changed?
No, from the start,
if you were involved,
none of my plans worked.
It all just falls apart.
Let it fall apart.
I'll ruin everything.
You're always going on about plans!
So?
Did anything in our relationship
go according to plan?
It didn't for me.
Divorcing you was my plan.
You know what happened.
I couldn't divorce you,
I couldn't escape you,
and now I can't live a single day
without you.
So I traveled halfway around the world
to come here!
Are you dumb?
How could you say
you can't live without me?
How…
can you say that when you know everything?
About what?
This is the only thing I can tell you.
He…
will never come back.
Did my sister say something?
No. Before that…
What did you find out that day?
Why did you look at me like that?
Answer me! What did he tell you?
Did you know?
Your father, Paik Jang-ho,
killed Hong Hee-joo's little brother.
Yeah.
That car accident.
Paik Jang-ho put out a hit
and ran them over with a truck.
Paik Jang-ho tried so hard
to hide me from the world,
but her little brother saw me.
From the blood running in my veins
to my name,
the only thing I ever did right
in this sinful life of mine
was protect you, Hee-joo.
THE LATE HONG YU-JIN
But it turned out
I didn't protect you.
Instead, I took so much from you.
Your brother,
your youth,
your dreams.
My father was the one
who crushed them all.
Did you…
finally figure it out?
What about Hee-joo?
She knows everything.
She knew everything,
yet she still risked her life for you.
Is that why you left me?
Because you felt bad?
I didn't leave you.
I needed time to punish myself.
I was looking for an excuse.
Since you already knew everything
and said it didn't matter,
I kept rationalizing it.
I thought I could just stay here,
pretending not to know,
and make you happy from now on.
When did it even start
that I can't live without you?
My goal was just…
to set you free.
And I felt…
so disgusted with myself for it.
So I wanted to punish myself,
until I could forgive myself.
How much longer do I have to wait?
You know it too.
We spent more time
misunderstanding and drifting apart
than cherishing and loving each other.
But if I still have to wait,
how much longer will it take?
If you have to be punished,
I should be the one to punish you!
You're punishing me now.
You're right in front of me,
and I want to hold you like crazy.
Can't you see I'm holding back?
I won't hold back anymore.
It was true.
We lived together for three years,
but I didn't know
because I never checked your phone.
They're all sunsets.
It was filled with you.
Is that why you came to Argan?
It was far from you,
but it was where I could see you.
But I never thought
I'd see you here like this.
604.
You called me from that number, right?
That day,
I had a dream.
You were crying a lot in the dream.
So…
Actually, that was just an excuse.
I just wanted to hear your voice.
That being said,
I didn't expect you
to just show up like this.
Why did you make a donation
to the sign language school in my name?
I donated two billion won.
Does that remind you of something?
Two billion won.
One, the groom cannot initiate a divorce.
Two, divorce is prohibited
under any circumstances.
Three, we will actively announce
to the public
that we are a married couple.
If any of these are violated,
the penalty will be two billion won.
That's right.
It's my settlement to you.
Because I'm going to break
our wedding vows.
Paik Sa-eon…
will divorce Hong Hee-joo.
What?
And I, not Paik Sa-eon…
will marry you.
- Do you want to switch spots?
- What? Why?
Well, the spokesperson
will come out when this door opens.
I'm feeling a bit overwhelmed and nervous.
- Will you switch spots with me?
- Nope.
This isn't the Presidential Office.
He's not the spokesperson anymore.
Don't be nervous.
Right?
Right…
Hello.
For you.
Get in here.
I'm starving.
- Wow!
- Look at that.
Goodness.
The food keeps coming.
Hee-joo, did you make all of this?
- Amazing. Everything tastes delicious.
- Yes.
- I made it.
- What?
- You did?
- You?
Are you saying you won't let your wife
lift a finger from now on?
I've taught you well.
It's not that.
She's not very good at cook--
Oh, my.
Your ring is so pretty.
Give me your hand.
Look at that.
Your ring is beautiful.
But I just don't get it.
Why get married twice,
especially to the same person?
I know.
However,
I approve of this marriage.
Congratulations! The fruit of true love.
Thank you.
By the way, is it true?
- Did you change your name?
- You did?
To what?
Well…
Paik Yu-yeon.
Paik Yu-yeon?
What does it mean?
Yu is for "only."
Yeon is for "love."
A one and only love in the world?
Oh, my.
Hey. Are these your true colors?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Congratulations on becoming
the most romantic husband.
So, tell us, when will you return
to the Presidential Office?
I won't be returning there.
Then what will you do?
Anyway, even though
it's hard to get used to,
let's celebrate Paik Yu-yeon
and Hong Hee-joo's marriage.
Shall we all toast?
- Congratulations!
- Congrats.
Thank you.
While we're at it,
will you congratulate us too?
To tell you the truth…
We're also…
getting married!
- Wow!
- Seriously?
Na You-ri!
Congratulations, You-ri!
Sang-woo!
Thank you.
I had no idea.
Congratulations.
Congrats.
You two look great together.
Let's toast!
- Congratulations!
- Yeah, congrats!
Being married is nice, right?
What?
Of course, it is.
Right?
Of course. You-ri, it's good.
What are you doing?
Hey!
Are you tired?
You said you did all the cooking.
But it's true.
Great job.
The lively atmosphere was nice.
I hope this house stays lively
and never quiet.
Really?
Then, we need someone other than us here.
I start work at the broadcast station
next week.
- The station?
- Yeah.
I've agreed to be
their sign language interpreter again.
And I'm going to continue doing it.
I like this job.
Sure. Congrats.
Cooperate, Hong Hee-joo.
If you want this house to be lively,
we need more family members!
What are you doing?
Cooperate!
JUAN RAW SEAFOOD
Try it.
It's your favorite.
Since that day,
I just can't eat fish anymore.
When I smell the fishy odor,
it brings back memories
of the fishing spot.
Help…
I'll make you something else.
No.
It's fine.
You're as good as ever.
Thanks.
Try the white kimchi.
Marriage registration?
I'll come back with him soon.
He wanted to come today,
but I didn't think
you'd say anything nice to him.
You're right.
You said you'd choose your own fate
and even went into that war zone.
And you married him without telling us.
Unbelievable.
You said you never saw her smile.
She's smiling now.
She looks happy.
What else could we ask for?
Where do you live?
The neighborhood's far from here.
Where is it?
Let's take it slow, Mom.
I'll visit from time to time.
Be happy.
I know how much he cares for you.
So live a long…
and happy life.
Hee-joo.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you
about the marriage.
But…
I didn't know how you'd feel.
I'm not trying to congratulate you.
Since we reunited,
I've been trying my best
to get closer to you.
But…
it was so hard.
But when I think about it,
I don't think I did it right.
Before we could get close,
I should've said this to you first.
Hee-joo,
I'm sorry.
I…
made you suffer for a long time,
both as the perpetrator
and the bystander.
In-a.
I'm going to forget everything
from the past.
If I keep dwelling on the past,
I'll be unhappy in the present.
You should try it too.
Forget the past.
Would that be okay?
In-a.
I'm happy.
And now,
I don't doubt my happiness anymore.
Because I'm someone who truly deserves it,
and he helped me believe that.
You deserve to be happy too.
Believe me.
Breaking news.
The ongoing Paltima airstrikes
are taking place in Izmael,
where Korean nationals have been kidnapped
by armed militants.
In response, the government has set up
a Protection Headquarters
at the Ministry of Foreign Affairs
and will send negotiator Paik Yu-yeon.
The government will prioritize
the safety of the hostages
and make every diplomatic effort
to rescue every one of them.
Reporter Lee is on-site now.
The number you have dialed is unavailable.
You'll be directed to voicemail after…
HUSBAND
Hello?
What took you so long to pick up?
Where are you? Are you okay?
The negotiations are over.
I'm coming home.
We're ready for departure.
I've been waiting.
Why were you so hard to reach?
I was in an area with no reception.
But…
what's with your tone?
What's wrong with it, 406?
Isn't it thrilling?
"Thrilling"?
Why? Do you miss her?
Yes.
I miss her.
What do you miss?
The chilly tone in her voice
when she threatened me.
That sharp voice.
Why did you like it?
She didn't hold back.
If you're upset with me
and don't say anything, I won't know.
And if you stay silent,
I might think I'm doing everything right.
I like it when my wife
doesn't hold back.
Don't hold back anymore.
Throw a tantrum, complain,
and nag if you want.
Do you promise?
Yes.
Do you swear?
But,
if I call,
what will you do for me?
Everything you ask me to, 406.
So from now on,
call me for the rest of your life.
I'll answer every time
as if it's the first call.
Then starting now,
I'll tell you what I want.
Listen carefully.
What's that?
Come back to me as soon as you can.
Right now, into my arms.
I'm on my way.
There's a couple here now.
The two have lived without being able
to open up to each other.
Would things have been different…
if they had been more honest
and shown their true feelings?
If they try to make an effort now,
could they live
like any other ordinary couple?
There's a couple here now.
They don't hide their true feelings
and are honest with each other.
They have promised to make
an effort to be happy together.
WHEN THE PHONE RINGS
Subtitle translation by: Sue Mounce