[The Epoch of Miyu]
[Episode 22]
Just to do Bai Yongjun a favor.
After all, he highly recommended that guy.
Do you have someone in mind?
Look at this.
[Career Direction Assessment Report]
This person's assessment result
is quite impressive.
Born to work in the hotel industry.
A bright future ahead.
Who is this?
Xu Miyu.
This kind of assessment
is similar to MBTI.
It's just for reference.
We shouldn't blindly trust it.
Besides, you should know
that cross-department transformation is
troublesome.
I can handle complicated procedures.
Now, what I'm not sure about is
whether my decision is too arbitrary.
What do you think, Rui?
Is Xu Miyu really capable of
being our lobby manager?
I saw her performance earlier today.
[Purong Hotel]
She is as calm and resourceful as Anna.
And she knows the hotel's situation
very well.
She is a very good candidate.
However,
I don't know Xu Miyu's opinion.
How about I talk to her?
Okay.
Transfer me to the Front Office?
That's right.
This is our preliminary resolution.
It still needs to go through
a management vote.
Also, we need to consider
your personal wishes.
So, I came to talk to you first today.
Are you willing to?
Thank you.
Director Bai.
Ms. An started her maternity leave
ahead of schedule yesterday.
You know about this, right?
So, now, in the Front Office,
a lobby manager position has opened up.
The leaders attach great importance
to this matter.
After discussing it with
the HR Department,
they've decided to assign
a new lobby manager.
Why do they need to send someone over?
Who is it?
Has the candidate been decided?
It hasn't been finalized yet.
It's just a pending candidate.
I want to know
why you chose me.
Do you remember this test?
[Controlling][Influential][Strict][Calm]
According to the report,
in the aspects of image,
communication skills, and loyalty,
you are stronger than
other candidates
for the lobby manager.
What do you think?
Do you have any concerns?
I have a concern.
Is it because you are my friends
and you are overestimating me?
Mr. Xue,
to be honest, recently,
I indeed felt a bit confused about
my career planning.
That is why I took this evaluation.
If I say I don't want to get promoted,
it will be a lie.
Today, knowing that
I have so many possibilities,
and could even become a lobby manager,
I am truly happy.
I also wish I could tell you
that I'm willing to give it a try.
However,
this is a cross-departmental promotion
after all.
Besides, I'm far from familiar with
the front desk work.
I think
you trust me unconditionally,
because you guys are my friends.
But also, for that reason,
I'm even more afraid of
letting you down.
Forewoman of the executive floor?
Xu Miyu, the one
who always flatters the leader?
Director Bai, you freaked me out.
Subordinates are spreading rumors.
But we shouldn't join in the fuss.
Ms. Xu is exceptionally capable
in her work.
In the opening of the Chinese restaurant
and Ms. An's emergency yesterday,
she was at the front line
and did an excellent job.
It's obvious to everyone.
Did the HSKP Department kick her out
and shove her into the Front Office?
She's just a forewoman.
How could she be a lobby manager?
When promoting someone,
we need to emphasize person-job fit.
Not to mention that the lobby manager,
who is the face of our hotel.
It connects upwards to
the general manager
and downwards to
every department and every guest.
You guys found such an ass-kisser
to fool me?
Your tricks are
too blatant.
Xu Miyu.
I'm sitting here
not to represent Mr. Ji and myself,
but for the interests of Purong Hotel.
Meanwhile, since we are friends,
we will not put you
in an unsuitable position,
letting you bear
undue pressure and criticism.
Just as we believe in you,
we hope you can believe in us,
and more importantly, in yourself.
I understand, Mr. Xue.
May I ask
who recommended me?
Is the answer that important?
It was Mr. Ji himself.
If you really
don't know where your path is,
you might as well start with
trial and error.
Step out of your comfort zone
and see the other sides of that iceberg.
♪ Bury everything in your mind ♪
Meeting guests' needs
is your responsibility,
while supporting you is mine.
♪ Hope love blossoms as wished ♪
I'm your boss.
I will be responsible for you.
♪ Rainwater silently nourishes flowers ♪
You can trust me a little more,
okay?
♪ At its own expense ♪
In the past,
when faced with things I wanted,
♪ In the hot summer ♪
I was always used to putting in
a little more effort than others,
♪ I'm melting ♪
cautiously pleasing others and weighing
♪ Before the flowers wither,
I pretend to be cool ♪
just to prove that I deserved
to have them.
But now he keeps telling me
♪  Ah  ♪
that everyone in this world
♪Talking to myself♪
is a shining star.
I can be seen without trying to
please others.
♪Ah♪
♪ Though I'm alone,
I pretend to be at ease ♪
I deserve to be firmly chosen
without having to prove myself.
♪ That fleeting moment I tried to hold ♪
[Chapter 2: Project Management Process]
[Chapter 3: Project Activation]
♪ Let it go when the glass runs dry ♪
For you, moving from the HSKP Department
to the Front Office,
[Project Selection and Feasibility Study]
in terms of specific work content,
♪ Unfinished longings ♪
you will face new challenges
and difficulties.
You need to get prepared.
♪ Drift like fading embers ♪
As for any other problems,
don't worry.
♪ Still longing for yesterday's glow ♪
[Project Selection and Feasibility Study]
Leave them to Mr. Ji and me.
I will work hard not to let you down.
♪ Yet sailing into
the ocean's depths at night ♪
Xu Miyu, do you remember what I told you
♪ Questions without answers ♪
in your interview?
♪ Let them go with the wind ♪
Purong Hotel will provide everyone
who has career aspirations
♪ Let them go ♪
with a matching path for promotion.
So, you should believe in yourself.
One day,
you will definitely become
an excellent hotel worker.
Your clothes have been washed.
Thank you.
Do you need anything else?
No.
Hello.
Here is the mineral water you asked for.
Thank you.
Do you need anything else?
No.
Room service.
-Sorry, sir.
-Get it right next time.
It's you.
Miyu.
No need, no need.
I made the bed myself this morning.
Then, I'll go outside.
Listen, Miyu.
The floor is perfectly clean.
You don't need to clean it anymore.
Can you please
stop doing one chore after another?
Come here.
Sit down and chat with me.
Daniel, I am your butler first,
and then, your friend.
Taking care of your daily life is my job.
You have to let me finish my work first.
No problem.
Leave the work for tomorrow.
It might not be me tomorrow.
What?
Is someone trying to fire you again?
Tell me.
I'll tell the Old Madam.
Let's see who dares to bully you again.
This is too much.
You mean when I was about to be fired,
Aunt Wanjun helped me?
Chairman Wei.
Why so distant?
For what happened before,
thank you.
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
She is your chairwoman,
your Aunt Wanjun,
and also my cousin Wanjun.
Who is your cousin?
You old fool.
By the way.
Miyu, let's continue where we left off.
Who wronged you again?
You'd better tell us
everything.
Your chairwoman will stand up for you.
Actually,
I wasn't wronged,
and I don't need anyone to
stand up for me.
It's just that
I'm going to be the lobby manager
at the Front Office.
You got a promotion!
That's great news.
Why didn't you tell me just now?
You made me worry for nothing.
I'm sweating.
I am happy.
But I'm a little reluctant to leave.
There's nothing to be reluctant about.
Young people
should stride forward.
Don't overthink things.
Do not act like an old madam.
What do you mean?
Can't you just keep quiet?
Miyu.
I heard
that Mr. Ji
was under immense pressure
to recommend
a forewoman of the HSKP Department
to be the lobby manager.
I had a feeling it was you.
Congratulations.
Getting promoted under Mr. Ji
fully proves your capability.
Thank you, Chairman Wei.
Aunt Wanjun.
Thank you, Daniel.
I'll leave it to you.
I'll be leaving now.
Okay.
Are you still hesitating?
Are you wondering
"if I am truly qualified
to be a lobby manager?"
Or "what kind of pawn Ji Feng
is using me as?
Will he push me into the crosshairs?"
Purong Hotel doesn't belong to me.
You must believe that it can provide
every capable and ambitious person
with a path to get promoted.
Striving for higher ground
is an eternal pursuit.
If you don't move forward,
you fall behind.
This time, I've decided to move forward.
By the way, Mr. Ji,
I heard that this opportunity
was something you fought hard
to get for me.
I want to sincerely thank you.
What kind of place
do you think the lobby is?
The lobby
should be the first impression
a hotel gives its guests.
When I used to book hotels,
I would also pay special attention
to the lobby.
Even though I don't spend much time
in the lobby,
a bright and spacious one
really makes me want to
stay at that hotel.
You and every staff member here
are the first sight of Purong Hotel.
A competent lobby manager
must not only uphold the hotel's image,
but also reflect its warmth,
elegance, and attitude.
The one guests seek help from the most
when they walk through this door
is the lobby manager.
It is no exaggeration to say that
a lobby manager
is the hotel's encyclopedia.
Try to imagine that
you are that door.
Do not hold back those who left,
and do not reject those who will come.
When you become one with this space
and can navigate it freely,
you have truly embarked on
your career path.
Don't doubt yourself.
Seize this opportunity.
Letter of Appointment:
Based on the hotel's operational
and developmental needs,
after a management meeting,
new personnel appointments have been made.
The specific appointments are as follows:
Xu Miyu is appointed to be
the lobby manager of Front Office,
in responsible for
the all-round management
and operation of the lobby
as well as the coordination
and optimization of guest services.
Luo Qingping is hereby appointed
as the forewoman of
the HSKP Department's executive floor,
responsible for the executive floor's
daily management and operations
as well as the coordination
and optimization of guest services
to continuously improve
service quality and operational efficiency
on the executive floor,
and fully showcasing
the hotel's premium image.
The above appointments are effective
immediately upon announcement.
Hereby notified.
Purong Hotel HR Department.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Change your clothes later.
I'll take you to meet your new colleagues.
Right now?
It's required for work.
I'll wait for you in the lobby
on the first floor.
Okay.
-Miyu, I don’t want you to leave.
-Miyu.
Miyu, are you just going to
leave us behind?
I will miss you.
I don't want to leave you, either.
But I'm not really leaving.
I'm just in the lobby.
If you miss me,
come find me,
or send me a WeChat message.
Time to work.
Go ahead.
Qingping.
From now on,
these brothers and sisters,
as well as our guests
on the executive floor,
are in your hands.
Don't worry.
I will do even better than you.
Thank you.
[HSKP Department, Xu Miyu]
Since today,
Xu Miyu will be the forewoman of
the executive floor.
When Black Card Ji
cancelled your bad reviews,
I could sense it.
You have a strong background.
Allergic to the towel?
Just in the past few days,
I kept sleeping
with the towel under my neck
and got an allergic reaction.
Who are you trying to scare?
Aren't you just a forewoman?
You're just a floor forewoman.
How dare you talk to me
about a common position?
Who do you think you are?
Found it.
Miyu, I'm sorry.
I won't disclose this matter.
But I have to remind you that
you should never
make such a mistake again.
Thank you, Miyu.
You are such an angel. Thank you.
I'll have this girl tally up
who wants to share the Yan Du Xian.
Does that work for you?
The manager always has a way.
You are the most considerate
hotel attendant
I've ever met.
Penalties must be given,
but compensations must also be made.
Let's get to work.
Chairman Wei, what brings you here?
Today is
your first day as a lobby manager.
I came to cheer you on.
Good luck.
Thank you.
Look.
On my first day working at Purong,
my mother gave this to me.
Today,
I am giving it to you.
I hope every day you work at Purong,
it stays with you.
[Purong Hotel, Front Office, Xu Miyu]
How can I accept this?
It suits you perfectly.
Ms. Xu, are you in the lobby?
Yes.
Go on.
I'll watch you leave from here.
Here she is.
Everyone is here.
Great. Please announce.
Letter of Appointment:
Based on the hotel's operational
and developmental needs,
after a management meeting,
a new personnel appointment has been made.
The details are as follows:
Xu Miyu is appointed to be
the lobby manager of Front Office,
in responsible for
the all-round management and operation of
the lobby of the Front Office,
and the coordination
and optimization of guest services
to continuously improve
the lobby service quality and
the operational efficiency
and present the hotel's excellent image.
The above appointment will take effect
from the date of publication.
This is to notify.
Purong Hotel HR Department.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Now, let's welcome our new lobby manager,
Xu Miyu, to say a few words.
Hello everyone, I'm Xu Miyu.
It's a great honor to
join the Front Office team
and become one of you.
I hope from now on we can work
side by side.
I also hope to do a good job in service.
More importantly,
I hope to get everyone's support and help.
Thank you all.
Good!
Awesome!
Applause, please.
Let's give her a round of applause.
Ms. Xu.
Welcome to the Front Office.
You are so beautiful and capable.
Being a forewoman in the HSKP Department
was indeed a waste of your talents.
Now that you are in our Front Office,
we will give you a stage
to fully showcase your abilities.
I believe you will bring
new breakthroughs to the lobby's work
and create new achievements
in the future.
Okay?
Thank you, Director Bai.
Come on.
Let's welcome Ms. Xu again
with a warm round of applause.
More passion!
More enthusiasm!
You went to the lobby?
I just took a walk around.
What's up?
Isn't patrolling the lobby
my daily routine?
Is it strange?
You patrolled exceptionally on time today.
But it's right to make an appearance.
Otherwise, a person like Xu Miyu
falling into the hands of
those little girls,
she would definitely be bullied.
If she is really that inexperienced,
it means our judgment is wrong.
With real ability,
one can stand firm anywhere.
I can't win this argument with you.
Who tried so hard
to persuade others
to give Xu Miyu this opportunity?
[Memorandum of Understanding]
[I'm from Jiang Zhichun's studio team.]
[We're interested in the brand image and]
Isn't this Dianjiangchun,
[unique charm of Purong Hotel]
[I think if we cooperate,
we will make great achievements.]
who advertised for us last time?
Such a popular blogger
came to us many times.
Could it be
because of the grand opening of
the Chinese restaurant last time,
or does she have other motives?
No matter what,
we have no reason
to give up this opportunity, right?
Okay.
I'll think about it.
[Purong Hotel Staff Apartment]
That lobby manager just now
was so beautiful.
Miyu looks really pretty today.
Your girlfriend is watching.
Hello, welcome.
This way please.
Excuse me.
You dropped your scarf.
Thank you.
This way, please.
Right here.
Who is this?
Hello, Mr. Duan.
This is my former butler.
Gorgeous, isn't she?
I used to see you mopping floors
and cleaning toilets
with your head down
in the executive lounge.
I didn't expect you to be
such a great beauty.
Thank you.
It seems
Ji Feng really has a good eye.
Putting you in this position
is making the best use of your talents.
Let's go.
Hello.
Is there anything I can help you with?
Excuse me, where is the sales department?
You need to take the staff elevator
up to the third floor.
Please follow me.
Okay, thank you.
I was just at the front of the line.
I just went back to my suitcase
to get my ID card.
Why do I have to line up again?
That was just now.
It took you too long to get your ID.
We can't have so many people
waiting just for you.
How could you do this to me?
You...
Let me handle it.
Hello, miss.
I'm sorry about that.
Lu Xiaoyan,
please help this guest first.
She was already here.
If you miss your number,
you have to line up again.
We all follow the rules
fairly and justly.
Ms. Xu.
You don't know the reception work.
So, could you please
stay out of this matter?
I think you should
take care of the guests over there.
Do you have any tissues?
Enjoy your stay.
Thank you.
Cleaners, please come to the lobby.
Hello.
She's your superior after all.
Why make her do that?
Come on.
Take some tissues.
Isn't that her old profession?
You don't know the reception work.
So, could you please
stay out of this matter?
I think you should
take care of the guests over there.
Ms. Xu.
Ms. Sun.
It is you.
You're getting prettier.
I almost didn't recognize you.
Ms. Sun, I'm sorry.
I didn't have time to greet you.
I'm transferred to the lobby now
and become the lobby manager.
Congratulations.
Next time I come,
can I see you in the lobby
at a glance?
Ms. Sun, maybe not.
Why?
With Ms. Xu's promotion speed,
now she is the lobby manager,
but next time you come here,
she might be
the assistant of general manager.
Thank you for flattering me, Ms. Lu.
I will definitely work hard
and won't let you down.
I like your personality.
You are brave and driven.
Keep it up.
I'll leave first.
Thank you.
Bye.
Take care, Ms. Sun.
Ms. Sun, this way.
No.
I want you to pick me up after work.
I don't want to eat at home.
I have something important to tell you.
The baby is fine.
The baby is okay.
Ms. Lu, please sign here.
I don't care.
I want you to get off work early today
and pick me up.
At 5 o'clock.
Love you, honey.
See you later.
Miss.
Hello.
We want to try yellow-feathered chicken.
Do you know which restaurant nearby
is the best?
You want to eat yellow-feathered chicken?
There are a few
good restaurants around here.
Please follow me.
Okay.
This way, please.
Look.
Go out this exit and turn right.
Then at the intersection over there,
turn left.
You will see a restaurant
after walking about 100 meters.
Thank you, miss.
You're welcome.
Take care.
Honey.
Who are you looking at?
Nothing.
Just waiting for you to get off work.
Drive.
This is the first Mediterranean restaurant
opened in China by Laura Garcia,
the famous Spanish chef.
Here,
you can taste
the most authentic Mediterranean food
in a strong artistic atmosphere.
In Shanghai's spring,
this is a good choice
to gather with friends.
My old friend is here.
Have a seat.
Okay.
I knew
you'd only come to see me
under the guise of work.
On our opening day,
I didn't know you were there.
Have I changed that much?
I recognized you at first glance.
It was mainly because
there were too many people that day.
Because of your video,
many customers
came to our restaurant.
Good wine needs no bush.
Your new signature dishes are
truly amazing.
When did you return to China?
Last November.
You spent ten years abroad before.
As soon as you came back,
you took over such a hot potato
like Purong Hotel.
I mainly wanted to save this place,
and also give my career
a happy ending.
You are indeed loyal and righteous.
Not exactly.
Just acting on impulse.
It's been a while.
Aren't you going to ask me how I've been?
I don't think I have to ask.
You are the head of Dianjiangchun team,
an influencer brand
with tens of millions of followers.
Although I've achieved my small dream
and earned money,
I'm still alone.
What about you,
Mr. Ji?
Are you as miserable as I am?
Don't think too highly of me.
I'm still the same.
Then,
we're in the same situation.
So, how exactly does Ms. Jiang want to
cooperate with Purong Hotel?
The famous Purong Hotel in Shanghai
actually has many themes to explore.
It depends on how far Mr. Ji
wants to go with me.
For a win-win cooperation,
I will hold nothing back, of course.
Don't worry.
I'll fully cooperate with you.
Let's eat and talk.
The food here is delicious.
Give it a try.
Let's try it.
What's up, baby?
I don't have an appetite.
Is the baby bothering you?
I wonder who it was
staring at his ex-wife
at the entrance of Purong Hotel today?
What?
Now that she's promoted to
lobby manager,
you're tempted again, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
I mean,
you and the baby are
the only things in my world now.
I wouldn't think of anything else.
Spare me your sweet talk.
I'm involved in
your history of cheating, okay?
It's not fair for you to say that.
When have I ever lied to you?
Nie Yucheng, your acting like this
makes me very insecure.
Okay, let me tell you some good news
to put your mind at ease, okay?
What good news could you possibly have?
Let's hear it.
I was promoted to vice president.
Shouldn't you have been promoted
to vice president a long time ago?
Does that not satisfy you either?
Okay then, tell me.
Let me know what you want
so I can satisfy you.
Sign the contract for the new house
next week.
Well, as for this...
Didn't you say there was no rush before?
How is this not a rush?
Look how big my belly is.
I'm going to give birth soon.
Where will the child live when it's born?
The three of us live in one room
with your mom?
Is that appropriate?
Okay. Fine.
But the problem is that
our family doesn't have
that much spare money.
We do.
Where did your millions in investments go?
I don't think we should use that money.
Nie Yucheng, what do you mean?
Why are you always making excuses?
Do you not love me and the baby?
No, no, no.
Tell the truth.
No.
Don't blow it out of proportion.
I love you.
Fine.
I promise you then.
Really?
Really.
I guarantee that
the baby will live in a new house
upon birth.
Are you lying?
I'm not lying.
When have I ever lied to you?
Are you happy?
You're happy now.
Okay, okay, okay.
As long as you're happy.
It must have been ten years
since last time
we walked side by side like this, right?
Time flies.
You know,
over the past ten years,
I've been having the same dream.
I dreamed of the day I left the house,
dragging my luggage.
Back then,
I always wanted to see the results first.
I was so impatient
and anxious.
And I left you so easily.
Ji Feng.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
We were both young back then.
I was just a hotel attendant.
I couldn't even see my own future,
let alone give you the life you wanted.
It was right for you to leave.
At least after leaving me,
you did what you wanted to do,
experienced a wider world,
and became who you are today.
So you don't blame me anymore?
It's all in the past.
Really.
Seeing how successful you are now,
I'm very happy for you.
Me too.
You're still the same as
I knew you ten years ago.
That's nice.
Here's to a pleasant cooperation ahead.
Yes, to a great cooperation.
I wish all the musicians
a successful performance tonight.
Just wait for
a big surprise.
Should we play a piece
for Miyu
to reward her?
Let's play one piece for her.
Okay.
Here we go.
Hello, Mr. Ji and Mr. Xue.
I just came to remind everyone
that tonight's performance
will last for a long time.
Take the time to rest for a while.
No problem.
I'll leave the Western restaurant to you
tonight.
Be careful, guys.
A little lower over there.
How is it?
How do you feel after listening to it?
You really dare to think and act,
getting a group of seniors to perform.
I admire your courage.
Rui, are you being sarcastic?
No.
They played very well.
I was also shocked just now.
With a performance of this level,
the alumni association
will definitely be thrilled tonight.
It will give everyone a pleasant surprise.
Pleasant is fine,
but surprise is unnecessary.
After all, they are old.
We still need to be careful
with tonight's performance.
Have the logistics team
keep a close eye on things,
and prepare various contingency plans
just in case.
Okay, I'll go check.
Okay.
[Purong Hotel]
Why does she keep running
to the Western restaurant today?
That goes without saying.
She went to show off.
There's a performance
at the Western restaurant tonight.
She got transferred there.
Alright.
She's just a cleaner from
the HSKP Department.
What's there to envy?
Stop talking about her all day
and making her a star.
[60th Anniversary of
Lussia University Alumni Association]
Ming.
Eat slowly.
Don't eat too much.
You have a performance tonight.
A full stomach gives me energy.
See, what did I tell you?
Ming.
What's wrong?
How is it?
It's stuck.
Is it?
What's wrong? What's wrong?
M-Maybe it's stuck?
Choking on food.