Subtitle by Kisskh.Asia Translator [ Admin Qari ]
May I be like the stars
and you like the moon.
As long as the world remains,
so shall we.
I only wish to stay with the one I love,
watching every sunrise and sunset.
I want to be with you forever.
Eternals and demons walk different paths.
You and she are ultimately different.
Have you ever
truly cared for me?
No.
Never.
In this life and the next, through all lifetimes…
May we live and die together,
and share life and death as one.
[Moonlight Mystique]
[Episode 4]
Young Lord.
That Eternal, Chong Zhao,
does not seem to be in the city anymore.
Your plan to frame him must have worked.
He must've went back to Lanling Sect
to tell on Bright Moon Palace.
Well then, let's make this city even more chaotic,
so that when the Five Eternals of Lanling arrive,
they get to see the best of hell.
If you die,
the Desireless Stone will come out.
That demon Fan Yue wanted to cut open my heart to extract the stone,
but was jolted away by Desireless Stone's divine rays.
It seems that the Desireless Stone is protecting me.
So, if I cut open my own heart,
will I be able to activate my divine powers,
and break through Chong Zhao's barrier?
My father is waiting for me.
I have to go back.
It's fifty-fifty.
I either live or die.
Xi,
you will protect me,
right?
Xi.
I did it!
You didn't go back to Lanling?
At the very least, I should take you back for interrogation.
Interrogate me?
I thought it's because you were worried about me.
Cut the crap.
From Bright Moon Palace to Cold Spring Palace,
where are you exactly from?
If you are so curious about me,
why don't you come with me
and join the Demon Race?
Since you wouldn't speak,
I will just simply take your body back.
Cloud Fire Bow?
You are indeed Cold Spring Palace's Fu Ling.
So what if I am?
Do you really think you can
lay a finger on my disciple?
Grand Master.
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Heavenly Sky Fan?
You are the master of Cold Spring Palace.
You have some knowledge,
but you're not smart enough.
Let me teach you.
In such situations,
even if you recognize this fan,
you should've pretended you didn't know.
Because it's only then
that I could possibly
spare your life.
The moment you used this fan,
you gave up on concealing your identity.
He's not that stupid.
Fine.
Let me test you some more.
If
the Eternal Envoy,
Sect Leader Jin Yao's head disciple
were to die a terrible death here in Ning'an City,
tell me,
how many people will the Eternals send here?
Will the murderer Fan Yue
still survive?
So you guys were the ones who framed the Master of Bright Moon Palace.
Yes.
I will need to trouble you
to lend me your life.
Give me a reason.
Fan Yue is a demon. He wouldn't save you.
He saved me once.
You mean...
You want to repay his kindness?
You know what he will say to those old men
when he returns to Lanling, right?
I know I was wrong.
I'm willing to be punished.
According to the rules of Cold Spring Palace,
the mistake you made today
is worthy of your death.
You are free to punish me.
But I saved him
not only to repay his kindness,
but because I think
he is a person who could be won over.
Win him over?
In order to save Bai Shuo alone,
he placed the lives of everyone in Ning'an city as a lower priority.
Although he is an Eternal,
there is a point of vulnerability in his heart.
If we exploit it well,
you may even have another spy within the Eternals.
A spy within the Eternals?
Your suggestion is interesting.
However,
besides that,
are you truly not harboring any other thoughts?
Of course not.
I, Fu Ling, am devoted solely
to you, Grand Master.
I'm not sparing you punishment today
because
your excuse was convincing,
but because
you are my disciple.
I can't bear to kill you.
If this happens again,
you will be severely punished.
Got it.
It's impossible
to frame Fan Yue now.
However,
the mission of retrieving the Desireless Stone
must be achieved.
Don't let me down again.
I understand.
Master, you seem to already know
which of the five Contemplations will appear in Ning'an City.
With the Nether Poison wrecking havoc,
Ning'an City will turn into hell.
Everyone is trapped with no escape.
The desire to kill will definitely emerge.
Master.
As you expected,
Bai Shuo is here.
Let her come up.
I'll tell you everything
I saw in the Desireless Stone.
In exchange,
I want the antidote to this demonic poison.
Ms. Bai.
Things have changed.
Ning'an City is now in chaos.
Governor Bai is also poisoned by the Nether Poison.
Do you really think you're
in any position to negotiate with me?
All these days,
you've been lying to me to about collecting the Five Contemplations.
You made me trust you and be used by you.
You already know that
my father was poisoned by this demonic poison.
Yet, you wouldn't make use of
this opportunity to try and win me over.
Why?
The Five Contemplations are key to activating the Desireless Stone.
In other words,
everything predicted in the Desireless Stone
is the origins of the Five Contemplations.
The demonic poison in the city might not have been your doing,
but you want to make use of the chaos in Ning'an
to force the Five Contemplations into existence, and use me to absorb their energy.
I did want to see
this Ning'an City turning into hell,
and force the Five Contemplations into existence.
But you are afterall human.
What can you do even if
you know what I am up to?
I'm indeed just a human.
I have nothing to threaten you with.
But regardless what you are after,
you cannot do without me.
If this demonic poison takes hold,
I will become a walking corpse
just like the maniacs out there.
Fan Yue.
Now,
do I,
as a human,
have the rights to negotiate with you?
How dare you threaten me?
Do you really think I dare not kill you?
You dare not,
you cannot,
and you will not.
The fact that you let me live until now
has already proven so.
I, Bai Shuo, may not be a big shot,
but I still have my family to protect,
and my benefactor whom I must find.
Everything I have done so far
is not to seek death, but to live.
Only by staying alive
can I accomplish those things.
But the current situation is forcing me to make a choice.
What I am betting on today
is not only your inevitability,
but also your heart.
I bet there's something you can't let go of in your heart too.
You'll give me what I want because of
the reason that compels you to gather the Contemplations.
This is Ghost Grass.
When its flowers bloom, it becomes a medicine.
It is the antidote of the Nether Poison.
But the Nether Poison is the strongest poison of the Demon Race.
There is no cure in the world.
The Ghost Grass can only suppress the poison,
but it cannot completely cure.
If you want to remain human,
consume one flower a day
without missing a single day.
Got it?
How can I
make it bloom?
With human blood.
A lot of blood.
Whether with your own or someone else's,
whether you kill yourself or kill or someone else,
it's your choice.
Use human blood?
Fan Yue.
Can I still trust you?
You claimed that my benefactor in the Lunar Hidden Sea
was your old friend.
Do you dare claim it's real?
It was fake.
I have no idea who is your benefactor,
nor do I have any idea who is it
you're looking for in the Lunar Hidden Sea.
But the Ghost Grass
is definitely real.
Believe it or not, it's up to you.
Whether you want it or not,
it's also up to you.
If my father is saved,
I will fulfill the promise I made today.
But if you lie to me again,
you can forget about activating the Desireless Stone ever again.
Cold Spring Palace
must be reported to the Eternals as soon as possible.
What does that demoness mean?
Why did she save me?
She must be up to something.
Regardless, I should report to Lanling first.
With human blood.
A lot of blood.
Whether with your own or someone else's,
whether you kill yourself or kill or someone else,
it's your choice.
Master.
Are you still angry?
Angry?
Why should I be angry?
I recall your original plans was for
Bai Shuo to come and beg you,
and the terms of the deal are yours to decide.
But now it seems like
she has the upper hand again.
Again?
Master, you are virtuous
and magnanimous,
and does not argue with the weak.
It's Bai Shuo's huge blessing
to have received help from you.
Enough!
Master.
Now that Bai Shuo is also poisoned by the Nether Poison,
and given that the Ghost Grass cannot fully remove the poison,
does that mean
she has to live on human blood for the rest of her life?
I am only using her to gather the Contemplations.
I don’t care
how she stays alive.
If she chooses to use the grass to save others,
the Contemplations you are after will be gone.
That Ghost Grass is just a medicine for relief.
Human nature is inherently evil.
Once this has been cast
and if greed takes over,
this herb that is meant to heal
will become a blade that kills.
Bai Shuo,
you took a gamble on human nature with me.
Let's see how you
clean up this mess
if human nature shifts.
Father,
have a good sleep.
When you wake up...
When you wake up,
I am not sure what will happen either.
But I won't let you die.
We still have to wait for Xi's return
and reunite with her.
But Chong Zhao will
no longer be part of this family.
He...
Forget it.
Let's not talk about unhappy things.
Without him,
we can still live a good life.
Truly no regard for her own life.
♫The person standing far away♫
♫Don't be afraid♫
♫The stars will guide you to me♫
Despite seeking immortality for 10 years,
all she has got is this collection of duds.
♫Walk towards me♫
She might be smart,
but also so foolish.
Humans may not be able to live beyond a hundred years,
but my benefactor is an immortal.
♫My heart feels so...♫
I may be afraid of death.
But I'm more afraid of not having a chance to repay him.
♫It's pounding as I wait for you♫
So I can be used by you,
and I'll never expose your identity.
But it must be an equal exchange,
and you must fulfill my wish.
♫The stars light up your eyes♫
♫You are my distant call♫
♫You are my first and last♫
♫My heart is trembling for you♫
♫In this moment where we embrace each other♫
Who said the path of cultivation
♫Let's never let go♫
must always be the path towards being an Eternal?
I've checked the deaths of several disciples
and their surrounding aura.
It's indeed the work of the Demon Race.
What's weirder is that
the disciples' eternal energy are all missing.
I'm afraid...
it's taken away the demons who killed them.
They killed them,
and even took their eternal energy?
I told you that those demons
are most deserving of death.
Why are you yelling at me?
I didn't steal it.
Chong Zhao.
What happened?
How did you get hurt this badly?
Were you also ambushed by the demons?
I, Chong Zhao, am guilty.
What happened?
I misjudged the Demon Race's tactics
and delayed reporting the real situation of the city.
This caused Ning'an City to be thrown into chaos
as Cold Spring Palace spread the Nether Poison.
I have failed my duty,
so I've come back to seek punishment from all of you.
I also beg that you could
lend assistance to Ning'an.
How could you be so muddled
and not report it right away?
Because if the Eternal Race descends on Ning'an City,
another innocent person will die.
I want to protect the city,
but also protect that person.
My hesitation gave the Demon Race a chance to strike.
After quelling the turmoil in Ning'an,
I’m willing to accept any form of punishment.
Master, I just ask that you
don't hurt Bai Shuo.
Bai Shuo?
What does this have to do with Bai Shuo?
Because...
the Desireless Stone
is in Shuo's body.
Father.
You're alright?
That's great.
I'm glad you're okay.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Why are you looking at me so seriously?
The people in the household said you saved me with a flower.
What kind of flower is that?
How did you get it?
It's just a flower.
I found it by chance.
I don't know what it's called.
I am perfectly aware of
what you're capable of.
A maniac condition that no doctor in the entire city could cure,
yet you happened to have its cure with a single remedy.
Tell me exactly what happened.
I went through so much to find the medicine to save you,
and yet you're not even the least bit moved.
Instead, you questioned me as soon as you came.
You wouldn't believe me even if I told you it was a coincidence.
Then, exactly what kind of answer
would satisfy you?
It's a complete chaos outside.
Half of our people have gotten the maniac condition.
It's not the time for you to be stubborn.
If we really have the medicine,
we should use it to save them.
If you know anything else,
spill it all out.
Me being stubborn?
So what is it that you want to hear?
You wouldn't believe everything I just said.
No.
It's not that you don't believe what I just said.
All these years,
you've never once trusted me.
You never once believed my words.
-I...
-Go take care of your people.
You don't have to worry about me.
There's too much going on in the city.
I was too anxious just now.
Besides asking about the medicine,
I also wanted to ask you,
why did you become so weak overnight?
Shuo.
This maniac condition is not that simple.
I don't want anything to happen to you.
You get some rest first.
We'll talk later.
It's not that I don't want to tell you,
But the Ghost Grass is a demonic object.
It feeds on human blood every day.
How am I supposed to tell you?
Watch carefully.
Don't put them there.
Keep your eyes wide open!
The city's soldiers,
cowering in fear at the first sign of trouble.
How dare you!
Stand straight!
General.
How is the city?
Following your orders last night,
majority of the people with the maniac condition
have been locked up in an abandoned yard in the east of the city.
But there are more of such people in the west.
We're short-handed.
There's no way we could hold them.
Now, we can only let the people who had fallen ill
stay at home.
Currently,
only the area surrounding the Governor's Mansion is guarded.
It's considered safe.
Don't worry.
The Governor has regained his consciousness.
He must have a way to deal with this maniac condition.
At times like this,
our spirits must remain unshaken.
The Governor has recovered?
-That's great!
-Great!
Didn't they say there's no cure for maniac?
So who could have
cured our Governor?
It's all thanks to Lady Shuo.
She was the one who found the medicine.
I didn't expect Lady Shuo to be so amazing!
It's really hard to notice on normal days.
Who are you to gossip about Lady Shuo?
Guard the gate well.
-Yes!
Grand Master.
How are things?
Although Bai Shuo has been resting at home,
Fan Yue has also been keeping a close watch.
It would be unwise to try and recklessly retrieve the Desireless Stone.
But Xixi heard
a piece of news just now.
Someone said
Bai Shuo has found a medicine
that detoxified Bai Xun's Nether Poison.
Only the Ghost Grass can alleviate theNether Poison.
And the Ghost Grass
originated from the Demon Region.
It looks like
it's the work of Fan Yue.
In that case,
let's give him a push.
Push?
The Nether Poison is rampant, and everyone is living in fear.
Who doesn't want the antidote?
Let me tell you something.
In this world,
it's not that people fear having nothing,
but that
you have what I don't.
A common's man only crime is to carry jade
that causes other's greed.
If everyone knows
Bai Shuo has the antidote,
does she have
any way out?
Since
the Desireless Stone has recognized its master,
it's not going to be easy to simply extract it from her heart.
I want to see
if
she dies for some other reason,
and the Desireless Stone has no master,
will it then
come out on its own?
I understand.
I’m on it.
As the Master of Cold Spring Palace, you came all the way here
but didn't come visit me at the Unriddled Pavilion.
Instead, you're hiding here.
Could it be that...
you're afraid?
It has been a long time
since you stole the Desireless Stone
from the Eternals.
However, you've been keeping it hidden.
As rumor has it, is it true that
you're injured
and urgently need
the Desireless Stone's divine power to save yourself?
Injured?
Bai Shuo belongs to me.
Don't you dare touch her.
You gave her the Ghost Grass
and sent her to death.
I honestly can't tell
you are trying to protect her.
The weapon is in my hands.
Whether I use it,
when and how I use it,
it's none of your business.
Get the Governor to come out!
Bring Bai Shuo out!
[Bai Residence]
Calm down, everyone.
The Governor will definitely think of a solution.
The Governor's Mansion clearly has medicine.
Why wouldn't you share it with us?
Come out!
What happened?
I don't know why, but suddenly word spread that
Lady Shuo could treat the maniac condition.
These people who were hiding at home
had all came to ask for the medicine.
There were also rumors that
that the Governor's Mansion is hoarding the medicine
and doesn't want to share it with the people.
Governor, please give us the medicine!
[Bai Residence]
What am I supposed to hear with all this noise?
Speak up and tell me one by one.
Governor!
Please give us the medicine
and save everyone!
Please save us!
Who did you all hear this from?
Everyone said so.
It's said that Lady Shuo found an effective remedy
and saved you, Governor.
They even asked us to come here and ask you for the medicine.
There are more and more people suffering from the maniac condition.
Please take pity on all of us
and give us the medicine.
Please give us the medicine, Governor!
The thing is, that medicine was something
my daughter stumbled upon.
There's really nothing left in the Governor's Mansion.
[Bai Residence]
Governor!
Please get Lady Shuo to come out
and treat all of us.
[Bai Residence]
Yes, Governor!
Everybody, please do not panic.
I will not leave this matter unresolved.
I ask that you trust me, Bai Xun.
Give me more time.
I will send people to look for the cure.
No matter how difficult it may be,
I will definitely give all of you an explanation.
Our Governor has been guarding the city for over 20 years.
He has always kept his word.
Everybody, there's no need to panic.
[Bai Residence]
More importantly, don't speculate.
Please trust me.
Please go home and wait.
Don't come out if there's nothing else.
It's best to avoid anyone with the maniac condition.
To solve this,
we must work together.
I, Bai Xun, promise
to keep all of you safe.
Exactly what's going on?
Governor!
Sir, bad news!
Lady Shuo suddenly fainted.
Bai Yu.
Calm down! Don't panic!
What's going on?
What happened to Shuo?
Just now,
I checked Lady Shuo's pulse.
There's a deficiency of both qi and blood.
According to my years of military experience,
I'm afraid it's caused by excessive bleeding.
Excessive bleeding?
Uncle Wang, how long has it been since you were with the military?
Your experience has long since been outdated.
I just didn't rest well last night.
Sir,
I'll take my leave.
Uncle Wang and I have been guarding Ning'an City for decades.
Given our battle-hardened experience,
he can't be wrong.
Tell me the truth.
How did you get that medicine?
How did you get so weak?
You still don't trust me.
It's not that I don't trust you.
It's just that the city is in chaos,
and people are panicking.
If we still can't find the medicine,
Ning'an City will be destroyed.
Who did it?
No one.
I accidentally hurt myself.
You call this an accident?
Shuo.
Can you tell me the truth?
I'm your father.
No matter how angry you are with me,
what can't you say
at this point?
Father, don't ask anymore.
There are some things that can't be solved
even if you are the governor.
Fine.
You won’t tell me?
I’ll ask Chong Zhao.
That kid is with you every day.
I want to see
who dares to
How dare you touch my daughter!
Father!
If Chong Zhao finds out about
the standoff between the Eternals and the demons,
he might simply destroy the Ghost Grass.
That way, I won't be able to continue the detox for my father.
I will tell you.
The Ghost Grass feeds on human blood.
It can suppress the maniac condition.
Consume one flower a day
without missing a single day.
♫What kind of flower would never bear fruit?♫
Sir, you mustn't!
This is the medicine to cure the maniac condition!
This is not medicine!
This is my daughter's life!
♫What kind of fruit never sees a flower?♫
As the governor,
I've failed to protect the city and instead caused chaos.
As a father,
I had caused my daughter to cut herself to feed this grass with blood,
♫Withstanding the stillness, you are a broken piece of me♫
in order to cure my maniac condition.
Bai Yu.
This is not medicine.
This is Shuo's blood.
♫I am the fruit to your flowers♫
What I am consuming every day
is my daughter's blood!
But Sir,
this grass is the only solution to the maniac condition now.
It has already bore fruit.
As long as we give its seeds to everyone
and plant it aplenty,
we'll be able to solve the maniac epidemic very soon.
If we need to water it with blood,
I am more than willing.
It won't work!
It won't work.
Governor.
How could this happen?
The Ghost Grass can only temporarily relieve symptoms,
but it cannot cure.
This is an endless abyss.
It's a life for a life.
Bai Yu.
You've been with me for more than ten years.
There's no kind of human nature you haven't seen.
You should know that once this grass is distributed,
it will cause bigger trouble
as long as someone becomes selfish.
By then,
it won't be chaos from the maniac condition,
but...
A massacre.
The vigor of youth often brings about arrogance.
I'll let you know very soon that
not everything
will always go your way.
A dragon without its tail,
no matter how it stirs the storm,
will never transform into a true dragon.
You?
What more can you do to upset me?
No hurry.
When the city is plunged into chaos
and conflicts unfold,
all that you desire and seek
will be in vain.
By then,
you'll know
what is means
to be upset.
The only thing you're trying to exploit
is Lanling Sect, isn't it?
Although those old men are annoying,
but they've been around for over a thousand years and are not fools.
How could they not see through
such a poorly conceived scheme?
Do you really think the Eternals
are the only ones I can exploit?
What else did you do?
The stage is ready.
You just need to
watch the show peacefully.
Since you are in the mood,
I’ll use your blood
and add some color to this stage.
It’s a mess outside.
You still have the mood for a barbecue?
Why not?
Can't I indulge myself
on my birthday?
Too many things have happened recently.
I can't believe I forgot about this big day.
Don't be sad, Father.
I've prepared a birthday present for you.
Let me go get it.
What gift?
Every penny you spent
came from me, isn't it?
Instead of spending money on those frivolous things,
you might as well sit down
and have a meal with me.
Where is Chong Zhao?
It's been days. Where did he go?
Maybe something happened at the steamed bun stall.
Who dares to buy steamed buns on the street now?
He better be okay.
I'll send someone to look for him.
Father.
He will be fine.
How would you know?
It's chaotic outside.
Other than steamed buns,
he can't even hold up a knife.
Anyway, just trust me.
Chong Zhao is fine.
Those people with maniac can't hurt him.
In a blink of an eye,
you've grown up.
You have your own secrets now.
Fine.
I'll trust you.
I won’t ask if you don’t want to tell me.
Chong Zhao is a good kid.
I trust him too.
He promised me
he'll take good care of you.
I don't need him to take care of me.
Father, has it ever crossed your mind that
even if I don't get married,
I can still live a good life?
Nonsense!
You're just spouting nonsense.
Fine, fine.
It's your birthday,
so you call the shots.
I am not going to make you angry today.
I heard
there were people making trouble outside today.
What nonsense?
Why would our people be causing trouble?
They are just afraid,
so they came to ask about it.
On the other hand,
how did you get your hands on
that bizzare Ghost Grass?
Don't let the bad guys fool you.
The world is full of strange things.
That grass is nothing.
After all, I was saved by immortals when I was young.
How hard is it for me to find a grass?
You're being strange today.
I mentioned the immortals,
and yet you are not scolding me?
You want to be scolded?
Weren't you always annoyed by my ramblings about the immortals,
thinking I was a disgrace
and not letting me bring it up?
I can't even keep track of
the number of times you've punished me over this.
So,
is my dear father
changing his ways?
Shuo.
I know you've suffered a lot.
All these years,
the city's people have always laughed at you and mocked you.
I am all aware.
You never told me any of your grievances.
All you ever did
was hide under the tree your mother planted
and secretly cry at night.
You weren't willing to tell me
because I've never taken your side.
I've never said I trusted you and supported you.
Not only did I not help you
chase away those who mocked you,
I even helped them
shut you up.
Why are you talking about this
all of a sudden?
Shuo.
Let me tell you a story.
Once upon a time, there was
a governor who was blessed
to marry the woman he loved as his wife.
Three years into the marriage,
his wife gave birth to
two adorable daughters for him.
But unfortunately,
his wife passed away a few years later due to illness.
The governor was grief-stricken.
He swore
he would never marry again,
and will raise his two daughters safely and peacefully.
But ten years ago on Lantern Festival,
he actually lost both his daughters.
The governor led his soldiers
to search for them everywhere,
and almost turned Ning'an City upside down.
In the end,
he found his daughters in a messy mausoleum outside the city.
But at that time,
he also saw
an unforgettable phenomenon.
-Lady Xi!
-Xi!
-Lady Shuo!
-Shuo!
Lady Xi!
-Lady Xi!
-Shuo!
Lady Shuo!
-Xi!
-Lady Shuo!
-Lady Xi!
-Shuo!
Xi!
Xi! Shuo!
Shuo!
Xi!
Sir.
Xi.
Tonight,
the girls simply got lost while playing in the city,
and that held them up from going home.
Nothing else
ever happened.
Understand?
Yes, Sir.
Father.
Shuo.
I saw that
purple moon.
I believe you.
I believe there are gods in this world.
Then why didn't you tell me all these years?
Because I'm the Governor.
The governor of the city must not only protect its people,
but also reassure its people.
Everyone in this city can talk about the supernatural
except for me.
In this life,
people seek gods and divination
just for peace of mind.
In the end, establishing oneself
requires personal effort.
♫If the wind intends to fill the sky with flowers♫
If even I falter,
if I too start talking about supernatural forces,
then people will also feel anxious.
♫The moon's brightness is also the result of stars falling into place♫
So no matter how much I trusted you,
I could not be on your side.
I couldn't even say,
♫As the wind stirs, the clouds gather♫
"I trust you."
♫As the clouds shift, the moon becomes full♫
So why
are you telling me now?
♫Love is the hardest thing to understand♫
Because I am going to do something.
Something you'll surely object to,
but I must do it anyway.
♫I'm finally back to where it all started♫
I just wanted to tell you that
from beginning to end,
♫All the answers are already explained♫
I have always loved you,
and I trust you.
What are you trying to do?
Father,
let me tell you.
♫I'll owe you all of my life♫
You must not do anything foolish that will upset me.
Or else, I won't forgive you.
♫But we're destined to part♫
Shuo.
♫How can I downplay this?♫
Live well.
What happened just now?
♫When you engrave your love into my heart♫
You...
♫When my star falls only for you♫
♫When the heavens fall♫
♫I can still connect with you through the waning moon♫
You drugged me?
Go to sleep.
♫When my pain blurs my eyes♫
When you wake up,
everything will be fine.
♫Out of the countless stars, I see only you♫
Wang!
♫As you turn into a falling star and crash into my heart♫
Sir.
Send Lady Shuo
out of the city immediately.
Sir.
Wang!
This city is my responsibility.
I will bear
any consequences.
Yes.
Father.
No.
[Bai Residence]
Come out! Come out!
Come out!
Calm down, everyone!
Our governor has been looking
[Bai Residence]
for a solution for everyone.
He's not the way you all think he is.
Save us! Screw you!
Step down!
Our governor has been trying his best
to come up with a solution for everybody.
Please give him more time.
I, Bai Yu,
thank you!
Bai Xun!
You scumbag!
Governor!
Sir, we can't hold the gate any longer.
The people outside...
Sir.
This...
Bai Yu.
Do you remember this sword?
Yes.
This is a gift from all the people in the city.
I remember that year,
Ning'an City was overrun with bandits.
I led you brothers
in six months of bloodshed
in order to wipe out the bandits.
The people found a piece of dark iron
and made this sword for me.
All these years,
I've always cherished it.
Bai Shuo, that child,
liked to play swords.
She would often sneak into my room
in the middle of the night to play with swords,
and would get a beating from me.
Because of this,
we were at odds for a long time after that.
Back then, Lady Shuo was still young.
She didn't understand your intentions.
She doesn't understand that
the value of swords
is not in its quality,
but its heart.
The people in the city
had not only given me a sword,
but also the safety of this city.
Bai Yu.
I've protected this city for twenty years.
It's time I protect it again.