♪Just To Meet You, you fell for me♪
♪Just to meet me, into my trap you fell♪
♪Wanna try a breathless love?♪
♪Every move hits the heart, close and sure♪
♪Just To Meet You, you love my playful charm♪
♪Just to meet me,
my romantic little schemes for you♪
♪Wanna play another brand-new game?♪
♪Layer by layer, we close the gap♪
=Just To Meet You=
=Episode 3=
=The Holy Maiden Arrives=
Kneel.
Master.
Young Master's return may be a good thing.
(Li Zhongtian, Chairman of the Li Group)
In that case,
all those rumors outside
about brothers turning against each other,
about the Li family splitting up,
(Li Hong, Second Young Master)
will disappear.
Now that Young Master is back,
rumors will surely
blow over.
Father.
I've finished the handover
for the hospital we acquired today.
My brother's back at the perfect time.
He can take over management.
With him,
the Li Group will rise again.
Seems like
none of you actually wanted me back.
Master.
Please calm down.
Our Li family
has a century-old legacy,
why must it depend on this unfilial son?
He looks more like
he's here to destroy the family.
Young Master,
hurry and apologize to your father.
Hurry.
Just apologize.
Father!
Give my brother whatever he wants.
I admit I'm not as capable as he is.
The future of the Li family
should be entrusted to him anyway.
Master.
It just so happens
the master
who picked an auspicious date is here.
Why not have him
cleanse Young Master of bad luck?
Welcome
the sorcerer.
Please take the seat of honor.
Kunping, Kunping,
by the command of blood,
with the power of the Baleng blade,
suppress all evil in every direction!
He is cursed with great misfortune.
You're the one Master trusts the most now.
Now it's your turn to perform.
Rest easy, Ma'am.
I've invited a powerful master from our sect.
Even if
Young Master survives,
he'll suffer greatly.
Young Master's evil aura
can only be cleared
by the Holy Maiden.
Master,
please invite the Holy Maiden.
Please bring the Holy Maiden here!
Bow in respect before Holy Maiden.
The Holy Maiden has manifested!
This man is possessed by evil energy.
Holy Maiden,
please dispel it.
please drive out the evil.
Holy Maiden, you...
You're drowning in debt,
your powers are gone,
and you still pretend to be divine?
He...
You fraud!
How dare you scam us!
- Guards!
- You...
Throw this fraud out!
Evil spirit,
you dare possess the Madam's body?
Withdraw at once!
You crazy woman!
How dare you hit me!
Such foul language,
it really is an evil spirit at work.
Not good.
The spirit has shifted again!
I see dark haze coiling round you,
let me
send you on your way!
Son.
That's enough!
All of you, get out!
Father, easy.
The Holy Maiden
really is performing an exorcism.
Mother.
How could you be fooled?
Good thing Xue isn't here today.
All you think about is Murong Xue.
You're going to
lose your place in the Li family.
If she finds out about this,
don't you think she'd instantly
run back to her childhood love,
Ye Lang.
(So Ye Lang's childhood sweetheart)
(is his brother's fiancée.)
(Classic rich-family drama.)
Young Master.
I can tell you possess a pure yang body.
May I borrow it temporarily
to suppress the evil spirit?
I shall comply
with your arrangement.
Stop right there!
You're not the Holy Maiden.
Who exactly are you?
She's a fraud
I hired with money!
Quick.
Go get her.
She's indeed not the Holy Maiden.
She's my lawfully wedded wife,
Jiang Niannian.
Ye Lang.
I sold you
and you don't resent me at all?
I don't.
Does someone like you
really exist in this world?
The Holy Maiden can tell fortunes.
Then tell me
why the person I love has come back.
I came back to save you.
As for selling you before,
let's call it even.
Just let it go.
Okay?
Of course we can't call it even.
You dumped me twice.
And you lied to me too, didn't you?
You said you were an orphan.
Turns out you have a stepmother
and a younger brother.
Those people
are not my family at all.
They even wanted me dead.
Wanted you dead?
I really have no one left but you.
The only person I care about is you.
Then what about your
childhood sweetheart,
Murong Xue?
She's just someone I knew as a kid.
Stop bringing up someone so irrelevant,
okay?
She's irrelevant.
Then who is important?
You.
(Jiang Niannian,)
(remember why you're here.)
(Use Ye Lang without hesitation)
(to find Jiang Xiaodi.)
Of course.
After all,
I said I'd help you myself
get rid of the evil spirit.
Why are you up so early?
Because
I want to be the first to say morning.
I haven't been to the office lately.
Too much work has piled up there.
Then you'd better get going.
Now go.
Alright, I'm going.
What's with Ye Lang?
Why is he living in such a cute room?
Xiaodi!
(Xiaodi.)
(Once I've secured my position here,)
(I'll find you very soon.)
(How long is he going to keep this up?)
I don't buy it.
No man falls in love that easily.
♪Stitched-up lips
tear open a blood-red dusk♪
♪You return reborn,
seeing through all my cracks♪
♪This tenderness, a trap or a gift?♪
♪Still, I'd wager my next life on it♪
♪Just for a moment to recognize you again♪
♪You are the blazing light in my despair♪
♪Lighting the edges of my frozen wings♪
♪I burn myself,
leaping into an illusion of fire♪
♪Breaking free
from dead vines in the ashes♪
♪You are the brightest star in the night♪
♪Awakening my dormant fate♪
♪Freeing me from this half-life prison♪
♪As the bells shatter the past♪
♪Life finds its way again♪