[Fate Chooses You]
[Episode 24]
Sister-in-law, you're awake.
Who are you?
Just call me Xiao Sha.
This is my home.
You were injured that day.
Lu brought you back.
I see.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Lu and I are like real brothers.
His business is my business.
His enemies are my enemies.
As for his family...
I must take good care of them.
Where is he?
Lu went out to buy some things.
He's been gone for a while.
I guess he should be back soon.
Sister-in-law,
please sit and have some tea
while waiting for him.
Okay.
Are you also a cultivator?
I am a disciple of Xin Xie Manor.
Xin Xie Manor?
I know.
You guys are amazing.
Are you a local?
Yes.
My family has lived here for generations.
Then how did you and Lu Qianqiao
meet?
It's a long story.
I was young and ignorant.
Once,
I offended Lu.
He taught me a harsh lesson.
After that, I was forced onto
the right path.
Forced?
Yes.
At first, I was reluctant.
But then I gradually realized
that my former buddies
who fooled around
all didn't end up well.
Then it all made sense.
Lu
looks cold but has a warm heart.
He always takes good care
of anyone he cares about.
He is indeed that kind of person.
So, Sister-in-law,
how did you and Lu
meet?
We met through marriage.
You're already married?
Lu moves fast, doesn't he?
So, Sister-in-law,
where are you settling down now?
If I go to the Central Plains
in the future,
I can visit you.
Settling down?
We haven't decided yet.
Haven't decided?
We got separated right after our wedding.
A lot happened afterwards,
and we just arrived in North Xiang.
So as for our future plans,
we haven't decided yet.
Well then, Sister-in-law,
where do you like?
Do you want to stay in North Xiang?
Why not stay in Phoenix City
and become my neighbor?
Better not.
I have to return to Xin Xie Manor.
My Master and juniors are all there.
Besides, I'm not used to the weather
in North Xiang.
It's too dry.
That's true.
You still have the immortal sect.
Unlike Lu,
who only needs to
worry about himself.
Your body hasn't recovered yet.
It's best not to appear in public
for the time being.
We also shouldn’t take anything
from the inn.
I bought you some
clothes to change into,
delicious pastries,
and some folktales
to kill time.
Come.
Try them on.
Do they fit?
They fit perfectly.
I don't know how to cook,
and Sha's cooking isn't good either.
I just ordered some dishes
at the restaurant.
The waiter will deliver them in a while.
If you're hungry,
you can eat some pastries first
to fill your stomach.
That's great.
Did you hear
everything I just said?
You knew I was outside?
I'm a cultivator after all.
You stood there for so long.
I didn't notice at first,
but I definitely realised later.
So you said all that
intentionally for me to hear?
Of course not.
But it's fine if you heard it.
You don't like North Xiang.
Not exactly.
I just don't want to be too far
from my Master
and my juniors.
Especially my junior—
she’s really attached to me.
When I was in Chongling Valley,
I saw her.
She seemed like
a very straightforward person.
That's because you
don't know her well enough.
My junior might look like
a little leopard on the outside,
but she's really just a little kitten.
She's very delicate and cute.
Really?
Really.
Believe me.
Our Xin Xie Manor is very big,
and only the three of us live there.
Actually...
Xin Mei.
After I finish renewing my blood,
my cultivation will drop significantly.
It will be roughly equivalent to
the Foundation Establishment Stage
of you human cultivators.
I know.
I'm also at
the Foundation Establishment Stage.
After renewing my blood,
I also need to transform my heart.
At that time,
I will lose all of
the War Demon's powers
and become an ordinary person.
You have to transform your heart?
Will it be very dangerous?
It's fine.
I can handle it.
But you can already
feel the pain by now.
Would transforming hearts
hurt a lot?
You still don't understand what I mean.
I mean,
afterwards,
I will become an ordinary person.
I will lose my power
and magic.
I'll no longer be able to
help you with any difficulties
you may encounter
in the Cultivation Realm.
Then I just won't live
Let's go back to Wei County.
That's my hometown.
You've lived there too.
And the Emperor
has already publicly declared that
your name has been cleared.
You don't even know.
The people there
now revere you as a living saint
and are building shrines
and temples for you.
And there are Lu Xiaodao and Lu Jiujiu.
They are your foster children.
They are living a good life.
If you are willing to go back
and live there,
you will definitely live a good life too.
Are you saying
you're willing to become
an ordinary person with me,
and give up cultivating altogether?
My Dao heart is unstable anyway.
I probably won't achieve much
on this path of cultivation.
And when I went back to
Wei County previously,
I saw my old friends.
I thought then,
if I hadn't left home back then,
maybe,
maybe I would have already lived
an ordinary and happy life.
♪ Once again I see
the world's cold indifference ♪
♪ Bending what I've cherished
all my life ♪
Xin Mei.
♪ Illusions and vanity blind the eyes,
how could one still care ♪
Thank you.
Lu Qianqiao.
♪ Having seen the widespread devastation ♪
I have my conditions though.
Tell me.
♪ How could I look on and ignore it? ♪
I want to bring my junior along.
Sure.
♪ If I do not fear the grave soil ♪
I also want to go back often
♪ I walk this path alone ♪
to see my Master.
Okay.
♪ So that all may share in ♪
And I want to live
in my Auntie's old house.
♪ The road to immortality ♪
Because there are many
of my friends and neighbors there.
♪ I fear not defying
immortal laws and sacred precepts ♪
It's very lively.
No problem.
A-Sheng, A-Sheng!
Follow me, follow me!
The head chef of Shanfu Vegetarian
had retired and returned to his hometown.
It's his apprentice cooking now,
and the cooking is much worse.
Here.
Thank you.
I say, Lu,
you’ve already married my sister-in-law.
Why are you still so polite?
Just eat your food.
Why do you talk so much?
Sha.
You are not young anymore.
Why aren't you married yet?
Love is a deadly poison.
I'm doing quite well alone.
Why should I find someone
to control me?
Besides,
I have high standards.
Ordinary girls
don't catch my eye.
Coming!
Sister-in-law, Lu,
you eat first.
You...
Is my senior here?
Sheng!
Senior!
I finally found you.
That day in Xutuo City,
you left a letter and left
without even saying goodbye.
It doesn't look like you at all.
Sheng?
You're hurt.
No.
Let me see.
I'm really not.
Senior, I'm fine.
It just looks scary.
The wound is actually very small.
Don't worry about it.
Are you hurt anywhere else?
No.
Brother.
That's...
Sister-in-law's junior?
Her name is Sheng?
Senior,
don't be sad.
It doesn't hurt anymore.
Who hurt you?
Tell me,
why did you end up like this?
Tell me the truth!
Senior.
You once asked me,
where my home is in North Xiang.
What I told you then,
that I have no home,
wasn't exactly a lie.
That place is indeed not my home.
He’s not exactly family either.
But I have an enemy.
We share a bitter and deep-seated hatred.
That person...
is my biological father.
Wushui Cliff is extremely tall,
teeming with poisonous mountains
and swarms of insects.
Even if he is
extremely skilled at the Void Stage,
he cannot escape death.
Senior,
rest assured,
he is dead for sure.
Those sons of his
are all dead too.
I even burned down the Qianyan Cave.
In the future, he will never
come to cause you trouble again.
Although he gave me life,
he never treated me as a human.
♪ Hear the Gu curse
turn into cries for help ♪
He originally wanted to
kill me in the womb.
♪ Blood-stained hand, sword drawn ♪
I was lucky to survive.
♪ Trapped in Qianyan Cave ♪
In that Qianyan Cave,
everyone could bully me
♪ Even hell must be broken free from ♪
and beat me.
He didn't teach me any techniques either.
♪ With every stroke of hatred ♪
If it weren't for my tough luck,
♪ Let it grow into a dagger I wear ♪
I would have died at his hands long ago.
♪ No need to show me mercy there ♪
♪ Let me take every blow ♪
Senior.
He is not human.
He is a beast, a sinner!
♪ Drag my wounds through the hollow road ♪
The number of people who died at his hands
is countless.
He deserves to die!
♪ I'll pluck the passion
locked in my brow ♪
Senior,
♪ At the end of the mountains,
I pick up fireflies now ♪
what's wrong?
♪ Burn me down, I feel no pain ♪
Why are you crying?
♪ I believe Heaven sees all ♪
Sheng.
♪ Its wrath shines upon demons ♪
I'm sorry.
♪ But who will show me mercy? ♪
You've suffered so much.
Senior.
♪ I believe I'm innocent ♪
♪ Turned into dust and scattered away ♪
This has nothing to do with you.
I'm sorry, Sheng.
♪ I accept this trial of love
fate has given me ♪
♪ I take in both love and hate alike ♪
She has fallen asleep?
Are you hungry?
Do you want something to eat?
I don't have much of an appetite.
If you're not hungry,
you still need to drink your medicine.
If you can't even take care of yourself,
how will you take care of your junior?
Let's go.
So that's the story.
I was wondering
why those people
would die so suddenly.
So it was all because of your junior.
Xia Xuanzi is an expert of the Void Stage.
and is skilled in the use of Gu.
Even you would have a hard time
winning against her.
Not to mention,
she is just a Golden Core cultivator.
Didn't you see
those wounds on her body?
Your junior
is not someone who easily
opens her heart to others.
Since she treats you this way,
it means
you're really good to her.
You said before
that the disciples of Xin Xie Manor
had all died
in the Battle of Pinghu.
So Sheng
joined Xin Xie Manor later?
That was
many years ago.
I was ordered by my Master to
go to the capital for an errand,
and met Sheng there.
She was having a hard time back then,
and was so thin and small.
She was wandering on the streets.
What?
Can't I even take shelter from the rain?
Here.
That customer just now
bought it for you.
Be careful when you eat.
Don't break my bowl.
I hadn't finished my errand,
so I rented a house and stayed there.
And then...
I met her again.
And then?
Then whenever I had time,
I would often go look for her,
but I couldn't find her most of the time.
She was very shy
and always hid away.
Later I realised
that once I stopped looking for her,
she would always come to see me secretly.
Come here.
Eat up.
Did she eat it?
She ate it all up.
After that, she kept coming for me.
She would give me an egg one day,
and some wild vegetables tomorrow.
But she never came close to me,
or talked to me.
This went on for about 2 months,
until something unexpected happened
with my plans,
and I had to leave the capital overnight.
By the time I came back,
it was
more than half a year later.
I went to look for her.
I searched for 3 days.
Finally, on the last day,
I found her.
Brat!
Let's teach her a lesson.
Beat her up!
Still not leaving?
Go, go!
Are you okay?
Why did they beat you?
Don't cry.
Did they
hurt you somewhere?
All's fine now.
It's okay.
And then?
And then I brought her back.
Xin Xie Manor is sparsely populated.
It was just me and my Master.
After Sheng came,
it became a lot livelier.
And she has immortal perception
and great talent.
She cultivates faster than I do.
Maybe it's because
I was the one who brought her back,
so she relies on me a lot
and listens to everything I say.
I have to thank her, too.
If it weren't for her,
I wouldn't know
how I would have survived
all these years.
You seem to really like your junior.
Of course.
She's my family.
[Phoenix City]
Knock on the door.
Yes.
With such terrible handwriting,
how do you have the nerve to show it?
I want to.
None of your business.
Do you know what it means?
I know.
Brother Tang had taught me everything.
What, changed your mind?
Don't want to learn swordsmanship
from Brother Rust-Sword anymore?
Of course I do.
Then you'd better think it through.
If you consider
my Brother Rust-Sword as your master,
you'll have to call me Uncle from now on.
In your dreams!
I can't be bothered with you.
Master,
have some tea.
What are you playing at?
I know you're not asleep.
Sister Zhanying.
Don't keep calling me your sister.
I'm not older than you.
Take off your boots.
Your boots are torn.
Come here, let me sew them up for you.
Torn?
That's not very appropriate, Sister.
You actually know how to do needlework?
Of course.
Who wasn't a delicate young lady
in her youth?
Embroidery, repairs,
I learned it all.
If my family hadn't suffered
a misfortune afterwards,
and I hadn't learned martial arts,
I might have become
a top-notch embroiderer.
Try it on.
You're quite good.
How is it?
It'll do.
After Tai Shiqian and the others
finish copying the books,
where do you plan to go?
I—
If you have nowhere to go,
why not come back to my hometown with me?
You have plenty of strength.
When the time comes,
you'll farm while I'll weave cloth.
Together,
we can definitely live a good life.
I'd better not.
I’ve had a rough life.
I simply don't have what it takes
to enjoy marriage.
I want to become
the best swordsman in the world.
For the rest of my life,
I am destined to wander on the road,
spending a lonely life.
Sister Zhanying,
you should find someone else to fancy.
Someone else?
But among all these people,
I have fallen for only you.
Others...
Forget it.
You don't need to worry too much about it.
I might like you today,
but maybe tomorrow,
I won't like you anymore
once I meet a better-looking man.
That would be a true blessing.
We only have a few days
left together,
so you should cherish me.
What day is it already?
It's been 8 days.
It's been 8 days?
It won't be long.
Yeah.
The plows of Qin, the rakes of Chu,
the sickles of Yan,
the hoes of Zhao and Wei,
though they may till the same soil,
they are not fit for the task,
because the nature of
the soil is different.
The plows of Qin, the rakes of Chu,
the sickles of Yan,
the hoes of Zhao and Wei—
Can you recite silently?
You made me memorize it all wrong.
I can't.
If I don't read aloud,
I can't memorize it.
What should I do then?
I'll go memorize it over there.
Anyway, that's how it is.
Regardless of what could be shared,
I’ve said everything there is to say.
What else do you want?
Junior Lin, you're worrying too much.
We just can't figure out,
if Lu Qianqiao had taken you as a hostage,
why would he suddenly let you go?
According to you,
I deserved to be killed by him,
and only then it would make sense, right?
Senior Bai is just asking.
Why get so worked up over it?
Junior Jiang,
what kind of magic potion
did this guy surnamed Bai feed you?
Don't forget,
we are from the same sect.
Senior Lin,
calm down.
Those demonic cultivators
are cunning
and difficult to deal with.
We just feel it's a shame
they got away again.
Logically speaking,
with your brilliance and martial prowess,
this shouldn't have happened.
Could there...
be more to the story?
Only you would be so sarcastic.
If you want to scold me, be direct.
Don't beat around the bush.
I wouldn't dare.
Of course you wouldn't dare.
You have no rights either.
He's at least
a Heavenly Talent born on
September 9th.
I’d put up with a few words of
his criticism.
Who do you think you are,
going on and on about me?
What about Lu Qianqiao?
Is he still with those
demonized cultivators?
I don't know.
Why don't you know?
Didn't you leave
with them?
That day,
we got separated.
We have been observing them
these few days.
After entering Sihe Library,
they haven't come out since.
And I haven't seen
that guy surnamed Lu.
I don't know where he went.
Intercepting them on the road
was originally the best choice.
Now that they are in the library,
it's not as simple.
This Sihe Library
has a heritage of a thousand years.
It has always been
a sanctuary for scholars
seeking knowledge.
There are many scholars
here right now.
If we act rashly,
I'm afraid the innocent will be harmed.
We have too little information.
How many enemies are there?
Do they have any backup?
The slightest mistake
can lead to oversights.
Then let's just burn everything down
and end it once and for all.
What did you say?
Otherwise, do you have a
better idea?
They are all demons and heretics.
They deserve to die.
I heard
that Sihe Library
opens only once every 5 years.
Even if we
kill them all today,
as long as Sihe Library exists,
5 years later,
they will definitely send
a new batch of people.
Are we going to
capture them again then?
Junior Jiang makes sense.
Destroying just one library
can destroy the demons'
hopes for resurrection.
It's totally worth it.
We can't destroy it so easily.
There are way too many classics
in Sihe Library.
Senior,
have you forgotten
how many humans and
how many immortals died during
the God-Demon War many years ago?
At that time,
the heavenly ladder was intact,
and the deities could still help us
fight against the demons.
Even with their help,
we still suffered great casualties,
and corpses littered the ground.
Now that the deities are gone,
if the demons revive,
who will resist them?
This Sihe Library
collects books from all over the world,
and its original intention was good.
But
the fact that the demonic manuals
were mixed in,
that itself is a sin.
Senior,
don’t think I’m being heartless,
but I still have to say this.
So what if we destroy just one library?
Even if I bleed out
and lose my life,
I am more than willing.
Senior,
I'm willing to lead the way.
Even if it means being condemned
for all eternity,
I will eradicate the demons
for the world
and the immortal sect.
Please let me enter Sihe Library, Senior.
Remember.
Your primary mission
is to destroy the
"Unparalleled Secret Magic".
Unless absolutely necessary,
you must not destroy the library.
Don't worry, Senior.
I am not crazy.
Besides,
those demonic cultivators
are just a bunch of
defenseless bookworms.
Taking two juniors with me would suffice.
Their main forces
will definitely be
defending outside the library.
When the time comes, please join forces
to fight this powerful enemy
and buy me some time.
Rest assured.
With my Chengying Sword here,
they certainly
won't be able to stir up any trouble.
Jin Lun?
Let go of me.
Let go of me!
Sheng?
Sheng, what's wrong with you?
Let go of me!
Sheng, wake up.
Let go of me.
Let go of me!
Sheng!
Sheng, wake up!
Sheng, what's wrong?
Sheng, don't be like this!
Sheng.
Sheng, wake up.
Let me go!
Sheng!
What's wrong with her?
I don't know.
I just can't wake her up.
No!
Sheng, you're awake.
Senior.
What's wrong?
Let's go back to Xin Xie Manor.
I want to go home.
The fish we raised in the pond last year
should be plump by now.
I want to eat your grilled fish.
Let's go back to Xin Xie Manor, okay?
I hate it here.
I hate North Xiang.
Once you recover from your injuries,
we will leave immediately.
The main dish is here!
I specifically warmed up
a pot of wine for you.
Thanks for the hard work.
Sha deserves some credit too.
I didn't really help muxg.
I just assisted a little.
Miss Sheng, you just recovered
from a serious illness,
so you should eat more.
I killed this fish.
Try it.
Senior, you have it.
You should eat more too.
Thank you, Senior.
Let's all eat!
Here, let me pour for you.
What kind of wine is this?
It smells so good.
If you want to drink it,
why don't you have it?
L-Lu, I'm sorry.
My stool...
The wine spilled.
I'll go warm up another pot for you.
I know what
you are up to.
You're trying to trick my senior.
Let me tell you.
With me around,
don't even think about it.
You know my senior is kind-hearted,
so you deliberately acted weak
and pretended to be wronged,
in order to trick her into marrying you.
After your scheme was exposed,
you erased her memory.
You feigned closeness,
repeated your trick,
and did it again.
You must be overjoyed now,
thinking your plan had succeeded.
You're the one pretending
to be weak and pitiful,
all while scheming tricks, aren't you?
What did you say?
As the daughter of Xia Xuanzi,
you could walk out alive
from a place like the Qianyan Cave,
cross the desert alone,
and arrive in the capital.
How could such a person
possibly be beaten up
by a few little beggars
without being able to fight back?
Little girl,
in front of me,
just stop doing all these nonsense.
This looks good.
Sheng.
Sheng?
Change into this.
Do you find it nice?
If you don't like it,
we can go to the city
and pick what you like.
Senior,
aren't we going home yet?
Wait until your injuries are better.
But I miss home.
Let's go home.
Previously, you said
you wanted to settle scores
with Lu Qianqiao.
Now that the misunderstanding is cleared,
we should go back.
Master is still waiting at the manor.
We can heal my injuries at home too.
But...
And I don't like North Xiang.
I'm scared.
I have nightmares every night,
dreaming that I haven't escaped yet.
That I am still in Qianyan Cave,
tortured by that lunatic every day.
Senior,
I'm so scared.
Let's leave, shall we?
I'm sorry, Sheng.
I was careless.
I didn't consider your feelings.
Let's go.
We'll leave right now.
[Sihe Library]
Hey there! Refill my water!
Coming!
Why does this tea
have no taste at all?
Is it about the tea?
Even if it were the finest tea
in the heavens,
after 8 pots of water,
of course it has no taste.
Then can't you change the tea?
I can.
Will you pay for it?
I booked the whole place.
The whole place!
I already paid!
Booking the place
doesn't include tea.
Do you still want tea?
Drinking water is fine.
It quenches thirst.
Fine.
These are all specialties of North Xiang.
You can't buy them in the Central Plains.
Our Master will definitely
like them when he sees them.
When did you join Xin Xie Manor?
Aren't we all family?
Family?
You and Immortal Xin are family.
Lu and I are family.
Well...
Did I leave something behind?
I'll go count them.
I haven't been to
the Central Plains for years.
I must be fully prepared,
seeing you off this time.
I'm sorry.
I promised to stay with you,
but Sheng...
It's fine.
It's not like we won't
see each other again.
Once I finish my work here,
I will go find you.
Really?
Of course.
While I'm away,
you must take good care of yourself.
Drink less wine.
Okay.
Also, if you have time,
use Spirit Projection
and tell me how you're doing.
I got it.
Senior!
Let's go.
It's time.
I'm leaving then.
Go ahead.