I'm so sorry.
I've come down with a fever.
Yes.
I should be able to make it in tomorrow.
Okay.
*Sigh*
I shouldn't have hung
around there after that.
I should've just gone straight home.
Did you think that just because you called,
I'd come running to you?
What do you even know about me?
We've only slept together a few times.
Let's not see each other for a while.
How long is "for a while" supposed to be?
Dammit!
For a while.
(Online Dictionary) Refers to a
short time, but not immediately.
What am I even looking up?
People are surprisingly fragile.
Apparently, you can
die just from dehydration.
If I collapse like this, I'm in trouble.
Even getting a glass
of water is a struggle.
At a time like this,
I don't have anyone I can just call.
I can't reach out to anyone.
Whatever.
It doesn't matter.
There's no point in trying so hard anymore.
I have nothing left to lose.
Ah...
But still...
If I could, I'd really like to...
one last time...
Kaji.
Are you okay?
What are you doing here?
Didn't you call me?
Did I?
You're burning up.
Here, drink something first.
Your mouth is so hot.
I'll catch it.
Yeah, you probably will.
But I can't help it.
I'm sorry,
but I want to give it to you.
Can we just
stay like this all day?
This feels nice.
Like this,
it feels like I don't have
to worry about anything.
Touch me.
I'll comfort you too.
Oh no...
I'm going to come.
Kaji.
Let's kiss.
It's like a dream.
Kaji.
Is this okay?
Fukami...
I told him we shouldn't
see each other for a while,
but I didn't mean it.
I really wanted
to be kinder to him.
A dream?
Just kill me now.
"Unexpectedly Naughty Fukami"
At times like this, I need to work.
Use work to forget all
these useless worries.
Sorry to worry you.
(Episode 5)
My fever's gone down a bit.
I'll work from home for now.
Huh?
If you don't rest,
HR will be all over me.
Just take the day off.
Being idle just makes things worse.
If I can't work,
I might as well deal with this frustration.
Having dreams like that
is just a sign of being unsatisfied.
Is he
still mad?
Wait, he never
asked if he was the only one anyway.
(40-pointer: Want to meet today?)
He's got a decent face,
but he's a loud "40-point" guy.
As long as I don't get
attached to one person,
I won't have to feel this pathetic.
Wait, do we really need all these files?
Please.
Kaji-kun still has a high fever.
Let him rest.
Oh, fine.
I get it.
Get well soon, Kaji-san.
Come on in.
Have a seat on the sofa.
I'm surprised you invited me over.
Want to shower first?
You seem like a different person.
Usually you're ready to kick
me out the second we're done.
Am I?
Yeah.
But
I didn't mind it that way.
Actually...
Can I shower first?
I'm all sweaty.
(Zero-point guy: I'm nearby. Are you home?)
Zero points.
What is this?
I used to think love
was something I didn't need in my life.
Even today,
I just felt like
I wanted to do it.
It's so embarrassing.
Acting all desperate
like some guy in a porn.
I should be more composed.
Like, just kissing and stuff.
Wait, right here?
When I'm with you,
I don't feel like myself anymore.
- Never mind.
- Akihiro.
You should at least know
the name of the person
you're sleeping with.
Why am I realizing this now of all times?
That took a while.
Hey...
Sorry.
You really didn't have
to walk me to the station.
At least let me do this much.
I hope things work out for you.
I'm sorry.
I told you, stop apologizing.
Fukami.
I was in the neighborhood
and heard you were sick.
Oh.
So you're the "Zero-point guy."
I saw his contact list.
He actually rates every guy he knows.
I'm a 40.
And you're a zero.
Funny, right?
I can't believe I kept in
touch with a guy like this.
I'm an idiot for coming
running the moment you called.
This guy looks down on everyone.
Me,
and you too.
Rating people
and tossing them aside
whenever he feels like it.
Who does that?
You're better off not
wasting your time with him.
What is he talking about?
He's totally got the wrong idea.
I don't want
to keep lying to myself
in front of this man anymore.
I'm sorry.
I know I'm terrible.
About the "zero points"...
That's really what I thought at first.
But
it's not like that anymore.
I'm not good at this,
- but I...
- Don't touch me.
I'm not like you.
I should just quit you.
This isn't like me at all.
If I knew it would hurt this much,
I never would've slept with you.
Fukami...
Life isn't a story.
There's no such thing as "the one."
"Happily ever after"
[To Akihiro-chan]
is just a fantasy.
That's why I decided
to find comfort with people as lonely as me
and live my life that way.
Of course he's angry.
I trampled on his feelings
and lied to him.
All of this
is my own fault.
I don't know how to start a relationship,
and I don't know how to end one.
(Next time) Hey, I heard someone
from Tech was in a car accident.
I heard they were brought here.
Are they here?
That person is very important to me.
I like you.
Even if you only look at
me with lust in your eyes...
One day, I'm going to
make him head over heels for me.