♪Just To Meet You, you fell for me♪
♪Just to meet me, into my trap you fell♪
♪Wanna try a breathless love?♪
♪Every move hits the heart, close and sure♪
♪Just To Meet You, you love my playful charm♪
♪Just to meet me,
my romantic little schemes for you♪
♪Wanna play another brand-new game?♪
♪Layer by layer, we close the gap♪
=Just To Meet You=
=Episode 18=
=True Love Or Deception?=
Niannian.
Ye Lang.
I can't find Xiaodi.
Don't panic.
He couldn't have gone far.
But he just had surgery.
He can barely walk.
What if...
Any accident
could kill him.
Don't worry.
I promise you
I'll find him.
Trust me.
We found an extra body.
Niannian.
(Name: Jiang Xiaodi
Signed: Zheng Lu)
Niannian.
Xiaodi.
Why is his heart gone?
Who was it?
Who took Xiaodi's heart?
Niannian.
- Let me go!
- Niannian, calm down.
Let me go!
You're only putting yourself at risk.
Calm down!
Ye Lang.
You lied to me.
You lied to me!
You said
you'd bring Xiaodi back.
You said you'd bring him back safe!
You lied to me!
It's my fault.
My fault.
I should've stayed by his side.
I'm sorry.
I'll find who did this.
I'll make them pay.
I promise.
Xiaodi must've been in so much pain.
All my fault.
Jiang Niannian!
What are you doing?
Xiaodi.
I'll take the pain for you.
I'll take it for you.
If anyone should take it, it's me.
It's not your fault.
I failed to protect Xiaodi.
♪Stitched-up lips
tear open a blood-red dusk♪
Give it back!
Give it back.
Put me down.
Snap out of it!
Let me go.
- Let go.
- Jiang Niannian.
Don't ever say that again.
Do you hear me?
Let me go.
I'm going to find Xiaodi.
♪You are the blazing light in my despair♪
♪Lighting the edges of my frozen wings♪
♪I burn myself,
leaping into an illusion of fire♪
♪Breaking free
from dead vines in the ashes♪
♪You are the brightest star in the night♪
♪Awakening my dormant fate♪
We already lost Xiaodi.
I can't lose you too.
Don't leave me.
Don't leave me alone.
Xiaodi.
Who was it?
Niannian.
Are you okay?
You've been dreaming.
Was it a nightmare?
Where's Xiaodi?
Xiaodi...
Xiaodi was handed over to the police.
Don't worry.
They will find the murderer.
Will Xiaodi come back then?
How can you
say that to brush me off?
You have no idea how much pain I'm in.
Weren't you reborn with memories?
Why didn't you change any of this?
I...
I wanted to change this.
But you didn't change a thing.
You know what?
Every time I close my eyes,
I see Xiaodi lying there.
Where are you going?
Let me go.
Let me go!
I'm going to the hospital.
I'm going to the cold storage.
I'll check every single
heart transplant record in Manlong!
- Let go of me!
- Jiang Niannian!
The police are already on it.
What are you trying to do?
What's the use of that?
By the time you find it,
it would be too late!
I remember
you were hurt here too.
You took Xiaodi's heart.
Jiang Niannian,
you can suspect anyone,
but not me.
I touched Xiaodi's heart.
It wasn't warm at all.
They took away
the last bit of warmth he had.
(Hospital surveillance.)
(City traffic footage.)
(Medical forums.)
(Organ Trafficking)
(Organ Trafficking, Fixed Price)
(Big Reward For A Kidney)
(Organ Trafficking)
(Heart, Fresh Donor, O RH-Negative)
(Starting Bid: 5 million, Sold)
No way.
How come there's an
organ trafficking network
(Heart, Fresh Donor...)
in Manlong?
(Organ Trafficking)
Cloud Gallery?
(Cloud Gallery)
(On Sale, Sold)
Li family's art gallery.
Li family...
Ms. Jiang.
The gallery you asked me to investigate,
its owner passed away 15 years ago.
It's been vacant ever since,
and has never been sold.
What's the owner's name?
A very famous artist,
Ye Mei.
Watch the step.
Why did you bring me here?
I was too impulsive before.
Actually,
I've always wanted to apologize.
Niannian.
You don't need to apologize.
From now on,
let's not fight anymore, okay?
I've been curious
what else
Auntie Ye liked
aside from painting?
My mom
was passionate about charity.
She used the proceeds from her paintings
to set up many foundations.
Then it sounds like
Auntie Ye
held auctions quite often.
Niannian.
We've been together a long time.
You don't need to
beat around the bush.
Just ask me directly.
Okay.
Then I'll ask you directly.
The buyer of Xiaodi's heart
on Manlong's dark web,
why is their IP tied to Ye Mei's gallery?
Niannian.
That's impossible.
My mother died many years ago.
I...
♪Stitched-up lips
tear open a blood-red dusk♪
♪You return reborn,
seeing through all my cracks♪
♪This tenderness, a trap or a gift?♪
♪Still, I'd wager my next life on it♪
♪Just for a moment to recognize you again♪
♪You are the blazing light in my despair♪
♪Lighting the edges of my frozen wings♪
♪I burn myself,
leaping into an illusion of fire♪
♪Breaking free
from dead vines in the ashes♪
♪You are the brightest star in the night♪
♪Awakening my dormant fate♪
♪Freeing me from this half-life prison♪
♪As the bells shatter the past♪
♪Life finds its way again♪