( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
[This drama is fictional and any similarity
with reality is purely coincidental.]
[Production guidelines were followed
when filming children and animals.]
[Episode 11]
Hold it!
I have an objection to the contest results.
I apologize, but during the judging process,
allegations have surfaced
that President Kang Du Jun
gave special treatment
to a specific participant.
That's absurd. In this judging session, I...
That female employee
President Kang Du Jun is seeing.
He deliberately gave
first place to that employee.
What?
- Oh, my.
- Is it real?
Du Jun.
No matter what, you should have
separated business from personal matters.
Don't you agree, sister-in-law?
- Sister-in-law?
- They're in-laws?
- What?
- No way!
- Jeez.
- How?
That woman is Manager Jang?
- Then...
- I mean they are...
The President and her...
- What?
- What happened?
Is he hurt?
Oh, dear.
Call! Call 911!
- Call them!
- Stay calm.
I'm on it.
The examination shows
a slight fracture in the scapula.
There's also some bruising
and swelling in the surrounding muscles.
If you move it abruptly,
the fracture could worsen,
so you must keep your arm
as still as possible today.
Is it that serious?
It doesn't require surgery,
but the initial pain is strong,
and we need to check for
any possible complications.
Please stay hospitalized
for a day or two for observation.
Okay.
Hospitalization is really necessary?
It'll heal over time.
Hey.
I told you not to move your arm.
I'm fine, really.
I don't have time to be lying around here.
There's so much to handle.
Didn't you hear what the doctor said?
For at least a week, you shouldn't
strain or move your arm.
If you want to heal quickly,
you absolutely must rest.
Don't you remember that?
I'll go to the office tomorrow
and fix everything.
I'll restore your reputation,
so don't worry too much.
By the way, will you be okay?
Everyone knows about our relationship now.
I feel relieved.
I was always wondering when we'd
be exposed and what I should say.
Now we don't have to hide it.
I imagined countless times
how I should handle it
when something like this happened.
Each time, I always ran away.
But now that it's actually happened,
I just felt confident, you know.
I think I've become
a different person from yesterday.
Wow, what is all this?
The President's woman is Manager Jang?
Exactly!
So until now, she deceived
everyone perfectly?
No, she didn't deceive us.
She just couldn't speak about it.
Then Manager Jang being pregnant...
So that's why she didn't drink.
What about it?
Do you think Manager Jang achieved those
just because she's the President's woman?
- No.
- But I still feel disappointed.
Hiding her pregnancy while working.
Then should she have announced 'I'm pregnant'
and spread the news all over?
Has Manager Jang ever once let the team down
because of her pregnancy?
- No.
- Exactly, she hasn't.
We're just fascinated
because it's Manager Jang.
Then what about the contest
first place issue?
Manager Jang never received help
from the President even once.
Manager Nah and I can vouch for that.
- Right?
- Huh? Yeah.
Everyone saw how hard Manager Jang worked.
But Team Leader, did you know about it?
That Manager Jang is the President's woman?
Huh?
Right? I noticed she started siding with her.
Huh? That's just natural instinct.
Oh my, how can anyone be so oblivious?
Alright, let's get back to work.
- She's quick to catch on.
- She seems very flustered.
She already knew.
Her shift in stance is so quick.
Why are you here?
Just stepping out front to make a quick call.
You must be very tired.
Si Hyeong will bring you back soon.
Before that, you should eat.
- Your meal is here.
- Yes.
Please give it to me.
No, just leave it.
I'm not that sick.
You don't need to go through
all this trouble.
And he's bringing food for you too
on his way here,
so we can eat together when he arrives.
No.
You need to take your medicine first,
so eat quickly.
I want to eat together.
It's my first time eating with my left hand,
and it's not going well.
Oh, here, let me help you.
Here, open it.
What are you doing? Open your mouth.
- Ah.
- I'll eat it myself.
But you said it's hard
to eat with your left hand.
Come on, open your mouth.
There you go.
Okay, now try some side dishes too.
Here, open it.
No, I'll really eat this one myself.
Are you embarrassed?
Open it.
See, eating well is so good.
Huh? You got some on your face.
Why are you avoiding it?
Du Jun, I brought...
I brought your underwear
and socks just in case.
Why did he bring underwear and socks?
I didn't even ask him to.
Should I step out for a bit? About an hour.
- Oh, no.
- No, no, is that food?
You probably haven't eaten, right?
- Let's eat together.
- Come on.
I suppose I'm a little oblivious.
Uncle.
Huh? Se Hyeon.
How's your shoulder?
It's okay, it's nothing serious.
I don't know why Mom is acting like this.
I feel so ashamed in front of Manager too.
Why? You don't need to worry about it.
I'm so anxious.
Can't you stop Mom, Uncle?
Right now, you're the only one
who can stop Mom.
That company, that position
Mom wants so badly.
I really don't need any of it.
Mom isn't doing this for me.
Se Hyeon.
I'm sorry about today.
I know how much effort
you put into preparing for the contest.
Why are you apologizing?
You didn't do anything wrong.
I'm okay.
You know I didn't do it, right?
Of course, absolutely.
Then that's all that matters.
I know, and you know.
The truth will come out eventually.
Well,
I safely escorted the ladies home.
Oh, what happened with the investigation
about the contest?
Ah, I did manage to get it.
It's the evaluation form filled out
[Taehan Liquor in-house contest judge]
by the external judges.
Your name's right there
on the list of attendees.
[Taehan Liquor in-house contest judge]
The judging criteria here are vague,
and it's awkward to disclose this
to the employees.
Exactly.
That's exactly why they put your name on it.
[External judge information]
Hidden Partners?
What kind of company is this?
It says it's a marketing consulting firm.
But there's no detailed
information available.
CEO Seo Myeong Ho?
This name sounds familiar.
Si Hyeong, dig deeper into
this company and its CEO for me.
- Okay.
- And
how about the CCTV footage you were checking?
Yes, that's correct.
The CCTV inside the main auditorium at 2 PM.
And please check the surrounding
CCTV cameras as well.
Yes, the main auditorium at 2 PM?
What is it?
Just a moment, I'll check
some other places too.
Just a moment.
[Around the main auditorium]
What?
It's already been deleted?
The CCTV footage has all been taken care of.
- Good work.
- What about the contest winner?
Pretend it never happened.
We'll pin it on corruption anyway.
While we're at it, invalidate the 2nd
and 3rd places completely too.
Pardon? Why the 2nd and 3rd places...
Because nothing is more troublesome
than making enemies.
- I have no choice.
- Hello.
- Are you okay?
- Well, I could have won first place.
That's the woman, right?
The one with the President?
Right? She's really shameless.
I heard she even got pregnant.
She's really something else.
Still, giving her first place in the contest
is a bit over the top, don't you think?
She came to work again.
I thought she'd be
too embarrassed to show up.
Jeez, I could never do that.
- Let's go.
- Yes.
Ride the next one with me.
You go ahead first.
Were you shocked that day?
What about Yeol Mu?
This much won't bother me.
Right, Yeol Mu?
You almost got yourself in big trouble.
Do you know how scared I was
thinking you were hurt?
This won't do.
If it's tough being next to the President,
tell me right away.
I'll just squeeze in like this and...
Ah, not again.
Yeah, it was just a joke to get you laugh.
I know it's a joke.
Let's go, let's go.
How should we treat Manager Jang?
- What do you mean?
- Should we call her Madam?
Madam?
Why? If she marries the President,
she might not even share a table with us.
You think Manager Jang would really do that?
It wouldn't hurt to make
a good impression in advance, though.
Team Leader Bang!
Come out.
What is this?
I heard the contest is void.
Why are you coming
to our team and doing this?
It's not like we asked for it.
It's because you team is involved.
This whole thing started
because of that one female employee.
Because we promoted
the contest so extensively,
now the company's image
is ruined with consumers.
Come on, just because they're dating,
doesn't mean she got any special treatment.
Exactly, our Manager Jang
isn't that kind of person.
Whether she is or isn't that kind of person,
our team winners are crying
and in chaos right now.
Well, if she's the President's girlfriend,
whether she stops the contest
from being voided or takes responsibility,
she should do something, right?
So why are you coming to our team
and doing this now?
Jeez.
What are you talking about?
Void?
Are you saying the awards have been canceled?
Change everything before Kang Du Jun arrives.
Wasn't I the target?
Was there any reason to do this
to the other winners too?
Well, it doesn't seem like what the person
at the center of the controversy should say.
I never received any special treatment.
Just because I'm seeing the President,
you shouldn't do this without any proof.
Even you confronting me like this could be
seen as a special treatment, couldn't it?
Other employees wouldn't dare
think of confronting the President directly.
Since you're dating President Kang Du Jun,
you don't seem to understand
what counts as special treatment.
If you have something to say,
go through the secretary's office.
You're the one who needs to keep
business and personal matters separate.
It was you who called me your sister-in-law
in front of everyone at the ceremony.
I will formally raise an objection
regarding this contest's judging process.
Whether I received special treatment or not
is something you need to clarify.
What can we do to increase
the reach of the new campaign?
Our team has been
working on the brand slogan...
Who decided to void the contest?
I thought you were taking a few days off.
Even if you're the co-president,
how can I trust you to hold down
the fort if you handle things like this?
Everyone, could you give us a moment?
We need to talk privately.
Can't you see we're
in the middle of a meeting?
Then shall we all discuss
the stunt you pulled
at the ceremony right here?
If Hui Won had got hurt,
I wouldn't have stood idly by.
Why do you think I did it?
Do you have any proof?
And what proof do you have, sister-in-law,
to slander me and Hui Won like that?
If my name was on the judging sheet,
does that mean I gave special treatment?
Then prove it.
Prove that you didn't participate.
Seo Myeong Ho, CEO of Hidden Partners,
was on the list of judges.
Are you familiar with him?
The firms on the list were included
based on executive recommendations.
What's the problem?
Yeah?
I just had a feeling you might know him well.
You shouldn't mention the company.
It's not even confirmed yet.
And if you acted like we knew something,
they might try to interfere in advance.
That's why I said it.
- Huh?
- So they'd move.
Because if they interfere,
it's like admitting guilt.
Let's just wait and see
how it plays out first.
And, Si Hyeong,
call in the contest winners.
Okay.
Huh? Here?
Yes.
First, I sincerely apologize
for upsetting you
regarding this competition.
Oh, no, it's okay.
The reason I called you here today is
because there have been
a few misunderstandings.
I never participated in this judging process.
And I never gave any benefits whatsoever
to Manager Jang Hui Won here.
After belatedly
reviewing the judging process,
we found issues with the judging criteria.
So I'd like to make a proposal to you all.
A proposal?
There are two options.
Although the competition has been canceled,
we can provide partial compensation
to the winners, that's the first.
The second is to conduct
a re-judging of the competition.
- A re-judging?
I believe it's only right to get
the winners' consent regarding this matter.
Whether you get another chance
through re-judging,
or take the compensation and stop,
is your choice.
Instead of taking compensation
and pretending it never happened,
isn't re-judging better?
But from our perspective,
if we fail the re-judging,
won't it feel even more unfair?
We don't know if we'll win an award
or fail in the re-judging.
Still, we worked hard, right?
It wasn't even our fault,
so canceling the entire contest
feels really unfair, doesn't it?
I feel wronged.
I worked day and night preparing for this.
I don't want it to just vanish
into thin air.
Exactly.
Well, I was thinking of giving up anyway,
so should we just go ahead
with the re-judging?
Let's try it. But then,
how will the judging work?
The first document screening will be done
by a mix of internal and external judges.
For the second round, we're still
figuring out the fairest method.
Previously the judging was blind,
but now the products are already revealed.
What about incorporating public evaluation?
- Public evaluation?
But would that be okay?
Posting the pitching videos online
to reflect public opinion.
Some people might still misunderstand you.
That's why I chose the direct approach.
If I make my proposal public
and prove it has real potential,
at least people won't say
I received special treatment.
That makes sense.
Once everything's out in the open,
no one will be able to say anything.
Because you are capable enough.
I hope so.
But may I ask why it's non-alcoholic?
Oh.
Well,
it reminds me of my mom.
I'm not sure.
Maybe it's because I'm about to become a mom,
or because I worry about my mom
turning to alcohol when things get hard.
It sounds silly, right?
Then I'm glad I reached out.
Pardon?
The weather's nice, and I thought
it'd be good to have a meal together.
Please eat.
I'm really sorry, but I have an urgent call.
Please excuse me for a moment.
I heard you met with the President.
Why didn't you tell me?
You didn't even call me once.
No matter what I say to you now,
you just call it nagging.
I have to talk directly
to my future son-in-law,
so he knows his mother-in-law is scary.
Son-in-law?
You're getting married, aren't you?
Huh?
Oh, right.
Am I the one getting married?
It's your marriage.
If you two are happy, that's fine.
Thought you'd object.
I'm tired of fighting with you.
Even arguing...
takes energy.
Are you feeling unwell?
Just a cold.
If you're sick, just rest.
You're not mixing medicine
and alcohol again, are you?
I told you not to do that.
- And not where I can see...
- Ugh, stop nagging.
I got it.
So don't get sick.
Do I have any other family?
You're all I have left.
Oh please, you take care of yourself.
What's with your face?
I'm doing well.
Make sure you eat properly.
You said you're sick.
Oh, I'll do it myself.
Ah, really, even if I take care of you...
Fine, that's enough.
Seriously.
[Taehan Liquor 1st In-house
Beer Brand Contest Final 7]
Ugh.
My heart's pounding so hard
I can't even look.
I told you not to expect
your name to be there.
But how can I just do that?
I'm really confident this time.
Please check quickly. I'm curious.
[Taehan Liquor 1st In-house
Beer Brand Contest Final 7]
- Uh.
- Jeez.
I'll check.
Oh, no.
Huh?
Huh? Manager Nah In Nam.
Manager Jang Hui Won!
Wow.
This isn't a dream, right?
Yes! There's no way my high-proof beer
wouldn't make it!
You both worked so hard, really.
All that effort up until the deadline
really paid off.
Manager Jang, congratulations.
Thank you, everyone.
But this is just the beginning.
So yesterday's allies become today's enemies?
[Second-round evaluation process]
Oh, so out of the final seven,
they'll pick 1st, 2nd, and 3rd place.
For the second round, if you upload
a 2-minute pitch video on YouTube,
[Views, Likes]
they'll score the marketability products
based on the video's views and likes.
So the key is how well you captivate
the public in a short time?
I guess
it's time I capture the public's attention.
Jeez.
Hey, they were congratulating me
the whole way here.
Manager Jang, are you confident?
- Du Jun.
- Yes.
About that Hidden Partners you mentioned,
suddenly all their tax records
were perfectly in order yesterday.
Their transaction history checked out too.
[Hidden Partners' Account Transactions]
It's like they're trying to show
'We're a perfectly legitimate company.'
This makes it even more certain.
They definitely embezzled, and there must be
[Hidden Partners' Account Transactions]
other money laundering routes besides this.
Dig into that.
Got it.
- Oh, Hidden Partners' CEO Seo Myeong Ho.
- Yes.
He used to be a reporter.
But how did he suddenly become a company CEO?
A reporter?
By any chance, Sungjin Daily?
Huh? How did you know?
Mr. Kang Du Jun! Did you deliberately
let go of your brother's hand?
Did you take him there intending to kill him?
Did you kill your brother
over the successor position?
Don't you feel any remorse
towards your family?
Explain yourself. Don't you feel any guilt?
Did you kill your brother on purpose?
Mr. Kang Du Jun! Answer me!
Mr. Kang Du Jun.
Say something!
Kang Du Jun! Why did you kill your brother?
Stop! Stop!
What's wrong? Who's that?
No, nothing.
It's clearly not nothing.
What is it?
It seems Kang Du Jun knows something
and is probing about Hidden Partners.
Uncle, did you leak something?
Are you doubting me now?
It's strange.
It's almost like he's caught on to something.
I've never seen you
this rattled before, President Han.
Didn't you put Mr. Seo's name
on the list so you could pin
everything on him if you got caught?
Well, that might be.
But since he's your man,
please keep him in check,
so he doesn't raise suspicion.
- I can trust you, right?
- Jeez.
15 years ago,
the one who first reached out
asking for help wasn't me, it was you.
When Han Jun died
and my brother covered it all up,
you asked to reopen the investigation.
And you were the one who pushed
to frame Du Jun as the murderer.
Why are you bringing that up now?
That's why I cleaned up
after you every time you messed up.
You do realize you owe me quite a bit
over the resort's shoddy construction,
don't you?
Didn't we agree not to mention
that matter anymore?
I'll cover for you only if I'm sure
we're on the same side.
Nothing comes for free.
Where are you now?
You'll need to lay low for a while.
As inconspicuous as possible.
You know what I mean, right?
Okay.
Hello, I'm Jang Hui Won from Taehan Liquor's
New Product Development Team.
What does beer mean to you?
To me, beer was a small comfort
at the end of a long day.
Ah, not great.
Hey, Jang Hui Won.
What? I'm fine. Why'd you come?
You know voice care is everything
before a presentation, right?
Here.
Drink it.
- What is this?
- This is
a concoction made with
everything good for the throat.
- Pear-and-bellflower root ginger tea.
- Ta-da!
We boiled this for four hours.
- Drink it all.
- Exactly four hours and forty-nine minutes.
- Yeah.
- You need to drink this tomorrow.
- Ugh, it's bitter.
- Come here.
Keep your throat warm
until the presentation. Okay?
- Thanks.
- Is your presentation prep going well?
Hmm, it's okay.
But I'm struggling with the concept.
If you only have about two minutes,
you need to grab the public's attention fast.
Then the concept really is important.
Just presenting plainly feels flat.
I need something distinctive.
If it's public evaluation,
it's like an audition, right?
In auditions, individual talent
and skill are important,
but I think their charm is determined
by their personal story.
Yeah, that's right.
Telling your own story about the beer
you want to make might be good.
A story.
My own story.
But it seems like it helped a bit, right?
I hope so.
Hui Won will do well.
She's always strong in real situations.
Right, that's who she is.
What about you? Are you okay?
- About what?
- Just wondering
if you're feeling any better.
I'm fine.
You're the one who said you were fine, okay?
Huh?
Buy me dinner.
And cake for dessert.
What are you doing?
Last time you didn't have your wallet,
I bought you dinner and dessert.
Buying isn't a problem, but...
From now on, I'm going straight for you.
I told you
it's not friendship for me.
It's love.
If you don't like it,
you can avoid it.
I don't know how to do that.
You coming?
Hurry up, Cha Min Uk.
[OB-GYN Appointment Day]
By the way,
I'm so curious.
Do you know the baby's gender yet?
- Pardon?
- Me too! I've been super curious.
But before that, are you
marrying the President?
Oh, right! When's the wedding?
You'll invite all of us, right?
A chaebol wedding must be
something different, right?
I'm really looking forward to it.
You'll have a wedding invitation
gathering too, right?
- Manager Nah.
- Yes?
For a father of three,
you sure love team dinners.
So how much did you tell them?
The gender? The wedding date?
I didn't know everyone would be this curious.
I'll tell you when the wedding date is set.
Of course, I'll invite you.
I'll be disappointed if you don't come.
And when the invitations are made,
I'll treat everyone to dinner.
As for the baby's gender,
I think we'll find out soon.
We're going to a check-up today.
That's why you took a half-day off.
Do you want a daughter or a son?
What difference does it make?
If the baby looks like you two,
there's nothing to worry about the looks.
Actually, I saw the ultrasound photo,
and whoever they take after,
their arms and legs are long,
and their fingers are pretty too.
The ultrasound photo!
- Show me too! Me too!
- Me too!
Do you want to see?
Here!
Oh my, so pretty!
Oh, look at this.
- Cute, right?
- Really pretty.
- So long.
- Yes.
The arms are so long.
- Right?
- Adorable.
- Looks like Manager Jang.
- Where are the feet?
Here.
- Here.
- I see.
[Delivery Room, Neonatal Intensive Care Unit]
I said I could come alone.
You must be busy,
especially with the dismissal issue.
What are you talking about?
What could possibly be
more important to me than this?
Are you feeling unwell?
Your complexion is a bit...
I guess I'm just a bit nervous.
Today is a historic day.
It's the day we find out Yeol Mu's gender.
But which would you prefer,
a son or a daughter?
Well...
Honestly, whether it's a boy or a girl,
I just hope the baby looks like you.
What about you?
I'd be happy with either.
I just want the baby to be healthy.
That's my most sincere wish right now.
Ms. Jang Hui Won.
Please come into the exam room.
- Okay.
Let's go.
Hello.
Wow.
Baby clothes are so fancy these days.
Cute, right?
We can't just dress the baby in anything.
Don't worry about the price.
Pick out whatever you want.
For our little Yeol Mu,
I'll give them the best of everything.
So cute.
This is pretty too.
There are so many pretty ones.
This one's really bright.
- How is it?
- It's pretty, but...
All of these?
I'm not done yet.
Could you pack these up for us?
The baby's daddy is already very eager.
What's the baby's gender?
A girl, a daughter.
I can't believe I'm going to be
a girl's dad.
This isn't a dream, is it?
Oh, we found out the baby's gender today.
Congratulations.
And don't we need skincare products too?
They apply smoothly and are made
with baby-friendly ingredients.
You're already going to be a doting dad.
Look here, these are organic products.
They're gentle products good
for babies with sensitive skin.
- And...
- Oh, no need to explain.
We'll take all of these,
and everything on that back row too.
All of these?
Yes.
Yes, all of it.
Yes, I'll prepare them for you.
Okay.
But isn't this a bit too much?
She'll change clothes
two or three times a day.
Our Yeol Mu.
She's beautiful even in the ultrasound photo.
She's truly a little princess.
Oh, pretty.
Are you okay?
Huh? What do you mean?
If anything happens, please tell me anytime.
Our Yeol Mu is ready to listen too.
Like I always say,
just having the two of you by my side
is more than enough for me.
You really can't lean on others.
Oh, right.
That time at the restaurant with Mom.
Thank you.
I never really understood her before,
but looking back, I guess I just
wasn't ready to understand.
I think I was too stuck in the past.
I should've asked her why she said
those things back then.
But thanks to you, President,
I found the courage.
Facing her wasn't such a big deal after all.
But starting is always the hardest part.
Thank you.
I can't let this slide.
I have to say what needs to be said.
How dare she try to bring down our Du Jun?
Oh, just a moment.
Yes, ma'am? How can I help you?
We've met somewhere before, right?
You and me?
- Where?
- Oh, that's right.
That blind date back then.
- Hello.
- Hi.
I'm sorry about that day.
I thought you were Hwang Mi Ran,
whom I met at the massage place here.
I must have been mistaken.
That is me.
Hwang Mi Ran.
But I don't think you're the same person?
Was it someone with the same name?
Well, it could be someone with the same name.
When we talked that day,
I felt myself drawn in
as if it were fate.
Even if it didn't turn into anything,
I was curious about what I felt that day,
so I wanted to see you again.
I see.
But I'm pretty sure it wasn't me.
I haven't had a massage recently.
And don't forget to use
my name when you go in.
Come to think of it, my friend
once got a massage in my place.
Your friend?
Uh, which friend?
Oh my gosh, no way.
No way? Why?
Wow, what a connection.
What, what is it?
You probably know her.
Jang Hui Won.
Jang Hui Won!
You mean the Jang Hui Won
who's seeing our Du Jun?
- Yes.
- Oh, no.
No, no, no.
Oh, what am I gonna do?
Oh, I... Oh, what am I gonna do?
Facing her wasn't such a big deal after all.
But starting is always the hardest part.
Yeah, it's me.
I need you to find someone.
[Health rumors surrounding Taehan Group
Chairman Kang Chan Gil stir market jitters]
Oh, dear. This is...
Is something wrong, Chairman?
It seems like there are many people
who care more about my health than I do.
Wait, was the dismissal vote
for Du Jun next week?
Yes, shouldn't you step in?
Actually, now seems like the perfect time.
It's the ideal time for them
to let their guard down.
CEO Seo Myeong Ho?
What?
Your title changed, but your taste
in food stayed the same.
Don't you remember me?
- Who are you?
- 15 years ago,
you wrote so many articles about me
during your time as a reporter.
15 years ago?
[Taehan Group Heir's Mysterious Fall,
Murder or Accident?]
[Reporter Seo Myung Ho]
Oh my, you've got the wrong person.
CEO Seo Myeong Ho, please have a seat.
You painted me as a murderer
and got a promotion to Deputy Editor
from my sister-in-law and uncle, didn't you?
I'm sorry about that.
I didn't have a choice back then.
I was just following orders.
You drove one person into hell,
and every business
you invested in since has failed.
So after all that, you even
lent your name out?
You must have known that's illegal.
Well, that...
Why? Did the Vice Chairman
promise to cover it up again?
He said he'd protect you?
He already promised.
They're not that generous.
When the investigation started,
they needed someone to pin it on.
They've been operating like that all along.
No, no.
We're on the same team.
He just asked to borrow my name,
said he'd never abandon me.
Please help me!
If I go to jail like this,
my mother will die.
I'll need to think about that.
First,
you need to help me.
[Taehan Liquor in-house contest waiting room]
Hello, I'm Assistant Manager Choi Jong Seo.
The product I'm proposing today is...
- New...
- No, that's...
- My product...
- Next, I'm going to...
Doesn't sound right.
Manager Jang.
Good afternoon.
How was it? Did it grab your attention?
You don't need to lower your voice that much.
I actually prefer your usual voice.
It sounds more trustworthy.
Oh, really? Well, my voice
does sound trustworthy.
Ah, but I'm so nervous.
I'll just go to the restroom
one last time and be right back.
Okay, go ahead.
Yeah, I'll be right back.
[President Kang Du Jun]
Today's the video shoot day, right?
Hui Won, you're always the best,
just do what you do.
I'll be cheering you on.
Yeol Mu, Mommy will do great and be back.
Next, Manager Jang Hui Won. Come in, please.
Yes.
Vice Chairman.
What are you doing?
Have you given it any thought?
Don't try to test me.
You came to me like this
because you don't have any evidence, right?
Well,
maybe you'll think differently
after hearing this.
[Recording of Vice Chairman Kang Moo Young]
All you need to do is write the article.
About that mysterious fall
of the Taehan Group heir.
The murderer who killed his brother.
Was he aiming for management control?
You know, sensational stories like that.
You know what I'm talking about, right?
But Executive Director,
this is a bit risky.
Come on, Reporter Seo.
You're aiming for Deputy Editor, aren't you?
Once this matter is settled,
I'll make you Deputy Editor.
I told you, you won't suffer
any consequences from this.
Here, drink up, drink up.
Oh, my.
- Executive Director.
- Yeah, yeah, here.
I'm counting on you.
It's not even a video, just a recording.
What could it possibly...
The vote is tomorrow.
If you're fired, who's going to believe you?
Do you really think this is my only evidence?
Do you know my sister-in-law
is putting together a new board?
These are the shares she recently
purchased under third-party names.
Including friendly shares
and the ones she just acquired,
her stake now surpasses yours.
[Confidential]
She intended to use you
and discard you from the start.
In the end, she wanted to become
the real power behind Taehan Group.
[Stock acquisition details list]
[Hidden Partners]
Please arrange a meeting
with the directors for this evening.
If the dismissal vote fails,
I won't bring up what happened
15 years ago again.
And that includes the Chairman, of course.
Hello, I'm from PR team.
- I'm Assistant Manager Choi Jong Seo.
- I'm Manager Kim Min Jae from Sales Team.
- The beer I'll be presenting is... Curious?
- I'm not presenting a new flavor of beer.
- If you're curious, don't scream,
- It's a beer that sets a new standard.
just hit the like button.
Hello.
Uh, Taehan Liquor New Product
Development Team's light and salt.
I'm Manager Nah In Nam.
- Salt, what?
- Light and salt!
- My role model.
- I'm Manager Nah In Nam.
Today, I want to share
one very simple yet realistic worry
with all of you.
Yeah!
- Do you drink beer?
- Isn't the action over the top?
For me, beer is, well,
it's a reward given to me.
Nah In Nam, you worked hard
at the company all day today.
And you really did well looking
after the kids when you got home.
That's the signal for
one perfect can of beer!
It's too much.
[Taehan Liquor 1st In-house
Beer Brand Contest Final 7]
But here's the thing.
One more can...
Did you just see that?
But here's the thing.
My voice was no joke, right?
Compared to how seriously you delivered it,
[Nah In Nam's Beer]
the likes and views are pretty underwhelming.
Is this really how you're going to be?
Give me some likes,
boost my views a bit,
and brag about it to your coworkers!
But here's the thing.
Manager Nah, are you
soliciting favors right now?
But here's the thing.
Now that you've said it so bluntly,
I kind of don't feel like
clicking it anymore.
I'm really desperate, you know.
Aren't we one team?
We should stick together.
Alright, let's say we've
all seen Manager Nah's video.
This time, play Manager Jang's.
Mine?
I've been dying to see it.
Me too, I'm really looking forward to it.
I can't wait to see
how you captured the audience.
Hello.
I'm Jang Hui Won
from the New Product Development Team.
[Jang Hui Won, non-alcoholic beer]
What does beer mean to you?
For me, beer was comfort.
- Cheers.
- At the end of a tough day,
when you clink glasses
with the people you love,
it felt like it was telling me,
'You're not alone.'
My mom was always on medication,
yet she could never give up drinking.
When I was young, I couldn't understand it.
If she was sick, why would she drink?
But when I became an adult,
and became a mom myself,
I finally understood.
As things you have to handle alone pile up,
and the things you're
forced to give up increase,
there's a thirst inside
that never quite goes away.
I think my mom felt that way too.
She must have been very lonely and exhausted.
That's when I started to wonder.
Isn't there a way to comfort people,
anytime, anywhere,
in a healthy way?
So I made a decision.
To create non-alcoholic beer.
[Barley]
You gonna try non-alcoholic?
Ah, not just for pregnant women,
but for non-drinkers too.
It'd be great if they could
enjoy beer happily.
'Isn't non-alcoholic beer just a beverage?'
To those who think this way,
I can confidently say
that the beer I'm making is different.
[Market Analysis]
The global non-alcoholic beer market
is growing 8 to 10% annually.
Now's the chance to capture
the emerging market early.
Not only will it have the crispness
and carbonation of a regular lager,
but by using techniques that preserve
the unique flavors and aromas
found in craft beer,
we'll create a non-alcoholic beer
that's tastier than regular beer.
Non-alcoholic beer is no longer
just a substitute for certain situations.
It will become a new trend,
an option of preference
that expands everyone's choices.
When this beer comes out into the world,
I want to drink it first with my mom.
I want to say, 'Let's drink this together
for a long, healthy time,'
as we toast.
Is there someone you want to comfort, too?
I created this beer
to support that warmth.
For my non-alcoholic beer,
please show lots of expectation and interest.
Thank you.
Oh.
I'm seriously about to cry.
It's made so well, really.
Nice, good job.
What did you think?
You worked hard.
[A glass of comforting beer]
Manager, this video's views
and likes are blowing up!
Really?
[A glass of comforting beer]
Huh? Amazing.
Oh.
Thank you.
[Nah In Nam's Beer]
That's way too different from mine.
Tak Soo, did you click it?
Yes, I clicked twice.
So it disappeared.
Hey, click it one more time for me.
Du Jun?
Should I greet you in advance?
I'll make sure to lead Taehan Liquor well,
so please don't worry.
Then, we will now move to the voting stage.
Voting will be done by a show of hands
to confirm approval or disapproval.
First, for those in favor of the motion
to dismiss President Kang Du Jun,
please raise your hands.
Yes, the count is complete.
What are you doing?
Then, for those opposed to the motion
to dismiss President Kang Du Jun,
please raise your hands.
Yes, the count is complete.
The tally results show a majority opposed,
so I declare this dismissal motion rejected.
This is ridiculous!
Kang Du Jun!
What on earth did you do?
What exactly did you say to the directors?
- Please take your seat.
- Yes.
First, here are hospital prescription records
proving I never took illegal drugs.
[Prescription records]
As you can see,
I've never abused drugs
nor received excessive prescriptions.
I reiterate that.
And if you look at the back page,
you'll see a list of bribes you all
received from President Han Jeong Eum.
[Records of external cooperation expenses]
What is this?
I agonized over this quite a bit.
Should I take this to the police?
Then I suddenly became curious.
What would your judgment be
if I showed you this?
I already have evidence of President Han's
bribery, breach of trust, and embezzlement
in my hands.
If this dismissal motion is rejected,
I might overlook all the bribes you received
and the atrocities you committed against me.
So,
what's your decision?
What are you in such a hurry for?
Honestly, I barely restrained myself
from publicly exposing your criminal record
in front of everyone.
What?
Just 4 billion won in fabricated service fees
through paper companies so far.
And you pocketed 2 billion won in rebates
from hotel advertising with RM Entertainment.
[Documents related to slush funds
of CEO Han Jeong Eum]
You bribed reporters to spread
malicious articles about me.
And you gave bribes
and illicit payments to board members.
Oh, about the tabloids, an artist
named Mr. Lee came to see me.
He seemed to hold quite a grudge against you.
You should have treated people better
while you had the chance.
It seems my uncle believed
you could discard him at any moment.
Seeing how meticulously
he took out insurance.
So
step down from the company on your own.
Otherwise,
I'll hand over all this evidence
to the prosecution.
Ah, and,
the CCTV footage you deleted
on the day of the awards ceremony
is being restored through a company,
so look forward to that as well.
Kang Du Jun!
Please leave a message after the beep...
Kang Moo Young.
How dare you stab me in the back?
Mom, stop it.
Let go!
Just stop it!
Wasn't I supposed to be enough for you?
Was it all a lie?
Wait, wait.
Ah, please!
What I want isn't to be
the owner of Taehan Group.
I just want a mom who eats with me,
goes on little dates,
and listens to my worries.
Mom, please!
Your uncle has it.
Your uncle has my documents.
Se Hyeon, could you go and talk to him?
Ask him to get rid of them.
He listens to you, at least.
Stop it, please!
I can't do it.
No, I won't do it.
It was your choice, Mom,
so you take responsibility.
If you go any further,
I'll never see you again.
What?
What are you doing?
- By what authority are you doing this?
- We're from the prosecution.
[Search warrant]
This is a search warrant.
A search warrant? What did I do?
Embezzlement, breach of trust
and suspicion of instigating serious injury.
Who ordered this?
- Kang Du Jun?
- It's the Chairman's order.
[Arrest warrant]
Ms. Han Jeong Eum, this is an arrest warrant.
We'll discuss the details at the station.
Take her in.
Wait a moment.
I'll walk on my own.
Don't touch me.
So that co-president really got fired?
That's what I heard.
And I heard the President wasn't even part
of the contest judging from the start.
It was all the co-president's doing.
Trying to take over the whole company.
Wow.
So even the part about Manager Jang Hui Won
receiving special treatment?
Wow, then what on earth is going on?
I doubted Manager Jang
without knowing the truth.
I kind of feel bad for her.
I'm really sorry.
Let's go.
What? Second place overall?
That's such a shame.
You totally deserved first place.
I'm satisfied.
A second place recognized by the public
is better than a dishonorable first place.
Seriously, you're amazing.
Anyway, I got second place
thanks to you guys,
so I'll treat you to a big meal
when I get the prize money.
Sounds great, okay.
Yeah, bye.
Manager Jang, why are you only coming now?
We've been waiting for a long time.
Manager Jang, congratulations
on second place!
- Ta-da!
- Wow, I got one too!
- Manager Jang, congratulations.
- Congratulations.
Congratulations.
What is all this?
The President sent all this for you.
Ugh, I'm so jealous.
Look at him openly doting on her now.
You're jealous again.
Manager!
Isn't our team totally the ace?
Second and third place both came from us!
Honestly, I feel a bit disappointed
the first place came from the Marketing Team.
Our non-alcoholic and high-proof beers
are way better than
their low-carb one, right?
Exactly.
Even people from other teams
say your idea should've won first place.
Honestly, if it weren't for the limitations
of the non-alcoholic concept,
it would've ranked first
in product viability too.
So close!
In that case,
Team Leader, aren't we having a team dinner?
Team dinner! Team dinner!
Beef! Pork belly!
Chicken! Tuna!
Ah, no. I'll treat you to dinner.
Yes!
Stop, how dare you take out
your card in front of the team leader?
I'll schedule a team dinner this week,
so everyone make sure you stay
on top of your work, got it?
- Okay?
- Okay.
- Then, dismissed.
- Really, congratulations.
- Congratulations.
You worked hard.
It must have been tough fighting alone.
No.
It's all over now.
What about President Han?
She's probably under arrest
and being investigated.
It seems Father also prepared a lot
because of my sister-in-law and uncle.
I see.
I don't feel good about it.
I think you feel the same.
Now that everything is back in place,
just think positively, Hui Won.
For our Yeol Mu.
Is that okay?
But seriously, how long are you
going to keep calling me President?
- What?
- Isn't it about time you get used to it?
And we're about to meet the parents soon too.
Then what should I call you?
Call me oppa.
Try calling me 'Du Jun oppa.'
What? That's weird.
What's weird about it?
They say if there's a four-year age gap,
you don't even need to check compatibility.
Calling me 'oppa' feels natural.
Just try calling me 'oppa' once.
Just give it a try.
O...
Ugh, I can't do it.
Oh, President suits you perfectly.
It's not like I was born President.
Okay, then.
If you don't like 'oppa', then,
there's also 'darling,'
or 'honey.'
Ugh, I've got goosebumps. Look!
Why would that give you goosebumps?
Other people call each other that just fine.
That's...
That's for people who were
natural about it from the start.
No one's natural from the beginning.
You get used to it over time.
Come here, let's get
you used to it gradually.
What if someone sees us?
So what if someone sees?
- Oppa.
- Huh?
- What did you just say?
- Nothing.
I think you said 'oppa'?
No.
Du Jun oppa.
What was that?
- Say it one more time.
- No, no.
Ah, it's warm.
Why are you so shy?
- Dummy.
- Huh?
I think you said something else just now?
No, no.
Ah, it's warm and nice.
I was a bit sensitive last time.
It turns out our bond wasn't
just some casual thing.
Pardon?
In a world where people
only think of themselves,
you truly raised your daughter
well and properly.
I didn't realize what a wonderful
character she has.
She still has much to learn,
so please guide her.
No, not at all.
These days, there's much
to learn from young people.
Hui Won.
Don't think of me as your mother-in-law,
just treat me comfortably.
Just think of it as having another mom.
You speak your mind about everything
even in front of your in-law.
Why?
Because I don't have a daughter.
I intend to think of Hui Won
like my own daughter.
That's alright, right?
Of course, I...
I'm a bit late, aren't I?
I can't even imagine how extravagant
his proposal must have been.
When is the wedding?
- You don't have the ring?
- So you really wouldn't mind
not getting a proposal?
Is the dead son's wife not family?
Everyone in this household will regret it.
No matter what happens,
I will protect you
unconditionally, to the end.
Please, just stop!
If that's family, I don't need you!
Why can't you see that you're
the one who betrayed our family?
Kang Du Jun, this is all your fault.
Because of you!