KING THE LAND
Now.
This is the highlight of the meal.
Are you all right?
Are you hurt?
No.
What will you do with all these?
As long as you aren't hurt,
it's all right.
Do I have…
permission?
Here.
Gosh.
Thank you.
I don't know what this is,
but it's really good.
I wanted to cook the best meal for you.
You already did.
It was the best meal
and the best dining atmosphere of my life.
I'm glad you liked it.
I'll cook for you again.
I'll cook next time.
When?
Tomorrow?
No.
Then when?
When you look the most adorable.
Cheers.
Let's eat.
You must really be good at everything.
Of course.
Though I don't know what this is.
EPISODE 9
We only need 500 more dollars.
We're doomed.
We're closing soon,
and there's not a person in sight.
Ha-neul, should I just buy a bag?
You don't want to face legal issues.
Just go on a trip with those 500 dollars.
But it's only fun if we all go together.
I'll pay for a team trip
if I win the lottery.
You don't even buy tickets.
I will from now on.
You all went through a lot
working overtime.
Let's eat grilled beef intestines.
It's on me.
Let's wrap up now.
- Yes, ma'am.
Yes, ma'am.
Welcome to Alanga!
- Welcome to Alanga!
Please come in!
- This way, please.
- What do you think of this?
It's the latest design.
Thank you.
Thank you. Enjoy your trip.
- Thank you. Enjoy your trip.
A toast to celebrate
Purser Oh Pyeong-hwa's promotion.
- Cheers!
- Congratulations.
Stop it. That's enough.
Why?
Ms. Yoo said the most important criteria
for promotion was in-flight sales.
You had the most sales
and our team came in first.
- There's no doubt about it.
- Of course.
You've been through a lot.
Purser Oh, once you're promoted,
don't forget about us and help us out.
I'll swear my allegiance.
That's enough.
I told you to stop.
Ma'am, over here!
Hello.
What took you so long?
We were so bored without you.
Seems like you were having fun.
You're better off without this old-timer.
Goodness. Why would you say that?
- Sit over here, ma'am.
- Thank you.
- One draft beer, please.
- Coming right up.
You all worked so hard.
Especially the major contributor,
Ms. Oh Pyeong-hwa, who carried our team
from last to first.
Why don't we give her a round of applause?
It's all thanks to you. Thank you.
It's thanks to you all
that our team was able to rank first.
This is a token of my appreciation.
I feel bad receiving this
when everyone worked so hard.
You have every right to receive it.
Treat yourself.
Thank you. I'll use it well.
Now for the highlight of the evening.
I have an important announcement to make.
Someone among us
will be promoted to purser.
Drumroll, please.
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR PROMOTION,
OH PYEONG-HWA
Congratulations on your promotion.
You've worked so hard, Mi-na.
Me?
Here's your purser scarf.
Thank you.
I'll do my best. Thank you.
Purser Hwang, congratulations.
Thank you.
This is amazing.
As expected, it looks good on you.
- Don't bash me
- Saying I'm a cruel woman
- It was for you
That I chose to break up…
I'm sorry.
How can I dare surpass you
when you're my senior by many years?
It's okay.
You don't have to worry about me.
You did a great job. Congratulations.
Cut the nonsense about being okay.
You must be jealous.
If you're jealous,
just say you're jealous.
The nonchalance
makes you look more pathetic.
Stop drinking.
You're drunk.
That's why you should've tried harder.
It's such a happy day for me
but I'm walking on eggshells around you.
You're making me feel sorry for no reason.
What is this?
How uncomfortable.
What are you doing out here in the cold?
You'll catch a cold.
Thanks.
Are you okay?
No.
I'm not.
I feel so embarrassed…
for getting my hopes up.
Pyeong-hwa.
Do you remember what you said before?
"I just like flying."
I did.
And I still do.
I heard that people confuse
what they want to do
with what they want to become.
Wasn't it your dream
to be a part of beautiful flights?
If I become a purser,
wouldn't my flights become more beautiful?
You're already amazing.
I want to become
a good flight attendant like you.
Like me?
Think about everything that's happened.
Look at me right now.
I am looking.
I always have.
You always try your best
to help passengers
have a safe and comfortable flight.
Being the best flight attendant
is much better
than becoming a purser.
Thanks.
It's not that comforting,
but I'll try to cheer up.
Let's walk.
Why did you want to walk today?
Isn't it great today?
The weather's so nice
and I'm in a good mood.
- There need to be days like this.
- How strange.
What is this refreshing smell?
- Did you spray cologne?
- Not "smell."
"Scent."
Scent.
Perfume.
Jeez.
Why do you care?
- Hello, sir.
- Yes, hello.
Mr. Gu.
He's the longest-working employee
at King Hotel.
Thirty years.
- Once you leave, make a left.
- Okay.
He is amazing.
Thirty years?
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Hello.
It's a good morning.
Yes.
It is a good morning.
Today is going to be a good day.
"It's a good morning"?
Don't.
What's this?
Why do you look so happy?
You're mistaken.
No, I'm not. There's definitely something.
Right, Sa-rang?
I'm not sure.
Face forward.
Why are you not sure?
That's strange.
Something's off.
You're grinning from ear to ear.
You look crazy.
Cut the nonsense.
Get off.
- Why aren't you getting off?
- I'll accompany you.
I can go by myself.
I don't want to send you alone.
People can see us.
Then I can just cover our hands.
They can't see now.
Only up to here.
No further.
Fine.
I'm only allowing it this once.
You can't do this next time.
Okay.
I don't think you understood me.
Go inside.
Okay.
He's so cool.
I'm going to work hard today!
He ordered coffee.
What's going on?
Why isn't he leaving?
I think he's here
to observe how hard we're working.
You're right. That's it.
It's giving me chills.
I thought he was better than this.
He's watching again.
He keeps glancing our way.
You're right.
He's here to keep an eye on us.
Sa-rang, go check on him.
- What do you mean?
- Check to see if he needs anything.
Find out why he's acting like that.
Gauge his mood.
- Hurry up.
All right.
Mr. Gu,
is there anything else
I can help you with?
No, I'm fine.
Then why don't you consider leaving now?
I don't want to.
Everyone finds it uncomfortable
to see you sitting here.
Don't mind me. Just continue working.
Well…
How are we supposed to do that
when you're sitting here like this?
- I have a meeting here later.
- What time?
At 5 p.m.
It's 2 p.m. right now.
Hurry up and leave.
- I'll leave in a bit.
- Can you just leave now?
Come on. It's because I want to see you.
Mr. Gu!
We are at work right now.
- You need to leave.
- But…
Did you have to get so serious?
No one can work properly because of you,
including me.
Fine.
After just one more cup.
You already had three.
I think it'd be best for you to leave now.
Hurry.
Is that what you want?
Yes.
I beg you.
"Beg"?
Okay.
I'll disappear as you wish.
VEGAN RESTAURANTS
MUST-EAT RESTAURANTS NEAR NAMSAN
MUST-EAT RESTAURANTS NEAR GWANGHWAMUN
"Thank you"
must be an expression
to use at times like this.
Don't mention it.
Thank yourself
for your great service skills.
- You're the best.
- That's true.
But what was that notebook earlier?
It had the restaurants'
most popular dishes,
their locations, and notes about
the employees' foreign language skills.
When I worked in the lobby,
a lot of foreign guests
asked for restaurant recommendations.
I created the list by touring
good restaurants on my days off.
Mad respect.
You're the best talent for a reason.
I'm seeing you in a new light.
Attention to detail is important
in customer service.
I'll leave this here.
You can look at it whenever you need to.
Is that okay?
You're giving away
your efforts and know-how.
What's wrong with that?
Our team will be using it.
We're all one family.
Is the 100th-anniversary event preparation
going smoothly?
Yes, everything's going smoothly.
Can you elaborate?
This isn't just any event.
King Hotel is the root of King Group.
This year, we're honoring
the past 100 years of the group's history,
as well as presenting our new vision.
I know.
We also need to invite public officials,
but you haven't reached out to them yet.
They're not the type of people
to come on short notice.
Hwa-ran is right about that.
You need finesse when approaching
people who work for the government.
Your sister has that network
in her pocket.
Ask her for help.
You entrusted me with it.
I can handle it.
You haven't even gotten anything done.
King the Land is hosting this event.
So everything is up to me.
No, it's a matter of the hotel.
King Hotel's capabilities
are to be displayed through this event.
You're right.
The entire hotel needs to be involved.
Then from now on,
I will take charge of the hotel.
Your sister is in charge
of King Air and Distribution,
so you can manage the hotel.
However,
you have to show me
what you're capable of.
Once the 100th-anniversary event is over,
let's talk again.
Mr. Gu, would you like some more coffee?
Absolutely not.
I need to have a word with you.
I thought you didn't want to
talk to me at work.
By any chance,
are you upset?
As if.
I'm not that petty.
Please. You're sulking.
What are you saying?
I'm just trying
not to mix business with pleasure.
As you asked.
Goodness.
I had no choice but to do that earlier.
Please. You begged me to leave.
Come on. Don't sulk over that.
Stop.
Don't be upset.
I mean…
- That's not--
- Forget it.
- But--
- I'll make sure
not to mix business with pleasure either.
I understand what you mean.
- But--
- Let's talk again next time.
But…
Can you do that one more time?
This is bad.
Mr. Gu!
- You're the--
- Get out.
You're the best. You're the man.
That is who you are.
What are you saying?
I heard you finally declared war
against Ms. Gu.
"I will take charge of the hotel."
You're so cool.
You're awesome. Good job.
This is just the start.
I will be at the forefront.
What? Why do you look so depressed?
You were over the moon earlier.
Why are you down in the dumps now?
What is it?
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
I don't think so.
Are you scared after drawing your sword?
It's nothing like that.
Then is it a relationship problem?
Do you need my advice?
- This is about someone I know.
- Okay.
He argued with his girlfriend at work.
The reason being his girlfriend told him
to stay away from her at work.
So the man got a little upset.
- Yes.
- But what I don't understand
is that when the girlfriend
hugged him from behind
to cheer him up,
the guy shuddered.
He actually loved it
but pushed her away
because he was startled.
Why did he get startled? What an idiot.
He must know nothing about dating.
I do know!
Leave for the day.
At this rate, you could end up
losing everything to Mr. Gu.
Mr. Gu's greatest weapon
should not be taken lightly.
What weapon?
The fact that he's his son.
I received an urgent message from the US.
They said they couldn't reach you.
Later.
It seems it's something urgent
regarding your son, Ji-hu.
Did you not hear me?
Understood, ma'am.
Are you worried, Mr. Choi?
Yes, slightly.
Do you not trust me?
It's not that.
Then,
why are you worried?
King Group was mine from the start.
And it's going to stay that way.
I'm not going to let Won have any of it.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Send invitations
to the people on our side.
Are you thinking of helping Mr. Gu?
Why would I help him?
Won may be in charge of the event,
but it's going to be
full of people on my side.
Won will be in charge in name only.
Do you understand?
I'm here, ma'am.
Goodness gracious.
What brings you all the way here?
Well…
Oh dear.
Be careful!
Goodness.
GENERAL MEDICAL CENTER
Jeez, it's fine.
Please lie down.
Why did you bring me to the hospital
over something like this?
You must have money to burn.
You could've been in big trouble.
The cartilage has degenerated
in both of your knees.
How have you been walking all this time?
With my two legs. How else?
It's normal for my joints
to act up at this age.
It'd be weirder if they were healthy.
Get out of my way. I'm leaving.
- Didn't you hear what the doctor said?
- What?
The doctor suggested getting
knee injections while you're here.
And considering your age,
they wanted to run a few more tests.
What about my restaurant?
I'll take care of it.
Goodness.
You talk big for a guy
who can't even peel onions.
Jeez.
Ma'am,
no matter what you say,
until you receive injection treatment
and run all of your tests,
you can't leave this hospital.
I'll do what I can with your restaurant.
All you have to do
is take care of your health.
What?
How dare you glare at me?
Look at you.
I thought you were a sluggard,
but you're quite agile.
Gosh.
Why did you come all the way here anyway?
Well…
I just dropped in while I was passing by.
You dropped in all the way from Seoul?
I saw some flowers
and I thought of you.
You should be thinking of
a woman you love.
Why did you think of me?
There must be something going on
between you and Sa-rang.
How did you know?
I can just tell.
It's written all over your face.
You have feelings for Sa-rang, don't you?
Yes, I like Sa-rang.
Then did you ask her out?
Do I have to put it into words
when we both know we like each other?
Come over here.
You can just tell me--
Come over here!
The thing is,
even if you feel
an emotional connection with someone,
if you don't express
how you sincerely feel,
it's likely they won't know.
It's the same whether things are good
or bad in your relationship.
If something made you upset,
just swallow your pride
and tell each other what made you upset.
You also have to listen with your heart.
That is how you should love one another.
Do you understand?
Yes.
I'll keep that in mind.
Okay. Here.
First things first.
Sign up to be a candidate.
A candidate for what?
You'll be candidate number one
for Sa-rang's husband.
I'll make a decision
after considering a few others.
But ma'am…
Grandma.
Grandma, are you okay?
I'm fine. This is nothing.
How bad is it? Where does it hurt?
- Are you in a lot of pain?
- Goodness.
I told you I'm fine. It's okay.
Why, you little…
You're so impatient.
I can't believe you told her already.
What are you going to do
with that big mouth of yours?
You've been admitted,
so I had to contact your guardian.
What? You're out.
I disapprove.
You get out of my way too.
- I'm getting up.
- Where are you going?
I need to run my restaurant.
Who cares about the restaurant right now?
I told you to stop working.
I make money now.
It's okay. I'm totally fine.
Are you going to keep worrying me?
Do you know how I felt on my way here?
Please.
Didn't I tell you to let me know
when you're sick
or going through a tough time?
I can't live without you.
How am I supposed to live without you too?
Okay. All right.
It's okay. Don't cry.
I'll get all the treatments
and tests done,
and I won't leave
until the doctor tells me I can.
So stop crying. There, there.
You promised to live longer than me.
Stop it. I'm not dying.
Where would I go without you?
I won't go anywhere.
So stop crying. Okay?
There, there.
Don't worry.
She'll be okay.
Her fall wasn't that bad.
Thank you.
You can go first.
I'll take care of the rest.
Let's do it together.
No, it's okay. I can just take a taxi.
I promised your grandmother
to take you home safely.
Let's do it together.
Don't we just have to
switch out the lightbulb?
No. We first need to
completely cut off the electricity
to ensure our safety.
Have you done this before?
Of course not.
Then I'll just do it.
No.
I'll do it.
Just trust me.
- This…
- What did you do?
All I did was place my finger there,
but all of a sudden…
Wait. Do you have your phone?
- Hold on.
- Where is it? Turn on the flashlight.
My phone is…
in my car.
- I put mine over there too.
- Hang on a second.
- Which way is the exit?
- What do I do?
- Okay, then let's…
- Where…
Wait…
- Should we go this way?
- I need to go that way.
- Okay. I'll go.
- No, it's not that way.
- Wait. Hold on.
- Gosh.
I'm sorry. Are you okay?
- Are you hurt?
- Freeze.
Just stay still right here.
All right?
All right.
- But--
- Don't.
Fine.
What?
Where are you?
Are you okay? Did you get hurt?
Where are you? Where in the world are you?
- Right here.
- Oh my god!
It's okay.
- I'm not okay.
- What's wrong with you?
Come on.
Why are you always fainting?
Get up. Seriously.
You should go back now.
Is that what you really want?
I want to stay with you.
Is it just me?
No.
I feel the same way.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
I can be so clueless sometimes.
I guess
I made a fuss
because it felt like
you didn't miss me or like me back.
Sorry for making you feel uncomfortable.
I'm also sorry for snapping at you.
I could've been more gentle,
but I was worried about what
the others would think,
so I was on edge.
No.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
If I ever make a mistake again,
you can sulk all you want.
I'll handle it.
Even if it may take a while,
I'll make sure to cheer you up.
So when you're with me,
don't suppress your emotions.
Just be yourself.
Come to think of it,
I don't think
I've ever expressed how I truly feel.
I like you a lot.
Will you accept my feelings?
But do we have to stay
this far away from each other?
This is my grandma's room.
I know that.
But…
You're so far away.
I can barely hear you.
Hello?
Can you hear me?
Do you want to go to Seoul this instant
or do you want to sleep outside?
Really?
You're so adamant.
We have to get up early tomorrow to prep.
We only have three hours before then,
so go to sleep.
Fine.
- What was that?
- Let's sleep.
Hurry up and go to sleep.
It's our second time.
What do you mean?
Sleeping in the same room.
Last time, there were two rooms.
You were so snappy then.
You were such a jerk then.
Even though I kept
giving you the death stare,
on the inside,
I was thinking, "What?"
"Why do I like her?"
"Why does she look cute?"
Really.
Come to think of it,
I liked everything about you
from the start.
Thank you for liking everything about me.
I'll always be next to you.
I'll always be in your line of sight.
I'll always be
within arm's reach.
Now I can see you clearly.
Let's sleep.
This isn't…
- Hey, you punk!
- Don't get the wrong idea, ma'am.
I swear I didn't do anything.
What? You didn't do anything?
Yes, I swear. I only held her hand, ma'am.
Why you little…
- You punk.
- Why?
- You idiot.
- What did I do?
- You idiot. You call yourself a man?
- What?
Are you a man, you punk?
- Grandma.
- You just held her hand?
Darn you.
You're not going to the hospital?
Why would I go back there
when I finished all of my treatments?
Then where are you going?
I'll be back soon.
You should peel the onions
and get the fire ready.
- Let's go.
- Yes, ma'am.
You're taking him too?
What's going on?
- Hurry up.
- Yes, ma'am.
Where are you going?
Ms. Cha!
Drink one of these.
Who is this?
Your grandson-in-law?
Don't be absurd.
He's just one of the men
who chase after Sa-rang.
A candidate.
I see.
You're so handsome.
That's the least he can do
to be in Sa-rang's league.
She's on another level.
You're right.
- Drink this.
- I'm okay.
It's my treat. Just drink it.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
Sun-hui!
I heard you went to the hospital.
Have one of these for a swift recovery.
Okay.
Who is he?
- Her grandson-in-law?
- No.
He's just one of the many men
who chase after Sa-rang.
He's just a candidate.
So?
How long have you chased after Sa-rang?
- Well--
- By the way, do you have a job?
- Yes, I--
- He works at the same hotel as Sa-rang.
King Hotel.
The best hotel in the country.
It costs several hundred thousand won
for one night.
No matter how great the hotel is,
it's still just a huge inn.
My grandson-in-law
works for a major company in Seoul.
Goodness.
A hotel is almost a major company.
But do you own a house?
I don't feel the need to yet.
Goodness.
I can't believe I'm hearing someone say
they don't need a house.
It's not easy to buy a house in Seoul.
He can take his time.
Why are you worried about his house?
It's okay.
My grandson-in-law bought a house.
He's only paid off half the mortgage.
You're all chatting again?
Aren't you going to work?
- Eat it with this.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
- Hey, my daughter-in-law.
- Yes?
- More radish kimchi, please.
Okay. Radish kimchi.
Where did they go?
What do you like about Sa-rang?
Just everything.
There's nothing I dislike about her.
Do you know how long Sa-rang lived here?
She used to live here?
Since when?
I ask the questions.
You just answer.
Yes, ma'am.
What's Sa-rang's favorite food?
She doesn't like raw fish.
Did I ask you what she doesn't like?
I asked you what she likes.
I will find out one by one.
If you like her,
you should first find out
what kind of life she's lived
and what kind of person she is.
How can you just declare you like her
when you don't know anything about her?
You don't pass as Sa-rang's partner.
Get up.
YANGGIL BANK
- Hello, ma'am.
- Yes.
This must be the man
who's been chasing after Sa-rang, right?
Your potential grandson-in-law.
Yes, that's me.
Ms. Cha is a hard nut to crack.
You're in for a rough ride.
What can I help you with?
Another savings account?
A housing subscription account.
Really? Why?
You already have a house.
It's not for me. It's for him.
This is for the first month.
Starting next month,
you make the deposits.
You're already taking care of
your grandson-in-law.
You're so loving, ma'am.
Grandson-in-law, my foot.
He's just a candidate.
Is this your first time at a bank?
Your ID.
Right. Yes, ma'am.
Here you go.
Please wait here. I'll make a quick copy.
Thank you, ma'am.
I'll save a lot of money.
You don't need a house right now.
You and Sa-rang
can work hard and save money.
Don't let something like that
get you down.
Just work hard
and live a good life. Okay?
Then are you finally
giving me your approval?
Didn't you hear me?
You're no good.
You don't pass.
Wow, what's all this?
Is this a feast?
I just prepared the usual dishes
with not much effort.
Eat up.
Thank you.
Grandma's food is the best.
- So don't be sick.
- Okay.
Hey, eat this first.
I asked them to give me their best cut.
But I'm not sure
if it'll be tender and juicy.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Here. You should try it too.
It's amazing.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
- You should have some too.
- Okay, I will.
It's so good.
Please eat.
Okay.
She told me I was the number one candidate
for grandson-in-law.
Is that why she cooked for you?
How odd.
By the way,
what's your favorite food?
Maybe spring rolls?
That's it?
What do you mean?
Spring rolls are amazing.
- What about you?
- I'll go with spring rolls too.
- What?
- I mean,
you're the person I like.
So I like what you like.
Let's go eat them sometime.
Okay.
Should we take one more lap?
I think we've taken over ten laps already.
Then…
we can just make it 20.
I'll allow it.
Let's go.
Sa-rang!
Where are you coming from?
What's up?
Goodness. Mr. No.
Mr. No?
It's really him.
What is all of this?
I'm going to drink like a fish tonight.
She can't survive right now
without drinking.
Why? Did something happen?
You know what an incentive trip is, right?
We reached our goal
after working our butts off for a month.
But they sent us on a day trip to Bali.
A day trip to Bali?
Yes.
I just got back.
Hey!
You ruined my hair.
Good grief.
I'm sorry.
Do you want to check these?
There's nothing special about Bali.
With a beach and a palm tree,
we're basically there.
YOU BETTER BALI-VE IT
So you're saying we can't go?
Yes, that's right.
This time, we can settle for this.
We'll go to Thailand next time.
You said we'd go to Southeast Asia
if we reached 30%.
We worked our butts off
without any bathroom breaks.
Tell me about it.
Next time, I'll do whatever it takes
to get you girls a trip to Thailand.
So let's increase the sales a little more.
Ms. Do.
We came somewhere nice.
Don't ruin the mood.
Let's talk about good things only.
I've been to Bali before.
It's identical to this place.
It's a waste of time to fly there!
Hey.
The special effects.
Is this good?
- Yes.
- Keep smiling.
Nice. Wonderful.
- You look like Lee Hyo-ri.
- Me?
That's the worst.
She's so evil.
She's just like my supervisor.
What did your supervisor do?
She promised to make Pyeong-hwa a purser
if she increased sales,
so she made her team first.
But instead,
she promoted Pyeong-hwa's junior,
her favorite.
She wouldn't have worked to the point of
hurting her back had she known.
Are in-flight sales
that important for becoming a purser?
They bring in a lot of money
thanks to their high profit margin.
The company keeps pushing us.
If your team doesn't reach
its monthly sales target,
you'll get a poor performance rating.
Are there any incentives
for selling a lot?
No, there aren't.
If I do well, it's a given.
If I do poorly,
I get on my superiors' bad side.
What do you expect from King Group?
Even Sa-rang was chosen
as the best talent for two years straight,
but all she was given was
a smiley face badge.
Hold on.
You were chosen as the best talent
for two consecutive years,
but all you got was a badge?
Since it was two years, I got two badges.
I wasn't expecting anything, so it's okay.
It's not okay.
You always say that with everything.
What can I do if it's not okay?
So the best talent only got a badge.
Da-eul, even after reaching your goal,
you weren't given the trip
you were promised.
Pyeong-hwa, you were promised a promotion
if your team came in first,
but someone else got it.
It's my fault for being so naive.
Why in the world…
The company should recognize
and reward its employees.
Also, a superior not keeping their word?
How does it make sense
for a superior to break their promise?
It does.
The higher-ups only look up.
They don't care about us.
If things go well, it's thanks to them.
If not, it's our fault.
Why is that your fault?
All three of you are not at fault.
The fault lies in the company
and your superiors for tricking you.
We cannot let this slide.
I'll do whatever it takes
and take responsibility to amend this.
- Wait.
- Won't it be difficult for you
to do much as a manager?
I know, right?
If he were a department manager…
That's hard too.
He needs to be a head manager at least.
Hey, didn't you hear what Sa-rang said?
She said her head manager
was a total jerk.
He goes to work for fun.
He wouldn't care about us lowlings.
Right, Sa-rang?
No.
No. He's not a jerk anymore.
He's a really nice person.
Hey, get your head straight.
As is the king, so are the subjects.
If he were a good person,
we wouldn't be suffering like this.
Right, Mr. No?
I think he's all right.
Someone like Mr. No
should be the head manager.
You're right.
Okay. May Mr. No become the head manager!
It doesn't matter who does it.
If you work this hard for the company,
the company should also treat you well.
I don't even expect that much.
I just want to be appreciated
for the work that I do.
Why do we have to wish for something
that should already be given?
We deserve what we deserve.
Anyway, it is an honor.
The best employee at King Air,
King Distribution,
and King Hotel.
I'm with the best employees
of King Group right now.
Like I said,
you should be the head manager, Mr. No.
If you run for the position,
I'll vote for you.
It's Mr. No.
- It's Mr. No.
Since you guys are rooting for me,
I can't sit still.
Order everything you want to eat tonight.
On behalf of the company, I…
As a manager,
I'll pay for everything!
Mr. No!
"Gang Da-eul, Oh Pyeong-hwa,
Cheon Sa-rang"?
The kind Ms. Sa-rang?
What is this?
The number one employees
of King Distribution, Air, and Hotel.
They are King Group's best employees.
Prepare an overseas trip
as their incentive.
The remaining employees
will be sent in turn.
Why are you so concerned
about the employees' incentive trips?
The company should reward them
for their performance.
Isn't that a given?
I've never seen
such an openhanded company.
There's one right here.
- Ms. Gu's approval is needed, right?
- No.
I'm making all the decisions
about the hotel.
With employees from Distribution and Air,
it's the group's issue.
- Will you be okay?
- You may proceed.
I'll take responsibility.
They are our group's best employees,
so it needs to be the finest
and most luxurious experience.
Me?
"A nice trip"?
WE'LL REWARD YOU WITH A NICE TRIP
What?
"Ms. Oh Pyeong-hwa, thank you
for your devotion and hard work."
"We'll reward you with a nice trip."
Congratulations.
The best staff of the group
are being given incentive trips.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
They're leaving tomorrow.
Is everything ready?
Of course.
They will experience
the best trip of their lives.
You'll be shocked.
Get in, sir.
What? You've never done this before.
No, this is what I usually do
as King Group's best assistant.
You know that, right?
- Are you sick?
- No, I'm perfectly fine.
I'll drive you home safely.
I'm so excited.
- I'm so happy!
- Hey!
Oh my. Mr. No!
You're here.
This is all thanks to you.
I didn't do anything.
We're going on this trip
because you told the higher-ups.
You'll be blessed.
Thank you so much.
For this trip,
let's forget about everything
and make this a happy, exciting,
and comfortable trip.
Let's go relax.
- Okay!
Let's go then.
I'm so happy.
What should we eat first?
That's a good question.
Head…
Manager!
Be quiet.
- Who is he?
- Someone he knows?
Why are you here?
This is a trip
for King Group's best employees.
I'm the best assistant.
I get what you're saying.
I'll send you on a trip next time. So go--
That's ridiculous. I need to assist you.
Assist me with what?
- Just leave.
- Who are you?
- Hi, Sa-rang.
- Hello.
- It is an honor to finally meet
- He works at the hotel.
the people who were on the papers.
Let me introduce myself. I'm--
He is
the man behind this incentive trip,
Department Manager Yoo Sang-sik.
What are you talking about?
Let's introduce ourselves again.
This is Mr. Yoo Sang-sik.
He's a department manager.
And I'm
Mr. No.
Thank you, Mr. Yoo.
Mr. Yoo, thank you.
Mr. Yoo Sang-sik,
thank you.
Mr. Yoo,
I will guide them from start to finish,
- so you may…
- Will you move, Mr. No?
- What?
- "What?"
- Pardon?
- Yes, "pardon."
I'm a department manager.
You're just a manager.
So can you go over there?
Let me introduce myself again properly.
I am the department manager
in charge of this trip,
No… I mean, Yoo Sang-sik.
It's nice to meet you.
The concept of this trip is "We go hard."
When we eat, go hard.
When we have fun, go hard.
- All together…
- We go hard!
You're so energetic.
But Mr. No,
why do you have your mouth shut?
Just act like I'm not here, please.
Unity is key for this trip.
Individual activities are not allowed.
We'll set off after shouting our chant.
- When we eat…
- Go hard!
- When we have fun…
- All together, we go hard!
- We go hard!
Okay. Let's go!
Why aren't you coming?
I'm not letting Mr. No get away with this.
I thought he was Mr. Yoo.
His enthusiasm is nice. Let's go.
Mr. No!
- Hurry up!
Okay. Coming.
I'm coming.
Mr. No, let's go!
KING THE LAND
Go hard!
- Go hard!
Let me announce today's schedule.
What about free time?
There's no free time on a group tour.
- Let's get out of here.
- Now?
Now.
A trip?
How could something in King Group
be carried out without my knowledge?
But I keep wanting more.
I feel so happy that I begin to wonder
if I'm allowed this much happiness.
I keep hoping that
I'll continue to be this happy.
I'll make every day of yours
filled with happiness.
Subtitle translation by: Stephanie Jung