I haven’t fallen in love yet.
You cooked for me?
Sam seems to be
in a good mood today.
What is this?
It’s just food.
Hey, you’re smiling
from ear to ear.
Cy said he thinks that
he’s already
fallen in love with me.
That’s perfect!
You’re falling in love
with each other.
What do you want?
I want to showcase clothes.
Redefine beauty and...
tell stories through fashion
on a global stage.
I want to be
an international model.
Modeling?
Politics is more impactful.
You’re really
a great older sister.
Thank you.
You’re really
a beautiful person, Maui.
I love you.
You mean that?
I love you, too.
Let’s go home?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Oh my.
Didn’t we agree to sleep
in the same room
once we’re official?
Maui, once we’re
officially together,
are we going to sleep
in the master’s bedroom?
Yeah, if you want.
I’d want to.
So, are we sleeping
together tonight?
Wait.
We said I love you
to each other.
Does this mean we're official?
But what if those 3 words
don’t mean the same thing for
him as they mean to me?
I better ask him
to define the relationship.
Hey! Are we...
Are we official now?
Are we like
a boyfriend-girlfriend thing?
Cy, hi! Are we a couple now?
Hey!
Hey, are we like, a boyfriend-
girlfriend thing now?
Shit.
Cy, I want to ask you if
we’re officially a couple now?
Are we like a boyfriend-
girlfriend thing already?
Shit. This is so embarrassing.
Okay.
Hey…
- Hey.
- Hey!
Can I...
Wait, before you say anything,
I know where this is going.
I know you want to ask me if
we’re officially a couple,
and I’m wondering
the same thing.
We already said
I love you to each other,
and I don’t take it lightly.
So,
I think
we’re officially together.
That means we can sleep
in the master’s bedroom
together tonight.
That's what we’ve
talked about, right?
I want to stick to our agreement
unless you don’t want to...
Sam, can I borrow
my phone charger?
Yeah.
It’s in my bag.
I’ll get it.
Hey.
I agree with everything
that you said.
Yes, we’re officially together
and yes...
I will sleep in the master’s
bedroom with you.
Okay?
Okay.
Good, I’ll see you there.
I’ll see you downstairs.
Shit.
It’s really happening!
Seriously?
We’re in the same bed
for the first time ever,
and he’s just going
to study beside me?
You're still going
to study at this hour?
Hm?
You're still going
to study at this hour?
Yes, I have an exam on Monday.
I see.
What time will you finish?
In a while.
Calm down, Sam.
Nothing spicy has
to happen tonight.
There’s still tomorrow.
But it’s a shame,
tonight is our first night
together officially.
You smell nice.
You even have a lip tint on.
This is my natural lip color.
Really?
Let me check.
I need to study.
Wait.
Is this your first time?
Don’t tell me you don't know
what to do with boobs?
Sam, I’m studying.
Just go to sleep.
He’s so adorable.
Okay.
After you’re done studying,
at least cuddle with me.
Good morning, Maui.
Good morning.
Do you need help?
Yeah, sure. I'm just
drying Summer off.
Hello!
- Here.
- Are you refreshed, huh?
Let’s go here.
- Here, here.
- Come here.
You’re so cute!
Here, too.
Sorry.
But why...
Maui!
I forgot.
This guy has been keeping his
hot body to himself this whole time!
But well, technically,
he’s mine now.
So...
Thank you, Lord,
for the blessing, I guess?
What?
You like what you see?
No, I don’t!
You don’t have to lie.
It’s okay to admit
you’re attracted to me.
So arrogant!
Wait.
I’ll just check my phone.
Okay.
You sprayed too much.
Hi, Sam.
Just wondering
when is your next visit?
I’m just asking though,
no pressure.
Hey, why are you smiling?
Naomi messaged me.
You should pay her a visit.
I’m pretty sure she misses you.
You think so?
Yeah.
I’ll cook food for you guys.
So you'll have something to
bring when you visit her.
Thank you, Cy.
You’re welcome.
And fine.
I’ll admit that
I’m attracted to you.
Go ahead, eat.
Have some more.
Let’s add this to your plate.
You know what,
Cy prepared this for you.
Sam, it’s my first time having
food made especially for me.
Thank you, Sam.
And to that scary guy, too.
I can’t believe he cooks.
Scary guy?
You think Cy’s scary?
I can’t blame you, though.
He looks so grumpy,
that’s why I thought
he was mean and
intimidating at first.
Grumpy?
- Yeah. He looks like—
- How grumpy?
He looks like that.
All the time?
How?
Scrunched up face, huh?
Yeah.
But I know he’s kind.
He even taught me how to use the
light settings of the camera.
He even encouraged me
to continue photography.
He likes my photos.
He did?
Yeah, that time he came up to
my room to call me for dinner.
He caught me using
your camera. So yeah,
he ended up teaching me
how to use it properly.
I didn’t know he actually
talked to Naomi.
But that’s such
a Clyden thing to do.
Sam, I’m so happy
he’s your fiancé.
You guys look so good together.
And Sam, thank you for the gift.
You're welcome.
Have you tried using it?
How is it?
I’m still learning
how to use it.
Do you have time?
Can I take photos of you?
Yeah. Sure.
Of course!
You don’t even have to ask me.
Don’t worry, I always
have time for you.
But...
can you do my makeup?
I’m not that good
at doing my makeup.
Not as good as you.
I only know the basics.
Really? But...
your natural makeup
looks good, though.
You think so?
I know so!
Thank you.
But, sure. Let’s do
our makeup, Sam.
Yes.
- After this.
- Okay.
Eat some more.
Okay, thanks.
If you want dessert, tell me?
We can ask someone to buy some.
How is it? Is it good?
Is it okay?
Yeah, it’s good. It’s tender.
I’ll tell him.
Sam, close them.
- Close your eyes.
- Okay.
Make sure it’s aligned, okay?
Hold on, okay?
Trust the process.
Wow!
You’re amazing.
Where did you learn
how to do makeup?
Makeup tutorial videos.
And sometimes
I use your makeup.
Sam, I’m sorry. I’ve been
using it without telling you.
Please, it’s okay.
I didn’t even notice since
I don’t really use it anyway.
You can keep them.
You know what, Sam?
You could totally be a model.
Really? You think so?
Yes.
And I’ll study photography
so I can be the one
to shoot your portfolio.
I’ll take your word for it.
- Yes.
- Deal?
- Promise?
Okay, promise.
- I promise.
- Okay.
Now, continue.
Okay, wait.
Next time, Sam,
let’s try baking.
I’m craving brownies!
Sure! The next time I come here,
I’ll bring baking ingredients.
Okay, I'll look forward to it.
Wait. You also want to go
to a photography workshop?
I can get you a slot.
Really?
I’ll see what I can do.
Thanks, Sam.
Idiot!
What do you mean
the money’s missing?
How could it just go missing?
If you don’t have
the money by tomorrow,
you’re the one paying for it.
Stupid.
I’ll go to my room, Sam.
Yeah. See you soon, Naomi.
Sam?
You’re still here?
I’m on my way out, Mom.
Who were you talking to?
No one, just some incompetent
employee of mine.
Okay.
I’ll go ahead.
Take care, dear.
I’m home!
Hey!
Hi, Sam!
Ridge!
We’ve met last time, hi!
Yes, sir.
Sorry, he just barged in here.
Wow!
Are you saying I’m being
a bother here or something?
Big time.
Jerk.
Hey, your makeup looks great.
Really?
- Yeah.
- Naomi did this.
We did a photoshoot
earlier to test her camera,
the one I gave her.
You didn’t tell me
that you gave her
some camera lessons.
Thank you.
And about the food,
she said you didn’t seem like
someone who could cook,
but she liked it.
Sorry, wait a sec.
I swallowed the whole chip.
I’m sorry.
It tasted like loneliness.
Too bad you didn’t choke on it.
How about I strangle you.
Are you still not done?
Why this asshole...
I’m sorry, Lord.
It’s obvious you’re trying
to get rid of me already.
Well, good thing you’re
finally picking up on it.
Jerk.
I missed you.
Well, well, well!
You’re really such a flirt.
You know, you were
exactly like this
back when we
were at the condo of...
Of?
This hand’s really nice, huh?
Oh wait, it’s my hand.
Such a pretty hand.
You said you never dated anyone.
Yes, I never did.
Huh?
No one.
But you were flirting
with someone?
Is she one of the girls
you kissed back in college?
Yes.
Yes? That’s it?
He’s not even going
to elaborate or explain?
What? Hey.
All right. Cool.
I’m heading downstairs, okay?
You guys continue
what you’re doing.
Ridge, I’ll see you later.
Sam!
I’ll just treat you to
some tapsilog later, okay?
I’m sorry.
You’re totally going
to hell, I’m telling you.
Bro, seriously?
You really brought that up?
I said I’m sorry.
Why do I feel mad about it?
It’s in the past, Sam!
Just let it go.
I know he kissed
a total of three girls,
but
how often did he kiss them?
Is he a good kisser because
he’s had so much practice?
You’re not sleeping here?
Alessandra,
Leanne,
Eva.
Those were the girls
I kissed back in college.
It was nothing serious.
I’m sorry.
Maui, please talk to me.
Eva?
You kissed your friend?
I told you it was only a dare.
It was my freshman year,
I was stupid.
That was my dumbest year.
And the girls you flirted with?
Leanne, freshman year.
Alessandra, sophomore year.
But all of those were just dares.
You seriously
get dared that often?
I told you I don't date,
nor do I show
any interest in dating.
And now? What changed?
You happened.
You’re the only one
I want to marry.
Okay.
We better stop...
- for now - But, wait.
But you were hard.
So, you were looking at it?
Anyways,
I have to study.
You have to sleep,
and I’ll prepare breakfast first
thing in the morning, okay?
Goodnight.
But...
If you end up with blue balls,
that’s on you!
I know I need to be patient,
but this is killing me!
Sorry, I woke up late.
I even said
I’d cook you breakfast.
I’ll make it up to you.
Hey, it’s okay.
You’re always
the one cooking anyway.
But
if you really want,
I know a way for you
to make it up to me.
Right now?
Yes.
All I need is your hand.
Just my hand?
I’m talking about this!
You’re not following me
back on my socials.
I even followed you.
Wait...
What were you thinking?
Nothing.
What are you assuming?
Happy?
Good.
I sent my follow request
a long time ago,
and you just
wouldn’t follow me back.
Actually, I followed you
a while ago,
but then I unfollowed you
right after.
Huh? Why?
I got annoyed with
your story, you were with...
that Sevi guy.
You’re so petty!
Wife?
We’re not married yet.
We will be.
So we’re not breaking
the engagement?
We’re not breaking
the engagement.
Whatever happens,
I promise you that.
Okay.
Stop.
Let’s eat breakfast now.
Okay. I’ll bring these
to the table.
Okay.
Hey, Sam! What’s your plan
for your birthday?
Same club as last time?
Yeah, I plan to host it
in a club in BGC.
You guys save the date, okay?
When did we ever miss out
on your parties, Sam?
Yanna can’t go, though.
I’ll cover for Yanna.
I’ll try, Sam, okay?
We’re in season right now.
We still have training.
It’s okay, Sevi.
Don’t invite him, please.
Don’t please.
Luna, if Kalix finds out
you’re invited,
for sure, he won’t go.
That’s good then.
You’re so bitter.
Wow.
Just because you…
You’re so annoying.
How about Arkin?
Via, where’s Arkin?
Huh?
I don’t know.
He probably has a shoot?
Ask Sevi.
How would I know?
Last time I saw him,
he was at the gym.
That’s why you shouldn’t steal
other people’s best friends.
You can’t steal something if
someone’s paying
attention to it.
Right, Luna?
Wow, Sevi.
You’re such an asshole.
That’s why no one’s
flirting with you.
Because you’ve got
such a bad attitude, Sevi!
Are you sure
no one’s flirting with me?
Yuck. Gross.
Can we kick him out
or something?
How about you, Sam?
Introducing us to someone
special on your birthday?
Huh? I'm not aware.
Is there someone?
She’s not answering!
Oh, my god! Spill the tea, sis.
Spill the tea.
Oh my gosh, she’s blushing!
I’m home!
Cy?
Are you on your way home?
I bought dinner for us!
Maui, sorry.
Go ahead and eat first.
We’re still studying at a cafe.
Okay. Don’t forget to eat, okay?
Good luck with your studies.
I wonder if he’s on his
way home. Has he eaten?
Hey, sorry I think we
might be here until morning.
Don’t wait for me, okay?
Good night. I love you.
You take care, okay?
Make sure to eat a proper meal,
not just coffee. I love you.
Good morning.
Morning. Sit down, let’s eat.
This looks so good.
Thank you.
What time did you get home?
Around seven?
And you even cooked
breakfast for me?
Yes, because
it’s been so long since
I’ve made food for you.
Even your lunch.
I’m sorry.
Hey, I told you it’s okay, Cy.
I know it’s not easy
on your part since
you're already
preparing for clerkship.
That’s why I’m here
to support you.
You know what,
I’ll take care of the cooking.
I can cook as good
as you, you know?
Maybe pasta, sure.
But when it comes
to other meals...
my cooking is still better.
Really? You just won’t
back down, huh?
Hey…
I missed you.
Are you free today?
Do you want to go
grocery shopping?
And then let’s eat out after.
I would love to,
but you haven’t slept yet.
No, it’s okay. Just give me
1 to 2 hours to sleep,
and then we can go.
Okay then, it’s a date.
Okay.
You bought so many ingredients.
What are you and Naomi baking?
We’re making brownies.
Are you baking too?
Why’d you buy so
many baking ingredients?
No, I’m making a different dish.
But I’ll cook it
for you next time.
That’s a lot of messages.
Is it for your org?
No,
I was sending invites
for my party,
so the guests were RSVPing.
Wait. Do you want to come?
It’s next week, Saturday.
Saturday?
I wonder if he knows
that it’s my birthday.
Should I mention it?
I can’t.
I’m going to
the hospital with Ridge,
and then we’ll study afterward.
We have two major
exams on Monday.
I’m sorry.
Never mind. He might
feel guilty about it.
It’s okay! Your exams
are more important.
Sam, I like this apron.
We should take a picture!
I’m glad you liked it.
- Wait…
- I ordered these online.
They almost didn’t
make it in time, though.
- Okay.
Let’s go.
Okay, that’s so cute.
How’s school lately, Naomi?
Same, same.
My classes are relatively easy
since I’m still a freshman.
I see. That’s good.
Did you really
wanna take Pol Sci?
I thought I wanted it, but...
I guess I just wanted
to impress Dad and
get validation from him.
I’m sorry.
I hope you learn to enjoy
your classes eventually.
I hope so, too.
Remember, I’m proud
of you as it is,
and you don’t have to
do anything more, okay?
Thank you, Sam.
As long as we’re okay,
all is fine.
I’m done with
the wet ingredients.
Want to mix it?
- Here.
- Okay.
Thanks.
This is pretty hard, Sam.
Let me help you.
Just don’t overmix it,
or else we’ll end up
with stone-hard brownies.
Yeah, just mix it.
Okay.
Sam, it’s your birthday
tomorrow, right?
Yes, you remembered.
Of course!
You know what,
I have a party at BGC.
Do you want to come?
I want to introduce you
to my friends.
I-
I don’t think I’m ready
to go out and party
after what happened
to my own birthday.
But I appreciate you for wanting
to introduce me to your friends.
Hey, it’s okay.
We’ll just have a separate
birthday celebration.
You, me, and Cy,
since he won’t be
able to attend either.
He won’t? Why?
Med school stuff. But it’s okay.
He doesn’t know
that it’s my birthday.
Of course, he knows!
He’s your fiance!
Maybe he’s just saying
that to surprise you.
Who knows, maybe he’s planning
a birthday surprise
for you tonight.
She’s right.
Cy might actually
surprise me later!
- Let me handle that.
- Okay.
Sam?
Happy Birthday!
For me?
Yeah,
of course!
I...
I compiled all our photos.
Really?
Oh my god, Naomi!
This is beautiful. I love it.
I’ll treasure this.
Thank you so much!
You know what, I’m so happy
that we’re okay now.
Whatever happens,
your big sister’s here
for you, okay?
I know, Sam. I know.
Thank you.
- Okay.
I’ll mix this now.
Okay. Continue that.
I’ll just put this...
Who knows, maybe he’s planning
a birthday surprise
for you tonight.
Oh my god. Wait.
What if this is the surprise?
Hey, are you still out?
What time are you coming home?
Yup. Coffee shop.
Might be home past midnight.
I’m still studying.
Past midnight. So he won’t be
here to welcome my birthday?
But what if he’s planning to
surprise me exactly at midnight?
I fell asleep! What time is it?
Hey, Maui. I might
stay over at Ridge’s place.
We’re not done yet. I’m sorry.
Good night. I love you.
No birthday surprise.
No birthday greeting.
Does he really not know
it’s my birthday?
Hello.
Happy birthday!
Happy Birthday to you,
happy birthday to you...
happy birthday,
happy birthday...
happy birthday, you crazy bitch!
Thanks.
How cold.
Why do you look unhappy?
It’s because of Clyden.
I think he doesn’t know
it’s my birthday today.
What’s the problem with that?
Then just tell him.
But shouldn’t he already know?
I mean, we’re a couple.
Even I know
when his birthday is.
You’re just annoyed
‘cause he hasn’t
gotten down on you yet.
Well, you have a point.
All right, just enjoy
your day, okay?
Maybe Clyden actually has
something planned for you.
If not, then go ahead
and get mad at him.
It’s totally valid
to feel a little upset.
Just tell him
he can make it up
to you with his body.
- Just like that.
- Yanna!
Okay, happy birthday. Bye!
- Love you.
- Bye!
Hi babies! Want to eat?
Okay.
Here you go.
Wow.
Go Summer, eat.
I’ll take a photo.
Smile! Cute!
Look. I already fed our babies!
Cute.
Thanks, Maui.
That’s it?
Just a thank you?
No happy birthday?
Summer, why are you not eating?
Eat already. Here.
Do I look okay?
Okay? Sam, you look gorgeous!
Really?
How’s my makeup?
I did the eyeshadow
technique you taught me.
It’s beautiful.
Enjoy the night, Sam.
Happy birthday!
Thank you, Naomi.
Bye!
The day’s almost over,
and he still hasn’t greeted me.
At this point, I’m not
expecting anything anymore.
Hey, do you even know
it’s my birthday today?
It’s useless.
Thank you guys for coming,
enjoy the party!
- Thank you.
- Yeah!
Welcome!
Hi!
Are you guys okay there?
- Sam!
- Shan! You’re here!
Of course! Happy birthday.
Thank you.
You didn’t have to,
but thank you.
You can put it there.
Sure.
And they’ve already
started serving drinks,
I know you want that.
Nice.
That’s really what
I came for, drinks!
I know, right?
- I’ll see you later.
- Enjoy.
Happy Birthday!
Luna!
Sevirous can’t make it,
so it's just going
to be Ke and Via.
It’s okay.
Happy birthday!
Thank you.
- Happy birthday!
- Thank you, girls.
Thank you for coming.
Kalix is not here. Don’t worry.
It’s not like
I’m looking for him.
Not looking ‘cause
you don’t want to see him,
or because you do want to?
I said I’m not looking for him!
So? Are you introducing
someone to us?
I wouldn’t want
to waste my outfit.
I love this song!
Girls, let's dance!
Come on! Hurry, let’s dance!
Okay, fine!
Come on, come on.
We’ll get to that later.
Happy Birthday!
Thank you.
Enjoy the night!
Girls, I’ll just get us
some shots, okay?
- Okay.
Stay here. I’ll be back.
Sorry, excuse me.
There. Some shots. Thank you.
Sam.
- Hey.
- Happy Birthday!
Lewis! Thank you. Glad you
could make it tonight.
Yeah. I need a break
from training.
Good thing,
Adi’s been, you know,
raving about your parties.
I wonder what other
stuff Adi said to you.
He said you throw
the best parties out here.
So you know, I had to check.
Although he did warn me that
I might get a little
too drunk tonight.
Yeah.
Wait. There’s a...
There’s something in your...
- What?
- An eyelash.
Let me just…
Thank you.
I’ll just go back to my friends.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, sure.
- I’ll just get back to Adi.
- Yeah.
I’ll see you later, okay?
Bye. Enjoy.
Hey!
Hello?
I’m not leaving.
What are you doing here?
Go back in there.
It’s your birthday, right?
So, you know it’s my birthday?
How could I not?
I spent the whole day looking
for a nice gift for you
only to see you having fun
with some other guy.
Wait. Is that him?
The football player slash...
what? Environmentalist?
Is that him?
I’m not having fun
with another guy.
We were just talking.
And he saw something
stuck on my face,
he took it out,
that’s it. It’s nothing.
I’m the one who
should be mad right now
because you
didn’t even greet me!
I was waiting the
whole day, but nothing.
I felt really bad.
I’m sorry.
I really wanted
to greet you in person.
I spent the whole night studying
so that I could show up
to your birthday party.
But it looks like
my plan kind of backfired.
I’m really sorry, Maui.
It’s okay, you’re here now.
Is it okay to do it here?
It’s tinted.
Is something going
to happen tonight?
Wait, is she trying
to seduce me?
Shit.
I think she is.
Should I give in?
All right Cy, let’s do it.
We're finally almost done,
this is crazy.
We can finally sleep, bro.
Nope.
- Are you heading home?
- I still have somewhere to go.
Right! That's why you're
in such a hurry.
Sam’s birthday?
Yeah.
I hope you already
have a gift for her.
You've been playing hard to get
all day with your future wife.
I do have one.
Oh heck yeah!
Hey!
Hope Sam likes it.
Come on, open it already.
Fuck! Sorry, Lord.
Damn, bro. That’s beautiful.
- Is that for real?
- Of course.
But why a ring?
Don’t you guys already have one?
Bro, that was a gift
from our parents.
I want something with
sentimental value for us.
I want to propose
to her properly, Ridge.
You son of a—
Wow, love is so sweet.
You’re an expert now, Clyden?
- Duh.
- Let’s go.
You two are so cute, I hope
you guys never break up.
You’re the only
good thing in this world.
What really
makes Christmas special
is the people you spend it with.
You probably know me already,
so I won’t bother
introducing myself.
Do you think there’s
pain there, Sam?
It’s a ruthless world
out there, Maui.
Then what do you want me to do?
Should I just follow
everything you say then?
You’re the one who
fucked up your own life.
Manners, please.
Just in case anything
happens to us...
you need Clyden.
You really miss him, huh?
Of course.
We’ve just been busy with
school, but we still make time.
They loved your portfolio!
They’re gonna sign you.
Wait! What?
I’m tired.