♪Shrugging off past burdens♪
♪Beneath the mask, who am I?♪
♪Release and find wider shores♪
♪Love's a riddle, and rain pours heavy♪
♪Crossed paths, now downward fall♪
♪From dust arises starlight's spark♪
♪Tearing through
the night's dense blockade♪
♪Heart's flame illuminates all solitude♪
♪Let time's sails drift endlessly♪
♪Through wandering exile♪
♪Breaking free from the cocoon,
I start anew♪
♪Moon as song, life as flame♪
♪Nameless heart clings fiercely♪
♪Let me♪
♪Charge toward the next raging river♪
♪Moon darts, snow falls♪
♪We tread rugged paths to reunite♪
♪Hands held tight♪
♪We forever live for love's sake♪
♪Shadow's spear burns fiercely♪
=Legend of The Female General=
=Episode 14=
I'm just puzzled
why you haven't joined the Xiao Army.
You're not young anymore.
Retiring from battle
is understandable.
I'm no deserter.
(Xiao)
This was my son's dagger.
I was indeed once
a member of the Xiao Army.
But Xiao Zhongwu
caused my only son's tragic death,
and my wife died of grief.
I swore before their memorial tablets
that I'd make the Xiao family
suffer complete ruin.
So you've been tracking the Xiao Army.
Exactly.
The son shall pay for
the father's debts.
I followed from Yaojing to Que City
to seek revenge against Xiao Jue.
But I never
found the right opportunity.
Perhaps
you'll get your chance soon.
His greatest value lies in
his knowledge of Xiao Jue
and the Xiao Army.
As for Lei Hou,
he makes a convenient weapon.
Rida Muzi and Hu Yuanzhong,
these Liehe men are ambitious wolves
(Strong Strength)
with strong military forces.
I leaked information about them
to him.
He didn't disappoint me.
He made Lei Hou
collaborate with the Liehe tribe
to attack the garrison.
A good utilization.
Who is this person?
His name is Chai Anxi.
He was once Xiao Zhongwu's deputy.
Wasn't he supposed to be dead?
Apart from the Xiao Army matters,
what else did he mention?
Did he say anything about Mingshui?
This man's resurrection
is quite suspicious.
Don't get yourself
involved in this mess.
Thank you for the reminder.
Chai Anxi and I
only met once.
I soon returned to the capital.
Later, we communicated by letters
until Lei Hou's defeat.
Our contact stopped.
Is that all?
I won't
conceal anything.
Forget it.
Clean up this mess.
Whether it's Lei Hou
or Chai Anxi,
eliminate them both.
As you command.
But the clues
about Chai Anxi and Lei Hou
point to Xiao Jue.
Seems I'll have to go
to Yezhou Garrison.
What pretext will you use?
Commander Xiao fought this battle well.
He deserves rewards.
I underestimated Xiao Jue.
He's more cunning than imagined.
Also,
prepare two corpses
similar in build
to Lei Hou.
Since I promised Master,
I must do it.
Understood.
Master's wording suggests
he's clearly wary of Chai Anxi.
Likely
Chai Anxi
has dirt on Master.
I'm curious
what kind of secret
this could be.
(Xiao)
Commander.
Are you available now?
Enter.
Commander.
It's repaired?
I said I'd thank you.
Are you sure it's thanks,
not an apology?
They're basically the same.
When you have time,
you can test its tone.
Then I'll go train now.
I heard
he spent the pay he saved
over these months on this qin.
- The envoy!
- Wait!
- Hurry!
Sir.
Chu Zhao.
Commander
Xiao Jue
is an expert trainer
and performed well against Liehe.
I'm pleased to grant him
a large sum of money
as a mark of honor.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
You must be weary from your journey.
I've arranged quarters for you.
Let Feinu
take you there.
Thank you.
Please take
my maidservant there first.
Earlier, I encountered an acquaintance.
I want to see him.
Then
I'll leave you to it.
Mr. Chu, you're too generous.
You came here.
It should be
my duty to play host.
I hope this simple meal
suits your taste.
Please.
Mr. He.
Thank you.
Word reached
the capital that a Yezhou recruit
crushed Liehe's spirit.
I knew
it must be you,
so I took this assignment
to visit you.
By the way,
I heard you suffered severe injuries.
How are you now?
Thank you for your concern.
I'm strong.
I'm fine now.
Mr. Chu,
you came from the capital.
Have there been
any interesting things
lately in the capital?
Interesting things?
Mr. Chu?
What is it?
Nothing.
Mr. He,
what kind of things
are you referring to?
Mr. Chu,
I hear
there's someone in the capital
as renowned as the Commander,
General Feihong.
Tell me,
what kind of person
is General Feihong?
You ask the wrong person.
I live in the capital,
but I'm a civil official.
I'm not acquainted
with him.
Then has anything unusual
occurred recently
in the general's house?
Unusual?
General Feihong stopped
wearing his mask,
revealing his true face.
He's peerless in martial arts,
and he is also
strikingly handsome.
Of course.
The stature
of our young master
is more imposing.
It's just the Mingshui Battle
weakened him,
forcing him to recuperate at home
and decline visitors
and keeping him
from greater feats.
Get out!
Rufei.
Why this outburst?
She's already dead.
Why does she still haunt me?
I am clearly He Rufei.
I am the true General Feihong.
General Feihong
is truly loyal and devoted.
He's a good brother.
He often visits
the Yuhua Temple to light
eternal lamps for his dead sister.
How loyal and devoted
General Feihong is.
Mr. He, why are you so interested
in General Feihong?
He is a role model for our generation,
so I admire him.
Though you serve under Commander Xiao,
you admire General Feihong.
Don't you think
Commander Xiao might feel displeased
if he knows?
Our commander
is magnanimous.
Then let me toast you
with this wine.
Mr. He.
Yeah.
Huaijin,
where did
Miss He go?
She's drinking with Chu Zhao.
You know it?
I didn't expect you to care so much
about Miss He.
Listen, Huaijin,
that's Chu Zhao!
Aren't you worried at all?
Is he that awesome?
Although Chu Zhao
serves under Xu Jingfu,
objectively speaking,
he's truly talented
and gentlemanly.
Miss He
usually encounters burly men
in the military camp.
Though someone is decent-looking,
he is
expressionless all day.
In my opinion,
Miss He might
get snatched away
by that heartthrob Chu Zhao.
What?
Going to see Miss He?
Don't block my light.
Fine, fine.
Keep pretending to be indifferent.
Mr. Chu.
Yeah.
People say
blood ties
are the hardest to sever.
Do you think
that's true?
If that's true,
why do we
even have
a story like Cain and Abel?
(Mother,)
(I learned a new song.)
Let me sing it for you.
Little birds fly,
streams giggle,
- fish chase...
- Who let you in?
Father.
I finished my studies.
Today is Mother's birthday.
I just wanted to celebrate her.
As the He family's eldest son,
don't indulge in feminine affairs.
Have you memorized
the Virtue chapter?
A nobleman's virtue
requires utmost sincerity,
righteousness,
and...
Recite like this
and claim your studies are done?
Useless!
Mr. He,
this song should be light and cheerful,
but your rendition
sounds so sorrowful.
You've heard this song, too?
Long ago,
my mother often hummed it.
My poor execution
fails to capture
its carefree essence.
Mr. Chu, cheers.
Let's drink.
Come on.
Let's keep drinking.
Mr. He.
He...
You were born free-spirited.
Why do you say such despondent words?
If something troubles you,
I'll be here to listen.
Mr. Chu.
Why would you say that?
I...
He Yan.
I am He Yan.
I was born
to roam free in vast seas
and soar across endless skies.
No longer confined by cages.
Come on.
Mr. Chu.
I hear
near Yezhou Garrison
lies Mount Baiyue.
Its scenery is breathtaking.
Come on!
Let's drink wine together
while admiring the moon.
Mr. He.
Let's go.
You're drunk.
Let's go back.
Mount Baiyue
won't go anywhere.
Mr. Chu.
I'm not drunk.
Come on!
Mr. He.
Commander Xiao.
Perfect timing.
Mr. He and I are going
to Mount Baiyue
to drink in the moonlight.
Care to join us?
Right.
To Mount Baiyue.
I...
Mr. Chu, if you want,
you may go alone.
I'll take He Yan
back to sober up.
Where are we going?
I want to go
to Mount Baiyue for a drink.
Put me down.
This...
Where am I?
Let me go!
I want to see the moon at Mount Baiyue!
Not drunk yet. I can still drink.
Mr. Chu.
Come on.
Drink.
Here, drink up.
You and Chu Zhao get along well.
Right.
I...
I want to see the moon.
More wine here.
Uncle,
I knew you'd go to snatch her away.
This...
Give me.
Huaijin,
you can't even
pull her away
when she's drunk?
Is it her injuries
holding you back?
You don't let me drink
because I can't recite
the Virtue chapter?
Father.
I can recite it.
Father?
How exciting!
What did you call me?
A nobleman's virtue
requires utmost sincerity,
righteousness,
and compassion.
Cultivate your virtue
before your character.
Virtue enlightens the mind.
Then set your purpose,
unshaken by external things.
How's that?
Father, I'm good, right?
First time seeing
a woman
calling you father.
What's it feel like?
Your daughter
recites texts well.
Quite clever indeed.
- If I...
- Shut up.
Father, you told me to shut up
because I didn't recite it well enough?
I'm not your father.
Father,
you want to disown me?
I've been working so hard.
I've never brought
shame to our family.
Father.
It seems when Miss He was at home,
her father was extremely strict.
That's why even when drunk,
she still craves her father's praise.
If you ask me,
just praise her already, Huaijin.
Better yet,
give her a reward.
A reward?
Father,
other classmates get rewards
after being praised.
Do I?
What reward do you want?
Not this.
Give me.
Why so harsh?
Don't scare Miss He.
By the way,
she's got good taste.
She immediately picked
your most treasured thing.
Have you seen enough?
Don't. I'm here.
Miss He,
do you like this pendant?
Yes.
Then do you like Chu Zhao?
Chu Zhao...
Cheng Lisu.
I'm doing this for your sake.
Miss He,
another question.
Do you like Xiao Jue?
Cheng Lisu!
Fine. Got it.
I'll shut up.
I'm leaving.
You... seize your chance.
Yes.
You like...
what?
Medicine.
Waist?
Has Lei Hou been
found?
Our scouts recently reported
the two
headed towards Que City.
Probably returning to Wutuo.
Recall the scouts.
No need to follow.
Also,
send back
the two corpses
as proof of completion.
Tell Master
the Lei brothers are dead.
Young Master,
will he believe this?
The Lei brothers
are just expendable pawns.
Master won't care.
Chai Anxi
is the real priority.
But Chai Anxi cut contact himself,
meaning he intends to hide.
Tracking him down
might take considerable time.
Xiao Jue must be investigating this too.
We can hardly
outpace him.
Why not let it be?
If we closely watch Xiao Jue,
we'll find Chai Anxi eventually.
If Xiao Jue
finds Chai Anxi first,
we'll lose the initiative.
But Xiao Jue's position
limits his freedom of action.
We can seize opportunities
and find Chai Anxi before he does.
What about Miss He?
Should we watch her?
She's close to Xiao Jue
and likely knows a lot.
No need.
She's invited me
to drink in Mount Baiyue.
I'll try
to get information out of her.
Enter.
You're awake?
You reek of alcohol.
Here.
I
prepared hangover soup for you.
Thank you.
Seems you are
fond of this jade pendant.
Still clutching it now.
Mr. Cheng,
I didn't do anything inappropriate
last night, did I?
Of course not.
You behaved well.
You just let Huaijin
experience
how it feels to be a father
and have a good daughter
at such a young age.
Father.
I'm not your father.
You remember now?
Hold it tight.
This is the reward
after you recited
the Virtue chapter.
Reward?
I snatched this, didn't I?
Miss He,
you're amazing.
After all these years,
this is the first time
I've seen him
in such a state.
Having
his most precious thing taken
and having to hold the bag.
His most precious thing?
Don't tell me
I actually
took liberties with him?
Of course not.
What's wrong with you?
Huaijin is...
I'm talking about this pendant.
This jade pendant
was originally black and white,
part of my grandaunt's dowry.
Later,
she had it split into two pieces
and gave the white piece
to his elder brother
and the black one to Huaijin.
I've heard
his brother's piece
is now with his sister-in-law.
Then Huaijin's piece...
Oh no, oh no.
Last time,
I destroyed his qin.
This time, I took
his future wife's pendant.
I must return it!
Your soup!
You eat it!
I'm doing good things
without seeking glory.
Morning, Commander.
Commander.
Are you attending to
your duties?
Get to the point.
Yeah.
Commander,
last night,
I was drunk. Completely wasted.
So
everything I said
was pure nonsense.
I shouldn't call you father
or take your belongings.
Commander,
please be magnanimous
and spare me this time.
You're like my second parent.
No.
I mean
your grace rebuilds my life.
Commander,
Mr. Chu has come.
Let him in.
Drink less.
You're part
of the battalion.
Calling me like that
is bad enough.
Don't lose face
in front of others.
Yeah.
Commander Xiao.
Mr. He.
Mr. Chu.
What brings
you here?
I came for Mr. He.
I couldn't find him
in his quarters.
Then I heard he was with you,
so I came to visit.
I never thought
you were the impatient type.
After all, Mr. He and I go way back.
Is that so?
You're here for me, Mr. Chu?
Yes.
After hearing you describe Mount Baiyue,
I became quite enamored.
Pity our plan fell through last night.
Will you have time tonight
to go there with me?
No problem.
Commander.
I'll take my leave now.
We found Chai Anxi.
Traces of Chai Anxi
were found in Jiyang.
Yingxiang.
Pack up.
Let's depart now.
We'll kill him before Xiao Jue
arrives.
Understood.
Young Master.
Are you writing to Chancellor Xu?
No.
This is for Miss He.
I need to write her
an apology
for breaking my word.
Shall I send someone
to Mount Baiyue
to deliver it to her
in case she waits?
I'll hand this letter to Xiao Jue
when I bid him farewell
for delivery.
Are you testing Xiao Jue's reactions?
Xiao Jue
knows Miss He's true identity
but helps conceal it.
Perhaps he harbors feelings for her.
Calling me like that
is bad enough.
Don't lose face in front of
others.
I've already tested him.
Our abrupt departure
will raise Xiao Jue's doubts.
This letter
will keep him occupied.
It may
(To He Yan)
buy us some time.
I knew he had
ulterior motives.
A decree delivery?
Actually he was probing
for Xu Jingfu.
Now, he must've heard something,
going to Jiyang overnight.
This is
within my expectations.
As a military officer,
without imperial orders
or urgent matters,
I can't just leave.
Moreover,
our family has some history
with Princess Mengji.
We must act cautiously.
Luckily, Jiyang,
though under Wei's rule,
operates autonomously.
With Princess Mengji holding power,
outsiders
without connections
find themselves constrained.
He won't locate Chai Anxi quickly.
Feinu,
hurry up and arrange
the identity change.
Yes.
- Feinu.
- Mr. Cheng.
Huaijin.
I just saw Chu Zhao leave.
He's supposed
to meet Miss He today, isn't he?
He definitely
hasn't made it to the meeting yet.
Huaijin.
This is a good opportunity.
If Miss He
truly has feelings for him,
and now he broke their plan...
Miss He
is still a girl after all.
She is delicate and sensitive.
Now,
she needs companionship.
If you offer her gentle consolation,
you'll surely win her favor.
She wants to see Chu Zhao.
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪I've seen the mountains♪
♪And trodden through ice♪
♪Day after day, I venture alone♪
♪Destiny is my creed♪
♪Ideals surge beneath the surface♪
♪Igniting the flame against the winds♪
♪A restless yearning in my soul♪
♪Gazing through the mire♪
♪Who cares about this boundless void♪
♪Charge ahead with blazing fervor♪
♪Stubbornly fighting with my life♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪