(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
CHARACTERS, EVENTS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND PLACES IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
Mr. Park.
Mr. Park, did you see…
I can't reach him.
He took his car and left
after 2:00 a.m. last night.
He has a bad fever.
He's not in a state to drive right now.
Then I should call the police--
Seonu Chan!
- Ben.
- Is he here?
I haven't been able to reach him.
Why? Is something wrong?
He sent an email to the headquarters
saying he'll quit.
What?
I can't get in touch with him,
and they said he even deleted
his email account already.
He must have vanished on purpose.
Goodness.
He's been planning it
for a long time.
He said he wanted to be with you
through spring, summer, fall, and winter.
He said he'd explain everything soon.
But it looks like
it's broken beyond repair.
He was hesitant
because his memories weren't fully intact.
And he was worried that
acting rashly would only hurt you.
He was going through a hard time too,
but his mind was only focused on you.
But it seems like
he missed several chances to tell you.
There was that issue
with your grandma too.
I…
made him leave.
You don't have to look at me
or listen to me.
Please, just look at this.
So please…
No exceptions.
Don't let anyone in my office.
Don't ever show up in front of me again.
You just pushed me back into winter again.
I should have listened to him at least.
What do I do?
Regardless of whose roommate
he was seven years ago,
what secrets he hid…
or what he did wrong,
I really can't hate him.
I'm only visiting.
I came from Boston.
:cue
END OF TRIAL
A three-month trial!
As soon as the three months is over,
I'll disappear without a trace.
I'm not someone who will leave
in three months,
nor someone who might never come back.
Ms. Song.
No, Haran. I want to stay with you.
I'm going to use that trial
for the rest of my life.
When did he come here?
Where did you go, Seonu Chan?
Then that accident…
Yes. It was all because of you.
You caused the accident,
and it killed Hyeokchan.
He…
disappeared.
The Seonu Chan I know
would never just leave like that.
I'm sure there must be a reason.
But I didn't even give him
a chance to talk.
So I'm regretting it.
You, he, and Hyeokchan knew each other
in Boston, right?
Yes.
His disappearance
seems to be connected
to what happened seven years ago.
What happened back then?
Please tell me.
I have to know.
I'm sorry.
Seven years ago,
I did something bad to you.
I met Hyeokchan for the first time
at a hospital.
He and I were both waiting for a surgery.
He was pretty stressed back then
because he couldn't reach you often.
What time is it?
I missed his calls again.
Did you download it?
Can you see my message?
Yes, I can see it!
You kept missing my calls,
so I thought we could at least
send each other messages on our laptops.
I'm going to bed now. Love you.
Oh, no…
The silk georgette…
- Haran, the draping fabric.
-  Coming.
Sorry, I'm in a bit of a hurry.
I'll call you back later. Sorry.
You shouldn't be smoking.
None of your business.
Are you Korean?
Let's meet up and chat from time to time.
We're both lonely students here.
We were the same age,
and we were both lonely students
studying abroad.
So we grew close quickly.
You were the only one
who could bring this.
But I didn't have your number,
so I asked the T.A.
Sorry for the hassle.
My number.
Call me if you need anything.
Not too often, though.
:cue
Sorry.
I heard
he wasn't close with his roommate,
but he asked Seonu Chan for a favor,
and that's when I first met him.
- Who's that? Your friend?
- No, just my roommate.
We developed feelings
for each other as we grew close.
We kept seeing each other
after we were discharged.
That's when Hyeokchan
started making excuses
and asking his roommate for favors.
He canceled his plans to go to Korea
and went traveling with me
during vacation,
but he accidentally took
his roommate's laptop instead.
And during that one month,
I think Seonu Chan was chatting
with you
on Hyeokchan's laptop.
Hyeokchan had already made up his mind
to break up with you.
I'm sorry, but the reason was me.
Seonu Chan didn't start it intentionally.
It was Hyeokchan's mistake,
and he asked him to message you.
Did you have fun
chatting with me like that?
Did you build some kind of fantasy
and start liking me?
Even though I knew about you,
I wanted Hyeokchan.
I'm sorry.
All right.
Seonu Chan…
disappeared because of me.
If his bleeding
was caused by the shrapnel,
it may be accompanied
by neurological symptoms
such as auditory or visual hallucinations.
There have even been reports
of memory distortion
in severe cases like this.
Memory distortion?
His memories are distorted?
I had no idea
he'd been suffering so much
from the explosion back then.
He told me never to tell you
about Hyeokchan and me,
but I thought I should tell you.
I get that about Hyeokchan,
but what do you mean?
Why did he disappear--
I did something…
I shouldn't have done,
as a person and as a doctor.
Your passport? Why?
I'm going to Boston to meet Chan,
since we have four days off.
What? Really?
You seem different these days.
What? Why?
Just a while back,
you didn't seem that into him.
Was that a month ago?
What's this sudden burst of affection?
I don't know, either.
When we were together,
I didn't notice him much,
but I feel like I can see him clearer
when I'm chatting with him
without seeing or hearing him.
I can tell how much he understands me
and how well we click.
Maybe it's because of this pen.
What do I do?
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
:cue
Mr. Yeon.
I'm going to the factory.
I'm meeting Mr. Chae
in front of the factory at 4:00 p.m.
I heard it's in Gangwon-do Province.
It's pretty far, so drive safely.
But what happened to your keychain?
Oh, I'm taking the company car
since it's far away.
Ah. Sorry, I can't come with you.
No need to apologize for that.
I know you're insanely busy
with Ms. Kim absent.
I'll see you later, then.
It's going to take so long.
I have to cheer him up.
Smile.
Huh?
"Kim."
YOUGYUM
Why isn't he picking up?
Yang Changmo.
Do you know where Yougyum is?
He's taking his stuff
out of his locker.
He says he's quitting baseball.
- What?
- He said
he won't be able to become
a pro athlete anyway.
CHA YOUGYUM
In 2007,
Park Jisung got knee surgery
and returned to Manchester United
after nine months.
He made it
to the Champions League semifinals.
In 2025,
Shohei Ohtani returned
from two elbow surgeries
and threw even faster than before,
rewriting his Major League career records.
And in 2015,
Ryu Hyunjin…
had a shoulder tear…
Shoulder tear…
Hadam, stop.
That's enough.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry,
but I can't make it.
Those athletes
took much longer to recover than expected.
But they returned stronger.
You don't have to play baseball.
And you don't have to join
the Major League.
But…
if you give up now
without trying until the end,
all you can do later…
is regret it.
Let's try everything we can until the end.
You can give up then.
Until you find something else
you want to do,
I'll take care of you, so--
I'm scared.
I'm scared I'll turn out to be nothing
even after I try.
Then,
you can be the Cha Yougyum
who at least tried his best until the end.
You can be that.
Then you won't turn out to be nothing.
You helped me stay strong
when I was having a rough time.
So it's my turn to help you stand back up.
Even if you give up baseball,
I won't let go of your hand.
I'll stay with you until the end.
So let's not…
run away from this.
I'll give it a try.
We can cry later if I still can't do it.
But right now,
let's try this.
REPORTER CHAE HYUNWOO
- Yes, Mr. Chae.
-  Hey.
We rescheduled the factory visit
to next Wednesday.
Can you join us then?
What are you talking about?
Ms. Song just left for Yeongwol.
:cue
Huh? I left her a message
saying it got canceled.
We can't enter
because of a blizzard warning.
MR. YEON
Hello, this is Song Hayeong's phone
that she leaves lying around every day.
Chae Hyunwoo.
You should've checked
to see if she got the message.
Send me the address.
I'm sorry.
Something urgent came up,
so I have to postpone the meeting.
I'm really sorry.
I can't believe this.
What is this?
Huh?
This is driving me crazy.
You can't enter
because of the heavy snow.
You have to head back, all right?
Hang on.
Excuse me.
You can't enter. Excuse me!
Sir! Wait!
My car won't start,
and I don't even have my phone.
It's so cold.
You can't fall asleep,
Song Hayeong.
Am I going to die here?
Well…
I've lived a happy life.
I was so stupid.
Ms. Song Hayeong.
Ms. Song!
Why am I hallucinating Mr. Yeon's voice
in a moment like this?
Huh?
Mr. Yeon?
Ms. Song.
Are you all right?
Is that really you, Mr. Yeon?
Yes, it's me.
Everything's okay now.
I'll call a car service right away.
Just a moment.
Wow.
I'm fine, so take this…
No.
Keep it on.
Don't make me get the wrong idea again.
You would've rushed over
even if it were Haran or Hadam, right?
I'm not sure.
What?
I think I was wrong.
What…
I think I do see you…
as more than a colleague.
I told myself I couldn't dare to,
since you're Ms. Kim's granddaughter.
So I guess I turned away from my feelings.
How could I not be attracted
to someone like you?
I know it's pretty late,
but if you're really okay
with someone like me…
would it be all right
for me to like you?
:cue
Gosh…
Let's clean up this place
so Chan can return anytime.
Yes?
Ms. Song, there's a delivery for you.
Have you been well?
It took a while,
but I put it together.
Restoration begins the moment
you decide to put it back together.
It may take a while,
but as long as you don't give up,
the pieces will come together in the end,
and those pieces
will contain a deeper story
compared to before.
I learned through this job
that miracles begin by not giving up.
If there is anything you wish to fix,
I hope a miracle occurs for you as well.
Not giving up…
The service center refused
since the model is discontinued.
Will you be able to fix it?
I could try if I had new parts for this,
but it'll be hard since this model
was sold briefly over 10 years ago.
I'm sorry.
Would anyone
be able to fix this drawing pad?
I'll repay anyone
who can at least recover the data.
What's this? An old tablet?
A drawing pad like this exists?
Wow,
I used this in middle school.
It's probably stashed somewhere.
I could try
if I had new parts for this.
Are you willing
to sell it to me if you find it?
If you are, please message me.
ARE YOU WILLING
TO SELL IT TO ME IF YOU FIND IT?
Hello?
Are you the one
who left a message saying
- you wanted to buy my drawing pad?
- Yes, I am.
I found a working drawing pad.
The parts are in there,
so you can fix it, right?
I can't guarantee that,
but you can leave it with me.
Thanks to the new parts,
I managed to restore the data
and move it to another device.
to HARAN
1. SUMMER, SEVEN YEARS AGO
IT STARTED WITH WALLS
Hyeokchan and I
were roommates
at the Boston Institute of Technology.
Can you message her back
and say I have to go to the lab?
Do me a solid.
One day, I was about to turn off
Hyeokchan's messenger alarm,
but your words caught my eye.
"Surrounded by walls."
Perhaps because I'd been feeling that way,
I wanted to be someone you could talk to.
I could guess
how lost you would be feeling.
IF IT'S OKAY WITH YOU, YOU CAN TALK TO ME
:cue
All I did was listen to you,
but strangely, it comforted me too.
THANKS FOR LISTENING TO ME COMPLAIN!
I thought
that would be
our first and last conversation.
But…
2. FOUNTAIN PEN, AND ENGRAVING
Around that time,
Hyeokchan hurt his hand badly,
and he asked me for a favor.
Anything that a woman
in her twenties can use.
He wanted to get you a gift,
but he couldn't make time
because of his treatment.
He felt really sorry.
I'm looking for a pen, like…
A pen for efficient design sketches.
Do you have them?
That's when
I remembered what you'd said.
You said you were surrounded by walls
and you couldn't sketch anything.
Hoping it would cheer you up a bit,
I chose a drawing pen.
Okay, I'll take this.
Is it a gift?
I could engrave it if you'd like.
"Haran."
I suddenly remembered
the name Hyeokchan had said
when he was calling you.
The design contest winner is…
Congratulations, Haran.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE MY SAVIOR.
Hyeokchan was away
to help our professor with some research.
I'm traveling around the East Coast
during vacation.
If our professor asks for me,
say I'm taking a break because of my hand.
Our laptops got switched
by accident back then…
…and soon after,
I had another day where I felt trapped.
How long are you going to keep doing this?
What more do I have to do
to make you stop?
Do you remember
how I said I stood alone
in a harsh winter as well?
I'd been barely holding on,
surrounded by walls,
but just as I was about to give up
and end everything…
…you suddenly spoke to me
right when I was about to die.
"You're…
my savior."
I knew those words weren't meant for me,
but I wanted to cling to them.
You said I was your savior,
but you were the one who saved me.
And that…
gave me reason to keep living.
Song Haran.
You saved me,
seven years ago.
You saved me back then!
Since then…
…I couldn't ignore the messages you sent,
thinking it was Hyeokchan.
GOLDBERG, NEON ALIEN, SMELL OF RAIN
THE PERSON WHO BROADENED MY WORLD
That Gold-something that
helps you sleep. I heard there's no proof.
It's like music to wake you up.
I'd forgotten how to smile,
but I started smiling because of you.
Shocking news.
I was eating lunch,
and there was eggplant in it.
Eggplant?
It's all mushy and squishy,
and it's neon-colored. Yuck!
The taste of a neon alien.
A neon alien…
I grew curious about you...
...and started looking forward
to what interesting stories
you'd tell me next.
My black-and-white life
began to be filled with colors,
and my tiny world
began to grow bigger,
thanks to your messages.
Thank you for helping me
not give up on what I love.
For giving me a reason to keep going.
If there was just a small crack
to breathe through, I could live.
I guess I wanted that pen
to be that "if" for you.
You became that "if" for me,
because I started drawing again,
thanks to you.
Hey, Chan.
Got the dorm maintenance notice.
Thank you.
Wow, you're really good.
You think you can draw me one day?
Uh…  Okay.
- Ah. Good, thanks.
-  And…
for the first time,
I started looking forward to the next day.
The moments I spent talking to you
helped me stay strong
without crumbling down.
:cue
5. THE EXPLOSION
But…
near the end of that summer,
there was an accident.
A lab explosion.
Everyone said I'd die soon
and that I would never wake up.
But…
Chan.
I heard a voice.
I love you.
I love you, Chan.
It was as if that voice
was trying to wake me up.
I woke to that voice,
but I couldn't remember
who called my name and woke me up.
I lost my memories after the accident
for about a year,
but for some reason,
that person's face and voice
kept popping up vividly in my mind.
And when I came to Korea for treatment,
I spotted her by coincidence.
On Christmas Eve,
at Jamsugyo.
I ran after her,
thinking she'd be the one
holding the key to my memories.
But fireworks suddenly went off,
and I remembered the explosion.
All my hazy memories
came flooding back.
That's when I realized
that person
was my old roommate's girlfriend,
and that I was just…
a complete stranger to you.
6. MEMENTO MORI
I immediately left
without a clear destination.
I wanted to get rid of my past.
I'd like a ticket
for the earliest departure anywhere.
But there was one thing
I just couldn't get rid of.
There was someone
who had helped me survive twice.
DRAW
At least for her sake,
I knew I had to stop
living like a dead person.
I got this tattoo
so I wouldn't forget that resolution.
"Memento Mori."
So I struggled for seven years
like I was trying to become someone else,
and at some point,
my environment, surroundings, and I…
had really changed.
It was as if my past did not matter.
7. NICE TO MEET YOU
Then one day, you appeared again
right in front of me, after seven years.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Song Haran, the lead designer.
I thought I was going to cry.
I was so grateful, and I missed you
and was curious about you, but…
It's nice to meet you. I'm…
You were someone
I shouldn't even think about.
…Seonu Chan.
8. LET'S HAVE FUN LIKE A SPRING PICNIC
If anything happens to you too…
Haran.
At first, I decided to avoid you
so I wouldn't get caught,
but I felt pained
while watching you.
The person who saved me seven years ago
was trapped alone in winter.
I thought I'd regret it later…
It's really valuable to me,
so I have to find it.
So I ended up making a crazy offer.
A three-month trial!
Then let's do this.
It'll be like we're on a spring picnic.
Let's have fun.
:cue
9. GREED
Many things happened between us
after that.
Tell me if it keeps hurting.
I'll carry you if I have to.
Ms. Song!
How have you been?
This is bad.
I ended up liking you so much,
even when
I couldn't explain myself to you.
10. MY BIRTHDAY, THE DAY I DECIDED
TO EXPLAIN MYSELF DESPITE THE GAPS
I feel like
telling you everything today, too.
I think I should stop
hiding things about myself.
Odd or even?
- I wanted to tell you everything…
- Odd.
But I knew my memories
weren't fully intact.
I grew worried that acting rashly
would ruin things between us
or hurt you in some way.
And in spring…
Will you not be here in spring?
I'm going to use that trial
for the rest of my life.
But…
I felt frustrated
that I couldn't talk about the future
with the person I loved.
So I made a decision.
I decided I'd slowly explain
what I could remember.
Do you have time after the movie?
There's something I have to tell you.
I knew you would see
how sincere I was.
I wanted to show you
that there's another way.
I learned it through that person.
She was just
someone who broadened my world.
You felt like someone you miss
called your name.
You already did that for me.
I thought it would be impossible,
so I scribbled it out…
but it might be possible now.
He went traveling with me.
Hyeokchan was away during vacation
to help our professor.
He asked me for a favor.
I chose to never do anything
that might get in the way
of her happiness.
Thanks to you, I just realized
that not digging up old wounds
is also a way
of protecting their happiness.
That was all about me.
I should've heard him out.
I should've listened to him just once.
:cue
-  Is this okay?
-  Let me see.
Good.
Your discharge is complete.
Congratulations.
- Great.
- Let's go.
-  Mr. Park is here.
- Ta-da.
Here.
- He's here.
- Congratulations on your discharge.
They're beautiful.
Let me give you a ride back.
I'll drop you off at SHIM.
Manjae. Should we walk back?
I want to take a walk.
I want to breathe in the cold air
and the smell of winter.
You'll catch a cold outside.
Just take our car.
They're right. You should get some rest.
A winter walk?
That sounds amazing.
It's amazing.
I thought walking and breathing
were just natural things in life,
but today,
it all feels like a gift.
I realized that too late.
Seeing such a beautiful sunset
and feeling the seasons…
I could have always
lived…
like life was a gift if I wanted to.
It's not late at all.
From now on,
we can do it all together,
little by little.
In the meantime,
we went through big and small changes.
No need to hurry.
- One at a time.
- Slowly…
Good job.
Almost there.
Yougyum.
What is it, Hadam?
"Congratulations, you've been…"
- Hadam!
- I'm a real med student now!
Great job, Hadam.
I can't believe it.
Yougyum, what's going on?
Why are you jumping?
Hadam's a med student now.
She just got accepted.
Hey. Why are you crying?
You're not her boyfriend.
I just got a call from the team.
I thought it was over
after I went undrafted,
but I got picked up by the Taesan Titans.
I'm going pro!
- Wow.
- Hey.
Yang Changmo!
Hang on.
Hey, how am I jumping?
Oh? It doesn't hurt.
Really?
It really doesn't hurt?
No, not at all.
It doesn't hurt!
Sir! Mr. Cha!
You shouldn't jump yet.
Sorry.
:cue
Are you heading out?
Yes, I'm heading out.
He said he has feelings for me.
He asked if he could like me,
and I said yes.
But he's exactly the same as before…
If you're free,
would you like to have some wine?
Just the two of us.
Just the two of us?
All right.
Sounds good.
What is this?
You just got surgery.
You need to regain your strength.
It's a local specialty from Jeju,
made by a master artisan. They're tasty.
- Mmm.
- Have them with your granddaughters.
- They look delicious. Manjae.
- Yes?
You should have some too.
All right. They look delicious.
Okay.
-  Eat up.
-  Okay.
Focus on recovering.
- You should eat too.
- All right.
-  Here.
-  Eat up, everyone.
Thank you.
Goodness.
Mmm! They're so chewy.
-  Good.
- They're so tasty.
This is good.
Mmm. It's delicious.
"This was the email
from the Comets."
"We watched the medical test video."
"We would like to verify
his rehabilitation progress
and other aspects besides the video,
so we suggest conducting a final test
at a local training center
as soon as possible."
What?
You have to go to the States for the test?
They must be worried because of my injury.
I'll go and try my best until the end.
As you said, if I give up
without trying until the end,
all that will be left is regret.
All right.
Go and show them everything you've got,
and leave no regrets.
Let's do this!
Gather our strength.
-  After many things happened…
- You can do it, right?
…during fall and winter,
the seasons passed…
It really is spring.
And winter began to meet...
...the beginning of spring.
However, the man who offered
a fun spring picnic
was nowhere to be found in spring.
- I really wanted something cold.
- Wow.
This is heaven.
It's so hot outside.
Here.
-  Thank you.
-  This is insane.
Let's go see
the cherry blossoms in spring.
We'll have…
shaved ice in summer.
Have some, Ms. Song.
Come and have one.
I'm okay. Enjoy.
Even as another season passed,
there was still no news from him.
:cue
GERANIUM
I CAN'T STOP THINKING OF YOU
It's that cloud, right?
The one that Ms. Song saw in Gyeongju
that was the inspiration for Won's outfit.
What was it called?
- An iridescent cloud.
-  That's right.
It's called an iridescent cloud.
They say you have good luck
if you see an iridescent cloud.
Come to think of it,
it's already been a year
since we went to Gyeongju.
I uploaded it.
Everyone, like my post.
Hey, Song Haran.
I'm not letting you slip away quietly.
Give me a like on my feed.
Here's a lucky charm.
You know you'll get lucky
once you see an iridescent cloud.
WE'RE USING THE DRAWING YOU GIFTED US
FOR OUR WEDDING INVITES!
IRIDESCENT CLOUD ARTIST
I JUST GOT A SURPRISE DRAWING GIFT
THANK YOU FOR THE GREAT MEMORY!
"Gangneung, 16 minutes…"
16 MINUTES AGO
I… I'm taking the afternoon off.
That's so sudden.
What?
She just got here, though.
Hello.
You looked so happy,
so I drew a picture of you.
Can I gift it to you?
- You're giving this to us?
-  Yes.
Thank you.
But what's this cloud?
It's an iridescent cloud.
They say it gives you good luck.
I wanted to wish you fortune.
Enjoy your trip.
Thank you.
You're here.
It's so pretty.
This is your sign, right?
Have you seen anyone nearby
who draws pictures like this?
I'm not sure.
Have you seen anyone
who draws pictures like this?
No.
Hello, have you seen
an artist drawing pictures nearby?
No.
Excuse me,
can I ask you something?
Have you seen an artist
who draws pictures with a cloud like this?
We received one earlier.
:cue
Isn't it this cloud?
When did you see him?
Just earlier today.
- Four or five hours ago.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Where on earth did he go?
Mmm.
- Hello.
-  Hello.
What a cool dog.
- Can I pet it?
- Sure.
Hi.
I was close to a dog
that looked just like this one.
Really?
Bye.
Sorry.
I dropped my pen…
again.
I found you.
I found you, Seonu Chan.
Why?
Why were you here alone?
I'm sorry, I realized too late.
Thank you for lying for me.
Thank you for protecting my scars.
No, it's all my fault.
I wasn't the only one
who didn't know what happened.
There are things you didn't know, either.
It's all my fault.
- I was being greedy--
-  No.
You didn't cause that accident.
Dr. Cha told me everything.
Seonu Chan disappeared because of me.
It was Hyeokchan
who caused the explosion.
And Seonu Chan was just a victim.
I lied to him.
I wanted to protect Hyeokchan
in any way I could.
:cue
I'm sorry, it was me--
It was caused by his lighter.
It happened because Hyeokchan
turned his lighter on.
Why would you
ruin everything like this?
Stop it, Hyeokchan.
Tell me!
You have to remember.
None of it was your fault.
You've been talking to Haran
while I was away?
Pretending to be me? Why?
Did you think it was okay
since I asked you a few times?
You were someone nobody even cared about.
Did you get excited
that someone paid attention to you?
Kang Hyeokchan!
You never hit Hyeokchan.
It was…
…Hyeokchan who hit you.
Tell me!
Kang Hyeokchan!
I have something to tell you.
Your messenger…
What?
While I was using your laptop,
I kept chatting with your girlfriend.
What?
What are you talking about?
Say that again.
We ended up
chatting after that.
But she thinks it was you.
Hyeokchan,
you left your earphones in my car…
Are you saying
you've been talking to Haran
while I was away?
Pretending to be me?
Sorry.
Hang on.
Who are you to do that?
Why would you ruin everything like this?
I was already feeling guilty
and wondering how to end things.
My head was already about to explode.
Do you have any idea what you've done?
I'm sorry.
Tell me.
What sort of things have you been saying?
Tell me!
Kang Hyeokchan!
Who are you to take away
my chance to end things peacefully?
What am I supposed to do now?
Why?
Did you think it was okay
since I asked you a few times?
You were someone nobody even cared about.
Did you get excited
that someone paid attention to you?
Stop it, Hyeokchan.
You're the one
who's been bad to your girlfriend.
No, it's us.
And you stopped liking her.
So don't take it out on your roommate.
You should leave for a moment.
Are you crazy? We're in a lab.
You're smoking too much these days.
Watch yourself.
Here for pickup.
Never leave the waste container like this.
Even a small leak will set off the sensor.
Be careful.
Sorry. I will.
The waste container had
nothing to do with the accident either,
because they collected it right away.
I was a witness.
It's not too late.
Go back to Korea and meet your girlfriend.
Explain everything to her
and apologize properly.
And apologize to your roommate.
You're the one
who took his laptop
and asked him to cover for you.
:cue
You're in a dangerous state.
Just go and get some rest.
I'll get going now.
Chan, I saw a vapor trail earlier.
But that made me want
to get on a plane to go see you.
It wasn't your fault.
The one who made me want to rush over
and say "I love you"
was you, back then and now.
I love you.
I love you, Seonu Chan.
Oh, no.
Where did he go?
The detailed exam confirmed
the shrapnel had shifted
and was stimulating his nerves.
It caused memory disturbance
and hallucinations.
Luckily, it shifted
to an operable position,
so we were able to remove the shrapnel.
Song Haran.
But due to severe mental fatigue,
he hasn't been able to wake up
for several days.
We'll have to wait until he wakes up
to see how the surgery
will affect his memories.
Every time I see you,
I swallow the same words
stuck in my throat.
11. WHAT I WANT TO TELL YOU
But…
I won't swallow them anymore.
I'm going to tell you
when I meet you today.
The words I decided to say to you
the moment my memories
were fully recovered.
I love you.
I LOVE YOU
I LOVE YOU, SONG HARAN
I love you, Song Haran.
:cue
Music start!
Congratulations!
Okay.
Kiss!
- Kiss.
Kiss.
Kiss…
Oh, my gosh!
He really did it!
Congratulations.
Here.
What? A baseball?
The ball from my final strikeout
that got me my first win.
I wanted to give it to you.
I know I'm still in the minor leagues.
Thank you, Hadam.
For not letting me give up.
Thank you for not giving up until the end.
But now that I think about it,
- we were so immature.
- What?
We thought we'd feel too anxious
being apart,
so we thought
marriage was our only option.
But now, no matter how far apart we are,
I don't feel anxious at all.
Right. I don't feel anxious at all.
Have we… matured?
Keep up with your rehab
during the offseason
and get yourself in perfect shape
before the spring camp.
Okay.
And…
sign this for me.
I'm your number one fan, remember?
I already signed it.
TO MY NO. 1 DOCTOR HADAM
I'M ALWAYS ROOTING FOR YOU, CHA YOUGYUM
I'm your number one fan too.
Hey!
:cue
-  Isn't B better?
-  Yes, B is better.
Who prefers option A?
What? It's 3 to 3?
What should we do, then?
C.
Ms. Kim!
Ms. Kim is here.
When you're not sure about both A and B,
- then it's C.
-  But, Ms. Kim,
you said you'd take a year off
with Mr. Park in France.
A month was enough.
Taking a long break isn't my thing.
All right, then I'll be expecting
an upgraded option.
- Okay.
- Yes, Ms. Kim.
All right, then.
Let's prepare option C.
Let's begin.
-  Let's do this.
-  Clean this.
Let's do this!
Are you heading out now, Ms. Song?
Congratulations on the bio-silk reorder.
Right. Thank you so much.
Is there something wrong?
Even outside the office,
you're always calling me Ms. Song.
Nothing's changed…
Forget it.
Ms. Song Hayeong will head home now,
COO Yeon Taeseok.
Hayeong.
Do you have to go home early today?
If I don't, then…
I mean,
it would be nice to have dinner
and watch a movie.
That sounds good.
I like movies.
Let's go.
- This way.
-  Okay!
Oh? What's that face?
You'd better not draw me weird.
Come on. I'm Seonu Chan.
Don't you know my skills?
All done.
Oh. Hang on. Give me just 10 seconds.
Let's close our eyes
and exchange them on the count of three.
One, two, three.
Oh! You're pretty good.
Why aren't you showing me yours?
Ah. I forgot. Can you count again?
All right.
One, two, three.
Let's go see cherry blossoms in spring,
eat shaved ice in summer,
see the autumn leaves in fall,
and go snowboarding in winter.
Will you share
every season of life with me
from now on?
You should stand up to match the drawing.
Huh?
Hmm.
Thank you for appearing in my life.
:cue
I told you,
I'll appear anywhere for you.
Thank you
for appearing
in my life and in my winter.
The cherry blossoms are beautiful.
-  This looks delicious.
-  Here.
-  Mm! Isn't it good?
- Mm!
This is nice.
Chan! Chan!
I read somewhere
that the seasons in life
don't come in order.
What if winter suddenly comes to my life?
It will pass one day.
Even if winter feels endless,
a spring breeze might blow someday
once you keep fighting through it.
I couldn't do that,
so I probably won't be able to
send this message,
but I hope that
when you're going through winter,
a warm spring breeze blows by eventually
and ends the painful season
before it gets too long.
And…
I hope that whatever season
you're going through,
they're all radiant.
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
Thank you for watching.
Be happy, everyone.
Oh, no. It's over.
What a radiant life it was.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
Translated by Juyoung Park