( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(Lee Na Young)
(Jung Eun Chae)
(Lee Chung Ah)
(Honour)
(Supported by the Culture Ministry
and Korea's Creative Content Agency)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and animals were
filmed under production guidelines.)
(Choi Ye Seul, Jo Yoo Jeong)
I really need to see these jerks' faces.
After doing something like this to kids,
they pretend they're decent.
They're not even human.
Identifying the users is
proving harder than we thought.
Not a single name has come
up. What about the police?
How's the server trace coming along?
As for the server location, Seung Jin...
No. It seems even Detective
Kim Seung Jin doesn't know,
and it looks like the trace is
going to take a while longer.
We need to crack it to get the user list.
You're not saying a word
about who the users are.
The arrest warrant for Park
Je Yeol will be issued soon too.
There's no point in
you holding out like this.
It won't do you any good.
Prosecutor Park will be sacrificed, sure.
But, Seon Kyu.
Those people, the
VIPs... They're different.
You think they'll even bat an eye at this?
No.
They know it. They know
they'll get away with it.
Why? Because it has happened
before, and they always get away clean.
As for who those people
are... I can't be the one to say.
And you call yourself a detective,
saying nonsense like that?
So
Is that why you went this
far? To Hyun Jin, of all people?
Look, man, I.
I know at this point, what I did
or didn't do doesn't mean a thing,
but this part wasn't me.
You guys...
You really still don't get it, do you?
Who was behind this.
Are you doing okay
staying with your parents?
How's Sang A?
(Episode 9)
That's a relief.
Tomorrow, we're going to file for divorce
the moment Park Je Yeol is arrested.
And of course, you'll
be able to get custody.
Okay, I'll keep you
updated on our progress.
Min Seo? Are you asleep?
- Yes.
- Where are you? Are you home?
- What about Han Min Seo?
Is she next to you?
Min Seo?
I think she's in her room. Why?
Get out of there. Right now. Hurry.
- Why? What's wrong?
- The green hoodie...
It's Han Min Seo.
What are you talking about?
I just talked to Seon Kyu.
Detective Kim told him.
You're in the same house as
Lee Seon Hwa's killer right now.
Hey, Yoon Ra Young,
are you listening to me?
Hey, Yoon Ra Young, answer me!
Ra Young.
Min Seo's gone.
Hyun Jin, I'll call you right back.
This is for you.
(Lee Jun Hyeok)
These are the candidates
for the evaluation committee.
Seven members will be
selected for the final committee,
but among them, the
most influential candidates
who are basically locks are these four.
(Lee Jong Jin)
(Kang Wook Min)
They have close ties
to high-ranking officials
who have a vested interest in this project,
so in this evaluation, they
will back our competitor.
If we can't get past them,
we don't have a realistic
chance of winning this bid.
So that's why you chose Haeil, right?
Because my mom has
enough pull to reach them.
How's the Connect case coming along?
It's been tough.
I doubt we'll make any progress
until Park Je Yeol is investigated.
That prosecutor will be dangerous.
We think so too, and
we're preparing for it.
For whatever his last
desperate move might be.
No. I mean the prosecutor.
Right now, he's the only one who
knows who the users really are.
The safest way to dispose of a
bomb that's served its purpose
is to just go ahead and pull the pin.
If there's anything I
can do, just let me know.
Thank you.
Prosecutor Park Je Yeol.
This is Detective Gu Seon Kyu
from the Mujin Police Station.
You think he might've already run off?
Sir, I checked the CCTV. He
was seen leaving two nights ago.
- Put out an APB, now!
- Yes, sir.
(Storage Locker)
Darn.
It's me, Prosecutor Park.
Why'd you bring the
server into the country?
To blackmail us with the evidence?
How foolish can you be, Prosecutor Park?
Do you really think you can
handle making an enemy out of us?
So you all get to just walk away from this,
and I'm the one who
takes the fall for all of this?
I was under the impression
that was the deal from the start.
You think that's all I have on you?
I was going to let it end here.
Get this straight.
You're the one who escalated this, not me.
(CCTV in front of Dasam Station Exit 2)
(Dashcam near Hansan-dong undeveloped area)
There's only one possible explanation.
She was a mole for Connect
from the very beginning.
But if that's true, why return
Jun Hyeok's laptop to us?
Detective Kim said the same thing.
That they didn't order her to do it.
He didn't seem like he was lying.
None of this makes any sense.
What could she have possibly wanted?
Whatever her reasons, Han
Min Seo attacked you both.
And Hyun Jin could've been seriously hurt.
Change your front door passcode now.
If she contacts you,
call the cops right away.
And don't go soft on her.
Hey, guys!
The hacker responded!
They'll hand over the
laptop's decryption key.
There was some information
hard coded in the code,
and it was a username I
recognised from a forum.
He said he was just hired and
wanted out, so I pressed him.
Nice work.
(Audio Transcripts)
(Evidence Photos, Personal
Info on Connect In, Timetable)
(Connect In User List)
A user list?
(Yeo Min Seok, Minister of Future Strategy)
(Choi Sik Yeong, Assembly Member)
A scandal that could
rock the entire country.
(Yoon Dae Hyeon, Seoul City Director)
(Ryu Seung Beom, Daily Baejin CEO)
So this is why.
This is why they killed Jun Hyeok.
This isn't just a list of johns.
Legal, political, and media circles.
They're all apex predators
in their respective fields.
They can all act as
shields for one another.
Exactly. This is a cartel.
If one of them gets into trouble,
another shuts down the press,
and someone else
obstructs the investigation.
A cartel bound together
by their depraved desires.
Is this
the Connect In server?
We don't have to worry about this, do we?
Because all the evidence against
us that was stored here is gone.
If this fuss drags on, we have
members recruited for this.
We'll throw a few to the
wolves, and things will die down.
All right, good.
I've got enough on my plate
with the National Assembly Audit.
Wasting my energy
on something so trivial...
It's just so aggravating.
What, you think you're the only
one going through this audit?
Hey, that's what I'm saying.
So cut me some slack.
He's different after hours.
He's got a sharp tongue on him.
So, how are we handling Prosecutor Park?
First off,
since public opinion is
a factor in the first trial,
how about 15 years, for appearances?
He's also up for soliciting murder.
But if the sentence is too long,
that might cause an uproar.
Seven years sounds about right.
We can whittle it down during the appeals.
- That works. The optics aren't bad.
- Okay, right.
- Then I'll pass the message along.
- Okay.
Okay, next time we pick an agent,
we must vet their background better.
You want someone who's
already in on the game.
I thought this educated
type would be different, but.
- I should've known.
- Exactly.
Gosh, I'm starting to get restless.
We should lay low until
Park's arrest, don't you think?
What's there to be afraid of?
Is this your first time at the rodeo?
- Haeil will tie up the loose ends.
- Of course.
- Let's have a drink.
- Let's.
- Cheers.
- Let's have a drink.
You all worked hard. What a relief.
Like getting a rotten tooth pulled.
- Madam Chairman.
- Hey.
Thank you for coming.
Of course.
Your plan for Shin Jae
to give her a way to escape Haeil...
Have you changed your mind about that?
No, I have not.
In that case,
this is my business with you.
(The Prime Smart City
Legal Retainer Agreement)
Are you terminating the retainer agreement?
I'm sure you know exactly what this means.
The Minister of Future Strategy,
the Chairman of the Ruling
Party Urban Committee,
and the Mayor of Mujin.
The most crucial players
for the Smart City bid.
You'd give up connections you
need to sway the evaluation committee.
And that's not all.
I will use every resource I
have to stop The Prime's bid.
And you of all people should know
that I have the power to do it.
If that's what you want,
then go right ahead.
However,
by the day of the bid,
do you really think your
connections will still exist?
I'm a firm believer that justice
will prevail, Madam Chairman.
Thank you for the tea.
Here's the background check
you requested on Baek Tae Joo.
How deep did you go?
Level A. Meaning we used
all our intelligence networks.
We investigated in Korea and the
US legal, financial, and real estate.
We have his finance and legal records
from school days to the present.
Interviews with his associates,
his health and medical records,
down to his private life, scandals,
and all the back-alley rumours.
Good work.
(Baek Tae Joo: Smart City)
(The story from those close to him)
("High School Student Baek Tae Joo,")
("Funding Sick Kids' Care")
("2006 Seo Ji Yoon Case: Her Tragic Death")
("The Powerful Figures on
the Vanished 'Seo Ji Yoon List'")
(Haeil Law Firm, 2006)
What do you mean, a call log?
There was no such evidence.
There was a tip. It's already
been sent to the prosecution.
It has our top clients' names.
They're already calling
it the Seo Ji Yoon List.
For us, this is the worst kind of evidence.
Then we just have to make it disappear.
Make it as if it never existed.
- How?
- Go,
and tell all those big shots on the list.
That they now owe us a huge favour.
("An Actress's Tragic Death,
How Did the Call Logs Vanish?")
(The identity of the mysterious hacker)
(Haeil Law Firm)
Hello, ma'am.
(CEO's Office)
What are you doing here,
waltzing into this office?
If you don't like it here,
you're always free to leave.
(Letter of resignation)
You're the one who must sign
this and clear out of this office.
You've got some nerve.
I'm speaking for every employee at LnJ.
We cannot accept a
Connect In user as our leader.
Is that so?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
I have never been involved
in any kind of scandal.
These are all just your
baseless accusations.
Is that all you have to say?
Then here's our response.
(LnJ attorneys hold press conference
releasing the "Connect In" list)
We are here today to name
the high-ranking officials
involved in the Connect In
sexual exploitation crimes.
The names of the
perpetrators are as follows.
- Goodness!
- Unbelievable!
We see the name of the
Minister of Future Strategy.
Is that correct?
Most are high-ranking figures
from politics, business, and law.
Do you have concrete
evidence to back this up?
Are you saying there
are more users than this?
- Is law enforcement aware of this?
- Are you saying this is true?
- Is there an additional list?
- Are you sure about this?
- Is all of this credible?
- Do you have proof that it's true?
The perpetrators named are
those who, by victim testimony,
were confirmed to have
sexually exploited them.
I'm sorry.
I can't look at them.
The look in his eyes
is exactly the same as it was that day.
Is this the guy?
Yes. I met him at around 10:30pm.
That's him.
I'm sure of it. Down
to the scar on his chin.
His wallet. He had a
National Assembly ID in it.
On behalf of the victims,
we will file criminal complaints
against these perpetrators.
Does the list you released today
include every Connect In user?
Today's defendants are on a list
of perpetrators we have obtained.
The rest will be submitted to
police for their investigation.
And we will take further
action based on their findings.
So how many more perpetrators are there?
I want to stress that this is not
simply a case about prostitution.
But a crime of sexual exploitation.
Victims were forced into prostitution.
And they knowingly condoned it
while abusing and assaulting them.
We won't rest until everyone
involved in this crime
is brought to justice.
Among the victims we represent
is one of the girls who dealt with you.
We'll see you in court.
(Letter of resignation)
So you've really gone
and caused this disaster.
Just brilliant, all of you.
Causing all this trouble again
because you had no self-control.
Seo Ji Yoon's list from 20 years ago.
If it weren't for that, Haeil
wouldn't be what it is today.
Have you really learned nothing
from what happened back then?
They were all terrified
their names would get out,
and since I was the one
who got my hands dirty to fix it,
you'd think they would've learned
to clean up after themselves.
And you.
When did you start
playing with fire with them?
When I put you with them,
it was to clean things up,
not to roll around in the mud with them.
This is the user list that
was submitted to the police.
Some of the names on
that list are on this one too.
If we let this go, Seo Ji
Yoon's list might surface again.
And people will start to wonder.
They'll wonder how the key
evidence, Seo Ji Yoon's call logs,
ended up disappearing
from the prosecutor's office.
Jung Hyeon. You need
to decide where you stand.
If you're here to threaten me,
then stop being so pathetic.
And if you're here to ask for my help,
then you need to drop the attitude.
I'm merely expressing my concern.
If things get serious for them,
where will Haeil find
shelter from the storm?
For now, come back to Haeil.
(Haeil Law Firm)
The Minister of Future Strategy...
The Chairman of the Ruling
Party Urban Committee...
The Mayor of Mujin...
The Minister of Future Strategy,
the Chairman of the Ruling
Party Urban Committee,
and the Mayor of Mujin.
The most crucial players
for the Smart City bid.
You'd give up connections you need
to sway the evaluation committee.
However,
by the day of the bid,
do you really think your
connections will still exist?
(CEO Seong Tae Im)
(Call records)
I'm a firm believer that justice
will prevail, Madam Chairman.
Yes?
Attorney Yoon?
Su Eun?
- Isn't she a little plain?
- You're too young to get it.
If you wanted someone more seasoned,
you should've gone to Gangnam.
Same old story. It gets old.
See? This is what they're like at that age.
There was this one day
when things were so
awful I just wanted to die.
And I thought if I died,
at least people would find out
the reason why.
So I made these recordings.
I should have given this to you sooner.
I'm so sorry.
Su Eun, you have nothing to be sorry for.
I understand. By having me listen to this,
Su Eun,
you had to relive that
painful moment all over again.
Even if you did it for my sake.
No one has the right to
know how you were hurt,
the specifics of it, or
how much you suffered.
If making this public causes you pain,
then
this would all be pointless, wouldn't it?
That's why, even if I'd gotten
this before the press conference,
I never would have released it.
Shouldn't we use it for the trial, though?
As evidence.
We'll follow proper procedure
to ensure it never gets leaked.
Thank you.
I gave you a clear warning.
You brought this on yourselves.
Sang A.
Sang A. I'm getting out of here.
Come with me, okay?
Why?
Are you worried it might be dangerous?
I saw it all on the news.
How could you do something like that?
Sang A.
- You're misunderstanding.
- To think that you're my dad
is just horrifying.
After everything I've done for you!
You're just like your mother.
Ungrateful and completely selfish.
You don't care what happens to me,
as long as you two get
away with it, is that it?
Don't ever come looking for me again.
Sang A!
What on earth? Let go of me, you jerks!
Let go!
Min Seo, I'm here.
There's only one possible explanation.
She was a mole for Connect
from the very beginning.
I want to hear from you
directly why you did it.
I
Have never seen my dad
act like that before.
So you resent your dad too?
I don't know.
I was just,
so scared.
Should I tell the police?
That my dad came to see me.
No.
Don't.
Then what should I do?
He has to pay for what he's done.
Not you. Your dad.
- This is LnJ Law Firm.
- Did the fax come in?
Can you give me a hand with this
when you're done? They keep coming.
- We just heard from the legal team.
- Yes, I'm aware.
Looks like they're making a move.
"Groundless," "false statements."
- "Defamation," "Libel."
- "Motion for a publication ban."
So predictable. Seriously.
I've seen this a thousand times.
Their next move is obvious too,
but the problem is it always works.
You need to keep your strength
up. These are a rare treat.
Have one, everyone.
Let's get our strength back.
Thank you.
They want a fight, they'll get one.
They think they'll get away with it,
but we're not exactly pushovers ourselves.
So they think they can
tie our hands like this?
The firms that sent these notices.
Pull up a list of all their
publicly traded clients
that these firms are representing.
Manager Lee, I'm Kang Shin Jae of LnJ.
The case your team is handling.
Hyundai Bank, Mujin Airlines, right?
Their legal counsel is Yakcheon Law Firm.
One perpetrator in the Connect
In case just retained Yakcheon.
And guess what?
One of our victims is a minor.
Using a law firm that
defends a child sex offender?
As their corporate counsel?
Your foreign institutional backers
won't be pleased about that, right?
Just thought you could use
that for your report tomorrow.
Yes, I'm Kang Shin Jae of LnJ.
Yes, of course. It's been a
while. How have you been?
Yes, I'm Kang Shin Jae of LnJ.
(On Top Entertainment
Idol Suspected of Drug Use)
(Real-time ranking 1.
(Z-ON member drug arrest)
(Z-ON member, drug scandal)
(2. Top idol Z-ON drug
use investigation expands)
(Z-ON member, suspected of drug
use, From the top to rock bottom)
Live from the Seoul Central
District Prosecutors' Office.
Soon, the controversial
figure in the drug case
from the idol group Z-ON
will make a statement.
It's Yoon Ra Young.
Right now, you are likely talking
about the downfall of a celebrity.
Our focus is on the
criminals hiding behind it.
Our priority is to reveal the real criminals.
LnJ files an additional complaint
against Lee Kang Eun,
CEO of On Top Entertainment, Z-ON's agency,
for his involvement in
the Connect In sex crimes.
A lawsuit? This is a huge scoop.
The list of culprits we're suing,
starting with CEO Lee Kang Eun,
is as follows.
(Second Connect In list released...)
(Connect In scandal reignites...)
If you just drop the lawsuit,
your child can have a fresh start.
Do you want them to be labelled
a sexual assault victim forever?
(Yeonbok Supermarket)
I'm just cutting in because
this is taking a while.
It sounds like you're offering
our client's mom a generous offer.
But this "generous offer" of yours...
It actually has a different
name under the law.
It's called subornation of perjury,
Article 152 of the Criminal Code.
Did you get screenshots of
all the donations they received?
Yes. I've got everything
from the last few years.
Okay. Send all of them over.
- To our little Grim Reapers.
- On it.
(Prosecution Service)
(Search and seizure warrant)
(Consultation Room)
Yes, exactly.
It's not about the perpetrators'
individual misdeeds.
It's that Connect In is a massive cartel.
Now the real masterminds in
hiding will start to make their move.
- Continuing with our breaking news.
- Get a focus on that article.
Given the Connect In case's
gravity, the prosecution
has decided to establish a
Joint Investigation Headquarters.
(Joint Investigation Headquarters)
I'll have to call you back.
Chief Prosecutor Ahn
Sung Joon of Seoul Central
- will lead the HQ.
- What? A joint investigation?
Deputy Chief Kim Jung Woo of
Seoul Southern will be his deputy.
And Lee Jae Ho, head of Criminal
Division Three at Seoul Central
will also lead a team.
The police will dispatch the
lead investigator to the Joint HQ
- to assist the investigation.
- What's wrong?
- Due to the Connect case...
- Isn't a joint HQ better for us
than the prosecutors working alone?
Will the investigation speed
up after a joint HQ is formed?
- It was my mom.
- The expectations are rising.
Every single person they
just named owes my mother.
Among those newly
assigned to headquarters
is Prosecutor Kim Jung Woo
of Seoul Southern Office...
So my mother's making her move.
He was a key member of the task force
that took down a major drug distributor...
Start with the office.
- The office.
- Wait a minute. What is all this?
Hey, hold on!
What do you think you're doing?
You're Attorney Kang Shin Jae,
CEO of the LnJ law firm, correct?
We're from the Joint Investigation HQ.
You're under suspicion
for obstructing justice,
and illegally obtaining
evidence against Park Je Yeol.
We'll now begin a search and seizure
- of all the evidence in this case.
- You can't go in there.
Sir.
Should we force our way in?
You know this is
obstructing justice, right?
Let's move!
(Police)
Mujin Police Public
Services desk. How can I...
What brings you here?
I came to talk about the
Joint Investigation HQ,
but what's all this?
It's nothing. I was put on standby,
so they just have me here for now.
- Once the internal audit is over...
- Right.
An internal audit? They
pulled you off the case,
and stuck you here as retaliation.
Calm down. Getting
worked up is bad for you.
Let's go. We can talk outside.
What do you think you're doing?
Sit down. I had some porridge
made for you to soothe your stomach.
The Joint Investigation HQ.
I know you're behind this, Mom.
You should have seen it coming.
You were just circling the
case without any hard evidence.
Didn't it occur to you that
the tables could be turned?
Who would've thought my own mother
would be pushing me to the edge?
We've never been on the
same side, but this is different.
Mom, you targeted me.
Why would you go this far?
I just did what I've always done.
What I know how to do.
For Haeil? For your clients?
That's right.
Then I guess I'll just do
what I've always done.
What I have to do.
Thank you for proving
that I was right, Mom.
Haeil must be eradicated from this country.
Be careful of Baek Tae Joo.
He has us both you and me
in the palm of his hand.
What is that supposed to mean?
I just hope that I'm wrong about this.
Make sure you eat the porridge.
(Boarding House)
(Please keep quiet indoors.)
It's safe here. Don't
worry, and come on in.
Remember what I told you on the way here.
Everyone, keep outside
contact to a minimum.
And don't tell anyone you're here.
Park Je Yeol is on the run,
and we don't know what
those users will try to pull.
- Okay.
- Right.
I'll show you to your rooms. Follow me.
Darn.
There are two ways we can do this.
First,
we silence you for good.
Second, we give you one last chance
to make up for all this.
Which one would you prefer we choose?
What are you trying to say?
That I should take the fall for all of you,
and go down alone?
Either way, I'm the only one
who gets screwed in the end.
The deal doesn't add up.
We'll make sure you
won't be in prison for long.
How long?
Once this storm blows
over, you'll be a free man.
And we'll provide a hefty
sum for your troubles.
I'll be at Seoul Central
District Prosecutors' Office
by 2pm.
We're live. Prosecutor Park Je
Yeol, a key Connect In case operator,
has announced that he will
voluntarily surrender himself
to the prosecution.
Could you please comment
on the current situation?
Prosecutor, could we get a statement?
(Prosecutors' Office)
First of all,
I sincerely apologise to the public,
for causing so much concern.
As for the Connect In app,
I was the one who operated it.
Are you admitting to all the charges?
Is the VIP list claimed by LnJ authentic?
I abused my position as a prosecutor
to make a mockery of the
law and to profit improperly.
To the victims irreparably
harmed in the process,
I have committed a grave sin.
However, the list that LnJ released,
the so-called "VIP list,"
is completely false...
What's going on?
- What is this?
- What?
- What are they doing?
- That's disgusting.
Are they kissing?
- What is that?
- What's happening?
These videos are being
posted on social media right now.
Care to explain?
(Today's bombshell)
Please help me.
I was brought here against my will.
- Please.
- Darn it.
- Give us a statement!
- Prosecutor, are you running away?
- Prosecutor, a statement!
- Sir!
- Prosecutor, wait!
- Please explain!
- Prosecutor!
- Where are you going?
- Was it all a lie?
- Is it true?
- Prosecutor!
- What's going on?
You said you'd turn yourself
in. Why are you running away?
Are you running away?
Prosecutor!
This is insane.
What is this?
Hey.
Put more emotion into your voice.
I told you, sound more
desperate when you sob.
That's more my taste.
Ye Ji, did you see the videos they posted?
You can see all the victims' faces.
- Report it and take it down...
- Everyone, come on out.
- As fast as you can.
- Turn off your phones,
and stay off the internet.
Attorney Yoon.
(Connect In Evidence Video four)
You think that's all I have on you?
You're the one who escalated this, not me.
That little jerk.
(Park Je Yeol, Mujin District Prosecutor)
- You dare screw me over like this?
- It wasn't me.
I also have no idea.
I have no idea how any of this happened.
All these videos were shot on our phones.
If you didn't tamper with
our phones then who did?
Who else could've secretly
filmed and leaked this trash?
I'll find out who did it.
I'll quickly find out who did this and why...
Shut it.
I'm about to teach you what
a fate worse than death
really is.
I just don't understand.
This makes no sense.
If Park Je Yeol didn't post it, who did?
Think about it. Why would
he suddenly surrender?
He must've gotten his story
straight with the other assailants.
But did you see it? How he
panicked when he saw the video?
You think that cunning
jerk would just throw away
his only lifeline like that?
Attorney...
We
Can't do this anymore.
- Su Eun.
- Our voices,
the brief glimpses of our faces...
People are already going crazy online
trying to identify us.
We'll do whatever we can
to stop secondary harm.
All we wanted
was to go back to our normal lives.
We believed punishing those
men was the only way we could.
But now, it feels like
it was all for nothing.
Just releasing that one audio file
took us two sleepless nights.
But
the whole world has seen it, Attorney.
What they did to us.
All right.
I'll give you all a ride.
But you have to pick up
when I call, at least once a day.
If you don't, I'm coming to hunt you down.
And don't forget. You're
always welcome here.
I'll start the car. Grab your
things and come on out.
Where's that wench?
That wench. Where is that crazy wench?
What's going on?
- What are you talking about?
- Han Min Seo, that wench.
You're hiding her, aren't you?
She told me everything herself.
Recognise me?
Those brass knuckles.
You're going to regret all of this.
You're going to regret
everything you've ever done.
Even the day you were born.
You...
Those videos? I'm the one who posted them.
I bet you're wondering how.
Where are you right now?
If you want to know, come and find me.
I'll send you my location.
What do you mean?
Han Min Seo was the one
who posted the videos? Not you?
I didn't even know the darn thing existed.
So, where is that wench?
Where is she?
Oh, right.
You're all here together.
Perfect. Now I can
take you all out at once.
Is he here for us?
Call the police, now. I'll get them inside.
You put her up to this, didn't you?
Trying to get revenge on me? Is that it?
You put her up to it, right?
I knew something was off. That's it.
It was a trap.
This was all a setup
from the start, wasn't it?
Right?
This piece of trash still doesn't get it.
Yes. You were there too, right?
You ruined everything.
You hear me?
You wenches ruined everything! You hear me?
I'll end this.
Someone's been hurt.
(Attorney Yoon Ra Young)
(Thank you...)
Thank you, Mom,
for killing Dad.
The safest way to dispose of a
bomb that's served its purpose
is to just go ahead and pull the pin.
(CEO Baek Tae Joo)
(The Prime)
It's infested.
If I leave it, it will
contaminate the whole thing.
So, you use pesticides?
Rather than that, I lure
them with the trap pests like.
The pests
take the bait without
ever knowing it's a trap.
(Honour)
I won't say rest in peace.
- You're in the fiery pit anyway.
- Find Han Min Seo.
She's the one who lured
Park Je Yeol to the villa too.
I'm sorry.
This has gone on long enough.
Stop Ra Young from being released.
We can't prove self-defence
without eyewitness testimony.
You just ruined my whole life, Mom!
I have to get out of here.
There's someone behind Min Seo.