(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
Let's grab a single on Mu-hee.
- For her close-up though…
- Okay. Great.
When I heard
we were shooting at the opera house,
I wanted to sit right here.
Do you like operas?
I don't know it well.
There's a scene in a film I like
where the two main characters
go to the opera.
Um, do you know the movie
Pretty Woman, starring Julia Roberts?
Ah, I do know that movie,
but wasn't that way before your time?
That's it. That's exactly right.
The leading man in that film
is really rich.
They go to the opera
and get the most expensive seats.
Just like these here.
This is why I wanted to come and sit here.
We need to find out the opera
that's in Pretty Woman.
- Pretty…
- Please go look.
Okay. Okay.
When we get it, we'll start playing it.
La Traviata.
The opera the characters watched
in Pretty Woman was Verdi's La Traviata.
This music also plays at the end.
It's the best scene, I think.
Amami, Alfredo.
Quant'io t'amo.
Addio.
What's that? Was that Italian?
But how?
They're opera lyrics.
Whoa. She memorized them?
What's she saying?
Love me, Alfredo,
as much as I love you.
Good
bye?
Love me, Joo Ho-jin…
as much as I love you.
Goodbye.
CAN THIS LOVE BE TRANSLATED?
TEN DAYS AGO, JAPAN
Aya-chan, you're brilliant!
Uncle Hiro's been studying lately too.
I'm learning Korean.
But your uncle's so smart
that he couldn't help it.
I'm not the kind of guy who meets someone
simply because they ask me to.
Thank you.
She's one rude woman.
Kissing me without permission.
If she wanted to meet,
she should have said when and where.
Now I'm waiting anxiously.
Aya-chan.
Maybe I've been infected
by a zombie virus.
So are you flying to Italy today?
I just came to give Aya-chan her gift.
Then I'll head to the airport.
How thoughtful.
And how was the shoot? Did you like?
Huh?
Why would I like a zombie?
And those dates are strictly work.
It's not like
I'm actually interested in her.
I was asking whether you liked Canada.
I wasn't asking if you liked that woman.
What's with you?
They kissed.
No. Honestly, it's not like that.
That zombie caught me off guard.
That's all.
I see, and I'm guessing
you fell for her too.
Huh?
Your first love.
The older girl
who was the neighborhood rebel.
Like Do Ra-mi.
Why would you bring that up?
It was the talk of the town.
The romance between the rebel girl
and the pretty boy.
Do we have a South Korea-Japan scandal
on our hands this time?
This should be fun.
- This should be fun!
- Right?
Maybe the pretty boy
has fallen for a zombie this time.
- Maybe?
- Right?
- Let's eat.
- Okay.
CHA MU-HEE
You're really here this time.
Hiro?
Did we arrive here together?
We've been together all along?
I wasn't here with Hiro.
I was alone.
CALL HISTORY
There's no one
I wanted to be with.
MESSAGES
I'LL BE WAITING.
I did text Hiro to come here.
Do Ra-mi's the one who invited Hiro.
But what he said about me kissing him…
You asked me to come,
but you don't look happy to see me.
Let's look at this objectively.
I flirted with you on the airplane,
and that's why you came all this way.
Hmm?
But no matter what,
these fingers texted you,
and I asked you to meet me.
And these lips,
um, well…
I kissed you with these, uh…
so I have to take responsibility.
Response?
So let me ask you this.
Do you like me?
Do you love me?
No, no! No way! Oh, no, no, no!
Oh, no!
I guess my showing up here
gave you the wrong impression.
I only came here to confirm something.
I came to see if you'd lied again
and to teach you a lesson if so.
Then that means
you don't like me?
Oh.
I don't like you.
Oh!
Oh, thank you.
Oh, this is great.
Of course, there's no way you'd like me.
You hate me. Oh, good.
Hey, then, sorry to ask you
a weird question. Sorry.
Sorry?
Actually,
I had debated
if I should go to Italy or not.
If I hadn't seen you when I came here,
I might've turned around
and gone back to Seoul.
Thanks for taking the time to talk.
- Thank you.
- Thank you?
I'll work harder now
because of what happened.
I'll fight hard. Fighting.
You…
Do you want to date?
Oh!
No! Not at all. No way.
No. Never. No romance, ever.
Don't worry.
I don't pick fights I can't win.
I'd be losing by liking you
when you don't like me back.
I will never lose!
Fight!
- Oh, yes. Fight.
- Yes.
Oh good. Fighting.
- Fight!
- That's it. Yes, yes. Fighting.
Fight!
- We should go.
- Oh, I can pay.
I'll take this. Thanks.
In Korea, the one who pays
is the one who asked for the meeting.
Call it a Korean rule. Okay?
I'm sorry, your card has been declined.
What?
Oh no. Wait.
Here you go.
Jeez. I'm sorry that my card got declined.
I'm sorry.
And thank you for the ride, too,
since my phone battery died.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Oh.
- Hello there.
- Oh, hi!
- Hello. Good to see you.
- Yes, hi. Good to see you.
Hiro. I have today's schedule.
Could you take a look?
Looks like you'll have a lot of downtime.
Shall we do a costume change
and touch-up here?
Yeah, okay.
- Hello.
- Yo.
Mu-hee, here's your headset.
- Great. Thank you.
- For your ears.
Were you cast in Josh Safdie's new film?
How did you know?
We're talking right now
and taking a look at the script.
I hope we can work together again.
I just signed on.
- Really? That's great. I'd like that.
- I would too.
- This good?
- Oh, yes. Looks good.
Cha Mu-hee, can you hear me?
Cha Mu-hee?
Yes, I hear you.
The weather's good for our first day.
When the weather's good on the first day,
it'll stay like this for the rest.
I hope everything will work out
for you while you're in Italy.
I'm grateful…
and happy to be working with you again.
Cameras, stand by.
Let's begin the Italian shoot
of Romantic Trip.
We're starting again here, in Italy.
Do Ra-mi must have worn this
to go out last night.
And she bought this hat?
Oh!
"Lemoncello"?
A lemon liqueur?
I went out drinking?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Well, I went drinking last night.
This area was a bathhouse long ago.
What is that?
In South Korea,
you buy snacks when you go to the spa.
It's… very popular.
It's called a jjimjilbang.
Mix.
Like a mix. You know? A mix of things?
In Canada, they were awkward,
and Mu-hee was sweet and laughed.
Hiro was a bit self-involved.
It was an odd vibe.
But now,
they're like two seasoned
traveling buddies reporting on things.
Huh.
How did it change?
- Maybe they're too friendly now?
- Think so?
Is it true Joo Ho-jin is booked off-site
at a place in Italy?
We'll need to process receipts for that.
He's staying at a friend's place
since they're out of town.
He said not to worry about it.
Huh.
It's your fault.
You kept asking him for favors,
Park In-su.
So he decided to stay elsewhere.
Poor Joo Ho-jin.
Uh, he's avoiding me because I'm annoying?
Ciao!
Oh, no. We're closed. I'm sorry.
- We closed already. I'm sorry.
- One drink, okay?
- No. Go find another place tonight.
- Why?
- Tomorrow, okay?
- Hey, no!
Ciao! Ciao!
Ciao!
Looks delicious.
- Bonjour.
- No.
Not bonjour.
- Thank you.
- Well done.
Oh, hi, honey.
I had hoped tonight would be relaxed.
You're here again.
Mm. Bueno.
Oh, hi, honey. Look, it's me.
This is just crazy.
Oh, honey. Accept this. It's great.
Whoa!
That's the one.
There are plenty of hats like that
at Dongdaemun too.
That's enough.
Let's head back to the hotel now. Stop.
- Do Ra-mi.
- This is cute.
Cute?
Ah.
Wow, really?
Here. This is for you.
Okay.
That's the hat she bought last night.
Cheers.
This is so good.
It's too much. Stop.
This isn't lemon juice.
Waiter!
I'd like another bottle for the table.
Or maybe two?
Two bottles? You gotta be kidding me.
I wanna go home.
Thank you so much.
They want us to go.
Ah, honey.
Sh. It's late.
Quiet.
- I need to use the restroom.
- Sh. Let's try and be quiet. Sh.
Is she okay?
Is she feeling okay?
Sure. I'm okay.
Well… I went drinking last night.
Maybe I should have said no.
This looks good. I want one.
Let's go.
- I want it!
- No.
Stop. Look at
their business hours. They open at 4:00.
Huh?
I'll wait until then.
What?
You kidding?
Really?
The lyrics from the opera
in that movie you like.
Thank you.
Hey, honey, this is super hard to read.
What does it say?
Write the pronunciations down.
When we're at the opera,
she'll come off as super smart
by saying lines from the movie she likes,
and it'll make her happy.
If you memorize this,
Mu-hee will know it too?
I've told you, yes.
We share the same brain.
We're stupid because she is.
If I become smarter, she will too.
That's enough.
Who knows if you can memorize it.
Especially if you drank so much yesterday.
Oh, are you worried?
You're a sweetheart!
Yes.
I'm doing the best I can to be kind
in the hope that you'll leave.
Would you sing these out loud
to help me memorize?
It's too hard?
Want me to make it easier?
Yeah.
Any way you can.
Rote memorization. Repetition works.
Now do it.
Mama… mama mia… ma… ma, ama…
- Ah!
- Get it together.
A… ama, mama… mama mia?
- Again.
- Ow!
I didn't get a proper look, man! Ow!
Okay.
Review the paper now.
One, two.
Amami, Alfredo.
Quant'io t'amo. Quant'io t'amo.
Quant'io t'amo. Quant'io…
Now try it.
A… amami, Alfredo.
Quant'io t'amo. Quant'io t'amo. Addio!
You memorized it.
Now keep repeating it to make it stick.
Amami, Alfredo.
Quant'io t'amo. Quant'io t'amo. Addio.
I memorized it fast.
That's right.
She's good at memorizing scripts quickly.
You can memorize. I'll give you that.
You see a passcode just once,
and you know it.
I want a reward since I passed.
Such as?
Why not?
Is it too public here?
Let's go kiss in the dark.
Yeah, sure. Why don't we do it here?
Oh my.
Mm. You're so adorable when you're afraid.
Oh?
Since you see me as cute,
I want to ask something.
Since we've arrived in Italy
and shooting has begun,
Cha Mu-hee has been looking
very happy, so…
so why are you still here?
Hmm…
It's a way to keep seeing you.
Don't joke with me.
You're not even cute.
Oh, you want me to say something not cute?
She can recall all of it.
The accident back then.
Accident?
I don't remember anything about it.
Even how my parents died.
The truth is, she saw it
and remembers every detail.
She lies and pretends
she doesn't know anything.
She pretended to smile
when she was little to hide her sadness.
They found it freaky
and weird and hated her.
I could tell you what Mu-hee doesn't know.
Before I went to your house that night,
I confronted her relatives.
You saw her family?
Yes, I dropped a few major F-bombs
in front of God.
Ho-jin, lighten up.
I didn't drop real bombs.
Don't take it literally. I didn't swear.
It was a Catholic church,
so I couldn't swear.
I wanna go to heaven.
And don't say she better be thankful
her family took her in.
She's been saying that her whole life.
I had a right to tell them off.
What's this? Forcing me to repent?
It's the kindness you want.
Just take it.
Way to go.
Let's go.
Kindness makes me wanna kill you.
She's becoming more violent.
"I felt like I might die
if someone was kind to me."
"For whatever I've done wrong,
it felt like kindness might kill me."
Kindness can be scary.
If you believe
it's going to end eventually,
there's nothing more terrifying
than kindness.
Amami, Alfredo.
Quant'io t'amo.
Addio.
What's that? Was that Italian?
But how?
They're opera lyrics.
Love me, Alfredo,
as much as I love you.
Good
bye?
Oh, what does that mean?
They're opera lyrics.
"Love me, Alfredo,
as much as I love you. Goodbye."
Whoa.
I just spoke Italian,
and I was speaking it right?
Yes. That's what happened.
So cool!
You must really love that movie.
Next time, let's go see
that opera you memorized
from these seats.
He wants to see the opera
in the movie you like.
Maybe you can see it together sometime.
Wonderful. Yes. I look forward to it.
That was easy.
One line, and he wants to date me
and see an opera from a film.
You don't like operas.
Watching something in a language
you don't understand
will make you fall asleep.
You've seen that opera before? With who?
She wants to know.
Not me. Cha Mu-hee.
Really?
She'll need to ask me herself
if that's true.
She's too embarrassed to be near you.
She can't talk to you.
She talked to me all day.
That's 'cause you're her translator.
You know she's good at that.
She says, "Ho-jin!"
Then she says anything that comes to mind.
She can't talk right now.
Joo Ho-jin.
Who did you see that opera with?
What's that?
A camera for pictures.
I have no idea how to use it,
but it cost a lot.
Did you use Mu-hee's credit card?
No, it's Hiro's.
Oh.
Why would you have that?
I stole it. That's why.
Did I mishear you?
P… please tell me
you didn't steal anything.
Yeah, I did.
Why would you do that?
This way, Hiro owes her a huge favor.
The camera is his prized possession.
When he sees it's missing, he'll get sad.
She'll find it super fast,
and he'll be grateful.
It won't end with the opera.
Here. Take it for now.
I'll keep it?
You're here to help her.
Keep an eye out and see when
it'll be good for her to find it.
No way.
You want me to lie and cover your theft?
I won't. I refuse.
What will we do, then?
The police could get a call from him.
What about the security camera?
They'll see me in it.
She might get cuffed
and sent to the station.
You don't want that? Do you?
Tomorrow's a day off,
so please raise your glasses.
- To the crew!
- Cheers!
Let's drink!
Cheers!
You said Hiro isn't around tomorrow night?
He was invited to a photography exhibit
around here by a friend of his, I believe.
Mm. Makes me so jealous.
Oh! We'll have to have our own party.
Yong-u can find
a trendy restaurant for us.
Ji-sun, where's your ring?
Oh.
Did you lose it or something?
No, I've got it.
I just take it off when I wash my hands.
You scared me. Be careful not to lose it.
I lost mine once,
and I almost got divorced.
Oh, honey. Seriously? You need to help me.
Put the camera back before you get caught.
No way.
I wanna act like I found it.
What is it?
What? You're cuddling?
Stay still. Don't move.
Right foot.
Move your right foot.
Left foot. Okay.
- This is all so yummy.
- Mm. It melts in my mouth.
So good.
Wait. Is that Joo Ho-jin?
Huh?
Joo Ho-jin?
That's him.
Yes, he was wearing that coat today.
That was really Ho-jin?
There was someone else.
It definitely looked like
a young woman under his coat.
- She must be pretty.
- Maybe she's Italian?
Please, let's hope they didn't see us.
No cuddling. Come on.
Enough.
Things will get more awkward
if she ends up in jail!
Honey, we need to protect her.
She's nothing but a thug.
We're going to where we filmed yesterday.
He might have lost
something important there,
so we all have to look for it.
Huh?
- I found this.
- That's just the lens cap.
Keep looking.
Let's find it tonight.
I'll look over there, okay?
Okay.
Why am I doing this for her?
She took my photo.
No, the lens was covered the entire time.
Or was it?
She fiddled around with it.
Just think. It was on.
Or was it off?
I found it!
Here it is!
I'll take it to the lobby.
I found it!
Oh!
Oh.
Wha… uh…
You found it?
Let me look.
Um, this is… good.
Looks fine.
This too.
Checks out.
Nothing here looks broken.
Oh, um, great.
Glad it's not broken. Good.
Um…
She's too embarrassed
to be near you. She can't talk to you.
Let's talk…
about operas.
So Carmen is less, well, boring
than La Traviata.
I zoned out while watching La Traviata,
but Carmen was very good.
Is that so?
But Carmen isn't the opera
in Pretty Woman.
Ah.
Then just go see that.
The person I went with really liked it.
Anyway, I'm glad you found the camera.
Wait a sec.
Who was that person with you?
Well,
is the person you saw it with kinda…
kinda like me? I mean, maybe?
We just might like
the same types of things?
I went with an author
I worked with on the project.
It was a book about operas.
His age was
about 50 or so. He was a man.
What do you think?
You and my friend can have the same taste?
Yes.
I bet we can.
Yeah, sure. I'm like a middle-aged man.
That's good.
The opera will be to your taste.
We haven't talked like this in ages,
but I hear your voice every day.
I've kept an eye on you this whole trip.
Oh.
You mean you've seen me on the monitors?
- How's the hotel you're staying at?
- Mu-hee, where are you?
Did you find it?
You found the camera?
Here.
This is really precious to me.
Thank you for finding it.
I'm very thankful.
Don't say thank you.
It's all right. I got you.
Everyone looked for it.
She said, "It's okay.
We all found it together."
You've seen that opera before?
Who was that person with you?
I guess I ended up talking to her.
Do Ra-mi did it deliberately
by stealing the camera?
La Traviata will be playing here soon.
I'd like to get tickets to it.
But before I do,
I'd like to ask you something.
Last night,
I saw you were out with a woman.
I saw you as well and ducked,
but you must have spotted us.
Were you able to see who I was with?
No, I wasn't.
Everyone I was with
thought it was your Italian girlfriend.
I did catch a glimpse of her shoes.
She was wearing the same ones Mu-hee wore
when she was filming yesterday.
Were you with her? Was that Mu-hee?
No, it wasn't.
That person's someone else entirely.
No one knows her.
Very well, then. Sorry.
This is the photographer
who took Hiro's photos when he started.
The camera we were looking for
was a gift from her
to congratulate him
on his accomplishments.
It's a gift with a lot of memories
for him, so thank you.
Yes, I'm so thankful it was found.
I heard you were the one who found it.
Thank you.
Oh, you're welcome.
So how's your trip to Italy with Hiro?
Was it fun?
If it weren't
for my exhibition, I'd want to join too.
But I guess I can't since it's a shoot.
Hmm. Do we think we need
to save Mu-hee from her?
I'm sure Hiro and Mu-hee don't care.
They've been hitting it off.
I wouldn't worry about that chick.
- There's booze there!
- With free-flowing champagne!
Ooh, let's go!
Do you want some champagne?
Mm.
There's a problem at the winery.
It's urgent.
What's the matter, Mr. Park?
There, uh, might be
a fire at our location.
Apparently, they canceled everything.
Our winery is impacted as well.
Then what can be done about it now?
I'm afraid we'll need to look
for another spot to shoot.
An olive farm, for instance,
or a superstore that sells wine.
He says there aren't any wineries
available for us.
Oh, I know a guy who operates
a travel booking site.
Wait a sec.
I read an essay that your fiancé wrote
about an acquaintance of his
who operates a large winery in Italy.
Uh…
Yes. I know her.
Call him. It's so urgent.
Ask for the show, please.
- It's our only hope.
- Please, Ji-sun.
Ah, hello?
Yeah, it's me.
I hope it works out. It would be great.
- What's taking so long?
- This needs to work out with Ji-sun.
Please!
It's done. The owner said
we can make our way there.
Oh, there is a God!
He's our savior!
My Ji-sun, your fiancé saved us all today!
I thought I was gonna die from stress.
- I need a drink.
- Oh, I need one too.
This is yours.
You were stressed too.
Uh, thank you.
You invited a Korean reality TV crew
to film here?
I couldn't say no.
It's a chance to see my boy again,
so that's why I said yes.
In that case,
it'll be nice for you
to see your son again.
Yes.
But, uh, I'm also scared.
It's been many years,
and I've hurt him very deeply.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
So you came alone today.
Why is your girlfriend not with you?
You thought she was my girlfriend?
Well, yes. You both looked so in love.
Or was I mistaken?
Yes.
- It's a misunderstanding.
- Ah.
Then she won't join you here anymore?
That's too bad.
I was hoping today,
I'd get my lucky seven.
What do you mean?
Every time she came here,
she drew one of these.
These are
four-leaf clovers.
I recognized her. I know she's famous.
I've seen her in some interviews,
but I didn't wanna bother her,
so I pretended not to recognize her.
I haven't told anyone she's been here.
I appreciate that.
I thought I might ask her for an autograph
once she gave me a seventh clover,
but I didn't get it.
She must really want her wish to come true
if she's collecting
so many four-leaf clovers.
She thinks that if she just keeps
on collecting more of these,
all of her wishes
will finally be fulfilled.
Wow, I get so anxious
when I meet someone new.
Oh, where's Yong-u?
The Northern Lights.
You know, I am
seeing the aurora borealis thanks to you.
I miss it so much.
I could have sworn the zombie was crying.
What's up with her?
MS. CHA MU-HEE
HONEY
She's supposed to be at the gallery.
Ho-jin!
Cha Mu-hee?
Did you think I was her?
You need to go to the gallery.
Why did you show up again?
It's only because I missed you, honey.
Oh, the party today was so fun.
The camera going missing worked.
It's because I laid the groundwork
with the love confession opera song.
Thanks to my guy.
In that opera, it's not a confession.
It's about leaving.
Huh?
Wait, that can't be right.
It's at the end of the movie,
Pretty Woman.
It's a happy ending.
It ends with them kissing in love,
so they wouldn't play a goodbye song.
Making out isn't a tragedy.
Well, I think it means
the happy ending isn't actually real.
In La Traviata, the aria is sung
just before the lovers part ways,
and then the woman dies.
So
the ending she believes to be true
was only a delusion?
In reality, she'll never, ever be happy?
It's also wrong to believe
you'll never, ever be happy.
You said it's impossible for her. Right?
Do Ra-mi, you have to let go of this
if you want a happy ending
that exists for real.
To finally get a happy ending,
I'll have to stop
meeting you this way, honey.
This setup is part of her delusion.
How is this an aspect of her delusion?
I told you I was doing what she really
wanted to do, but couldn't.
Honey, I keep coming to see you…
because she really wants to see you.
That's the truth.
She still has feelings for you.
You said from the start
that you've been manifesting because
she's afraid her secret
will be discovered.
That's right.
And it's you, Joo Ho-jin.
She's mostly afraid
that you'll find out the truth.
Then, I'm one of the reasons
you've appeared?
Let me also tell you another thing
Mu-hee could never, ever say to you.
As a kid,
she saw her mom and dad die,
even though she's always been pretending
she has no memory of it.
This is because…
…her mom murdered her dad,
then tried to kill her too.
She pretends she's forgotten everything,
but that's not true.
She knew
a child who witnessed
these horrible things
could never, ever find love.
That's why she became this crazy psycho.
She's terrified, walks on eggshells.
She thinks people hate her,
which has her go back and forth,
making up stupid lies.
She desperately wants to be loved,
then believes she never can be,
so she runs away.
She does have a crush on you too.
She pushed you away
'cause she didn't think she could do it,
but she wants you to keep liking her too.
Crazy psycho.
Ho-jin, you're a very kind, honest man…
with that pure heart of yours.
Leave this girl.
Then I can go away.
When you leave her…
and the painful delusion vanishes…
she'll be fine again.
That's our happy ending.
Just love me, dear Ho-jin.
Just like I love you.
Goodbye.
Every time I fall into your embrace
I feel like
It's the place
I've always wished and dreamed of
Something's changed
When you smile
I would stay forever and more
CAN THIS LOVE BE TRANSLATED?
Until you find out…
I'm not hiding anymore…
Someday…
When you're calling my name
There's only you and me
Just like my dreams come true…
Every time I fall into your embrace
I feel like
It's the place
I've always wished and dreamed of…