We're here.
Come down here.
Make sure we have all the tools.
We'll move in right away.
Photograph the scene from all angles.
Check for other bone fragments
once the water drains.
There's no remaining soft tissue,
so the cause of death is unknown.
Still, there are no fractures
or signs of homicide.
Judging by the pelvic bone,
I'd say it's a male
in his twenties or thirties.
- Did you say male?
- Yes.
JOHN DOE
"Twenties or thirties…"
- Kang Ji-hwon.
- Kang.
Hey, there's broken glass here.
Find all possible DNA to compare.
- Yes, sir.
Viagra?
Recently, we found a body in the sewers
with its face horribly mutilated.
The victim's name is Sarah Kim.
Due to the lack of defensive wounds,
we think the victim knew her attacker.
FUCK IT. I LOVE YOU
MY LOVE DAMNED IT ALL
The two of you were quite serious,
weren't you?
I believe you have a lot to tell me.
When did you get that scratch
on your hand?
Mr. Kang Ji-hwon.
No secret can stay hidden forever.
I…
I killed her.
One more shot!
Let's do one more.
That's weak!
Come on, let's go!
- Damn.
- Nice.
Eun-jae was my whale.
Wait, not Mok Ga-hui?
No, Kim Eun-jae.
That's Sarah Kim's Korean name.
Hang on.
Mok Ga-hui?
Mok Ga-hui? Is that her real name?
That wasn't her birth name either.
Everything on her résumé was fake.
She cleverly used the fact
that résumés aren't properly checked.
It's likely
she used similar tactics
to get close to you.
No, that wasn't the case.
I approached her first.
Goodness.
We have a new face.
Your name?
Kim Eun-jae.
Nice to meet you. I'm Kang Ji-hwon.
That's "hwon," not "won."
I heard you use the names of people
you really hate as your aliases here.
Is that true?
Where on earth did you hear that?
So, who is Kang Ji-hwon?
I feel bad for the poor guy.
It's my real name.
Allow this "poor guy" to pour you a drink.
I only dealt with married women.
They tend to open their wallets and hearts
more readily than single women.
Wait. Are you saying…
Yes.
Eun-jae
was married.
Are you new to this scene?
It's all a bit awkward, right?
THE ART OF SARAH
KIM EUN-JAE
FOUND YOUR CAR KEYS
CALL ME. JI-HWON
- Nothing yet?
- I can't even enjoy my cig.
I'm smoking. Why eat here?
- For fuck's sake.
- Damn it!
What's with the attitude, you fucker?
Leave him alone.
He tried hard to con this woman,
but got rejected.
This guy's a total has-been now.
Shut the fuck up!
Don't.
- Damn, what a temper.
- Relax.
Let go.
I NEED YOUR HELP
- What the…
- Damn.
Over here.
Take them off.
What? Here?
Your shoes.
Right, my shoes.
Man, did you come out in a hurry?
Here you go.
Be sure to pay me double
for the off-premises fee.
And if you wanted me for--
- Run.
- Wait, where?
Did you run away from home
just to have tteokbokki?
My husband put me on a strict diet.
I can't eat stuff like this.
What does your husband do?
Do you know Hong Seong-sin?
Hong Seong-sin?
How could I not know that name?
Detective, half the guys in this game
owe that prick money.
And the other half
are still paying him back.
What about you?
How much debt did you have?
Well…
Do I have to share
personal stuff like that?
Why are you even married
to a piece of trash like that?
Has he got something on you?
He's a man who needs no explanation.
And when I'm with him,
I no longer need one either.
Why did you drop honorifics?
You look younger than me.
I was born in '92.
I was born in '86.
Come on. Don't lie.
You can't fool me. I don't know much,
but I never get a woman's age wrong.
What do you know about women?
A woman might take years off,
but she'll never add them.
Do you really think I don't know women?
Did you really call me out at this hour
just to eat tteokbokki?
Maybe you wanted to hook up
with a younger guy?
You sound so cheap.
Acting coy would be a misfit move
in this industry.
You were the only one I could contact.
CONTACTS
HUSBAND, CAR KEYS
Ma'am, please give him the change.
- Where are you going?
- Home.
Like now? Why?
Damn, she's a real misfit.
She does think I'm cheap.
I'm a very classy…
Change, please.
Here you go. Please come again.
Wait for me!
Seriously.
CAR KEYS:
PORK BELLY?
HEADING OUT NOW, ICED AMERICANO?
JUST ARRIVED, I'M HERE
Wanna run away with me?
I'm joking.
I won't ask you for money,
so stay another hour with me.
Take it.
What's this?
Hey, this is…
No, this is way too much
for being a runaway's friend.
Your thoughtfulness is enough.
Just take the watch.
You can exchange it if you want.
- Damn prick.
- Damn it!
Bring the money while I'm asking nicely.
For fuck's sake.
That's when it began.
All I did was pour drinks…
WHALE 3
…but for the first time,
I began to pour my heart into the work.
KIM EUN-JAE
Slow down. Don't eat so fast.
Here.
Wait a minute.
What is all this?
- It's nothing.
- No, wait. Are you…
I had enough junkies around me…
Hey, this is…
…to know what they were.
They were track marks.
And those bruises on her
pulled the trigger.
It was him, wasn't it?
Is that fucker making you shoot up,
on top of everything?
- It's not like that.
- Don't give me that crap. This is…
How can you even eat right now?
Why do you live like this?
Are you a fucking idiot?
And that fucker?
Want me to kill him for you?
What?
That fucker…
I really am gonna kill him.
KIM EUN-JAE:
NOW
With him dead,
Eun-jae would inherit his entire fortune.
I thought…
that was the only way
for everyone to be happy.
Is that when you killed Hong Seong-sin?
No.
I couldn't kill him.
Run.
Eun-jae!
Careful now.
Here we are.
I thought I had run far away,
but I realized I had gone nowhere.
I thought the first snow had arrived,
but it was Eun-jae.
I NEED YOUR HELP
Eun-jae had changed a lot
in just a few years,
from the way she dressed and spoke
to her personality.
She even had a different name.
Sarah Kim.
After what happened,
she said she ran like hell
as soon as she came to.
She said she was using an English name
to keep her husband from finding her
and was going to start a whole new life.
She told me
that once Boudoir got established,
she wanted me to manage one of its stores.
So she asked me
to help get it established.
At the time, the person
Eun-jae asked me to entertain was…
- Choi Chae-u.
- You believed those empty words?
- You really expect me to believe that?
- Look.
I had no choice but to believe her.
You see, we had…
promised to have a future together.
Nice house.
Or maybe it's nice to have money.
I'm glad you like it.
Take it. It's a gift.
Okay.
I'll visit often.
The house, not the key.
- I put the contract in your name.
- What?
You did what?
Let's start fresh
and forget all about the past.
They say this place gets so sunny
you don't need an alarm.
We can now sleep at night and wake up
in the morning like everyone else.
Why are you so quiet?
Listen.
Hold on.
About those car keys back then…
Actually, I stole them.
I know.
You knew?
I guess even prestigious Oxford
doesn't teach you to watch out for men.
I mean, after Hong Seong-sin,
you had to choose me of all people.
People are so strange.
They claim that love transcends
status, borders, age, and gender,
but if you fall in love like that,
they'll say it isn't real.
I'm ready to handle anything.
What about you?
Yes, me too.
Whatever it takes.
I can do anything you say.
What can I do to help?
Do you know where people lie the most?
In bed.
I thought you were going to quit smoking.
The cessation pills don't agree with me.
Oh, right.
Chairwoman Shin of GL picked me.
She wants me to come
to Seongbuk-dong tomorrow.
So?
So…
I told her I quit.
You're responsible, you know.
I was forced into unemployment.
I'll get you a position at the office.
Start coming in soon.
Thank you for visiting our humble store.
Oh my God!
Everyone out!
- Now.
- Everyone leave. Now!
You too.
Thank you, Chairwoman.
You know what?
I've never seen the sun once
in all the time I've lived here.
A cold snap is coming
on the day of the party.
I wanted to hold the first part outdoors.
Hey, I…
want to stop.
I'm sick of everything.
Boudoir has really established itself now.
I'm going to tell Choi Chae-u
that I'm quitting.
Who are you to decide that?
- Kim Eun-jae.
- Sarah Kim.
Call me Sarah Kim.
Yes, someone left something at my door.
Could you check the visitor log for me?
- One moment. Apartment 1102, right?
- Yes.
The only visitor on the log today
is Sarah Kim.
Sarah Kim?
Yes, Sarah Kim.
WHALE 2
Hey.
Were you sleeping?
Yes, I wanted to ask you something.
Is your husband the president
of the Oxbridge alumni association?
Then can you look up an alumnus for me?
The name is Sarah Kim.
Born in '86.
That was
a blatant yet subtle threat.
She knew that with me knee-deep
in this mess,
I couldn't report it or do anything.
Why do you think she went to such lengths?
She probably needed me
to lure Choi Chae-u.
If she had even pretended to deceive me,
I would've played along till the end.
Just as I'd pretended to love her…
but ended up actually falling for her.
But she knows that.
She knew how I felt, and she still did it.
Fuck!
How dare you fool me, bitch!
Fuck.
Fuck!
Hong Seong-sin.
Find out his number for me.
Back then, I told Hong Seong-sin
that Eun-jae and I had conspired
to kill him for his money…
and that he'd married a fucking fraud.
I told him everything.
And then,
a few days later,
I saw on the news
that an unidentified body was found
in the sewer.
I knew as soon as I saw it.
"It's Eun-jae."
Are you saying Hong Seong-sin
killed Sarah Kim?
No.
No, I killed her.
I killed Kim Eun-jae and Sarah Kim.
I killed them both!
INTERROGATION IN PROGRESS
I guess it literally was "blind love."
Was it?
He acted exactly like a man
who makes a living calling a con "love."
Didn't you see his eyes earlier?
If that was acting,
then sincerity doesn't exist.
Didn't you notice
he was making statements in his favor?
Kang Ji-hwon is the sole beneficiary
of this scam,
making him at least an accessory.
He's lost too much
to say he has gained financially.
That can't be said for a man
draped head to toe in luxury goods
gifted by whales.
"I only did as I was told.
I was impaired due to intoxication."
"I'm the victim."
All things typically said by criminals.
Thank you.
I was suffering from kidney failure.
I found out
my kidneys were completely shot
only after my kidneys
were completely shot.
The doctors told me
a kidney transplant was my only option.
However,
my siblings from the same mother,
my ex-wife, my estranged children,
and even my lifelong friend of 40 years
all refused to donate a kidney to me.
I was drowning myself in alcohol
like there was no tomorrow.
That's when we met.
I met her when she was working
under the name "Du-a."
Eun-jae, that is.
- I can't stand the sight of you. Get out!
- Hurry up! Come on!
What are you doing?
Well…
It's past our closing time.
I thought you should settle the bill.
Get lost.
Keep it.
Thank you.
Why's a rich man living like this?
I said get lost.
Let me at least make up for the watch.
So I told her about how I had lived
and how I was dying.
I told her everything.
I guess I just wanted
to talk to anyone who would listen.
I'll be your donor.
Give me 500 million won in return.
You want to do an organ trade?
I'm saying we should fake a marriage.
But how can I trust you?
You can pay me afterward.
And just like that,
Du-a jumped headfirst into my dull life,
where I had been only waiting to die.
RESIDENT REGISTRATION CARD
KIM EUN-JAE
Use that one.
The first thing we did
was give her a new identity.
"Kim Eun-jae."
MARRIAGE REGISTRATION FORM
"Kim Eun-jae." I gave her that name.
That was how we became husband and wife.
That was how we began a marriage
without love, respect,
reverence, truth, duty, or vows.
Since the law required
at least one year of legal marriage
for organ transplants between spouses,
the fake marriage
was intended to last two years.
Our age difference was abnormal
in everyone's eyes,
and even I would've found
the sudden marriage suspicious.
"Oxford"?
If someone asks you about your major,
just say you had your thesis ghostwritten.
Don't clumsily fake it.
That might just rub people the wrong way.
It means I'm stupid and dishonest.
People will look past your ignorance
and only remember your wealth,
which bought you an Oxford degree.
They will be surprised by your frankness
rather than your dishonesty.
"The woman who secured an Oxford degree
by having her thesis ghostwritten."
That one sentence
will engrave you in people's minds
as a genuine, talented, and wealthy woman.
If you know so much,
why don't you manage your reputation?
You're notorious
for being a ruthless loan shark.
Because that is precisely what I want.
Now go shopping for yourself
so you don't look like a bar hostess.
Stay still.
KIM EUN-JAE - F
Press down firmly without rubbing.
When I was young,
a friend used to constantly tease me
about my family's loan business.
One day, that jerk came to see me,
now the CEO of a failing company.
He needed a loan.
What do you think I did?
Did you not lend it to him?
I lent him so much
he could never repay it in his lifetime.
It was enough for him to die,
leaving his son the debt to pay.
One day, the son brought me
that pine tree,
saying he'd dug it up
from his father's grave.
He said it would easily be worth
over 500 million won.
I don't know what got into me at the time,
but I wrote off the rest of his debt
in exchange for that one pine tree.
That was the only act of kindness
I ever showed.
How is that…
an act of kindness?
Because a loan shark gave up
being a loan shark.
I wouldn't have done that.
I'd promise,
but I wouldn't lend them anything.
Then I can get the most painful revenge
without spending a dime.
Because a glimpse of hope
is far more agonizing
than continuous misfortune.
It appears…
you should be the loan shark, not me.
I will repay you double soon.
By the way, why do you look so unwell?
Is your young wife
draining all your energy?
I'm just old too.
You need to come to your senses, Mr. Hong.
Kids these days are very crafty.
I extort money for a living.
Do you think anyone will extort me?
I've already had my will notarized.
Of course.
Excuse me.
I brought some tea.
To appear legitimate and genuine,
we needed a story
that would dispel any doubts about us.
Just do as we practiced.
Today's goal is to make credible people
witness to our relationship.
Understood.
Don't try too hard to impress them.
You'll look desperate.
Do I look desperate?
You're asking me if you seem desperate
with desperation.
Only because you see me that way.
Instead, we build an underwater tunnel
and operate a KTX line
connecting Seoul and Jeju.
But will the airport authorities…
Not a single person there
questioned Eun-jae's background
and origins.
- Wow!
- When will you break ground?
All right.
I think that man is a con artist.
Last time, he said he was an equestrian.
Today, he says
he has swum across the Korea Strait.
I bet next time,
he'll say he was an expert shooter.
Actually,
I saw you lend him
a large sum of money last time.
Maybe you should run
a proper background check.
You think so?
A businessman is not so different
to a con artist.
But there is one thing
that sets him apart.
Do you know what?
He may begin with a bluff,
but he never ends with one.
What are you doing?
You need to undergo dialysis
every six hours.
I know you hate appearing weak,
but don't do that with me too.
- Your buttons. Let me--
- I'll do it. Get out!
You're trembling.
Before I knew it, Eun-jae had become
someone who knew me better
than I knew myself.
Earlier at the party,
what did you say
to make everyone laugh like that?
My husband's flaws.
It seems you had fun.
It made me sad…
because it was all fake.
Well, not everything.
You know your real self comes out
when you let your guard down, right?
And you seem even less aware
that people like that side of you more.
That's the problem.
Even I'm starting to feel confused
about where the lies end…
and the truth begins.
Do you regret it?
Living with you made me realize
that wealth is not a state of being
but a feeling.
It would've been better…
if I had never experienced this feeling.
Eun-jae.
Eun-jae!
I'll call an ambulance. Hang in there.
Did you ask me if I regret it?
I don't.
What should I do?
I think I want to keep living
as Kim Eun-jae.
Eun-jae!
How are you feeling?
Are my kidneys okay?
Do you know the first thing Eun-jae said
when she regained consciousness?
Are my kidneys okay?
Keep the funeral simple.
Cremate the body
and scatter the ashes in my hometown.
And lastly,
I bequeath my entire fortune…
to my wife, Kim Eun-jae.
Your staff is outside.
They've been waiting a while
to greet you in person.
I'm just going to drop by the house
and bring some things too.
Get someone to do it.
I'm feeling stuffy
just being in the hospital.
I'll be back soon.
Okay.
Okay, relax. That's a good girl.
What are you waiting for?
Hurry up. Go make some money.
The day before the operation,
I found out who Eun-jae really was.
She had ended up working at a hostess bar
because she owed money to loan sharks.
CHAIRMAN HONG SEONG-SIN
And that they work for a place I run
called The One Capital.
She was a bitch who borrowed money
from The One Capital about two years ago.
We went to some department store
to press her for the money once,
but we couldn't reach her after that.
Only to turn up here.
She never came by the house.
Looks like the bitch ran already.
I'd promise,
but I wouldn't lend them anything.
Then I can get the most painful revenge
without spending a dime.
Because a glimpse of hope
is far more agonizing
than continuous misfortune.
CHAIRMAN
What happened?
We got her.
It appears she's been planning
to stow away on a boat for months.
She intentionally got close to you
to con you from the very start.
Let her go.
Sir?
I haven't lost anything.
I was the one who had agreed
to be fooled from the start…
so how is that a con?
They say you change
when it's time for you to die.
I started to think
this was karma coming back to me.
Why?
You're awake.
Why did you give me the transplant?
If you had left me to die…
you could've had the entire fortune
to yourself.
I'll just wait a bit longer and get it.
It doesn't seem
like I'll have to wait long.
I wonder
if Eun-jae felt the same way I did.
I can't say for sure.
Go back to sleep. I'll just finish…
I'm certain about one thing.
For that moment, at least,
the con artist gave up being a con artist.
KIM EUN-JAE
And then she vanished,
like she never existed in the first place.
Along with a pine tree
worth 500 million won.
I'll call the landscaping company
and have it restored by today.
No, let's leave it this way.
Did she really
go through with the transplant?
If not, how else would I still be alive?
MEDICAL RECORDS
ORGAN DONATION CONSENT
DONOR - KIM EUN-JAE
RECIPIENT - HONG SEONG-SIN
There weren't any.
There were no signs of surgery
on the body.
Sarah Kim is alive.
SEOUL METROPOLITAN POLICE AGENCY
PRESS CONFERENCE
This is Park Mu-gyeong
of the Seoul Violent Crimes Unit.
We will now begin the press conference.
Over the years, the suspect has changed
her name, age,
nationality, job, and education,
living under
at least three false identities.
SEOUL METROPOLITAN POLICE
Due to the crime's severity,
a public wanted notice has been issued.
- It is to be effective immediately.
- The one choice
- If you have any information, we urge you.
- It will change your life
Please contact
the Seoul Violent Crimes Unit.
The one choice
Do you know when we find people
who vanish voluntarily?
When they decide to return.
Subtitle translation by: Yung Un Choi