LOVE NEXT DOOR
SEOUL OLYMPIC SWIMMING POOL
Seung-hyo, is your mom here?
Wasn't she coming to Korea for the match?
No, something urgent came up,
so she couldn't make it.
Is that so? What about your dad?
A lot of his patients need critical care,
so he couldn't leave the hospital.
They're important.
You get it, right?
- Yes, sir.
- Okay.
Let's focus on the meet.
You'll make the national team if you win.
The 200-meter freestyle finals
will begin shortly.
Let's go!
HYEREUNG HIGH SCHOOL SWIM TEAM
In lane 8, Choi Seung-hyo
from Hyereung High School.
You can do it, Seung-hyo!
Choi Seung-hyo from Hyereung High
in lane 8! Let's go!
What on earth? Why is she here?
Hey, Seung-hyo! Over here!
- Over here!
- Please, stop calling my name.
Let's go, Seung-hyo! Crush them!
Leave them in the dust!
Jeez, Seok-ryu.
If you don't win,
don't even think of coming back home!
You can do it!
Take your marks.
Let's go!
Go!
You're doing great!
Come on!
Let's go!
CHOI SEUNG-HYO
SIXTH
It's okay! Keep going!
Go, go, go!
Hey!
Wow.
She seriously must be crazy.
Wow, seriously?
Do you know what time it is?
I don't.
Look at your watch if you're so curious.
You think I'm asking for the time?
- Don't you get what's implied?
- Gosh, he's loud.
College entrance exams were ages ago.
What's with the comprehension questions?
It's 3:00 a.m.
Even the birds and lambs are asleep.
So why am I hearing your screams?
Goodness, poor Seung-hyo.
Did I wake our precious baby?
Don't do that.
Our baby can't sleep?
Do you want me to sing you a lullaby?
Hey, stop talking like that.
Then, go back inside and sleep
if you don't want to hear it.
You're so loud.
Hey, in that movie,
the curly-haired one is the ghost.
Hey, did you just say a spoiler?
That's so unethical!
How could you reveal a spoiler?
This isn't The Sixth Sense!
Curly-haired?
I'll make sure you don't sleep tonight!
You have serious character issues.
Hey! Keep going! Just a little more!
You're doing great! Let's go!
Go all the way!
FIRST PLACE
CHOI SEUNG-HYO
Hey, you came in first!
You did great!
Great job!
EPISODE 3
STOP LINE
She's quiet now that it's morning.
Seung-hyo, you're up early.
- Yes.
- I didn't see you come in.
Did you work late?
- Yes.
- How worrisome.
My son's working so hard.
It's fine.
Come down after you wash.
Let's have breakfast.
I wanted to make some jambon-beurre.
But I didn't have the right ingredients.
We used to eat it at times in France.
Do you remember?
No, I don't.
Right? You were so young.
Still, since we're together…
It's nice to eat together.
I never imagined you'd come back
to live here with us.
It's close to work. That's all it is.
Did you clear out your studio apartment?
Yes, building an office building
wasn't easy.
If it's about money,
you should've told me.
Architecture is a business too.
Don't overdo it.
Yes, sir.
Always be careful on site too.
We get a lot of injured workers in the ER.
I will.
Thanks for breakfast.
This toast tastes awful.
I'll buy some baguettes
and butter for tomorrow.
There's no need.
I usually don't eat breakfast.
Really?
When are you being assigned?
You asked the same question as your dad.
Why? Do you want me to leave again?
It's not that…
You don't like staying in Korea
for long periods.
Thank you for breakfast.
I'm off to work.
Gosh, you scared me.
Did you deliberately set off
an explosion at me?
What? No, it's a party popper
from Hyeong-chan's birthday party.
No, that's an explosive device.
Don't you know people have died
from those things?
An architect
who disregards safety is trouble.
I'm the one who's troubled.
I'm getting an earful
for congratulating you.
Congratulate me for what?
Hey, Seung-hyo! We did it!
Mr. Yoon will tell you.
What is it? What's going on?
We can finally breathe.
We got a huge offer.
A term reserved
for only the top 1% of Korea.
A prestigious retirement community.
Danyeong Medical Foundation
is partnering with YR Group to build it,
and they came
directly to us to oversee it.
She said something would happen
in the latter half of the year.
- Hye-ran was right.
- Your wife went to a fortune teller?
Yeah. It was tarot cards this time.
We're riding
on the colossal wheels of fortune.
POMEGRANATE TREE
The leaves look a bit dry.
You're worried
about that measly plant right now?
- Someone cast a curse.
- What?
Our company's fate rests on it.
We'll shut down if it withers.
Goodness. Why didn't you water it?
No, never mind.
Can someone go
and buy some plant nutrients?
You're such a slave to superstitions.
That's how desperate I am.
If this deal goes through,
we won't have to worry about anything
for a while! We have to risk it all!
I want to do this.
Of course. But we can't just do it.
We have to do it well.
I want to do it.
I want to do it too.
I want to do it so badly!
No, I want to see you do it!
HYEREUNG HIGH GYM REMODELING
AND EXPANSION DESIGN COMPETITION
Mom.
Mom?
Is no one home?
I made curry. Heat it up and eat it.
Why is she suddenly being so sweet?
A hundred rolls of kimbap.
Where did this incredible order come from?
I don't know.
They're snacks for some TV shoot.
They'll pick them up at 6:00 p.m.
Is that so?
I'll ask what they're shooting later.
So you've decided to leave Seok-ryu be?
- Yeah.
- Really?
What for?
It's called the Romeo and Juliet effect.
They say love becomes more intense
the more the parents interfere.
What does that have to do with this?
Keep listening.
It's an absolute truth that applies
to other areas as well, not just love.
The more parents oppose
and try to control their child,
the more the child rebels.
Yeah, you're right.
You made a good choice.
You should be as gentle
when rolling kimbap too.
If you try to keep things in by force,
the sides…
Seok-ryu won't last long.
How do you know that?
Not just anyone can be unemployed.
She's been diligent her whole life.
She'll end up caving in on her own
with a slight nudge.
I'm waiting for that moment.
It'll come soon.
We need to make 100. How can you eat that?
It's so good. I'm just tasting it.
- Is it good?
- Yeah.
Hurry up!
Done.
BAE SEOK-RYU'S UNEMPLOYED SCHEDULE
PLAY GAMES
Nice.
SPACE OUT
I'd be so good at that.
WATCH TV
They're not doing it right.
You can't do it like that.
TAKE A NAP
- What's up?
- I'm busy. Bye.
Wait. I didn't even tell you why I called.
What if it's important?
What is it?
The one with straight hair was the ghost.
I'm hanging up.
Wait! It's important.
- Let's go read comic books.
- You may not know this.
But people with jobs work on weekdays.
Hey, I didn't mean now.
I plan to be there
from 6:00 p.m. to 8:00 p.m.
Come when you get off work.
No. I'm hanging up now.
Heartless jerk.
Forget it. I have other friends.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
Hey!
My best friend.
My very close and long-time friend!
What's with all the flattery?
I didn't even get most of it.
Mo-eum, you're so gloomy.
Did you have a hard day?
Seok-ryu, you're so cheerful.
Did you have fun doing nothing?
Of course.
What do you want to read?
I got something from every genre.
Romance? Martial arts? Shonen manga?
They all sound boring.
FOR ADULTS ONLY
I want something red.
I see.
We're in a public space
in my neighborhood.
I've never seen anyone so brave.
Right?
I took a peek earlier.
See Rose of Bliss?
It looked pretty good.
Grab it when no one's watching.
Pass it to me when you're done.
Okay? Go.
Now. No one's watching.
- Right now.
- Seok-ryu?
That's not the "red" I was talking about.
Something with fresh blood and torn flesh!
Things like that.
Like those.
That type of red? You could've told me.
Hello.
Your other best friend's here.
Nope. As of today, he's out.
He's been disqualified.
You won't even say hi?
You came. You said you wouldn't.
I didn't come for you.
There's a book I wanted to read.
Really? What book is it?
Well… Here it is. This is what I wanted.
The book you wanted…
was "Princess"?
Wow.
What?
You have a problem with my tastes?
No, I have no prejudices.
But you liked tragic love stories
and sad endings?
Yeah, he does.
How do you know that?
I just do.
A weirdo next to an oddball.
You two should stick together.
You'll bother less people that way.
He picks a fight as soon as he comes.
So annoying.
What should we do now?
What do you think? Let's go home.
No, I have free time outside
from 8:00 p.m. to 10:00 p.m.
You planned out your free time too?
Old habits die hard. What a tiring life.
What? What's wrong with that?
I might as well have fun
in a planned and systematic way.
On that note, how about some board games?
Next time. I have to go home and study.
Study for what?
Powerboat certification.
A boat license? You want drive a boat?
No, I developed an interest
in something recently.
But it's required.
I still have work left.
I have to get back to the office.
What is this?
Are you saying you're both leaving me?
Is this really the end?
Bye. Call me tomorrow.
Don't call me.
Come on.
Yeah, fine! You loyal citizens.
You pillars of industry!
The future of Korea depends on you!
Keep up the great work!
What do I do by myself?
Okay. Here's your morning coffee.
Thank you.
Sure. There you go. It's better with that.
That's right.
The sweetness is really getting
my blood pumping.
Don't you have a coffee machine
or a pour over set?
If she did,
this wouldn't be a real estate office.
- My back hurts.
- Jeez.
- Jae-suk, give me that cushion.
- Just take it yourself.
She doesn't lift a finger.
Good morning!
- Hey.
- What's with the flowers?
I bought them from a flower shop
after taking the subway.
Pretty, right?
- Gosh.
- They are!
My husband never buys me anything
this pretty.
Nor do my kids. So what can I do?
I'll buy them for others.
- Thanks so much.
- Pretty, right?
I can't remember
the last time I got flowers.
- Wait, I want to take a picture.
- Sure.
- They're lavenders.
- Send it to me.
- Okay.
- So fragrant.
- Move your face, Jae-suk.
- This smells so nice.
Right?
Move your face, Jae-suk.
Listen while you look at these.
- There!
- I have a matter to bring up.
Let's change the name of our group.
- Why?
- You want to change our group's name?
Yeah. You remember how nasty
the Hee Sisters were?
- Yeah.
- The worst.
I don't want to be associated with them,
and our name doesn't help.
Let's change it
to something really nice this time!
Like what?
You know,
something refined and elegant.
Should we translate Suk to English?
Hye-suk, what's "suk" in English?
I don't know.
You're a diplomat. You don't know?
- How can I know the names of plants?
- Seriously?
- How can you ask that?
- Search on your phone.
Wait. Let me search it.
Wait. They don't eat it outside of Korea?
- I don't think so.
- I've never heard of it.
Hey, I found it.
- What is it?
- Mugwort.
- Mug… What?
Wort. Like this.
Are you barking?
- It's worse than "mug cup."
- What?
No, it doesn't roll off the tongue.
But isn't mugwort a type of herb too?
- Yeah.
And what's the ultimate herb?
Lavender!
You have to be quick!
It's settled! Lavender.
NA MI-SUK
LIVE WITH FRAGRANCE
- Hey, Dad?
- Yeah?
How do you live with fragrance?
I don't know.
Ask your mom when she gets here.
She must be getting old. Take a look.
She put flowers as her profile picture.
- Lavenders.
- Saying your mom's old behind her back?
This is why I can't leave you two alone.
You're so violent.
I wasn't talking behind your back.
I just stated a fact.
We're growing old together.
Just keep quiet.
Why are you making so many?
We still have a way to go.
We need to make 100.
- A hundred?
- Yeah.
A TV production crew came
and bought them before.
They liked them and ordered again.
Really?
I guess I have no choice.
I should help out.
Hey!
Forget it. What can you do?
Don't get in the way.
Just eat some kimbap.
Or have tteokbokki.
- Do you want some?
- No, you're busy.
Welcome…
- Welcome!
- Hello.
Ms. Yu!
Goodness. Is that you, Seok-ryu?
Wow! You haven't changed at all.
I knew it was you
as soon as you walked in. Wow!
Mom, my homeroom teacher from high school.
- Goodness!
- Hello, Ms. Yu!
I'm so sorry I didn't recognize you.
No, it's fine.
I only realized after seeing Seok-ryu.
I forgot her parents ran this shop.
What brings you here?
I came to order food.
Can I get 20 orders of tteokbokki
and 20 orders of sundae?
- Of course.
- Goodness.
We'd be so grateful.
But it's so much.
Can you take them by yourself?
I'll help her.
No, I'll go. You're busy.
- You will?
- Just a moment.
- Okay.
- Honey.
- I'll do that.
- Just a moment.
- Okay, hurry.
- Hey.
Get Ms. Yu a drink.
Thanks for delivering this for me.
Of course.
Wow, the school hasn't changed at all.
It's always the same here.
Maybe that's why I keep forgetting
that time's passing.
It's amazing.
I can't believe you're the principal now.
You too.
You were so childish.
I can't believe you're all grown up now.
Are you visiting Korea
for a short while? A vacation?
What?
I heard you work at Greip.
Yeah…
I was so happy when I heard that.
And I wasn't the only one.
All the teachers still talk about you.
You were so capable and smart.
A renowned figure of Hyereung High School.
Look, another renowned figure
of Hyereung High School.
What?
You applied for the gym remodeling
and new building design competition?
Yeah, today's the site briefing
for the participating companies.
I had my doubts
when I saw a familiar name on the list.
This is great.
It would mean so much if you did it.
Ms. Yu.
Doesn't that mean he shouldn't
be sitting here with you right now?
He technically has academic ties.
It violates fairness.
You haven't changed.
Experts from the education department
will do the evaluations.
I have no authority.
Nice try.
Rats.
It's been so long.
Are you free this afternoon?
Of course.
I'm sorry.
I missed a few things
from the site visit earlier.
I need to look more thoroughly.
Is that so? That's too bad.
I'll have to ask Seok-ryu then.
Since you're here, talk to the students.
A chat with an alumnus.
Excuse me? Me?
I think you'll set a good example.
I bet the students will be excited
to hear you work at Greip.
But I…
I'll get going then.
Okay, I know you're busy. Thanks.
I'll wish you luck.
Thank you.
Are you okay with meeting the students?
Sure.
This is Bae Seok-ryu.
She's a graduate of our school.
She works at Greip in the US.
- Greip?
- That's cool!
I hope her energy rubs off on you.
This old boomer will leave,
so talk freely.
- Yes, ma'am!
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
Hello, I'm Bae Seok-ryu.
This was actually came together
very suddenly,
so I didn't prepare anything.
You can ask me questions if you want.
I'll answer them.
What college did you go to?
I was accepted to Hanguk University
after I graduating.
After attending for a year,
I studied abroad in the US.
I enrolled at UC Berkkeley and graduated.
Does that mean your family's rich?
Not at all.
A friend was preparing to study abroad.
I wanted to study English, too,
so we prepared together.
After I was accepted,
I received a scholarship for four years.
That's how I went.
- That's nuts.
- Wow.
- Wait…
- Yes?
What do you do at Greip?
It's called a product manager.
I'm responsible for overseeing
and managing projects
from their planning stage
to the end result.
Was being a product manager
always your dream?
I don't know. I don't think so.
Then, what was your dream?
- My dream?
- Yes.
When you were in high school,
what did you want to be?
Hey, Seok-ryu.
There you go ignoring me again.
Have you had lunch?
Don't talk to me. I want peace and quiet.
Then, quietly come with me.
Later.
We have to go now.
Says who? I don't want to go.
Come with me!
Are you insane?
How dare you grab a woman by the neck?
How could you be so thoughtless?
Speak for yourself. Are you insane?
You're no woman.
Of course, I'm a woman.
Am I a man? What am I then?
You are…
almost gender neutral.
Do you want to die today?
- You want to be buried behind the school?
- Let's go then.
- What?
- Let's go.
I'm sure it was around here.
You've been saying that for 30 minutes.
Why are we looking for this?
We agreed to take it out after ten years.
It's way past that deadline.
I know.
We forgot about that time capsule.
What's so important about it?
I don't even remember what I put in there.
Hey, you're the one who wanted to do it.
I think it was a letter.
"A letter to me in ten years."
I must've been crazy.
That millennial sentiment is awful.
Forget it. Don't look for it.
Let's keep it deep in there.
Let's hope it's found a billion years
from now like a dinosaur egg!
No, it'd still be embarrassing.
The Seok-ryu I know would let curiosity
overcome her embarrassment.
Aren't you curious about it?
I'm sure it's full
of dazzling and innocent words.
But so what? The reality is
we're just digging really hard.
Hey, anyone can tell
that you're digging half-heartedly.
It was around here.
Why did you do that earlier?
Do what?
I acted like I still worked at Greip.
Why did you play dumb too?
I shamelessly gave a lecture too.
You did work at Greip.
Was that a sham too?
Shut up.
That's good enough.
Your experience there was real.
I think that's enough
to give the kids good advice.
Why won't this dirt come off?
Stop pretending to be clean.
Just wash it off later.
I want to go home.
Hey, let's dig a little more.
I have a good feeling.
We're almost there.
I think it was between these trees.
You look for it.
Are you really going?
Seok-ryu!
Damn. I'm sure it was between these trees.
Seok-ryu, wait for me.
We were almost there.
Hey, Seok-ryu!
I'm home.
Hey!
What's all of this?
Gift boxes.
It's the neighbor's side job,
I asked for some.
Why would you do this?
What's wrong with your hand?
What's with the pain relief patch?
I think it was all the kimbap.
My wrist hurts.
I said I'd help.
You help by doing nothing,
you little brat.
I can put 100 more of these patches on.
I hope I can sell 1,000
or 10,000 more kimbap.
- Give it. I'll do it.
- Why would you do this?
This is my work.
Don't interfere with my pocket money.
Go do your work.
Hey, Dong-jin!
She's going nuts again.
You could've helped Mom
if you were at home!
What do you do all day in your room?
What's with you?
I went to work today
and came for my stuff.
- Mom!
- Yeah?
I have a private lesson. I'll be late.
Okay, have a good one.
- I'm off.
- Bye.
Dong-jin has his act together lately.
I didn't think
he'd do anything with his life.
He's living like a human being now.
It's a part-time job, but he gets paid.
The gym owner's helping him
become a personal trainer or whatever.
And he's exercising.
That's good.
Can I really keep doing this?
Aren't you going home?
A little later.
What are you doing?
Is this where you used to swim?
Yeah.
It is pretty old.
Is it still used today?
Sometimes, during PE class.
Take it easy. You know public facilities
don't make money and are full of red tape.
Tomorrow's client meeting
is what's important to us right now.
They're both important.
It may seem like you have a reputation
and we're doing well on the outside,
but you know this industry
isn't that easy.
A slight downturn
can even affect major corporations.
I know.
So turn off the pool,
and turn on the retirement community.
Are you pressuring me?
No, suggesting.
Also, our interview article for
The Chungwoo Daily was published.
It'll be in the paper tomorrow. Bye.
Bye.
BUILDING ARCHITECTURE AND PEOPLE
ATELIER IN'S CHOI SEUNG-HYO, YOON MYEONG-U
CHOI SEUNG-HYO WINS 200M FREESTYLE
AT 2007 SEOUL NATIONAL
SWIMMING CHAMPIONSHIPS
You scared me.
Why are you standing there?
This is why there are so many
strange rumors about you at work.
They say you have spiritual energy
or a third eye on your forehead.
They say I have a third eye
and can read people's minds.
I'm just farsighted due to old age.
How's the article? Do you hate it?
It's not bad.
The concept's good
and the content's clear.
So why doesn't it sound like a compliment?
You're getting sluggish.
Your writing shows
that there was no legwork.
Kang Dan-ho.
I thought you were a madman
when you first joined the company.
When you went around police stations,
you'd pack a backpack
and wouldn't come home for months.
So what? Am I too focused
on maintaining a work-life balance now?
I get it. I really do.
Let's be more proactive.
I'll keep that in mind.
- Are you putting it into action now?
- No, I'm going to buy rice cakes.
Not bad.
- Where's the patient?
- Over there.
When did his seizure start?
About ten to 15 minutes ago.
Do-hyeon suffers from status seizures.
Let's move him. Mo-eum, sit up front.
Okay.
Just a second.
What do we do? The road is blocked.
We're transporting an emergency patient.
Please cooperate.
A seizure over 20 minutes is dangerous.
Why aren't we moving?
We have a sick kid. Please, move.
What's that person doing?
I think he's trying to clear a path!
What?
I LOVE YOU, MUDFLATS
MUDFLAT GUARDIAN
Okay, that's good.
I LOVE YOU, MUDFLATS
A lot of retirement communities
have been popping up lately,
but the quality varies widely, doesn't it?
Thus, our cheapest unit will start
at two billion won for the deposit.
We plan to build
a luxurious retirement community.
The facility will be designed exclusively
for the top 1% of the senior population.
It'll be as beautiful as a landmark since
it'll be located in the heart of Seoul.
It'll be a place that not just anyone
can have access to
or even look at.
For example, the elderly
who ride the subway for free.
I love the subway.
I drove my car today,
but I ride it often
when I have to travel a lot.
I'll enjoy it in the future too.
I'm in favor of welfare policies
that provide transportation benefits
to the elderly.
That's great.
We weren't trying to be demeaning.
It was just a comparison.
- Yes, of course.
- Right.
But if it's going to be at a level
where people can't even look at it,
how high are you planning to build it?
People's necks will hurt.
Well, what Mr. Choi is trying to say
is what kind of concept
are you looking for?
Are you thinking of something
luxurious and extravagant?
Yes, that's why we prepared some drafts.
I'd like to mix in some of these designs.
Excuse me?
As you can see, these are works
by renowned international designers.
Our potential clients have spent
a lot of time overseas before.
Their tastes and standards are quite high.
So, ordinary domestic designs
won't be able to satisfy them.
So you're saying…
you don't trust our capabilities
and want us to replicate
verified designs, right?
Is that what you're requesting?
Excuse me, Mr. Choi?
It's an homage.
All artistic creation
is a form of imitation.
Nothing's ever really new.
No, this is clearly plagiarism.
You don't have to worry about that.
Everyone cries about plagiarism lately.
But when it's debated in court,
it's difficult to enforce penalties.
I can't do this.
Don't try to talk me into it.
I'll never change my mind.
Just hear me out first. I have a plan too.
What plan?
First, we pretend to play along.
Then, we change the design as we proceed.
We offer a new design.
Come on. The dates and budget are all set.
They can't stop midway either.
We'll gradually make changes
and integrate our style.
Sounds good, right?
So you want to retouch
a plagiarized design!
Think of it as a reference.
Are you joking?
Myeong-u.
I know that architecture can't be done
without a client,
I can't work with people
who have that mindset.
With that kind of attitude,
we won't be able to do anything.
We'll have to deal with all sorts
of dirty, disgraceful things.
Is this how you'll act?
We built our office on a mountain of debt.
We have employees to take care of.
For their sake, I won't do it.
I want to preserve their pride
as architects.
You fool!
Do you know what they really need?
They don't need this abstract sentiment.
They need practical incentives.
Salary increases!
If we want to do that, we need money.
The company must do well.
So you want to sell your soul for money?
Is that really what's best
for our company?
Then, what about you?
Are you doing anything for the company?
You didn't care
about the retirement community!
- You're always looking at that pool!
- What?
A retirement community worth hundreds
of billions and a simple gym renovation!
One can't even compare with the other!
You brought personal feelings into work!
Myeong-u.
That damn pool reminded you of the past…
I mean… Look, Seung-hyo…
I'm heading out.
Wait…
Great job.
Great work.
Great work!
I'm glad Do-hyeon is doing better.
This is all thanks to you, Mr. Yeon.
It's my area of expertise.
When Se-yoon was first diagnosed
with epilepsy,
I thought my world was ending.
I guess it was a task given by the heavens
to turn us into better paramedics.
- Se-yoon's a gift from the heavens.
- Of course.
Who's the savior
that cleared the road for us?
- My ideal type.
- What?
I usually preferred people
who were like action stars.
But not anymore.
I like someone
who's stoic but full of drive.
The silent but determined type.
Wow. That's what's really sexy.
It's the first time she's describing
someone who's not Iron Man as sexy.
No, she said Spider-Man was sexy too.
The muscles through the tights…
What did it say on the back of his shirt?
Mud something?
"I love you, mudflats."
Yeah, that's right.
That means he's Mudflat Man.
Iron Man, Spider-Man, Mudflat Man.
Mudflat Man.
Did anyone see
Mudflat Man's license plate number?
Sorry. I should've checked.
Things were so hectic.
You should've checked.
How will I find him now?
Ms. Jung, this came for you.
I see. Thank you so much.
- What is this?
- What is it?
Rice cakes? I was getting hungry.
Can we eat some?
Just a second.
Let's see who sent them first.
Here it is.
- There's a card.
- There it is.
Okay.
Come on. Wait.
Thank you so much for last time.
I promised I'd reach out, didn't I?
Paramedic Jung Mo-eum.
What?
How did he know my name?
But why did he have to send rice cakes?
It's making me thirsty.
Give me some.
It's good.
Ms. Bae Seok-ryu?
- Hello.
It's nice to meet you. I'm Lee Jin-young.
- Thank you.
- Were you surprised by my call?
Not at all.
I could've come to meet you.
Thank you for coming to my neighborhood.
It was nothing.
I should come to meet someone
as esteemed as you.
But how did you get my number?
I've got a great radar.
I heard a talented person
came back to Korea,
so I started to ask around.
You flatter me. Thank you.
I mean it.
If you don't mind,
may I ask you why you quit Greip
and came back like this?
I had a personal reason to come home.
I see.
Then, how long did you work at Greip?
I joined the company in 2015,
and I officially quit last month.
So ten years?
No, I took a year off in the middle.
You did?
Yes, when I was 30.
Was that for personal reasons as well?
Yes.
Being 30 is like that.
I transferred jobs at that age.
Your career and portfolio
are very impressive.
I don't think it'll be a problem.
The position I want to offer
is at Serendipity…
Bae Seok-ryu.
Why are you dressed like that?
What's this?
Why do you keep showing up like this?
Because we live in the same neighborhood.
I'm not happy about it either.
Looks like we're on the same page.
Just be on your way.
Where are you going?
To wake up and smell the coffee.
How have you become
even more carefree?
You sure are bold.
- Want some?
- You drank from that.
- At least rinse it.
- You think I'm dirty?
You don't look clean.
- Come on.
- Sorry.
Seriously?
- Did you spray water on me?
- No, my hand slipped.
Just you wait.
To spray on me?
Our country has a water shortage.
This is for the Earth.
Where are you going now?
Why are you so unpredictable in everything
that you do?
I've lost muscle mass
lying around all day.
I have to regain it.
Do you have any muscle mass to lose?
You also never dress right
for any occasion.
It was right until now.
I met with a job recruiter earlier.
- Why?
- I don't know.
I don't know how she got my number.
But you know how capable
and talented I am.
What did she say?
She offered me a few positions.
GLO Korea and Serendipity.
The conditions were pretty good.
It's not as much as before,
but the pay is decent too.
Really?
It's similar to the work I did before.
I'll adjust quickly.
Great, right?
Do you want to do it?
- What?
- You want to do that kind of work again?
Work is just work.
- Does it matter if I want to do it or not?
- That's not right.
It's your work,
so you should do what you want.
How can people only do
what they want to do?
Why not?
Why does everyone compromise with reality?
You said you overheated and shut down.
- You said you wanted to reboot.
- Yeah, but…
This is the courage you mustered?
Returning to your old life?
- So what if I do? What's it to you?
- You think I don't know you?
When you want to do something,
your eyes light up
and stomp with excitement,
but I don't see any of that now.
Do I still look like a teenager to you?
Don't act like you know me
because we were friends as kids.
I just wish you'd find your real dream.
Dream? Hey! Dreams?
Do you think dreams can just be had?
Only those who have the luxury
to search for them can dream.
Those who get the chance to rise again
after failure can pursue their dreams.
You wouldn't know. You've always lived
in a Mediterranean climate.
A clear, mild, and perfect environment.
Me? Warmth is only momentary.
I'm stuck in Siberia most of the time.
The winds are biting cold.
It snows, rains, and hails.
- Do you know what that's like?
- I do know.
I've had winters like that too.
I thought you'd remember.
You scared me.
- Why are you here?
- I was waiting for you.
Are you in puberty?
What's with your voice?
It's your first day on the national team.
I'll let it slide.
What are you doing?
Did you do something weird again?
It's a gift.
This towel's a gift?
Yeah, open it up.
CHOI SEUNG-HYO, 2008 BEIJING OLYMPICS
GO FOR GOLD
Are you joking?
Isn't it cool?
I asked them to embroider it like that.
- Take it with you.
- No, it's embarrassing.
What if someone sees?
Fine, I'll take it. Okay?
Take care of yourself.
Bring honor to your country.
It's not like I'm going
to the Olympics tomorrow.
Good luck! You got this!
Good luck!
You can do it!
WE'LL REPAY YOUR SUPPORT WITH MEDALS
We bring you some unfortunate news.
Choi Seung-hyo, who secured his ticket
to the Olympics after winning
the 2007 National Swimming Championships,
has been involved in an accident.
- Seung-hyo's okay.
- Seung-hyo…
Seung-hyo…
It's okay.
It's okay. It'll be okay.
It's okay, all right?
With rehabilitation,
you'll be able to walk again.
But I don't think
you'll be able to continue…
your career as an athlete.
I do know.
I've had winters like that too.
I thought you'd remember.
I left my phone in my office.
I heard you two fought.
Mr. Yoon told me.
Why would he tell you about that?
I have some talent in counseling.
I've heard both sides.
I think you're right.
Covert plagiarism? That's so insulting!
Moreover, a person should look ahead.
We're going to succeed in the future.
We can't have plagiarism issues
bring us down.
- Are you taking my side?
- You should let me finish.
However, Mr. Yoon's right too.
I want to work nine-to-five
and get paid well.
To do that, the company must do well.
We have to hire more people too.
Due to the nature of architecture,
we're always beholden to the client.
But you don't know how to do that.
Maybe you're too content.
I heard something similar yesterday.
Whoever they are, they were right.
- You know it's true.
- What?
Seung-hyo,
you're marvelous.
You speak beautifully like poetry.
You're an idealist
who loves dreams more than reality.
You're always so full of pride.
But do you know
where all of that comes from?
It comes from privilege.
Hey! Dreams?
Do you think dreams can just be had?
Only those who have the luxury
to search for them can dream.
Those who get the chance to rise again
after failure can pursue their dreams.
So in conclusion, for the development
and glory of Atelier In,
I hope you two CEOs
can work together beautifully.
Just so you know,
Mr. Yoon stood outside
your door for a long time.
- You're a great counselor.
- I know.
Come in.
It looked like you didn't take your coffee
because of me earlier.
Yeah, thanks.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
I put you in a tough spot.
No, it's fine.
I know it was a bad call,
but I pretended otherwise.
I'm so ashamed.
Stop it. What are you saying?
I was being selfish for personal reasons.
You were right.
I wanted to work on the pool more.
I thought it was my chance
to turn the page there.
I get it, and I gave it some thought.
I thought about how you must've felt
when you quit swimming.
I can't even imagine.
Na-yun just told me…
we'd both fail
if we ran separate companies.
What?
Unless we want to starve,
she said we should stick together.
She really does say whatever she wants.
Millennials and Gen Z sure are different.
Look, you're great and all,
but don't talk about
millennials and Gen Z like that.
What?
Only old people do that.
The kids don't care.
So don't group them
as a generation like that.
So you don't like me?
You won't work with me?
I'll do it. Why wouldn't I?
Yeah, I knew you would.
You're too close.
- I can't work like this.
- Okay.
- I'm really sorry about yesterday.
- No, I'm sorry.
There you go!
Then, what was your dream?
My dream?
Yes. When you were in high school,
what did you want to be?
Now that I have to answer,
I don't really know.
Back then, just coming in first
in everything was my dream.
I wanted to be a daughter
my mom could be proud of.
I wanted my teachers to praise me.
I wanted everyone to recognize me.
Looking back now,
I feel a bit sorry for myself.
Why?
I cared about how others saw me,
and I don't think I paid attention
to myself.
THE RECRUITING TEAMS AT GLO KOREA
AND SERENDIPITY BOTH WANT INTERVIEWS
Is our family's knucklehead hero
finally up?
I'm hungry.
Are you hungry?
I just started the rice cooker.
It'll take some time.
Eat some rice cakes on the table.
What?
I've been eating rice cakes
so often lately.
Who are they from?
The new neighbor who just moved in.
Hey, I was the broker for that house.
It was on the market for ages
with no prospects.
I was so worried. Isn't it great?
Is it good?
It's good.
Is that you, Seok-ryu?
Ms. Yu?
It's a pear and bellflower tea.
It's good for your throat.
Thank you.
I'm sorry about earlier. Did I scare you?
It's okay. I'll stay cool for summer
with the chill you sent down my spine.
Speaking of which,
what were you looking for?
A time capsule.
I buried it with Seung-hyo and Mo-eum.
You all did something that cute?
But you couldn't find it.
It's for the best.
I thought I'd find the answers
if I saw it.
I think it'll just confuse me more.
What?
Ms. Yu,
I lied to you.
I don't work at Greip anymore.
I quit.
To be honest, I don't know if I quit
or got chased out.
Seok-ryu, you've always done well.
That's why I worried about you.
What if you couldn't do something well?
What would you do then?
I don't think I taught you how to do that.
But I realized something
after being a teacher for so long.
Children keep growing.
Even if I don't teach them,
they all find the answers
on their own somehow.
Was there an answer you thought about
when you quit?
Then, don't change your mind.
Trust your choice and move on.
Changing it always ends up wrong.
You're right.
Go to the pool when you're done.
I think Seung-hyo's there.
Okay.
Hey, Seung-hyo!
Did you find the time capsule?
You scared me. What are you doing here?
I should be asking you that.
Hey, what's that in your hand?
Is that my letter?
"To Bae Seok-ryu ten years from now."
"Hi!"
- "It's me. The best and most beautiful."
- Hey!
- "Bae Seok-ryu!"
- Don't read that. Hey!
- "What am I like in the future?"
- I'll kill you!
"I'm imprisoned in a classroom
due to the crime of being a student."
- Hey, don't run! You'll slip!
- No!
- Don't read my letter!
- "My school uniform's a prison uniform."
I was crazy. What did I write?
- Hey!
- "I'm punished with school work."
- "I'll be released with graduation."
- Give it!
"The best and the first."
- "Do you know they're similar?"
- Are you kidding?
- "Do your best."
- Hey.
"And you'll probably come in first."
I told you to stop!
We should've kept this buried.
They'll put this in textbooks
if they find this later.
A statement that will go down in history.
It's truly a gem!
Gem, my foot! Give it to me.
Give it to me!
Are you crazy?
Wow, that's low.
Did you jump knowing I can't swim?
Come in and take it from me then.
No, I'm scared of the water.
Did you know?
After I quit swimming,
this is my first time in a pool.
Wow, why didn't I come in until now?
It's so nice.
Hey, I didn't mean what I said before--
Do you remember?
When I couldn't swim anymore
and I was cooped up in my room?
Seung-hyo, what are you doing?
I brought some comics.
Let's read them together.
Then, I'll make you some ramyun instead.
No eggs, just how you like it.
What are you doing? Hey!
Why are you pushing me?
I have to read that.
Seung-hyo, at least give me my comics.
Did you think I couldn't come in
if you locked your door?
I knew the keys were
in the top shelf of the shoe cabinet!
Okay, instead of ramyun,
I'll buy you barbecue!
I'll buy you meat! How does that sound?
Hey! Wait! Hey!
Hey! Do you think I'll give up like this?
What are you doing?
My gosh!
- Seriously?
- You really scared me.
What are you doing?
Move over.
Come on!
Move out of the way.
You're insane.
Are you really laughing right now?
Why would you climb up here like that?
You almost died!
Yeah, so why would you lock
your doors, you jerk?
I almost died because of you.
I just saved your life.
You're so ungrateful.
You're such a lunatic.
If I'm a lunatic, what are you? A bear?
Did you think you'd turn into a human
after 100 years in your cave?
You fossilized trilobite-looking fool.
You've regressed into a baby.
A baby?
You're the one who's like a Neanderthal.
Do you lack the brain capacity?
You can't distinguish between
what you can and can't do, can you?
What is this smell?
Is it mugwort and garlic? No.
It smells like a lonely old man!
I don't smell anything.
Shut up and get lost.
Go back to where you came.
If I get lost, are you going to stare
at the wall like a loser again?
- Loser?
- Yeah, you stupid dumbass loser.
- Stop it.
- No.
Dummy. You're the biggest loser
in the world, bitch.
- Don't cuss.
- What are you going to do about it?
Go and eat from your dog bowl,
you bastard.
What's wrong with you?
I told you not to cuss!
You damn loser. You're so dim-witted.
I told you not to cuss.
What are you, five years old?
You stupid…
Damn it, I said stop!
You think you're cool, don't you?
You're frustrating and meek, you bastard.
Damn it, I already feel like crap.
- Why are you here bitching at me?
- You're the one acting like a damn fool.
Damn it, I'm hurt and can't do anything.
Why are you here bitching at me?
Do you even know how I feel?
Do you even know what I'm going through?
Do you feel better now?
It's my first time hearing your voice
in a month.
So what?
Hey. Why do you have that in your bag?
Lock your door again,
and I'll break it down.
Damn it.
That's who you were.
A damn lunatic wielding an ax
at a bear who trapped himself in a cave.
That's your identity.
Stop cowering. It doesn't suit you.
- You call that words of comfort?
- It means you stink.
What?
The old Seok-ryu was lively and energetic.
But you're so bland now.
You're no fun. You're boring.
You'd better take that back.
Hey!
Hey…
Wait! Hey!
Help me!
I got you! You won't die. It's okay.
Damn it!
Why would you jump in if you can't swim?
Why would you piss me off like that?
- Do you know why you're sinking?
- No!
It's because your body's tense!
Relax a little! Relax!
I can't relax when I get a shot
at the doctor's! How do I do it now?
Wait, just… Yeah.
Pretend you're a jellyfish.
Sway your limbs.
Yeah, just let the water take you.
- Sway? Like this?
- Yeah.
There you go. Like that.
What? I think pretending
to be a jellyfish is working.
- It's working. Yeah.
- It's working.
It's not working! It's not!
It's not working!
My head!
Hey! I drank some water!
Don't grab my hair. Please.
Am I really floating right now?
This is so cool! Wow. I feel so strange.
Do you want to keep talking
even in this moment?
Feel the stillness in the water.
Hey, Seung-hyo?
What?
I was actually nervous.
I wanted to quit because I was exhausted.
I wanted to rest and dream of a new life.
But…
I felt like nothing
without my Greip background.
Everyone is moving forward,
but I'm the only one who's stopped.
That's how I felt after I quit swimming.
The start signal had sounded,
but I felt like I was standing alone
at the starting line.
I thought,
"It's going to be hard to find a place
where I can swim freely again."
But you found it.
I know.
I found it, so why can't you?
I hated going into bathwater,
but I'm able to jump back in again.
You think so?
Can I swim somewhere new too?
Of course.
Hey, I'm just curious.
Hypothetically.
Let's say you could swim again.
If that were to happen,
would you still be an architect?
Yeah.
- Really?
- Of course.
What about you?
- What?
- Hypothetically.
Let's say you go back to before you quit.
If you can go back to Greip,
will you go back?
No.
One more.
Hypothetically.
Let's say you go back to before
your engagement was broken,
what would you do?
No. I wouldn't go back.
Okay, then.
We'll write letters to our future selves
ten years from now.
Okay.
Do we have to?
Shut up and write.
Let's open it in ten years.
If anyone opens it before then,
they'll have bad luck for 1,000 years!
Pinky swear! No take backs!
Hi, Bae Seok-ryu ten years from now.
It's me. The best and most beautiful.
Bae Seok-ryu!
What if I can shoot webs
with the advancement of technology?
There's a rumor you climb on the ceilings.
Ten years from now feels so far away.
By then, you probably told Seok-ryu
how you felt, right?
STOP LINE
STARTING LINE
LOVE NEXT DOOR
But still, how could I
leave evidence like that?
Those feelings have long since expired.
You finally opened it after all this time?
I dug it up that night. I was curious.
Greip contacted us!
I moved here recently.
It's so nice to run into you.
Really?
It's the reporter again.
Have our tastes overlapped again?
No matter how hard you try,
it's a waste of time.
Don't talk about my hard work like that.
Seok-ryu?
Seung-hyo!
What the hell did you just say?
Subtitle translation by: Sue Mounce