(Lee Jae In, Kim Woo Seok, Choi Ye Bin)
(Cha Woo Min, An Ji Ho, Jung So Ri)
(Scriptwriter: Kang Min Ji)
(Director: Im Dae Woong)
(Night Has Come)
(All people, organizations, locations, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
Kim Dong Hyun was a Citizen.
Hey, they're back.
What happened to Dong Hyun?
Hey. Say something. What happened to Dong Hyun?
What's going on?
He thought...
the line stopped there.
So he was checking.
Then he slipped.
Then how far into the village were you able to go?
You said you would meet people and call the police. Did you do it?
We couldn't go.
The entire place is enclosed with the line.
We're completely locked in here.
Then does it mean...
we can't leave this place until the game is over?
Right.
Are you crying?
If...
I didn't say...
we could try going to the mountain,
he wouldn't have died.
That was a stupid thing to say.
It's all my fault that Dong Hyun is dead.
You didn't make him go.
They volunteered to go.
You didn't know there wouldn't be a way out.
You can't blame yourself for not knowing that.
So...
what will you do?
We can't leave this place until the game is over.
Are you just going to cry here?
No.
We must find another way out.
Hello?
Hello? Hey!
Come on.
Where are you going?
Oh, hey.
Kyung Jun and the other guys wanted to see me.
Don't go if you don't want to go.
But still. I should go.
Why?
Hey, Jun Hee!
What are you doing?
Isn't the phone ringing?
What's wrong?
Hello?
Forget it.
What's wrong?
It's fake. Everything is.
What?
The phones were never connected.
What is this?
(Retreat Center Committee)
(Accounting and Finances of Muryeong Retreat Center)
Look at this. The files are empty.
(Swimming Pool Cafeteria)
You love this sesame-seed-flavored ramyeon.
Right. Thank you.
The ramyeon preference is the only thing we have in common.
Then do you have a different preference in music?
Darn you. Do you have a death wish?
Don't shove that perverted music on me.
Okay, chill. I won't do that.
Nerd.
You're the game expert.
Is this an existing game?
No. It's my first time seeing it too.
But I'm not a nerd.
Okay, sorry.
So what should we do to win this game?
It's the same as playing the Mafia Game.
Haven't you played it before?
You don't think I know that, you punk?
Everyone's identities are not revealed...
until they die.
You have to find out who your opponents are.
Doctors and Police are on Citizens' side.
The team that wipes out the other team will win.
Gosh. Darn it. Come on.
It'll take forever to find the Mafia.
Hey.
Why don't we just kill off random people?
Then the game will end.
You said you were a Citizen too.
We can just get rid of the Mafia. Why kill off other people?
It said we had to wipe out the other team. You idiot.
Why do you want to kill off people on your team too?
You can't even follow through with it. Stop acting tough.
You were super scared when you saw the kids dying.
- You jerk. I was never scared. - Come on. Shut your mouth.
Choi Ju Won.
He was the Mafia. Why did he die?
I don't know why he died either.
The rule said the Mafia had to execute someone.
I don't know what happened, but maybe, the Mafia had...
a good reason to kill Ju Won instead of a Citizen.
What if a Citizen were to kill the Mafia?
Is that allowed?
That wasn't in the rules. So I'm not sure.
Instead of playing this game,
let's find all the Mafia and gather them in one place.
Then we should make them kill each other.
- That's a great idea. - Right?
That's an awesome idea.
- Right? - Totally.
Gosh. You idiots.
Your idea is awful.
Do you think that would work?
What if one of us dies again tonight like Ju Won?
We should hide and lock the door.
Are you going to vote?
We have to.
But how many people are Mafia?
I don't know. It doesn't say anything about their number.
Right. Police.
There was an announcement that Police used...
their skill this morning. They must know then.
Are you really all Citizens?
None of us are Police?
Darn it.
- Look at this. - Hey.
Be quiet! You're distracting me.
If you plan to vote, let's call Jun Hee here.
Get Jun Hee.
Can't she get him herself? Gosh.
Darn it.
What about Na Hee?
I don't know. She's probably sleeping in the infirmary.
Park Woo Ram! Get Na Hee too.
When I got injured,
I should have said I was in pain and stopped us from going.
If we came right back, that wouldn't have happened.
No.
Even if you said you wanted to go back,
they could have kept going anyway.
It's not your fault.
But still.
Everyone is responsible.
I saw Dong Hyun die right in front of me.
But I couldn't do anything.
Hyun Ho.
Let's stay alive and get out of this place.
I'll protect you, no matter what.
You will?
When we get out of here,
I want to watch you play.
Don't fall for me when you do.
You know, the person who created this Mafia Game...
What's the reason behind putting us through this?
We must find out who made this game and the reason behind it.
Where do you think the creator of this game is?
It's just us here.
Maybe, the creator comes in when we fall asleep.
Maybe, that's when the creator killed Ju Won.
It said the Mafia killed Ju Won.
But only the students from our class are on the list of participants.
If there was someone else, the name would've been on the list.
Right.
The creator probably selected the Mafia...
when assigning the identities.
Then...
someone in our class really killed Ju Won?
According to the rules,
probably.
Then who do you think might be the Mafia?
Seeing how Ju Won died,
it might be someone from Kyung Jun's gang.
Right. They bullied Kyung Jun a lot.
It looked like Jin Ha and Seung Bin borrowed...
a lot of money from Ju Won too.
I'm not sure about Ju Won.
Usually, Mafia would want to kill off Citizens.
We might be able to learn something from yesterday's vote.
Let's kill Heo Yul.
Why are you looking at me?
Well,
you wanted everyone to vote for Heo Yul yesterday.
I voted for him because you told me so.
Choi Mi Na.
You think I'm the Mafia?
Eun Ha.
Why did you tell us he was the Mafia?
I'm not the Mafia.
Do you think I killed Yul on purpose?
You took the lead in that round, and that's how Yul ended up dead.
Right?
That's true.
What? What are you guys doing?
Hey, So Mi.
Then why did you do it?
Me?
Do what?
I saw you push Dong Hyun at the mountain.
Hey. I'm slipping down.
He died because of you!
Have you gone mad?
You think I pushed him?
No, that's not true.
I almost died stopping Kim Dong Hyun from falling.
Other people saw it. What kind of gibberish is that?
Guys. I really had no idea. It was just a joke.
But she pushed him on purpose when she knew he was going to die.
I never did.
Tell Jun Hee and other kids to come.
Ask other kids!
- Hey! - Stop it.
There's nothing.
Can I...
Nice.
What are you doing?
I need to check whether you're on my side or not...
before having a meal with you.
What are you talking about? Give me my phone back.
Hey, is it any good?
Dang it.
Stay still!
If I spill any, you're dead.
It's one punch for each drop.
(Vote)
Dang it.
It's the same as ours. It won't show his occupation.
Darn it.
Shoot, I spilled.
Give me my phone back now.
Wait. I'm not done checking yet.
Check what?
If I can vote with someone else's phone,
it means I can give all the votes on the person I want.
Kneel.
Don't touch me. Let me go.
Hey.
Pick one. I'll vote for that person.
No.
Then it'll be you.
What? Don't do that. No.
Don't! Stop it!
I said no!
Seriously. Don't.
(Failed to vote)
I guess you can't vote on someone else's phone.
Gosh.
Hey. I was looking for you.
Let's go. Everyone's saying they're going to vote.
Yul died after we voted, and they want to vote again?
We can't leave until the game is over.
We have no choice.
Still, how can we do that again?
We have to stop them.
We must not vote.
How are we going to stop them?
Even if we want to persuade them, we need an alternative.
I'll persuade them. Is everyone together?
No, in their rooms.
Then let's gather them first.
I'll help.
Wait, Da Bum.
He left when Ko Kyung Jun called him.
Those punks.
I never liked them.
Let me go!
Just wait.
Stay still.
It won't work.
This is messed up.
Hey!
That's enough.
What on earth are you doing?
What's your deal?
- You scared me. - Get up.
Get up, Da Bum.
Three on one guy?
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
Where do you think you're going?
Hey.
Stop it.
Come with me. I have something to say.
Why do I have to listen to you?
- Hey! - Seriously.
You jerk.
You're not the boss of me.
Get it?
Jerks.
You never get it when I say it nicely.
I need to teach you a lesson.
Jerk.
Jerk!
Come here.
Let go of me. I said let go, you prick.
Are you going to listen?
Are you going to do as I say?
I get it, jerk.
Let's go.
Hey.
Come here.
Will you stop for goodness' sake?
Can I tell other kids what you just did?
What do you think they'd say?
Come to your senses.
What's the point of talking to him?
If we vote on you now, everyone else will vote after us.
What do you say?
Do you want me to press your name?
You wench.
Drop this now.
I won't tell other kids, so drop it now.
Stop it, for goodness' sake.
Seriously.
We're all going to gather in the assembly hall.
You should come too.
Leave the cafeteria door open...
for the others to use.
Shoot.
(Participant list)
I gathered all of you here...
not to decide whom we should vote for,
but to give up on voting.
Give up on voting?
Are you sure about that?
If we vote, one person is guaranteed to die.
But if we don't, we'll all survive.
What if we agreed not to vote, but someone votes in secret?
What are you going to do then?
She has a point. How am I supposed to trust you?
We should trust each other.
We can collect all our phones, so no one can vote.
He's right. If we collect our phones, no one can vote.
That'll work.
Who's going to keep the phones?
The person in charge might change his mind.
Let's keep them in the center for everyone to see.
Yes, we can all watch together.
What if someone steals it?
I'm not doing it. I'm not handing in my phone.
I think it's a good idea. Let's hand in our phones.
Are you crazy?
Who'd steal your phone? Just hand it in.
- No. - Can't you live without your phone?
- Don't. - Why not?
Why are you yelling at me?
If we hand it in, no one will die.
Oh, be quiet.
The class president is actually making sense for once.
Why won't you cooperate?
Hand in your phones, so no one can vote.
Everyone, make sure to hand in your phones.
Listen to me when I'm being nice.
Where's your phone? Hand it in.
What are you doing? Hurry up and hand it in.
Hurry up. There's no time.
A minute left to vote.
Gosh.
Darn it, seriously.
Hey, Class President. Are you sure we're okay?
Let's just wait.
It's not midnight yet.
Gosh.
Hey.
It's past midnight, but there was no announcement.
Did it work?
Are we okay now?
We did it.
- We're safe. - It's over.
We're safe.
Are we okay now?
Participants must vote and identify the Mafia.
(Participants must vote and identify the Mafia.)
Hey! What are you doing?
What else?
What if we do nothing and die?
Are you going to take responsibility?
She's right.
Wait.
We don't know yet.
Don't know what?
The game didn't end.
What if we die for listening to you?
Are you going to be responsible?
Hey!
Stop blaming Jun Hee and calm down.
For breaking the rules, Lee Soo Bin...
and Park Ji Hoon will be executed.
Lee Soo Bin and Park Ji Hoon were Citizens.
Did everyone hand it in?
Participants must vote and identify the Mafia.
What do you think you're doing?
Get your phone if you don't want to die.
- Shoot. - No.
If we don't vote, we die.
I have to vote!
For breaking the rules, Oh Jin Seok will be executed.
- No. - We'll die.
- No. - Wait.
- Wait. - Where's my phone?
Jun Hee, hurry up.
Jun Hee.
What are you doing?
We're all going to die.
Kim Jun Hee!
(Electrical Shock Hazard)
Move!
Get off me!
Oh Jin Seok was a Citizen.
- It's mine! - No.
Where is it?
I found it!
Gosh.
Idiots.
(Night Has Come)
(Gwangju Information and Content Agency)
(This content was produced through Gwangju Information and...)
(Content Agency's 2022 OTT Platform Content Production Business.)