(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
Today,
with deep sorrow,
we bid farewell to Mr. Xu Zhaoming.
He was not only
the pillar of his family,
but also a leading figure
among outstanding entrepreneurs.
Next, please welcome
the daughter of Mr. Xu Zhaoming,
Xu Wanxin, to deliver her remarks.
My father,
Mr. Xu Zhaoming,
lived his life guided by the principle
of creating value for the people
and contributing
to the prosperity of the nation.
He often said,
all our research
has the potential to change the world.
I do not fear his passing,
because I will always remember him,
and carry forward
his spirit and the spirit
of Minghui Group.
I believe
this is the meaning of how we
became father and daughter
beyond blood ties.
(The Tomb
of My Beloved Father, Xu Zhaoming)
I love you.
As your daughter,
I am proud.
(The Tomb
of My Beloved Father, Xu Zhaoming)
♪Tonight the rain falls soft and slow♪
♪Blending with letters left unread
drifting through the air♪
♪You turn and look back at me♪
♪In those same eyes
familiar tears quietly appear♪
♪It feels like we have carried so much♪
♪So many questions time itself
could not make clear♪
♪The moment you walked into my life♪
Okay.
♪Every dream I had became
something I want with you near♪
Wanxin,
your grandfather is awake.
=Echoes of Gang City=
=Episode 5=
(A Familiar Soul Returns)
Dad.
(Gang City Financial News)
Welcome to the morning financial news program.
I will go see Grandfather first.
I do not know
how much he understands
about us and the company.
(Filial)
Understood.
Grandfather.
Wanxin.
Child,
do not cry.
Do not cry.
During this time,
with everything happening
in the family and the company,
you have been through a lot.
Grandfather, I am not tired.
What I worry about most is you.
I'm fine.
I have seen life and death many times.
As you have grown little by little,
I am willing to believe
that if you hold kindness in your heart,
blessings will follow.
Alright,
let me ask you something.
Go ahead, Grandfather.
You married Shen Gu, is that right?
Yes.
Your marriage
must never be a compromise
for the sake of family interests.
And I would never
sacrifice your happiness.
Grandfather, it was only after
I received the call from Qingniao Group
that I decided to marry him.
When something happened at home,
he was the first
to come and check on us.
Regarding my father,
and even your attending physician,
he helped with everything.
Even if we were not married,
he would have done the same.
So,
I trust him.
Thank you.
Wanxin,
how is Grandfather?
He is doing alright.
He wants to speak with you.
Okay.
Shen Gu.
He already knows about our marriage.
It is just that
he does not
quite agree with my decision.
Let us go.
Grandfather.
I am Shen Gu.
You are awake.
Who are you?
I am Lin Shuyi.
He is Shen Gu.
I do not have money
to repay your medical expenses.
I fled here from the countryside.
My family is all gone.
Silly child,
you do not need to repay us.
Since we saved you,
we will take responsibility
for you to the end.
Mm.
You can stay with us from now on.
What is your name?
I am the fourth child in my family.
They all call me Xu Si.
Xu Si.
In the fields and crossroads of life,
every direction
can lead to a way forward.
From now on,
you will be called Xu Qianmo.
What do you think?
Qianmo.
Mr. Xu.
What is it?
You two,
Mr. Xu should not
be overly agitated today.
That is all for today's visit.
Miss Xu, do not worry.
We are here.
Step back.
Let me check his pulse.
Take a deep breath, say it.
Mr. Xu, do not get agitated.
- Come, take a deep breath.
- Calm down.
Calm down.
Slowly.
Ease your emotions.
I am fine now.
You may all go out.
I
would like to be alone for a while.
- Okay.
(In Commemoration of the Engagement of Lin Shuyi
and Shen Gu. April 6th, Year 25 of the Republic)
Three, two, one.
♪Tonight the rain falls soft and slow♪
♪Blending with letters left unread
drifting through the air♪
♪You turn and look back at me♪
♪In those same eyes
familiar tears quietly appear♪
♪It feels like we have carried so much♪
♪So many questions time itself
could not make clear♪
♪The moment you walked into my life♪
♪Every dream I had became
something I want with you near♪
♪How many letters
have I written just for you♪
♪If only you could truly hear
what my heart is trying to say♪
♪From this life on no distance
could keep us apart♪
♪The promise we made♪
♪Will find its way
to be fulfilled one day♪
♪But I want more
than just that fleeting gaze♪
♪Still I have not heard your answer♪
♪Can we still rewrite
the ending we face♪
♪When regrets begin to turn around
you will hear it all♪
♪Everything that leads me back to you♪