CJ ENM presents
a THE LAMP.ltd production
To Phantom
Commence the operation
Do not stop
- until it succeeds
- This just in!
Last night, in Shanghai,
an assassination attempt was made
upon the next Governor-General to Joseon.
A group of terrorists known as the
'Shadow Corps'
has been coordinating organized crime
using a network of spies
known as 'Phantom.'
A violent shootout ensued.
All terrorists were killed.
There were no survivors.
A new day has dawned.
May your day be full of promise.
Intelligence Department,
Japanese Government-General
From no. 5.
Intelligence report
Supervisor
Murayama Junji
79. It's sunny today
It's sunny today.
New Governor-General
to visit Joseon Shrine
Cryptography officer
Cheon Eunho
Are you spying on me?
I'm here in an official capacity.
Get a move on, then.
Cafe Gold
One ticket, please.
New Governor-General
in Kyungsung
Eliminate him at Joseon Shrine
Can I borrow a light?
You need your matches.
I heard about the mishap in Shanghai.
You can relax here in Kyungsung, sir.
We have a strong hold over this region.
You can focus on the inauguration.
It's been a while back in Kyungsung?
It must feel
foreign.
First column from the left!
Attention!
All attention!
Formation!
The Guards Division act like
they run the place already.
Formation
It's our great honor to have you
as the new Governor-General of Joseon!
My service is entirely at your disposal.
Enough out of you!
Governor-General,
did you have a chance
to try Naengmyeon?
Naengmyeon?
They say the term "Naengmyeon"
comes from China.
But I'm not sure.
I always wanted to let you try Naengmyeon.
At first, Naengmyeon were accompanied
by first-class beef, but later...
Platoon 2, follow me!
This way, sir.
You useless idiots!
Guards! Come and help him.
Let me help you.
Nanyoung...
Murayama.
Takahara.
Multiple shots fired,
but no catch.
Should I question them one by one?
Not yet.
Phantoms...
You said you wiped them out
in Shanghai?
Kyungsung was a blind spot for us.
I'm at fault, sir.
Fault...
On my first day in Joseon?
I'll make sure we're in the clear.
I just declared
a non-military rule policy.
See that it's done quietly.
Wipe the place out!
The Phantom
I'm sure you've heard of it.
Yesterday's attack resembles
the Shanghai terror.
The Guards Division suspects
that a Phantom has infiltrated
the Government-General office.
How come you're telling me this?
To give you the upper hand.
The Police Department has always
had command over Joseon.
You can't let the Guards Division
take control away from you.
Whoever catches the Phantom
will get the upper hand.
Reinstate me to the Police Department.
You don't give up, do you?
But to what end?
One, please.
Cafe Gold
It's me.
I saw the Chief Guard in the theater.
He led anti-Phantom operations
in Shanghai.
Be careful.
I'm prepared.
My time will come when it comes.
Well, don't think about dying first.
Nanyoung must've been the same.
Enough blood has been shed.
Let's stop it now.
I'm sorry, but today's showing is over.
How curious...
there is a movie theater
in this neighborhood
that's run by a Korean?
We took the liberty of packing,
due to time constraints.
Shouldn't you at least tell me
where we're going?
I had the weirdest dream last night
about snakes.
50 or so silvery snakes were
squirming in a big silver basin.
What do you think it means?
What a trouble being dragged here
out of the blue!
Here.
Did you get car sick?
Well, I threw up 3 times.
Take a seat.
Have you heard anything?
At all?
Why bother? She's got 'clueless'
written all over her face.
It's written all over all our faces.
Look, she's from
the Deputy Governor's office.
He's from the Police department,
and we're from Intelligence...
Nothing in common.
So then why are we all here?
If anyone would know, it's you.
You have a different background than us.
Where are you from?
Who put you up to this?
These fuckers are playing dumb with me.
I'm the Deputy Governor-General's
head secretary!
Quiet down.
You may be the head secretary,
but you're not the Deputy himself.
You quiet down.
With the Police department?
You were demoted a long time ago.
Shame on you.
What are you doing here?
You went back to your hometown.
Your mother's ill.
I was on my way when I got taken in.
It took some time to gather all of you.
Let me introduce myself properly.
I'm Chief Guard to the
new Governor-General Yamagata,
Takahara Kaito.
The Gold Theater in Gold Avenue,
I brought something back from there.
Dracula?
A blood-thirsty demon
that wakes up at night?
I found something interesting
on the bottom of the poster.
It might seem like a print error,
but no, it's more than that.
It's a code.
Mr. Cheon, you're an expert
in cryptography.
Would you do the honors?
But this is a complex cypher
composed of two different...
This is a complex cypher
composed of two different systems.
I'll need a decoding book.
The Shadow Corps
based in Shanghai
infiltrated the Chinese Intelligence
with secret agents known as
"Phantoms."
I thought Kyungsung was safe.
But unfortunately,
it's been confirmed that
we've been infiltrated too.
And that Phantom
is in this room.
Last chance.
Jan 10 12:00pm,
Kyungsung Public Hall.
Governor-General's
inauguration ceremony.
All agents are to turn
up at the inauguration
...to kill the new Governor-General.
There were messages about
Jan 11 and 12
with a couple more venues but
'Jan 10, Kyungsung Public Hall.'
Only this message was coded
in the Shadow Corps' unique style.
And only you five have had
access to this message.
It's no use denying.
To get to the point,
the inauguration will not happen
at Kyungsung Public Hall.
'All agents to show up.'
But thankfully, it looks like
the entire group will be there
tomorrow!
You are all equally under suspicion.
That suspicion won't go away by itself.
You must either prove yourself clean
or identify the culprit to survive.
I'll give you until noon.
I hope you think wisely.
At noon, I'll start
torturing you one-by-one
in random order to be fair.
That's all for now.
I look forward to your cooperation.
I'll show you to your room.
Are you trying to get yourself killed?
This is fuel storage.
No smoking!
Is that right?
Sure you lost it in the car?
It's gotta be there somewhere.
Look again.
This wouldn't have happened
if you had let me pack.
Is this it?
There you are.
A shared room?
Are they kidding me?
I'll rip their heads off.
Pretend I'm not here,
I'll do the same.
Light.
I said light.
The damned phone is dead!
Get out.
Can't you hear? I said get out.
Are you deaf?
Get your hands off me
before I break them.
Relax, bitch.
Fine, just give me a moment.
I need to change.
I said I need to get changed.
Don't be shy.
Removing clothes is your second nature.
What an unbelievable bitch you are!
You wanted to see me, Murayama?
This doesn't come as a surprise.
Ever since I heard
you were coming to Kyungsung,
I knew you'd have it out with me
one way or another.
Let's cut to the chase.
This Phantom...
Don't waste your time trying.
You don't have what it takes.
The Phantom is mine.
In return,
you'll pay for the humiliation
you have brought upon me.
Gold Theater
You.
I'm going to Kyungsung now,
and the first thing I'm going to do
is sack you.
What the...?
You snuck up silent as a mouse.
I came to ask you something.
What can you hope to learn
when I know nothing?
Earlier, in the dining room,
you were talking about Park
and said she's different
from the rest of us.
What did you mean by that?
You really don't know?
It's an open secret.
Park's father bought a plane
for the former Governor-General.
Even the Japan acknowledges
her family's wealth.
I thought she might know
something we don't.
Or heard something at her home.
You have an idea about
who the Phantom might be?
It's clear the Phantom is among us.
Bring me a phone!
You better stay in your place.
You pigs bring it to me when I say so!
Return to your room at once.
Shut up and bring me a phone!
What's gotten into her?
I'll take a look.
There's no one here.
I want to ask you something.
That day...
We'll put a tap on Park and Baekho.
Once I make that call,
you're all good as dead.
You sons of bitches!
Get me the Deputy Governor-General.
I know you're listening to this,
so cut the crap and connect me!
Hello.
Who the hell are you?
This is Ayanami,
secretary to the Deputy Governor.
Who are you kidding?
I'm the Deputy's secretary!
How dare they replace me!
Don't you dare fuck me over!
The same to you, fucking bitch!
Good day, then.
Hello? Hello?
Bitch!
Go on.
Calm down.
Don't touch me.
Just shut up.
Out of my way!
They have wires everywhere,
recording everything we say.
You have something to ask me?
Hana...
Wait for me, baby...
Wiretap report
Do you trust him?
Sir?
Do you trust Murayama?
Of course, sir.
I trust Murayama.
The former Chief Guard
Murayama Toshio
killed himself without leaving a note.
Murayama Jr. lost all his
professional advantages like that,
and has since been demoted.
That's all you know?
Murayama!
Murayama Junji!
The appointment to Shanghai
was supposed to be yours,
but Takahara took the post
at the last minute.
I wasn't happy but complied,
and it turns out...
You're of Korean blood?
What was the blood I saw that day?
Anyone can make up an excuse
to that question.
That's not what you want to know.
Are you the Phantom?
Please say no.
Chakyung!
Are you the Phantom?
I beg you, Baekho...
Save yourself.
I've always liked you.
I know.
My mother was the only Korean
in my entire family.
That small fact
doesn't change the entire line
of blood I've inherited.
7th generation of
the Murayama family.
The promising, elite heir
born in Kyungsung, fluent in Korean.
Where does the lie begin?
Answer me, fraud!
The fact that I'm born of
a Korean mother changes me?
Do you want to deny me?
As long as Korean blood
flows in your veins,
you're nothing more than
one of the suspects.
You'll have to prove
you're not the Phantom.
To Kyungsung! Now!
You pathetic scum.
You were lingering around
like a dog in heat
wanting to be like me.
So I took you under my wing.
And now, you want to bite me?
Fine! Doubt all you want.
You'll end up paying for it.
Get him!
This is a final warning.
Get out of the car.
This is my final order.
Start the car.
You can't shoot me.
Why not?
I could be the Phantom.
What's stopping you?
Shoot her!
You're not so sure now.
You don't have the balls.
Do you have what it takes?
I didn't use a gun or a knife
when I killed my mother.
Strangling out the last drop of
her insolent blood,
I stopped her breath.
There's no ground for denying
the legitimacy of my blood.
If you plan on continuing
to defame me,
remember.
I will use neither
gun nor knife with you.
Wait and see.
I'm catching the Phantom
before sundown.
Stay clear of Murayama from now on.
Get your act together.
Look at me!
No one will suspect or interrogate you.
Everything will be settled
before the end of the day.
You gotta stick it out, okay?
Alright, alright!
Get the fuck off me!
You're not stupid, are you?
I'm disappointed in you, Miss Yuriko.
Think about it.
Could I bring you here
without the Deputy knowing?
It was his idea.
He wanted to check you out
because you were his bitch.
Do you understand?
Your time was up.
Let go of me.
Poor Hana...
You must be starving.
Hang in there.
I'll be home soon, darling.
Hana...
Who should be called in first?
There are two types of commanders.
One goes for the prime suspect
right away.
The other starts with the witness
who knows the secret.
The former is fast,
the latter cautious.
Which do you think I am?
Hey!
Don't walk around
without permission!
You...
I couldn't care less who the Phantom is,
but right now,
I would like it to be you.
You'll see what I mean.
And you will live.
Your eyes say you won't go easily.
Hey!
Lost something?
Serves you right, bitch.
Report every movement
the suspects make.
You!
Where are you going?
I... have to check something.
I can't tell you what it is.
But I have to go.
It's past 12:00! There's no time.
I've got to go now, right now!
Return to your room.
Don't try to stop me.
Let him go.
I said let me go!
Thank you!
Yuriko darling, no one's here, right?
I'll be honest with you.
You're here as a formality.
I could've let you go
see your mother.
You're all she's got.
You could walk free right now.
But if you keep quiet,
you become a party to the crime.
Why take the risk?
Tell me what you know,
and you'll walk free.
Who is the Phantom?
You'd better not waste any more time.
I...
have no idea.
You don't know.
See?
These cards are supposed to
tell me who the phantom is.
They've never once been wrong.
But...
But what?
Who does it say it is?
Me.
I'm really not!
But they point to me every time.
What do you think?
I don't think it's you either.
Really? Why not?
If the Shadow Corps had a brain,
they wouldn't give the job to anyone.
Huh...?
Well, thanks anyway.
Please tell them it's not me.
I have to be home by tomorrow.
My baby is starving,
waiting for me to come home.
Please.
Cheon.
Come in here.
Park Chakyung!
You saw it, right?
Murayama going all crazy
and shooting at me.
I was shocked to see him
completely overreact
in front of everyone, no less
as if trying to show them.
He was trying to prove
that he isn't the Phantom.
What?
He can't be...
Right?
That's what I thought too
but when I came back to my room,
I found out Murayama
had snuck into my room.
You know what I found after he left?
That's enough, Park.
He had planted it in Park's suitcase.
Murayama had it on him
which means...
He is the Phantom.
And he was trying to frame Park
with the evidence.
You're right!
He snuck into my room, too!
If I hadn't caught him,
he'd have framed me instead! Fuck!
Fuck, right!
That sneaky bastard!
Take the evidence and report him.
It could even lead to your promotion.
I thought about doing it myself...
Why didn't you?
It's such a good chance.
It's just how I feel.
Yuriko darling!
What?
Let's all just go home, okay?
Okay!
Informer
Cheon Eunho
What that is is...
Take it to the Chief Guard.
He'll know what it is.
Careful! Ink's not dry yet.
No one can hear us now.
Listen carefully, Park.
I'm the Phantom.
And I know
that you're a Phantom, too.
You'd already know
it's impossible to get out by yourself.
We need to work together.
In order to do that, I need to be sure.
Tell me, Park.
Are you a Phantom?
What the hell?
What are you doing?
Are you crazy?
What the fuck's going on!
Jan 8
6:00pm, Gold Theater...
Exactly when I was
looking around the theater.
You managed to avoid me.
Is this where
your intuition misled you?
Intuition can't beat solid evidence.
Don't ask me, ask yourself.
Takahara,
do you truly believe
that I'm the Phantom?
Is that right?
Now that I hear it,
that question isn't for me.
Why did you help me?
Is that what you think?
You could've reported me.
You think the world
revolves around you?
Help you? No.
This is between me and Murayama.
I name Murayama as the Phantom.
Do you have any objections?
If you say nothing,
that in itself is a clear answer.
We'll conclude that it's Murayama
and close the investigation.
It looks like your mother arrived
in the hospital just in time.
I don't know if you're aware,
but you have given your answer
to this question, too.
A clear one.
Kill her.
No!
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry.
Please spare my mother.
I'm sorry. I beg you!
Hold.
I'm sorry.
Now we can begin the discussion.
I'll ask you for the last time.
Who is the Phantom?
It's Park Chakyung.
How was your long day, everyone?
I did quite a bit of legwork,
and eventually found one witness
and one piece of evidence.
What's funny is that
each points to a different suspect.
The evidence points to Murayama,
the witness points to Park.
To be honest,
I've had enough discussion
about the evidence.
I'd now like to verify
the witness's testimony.
I'm talking about you,
Park Chakyung.
If you're the Phantom,
as the witness says...
Look.
They're in boiling water
because of you.
Relieve them of their suffering.
Give us an answer, Park.
Are you the Phantom?
Fine.
Let's talk about him instead.
What's this young man's crime?
He put his own life at risk
and did his best
to protect you, Park.
Now you must answer this question.
What can you do for him in return?
What will you put on stake?
Answer me, Park!
Will you be a coward?
To the end?
What will do you for this boy
who risked everything for you?
What can you do? Say it!
That's a shame.
You haven't eaten all day, have you?
Please, dig in.
You...!
Ready, aim!
Hold your fire.
Now!
Murayama, you're the Phantom!
We all know,
so you'd better come clean.
Lower your gun.
You may be a Phantom,
but surely you can't sacrifice the life
of an innocent person!
Give me a gun! Quickly!
I...
...need to be home
more than anyone in the world.
I'll kill anyone who gets in the way.
Yuriko!
Don't die yet, Miss Yuriko.
Get her!
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize, Baekho.
You don't owe me anything.
Get ready.
Not here!
No one here, either.
Father...
I did it.
Why?
I was afraid this would go on.
Are you crazy? Why...
Why did you do it?
For Joseon?
For your country?
What is that? What is Joseon?
What the hell is that...!
Junji...
The sounds of the river never
silence the regrets of fallen heroes.
Only after the coldest night
does the green of the
evergreen look brighter.
Who are you?
Tell me you who are!
I'm going to save you with my life.
You'll get out of here and
save our comrades with your life.
I will finish up here.
Don't think I'm helping you.
We're all doing what we can.
You... what are you?
There are only two bullets left,
use them well.
Are you saying
there are two Phantoms?
Someone like you, no less?
I got these scars when
I was tortured in Manchuria.
When I first took off my clothes
in front of the Deputy,
I told him they were self-inflicted,
and he loved it,
sick pervert...
But his perversion made it easier
for me to serve my country.
Here are the scars I got
from the Deputy.
Up to here are
from the first winter...
And from the following spring.
Every time he burned my skin,
'I'm dead, I'm dead.'
I said to myself, over and over.
There's nothing left for me
in this world.
It's okay if I die.
Sir...
One must judge people based on
experience, not reputation.
This is your last chance.
Don't disappoint me again.
I'm sorry, sir.
Do whatever you have to.
Just don't get in my way.
I had no idea they'd planted
two Phantoms in the government.
Me neither.
A backup just in case?
Or, to help the other out
in case of trouble.
Live.
Die only when your time comes.
Keep searching.
We gotta move now.
We have to cut the comms line
and buy time until dawn.
With this size of military,
there's gotta be an armory.
I scouted the premises inside out,
but didn't find any.
The only place left is the basement.
To the left of the gate is a fuel storage.
It will come in handy.
In the corner is a small garage.
There is a civilian car inside.
Secure the vehicle and weapons,
and we can make it to Kyungsung.
Here's the comms line and electricity.
I'll take the comms.
This'll soak up petrol well.
It'll make it easier to run.
We haven't exchanged names yet.
I'm Park Chakyung
from Kyungsung.
Why bother?
Fire!
The engine room.
- Get the fire extinguisher!
- Yes, sir!
Hurry!
It's the engine room.
Are you alright, sir?
You can't search this tiny little hotel?
Catch them before dawn, or I'll kill you
for failing to follow orders.
Follow me.
Upstairs is the hotel.
They'll have it for all the buildings.
I'll take the top.
Three, two...
It's too dangerous to go back out.
There's gotta be a way out.
This way is the ocean.
Should be safer.
Shush!
You go first and pull me up.
What...?
Quiet.
Don't be stupid!
Go.
Come on, you can make it.
My name is Ahn Kangok
from Hamgyong.
Thank you for asking my name.
Get out of here and
save all our comrades.
No!
Who is it? Freeze!
Put your hands up.
I'm Ahn Kangok with the Shadow Corps.
I'm the Phantom.
And... you will never catch me.
Take her to the torture chamber.
Shall we start, Miss Yuriko?
Coordinating with Shanghai to plant
a Phantom in the government...
I'm impressed.
Too bad for you...
We'll always be
anywhere and everywhere.
That sickens me about you.
Your tenacious obsession...
like maggots that relentlessly
hang on to pitiful life in a pool of shit.
You disgusting vermin.
Who is the leader
of the Shadow Corps?
Say it.
Cut off comms and electricity
for isolation,
divert attention by setting fire.
You've been well trained.
Everything's okay,
but they took Yuriko.
Let me save her at least.
I beg you.
It is a pity.
I should have caught
both of you with my bare hands.
It was all going to
come to this eventually.
Couldn't you have just believed me
when I said I was the Phantom?
You're under arrest by the
authority of Police Department.
You know,
I've been wanting to say this.
You...
Shut the fuck up.
The fuel storage has exploded.
I should've come sooner.
I'm sorry.
This is not professional...
Thanks for making me feel less bad.
Takahara, there's no time for this.
We'll lose the Phantoms.
Tenacious bastard...
Korean blood sure flows in your veins.
Of course you're obsessed with blood.
You know why?
Because you're afraid I might
take my place back from you.
You've gotten to where you are
by slandering my reputation.
And you know so well
that you have no power or guts,
nothing on me.
You gonna shoot me?
Go on.
Do it if you dare.
Shut up, Murayama!
Your father
was murdered by your
own Korean mother, right?
A family murdering each other
like animals.
Filthy, lowly blood line.
Mr. Junji...
You said you'd use neither
a gun nor a knife on me.
All the tires have been slashed.
Mechanic!
The Chief Guard's dead.
It's the Phantom's doing.
I told you this was a waste of time.
Morons. Put me on the phone
with the Chief of Police.
Yamada speaking.
Two Phantoms killed the Chief Guard
and ran off to Kyungsung.
It's a race against time.
Before the end of the night,
we must wipe out the Phantoms
and the entire Shadow Corps
or it'll be the end for us.
I will command the field.
No... Wake up.
Open your eyes!
This is an official order
from the Chief of Police.
I will oversee all operations
regarding the emergency situation.
You're all under my command now.
Is that clear?
Wait up, sweetheart.
I'm sorry for intruding.
We're injured...
Take your time.
Why are you helping us?
The traitors don't get hurt.
Only those defending do.
I told them the goal is
to sweep the entire Shadow Corps.
I restricted the attendants to
Koreans to be sure.
It's been made clear that
Park and Yuriko are to be
shot to death immediately.
Neither Park nor Yuriko
is our biggest priority.
There's someone else
we must find first.
Why am I here...?
You should've just left me.
Dumb cow...
Why didn't you just remain in
the comfort of your family wealth?
Why are you doing this?
You don't come across as
the courageous type.
This was a conviction of my lover.
I want to honor it for her.
You've come far enough.
This is where you stop.
Look who's talking.
You can barely breathe.
You have nothing more at stake.
Stubborn cow...
Allow me to introduce myself first.
I'm Murayama Junji
from the Police Department.
I'll get to the point.
No inauguration ceremony
will take place here today.
This is a trap.
I know all seven members of
the Shadow Corps are here,
and you'll all be apprehended.
But I'm going to give you
one last chance
to give yourselves up.
All of you.
I know it's not easy.
You have reputations to preserve,
causes to uphold.
Actually, I only need
five of you to come forward.
I already have two here.
This girl disguised herself
as an employee of this public hall
to gain access for this old man.
The Shadow Corps were supposed to
get their weapons from him.
The objective: to assassinate
the new Governor-General.
But as you see, all your weapons
are in this crate,
which means that you're unarmed.
What's the point of struggling now?
I feel a sense of duty
to open your eyes to the truth
you blindly choose to ignore,
believing there's still hope
for independence,
the stupid notion that
risking your life is the only way
to love your country.
Let's take a step back
and look at this objectively.
Pathetic Koreans.
You do not have a nation to defend!
Your nation perished 10 years ago!
And you're still clutching to its ghost.
Do you believe
you can still do something?
Let bygones be bygones
and move on.
Open your eyes to reality!
Japan and Joseon share one root!
Paint a greater future
as part of a greater nation!
You are subjects of Imperial Japan.
Repay the sovereign with loyalty.
Come out, Shadow Corps!
Don't budge!
It's not your time to die yet.
Stick it out.
Come on out!
Hold on!
Surrender!
If you see interests,
think then justice.
If you see dangers,
give then your life.
Dongwoo!
Sister...
It's the Phantom! Upstairs!
Get people out first.
Stand back.
We're the Shadow Corps, you bastards!
Follow me.
Catch him!
Hold tight!
Don't you get tired?
Why are you so relentless?
What is Joseon?
Murayama!
Drop your weapon!
Sir!
Go on... Continue fighting,
generation after generation,
forever.
You're going to lose anyway.
Don't feel sorry for surviving.
It's not that...
It's so cramped
and so dark...
I feel sorry to put him here.
We'll go above ground one day.
All of us.
When we get our country back,
maybe I'll quit smoking.
Why? It'll taste even better.
The new Governor-General's inauguration
was successfully conducted.
More than 300 distinguished guests
have shared the joy and vision of
Joseon under the leadership
of the newly appointed
Governor-General.
In the wake of the recent
terrorist disturbance,
we find there are still some people
undeserving of advanced civilization
and all its benefits.
And so, as of today's inauguration,
I resolve to establish one empire!
Move your car.
You're causing a traffic jam.
A man is hurt, heartless bastard!
Hey, you bastards!
What is it?
I'll look into it, sir.
Find out what's going on.
Yes, sir.
WANTED
From Phantom
We'll commence the operation
We shall not stop
until we succeed
PHANTOM
Written and directed by
Lee Hae-Young
Inspired by the novel
'THE MESSAGE' by MAI JIA
Sul Kyung Gu
Lee Hanee
Park So Dam
Park Hae Soo
Seo Hyun Woo / Kim Dong Hee
Produced by
Park UnKyoung
Co-produced by
QI JI Yan Yan