Aren't you going to eat anything?
What the hell are you all doing?
-Sir.
-Is this the time to be sleeping?
Hello, sir.
What about the warrant?
We weren't able to request it yet.
Wasn't the murder site found?
Well, we found some evidence, but…
It's pretty much like we didn't.
-Yes.
-What are you saying?
Where's Park Mu-gyeong?
Sir.
What the hell have you been doing?
What's your plan for the warrant?
The prosecutor on duty
was one of the Boudoir's purchasers.
She got arrested
knowing the warrant would be denied.
-Bring the suspect.
-What?
Yes, sir.
Why, that little…
Coffee?
What about me?
Have a cup of coffee.
This is nice.
There isn't much time left.
Not for you, there isn't.
I wondered why
you'd come here on your own.
You voluntarily got arrested…
so that you'd be released.
I'm not the killer, that's why.
We can't prove you faked your death
and tried to live as someone else.
You came here,
so you're not a flight risk.
And the DNA analysis proved
that you weren't the killer.
I won't be requesting a warrant.
It'll be denied anyway.
What about the injustice
I've suffered in here?
Who will compensate me for that?
I'm the victim here.
And you're the perpetrator.
"The victim"?
Speaking of which,
it seems you and the victim
were very close.
Why pretend not to know her?
What's up?
The victim really came here
from the boutique?
The taxi company verified it.
-Search the place. Now.
-Yes, sir.
We're not finding prints or anything.
It's far too clean here too.
There's nothing.
It looks like everything's been wiped.
Come check over here, please.
PARKING GARAGE
Excuse me.
Do you work here?
Yes.
-Police.
-Right.
Did you ever see the people
working in the next building over?
The place should be empty right now.
Everyone got taken away
in a recent immigration raid.
When was that?
Maybe, like, ten days ago?
Your hand…
-Sorry?
-The calluses on your hand.
This? It's from using
a leather skiving knife for years.
It's a garment cutter's mark.
The victim worked at a bag factory,
and those who could verify that
have been deported.
This is the first I've heard of it.
The boutique told us
the dead person was Sarah Kim.
Then
was the victim impersonating Sarah Kim?
Or are you impersonating the victim
right now?
Choi Chae-u said the same thing.
That the impersonator killed Sarah Kim.
Then who's the person
sitting in front of me?
How interesting.
I'm Sarah Kim, of course.
Prove it.
You probably can't.
It really doesn't matter
since both are fake anyway.
I told you I'm Sarah Kim.
Sarah Kim does not exist.
You've been impersonating Sarah Kim,
who doesn't exist.
No, that's not it.
Then the victim found out
you were an unregistered person
with no identity.
-No.
-You pretended to be Sarah Kim perfectly.
And thanks to that,
staging a murder was also easy for you.
The victim had planned to kill you
from the start.
But you managed to use that plan
to your advantage.
Because you wanted to live as Sarah Kim.
How will you prove that?
I'll make you prove it yourself.
Did you like the coffee?
I bought it
near the broadcasting station in Sangam.
You were arrested two days ago
at 6:05 p.m.,
so you can watch it
right when you get out.
The prime time news tonight
will cover the Boudoir scam.
I have people from news outlets
among my clients too.
I told you.
Nobody would be willing
to become victims of fraud.
This is the notebook of Woo Hyo-eun,
former Boudoir manager.
It's all here.
From the names of your clients
to sensitive details
they'd rather not reveal.
How will people react
once the Boudoir scam is exposed?
Secrets come to light in the end,
people leave all too readily,
the truth is always brutal,
and illusions are bound to shatter.
To shake you…
I had no choice but to shake up Boudoir.
Are detectives allowed
to arbitrarily leak case info?
You'll be terminated now, not demoted.
I told you I'd go all the way.
Are you trying to die together?
I'm just chasing a criminal.
If you stop, I stop.
Perhaps…
Boudoir could've been real.
If you had been real.
But you're a fake,
and that made Boudoir fake.
You don't have much time left now.
The so-called "Boudoir-gate"
is causing a stir.
No one doubted its authenticity
until the fraud was exposed.
People were deceived by the illusion
of limited editions and VIP status…
That bitch behind the Boudoir fraud
should be executed.
Get lost, seriously.
Why do you live like this?
Are you a fucking idiot?
Flaunting is a sign of insecurity.
Imitating someone like that
is a form of mental illness.
How pathetic and miserable do you have
to be to steal someone else's life?
All you'll ever be is an imitation.
Secrets come to light in the end,
people leave all too readily,
and illusions are bound to shatter.
Perhaps
Boudoir could've been real.
If you had been real.
Voluntary appearance and confession.
-That may reduce a sentence.
-How are they doing?
They just began.
Cooperating and showing genuine remorse
may act as mitigating factors.
This is the extent I can help you.
The rest is up to you.
I've already decided.
The real thing needs no explanation,
and fakes can't exist without one.
Which is why
I have a lot to explain, starting now.
Excuse me.
Can I help you?
Is the factory manager here?
They're on a long business trip overseas.
-Can I sit for a bit before I go?
-Sure.
Thank you.
It's not easy to find a factory
that handles leather goods well.
Because it's not profitable.
You speak Korean well.
Because I need to earn money.
Your feet must hurt. Use this.
Thank you.
You make knockoffs here.
Sorry?
Your manager was taken away for it.
Excuse me. No, wait.
It's okay. I won't report you.
It's fine. I'll just take a look.
Wow.
This is more than just okay. It's…
Who made this one?
Are you Korean?
What's your name?
Kim Mi-jeong.
Want to make a handbag together?
But how do you tell
the fake and real ones apart?
Burning them is the easiest way.
Synthetic leather deforms
in an ugly way as it burns.
The real thing chars, turning into ash.
But since that's hard to do,
we listen to the zipper.
"Listen"?
The real ones even sound different.
Want to listen?
I'll go with this one.
You have good instincts.
This is a product
used by Goyard and Loro Piana.
Sir, do you have anything
of better quality?
All right, follow me.
Here.
What do young people know?
They make great faux leather these days.
If you guess which one is cowhide leather,
I'll give you 10% off.
I think it's the one on the left.
See? You got it wrong.
The one on the right is cowhide.
What?
You can't burn that!
Burning it will tell me if it's fake.
It's burning! Come on.
So this one is real.
Man, this may not be leather,
but it's still pricey.
-Thank you.
-Enjoy.
How did you know
the one on the right was fake?
What would I know about leather?
But I know how to read people.
You seem different from other people.
How so?
You're supplying the bags to Dongdaemun,
but you focus on every detail,
as if making luxury goods.
I want to become like you.
You must not know how to read people.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have changed the design
without asking.
No.
I've never seen anything better.
-Wow!
-Wow.
Mi-jeong.
-Congratulations.
-Never disappoints.
Who could that be?
We're not expecting anyone.
-I'll get it.
-Check who it is.
Hide.
It's me.
It's Ms. Kim.
It'd be a shame to just end things.
Can I come in?
This is tasty.
Today is Boudoir's birthday!
Happy Birthday!
-Love you. Congratulations!
-Blow it out.
Thank you.
-Congratulations.
-We love you.
Production will start
as soon as I get the investment.
I'll leave things in your trusted hands.
I'm only good at making replicas.
It's fake talent.
If you can't tell the fake from the real,
is it really fake?
I'll give you a generous advance payment,
so let's work together for a long time.
Can you
give that to me in cash?
Cash is convenient and simple.
May I ask why?
Also, you're young
and working at a place like this.
Are you on the run?
It's not that different.
I was actually joking.
I ran away from home at a very young age.
I couldn't get a resident card,
so I couldn't open a bank account.
I'm not that different.
What do you mean?
The running away part.
Give it to me here.
Mi-jeong, can you take a look at this?
Like this, right?
No, I got the dates mixed up.
Hurry up!
You just need to check
my measurements, right?
Mi-jeong.
I understand.
Can you do me a favor?
Sure. What do you need?
Can you do a fitting for me
at the boutique?
I barely managed to make a reservation,
but I accidentally double-booked.
You want me to go?
They need my measurements
as it's my first time.
Where did my wallet go?
I have money too.
Come here.
We're the same height
and have similar builds.
Don't you think we look quite alike?
I don't think we look alike at all.
Say my name, and they'll do everything.
What name is the reservation under?
It's Sarah Kim.
I seem like a different person.
This is what you really look like.
Maybe it's because
I've heard so much about you,
but I feel like I know you already.
Actually, I'm…
-Here.
-Okay.
Shall we try on the earrings too?
May I call you Sarah?
Sure.
Time to eat. What do you want?
Let's go to eat.
Let's go eat, Mi-jeong.
Go ahead.
Mi-jeong.
It's a gift.
That's my number, so save it.
Here. Come with me.
You can learn the world
without going to college.
Thank you.
For the phone too.
I figured you wouldn't have one
if you didn't have a bank account.
I'm lending you my name briefly.
Call me if you need stronger meds
than aspirin.
If you don't have an account or phone,
you probably never even visited a doctor
when you were sick.
Why are you
so nice to me?
You remind me…
of someone I know.
No, you must be mistaken.
I told you I've never used my card there.
The impersonation went on
for over six months, but no one knew.
Many had heard the name,
but only a handful knew
what Sarah Kim looked like.
That's possible for others,
but you must've known.
It is not lies that blind us.
It's trust.
There wasn't a single honest person
in this relationship…
but we trusted each other too much.
What was that?
If you can't tell the fake from the real,
is it really fake?
If you can't tell the fake from the real…
Ms. Kim?
Can I come in for a bit?
Can I ask what's wrong?
I just…
didn't pay back the money
I borrowed from a friend,
and so I got beaten up.
Trusting something trustworthy is easy.
But trusting someone
even in an impossible moment?
That's real trust.
I trust you.
It felt like
I was the one talking just now.
Did it?
They say people start talking alike
when they grow close.
Those earrings.
They're the same as mine.
They don't really
suit me, do they?
No, they suit you well.
You know, fakes look
like the real thing nowadays.
And this.
You have it.
I don't need it anymore.
Thank you.
But…
why do you assume these are fake?
May we have a word with you?
We need to check a matter
regarding the membership card you used.
Don't you know who I am?
I'm Sarah Kim.
The card you used was reported stolen.
Please come with us.
Whatever, damn it.
Let go. I said let go.
Let go!
The card owner wants
to resolve this amicably.
She says to just let her go.
She's just letting me go?
Man.
Consider yourself lucky.
Seems the owner prefers
not to involve the police.
She's not reporting me?
But why?
JULIET WITH A GUN
I've never seen anything better.
This bag.
How much is it?
It's 50 million won.
It's our most popular steady seller.
Its unique stitches are made possible
by the delicate craftsmanship
of a seasoned artisan.
It's one of the reasons
it's considered a work of art,
not just a handbag.
"A work of art"?
Yes, that's correct.
I made that.
I'm the one who made that.
Ms. Kim?
It was you. You've been impersonating me.
Why did you go through my room?
It was you, of all people.
There were all those rumors
about how I was vulgar and nouveau riche.
That was you.
Can't I do that?
Why can't I have what you have?
We promised to work together
for a long time.
"A long time"?
"Together"?
Then you shouldn't have gotten in my way.
You should've imitated me properly.
And at this vital time. How dare you…
You shouldn't talk to me that way.
Not after all I've done for you.
You're fired.
Quietly pack your stuff and leave.
Weren't we indispensable to each other?
Why would you ruin that?
Keep acting in desperation like that.
"Desperation"?
She stole her name…
isolated her from those around her…
Immigration office?
I'd like to report illegal immigrants.
…got rid of those who knew them…
erased the traces
that would identify them…
Desperation.
Fuck.
…and became the perfect Sarah Kim.
Are you admitting to the murder?
I killed her.
Okay!
We got her.
Serenity is the only gift of confession.
I hope you can find peace now.
-That concludes the interrogation--
-I impersonated her.
And I killed her to become Sarah Kim.
My name is…
Kim Mi-jeong.
KIM MI-JEONG
THE ART OF SARAH
Subtitle translation by: Yung Un Choi