BOYD:
Previously on
From.
Boyd, are you seriously okay
with him taking magic mushrooms
that he found
in a haunted forest?
If there are answers
in his head,
we need to get them out.
Okay, you ready for this?
Fuck no.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
BOYD:
She's making a golem.
It's a giant made of clay.
It protects people.
It's a champion.
That thing
I carried inside me,
I still feel it.
It goes both ways.
He feels how afraid I am.
But making this,
it makes me feel strong.
VICTOR:
I thought
his yellow suit was funny.
He came in a car
just like the rest of us.
But he wasn't like us.
When I found Mom out
by The Bottle Tree, I saw him.
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
VICTOR: He was eating her.
Oh, God.
[MUSIC TURNS OMINOUS]
[BONES CRUNCH]
[GROANS]
I can't imagine
what this is like for her.
[SOPHIA SCREAMS]
KRISTI: Wait!
I'm coming! Don't move, okay?
Where does it hurt?
[WHIMPERS] My... My arm.
This could actually be
an instruction manual
on how to save my dad.
[MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[MUSIC SOFTENS]
[BREATHES SHAKILY] Fuck!
It didn't fucking work.
I need to find
the Lake of Tears.
My dad told me it's here.
Maybe once I find it,
it can make him better.
Mom?
[MUSIC RISES]
[MUSIC FADES]
[WATER LAPPING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING, SQUAWKING]
I'm telling you,
those are bodies.
We should pull them in.
Are you insane?
Something floats up
from the bottom
of a nightmare lake,
and the first thing you want
to do is drag it ashore?
[SIGHS]
You may run things
back at Colony House,
but we all get a say here.
Look, we have
to sleep here tonight.
Even if we took off
running right now,
we'd never make it back
to town before dark.
I don't know about you,
but I would feel
a whole lot better
knowing who or what
just floated
to the surface of this lake.
She's right.
You're quiet.
What do you think?
Let's pull 'em in.
[DONNA GRUNTING]
Come on!
[GRUNTS]
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
[ELLIS GRUNTING]
[DONNA GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
Okay.
[PANTING]
Jeez.
Now what?
Get it up on land.
Okay.
[MUSIC FADES]
I'm sorry
we couldn't save you.
I really wanted it
to be the Lake of Tears.
I know.
Mom?
Yeah?
Are we gonna be okay?
I hope so.
Hey, Boyd.
[ELECTRICITY BUZZING]
Boyd.
I think the mushrooms kicked in.
BOYD: Jade?
[SIGHS] It's a little
more direct than I expected.
Okay.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[SKITTERING]
Uh...
[YELPS] Oh, Jesus! Fuck!
BOYD: Oh, what?
[SCREAMS]
Jade! Whoa, whoa!
Hey, Jade! Jade!
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey!
Look, there's nothing there.
Nothing there.
Oh, God.
[MUSIC CONCLUDES]
This may not have been
such a great idea.
[GROANS]
Hey, maybe we just...
Maybe we go see Kristi
and we just...
[GROANS] No, no, no. No.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
I have to do this.
But I need you.
I need you to be
my anchor, my guide.
You need to tell me what's real,
and, you know, what isn't.
And we need a safe word,
something that you can say
if things start to, you know,
go off the rails,
something that'll... [INHALES]
...bring me back.
Okay. Safe word.
What's it going to be?
[INHALES DEEPLY] Uh...
[SIGHS]
Capricorn.
Capricorn, okay.
JADE: Yeah.
Okay.
Let's go get weird.
Right.
All right, where do we start?
We go this way.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[ELECTRICITY BUZZING]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
MARIELLE: You just take
nice deep breaths, okay?
You're gonna do great.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Okay, ready?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Maybe we don't have to do this.
I mean, maybe we should wait.
[HESITATES] It doesn't...
It really doesn't hurt
nearly as much as it did.
I know you're scared,
but if we don't reset this bone,
you're not gonna heal properly.
And then we're gonna have
much bigger problems
than we can handle here, okay?
Okay.Okay.
Just breathe.
Okay. We'll go
on the count of three.
And I need you to take
a nice, big, deep breath in.
Ready?
Big breath.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
One...
[BONES CRUNCH]
[GASPS, SCREAMS]
Sorry, I know.
That was the worst part.
Just thought it'd be better
if we did it quick.
You're okay.
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
KRISTI: Do you have the brace?
No, it's in the ambulance.
I'll be right back.
You did great.
[BREATHES RAPIDLY]
MARIELLE: You cut your hair.
Looks nice.
Thanks.
It's a long story.
[METAL CLINKS]
[MARIELLE GASPS]
[GRUNTS]
[CHAIN RATTLES]
[GROANS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHAINS RATTLING]
[WHIMPERS, GROANS]
[DISTORTED SCREAMS OVER RADIO]
[SCREAMS ECHOING]
[GROANS]
[SCREAMING CONTINUES]
[MUSIC RISES]
[MUSIC FADES]
["QUE SERA SERA" PLAYING]
♪ When I was just a little boy
♪ I asked my father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be handsome?"
♪ "Will I be rich?" ♪
♪ Here's what he said to me ♪
♪ Que sera, sera
♪ Whatever will be, will be
♪ The future's not ours to see
♪ Que sera, sera
♪ What will be, will be
♪ Now I have children
Of my own ♪
♪ They ask their father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be pretty?"
♪ "Will I be rich?" ♪
♪ I tell them tenderly ♪
♪ Que sera, sera
♪ Whatever will be, will be
♪ The future's not ours to see
♪ Que sera, sera
♪ What will be, will be
[SONG CONCLUDES]
PATTY: They're dolls.
Jesus.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
ELLIS: What are you doing?
Making sure
there's no more surprises.
[GRUNTS]
Why would someone put those
in the lake?
Shit.
What?
There's only one reason
I can think of
that people put life-sized dolls
full of stuffing outside.
Scarecrows.
Put them in the field
to scare the birds away.
What if the reason
these were in the lake
is to keep
something else down there
from coming out? [EXHALES]
[EERIE MUSIC BUILDS]
[MUSIC FADES]
[BIRDSONG ECHOING]
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
[RETCHES]
[GAGS, SPITS]
[GRUNTS, EXHALES]
You okay?
[SIGHS] Yeah, I'm okay.
I'm okay.
So, uh... So what now?
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
BOYD: Jade.
What?
BOYD: What exactly
is the plan?
What, do we just
walk around the forest all day
waiting for the trees
to start talking?
[CHUCKLES]
BOYD: What--
What are we looking for?
You're right. Oh!
BOYD: About what?
I haven't asked the question.
We need to ask
the right question.
Set the... the...
the right intention.
Okay, I got this.
Show me what I used to know...
that I can't remember.
Show me what's in here
that'll help us leave.
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
[SOFT VIOLIN MUSIC PLAYING]
Do you hear that?
No.
[JADE BREATHES SHAKILY]
[MUSIC GROWS LOUDER]
Oh, God.
What's wrong?
What do you see?
JADE: Something I forgot.
It's me...
when I was 12 years old.
It's the day
my grandmother died.
I don't understand.
JADE: She asked me
to play for her, so I did. I...
I played all day.
And at some point,
I... I knew she...
she just wasn't
in the room anymore.
But I couldn't look at her.
I just kept playing.
'Cause I knew
the moment I stopped...
she was really gone.
So I just played
and played and played.
[SOBS SOFTLY]
Goddamnit. God... Goddamnit!
This isn't what I asked for!
I want to remember
why we're stuck here!
how to get home!
I don't want this!
BOYD: [ECHOING] Hey, hey.
Jade, Jade, Jade, Jade.
[YELPS]
It's okay.
I want to go back.
I just want to go back!
I want to go back!
[GASPS, BREATHES SHAKILY]
Oh, shit.
How did you get here?
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
BOYD: Jade?
[JADE GASPS, BREATHES HEAVILY]
Oh, Jesus.
BOYD: Jade?
[JADE PANTING]
Talk to me.
He...
It's the guy from the...
Fuck.
Where is he?
Where did he go? He was...
MAN: Anghkooey.
[GASPS]
[SOFT VIOLIN MUSIC PLAYING]
BOYD: Jade!
MAN: Anghkooey.
I fucking heard you!
Stop it. Stop playing that song!
[MUSIC STOPS]
BOYD: Jade?
I'm gonna need an update.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Some asshole I saw
nailed to a tree
out at the settlement
wants me to drink
the same skull of blood
he's been schlepping around
with him since we met.
And he keeps saying--
Anghkooey.
Doesn't that mean "remember"?
Yes.
So drink it.
Easy for you to say.
BOYD: Jade...
the blood is not real.
[HAUNTING MUSICAL STING PLAYS]
Well, it looks real enough.
Hey, maybe
he's trying to tell you
how to get your answers.
[SIGHS]
[DISTORTED] Anghkooey.
Don't drink it.
What?
Jade...
the blood isn't real.
JADE: Goddamnit.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
[JADE GLUGS]
[RETCHES]
[GRUNTS, BREATHES HEAVILY]
You good?
[MUSIC CONCLUDES]
YOUNG JADE: [IN FRENCH] Shit.
Why "shit"?
You're not the one
who had to drink it.
I told you not to.
You don't get to pick
and choose your memories.
Now you're going to see.
Things that you don't
want to see.
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
[IN ENGLISH]
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey, what's... what's...
Jade?
[SIGHS]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Come in.
Hey.
Wow.
I'm really, uh... I'm...
I'm starting
to see the shape now.
Did you need something?
Yeah, I... [SIGHS]
I just...
I wanted to say I'm sorry.
Earlier, I should have tried
to listen more
instead of reacting.
We're strongest when
we back each other up,
and I was not doing that.
I got scared,
and I should have...
uh, backed you up.
That's all.
Thank you, Kenny.
Was there something else?
[SIGHS]
It's okay, you can ask.
You said you were
still connected to that thing.
What does that feel like?
Terrifying. [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
In a way
I can't really explain.
Every night, I...
[SIGHS]
...I go to that window
and I look outside,
knowing that
one of these nights
I'm gonna see him
standing there,
staring back at me.
What happens then?
I don't know.
Listen, if you need, um...
if you need anything...
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Thank you, Kenny.
KENNY: Henry.
Uh, Kenny, hey.
Is that from the bar?
Yeah, I just, um...
I keep a little stash
on hand, you know,
just to take
the edge off. [CHUCKLES]
Okay.
Help yourself.
No, thanks. I'm good.
Hey.
What's taking so long?
[GRUNTS]
Did you find the splint?
Hey.
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
What's wrong?
Um...
Uh, I'm fine.
I just needed a minute.
Found it.
I'm fine.
Baby.
Hey.
I'm fine, okay?
KRISTI: You're not fine.
MARIELLE: Kristi, leave it.
I'm good.
KRISTI: Fuck.
[SIGHS]
Once in a while,
I stop and think about
the types of things
that have become normal for us.
I mean,
we're sitting here packing
life-sized dolls full of rocks
'cause we think
that they're gonna...
Take my advice.
Stop thinking about it.
Think about something else.
Think about
getting back to your wife.
We need to get these fuckers
back in the water.
Do you really think there's
something bad in the water?
I think I'd rather not find out.
Thanks.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC FADES]
Tabitha, can you help me
with something?
Yeah.
DONNA: Over here.
DONNA: Okay. I saw that look
on your face.
What's going on?
Something about those dolls.
I don't know.
It was familiar. I don't know.
Good familiar, bad familiar?
TABITHA: I don't know.
I don't know.
I think I've seen them before.
Okay. Try-- Try to remember.
I'm trying, Donna. I'm trying.
All I see are, like,
little pieces and their faces.
And it's... it's weird.
Is there something in that lake
that we need to be afraid of?
I don't know.
We're ready
to drag them back in.
Okay, let's do it.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Just grab them.
DONNA: Okay.
Okay.
[SIGHS]
Come on.
Careful, Patty. Careful.
ELLIS: Yeah.
[GRUNTS]
Yeah.
[GROANS]
[ELLIS GRUNTING]
[MUSIC CONCLUDES]
JADE: Hey.
Hey, what does that mean?
That I'm gonna see things
that I don't wanna see, huh?
Hey. Answer me!
[ECHOING] Hey!
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
[EERIE MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Hello?
[SOUND DISTORTS]
Hey, Boyd, did you see...
Boyd?
Boyd!
[MUSIC STOPS ABRUPTLY]
Don't do that. Don't fucking
leave me like that.
I didn't.
I've been here the whole time.
Hey, are you good?
Yeah, I'm... I'm...
I'm good.
BOYD: You're sure?
Jade, we can stop.
If this is too much,
we can still go back.
[SOFT VIOLIN MUSIC PLAYING]
This way.
Jade. Jade.
[MUSIC GROWS LOUDER]
[SOFT VIOLIN MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WIND RUSHING]
Boyd...
where are we?
We're outside Colony House.
What do you see?
[SIGHS] I warned you.
The answers you sought
come wrapped in painful truths.
[MUSIC CONCLUDES]
[SIGHS]
Dad?
[MUMBLES, INHALES SHARPLY]
I don't think you should
look at that anymore.
[MUMBLES ERRATICALLY]
I just, uh...
I... I just...
What do you do here for fun?
What?
Well, so much time
just sitting around
worrying if you're gonna
survive the night.
You can't forget to live.
You... You have to live, son.
Come on, let's-- let's...
[GROANS]
Whoa.
No, I'm fine.
I'm okay.
Just... Just...
Dad.
HENRY: Just...
VICTOR: Dad?
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
You got any cards?
What?
Cards to play. You got cards?
Maybe in the kitchen.
What are you making?
That's nice.
VICTOR: Dad.
See? That's... Good for you.
Hey, these guys are having fun.
Is he okay?
Yeah.
Does this work?
[DISCORDANT KEYBOARD MUSIC
PLAYING]
Ooh, look at that.
Maybe you should go lie down.
Lie down?
I don't want to lie down.
I want to...
["LEAVING ON A JET PLANE"
PLAYING SLOWLY ON KEYBOARD]
♪ All my bags are packed ♪
♪ I'm ready to go
[LAUGHS]
♪ I'm standing here
Outside your door ♪
[CHUCKLES]
♪ I hate to wake you up
To say goodbye ♪
You remember? That's fun.
♪ So kiss...
♪ Kiss me and smile for me ♪
You... right?
[GROANS]
♪ Tell me that
You'll wait for me ♪
♪ Hold me like
You'll never let me go ♪
Dad, stop.
You remember
when we used to play?
[SHUSHES]
We used to sit at the piano
and you would...
I'd give you a note.
That was your note.
And you... you were so little.
And-- But your mom,
she had such a beautiful voice.
You remember?
[WHISPERS] Dad, please.
HENRY: You must... Come on.
We-- We'd sit there
and we'd talk about
how we'd all go
around the world someday
and see
all the beautiful things
and we'd be...
♪ Leaving on a jet plane
[SHUSHES]
Come on.
♪ Don't know
When I'll be back again ♪
♪ Oh, babe, I hate to go
[LAUGHS]
♪ So kiss me and smile for me
[SOBBING]
♪ Tell me
That you'll wait for me ♪
♪ Hold me like
You'll never let me go ♪
♪ Go...
[DISCORDANT KEYBOARD MUSIC
PLAYING]
Hey, Henry, can we--
No, no! No!
[MUSIC STOPS]
HENRY: Who the fuck
are you to tell me...
Do you know what he did?
What he did to my wife?
[DISCORDANT KEYBOARD MUSIC
PLAYS]
Henry, please,
let's take it upstairs, right?
[HESITATES] Victor, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean-- I...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
Okay.
Okay, okay.
HENRY: I'm sorry!
Okay, let's... let's go.
No. No, you...
You... You don't know.
Oh, okay.
You don't know what he did.
Victor, show him the picture.
Show him the picture
of what he did. [GRUNTS]
What's wrong with you?
Show him what he did!
Okay, okay, okay.
[WHISPERS] Okay, okay.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC FADES]
What's the fire for?
Hold on.
You telling me you didn't
bring the marshmallows?
Are we gonna be okay?
Of course we are.
'Cause I don't want
Julie to be alone.
Tell you what,
first thing in the morning,
we're going to get up,
grab our packs,
and get the heck out of here.
Okay?
Go on. Get in the cabin.
I like it when you're here.
It's not scary
when you're around.
[CHUCKLES]
JULIE: Randall...
listen to me. Listen.
RANDALL: The one time
you tried doing something
that would have actually proved
it was real, it didn't work!
JULIE: This isn't just about me
or the bookmark.
Okay? This is about you
and you being scared
of those ruins.
Are you serious?
JULIE: You're a fucking
coward, Randall.
At least I'm not a little child
that doesn't know
what the fuck's
in front of her face.
[SCOFFS] Really?
What is that, huh?
This place is fucking
with your head
because it knows
how much you miss your dad.
JULIE: No.
You're wrong.
I watched you have two seizures
in two days, right?
You're literally
frying your own brain,
so why don't you tell me
what's more likely?
That you're traveling
through chapters of a story?
Or that one of these days
you're gonna have a seizure
that doesn't stop?
JULIE: I don't care.
That is a risk
I am willing to take.
Then you're a moron.
And if your dad
was here right now,
he'd be fucking stunned
at how goddamn stupid you are.
You're only angry
at me right now
'cause you know I'm right.
[EXHALES]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
MARIELLE: I'm fine.
KRISTI: You're clearly not okay.
Okay, I was having
a moment, that's all!
KRISTI: That was way more
than just a moment, Marielle.
Okay, so this place
has never gotten to you before?
Oh, my God.
Really?
You haven't just needed a minute
to freak the fuck out?
It is not a big deal.
KRISTI: Mary!
Just give it a rest, Kristi.
[MUSIC RISES]
[MARIELLE GASPS]
Sorry.
It's okay.
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMS ECHOING]
[SCREAMS]
Mary!
[MUSIC SOFTENS]
[MARIELLE SOBS]
[SHRIEKS, WHIMPERS]
[SOBS]
[SOBBING]
[MUSIC FADES]
[SOFT VIOLIN MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC STOPS]
What do you see?
It's the people
from my hallucinations.
Why are they here?
Why were they playing that song?
You know why.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
They're all me.
These were the lives
that I lived here.
Some of them, and many more.
Look at them closely.
What do you see?
[MUSIC DARKENS]
None of them are ripped apart.
They weren't killed
by the creatures in the woods.
These men were murdered.
By who?
You know who.
[IN FRENCH]
Minnows in a shark's net.
[IN ENGLISH]
"Minnows in a shark's net"?
What does that...
Oh, my God.
They were murdered
by the people in town.
What? Jade,
who are you talking--
Just give me one...
YOUNG JADE:
It's always the same.
Once they learn the truth
about who you are,
that it was you that
the children were calling for,
first they blame you,
then they hate you.
Eventually, they kill you.
And Tabitha?
For Tabitha, it's worse.
Whoa. [BREATHES DEEPLY]
If I die every time...
What are you saying?
Are you saying
there's no way home?
[ECHOING] How...
How does this help?
How do I stop it
from happening this time?
Answer me!
Jade, hey. Jade. Jade.
[MUSIC CONCLUDES]
[MUMBLES]
Okay, let's back him up
this way.
[MUMBLES, GROANS]
KENNY: Okay. One, two, three.
[HENRY GROANS]
KENNY: Okay.
[HENRY GRUNTS]
KENNY: All right.
Are you gonna be
all right, Victor?
Yeah, I'll take care of him.
[SIGHS]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Hey, Victor.
[CLICKS TONGUE] What, uh...
What was he talking about?
The man in the yellow suit
ate my mother.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
But I never
should have told him.
Hello?
Where the hell did he go?
Hey, can we just
take a minute here?
Why the fuck
were you talking about
people murdering you out there?
[JADE GASPS]
Hey.
Over here.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASPS]
What are we doing?
Why are we down here?
[IN FRENCH]
You have to clear the way
to see the path.
[IN ENGLISH] Hey.
[JADE GRUNTS]
Hey! Be careful.
Give me a hand! Come on!
[OBJECTS CLATTER]
[GRUNTS]
Boyd...
do you see a door in that wall?
Yep.
[OBJECTS CLATTER]
[MUSIC FADES]
Here you go.
Thank you, Sophia.
Can you try to tell us
what happened in the ambulance?
Uh, the radio came on.
Okay.
And?
I heard them screaming.
Who's... Who's "them"?
MARIELLE: Everyone.
Every single person
who's ever died here.
That's what it was like for me
when we were in the chamber.
All I could hear,
all I could feel was...
the suffering
of every single person
who's ever died here.
I kept telling myself
it wasn't real,
that it couldn't be.
But when the radio came on,
it was like
all that pain and horror
just shot through me again.
You're a prophet.
What?
Maybe God has chosen you
to hear their suffering.
Okay, I can't do this.
Mary! Mary, wait.
MARIELLE: No.
Just...
[SCOFFS]
...wait.
I've seen this
happen here before.
This place, it gets
in people's heads, and it--
This is different, Kristi.
There is something old here.
Something... ancient.
And it's feeding
off our suffering,
and it doesn't stop.
Even after we die,
we are still trapped here.
And we never get to leave.
[SOBS]
[SIGHS]
Sometimes I forget
he's just a kid.
He's always seemed
so grown up.
He's always been like that.
Jim used to call him
the little professor.
So curious
and full of questions.
Maybe he could figure out
what's in the goddamn lake.
Stop it.
Sorry.
How much longer till sunrise?
Five minutes less
than the last time
someone asked.
Just try to get some sleep.
You're joking, right?
[SIGHS]
All we have to do
is hold on until the morning
and we can get
the hell out of here
and back to the nightmare
we understand.
Got a long walk
in the morning, so...
[SOFT VOICE VOCALIZING
IN DISTANCE]
What the hell is that?
[VOCALIZING CONTINUES]
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Tabitha?
I know that sound.
The dolls...
[YOUNG TABITHA VOCALIZING]
TABITHA:
They were smaller.
They were mine.
I was playing with them.
What is she talking about?
[SHUSHES]
Mom?
What else?
A man, he was angry.
He came and took them from me.
He said
they gave him nightmares,
so he threw them in the lake.
But one day the man died.
And his nightmares...
his nightmares
came out of the lake.
[SCREAMS]
Oh, my God, Donna.
We have to go.
We have to go right now.
Tabitha, we can't--
TABITHA: Donna.
No, you don't understand.
You don't understand.
We're not safe here!
We can't stay here.
No, there's--
We have a talisman on the door.
No, a talisman won't protect us.
Not from this.
ROGER: How do you know that?
How the fuck
do you know any of that?
[SCREAMS]
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Go! Go! Run!
[PATTY SCREAMS]
Go! Go! Come on! Go!
[INDISTINCT CLAMORING]
TABITHA: Ethan!
ELLIS: Go! Get out!
ROGER: Oh, God! Oh, my God.
[SCREAMS]
[GROWLS]
ELLIS: Hey! Get off him!
[ROGER SCREAMS]
Oh, my God! [SCREAMS]
ELLIS: Donna!
Ellis!
[WHISPERS] Where's Patty?
[WHISPERS] She's not with you?
[WHISPERS] No!
Shit!
Ellis!
Fuck! [GROANS]
No, Donna, please stay, stay!
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
[MUSIC RISES]
[SCREAMS]
Mom!
It's okay.
[HAUNTING MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMING]
No! [SCREAMS]
[SCREAMS]
[FIRE SIZZLES]
[PATTY SCREAMS]
[ELLIS GRUNTS]
Hey! Come on!
[SCREAMS]
ELLIS: We gotta go!
Go!
DONNA: We have to run.
No matter what happens,
we have to--
TABITHA: Donna!
Donna! Donna, no!
Donna! Donna!
[DONNA GRUNTS]
[CHOKES]
[MUSIC RISES]
[TABITHA GRUNTS]
[GROWLS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASPS]
[BREATHES RAPIDLY]
[THUDS]
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
Donna! Hey, are you okay?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[GRUNTS, PANTS]
[PANTING]
What just happened?
[MUSIC FADES]
I remembered.
I remembered how to hurt them.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[WHIMPERS]
[MUSIC CONCLUDES]
[JADE GRUNTING]
[PANTS]
Oh, fucking...
Jesus.
Boyd!
The fuck are you?
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
Okay.
[MUMBLES INDISTINCTLY]
[GRUNTS]
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Fuck.
Boyd. Boyd!
Boyd.
[DRAMATIC MUSICAL STING]
[SCREAMS]
BOYD: Hey! [SHUSHES]
[SHUSHES]
Hey.
Jade, we have to go.
We cannot be down here.
But this isn't real.
This can't be real.
BOYD: Jade! Listen to me.
What? Huh?
Capricorn, okay?
Capricorn, this is real.
You asked me to be your anchor,
so fucking listen to me.
No, Boyd.
We're just in Colony House.
The tunnels aren't this close.
Close? We've been walking down
that creepy hallway for...
It stops now! Let's go.
Okay. Okay.
Okay. All right. Huh?
Hey!
I will drag you out of here
if I fucking have to.
Okay. All right. Okay.
[EERIE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JADE BREATHES HEAVILY]
[EXHALES]
This is where
the children were sacrificed.
How does knowing that
get us home?
Tabitha and I,
we already tried to save them.
We have tried so many times.
[HESITATES]
Is there something here?
Is there something,
something we need?
Tell me how we save them
when we've already failed.
Hi, Jade.
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
CREATURE: You should have
listened to Boyd.No!
But you were never really
the smart one, were you?
[YELLS]
No! No! No, no, no, no!
[YELLS] No, no!
[GROANS]
Get the fuck off of me!
[MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
Stop! [GRUNTS]
[GRUNTS]
No! No! No!
No!
Anghkooey.
[SCREAMS]
Jade! Jade!
Hey, hey, hey! Oh!
Oh, are you okay?
You okay?
[MUSIC FADES]
What the fuck are we doing here?
What?
How did we get here?
[HESITATES] What?
How the fuck did we get here?
Jade, you never left.
No, no, no.
We were in the tunnels.
No, you've been
sitting here for hours.
You were at the window.
You sat down.
And that's it. You...
No, no.
There was more. There was...
There was a lot more.
[SOFT MUSIC BUILDING]
I know where they are.
What?
I know what we have to do
to go home.
I know how we can save
the children.
[MUSIC CONCLUDES]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]