Mr. Gu,
since your identity was made public,
the image of both you and the company
has been moving in a positive direction.
We all watched your interview
with Ms. Xu.
It was excellent.
(Video Conference in Progress)
You're now the dream lover in everyone's heart.
I'm married.
Shen Gu.
Wanxin...
♪A lonely bench on the street corner♪
♪Where all feelings come to rest♪
♪In the night sky, the moon's trail♪
♪Stitches up and soothes my sorrow♪
♪The courage to get close to you♪
♪Drives away my hesitation♪
♪Fate turns and brings us together♪
♪I search my memories with all my might♪
♪Love catches me off guard♪
♪You, in the album♪
♪Shine through my past like starlight♪
=Echoes of Gang City=
=Episode 21=
(Shen Gu's Long Journey Through Hardship)
Mr. Shen,
why didn't you tell me
you had to work tonight?
(Video Conference in Progress)
Let me introduce.
Chief anchor of Gang City Finance
and Chairwoman of Minghui Group.
My wife, Xu Wanxin.
Hello.
I'm Xu Wanxin.
Your financial interview
was as professional
and insightful as ever.
She'll also be more involved
in our decision-making going forward.
I hope you'll support her
just as you support me.
Of course.
We'll give her our full support.
Thank you.
I'll be counting on you all.
That's it for today's meeting.
See you next time.
See you.
Bye.
Why didn't you tell me
you had a meeting?
There's a time difference.
I was going to head back after it ended.
There were so many of them just now.
I...
You're my top decision-maker.
That's fine.
Let's head back.
Why is this photo here?
It's a gift from you.
I did?
I don't remember.
When Qingniao was starting to pick up,
I wanted you to be the first to know.
So I came back to Gang City,
dressed up as a teddy bear,
and snuck into your school.
We graduated!
Xu Wanxin.
I'll make you
the most popular financial anchor
in Gang City.
Then I'll make you
the youngest top producer
in the station.
Let's take over the entire
Gang City media industry together!
The future looks bright.
Good.
Mr. Xu, you're here.
Grandfather.
You've got big ambitions.
That's wonderful. You're here.
My dear daughter
is going to become the lead anchor
of a financial program.
I'm proud of you.
Dad, you'd better work hard
and try to become a guest on my show.
Wait. The teddy bear is so cute.
I want to take a photo with the bear.
Excuse me.
Can we take a picture together?
Me?
Hi, little bear.
Look here.
Let's say "Happy Graduation!"
Happy Graduation!
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Happy graduation.
Wishing you a bright future.
Mm.
♪If only you could truly hear
what my heart is trying to say♪
♪From this life on
no distance could keep us apart♪
♪The promise we made♪
There, there.
Stop crying.
Shen Gu,
what else do I not know about you?
Come with me.
♪I've always been behind you♪
♪As long as you're here, I have it all♪
♪The whole universe♪
These are my favorite comic books.
I've prepared so many gifts for you
all these years.
I didn't know if I'd ever
get the chance to give them to you.
This
is the teddy bear from the year
I was born?
Nothing inside.
This was what held it.
What's this?
A compilation of your
on-air slip-ups over the years.
All of them.
Don't look.
This too.
Give it back.
(Trending Topic: Shen Gu
Talks About His Startup Story)
He's a criminal's son.
What's there to talk about?
Exactly.
Disgusting.
Tell me about it.
If you don't know the full story,
don't talk nonsense.
Their family is the real victim.
Stop spreading rumors.
I'll have Xi handle that.
Once this settles down,
we'll go visit Mom together,
alright?
Alright.
Go freshen up.
I'll drive you to work.
I'm off today.
What's wrong?
What's it?
It's fine.
Don't move.
Don't smudge it.
What are you doing?
Trying to cover up the evidence?
It won't look good if someone sees this.
Stop it.
Go to work now.
Give me a kiss.
Go.
Go to work now.
Give me a kiss.
Go
to work.
Just one kiss.
Boss,
Yinghai Group has just made
an announcement without informing us.
Due to unforeseen compliance reviews,
they'll suspend
all high-performance computing equipment
and technical support indefinitely
to Qingniao.
Have you told Fang Hongsheng?
Lawyer Fang is already inside.
(Video Conference in Progress)
I understand.
My father boarded a flight
three hours ago.
He's working on it.
How long can we hold out?
I've told the team to push
legal procedures as fast as possible.
Even if my dad steps in,
cross-border cases will take
at least three months.
What about you?
Yinghai Group's suspension
takes effect immediately.
Even with all energy-saving
and task-scheduling optimization measures
applied to our current inventory,
we can only guarantee the operation
of the Spark core risk control module
and the two highest-priority
research projects.
All the other newly signed projects
will only be able to sustain low-precision
computing for 72 hours at most.
Have we started backup plans?
We've reached out
to other global suppliers,
including Yinghai's secondary channels.
But they're all under pressure
from Yinghai and its affiliates.
They've made it clear.
They won't supply us.
Even if we find a new supplier,
we all know there's a huge generational
gap in terms of computing density,
software ecosystem compatibility,
and especially for the specific AI
training and inference cores we require.
They can't meet Spark's scale and
precision requirements in the short term.
Also, Raymond Group has teamed up
with nine of our competitors
to pressure Yinghai Group.
In the end, they chose to cut us off.
They're using Yinghai Group
to impose technological dominance
on us
through unfair competition.
Guys, this is our test.
Activate all contingency plans.
Focus computing power
on solving supply issues.
This won't be easy for us.
You're back.
Why are you cooking for yourself?
I wanted to make you some soup.
Here, try it.
How is it?
It's good.
But
I can't stay home for dinner tonight.
I need to go to Shen City right away.
Did something happen at the company?
Yinghai Group is suspending supply
to Qingniao indefinitely
due to unforeseen compliance reviews.
Yinghai is your biggest supplier.
If they cut you off,
your system could collapse.
It can get tricky.
That's why I need to head back
to the headquarters
and coordinate with the tech team.
When I get back,
you can make me soup again,
alright?
You can have the soup anytime you want.
The company comes first right now.
How long
will you be gone?
I'm not sure yet.
But I'll be back as soon as I can.
For now,
I'll be fully focused on the company.
I might not have much time for you.
Maybe you could move back
and stay with Grandfather for a while.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of myself.
Just focus on the company.
No matter what happens,
Minghui and I
will always have your back.
♪Tonight the rain falls soft and slow♪
♪Blending with letters left unread
drifting through the air♪
♪You turn and look back at me♪
♪In those same eyes familiar tears
quietly appear♪
♪It feels like we have carried so much♪
♪So many questions time itself
could not make clear♪
♪The moment you walked into my life♪
♪Every dream I had became something
I want with you near♪
♪How many letters have I written
just for you?♪
♪If only you could truly hear
what my heart is trying to say♪
♪From this life on
no distance could keep us apart♪
♪The promise we made♪
♪Will find its way to be fulfilled
one day♪
♪But I want more
than just that fleeting gaze♪
♪Still I have not heard your answer♪
♪Can we still rewrite the ending
we face?♪
♪When regrets begin to turn around you
will hear it all♪
♪Everything that leads me back to you♪