(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
I don’t want
our agreement to be just business.
I want us to love each other.
And get married.
Number 18.
That’s basically my number.
How so?
It really is Si.
The mud here is so sticky.
I’ve washed it ten times and it’s still there.
Come, let me help you.
You.
Don’t cross the line.
She looked so innocent.
That’s why I trusted her.
Why did she cross the line?
(Somkid Agriculture 18-8-8)
I reek of mud this much,
and she still came close.
That fertilizer girl...
And even...
I got kissed by that fertilizer girl.
Khun Si, what are you doing?
Washing clothes.
Washing clothes?
Hey.
Not even here,
and still causing trouble.
Khun Si.
I’m so glad you came.
I...
I’m sorry.
Sorry for what?
Well...
About...
taking advantage of you.
And...
breaking your trust.
Please forgive me.
Good.
At least you know to apologize.
- I...
- Stop.
I’m not done talking yet.
And remember this.
From now on,
don’t even think about doing that again.
Got it?
If you’re going to kiss me next time,
at least make it more romantic.
That was our first kiss.
Huh?
Actually,
right now,
the atmosphere is nice.
The moon is beautiful too.
Well...
it feels pretty romantic.
Then...
Hmm?
What are you going to do?
It was a dream.
Pao.
You little rascal.
I brought you some gifts from Suphan Buri.
This is sali cake
and sun-dried snakehead fish.
And Inca peanut coffee.
Good for health lovers.
Thank you so much.
But you’re not being nice first
to lower our guard,
then attack us later, right?
I’m not thinking like that.
By the way...
Has someone done that to you before?
A lot of them. People from Bangkok.
They tend to do that all the time.
But we’re from Suphan Buri.
We’re honest and sincere.
Nothing complicated.
If we love, we say we love.
If we hate, we say we hate.
So, you coming today,
is there something?
Did my sister break any agreement?
It’s not about that.
I just want to talk to her.
Well, if you two have any issues,
you can tell us.
In case it’s something serious,
is it something we need to know?
Well, for Khun Si,
you could call it serious.
Wait a second.
Right now you’re making me nervous.
I’m not sure...
Has Si been going to see you often?
Yes. Since the day we met
in that meeting room,
whenever she has problems at home,
she would
drive from Bangkok to Suphan Buri
just to vent to me.
But I think
she just wanted someone on her side.
And yesterday, I acted a bit out of line.
So she got mad at me.
That’s why I’d like to
ask to see Khun Si today.
She’s probably still asleep right now.
She usually wakes up around noon.
How about this?
You can wait here first.
I’ll inform the housekeeper.
We have to head to work.
Sure, and...
I have something to ask for permission.
Pao.
How did you get here, you chubby?
I missed you so much.
Good afternoon.
You came too?
Huh?
What, you expected Pao
to take the bus alone?
Good thing my dad’s not home.
Otherwise, you’d be out
running around outside, Pao.
Don’t worry.
Because I already asked your dad
for permission to bring Pao in.
And I’ll have someone come clean up
before he gets back.
Because I remember...
he’s allergic to pet fur.
You really know a lot.
And...
what are you doing here?
Well...
I’m not the kind of person who...
ignores my own mistakes.
I’m sorry
for what I did yesterday without thinking.
So I came to apologize.
I want you to know that...
I’m really sorry.
You shouldn’t have had to go through
what happened yesterday.
Please forgive me, Si.
Alright.
I’ll forgive you.
But...
if you ever try to take advantage of me again,
those two buffaloes at your house,
I’ll slaughter them, including Jon.
What about Pao?
I’ll spare one because
Pao is my favorite.
Come on.
I promise
I won’t take advantage of you again.
You better mean it.
Pao.
You.
Did you change your shirt?
Yeah, I just got a new one printed.
From now on,
I’ll only wear number 18.
Do you like it?
If you do, I’ll order one for you.
Mm.
It’s pretty nice.
Then I’ll order one for you.
But yours
has to be number 9.
Why?
Because it’s my name.
A fertilizer shirt like this,
who would even want to wear it?
Right, Pao? Right?
It’s what I promised the village head.
that I’d find a way to help the villagers.
Khun Si has an idea
for us to make products to sell at S Mall.
-Where is S Mall?
-But S Mall
is your family’s mall in Bangkok, uncle.
-Oh.
And you didn’t say anything.
That sounds interesting.
We’re just ordinary villagers.
We don’t really know anything about business.
If someone knowledgeable helps us
think it through, that’d be great.
-Yeah, yeah.
-Right?
-Applause.
Yes.
Yes, that’s great.
Khun Si is really capable.
Her family has been
in business for a long time.
In that case,
could you explain it clearly
to the villagers again?
Sure.
-Go on.
-Come on, I want to hear it.
Suphan fragrant rice
is already aromatic and high quality.
We just need to come together.
to increase its value.
Then we can sell it at a higher price.
As for me,
I’ll start by selling it at S Mall.
So people in Bangkok
can try Suphan fragrant rice.
Fragrant and delicious.
-Awesome.
-That’s great.
Exactly.
And another thing,
the mall will help promote it specially.
In exchange, I’ll help reduce
the land rent for several years.
If I succeed with this plan,
I’ll help come up with more projects.
So we can create jobs
and generate income for farmers like us.
Wow, I’m getting excited.
Hey, bro.
What should we name
the Suphan rice brand?
Make it cool and catchy.
-What name?
-The name is...
-What is it? Do you have an idea?
-It’s just rice.
Suphan fragrant rice.
How about 189?
-What?
-What is that?
Sounds like a lottery number, 189.
So what does it mean?
-Are you giving lottery numbers or what, Klao?
-Yeah, exactly.
-Yeah, right.
-It’s nothing, uncle.
I just thought
the number looks nice.
-And you didn’t say, I thought it was a tip.
-Yeah.
-Good, alright.
-So I can go buy it.
Everyone,
does anyone have any questions?
-None at all.
-None.
-None, right? It’s good, right?
-No issues, we fully support it.
I think, to make it better,
it should be
Suphan fragrant rice 918 instead.
That sounds like lottery again,
flipping numbers back and forth.
Three-digit, four-digit, I don’t know.
-Flipping numbers is good though.
-It really sounds like lottery.
-918.
Want to buy some food? Food.
Here we go, watermelon, Thai melon.
Big shrimp.
All ready in my truck.
We’ve got coconut water too.
Come on over.
-Everyone.
-Hey, do you have frogs?
We’ve been in a long meeting.
Let’s go find something to eat.
I’ll treat everyone to this meal.
-Nice.
-Okay.
Awesome.
This meal has a sponsor now.
Parrot lady says let’s go.
-Let’s go.
Hey, do you have frog with eggs?
-It’s great when someone’s paying.
-Follow me.
Can I get some frogs?
Thank you, Khun Si.
What are you thanking me for?
I should be the one thanking you.
Thank you.
Thank you for making me feel
like I matter to someone too.
Come on, let’s go.
Boss, what do you want?
I’ll serve you myself.
One sugarcane juice
and one coconut water.
Coming right up.
Grab it, someone’s paying.
Here you go, boss.
Here you are, Parrot lady.
Go ahead.
You look prettier.
-Jiw, what would you like?
-Can I have you?
You little brat.
-Sis.
-What is it?
Can I get the song "Melon Garden Girl"?
-Bring the bananas.
-Got it, kid.
Melon garden girl of Suphan.
Talked about all over the city.
(Jane)
I’m in Thailand now.
See you tomorrow.
Is something wrong?
Oh.
Well...
I think
I might have to go home tonight.
I have something urgent to take care of.
And
tomorrow I plan to go to the office
to discuss the project
we talked about today.
Are you hiding something from me?
You’re not good at lying.
Your face gives it away, you know?
Oh.
Well...
There’s something
really important I need to settle first.
Once I get everything sorted,
I’ll tell you everything.
I’m not trying to pressure you,
but that thing you mentioned,
is it about...
someone else?
Come on, you.
It’s nothing.
You promised you wouldn’t cheat on me.
I won’t betray you either.
I trust you.
I actually want to drive you,
but I’m not good at driving at night.
I’ve got a bit of trauma.
Trauma?
About what?
My parents.
They used to fight when I was little.
So they drove fast out of spite.
And I was sitting in the back that day.
In the end, there was an accident.
And I was the only one who survived.
That must have been really hard for you.
It’s okay.
Today, I promise
I’ll drive slowly
and carefully.
And I’ll call you as soon as I arrive.
Don’t worry.
Mm.
I’m heading out now.
Go on.
You’ll come back, right?
Of course.
Where else could someone like me go?
It’s been a while.
How have you been?
Are you doing well?
Do I look sick to you?
I missed you.
Excuse me.
Si.
Say something to me.
Anything.
If you have something to say, just say it.
I don’t have much time.
I just got back to Thailand.
I just wanted to see my girlfriend.
Do people in a relationship
need a reason to meet?
Coconut water, please.
Si.
I’m sorry.
I’m sorry for not replying to your messages.
I’m sorry for not answering your calls.
But things over there were really busy.
And you know our time zones are different.
I came to see you, didn’t I?
Where are you going?
To the restroom.
What’s wrong with her?
Excuse me, serving.
I’m sorry.
It’s okay, I’ll clean it up myself.
Do you want anything else?
I’ll order it for you.
Want some?
Si.
Do you want anything else?
So,
you don’t have anything to say, right?
Then...
I’m leaving.
Si.
Damn it, I really messed up.
I should’ve replied to her messages.
Then I could’ve kept her around.
Consider it compensation
for my wasted time, Si.
Go on, what is it, my child?
I have a new project
with the villagers in Suphan Buri.
to present to you.
You might not be interested right now,
but I think this project is interesting.
If you agree,
Klao will reduce
the land rent for S Mall.
And you can develop the marketing plan as CHR
to support Thai farmers.
This deal
is a win-win, Dad.
Dad, P’Si,
is something going on?
I just brought a project to present.
I’m not here to take your CEO position.
Don’t worry.
I’m leaving now, Dad.
If
you’re interested,
just let me know.
Your sister brought me a project.
I think it’s quite interesting.
You can take over and handle it.
As soon as possible, my child.
Yes!
Why are you so late?
What?
Weren’t you the one who told me
to drive slowly and safely?
So why are you complaining now?
Sorry, but...
I don’t want to keep them waiting.
So how are we getting there?
Tada.
You bought a new motorcycle?
Nice.
Now I don’t have to deal with messy hair
because of that “old uncle” anymore.
So, can we go now?
Yeah, let’s go.
Wait, let me change first.
This outfit doesn’t really fit with the uncles and aunties.
I already prepared something for you.
Here.
Wow, really?
How could I be slow with something like this?
Give it to me.
Hey, you.
You’re changing right here?
-Why?
-Aren’t you embarrassed?
Embarrassed of what?
Weren’t you the one who said
we’re both women,
so why be shy?
All done.
Let’s go.
Here, I’ll put it on for you.
-Let’s go.
Alright, let’s go.
-Hello, hello, kid, hello.
-Okay.
-So drunk.
-Hey.
They’re here.
Come on.
Klao, look.
-Hello, Uncle Headman.
-Hello, kid, hello.
Sorry I’m late.
I had a work discussion in Bangkok.
That’s alright, kid, it’s alright.
Si also said
that the mall executives
have approved our business plan.
Wow, that’s great.
Today, the uncles
prepared lots of food.
Let’s go share the good news
and celebrate together, kid. Let’s go.
-Sure.
-Let’s go, kid.
Alright, everyone.
This is Si.
-Hello.
-She’s from Bangkok.
She’s going to be our village’s
new daughter-in-law.
She’s pretty.
She really is.
Klao is all smiles.
I’ll take care of you myself.
Have a seat, boss.
You’re number one to me.
Yes, thank you. Hello.
Yes?
You brat.
Cheers.
Sis, is she your wife?
She’s really pretty.
Cheers.
-Finish it, sis.
-Yeah.
Hey, hey.
You.
She’s jealous of you.
Chill.
What do you mean chill?
Parrot lady, don’t interrupt my sister.
She’s just getting tipsy.
Let it slide, just a little.
You too.
You’re still young, why are you drinking?
If your sister gets too drunk to ride home,
then you carry her back yourself.
What are you talking about?
Whoever’s girlfriend she is can take care of her.
So sweet.
She’s the boss.
-Si.
-Yes, Uncle Headman?
Come here, kid.
Come on.
This way.
It’s starting.
I’m here.
More, more.
Wow, my sister is number one in Suphan.
Strong drinker.
-Strong drinker.
-Strong.
You’re intense.
So intense.
Totally wild.
You even said
you’re that intense.
Everyone
wants to tie a string on your wrist
to welcome the new
daughter-in-law of our village.
-I’m not a daughter-in-law yet.
-Come on.
You will be soon.
-Yeah.
-Right?
What’s the name of this village again,
Uncle Headman?
The old name is outdated.
Besides,
our products
are about to go nationwide.
So we changed the name to...
Village 918.
Do you all agree?
-Agree.
-Okay, right? Yeah.
-Yes, Headman.
-Come.
Let me tie it for you, kid.
Long life and good fortune.
Now that you’re here,
may you have happiness and prosperity,
and be loved by everyone.
Bless you.
Come on.
Come in.
-Come in.
-Live in peace and happiness.
Do you have a longer string?
-Welcome gift.
-Yeah.
Here, share it.
Sis,
you can stop smiling now.
-Your cheeks are about to burst.
-It’s just...
I’m happy.
You’re happy,
I’m happy too.
Want another drink?
Go for it.
This jar,
it’s on me.
Sis,
add some ice too.
Here we go.
This whole jar,
perfect for the young ones.
Hey,
I’m not very steady driving, so don’t move too much.
Mm.
Hold onto me tight and rest your head on my shoulder.
Hurry.
The bike might tip over.
You idiot, you perv.
Get your hand off my chest.
-It’s soft.
-Or I’ll kick you off right now.
-So soft, so soft.
-You idiot, take it off.
-The bike will fall.
-You told me to hold on.
“Hold my waist.” Do you know what “waist” means?
You pervert.
I’m in trouble now.
You...
Tonight you’re sleeping outside with Pidpee and Muedmon.
-So soft.
-Take it off, you idiot.
Get your hand off already.
So soft, so soft.
You idiot.
So soft.
Take your hand off, the bike’s about to fall.
Are you okay?
Hey, be careful.
Let’s go.
You...
You can kiss me
if you want to.
I’m not going along with your plan.
If I do that,
you’ll get mad at me and...
and find an excuse to go back to Bangkok.
You sure act like you know everything.
So, are you going to kiss me or not?
Are you serious?
Mm.
But how about this,
if
you can walk straight toward me,
I’ll let you kiss me.
You can do it, right?
There.
Guess you’re not getting that kiss.
You’re swaying all over the place.
-One more time.
-Again?
Again.
Alright, alright.
Go on.
If you can’t do it this time,
we’re going inside.
One more. One more.
One more time.
Hey, hey.
Stop it.
That’s enough.
If you want to kiss me, just do it.
I allow it.
You idiot.
What are you doing?
I told you not to drink too much.
You smell sour like fermented pork.
You really don’t know your limits when drinking.
I warned you and you didn’t listen.
Damn it.
What did you eat?
You smell like fermented pork.
What are you doing?
Miss high society.
I’m going to change your clothes.
How can you sleep like this all dirty?
Alright.
Wait.
Oh damn.
I don’t really want to see
that part of someone else.
I’ll go take a shower first.
You can sleep if you want.
Hey.
It's this late and you're still asleep.
Pidpee and Muedmon
haven't had water or grass yet.
Hey.
What should I do.
It's already so late.
How the hell do I ride this.
Pidpee, Muedmon.
Wait for mom a sec, babies.
Muedmon, come here, sweetie.
Come on, that's it.
That's it, that's it, Pidpee.
Yes!
Come on, Muedmon.
Good job, babies, Pidpee and Muedmon.
Parrot lady.
Am I dreaming.
Guess I'm not dreaming.
Is that hi-so Parrot lady or what.
Full already.
Oh, you're here, you damn mutt tapeworm.
I've been here forever, sis.
Is that really the real Parrot lady.
You usually dress like this.
And...
When did you even get here.
Since this morning, sis.
I finished everything
before you even got here.
What.
Why didn’t you tell me.
You let me do everything alone for so long.
I just wanted to see.
Hi-so Parrot lady raising buffalo.
It’s truly a feast for my eyes.
You little brat.
You mutt tapeworm, cow tapeworm,
buffalo tapeworm, bear tapeworm.
Hey.
How was it, sis.
Your first time raising buffalo.
Was it fun, sis.
Why the hell are you following me around.
And...
Why are you walking along the ridge like that.
I’m just copying your boss.
Do you even know.
why my sister does that.
I don’t know.
And don’t you dare stick your nose
in and tell me.
Because I don’t wanna know, got it.
You damn mutt tapeworm.
Go wherever you want.
I’m not going.
Pao.
It’s almost noon and she’s still not up.
I’m not even your sister’s wife.
Why do I have to do everything for her, Pao.
Huh, you chubby thing.
Come on, answer me.
Do you know someone like me.
Who would’ve thought I’d be doing this.
Raising buffalo and frying my own omelet.
And today I even boiled eggs for you.
If I told anyone, who would believe me.
Is it good.
There’s just one thing left.
Taking care of that Jon guy.
Hey, you.
Sleeping in this late.
I thought you died in your sleep.
I woke up a while ago, but.
I had a bit of a headache,
so I went back to sleep.
I guess...
I drank a bit too much last night.
That’s not “a bit” at all.
That’s called...
going all out.
You were a total mess.
I don’t get that wasted like this often.
Good.
Do you know.
you’re really heavy.
Last night, dragging you up the house.
almost broke my back.
Did you change my clothes last night.
Did you do anything to me while I was drunk.
Are you crazy.
Last night.
you threw up all over me.
Both you and I were a mess.
Who would do that.
So that means.
if you weren’t drunk, you would.
You idiot.
Why are you wearing a farmer shirt.
What.
Well, you were sleeping like
you owned the place.
I was worried Pidpee and Muedmon
would be hungry.
So I took them to drink water and eat grass.
Just like you do.
I already hired Jiw to do it.
What.
Then why didn’t you tell me from the start.
Didn’t you run into Jiw.
I did.
But that mutt tapeworm, pig tapeworm.
He’s super sneaky.
He let me finish everything first.
Then he told me he already did it all.
Left me battling with buffalo forever.
But you still managed to do it.
Well...
I was copying you.
You’re really good.
You can do anything.
It’s nothing special.
Song, send me next month’s schedule too.
Sure.
P’Si.
Oh, Si.
Come here, sweetheart.
I’ve got something to ask you.
What is it, Dad.
I just want to ask you.
How far things have gone with the landowner.
What.
Well, P’Si.
We were just wondering.
your relationship with Klao.
doesn’t seem like just a contract anymore.
That farmer-shirt girl.
What makes you all think that.
Well...
You go to Suphan so often.
-and you even stay overnight.
-Mm.
If there’s something, just tell us.
-Okay, no need to be shy, I wanna know.
-I wanna know too.
There’s nothing in the bamboo shoots at all.
-Bamboo grove.
That’s it.
Both the shoots and the grove.
Nothing at all.
But I think.
you should trust your little sister this time.
If you can catch her, then just go for it.
She.
is pretty cute.
She’s rich.
And she seems sincere too.
Catch what, Song.
You’re gonna get smacked.
Am I getting smacked too.
Because I agree with your sister.
I agree with your sister too.
Everyone, stop...
pestering me already.
If something really happens.
I’ll tell you myself.
Ohhh.
-She’s off.
-Ohhh.
Sweetie.
Do I need to practice that country accent.
The Suphan accent.
What about me, do I need to speak it too.
Me too.
The whole family’s gone crazy.
Oh, my daughter.
Now she even has to practice riding buffalo.
Pidpee, Muedmon.
Khun Si has gone home.
Do you miss her.
I think.
I really miss her.
When will she.
come complain to me again.
I think.
I’m gonna die.
Not seeing Si’s face.
Don’t you think.
Who am I even talking to.
Hello, jasmine rice, Suphan 918.
Feel free to come take a look.
This way, please.
You can come check inside.
(Klao)
What’s up.
You said.
you were going to check on their rice booth.
Then you’d hurry back to Suphan, right.
Hurry back already.
I know.
I’ll be back soon.
(Klao)
Oh, Si.
I’ll hang up for now.
I’ll call you back.
Does Si have a new girlfriend.
Hey.
What are you doing.
Can’t I hug my girlfriend because I miss her.
Jane.
Stop, let go.
Why.
Don’t you miss me.
I miss you so much I could die.
Wanna do what we used to do.
You liked it, didn’t you.
Stop being crazy.
And stop saying we’re girlfriends.
You disappeared for a year without a word.
I’m not waiting anymore, Jane.
I’ll just assume you’re dead.
And don’t come see me again.
I’m sorry.
Give me another chance, Si.
-What are you even saying.
-We just had bad timing, didn’t we.
-I tried to reach you.
-Jane.
Security.
I won’t let you leave me.
Try me.
Whatever happens, happens.
How do I even get in.
Hey.
You scared me.
You’re not asleep yet.
I saw you on the CCTV.
Why didn’t you tell me you were coming.
I didn’t plan to come.
It was late, so I thought you were asleep.
So I didn’t call you.
Turn off the engine for me.
I’ll go check on Pao first.
Usually.
Do you sleep with Pao every night.
Not every night.
If I want a peaceful night.
I let her sleep in another room.
Then...
Can she sleep in another room tonight.
Yeah, sure.
Good night, chubby.
What about you.
Is something wrong.
You can tell me anything.
You don’t have to be scared.
Because I want to be your comfort.
Have you...
ever had any naughty thoughts about me.
I don’t mean.
hurting me physically or emotionally.
Then...
what do you mean.
Do you really not know or are you pretending.
Well...
maybe I do, but...
I’m not sure.
So...
what’s your answer.
Have you ever had naughty thoughts about me.
Right now...
I’m having them.
What do you think.
if the two of us really dated.
Do you think it would work.
Well...
it’s hard to say.
But I do hope...
we can make it work.
What if.
I have a past full of mistakes.
Can you accept that.
Who hasn’t made mistakes.
The point is.
if you were wrong.
are you willing to fix it.
I’m sorry.
Do you...
like it when I do this.
Can you not do this.
I don’t want you to get mad.
Besides.
I...
can’t hold back either.
Do you like it.
I love it.
Stop pouting.
It’s making me lose confidence.
Lose confidence about what.
Well...
I’m afraid.
I might not be good enough for you.
Or...
you might not be happy.
You’re really good.
I’m so happy.
Khun Si.
I...
want you to be my life partner.
Will you marry me.
You’re proposing right now.
Yeah.
Why are you here so early? It’s not even 7 yet.
Well, you told me to come early this morning.
I feel like you’re right here in front of me.
Wait… are you about to—?
Yeah.
You’re slaying!
You should dress like this more often.
Dressed like this, even Pidpee and Muedmon would come chasing after
I keep telling you—we’re already broken up.
If you want to break up, go ahead and do it alone.
You really look like my ex.
Seeing you just reminds me of her.
Can I hug you for a second?
Hey!!
Was it fun climbing the wall.
So much fun.
-You always find something to do.
-Put this on the front.
Action.
-Hold on tight, tight around the waist.
-Yes, yes.
-Yes, the waist, yes.
-Good skills.
I said hold the waist.
(This is your specialty.)
-Cut, can we do it again.
-What is it.
-Okay, sound camera.
-Pull it harder.
(This time, extra sweet.)
-Cut, that’s good.
-Cut.