Officail Website : kissasia.id  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
♪ Hold me tight,
let the darkness drown me ♪
♪ Even one second of truth is enough
to lose myself in it ♪
♪ Hold me tight,
let the darkness drown me ♪
♪ Even one second of truth is enough
to lose myself in it ♪
♪ Whether you're light or a lie,
I can't pull myself away ♪
♪ In this game,
truth or lie no longer matters ♪
[Queen of Darkness]
[Episode 17]
Get out.
Why should I leave?
This is my house.
You're my wife.
I can do whatever I want.
An Ning.
Have I been too nice to you lately?
You think you're tougher now, huh?
Giving me attitude?
Cheating on me?
What does Huo Xiao have that I don't?
You're a beast.
How can you compare to a human?
You'll never be his equal in this lifetime.
You shameless one.
Have you forgotten?
Have you forgotten
how you begged to marry me?
How you cried
and begged to sleep with me?
I...
Seems like you're asking for trouble.
Tonight I'll make sure you remember
who's in charge.
So that
you stop fooling around
with other people all day long.
I'll hit...
You...
You dare to hit me back?
Since we're saying everything out loud,
let's settle all our scores today.
Do you hear me?
This...
When you hit me back then,
weren't you so proud of yourself?
You sneaky woman.
How dare you steal the videos
from my phone?
How else could I stand up for myself?
You were the one
who had your eye on me first
and begged me
again and again to marry you.
I once had hope for you.
I once looked forward to a good life.
But what about you?
What did you give me in return?
I...
Your cruel words.
Your violence.
And endless pain!
Today,
this little bit of pain
is just a small part of what you owe me.
From now on,
I'll settle with you one by one!
We've arrived at the company?
You've been exhausted lately,
haven't you?
Share restructuring
and staff reorganization
take a lot of energy.
Why are you following me?
You…
You're our young lady, Ye Ying.
Miss.
Huo Xiao...
Huo Xiao is the one
who killed your father.
How could you be with the man
who ended your father's life?
Although there were some errors earlier
when verifying your identity,
from your movements and habits,
your combat stance,
even the way you draw a gun,
you could never be the housewife,
An Ning.
You're our young lady,
Ye Ying.
Miss.
This is a video secretly recorded
by our guy
before the boss was killed.
After we left,
only the boss and Huo Xiao
stayed on the rooftop to talk.
So the boss's death
must be connected to Huo Xiao.
Don't let Huo Xiao fool you.
Why Huo Xiao?
Why him?
That's impossible.
Miss.
Are you alright?
I'll go find him myself and get the truth.
Why are you here?
What do you mean?
Is this
a special surprise?
Why you?
Why did you kill Ye Hong?
Why ask that?
I'm the one asking you.
Answer me!
An Ning.
Calm down.
Don't trust everyone too easily.
Don't be used as a pawn.
Believe it or not.
I can make my own judgment.
Huo Xiao.
I came to find you.
All I want is the truth.
The truth.
What truth are you looking for?
I'm a policeman.
He is a gangster.
It was my duty to arrest him,
wasn't it?
As for his death,
the case hasn't been closed yet.
So I can't give you a definite answer.
You know everything.
But you're just hiding it from me.
Huo Xiao.
Since you won't tell me the truth,
I'll find the answers myself.
I know you have a lot of questions now,
but this isn't the best time
to answer them.
You need to remember who you are.
You're An Ning now.
You're Ti Cha's wife.
You're the chairman of Longxing Group.
I don't know what game you're playing,
and I don't know
what role I'm supposed to play.
But starting today,
you're you,
and I'm me.
Huo Xiao took down our warehouse before,
and he found that shipment.
We suffered
heavy losses.
I was planning to
take advantage of him at first.
Didn't expect that guy to be
so uncooperative.
He's been opposing us at every turn.
We have to get rid of him now.
Alright.
I'll go finish him off right now.
I was just about to come looking for you.
Didn't expect you to come to me yourself.
You want to kill me?
What's wrong?
Trying to beg for mercy now?
Too late.
You don't even realize the end is near.
No wonder
you've never amounted to anything.
Huo Xiao.
I did give you a chance.
But you
never learned where you truly stand.
You thought I was just against you,
but you never realized.
I was trying to save you.
Huo Xiao.
You checked our accounts,
stole our goods,
and almost took down Jiang Meng.
You even backed that scheming An Ning,
trying to take our place.
You call that saving us?
Huo Xiao.
Have you lost your mind?
The audit order
came from above long ago.
Checking accounts means clearing debts.
The warehouse location
was already exposed.
Seizing the goods was cutting losses.
Not finishing you off was unexpected,
since you dared to pull a gun on me.
Huo Xiao.
Do you think saying this
will get you off the hook?
Well?
You really want to kill me?
Are you so sure
that you can clean up every mess?
Jiang Meng.
Calm down first.
Let him finish.
Right.
Now that's how partners should talk.
Don't get cocky.
You still haven't told me
why you want An Ning
in the chairman's seat.
This is the final step
to becoming legitimate.
Everything I did before
was just trimming the group's excess.
As for the final result,
someone still has to take the fall.
I told you before,
the police are digging into
Longxing Group.
Did you really think their silence now
means that order is nothing
but empty words?
Huo, my dear nephew.
You should've said so earlier.
If you had spoken up sooner,
we wouldn't have had
so many misunderstandings.
With that, we wouldn't have been acting
so convincingly.
If you said something else,
maybe I'd believe you.
But there must be something fishy
between you and An Ning.
Officail Website : kissasia.id  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Unless,
you arrest her
in front of everyone.
Huo.
This pledge of loyalty
isn't hard, is it?
The police confirm Longxing Group is
deeply involved in gang crime.
[Arrest Warrant]
The group's leader, An Ning, is hereby
taken into custody for investigation.
♪ Mist coils around the sleeping forest ♪
♪ Memories scattered
through cracks of darkness ♪
♪ How to escape this real-feeling dream ♪
♪ Lies reflect in water's gleam ♪
♪ Traces of existence
can never be erased ♪
♪ How to find the self I can't reclaim ♪
♪ Fly away, hear she says ♪
♪ She'll fly out from
thorns of woven lies ♪
♪ Pierce the fog,
shatter this dream tonight ♪
♪ Burn like fire ♪
♪ Just burn like fire ♪
♪ The maze in the abyss starts to clear ♪
♪ Yet night keep on whispering ♪
♪ Surrender to fate,
no clear direction ahead ♪
♪ She will rise as the dawn
that breaks the darkness ♪
♪ Never slowing down,
for tomorrow cannot be stopped ♪
♪ Surrender to love and find the way ♪
♪ Even if fate tries to forget her ♪
♪ Never despair,
for the heart burns with endless light ♪
♪ Waiting for dawn ♪
[Copyright of this short drama
belongs to]
[Shanghai Chuqi Weishi
Culture Media Co., Ltd.]
[and Youku Information Technology (Beijing)
[Co., Ltd.]
[Youku Information Technology (Beijing)
[holds exclusive global online
and broadcast rights]