ALL NAMES, PLACES, AND PRODUCTS
ARE FICTIONAL AND DRAMATIZED
AND DO NOT REFLECT REALITY
The visitation has started.
I see we have a greenhorn.
Have you ever done a prelim?
Yes.
And you came like that?
Look at you, displaying your ID.
Listen up. I'm not going to say it twice.
Have you heard of "Boudoir"?
The regional head there, Sarah Kim.
This story is about that crazy bitch.
THE ART OF SARAH
SARAH KIM
Do you also
kill people for money?
Ma'am,
didn't you see the sign out front?
We only recover money owed.
So, how much are you owed?
Fifteen billion won.
I may not kill people,
but I can make them wish they were dead.
- That's her, right?
- Yes, sir.
- What's she doing?
- She's giving him her gloves.
Just the kind of thing
that makes someone hated.
Well-meaning deeds get people killed.
Who'd give money to a homeless guy
wearing such expensive gloves?
She has absolutely no idea
how the world works.
She even gave him her scarf, boss.
Or when to back off.
You see,
I was going to give her a scare
and back off.
I had no intention
of resorting to violence.
Man.
Look at her using English,
now that she's in a bind.
What'd you do with the stolen 15 billion?
What else would I do
with the investment money?
I ran a business.
I threw a launch party,
paid the store deposit, paid the staff…
- What's wrong with that?
- So, what?
You spent it all?
If I'm going to do it,
I want to do it right.
The new collection launches next week.
I can pay back in full.
If you give me a week--
Are you saying
you can't give me the money?
Collateral.
I can give you collateral.
"Collateral"?
Boudoir bags.
"Boudoir bags"?
What's that?
Look it up.
Yes, boss.
Boss.
These cost over 100 million won apiece!
You fool. No bag costs 100 million.
You ignorant fool!
System disarmed.
So, is this Boudoir?
It looks pricey from the entrance.
Check out the flooring.
It's all carpet, right?
This is one of those Persian rugs
or something, right?
Mind the stairs, boss.
Wow!
Look at this!
Holy shit, right?
A hundred million won. Two hundred million
won. Three hundred million…
- Hey, hurry up and grab them!
- Yes, boss.
Boss, how should we get these out?
Why are you asking me, you fool?
You need keys to unlock them.
Where are they?
Here.
- Here. Hey, catch!
- Yes, boss.
Even at a glance, they look expensive.
The ones inside the room
are more expensive.
Hey. Grab the ones inside first.
- Yes, boss.
These poor bastards have no taste.
Right?
It's because they grew up poor.
Wow!
What do we have here?
Isn't this like Baroque
or Renaissance or something?
This would look absolutely killer
hanging in our office.
Moron.
What did you just say?
I called you a fucking moron.
Why steal if you can't even tell
what's valuable?
Take it. It's a forgery anyway.
I see.
A forgery, huh? Why, you!
Are you crazy?
What the…
What's going on? Huh?
The shutters are closing!
Hey, snap out of it!
Look for the keys over there!
Okay, got it!
Crazy bitch! Get out.
Get out here!
Get the fuck out of here! Out!
Open it. Get that thing opened.
I said open that fucking thing!
Move!
Damn you, you crazy bitch! Fuck!
I'm sorry. Please don't hurt me.
- I'm sorry. Please don't--
- Open it now before I kill you.
Hey, find the keys! Now!
- You still don't get it, do you?
- What?
Secom will be here
in less than five minutes.
Even this is all on camera right now.
What?
Please don't kill me.
I'm sorry. Please don't kill me.
Please spare me!
I'm so sorry. Please don't kill me.
- Fuck!
- Please don't kill me.
After that, the bitch sued me
for kidnapping, assault, and extortion.
Jeong Yeo-jin said she hired me
to get her money back, not assault her,
and pinned it all on me.
But get this.
The name of the person suing me
wasn't Sarah Kim but Woo Hyo-eun.
The last name wasn't even "Kim."
It was odd, so I had my boys look into it.
Turns out that Woo Hyo-eun
was Sarah's former employee
who recently left the company.
That means Sarah Kim sued me
while impersonating Woo Hyo-eun.
This is a tactic con artists use a lot
by extorting money
and then inciting violence.
The perpetrator becomes the victim,
and you lose the upper hand.
The key figures
in the Sarah Kim murder case are
Jeong Yeo-jin, Min Byeong-kwan,
and Woo Hyo-eun.
This is the information
I obtained from the tip-off.
This does appear to be a con.
Why do you think she did this
when there's an easier way?
She could've fled
when she got the 15 billion won.
What if she wasn't satisfied
with 15 billion?
Ponzi scheme.
There may be more victims of the scam.
At this point,
is Jeong Yeo-jin the prime suspect?
No. The Financial Crimes Unit
had been watching her
since the kidnapping case.
The partials from the bag
didn't match hers either.
Do we know who Kim contacted
on the day of the murder?
Yes, they've been identified.
BOUDOIR 2024 S/S PREVIEW PARTY
POLITICAL/BUSINESS CIRCLES
ENTERTAINMENT
SHIN SO-UI
ACTOR
BOUDOIR
BOUDOIR BAG, WHY IT WAS THE PERFECT CHOICE
I GOT THE LUXURY BOUDOIR BAG LOVED
BY EUROPEAN ROYALS FOR 100 YEARS
CHEONGDAM GODDESS
Five years ago?
POSTS FOR 010-5780-4913
SEEKING PART-TIME
DEPARTMENT STORE LINE SITTERS
LINE SITTERS WANTED
CREATE A NEW OPEN PROFILE
DOGGO
TRAILER
HI! I'M INTERESTED
IN THE PART-TIME LINE-SITTING JOB
CAN YOU HANDLE
LESS SLEEP AND LESS FAMILY TIME?
DOING THAT ALREADY
CAN YOU COME
TO THE DEPARTMENT STORE RIGHT NOW?
ON MY WAY ALREADY
THE PASS NECKLACE IN THEIR HAND
Whoa, sir!
- Ms. Resell Queen?
- Here.
- Ms. Chic Sister?
- Mr. Rolex Shrek?
- Right here.
- Ms. Debt Coin?
- Yes.
- Ms. Chanel Number Seven?
- Here.
- Mr. Doggo?
All right, everyone!
Line-sitting is the only thing
in the world
where endurance means victory.
Chanel is the cheapest today,
Rolex will still be sold out tomorrow,
and so we line up again.
All right. Today's first in line is…
A round of applause
for Ms. Balenci-mother!
Congratulations!
I'm so jealous.
- I'm so jealous.
- Yeah, seriously.
You've got to be kidding me.
What are you doing?
Sorry?
Mr. Doggo, don't tell me
that's all you're wearing!
Goodness, you'll catch a cold.
You're lucky we're waiting indoors today.
Your body's an asset.
Thank you.
Is this your first time as a line sitter?
Yeah, I'm saving every bit I can
to buy luxury stuff.
Right.
Your first luxury item.
Yes, that's special. It really is.
What brand?
Balen? Maison?
You're slender, so I think
Saint Laurent would look great on you.
Boudoir.
Don't buy from there.
Any luxury good
below the Big Three standards is crap.
Isn't Boudoir the most popular right now?
I've seen many reviews
on online communities.
Bullshit! That's all fabricated!
Look, Boudoir only sells
to the genuine VVIP.
Do you really think people like that
would personally write reviews online?
How do you know all that?
You must be a pro at this.
I used to work at Boudoir.
I was scouted, actually.
Wow! Then you must know Sarah Kim well.
I'm sorry for back then.
Our customer policies are quite strict.
I would think you could be flexible
and ignore the rules from time to time.
I guess you don't do that.
I can do better.
I'm saying that I like that attitude.
It makes me curious about your taste.
I needed to win her over.
She was someone who spent
tens of millions on each visit.
How is this color?
I couldn't ignore the commission
from those sales either.
I don't think I need to see anymore.
We're done.
No, I don't think that's it.
It is. Look at this.
Hey, this is…
- This?
- No, this is how you do it.
- Then…
- Damn it!
- Excuse me.
- No, I mean…
Could you at least turn the sound off?
And isn't the food court downstairs?
Where were you?
I was on my break. Why?
It was Sarah Kim.
It was so crazy a moment ago.
- Did she file a complaint?
- It's not that.
She purchased every single bag
you showed her.
And paid the full amount in cash again.
She also asked me
to pass this onto you, Hyo-eun.
Actually, she was the one
who bought my loyalty.
For a mere 3,000 won.
Call me if you want to change jobs.
What is this place?
The Boudoir flagship store
will be built here.
We'll remove the clock,
raise the ceilings,
and display the bags in showcases
so they can't be touched by just anyone.
I need someone who knows
the workings of this industry well
and will treat clients by their status.
When clients leave here after shopping,
I want them to feel an unparalleled sense
of immense satisfaction.
And I'm certain the person
who best understands that is you.
I do?
I think you have an eye for beauty
others can't see.
How about it?
Won't you come work for me?
It's Choi Chae-u
of Samwol Department Store.
The chairwoman has a personal shopper,
so she doesn't come to the store herself.
But the fact that she's here means…
Oh no!
Didn't you send her an offering?
Should I have?
It's an unspoken industry rule.
She might be here to vent, not to shop.
Don't worry.
I invited her.
Thank God.
Countless brands pulled out of Korea
because they got on
Choi Chae-u's bad side.
Shall I say I invited her
by not inviting her?
Thank you for visiting our humble store.
Allow me to show you to the lounge.
Your store is by no means humble.
I may be a person of high rank,
but you mustn't speak so lowly
of your brand.
Shall I show you other items?
No, it's not that. I don't feel…
- Where is the restroom?
- This way.
- Oh my God!
- Oh no.
Are you all right?
Bring me something to clean up!
Everyone out!
- Now.
- Everyone leave. Now!
You too.
Ms. Choi should be okay, right?
I don't know.
Hey, what's this?
What is this?
That's Ms. Kim's.
YOUR NON-SMOKING CHOICE
Was she a smoker?
Yes, ma'am. Have you arrived?
SIDE EFFECTS: NAUSEA (GAGGING)
That must be so filthy.
It's my job.
I'm so sorry.
I should've been more attentive.
Having my lunch too quickly
must've been the issue.
I'll pay for that bag.
Don't tell me you shoved it in my face
just to sell me one?
If you did, you're a master salesperson.
Of course not.
It's on me
for not handling things properly.
There's no need for compensation.
What is your name, dear?
I'll tell them to promote you.
Or
would you like to work for me?
Your kind sentiments are enough.
Thank you.
It's just that I don't have a superior
who can promote me.
What?
I'm the regional head of this brand.
You're Sarah Kim?
Even the final details were perfect.
We used the same courier
as the one for national exam papers.
That's what we call quality
in our world. Quality.
Sarah Kim was a person
of exceptional quality.
Yes, ma'am. Have you been well?
Sarah Kim's acknowledgement
inspired and motivated me.
I'm calling because…
It felt just like
when I bought my first luxury item.
That's the point
where our honeymoon ended.
It was far too short.
So the person who brought
all those VIPs to Boudoir was…
You must've earned quite a bit
in commission.
As if.
Do you think I'd be here
doing this if I had?
I hardly had a chance to sell the bags.
"Treat clients by their status"?
It meant cutting out
anyone below standard.
I mean, most of my job
was kicking clients out.
I honestly thought,
"At this rate, we'll go bust."
But I had been shortsighted.
It's the nature of the rich
to chase things money can't buy.
The more exclusive it became,
the more people insanely sought it out.
There's a line.
And as if it were all part of a plan,
Boudoir drastically raised its prices.
The proprietor was king, not the customer.
It was as though
it were the kingdom of Sarah Kim.
Here, try it on.
- Oh my.
- How much is this?
That one?
The Tton will be 145,000 won.
My, isn't that perfect for you?
You have a good eye.
Just bring me a neat one
and keep the change.
It seems you know
what you're talking about, pretty lady.
Give me a second.
What are those doing here?
Unreleased bags from the new collection
were already circulating in Dongdaemun.
How could this happen?
Shouldn't we report this to headquarters?
As long as luxury goods exist,
there will be counterfeits.
There's no explanation for this
unless it was an internal leak--
By the way, how did you come across this?
I think that needs more explanation.
Hyo-eun, take the food home in a vinyl bag
if you don't want to throw it away.
You might choke on that.
See? What did I tell you?
Once I began to get suspicious,
I started to see all the signs.
What's so weird about that?
Sarah Kim used Konglish!
A vinyl bag? That's called a plastic bag.
No one uses such language in this world.
A Korean American regional head
of a high-end brand who uses Konglish?
Sarah Kim and Boudoir are all fake
from top to bottom!
I'm sure of it.
Just for calling it a vinyl bag?
All you're giving me are your opinions.
Give me some concrete proof,
Ms. Woo Hyo-eun.
Seriously?
God, what's with all the noise?
This is my friend.
Go back to sleep.
- Go on.
- Who is this?
Sorry.
By the way, Mr. Doggo,
how did you know my name?
I never told you my name.
Why, you…
Over here!
- So-ui!
- Please look over here!
- You're so pretty!
JULIET WITH A GUN
Wow! So-ui!
SARAH KIM HAS BEEN MURDERED
Yes, hello?
Yes, sir.
I think we're leaving in about 30 minutes.
Yes, I understand.
I think I may know who killed her.
There was an uninvited guest
at the Boudoir party.
God, I'm getting the chills.
Who was it?
It was Woo Hyo-eun,
that Boudoir salesperson.
Ugly rumors were going around about her.
You know, about how she's selling
clients' personal information for money.
They say celebrities' phone numbers
go for a few million won.
Where did you hear that?
If I knew the source of the rumor,
it wouldn't be a rumor, would it?
But I do know one thing for sure.
Sarah Kim and Woo Hyo-eun
had a major falling out.
Sarah Kim made a clean break
and blacklisted her from the industry.
Oh, right!
I should have a video I took that day.
Here.
Screw you!
I hope you crash and burn!
- Crash and burn!
- Go fuck yourself, moron!
- Fuck you! Whoa!
- What are you doing?
What are you doing?
Yes, video analysis confirms
that the person with Woo in the footage
is Yang Da-hye,
who discovered Sarah Kim's body.
They worked at the same store
a few years back,
and now they run a reselling business
through unofficial channels.
Find and send me
the most recent signal for Woo's phone.
Yes, sir.
What the…
Sir?
What are you doing?
You're here already?
Ms. Yang Da-hye?
Hello.
What are you doing?
Here, have a hand warmer.
They say they have proof
that Boudoir is a fake.
Wait, that woman is dead?
Ms. Yang, you were the one
who discovered Sarah Kim's body.
What? You were?
So are you telling me
that the body with the smashed up face
was Sarah Kim?
Damn.
She really crashed and burned, didn't she?
Did you really not know?
No, I didn't. I was so overwhelmed.
Wait, are you suspecting us right now?
Look.
Da-hye proved she'd been camping
outside the store for the opening rush.
I was there with her,
so I've got an alibi too, right?
Tell them, Yang-da.
I already told them dozens of times
during the interview.
Maybe you held a grudge
over being unfairly fired from Boudoir?
Wait, you were fired?
The two of you gatecrashed and terrorized
the party on the day of the murder.
Hey, that's a bit harsh.
- "Terrorized"?
- That's a bit much.
That's a gross exaggeration.
I'd call it a curse.
Just so you know,
I had a smoking gun
that would have ruined Sarah Kim.
What exactly was this smoking gun?
Her.
Oh.
Well, about a month ago,
I visited the Boudoir store.
Ma'am, would you like to try this on?
It's part of our newest collection.
It's totally my style.
Allow me, ma'am.
Yes, thank…
Photo, please.
- Please handle with care.
- Of course.
- Looks good.
- Pretty!
It's gorgeous.
That totally goes with your outfit today!
Are you sure it's okay for us to do this?
Didn't you say your boss was super strict?
It's fine. She doesn't come to work
at this hour.
Really? That's a relief.
Ma'am, would you like to try on
another bag?
I almost died
trying to get that money together.
This is pretty much my life savings.
I'd say splurge even more,
even if you have to borrow money.
These are not bags. They're jewels.
Really?
Let's try this one.
Try it on.
Is there anything else you need?
Sorry?
No, I'm fine.
The client requested
a private appointment,
as she is anxiously social.
I see.
Please excuse me.
Hope you have a pleasant time.
Thank you.
You said she wouldn't be here, damn it!
Did we fool her?
- Hey!
- What?
What was that? Don't you have a brain?
You're one to talk. "Anxiously social"?
It's social anxiety, fool!
- Anxiously social?
- Anxiously social, my ass.
What the hell did I say? Oh no.
Good thing I came wearing
all these fakes, at least.
She totally fell for it.
Are you an African tribal chief?
At least stick to one jewelry brand.
And take that necklace off.
It doesn't suit you.
Hey, this is the only piece that's real!
It doesn't look real on you!
Bite me!
Wait, that's real?
It's totally real.
I almost got humiliated
for being caught wearing a fake,
so I bought this right away.
No, wait.
Look, that camel one is gorgeous!
- Leave!
- Just three minutes. Okay, one.
Just one second, then. Come on!
I'm going to die of a heart attack,
you crazy girl!
Okay.
Calm down and chant the power word.
The Big Three!
It'll be all right.
Damn.
So, you're saying
that person is Sarah Kim, right?
I swear I've seen her somewhere.
Where did I see her?
You probably saw her at the store.
She's a shopaholic.
You want to fire me?
I expected only one thing
from you, Hyo-eun.
That you act according to status.
What you did was like
wearing open-toed shoes with pantyhose.
Can you sign and leave now?
"Wearing open-toed shoes with pantyhose"
means you've broken etiquette.
Yes, I'll send over the revised policy.
This is Kim Yu-jin
of Korea Life Insurance.
Sure. I'll be in touch.
But our store doesn't have
any openings right now.
Maybe this is a good chance for you
to pivot and try beauty or SPA brands?
I've been in this field for a while.
I can't just start over.
Are you feigning ignorance,
or do you really not know?
Sorry?
This industry has ears everywhere.
Did you think word wouldn't get around?
I heard you sold personal info of clients
to an insurance company.
What?
I did what?
Wait, what are you…
This is Kim Yu-jin
of Korea Life Insurance.
Why, that fucking…
She's a total crazy bitch.
She's behind this whole thing. Sarah Kim…
Sarah Kim set the whole thing up.
Sarah Kim did?
Why would she?
My point exactly! Why?
Why the hell is she doing this to me?
Damn it. Seriously.
What in the world happened to you?
Look, if your boss hadn't stepped in,
you'd be in jail already.
Get it?
It was only when I began
to look for a job again
that I realized Sarah Kim had kicked me
out of the industry, not Boudoir.
TIP WITH SCREENSHOTS
NOTE IF ANONYMOUS
EXPOSING SARAH KIM, THE CON ARTIST
Did you get off work already?
Hey!
I got fired!
What?
Someone filed a complaint
saying I violated the grooming guidelines.
Some crap about me
"wearing open-toed shoes with pantyhose."
Who wears open-toed shoes in winter?
My hands and feet are always cold.
I get it if it's just me. But Yang-da too?
This was her taking revenge.
Hey, get up.
You said you'd seen Sarah Kim before.
Do you recall where?
And that's when we realized
that Sarah Kim was not kicking us out.
She was avoiding us.
I can't remember for the life of me.
How about I try hypnosis?
It seems to work on Unanswered Questions.
In conclusion,
you don't know.
- She's on the verge of finding out.
- Yeah.
Let us finish.
Then did you know Sarah Kim had stolen
your identity, Ms. Woo?
- She what?
- What?
My identity?
Sarah Kim underwent a police investigation
using a copy of your ID.
Damn!
No way!
No wonder.
I kept getting weird notices from court.
She must've used the copy of my ID
I submitted with the job contract.
Hey, you've made it now. Congratulations.
This isn't exactly a laughing matter,
don't you think?
It's funny, isn't it?
- Totally.
- It's brief.
But she wanted to be me for that time.
By the way,
Mr. Doggo, this is for you.
Open it.
I collected bits and pieces
of what I could,
but it's not much.
That's not true.
There is a lot of evidence in here.
Why didn't you report her sooner?
She burned the entire remaining stock
when the season ended.
She would've preferred
to destroy the bags herself
than see them be treated
as leftover stock.
Sarah Kim really did love Boudoir.
It may have been all fake,
but it wasn't a lie.
Which is why people of high rank
hung onto her every word.
I heard the brand is pushing
to get into a department store.
Why didn't I report her?
Do you think those people would allow
their names to be tarnished?
ENTERTAINMENT
POLITICAL/BUSINESS CIRCLES
Is it Samwol Department Store,
by any chance?
Did Sarah Kim have anyone around her
who could help her?
It's all there in the notebook.
The secrets, tastes, and even minor habits
of the VIPs I managed.
BANG EUN-SUK (COLUMNIST)
KANG EUN-JEONG (ASSEMBLYMAN'S WIFE)
VVIP SOCIAL CLUB MEMBER
Are these their sizes?
Cell phone patterns.
I tend to write it all down. Just in case.
Why? Do I seem shady?
What about Sarah Kim?
The only thing I know about that woman
is that I don't know anything about her.
You can figure out the rest,
Mr. Handsome Detective.
Yes, we've arrived.
What do you think you're doing?
This is a search and seizure warrant.
Do not touch anything from now on!
- Get started.
- Yes, sir.
- Excuse me.
I suggest you step back.
That costs 100 million won.
Can you even pay if it's scratched?
Gloves, please.
She's already cleared out her things.
Just one week…
Just make it through a week.
Excuse me.
I don't have a handkerchief.
Isn't it your day off?
Something about the timeline doesn't fit.
What timeline?
I found the first online post
about Boudoir.
It was dated five years ago.
But actual sales of the brand
only started last May.
A bag review written five years ago
when Boudoir wasn't even in Korea.
I figured we might get lucky,
so I asked the portal to verify the user.
What about you, sir?
I'm going to go back to square one.
The scene of the crime never lies.
The body was found
in the luxury street of Cheongdam-dong,
an area where there are dozens
of security cameras in a block.
But the suspect dumps the body
without being seen on a single camera?
That's absolutely impossible.
There's only one answer.
The sewers!
But didn't the forensic team
already comb through the area?
Not all of it.
If you want to know about rock bottom,
you have to become it.
Come with me.
Am I going with you?
Don't you want to?
Sir…
No, I want to. I so want to.
I'd freaking love to!
I thought you'd freaking love to.
You so wanted to.
Damn.
Oh, look!
Oxygen tanks go for 200,000 won
on Coupang!
See?
I'll go down when they arrive tomorrow.
I read an article about someone
who died from toxic fumes cleaning sewers.
- Get out.
- Yes, sir.
What are you doing?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Gas mask, walkie-talkie, flashlight.
Why do I even bother?
Keep going straight,
then turn left once you see a passage.
Gradually, you will forget
you're even breathing.
I simply exist in this space.
Far in the distance,
I see the door to my memories.
Now, open the door with energy.
One,
two,
three.
I remember!
Fucking hell! You scared me.
Holy cow.
I met that bitch
at an employee sale.
What?
Her name was…
Her name was?
Fuck, what was it?
Sir!
RE: REQUEST OF USER INFO
FOR "CHEONGDAM GODDESS" OF NOBILITY
USER NICKNAME: CHEONGDAM GODDESS
USER NAME: MOK GA-HUI
- Mok Ga-hui?
- Mok Ga-hui.
MOK GA-HUI
Subtitle translation by: Yung Un Choi