♪Just To Meet You, you fell for me♪
♪Just to meet me, into my trap you fell♪
♪Wanna try a breathless love?♪
♪Every move hits the heart, close and sure♪
♪Just To Meet You, you love my playful charm♪
♪Just to meet me,
my romantic little schemes for you♪
♪Wanna play another brand-new game?♪
♪Layer by layer, we close the gap♪
=Just To Meet You=
=Episode 11=
=Counterplot &amp; Secret Exposed=
Ye Lang.
You're the eldest son of our family.
For a woman,
you'll ruin your future?
Mr. Li.
I know what I should do
and what I shouldn't.
Everything ready
for the press conference this afternoon?
Have you reached out to the media?
Not yet. Shareholders are still talking.
They're not that foolish.
Perfect timing.
Everyone,
why not check the financial news?
Dear viewers,
at the afternoon market open,
Li Group's stock rebounds sharply.
In just three minutes,
the stock price has doubled.
Investors in dire straits can relax now.
In only two hours,
the market value doubled.
How is that even possible?
Ye Lang,
tell me
what exactly you did.
I sent Niannian into the study.
This was all
to set a trap for the mole.
Now we have the mole's IP address.
Liu,
care to explain
why your son works for the Ming Group?
These recent leaks,
were they tied to him or not?
Young Master.
You must be joking.
My son is just a junior staffer.
Hello?
Mom, the police said
they have proof I stole trade secrets.
Please beg the young master for me, Mom.
Young Master!
My son was led astray.
I'm begging you.
Please spare him.
Liu.
For all you've done for us,
I can choose not to press charges.
But the evidence is solid.
He'll face legal consequences.
(When did he plan all this?)
(How did I not notice a thing?)
(Was my entering the study)
(part of his plan?)
Such an important plan,
and you trusted it
to a woman who never went to college?
Niannian was only twelve
when she won
the National Computer Championship.
The woman I chose
is never wrong.
With someone so capable by your side,
Brother,
you've really gained a strong advantage.
I won't take advantage of her talent.
If she doesn't want,
I would never force her.
(I wiped those old things clean
using a fake identity.)
(My hacker alias is deeply hidden.)
(How much does he know?)
(And when did he start looking into me?)
Young Master.
Next time we cooperate,
have the contract ready first.
Niannian.
(Ye Lang.)
(You know every ugly part of me.)
(That feels even worse)
(than forcing)
(and using me.)
You're not my mom.
You're the other woman my dad kept!
You two killed my mom!
Don't talk nonsense!
Your mom died of late-stage cancer.
Anything to do with your Aunt Liu?
You're all awful!
I'm going to find Mom!
Want to find your mom?
Then you'll have to die.
You little brat.
I'm leaving this place.
I won the Computer Competition.
This prize money
is enough for Xiaodi and me.
Prize money?
Keep dreaming.
Your dad already gambled it away.
Do you think
you can take your brother?
No chance.
Give me back my money!
Give me back my mom!
How dare you!
Calm down.
She's just a kid.
(Atherton University, Jiang Niannian)
Why do you have
my admission letter?
How much can college earn you?
I've already arranged a marriage for you.
Mr. Zhang is 20 years older than you,
but he's thoughtful,
and generous with money.
Don't be so ungrateful.
(Jiang Niannian)
You crazy girl!
What are you doing?
I'll beat you to death,
then marry you to a dead man!
Don't hit my sister!
Xiaodi!
What bad luck.
If he dies, that's his fate.
We can't afford treatment.
I'm begging you.
Please save Xiaodi.
Please.
I'll go earn money.
I'll get married.
Please save Xiaodi.
I'm begging you.
Please.
I'll go earn money.
I'll get married.
I'm begging you!
Please save Xiaodi!
Of course.
I'm always the one who gets hurt.
Does it hurt?
Let me help you.
No need.
The same wound,
I won't take it a third time.
If you don't treat it, it'll get infected.
Be good.
Put it down.
I can do it myself.
Jiang Niannian.
Why are you
making things harder for yourself?
None of your business.
Ye Lang, what are you doing?
♪I falling for you, I falling you♪
♪Lost in your deep eyes♪
♪You slowly melt my frozen winter♪
That hurts.
♪Is walking the path of joy with you♪
Since
you won't let me help you,
then help me instead.
Okay?
Go sit on the couch.
♪I falling for you, I falling you♪
♪Lost in your deep eyes♪
What?
Got hooked?
♪I falling for you, I falling you♪
♪You slowly melt my frozen winter♪
♪Time stands still, I breathe so softly♪
♪Hearing your gentle voice so near♪
That day, you slipped into my study.
I already covered for you.
Niannian.
Do you trust me now?
Why?
You took the whipping,
hid the truth,
and set up something this big.
You even knew my hacker identity.
Such thorough investigation.
Ye Lang,
what do you really want from me?
♪Stitched-up lips
tear open a blood-red dusk♪
♪You return reborn,
seeing through all my cracks♪
♪This tenderness, a trap or a gift?♪
♪Still, I'd wager my next life on it♪
♪Just for a moment to recognize you again♪
♪You are the blazing light in my despair♪
♪Lighting the edges of my frozen wings♪
♪I burn myself,
leaping into an illusion of fire♪
♪Breaking free
from dead vines in the ashes♪
♪You are the brightest star in the night♪
♪Awakening my dormant fate♪
♪Freeing me from this half-life prison♪
♪As the bells shatter the past♪
♪Life finds its way again♪