(All characters, places,
and organizations are fictional.)
(Children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
What if it were possible...
to swap only the brain
without changing the face?
By any chance,
are you talking about you, Director?
If it were possible,
who would I swap with?
Momo.
No way.
Looks like we're the only guys here
on our own.
I guess it's because of your job,
but you're always so conscious
of what others think.
- I think that's him.
- I'm telling you, it is.
I think that woman
over there recognizes me.
- Right?
- She must.
A look like this is one of a kind.
Doesn't anyone recognize you?
Sometimes. The younger crowd, mostly.
I can't even eat out with actors.
They're always asking
for an autograph or a picture.
You win some, you lose some.
That's the price of fame.
Didn't you always say
there's no such thing as a free lunch?
Yesterday, Ju Shin said...
you and Reporter Geum looked
like a couple.
- And?
- I told him he's way off.
You two must have been pretty cozy
for him to say that.
What are you talking about?
You two are like brother and sister,
while she keeps me at arm's length.
Hey.
Do you really like Ba Ra?
I do.
Then stop thinking about your feelings.
If you were Ba Ra's actual brother,
and she told you she was dating a man
23 years older than her,
would you say "That's great, go for it"?
You sound just like her actual brother.
Loving someone means you must respect
and consider their feelings, not yours.
That's what real love is.
I think Manager Yoon is perfect for you.
"Perfect" how?
There has to be a spark.
Your standards are too high from dealing
with celebrities and their wives so often.
You're not one to talk.
(Ju Shin)
Momo is a commoner.
- Yes?
- So you went to the hospital together?
- Yes.
- His phone was off.
We're having breakfast together now.
Just as I thought, everything's fine.
Tell him he got a clean bill of health.
Okay. And tell him to cut back
on the sugary drinks.
An upset stomach can cause headaches.
Got it. Thanks.
Was that Director Shin?
- Hello?
- I don't feel well.
How so?
Could you pick up a pregnancy test
for me tonight?
A pregnancy test.
Okay.
Talk to you later.
Did you marry when you were young?
If you thought
Kim Jin Ju was your daughter...
I wasn't married.
It was back in high school.
- She was a year older than me.
- An older girl?
Yes.
We were young and reckless.
She got pregnant during my senior year.
So your girlfriend gave birth
when she was 20?
But then my family's business went under.
After my family went bankrupt,
she left our three-day-old baby
with me in midwinter December...
and disappeared.
But didn't she have a family?
Even her widowed mother, a cleaner,
didn't know where she went.
Creditors were hounding us,
so my parents went into hiding,
and I crashed at a friend's place
with the baby before moving to Japan.
When you came back,
did you ever hear from the baby's mother?
- You met her?
- I did.
And? Is she doing well?
The thing is...
I'll tell you more once I find my child.
Is she someone I might know?
She has to be someone I know.
Can you pull up a list of our clients
between the ages of 47 and 50?
- Both men and women?
- Just the women.
Right away.
Isn't that for Kang Ma Ri?
She doesn't want it?
- That's right.
- What is it now?
She says it makes her arms look big.
That's because her arms are big.
She should lose weight or chop them off.
She said the last one made her look
flat-chested.
She hated the Pedro dress
because it showed the top of her feet.
She's still complaining?
She's the one who stepped on the dress
and fell at the press conference?
I've reached my limit.
Tell her to find another sponsor.
Are you serious?
Yes.
(Director Shin)
Hello?
Is now a good time to talk?
- Yes.
- Do you have time to meet?
I wanted to ask you about the orphanage.
I'd like to get your advice.
- Okay.
- Today.
I'm booked until the day after tomorrow.
- Wednesday.
- Yes.
Were you right?
Goodness. Congratulations!
Congratulations?
You two are getting married anyway.
I'm not ready for that.
Just hurry up and have the wedding.
I don't want to have it.
Director Shin would be so happy.
Who cares?
This is the sky's way of helping you
forget your sorrows with a new life.
It's a gift
so that you can be happy again.
Are you saying all mothers are happy?
If you ever need help, ask anytime.
I don't need any.
You really don't get people, do you?
Don't jump to conclusions.
It's not my baby.
How could it be mine?
- Knock before you come in.
- But the door was open.
Close them.
Hello.
That's not me.
I heard that person quit.
What's your relationship to her?
I'm her father.
When I saw how startled you were,
I started thinking,
and I wondered if you had some trouble
when you lived at the orphanage.
Am I right?
After the director passed away,
have you happened to visit the orphanage?
The babies and toddlers...
are especially heartbreaking to see.
They play some lullaby-like music,
and it's already sad seeing
two or three babies napping together,
but imagine
if there's thunder and lightning.
The babies get absolutely terrified.
I wish they could hire more caregivers,
at least for the nursery.
So they're like aunts to the kids?
Yes.
Have some.
You don't care for wine?
No, that's not it.
To be honest,
I don't really know much about wine.
May I tell you a bit more?
You know you're not supposed to
let toddlers watch things on a phone.
Of course not.
You should bring it up
with the office manager directly.
I tried talking to the office manager
about it after I left.
He said they don't have
the resources for it.
I guess you don't get involved
in these matters at all.
It's not so much that I don't.
The office manager has been in charge
of running things since my father's day.
And we have advisors, too.
Well, it's a relief that
you're taking an interest now.
You make a donation every month,
don't you?
I saw your name on the donor list.
As I mentioned last time,
I wouldn't be where I am today
without the Nua Foundation.
I just want to give back
a little something...
Have you thought about quitting reporting
and taking over the orphanage?
As the director?
- That's out of the question.
- Why is it out of the question?
You're more than qualified.
Didn't Momo tell you?
I'm leaving my job at the end
of the month to help Momo out.
You're going to be her manager?
You're quitting the paper for that?
She says she needs someone
who can be like family.
That's why.
Momo's offer...
is for me to officially take over
and run the gallery in two to three years.
But above all,
I don't have anyone either.
Are you lonely?
Why did I ask something obvious?
I have a soft spot
for people younger than me.
So you're saying you're tough
on Yong Joong and me?
Also, it would be nice
to let the girls grow their hair out.
- They're forbidden to?
- It's high maintenance and hard to wash.
I was always so envious
of the girls with long hair,
watching them braid it,
tie it up, and put in pins.
I'd find myself staring
for the longest time.
Long hair suits you.
I cut a lot off when I started this job.
How long did it used to be?
Below my waist.
Do you have a picture?
What was your mother like?
She was incredibly devoted
to my dad and me.
You call him "Dad" too.
Who else?
Yong Joong?
It sounds so affectionate.
In what way was she devoted?
She was wise, I'd say.
She never graduated from college.
She met my dad during her sophomore year,
and they got married.
Do you take after your mother
or your father?
- In looks?
- In personality.
I don't take after my father, do I?
What's that nod for?
No reason.
And I'm nothing like my mother, either.
You and your father visited the orphanage
when I was in elementary school.
This might sound a little strange, but...
You were just so elegant and graceful.
Doctor...
This might sound a little strange, but...
Your looks are kind of wasted
on just your patients.
Have you ever been scouted?
Have I lost it all now?
You even talk like that?
Don't change the subject.
Do I look worn out,
beaten down by the world?
No.
Then and now,
you've always been hard to approach.
What's your type?
- I haven't thought about it.
- That would be a lie.
I think most women are
pretty much the same.
A man who's thoughtful and caring.
No. I know plenty of women
who like bad boys.
What about me?
The mean type?
There's a difference between being mean
and being a bad person.
And just because someone's cold
doesn't mean they're a bad person.
You do a lot of good, after all.
Through your hospital and the foundation.
Honestly, it's overwhelming.
I'm sure most people are...
if they're determined to live life
the right way.
In ten years,
I'll offer you the director's position.
We should do this from time to time.
And please continue to look after
the foundation.
Okay.
Can we get another carpaccio?
- Another one.
- Yes, sir.
It's nice to see you eat so well.
This is on a whole other level.
We'd sometimes get bulgogi
at the orphanage,
but the meat didn't even seem to be
imported beef.
To put it bluntly,
it was like eating stir-fried tire.
I take back saying
we should do this again.
You'll bankrupt the foundation.
What kind of mom do you want to be?
I'd have to get married first.
You're not the marrying type?
I guess that's probably how it'll be.
Why so hesitant?
- But you're so confident and smart.
- I'm just good at faking it.
When Momo has her baby,
I'll be happy just to be its aunt.
Let me rephrase the question.
What kind of aunt do you want to be?
The fun aunt.
You and Momo can be the villains,
and I'll just be the one
who spoils the kid.
(The Humanities of Discovery)
Looks like she's busy again today.
I wonder what the housekeeper
left for us to eat.
Give me back my head.
My head...
I am not Momo.
This is only Momo's body.
- What is she talking about?
- Inside my head, my brain...
is that of Geum Ba Ra,
a reporter for the Sungwoo Daily.
For real?
Everyone,
have you ever heard of a brain swap?
It is possible.
And the mastermind
with the divine touch is...
Director Shin Ju Shin
of Nua General Hospital.
- This is absurd.
- Seriously?
Oh my, what is that?
Is that really the scar? No way...
- Please, open the door!
- Director Shin!
(My daughter has a brain tumor.)
(Give my brain to my daughter,
Director Shin Ju Shin)
(My older brother is brain-dead.)
(I don't want to live,
so please save my brother, Director Shin!)
(My wife wants to die
because of her depression.)
(Her mother is in a nursing home
and could pass any day. Please, Director.)
- Director Shin Ju Shin!
- My brother is brain-dead!
(Hospital Director, Shin Ju Shin)
Please save my mother-in-law.
Please, Doctor!
- Please save my mother-in-law.
- Please save her, Director.
- Please, save her, Director!
- Director!
- Please, help us!
Help me, please!
Shin Ju Shin, you're under arrest
for the murder of Kim Jin Ju.
It doesn't look like
the director knows yet.
- Why didn't you tell him?
- You met him?
Yesterday.
- Why?
- He asked about the orphanage.
- Now that he's the foundation's chairman.
- The manager...
He has a manager for that, doesn't he?
He can just get a report.
There are things you can get
from a manager's report,
and things you only hear
from someone who was there.
I'm not having it.
That's ridiculous.
This isn't a decision
you get to make alone.
- What if he wants me to have it?
- Obviously.
At least talk to him about it.
My life is over if I have this baby.
Over? Not everyone gets to be a mother.
What time do you usually go to bed?
My articles go live early in the morning,
so I try to be in bed before midnight.
The chef is asking
if there's anything else you need.
I'm full.
- Check, please.
- It's already been taken care of.
It has?
When?
When I stepped out
to take that call earlier.
I'm the one who asked you to dinner.
Buying you this meal
is the least I could do.
The Nua Children's Home
may have fed you terrible meat,
but they sure raised you right.
Next time, I'm treating you properly.
I know a great Hanwoo omakase place.
It's members-only.
I didn't realize you were such a foodie.
I wouldn't say I'm a foodie.
What do you do for stress?
Just working is how I relieve stress.
If you're that satisfied with your job,
you can't just quit.
If I were the one
who desperately needed help,
I'd be heartbroken
if someone turned their back on me.
Do you trust people?
I have to, at first.
But I never want to be betrayed.
What if they do?
What happens then?
I cut them out of my heart.
I'd better be careful.
- Yes, Director Shin.
- When are you free?
I need to make
a reservation at the restaurant.
Can I check my schedule and text you?
Is it your bedtime?
- Sorry.
- No, not yet.
What about you, Director Shin?
What time do you go to bed?
I'm wide awake at this hour.
(Momo)
- Yes.
- Can I come up?
Is something wrong?
I'm pregnant.
I was feeling off,
so I took a pregnancy test.
Are you sure?
Those can be inaccurate.
If it's positive,
we should terminate it, right?
No.
I just had surgery,
and I've been on all these antibiotics...
They're still born
perfectly normal and healthy.
- What if...
- Don't even go there.
You're having the baby.
It'll be bad for our public image...
We're publicly engaged.
You're having the baby.
You don't seem very happy.
I'm just in shock. I wasn't expecting it.
It doesn't even feel like my baby.
By that logic,
are you never going to have kids?
I'm not ready for this now.
I've never even thought about it.
Then start thinking and preparing now.
And you must be diligent
with your prenatal care.
I'll be more attentive.
I had a scary dream
when I was waking up from the anesthesia.
I guess it was a conception dream.
What dream?
Paul.
I saw this outfit and thought of you.
I thought it would look amazing on you.
Thank you, but I can't just accept this.
Clothes are all I have to give.
It was sponsored for one of my actors,
so it's not new.
It'll just collect dust in my closet.
A huge movie star wore this.
(Seoul)
Are you planning to stay single forever?
Yes.
But we're both in our prime.
I can't trust women.
They're just not trustworthy.
They'll leave you in a heartbeat
if they think you've got nothing to offer.
That's not always true.
There are plenty of kind,
wonderful women out there.
Have you ever seen a fortune teller?
Is any of that stuff ever right?
They can be.
So what did they say about you?
That I'm destined to get married
within five years,
and that my soulmate is a younger woman,
old enough to be my daughter.
- Really?
- And then she appeared right before me.
- A young woman?
- Yes.
And then what?
After agonizing over it by myself,
I decided to let it go.
Why? It could've been fate.
I don't think so.
She doesn't see me that way at all.
Well, they did say five years.
You should wait and see.
You never know what life has in store.
Take Kim Jin Ju, for example.
And CEO Hyun Ran Hee, too.
You've met CEO Hyun, right?
She asked for your number,
so I gave it to her.
Yes.
Did she buy one of your pieces?
By the way,
can't you tell me who your first love was?
I won't tell a soul.
Some other time.
Are you still looking for your child?
I'll never give up.
As long as my child is alive.
Somehow.
Do you know the exact time
your child was born?
If you do...
Well, I'm not talking
about some divine act,
but a fortune teller might be able
to find something out for you.
Hey, Yong Joong.
- Did you pick up Pickles?
- Yes, the housekeeper was just leaving.
You should've just waited.
I'm on my way now.
I'm at Momo's place.
I wanted to show her Pickles.
You should come, too.
No, it's okay.
I'm sure Momo won't mind. I'll ask her.
Pickles.
You're so fancy.
Why would anyone abandon you?
Momo says we should all order some food.
(Today was another tough day.)
Today was another tough day.
No one talked to me,
and even though I got first place,
my homeroom teacher didn't praise me.
She was probably hoping
Park Ji Ah would take first.
Whenever I feel sad or treated unfairly...
and heartbreaking tears
well up in my eyes,
I get through it
by thinking of Yong Joong.
His warm embrace...
is unforgettable.
The warmth has been etched
into my very soul.
I'll become someone amazing...
and then go see him again.
Are we going out to eat?
No.
Welcome.
Oh my.
You shouldn't have.
I saw a flower shop in the building.
This is perfect.
I was all out of flowers and dessert.
There's a vase in the kitchen.
Put this in the fridge.
We can have that for dessert.
Please, have a seat.
Look how much he likes you.
Hey, Pickles.
That breed's pretty rare here, isn't it?
Yes.
What are you in the mood for?
There's a place
that has great eel rice bowls.
I'll leave it up to you, Momo.
I'm not a picky eater.
I'm so bad at deciding.
- Ba Ra!
- I'll do it.
And some sushi, too.
For two.
Does Pickles eat salmon?
He does.
You must be a total pro at games.
I wouldn't go that far.
Developing them is different
from playing them for fun.
I'm terrible at games.
I can't act.
Company helps me laugh and feel at ease.
It really does.
But I can't just invite anyone over,
you know?
Apparently, a hidden camera was installed
at my friend Yoo Kyung's place.
Don't tell me it was an acquaintance
who put it there.
Apparently, the housekeeper always watched
any repairmen who came over.
So now, Yoo Kyung doesn't invite
anyone over anymore.
She only attends parties outside her home.
It might look glamorous on the outside,
but it's an exhausting and lonely job.
Mr. Ha.
I'm just going to call you Yong Joong
from now on.
Let's drop the formalities.
"Mr. Ha" makes me uncomfortable too.
I bet you get to do everything
you want in life.
Is there...
anything you've wanted to do?
I'd love to just drive to the coast,
like in Gangwon Province.
Then you should go.
I'm not confident enough.
I've only ever pretended to drive
for a role.
And Director Shin Ju Shin
is always so busy.
Let's go today for some driving practice.
I have to watch Pickles.
Is it about a three-hour drive
to Gangneung?
There's no traffic at night.
Pickles, let's go.
At least eat dinner first.
I'm almost there. Be ready to go out.
Ju Shin is on his way.
He told me to get ready
because we're going out.
- A restaurant?
- Then he would've asked if I'd eaten.
We should get going.
- At least say hi.
- You can't freeze sushi, so take it.
I can't pick an outfit
if I don't know where we're going.
You can go to Gangwon Province anytime.
At least you got to see each other...
Hello?
Yes, speaking.
I'm not doing any interviews.
I just said she was my cousin back then.
I'm sorry.
How about we grab a meal sometime instead?
It will be my treat.
Okay.
All right.
Water.
- Hungry?
- Not really.
Then why are you cutting it?
Momo is going out too.
I'm going to freeze it.
Don't worry.
I don't like Shine Muscat cake.
That's not what I meant.
What do you mean?
Is that how you do it?
Let me do it.
Wash your hands first.
Should we get going?
I think Pickles has to go...
- You're were here?
- Yes, with Yong Joong.
It looks like he needs to go.
Just put a pad down for him
in the bathroom.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
Where are we going?
For an ultrasound.
I guess you guys ordered dinner?
Then eat before you go.
Put something down for him
in the bathroom.
Did you guys know I was coming?
We ordered plenty for four.
Are you not feeling well?
We're going for a pregnancy ultrasound.
Aren't you going to use any sauce?
This is so embarrassing.
The car's in the basement.
I called a cab.
Why?
His fur gets everywhere.
And he might scratch your expensive car.
It's not like it's his first time
in my car.
Are you upset about something?
No.
I'll keep him over the weekend.
Hold on.
My cab is here.
(Nua General Hospital)
(Congratulations on this new life!)
This will feel a little cold.
(Pet-friendly ride)
You know most drivers don't like
having dogs in their cars.
There's a special taxi service for dogs.
They have taxis like that?
Yes.
The doors are closing.
You're just going to leave me?
You came all this way.
Come up and have some fruit.
(Jaeil Apartments)
The doors are closing.
Pickles. Wait.
Wet wipes.
You'll spoil him.
I don't give him one when we're alone.
Do you like strawberry cake?
Mango cake?
Yes.
Strawberry? Mango?
Both.
Look at me.
I know what you're upset about.
But don't get me wrong.
That goes for you.
I'm the one getting it wrong?
I just don't like Shine Muscat cake.
But you added, "Don't worry."
I don't know.
It's just what I said in the moment.
Reporter Geum Ba Ra, you're difficult
when you get like this.
You're clearly in a bad mood.
It's so obvious,
but you just keep saying you're fine.
Am I supposed to be smiling all the time?
I wasn't saying
you couldn't have any cake.
I just meant we should all share it.
I know.
Don't look.
You had a taste. That's enough.
I feel like you treat Pickles better
than you treat me.
How could you say that?
Just be straight with me.
Tell me what's going on.
Momo hates flowers.
I'm the one who bought her
the pregnancy test.
You were so excited to see Momo,
with no idea she was pregnant,
that you brought her flowers and a cake,
which you never do for anyone.
I just felt a little bad for her,
that's all.
That's it?
Once you see her living happily
with Ju Shin,
you'll be able to let go and feel at ease.
I'll admit, I was a little surprised.
I never saw it coming.
But it's perfectly normal
for an engaged couple to have a baby.
You big baby.
Stop being so sulky.
You're starting to scare me.
There's that smile.
When the baby's born,
what will the kid call you?
Mister? Uncle?
Uncle, mister, whatever.
- Time to go.
- Can't I stay?
I know you're not serious.
I am serious.
I really do want to sleep over
with Pickles.
Be my guest.
But you don't have a change of clothes.
I wonder if Momo's baby
will be a boy or a girl.
If it's a girl,
Ju Shin will probably soften up.
He was so good to Momo in the beginning.
Isn't that because his father passed away?
After all, he's still in mourning.
That could be it.
I hold all the cards now, don't I?
I should start keeping a change of clothes
in my car.
People would get the wrong idea
if I kept a set for you here?
- The doors are closing.
- The wrong idea? From who?
Some of my reporter friends
come over sometimes.
If they were to see them...
And here I thought
I was your only close friend.
Momo stops by sometimes too.
Since when did you care
what other people think?
You have to.
The world doesn't always go my way.
Then I'll take the heat.
Move into my place.
I really can't seem to make myself leave.
Go on inside.
Try to get some proper sleep this weekend.
You look exhausted.
What?
You want me to get off? Stay?
Hey...
Yes?
The thing is...
I guess I was sulking.
- I knew it!
- You treat Momo better than me.
I was jealous and upset.
It's wonderful to see you. Welcome.
The lucky draw is over here.
Okay.
Hi! I'm a huge fan.
Thank you.
(Korea and Arnia 28th Anniversary
Cultural Exchange Festival)
- You're so stunning today.
- Thank you for coming.
You always radiate such beauty and energy.
It's lit up here with your bright energy.
It's been a while
since we last saw each other, hasn't it?
Yes, indeed. So good to see you again.
- Me too.
- Please come in.
(Korea and Arnia 28th Anniversary
Cultural Exchange Festival)
(Director Shin Ju Shin,
Nua General Hospital)
Director Shin.
Yes, Minister.
I'm surprised to see you.
I know how busy you are.
You're the ambassador's personal doctor?
Yes.
This is Minister Yu Jong Won.
- It's a pleasure to meet you.
- The pleasure is all mine.
- And your wife?
- She's already inside.
You're even more beautiful in person.
- Thank you.
- We'll head inside after saying hello.
Of course.
Hello, Ba Ra.
- How are you?
- I'm fine. Good to see you again.
Yes, me too. I'm so happy to be in Korea.
Doctor Shin.
Thank you for inviting.
This is Momo.
It's a pleasure to meet you, sir.
Please come in.
- See you again.
- See you later.
Hey!
Momo's here.
- Ms. Kim.
- Director!
- Fancy seeing you here.
- You transferred to Sekyung? Yes.
- You made it.
- Are you close with the Ambassador?
We see each other now and then.
I've even been invited to the residence.
- Go on in.
- Actually, I have to go.
Why?
I have an important meeting for a story.
You should've taken
your English classes more seriously.
Plenty of people can't speak English
even after four years at school.
Get an English tutor immediately.
You need to have some grit,
like Ba Ra.
Are you saying I don't have any grit?
You both grew up in the same environment,
but Ba Ra is fluent, isn't she?
(NUA)
I'm sorry.
Can you just write anywhere?
You can perform surgery anywhere
as long as you have your tools, right?
That's only possible
because it's physical work.
I have a hard time
just writing a birthday card.
And I'd be terrified
just holding a scalpel.
(Nua Children's Home)
(Infants and Toddlers)
(Ju Shin)
Breathe.
And rotate.
Keep your shoulders still.
Now, deep breath in.
- Almost there.
- Okay.
There you go.
Okay, that's it.
We've decided to grant you
a one-year leave of absence,
so take that time to think things over
and then decide.
Okay.
How about we get married
at the vacation house?
There are no wedding venues available.
The high-end hotels are fully booked
until the end of next year.
I don't want an outdoor wedding.
I don't care if we wait.
I want it to be at the Sera Hotel.
Does it have to be the Sera Hotel?
They say the photos are great there.
After the baby's born?
I lost...
the baby.
What do you mean you lost it?
I had a miscarriage.
When?
Why didn't you tell me?
You have surgery every single day.
I was afraid it would throw you off.
Besides, it's not exactly good news.
We can always try again.
Which hospital?
Why didn't you come to me?
Why didn't you tell me?
How dare you lie to me?
Lie?
Why would I?
Then name the hospital. Why can't you?
If you can't trust me, how can we marry?
That's my point.
You have to act trustworthy
if you want to be trusted.
Director Park Sun Jung.
You know her, right?
She promised she'd keep it confidential.
Is this who you really are?
Do you think I'm a pushover and a joke?
I have dignity, you know.
Then you should've just told me
the truth from the start.
How can you enjoy strawberries right now?
Like nothing's wrong?
Yes. I must be low on Vitamin C
because they're delicious.
This is really pissing me off.
You're pissed off?
Would I feel good after getting hit?
If I did, I'd be a sicko.
It's not like I'm the one who's pregnant.
You're right. I think it's for the best.
Check for yourself.
She said I could call her anytime.
You should've been worried
and asked if I was okay first.
Don't tell me you think
we cooked this up together.
This isn't just some minor issue.
Was this something you should have
handled by yourself?
That shows how much she thought of you.
She was worried you'd be upset.
Are you just going to hit me
whenever you want?
- Watch your mouth.
- And you're so classy you use violence?
Are you going to argue
with every single thing I say?
I'm sorry.
Then act like someone
I can continue to respect.
Respect is earned through
courtesy and consideration.
I'm the only son in my family.
You don't think this kills me?
- It's not like you control having kids.
- That's my point.
I told you not to swim.
Do you have any idea
how strenuous swimming is?
- And that's why you miscarried.
- It was fate.
- A proper marriage...
- Fate? What nonsense is that?
You should've been careful. It was early.
I was trying to have a healthy baby.
Don't make excuses.
You took those swimming lessons
on purpose.
I'm sick with pent-up rage, you know.
You tell me to be Momo, but you treat me
like the old Kim Jin Ju.
This is the last time
I'm letting this slide.
Stop trying to be clever.
Stop your petty little schemes.
I'm the one in control now.
Yong Joong.
Are you avoiding me?
Was what I said...
too much for you?
- Hello.
- I'm sorry, he's not in.
- Is he running late?
- He's out of the country.
- What about Pickles?
- James took him.
Meow.
Yong Joong.
There's a little kitten.
- How big?
- About 20cm?
It's skin and bones.
Did I really have to hear it
from your housekeeper...
that you went abroad?
Abroad?
It was just a business trip
to a nearby country for a few days.
You went to my place?
Because you missed me?
Why didn't you call?
I could've been home late.
I didn't want to disturb you
because you're always meeting people.
I figured the lights would just turn on
when I you got home.
Meow.
You know, some cats will come
and rub right up against you.
In other countries,
like in Europe,
they always keep
their garden sandboxes covered.
It's because stray cats
will use it as a litter box.
Ever do "Pat-a-Cake?"
Have you ever played that?
No, but I've been buried in the sand.
- At the beach?
- Of course. Where else?
What's it like?
I'm curious.
Let's go now.
Find out for yourself.
How?
Why not? We have a car.
You must be tired.
Just go home and unpack.
I'm not tired at all,
and I have nothing to unpack.
All I have is my carry-on.
Want to try driving?
This expensive car?
There's a rest stop coming up soon.
No way. I'm too scared.
"A chicken instead of a pheasant."
Momo's the one who should be here.
Don't say that.
You're neither a chicken nor a pheasant.
You, Geum Ba Ra, are a peacock.
The male peacocks are the flashy ones.
Exactly. You're not flashy.
You're graceful and elegant.
You're too much.
I'm not graceful in the slightest.
It's not about how you're dressed,
it's your aura.
Is Momo having trouble eating?
Morning sickness.
She says she doesn't want to have it.
- The baby?
- Yes.
- Why not?
- She says she's not ready.
But she has to.
I saw Momo and Director Shin
at the embassy party.
They seemed so happy.
Which embassy?
Arnia.
If you're not going to drive,
why don't you get some sleep?
Are you sure you're not tired?
Not tired.
Driving on an open road like this
is actually a great way to de-stress.
You seem like the kind of person
who never gets stressed out.
You're right. I rarely do.
It's just not in my nature
to get stressed.
You have no flaws. No shortcomings.
Just one request.
What is it?
Don't ever shave your head
and become a monk,
seeking enlightenment.
Did I figure out your secret plan?
I've never even considered it.
I've just read a lot of books by monks,
that's all.
Actually, not that many. Maybe 20 or so?
Hasn't that head monk you know so well
ever suggested it?
Head monks don't just ask anyone
to shave their head.
They have an eye for seeing
a person's true capacity.
He probably saw right through
my materialistic nature.
You? Materialistic?
I've thought about it, though.
About becoming a nun.
Why?
Kids who used to bully me in school
would say...
"Ashes, ashes, Ba Ra falls down."
They used to tease me with that sometimes.
I could have been born in a temple,
you know?
No, you weren't.
My eyes are stinging a little.
I'm just going to close them for a bit.
Alright.
Should I skip the rest stop?
You have to pull the bottle away
every so often...
and let them take a break
for a few seconds.
Otherwise,
since they don't know any better,
they will just guzzle it and spit it up.
We know how exhausting it is to throw up.
Is this who you really are?
Do you think I'm a pushover and a joke?
I have dignity, you know.
(Aren't you going up?)
(Are you going to do your rounds?)
How long has it been
since you've been to the beach?
The year before last for a story.
That long ago?
What about you?
Last month.
I just come here on a whim
whenever I have something on my mind.
I guess he didn't need to come here
just to think about what I said.
I think they maintain the sand here.
It's always clean.
There aren't even any seashells.
Speaking of regrets,
I do have one.
My dad and I...
never got to play catch. Not even once.
He was always so busy.
Doing it at a beach like this...
would've been so nice.
Nine is too young to lose your father.
Tell me about it.
So I can't even imagine
what it's like for you.
When you look at those waves
endlessly crashing on the shore,
what comes to mind?
Right now, nothing.
It just feels refreshing to watch them.
Does it help you feel a little lighter?
What about you? What comes to mind?
They remind me of the adversities
we face in life.
You get over one hurdle,
and there's another.
I suppose my waves have been
relatively calm,
so far, at least.
But you, Ba Ra, from a very early age...
were hit by a tidal wave,
but you weren't swept away. You held on.
I'm so incredibly proud of you.
When I was in Japan,
I thought long and hard
about what you said...
Where is my head?
What's wrong with me?
- What is it?
- It's in the car!
- For today...
- You don't need to show us.
All right.
How are you so good with babies?
Try asking what I'm not good at.
I left it in the trunk.
You brought this just for me?
Of course. Who else?
- You probably can't smell it by the sea.
- I can.
That explains it. On the drive here,
I wondered if you bought a perfume.
I didn't get you any
because I didn't think you wore perfume.
That's because I don't have any to wear.
I'll buy you some first thing tomorrow.
I'm just kidding. I don't wear any.
I hope the cream didn't melt.
It should be fine.
Look, they put an ice pack in.
I'm sorry it took me this long
to give you flowers.
I should have given them to you first.
It's not like big brothers usually do this
for their little sisters, anyway.
Even now, that first time we met
in front of the supermarket...
feels like only yesterday.
Your eyes were just filled with tears.
Just forget it.
It's not exactly a good memory.
It's not about whether
it's a good or bad memory.
When I think about
what you said back then,
my heart just aches.
I realize I never truly understood
what you were going through.
And I'm supposed to be
the one closest to you.
Aren't I?
You are.
It wasn't that I was being insensitive.
It was just that instead of
a small gift like a cake,
I wanted to do something
so much better for you.
To me...
you're not a little kid anymore.
And at some point,
I started to see you in a different light.
(Doctor Shin)
- Thank you.
- Are you her stylist?
I'm still just an assistant.
If Ba Ra finds out it's me and not Momo,
she is going to flip out.
Since you've decided,
can't you just do it once?
If you come with me,
I'll go three times instead of twice.
- Four times?
- I'll go with you every single time.
He might want to get rid of me,
but he can't just take out the brain.
To get rid of me, he'd have to kill Momo.
Could he kill Momo and get away with it?
Do you like Director Shin?
I used to have feelings for him.
- Grandpa says she died and came back.
- From the dead?
To Kim Jin Ju, Director Shin is
a deity or her Prince Charming.
But now it's my turn.
- Hey, James.
- Get over here, quick!
- What's wrong?
- What am I going to do?
My first love is...
Ba Ra.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)