Your Grace, be careful where you walk.
You might set off the alarms.
Just stay inside the mark--
Tell me how you did it.
How did you manage
to get through my high-tech security?
As you can see, it wasn't that high-tech.
But let me reassure you, it'll be easier
to steal The Lady with an Ermine.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
Aim for his head, Samuel.
What's going on here?
Have a seat.
Seeing how easy it was for us to break in,
you can imagine just how far away
we could be right now
with your Modigliani and your Rembrandt.
I'd say your collection is worth
approximately one billion euros, at least.
Mm.
So why did you call me
instead of making your escape?
Because there's something
that I need you to understand.
In my line of work there's
one fundamental rule for everyone. Trust.
So now you know that I'm capable
of doing the job and I'm trustworthy.
You can appreciate that my loyalty
is worth more than the billion euros
that I could've gotten away with.
It's okay. Go ahead.
Please answer the phone.
It is your place, after all.
- Yes?
- Your Grace, it's Santos.
There are people out to rob you.
They shot me, they kidnapped me,
and those sons of bitches stole my truck.
And they took the keys
to your property, sir.
It's okay, Santos. I'm aware.
I know these people.
You don't have to worry about it.
And from now on, you should know that
these gentlemen are welcome in my home.
You gotta be kidding me.
I don't fuckin' believe it.
Kid, you okay?
Listen, there, uh… There's been a fuck-up.
Come here. Let me help you.
Easy, or I swear to God
you're a fucking dead man.
Get below.
I'm very impressed by how much effort
you've put into gaining my trust.
And honestly,
you've succeeded.
- Sherry?
- Yes, I'd love some.
Sherry it is.
Your Grace, now that our friendship
is off to such an auspicious beginning,
may I ask you a question?
Be my guest.
What's going on here?
It's plain and obvious
that your collection is amazing.
But what's with this room?
And with the bed?
I've spent more nights in this place
than you can possibly imagine.
This is… my secret place.
But not… anymore.
This room is dedicated to beauty.
Exclusively.
Do you understand what beauty is?
I have a vague idea.
Well, for me,
it means waking up in that bed…
…with my beautiful wife.
And perceiving
the first rays of the sun
as they penetrate that dome
and light up
the beauty that is Vermeer's Concert.
I get emotional thinking
that I am the only person on earth,
the only person in the universe,
capable of experiencing
the joy of contemplating it.
Realizing this entire collection
is just for me.
For my eyes only.
As if Raphael, or Claude Monet,
or… Caravaggio…
had made these paintings for me alone.
Wealthy people like to spend their money
on things that give them pleasure.
Like real estate.
They buy yachts or bunkers.
Me? I have the sand from my bullring.
I have the aroma of my wine barrels.
I have my bulls.
And I have…
…my collection.
Does this satisfy your curiosity?
Come with me.
This is horseshit.
The bitch won't even listen to me.
This is a fuckin' nightmare.
You're a little late to the party, babe.
I was trying to help him.
Why would I fuckin' trust you?
You tried to rip my face off, asshole!
That was before. Right now,
my boss and your boss are meeting.
I just got off the phone with him.
Impossible. There's no signal
at the house.
Of course not.
There are jammers everywhere.
I called the landline.
Easy now,
or I will blow your fuckin' brains out.
Just let me get his phone, girl.
You'll see I'm not lying to you.
Nice and slow.
Give me your boss's name.
Nice try.
Check recent calls.
It's time to begin negotiating.
Cheers.
Um, please go ahead.
I mean, it can't be for me.
- Yes?
- Good evening.
May I speak with Berlin?
Well, guess what? It's not for me.
- Who is it?
- It's Roi, sir.
The warden told us you're with the duke.
Is it true?
Yes, it's true.
What do I do with him?
Nothing, Roi. Everything's fine.
So I'm just supposed to let him go?
This gentleman will need some rest
or even a visit to a hospital.
He's had enough excitement
for this evening, I think.
Hm.
I told you, kid. Everything's cool.
We're on the same team.
Not yet.
That's for my midnight dip.
Now we're even, asshole.
Might I suggest
we get down to brass tacks?
How much money shall it cost
for The Lady with an Ermine?
Thirty-five million euros.
How does that sound?
Not just for the heist.
There's planning involved.
There's significant personal risk.
Plus, we keep the painting hidden
until the police run out of leads,
and we can finally deliver the product
safely and without risk to you,
for your own individual pleasure.
If we take into consideration the value
of the ten most expensive works of art
is above 200 million dollars,
and understanding that Leonardo da Vinci
is the master of all masters,
then 35 million is quite a steal, really.
My dear Berlin, no need to explain.
Did you see me blink?
Not at all.
Because of the fact
that I find the price quite reasonable.
We'll also need an advance of four
or five million in unmarked,
nonsequential, used 100-euro bills,
all sealed and vacuum-packed.
Whenever the money is ready,
you let me know.
I'll have it for you by morning.
I'll wait for you at my estate
at 10:00 a.m. for breakfast.
I'll see you tomorrow.
How can he find that much in five hours?
You're asking the wrong question, Roi.
I can answer.
Those four or five million euros
in nonsequential, unmarked bills
don't come from an ATM.
Nor from some offshore account
in the Bahamas.
And definitely not from a Spanish bank
because it's Sunday.
So unless this guy has his own
money printing machine in the basement,
most likely, our friend the duke
keeps his cash well hidden somewhere.
I'm guessing it's undeclared income.
In other words, dirty money.
No one plans a heist with their own money.
So, Roi, would you please rephrase
the question?
Where does he keep his dirty money?
Bingo.
Duke Álvaro is hiding a fortune somewhere.
A large undeclared fortune,
somewhere not far from here.
And so that is precisely what we're going
to rob from that cocksucker.
He must be sitting on a lot of cash.
There were 15 paintings
hanging on the walls.
Do the math. If he paid 20
or 30 million for each of them,
it means he could have
over 400 million euros.
Okay, but how does a Spanish nobleman
like our duke
end up with more than 400 million euros
in dirty money?
It's not the wine. No way.
And it's not the prize bulls.
It's the yachts.
Renting out boats to movie stars
will hardly make you a fortune.
Well, it would if you're not just
transporting movie stars.
This might be worth looking into, no?
Sure, but none of us
are interested in where it comes from.
Actually, I'm very interested.
The more we know about him
and his business,
the more we have him by the balls.
I'll go.
I can infiltrate one of his yachts.
But I'll do it solo.
Good idea.
I'm really sorry that your reconciliation
with Roi didn't pan out.
I'd say you're less interested
in infiltration
than you are with getting away.
Getting away from him.
Yeah, so?
So be it, then.
No way. It's too risky.
She can't infiltrate all on her own.
If she wants to, she can.
She has to grow up at some point.
But as the leader of
our little gang of thieves,
I believe I have
the right to know what happened
between the two of you
that was so damn bad
that you never want
to spend any time with him.
He pushed me too far.
Can you get that, please?
Hello?
Hey there, lovely.
Her ex turned up one day by surprise.
And I'm guessing
that made your blood boil.
Not really. I wasn't the one
who was thrown off by the visitor.
When I told Nora I had a gig here,
she told me you lived in the area.
What a coincidence.
Hey.
Time for a walk?
No way.
- Who is it?
- Come on down. I just wanna chat.
Get the hell out of here!
You won't make me come down.
Listen, our life was a fuckin' mess.
I get that.
But we need to be able to talk about this.
I should've realized then and there
that you needed professional help.
Stop.
But I didn't notice.
Or I didn't want to.
You've ruined my life.
Calm down. You'll be okay.
I'm not gonna calm down!
Not until this guy disappears, got it?!
I just wanted to help.
She doesn't want to, okay?
It'll be better if you leave.
There's no fuckin' way.
Not until I see her.
I wanted to ease your pain.
Or your anger. I don't know.
You're a piece of shit!
Roi, I begged you for help.
Come down. I just wanna talk.
Can you hear me?
- Don't worry. Relax. It's okay.
- Make him leave.
Please come down!
Just breathe.
I'm trying to breathe, Roi, okay?
I'm not leaving
until we find a way to get some closure!
Someone has to go down
and teach him a lesson,
or he's never gonna leave.
- I can't.
- Why can't you?
Because I think it has to be you.
You have to go down and face him yourself.
I know you can do it.
You're not the same person
who fell in love with him.
You're stronger now.
You're the bravest woman I know.
Babe.
Go talk to him.
Go down there and tell him it's over.
You'll close that wound once and for all.
Close my wound?
That's not what you wanted, Roi.
You're lying.
You just wanted to stand on the balcony
and watch me reject him and choose you.
You sent me down there to face your fears,
not mine.
- Because deep down, you don't trust me.
- Cameron.
I wanted you to go down and say goodbye.
Not to go and fuck him.
I'm not the guilty one, Roi.
You are. You forced me to see him.
- It was too painful, but…
- …you made me.
- You're…
- …a pyromaniac.
With no self-control.
- You're so unstable, you can't hold on…
- …to anything.
- -Every shitty thing that happens to you…
- …you deserve it.
You destroyed it all.
With no thought for the damage you do.
I've decided to give me
and Jimmy a second chance.
Because the chance I gave you
only made me miss him even more.
It's over between us.
I never wanna see you again.
Don't try to find me.
And if you ever see me in danger,
turn the other way.
Good morning, Captain.
We have a date.
- Oh, yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
I don't remember.
Because you didn't know about it.
But it's okay. I did.
I wanted to say thank you
for all that you've done.
For my reckless and dangerous driving?
For escaping the police?
No, something better. Much better.
It's been 24 hours, a full day,
since I thought about my ex.
Amazing, isn't it?
I think it is.
Okay. You grab a shower.
I've prepared everything.
This will look good. Try it on.
See how it fits.
We can't have you clashing.
Clashing? With what? Hm? Tell me.
That's a surprise.
So how did you find me?
When I went through your wallet,
I found a bill for the marina,
and then, pop, a light went on in my mind,
and I thought,
"Candela, could he be the kind of man
who travels only by yacht?"
Well, I was right.
Hey.
- Good morning, miss.
- I think we woke him.
Simón, may I speak with you for a moment?
- Pardon me.
- No, no.
One second.
Damián, I'm taking
the rest of the day off.
Taking the day off?
You have a meeting
with the duke, remember that?
He has a little something for you.
Four or five million euros
in unmarked bills. Ring a bell?
Of course it does. Okay?
I've been up all night with Keila,
working on plan Ali Baba.
It's amazing.
And just as I was falling asleep,
she came into my cabin.
And what the hell is plan Ali Baba?
Damián, it is a work of pure genius
that will lead us to his cave
as soon as he gets you the cash,
all right?
- Why would he give it to me?
- Damián, come on, focus.
The hard part was the plan, right?
Now that it's done,
it's time for you to execute it.
Talk to Keila.
And please do me a favor.
Bring a classy bag, something elegant.
I can't stand thieves
who carry cash in briefcases.
It makes us appear unprofessional,
like accountants.
Wait. And what will you be doing?
Simple. Embracing life, my brother.
Let me show you the narrowest street
in all of Seville.
- Do you know its name?
- No.
It's called The Alley of the Kiss.
So…
Do you have any idea
why I brought you here? Hm?
I really have no idea whatsoever,
but I'm eager to find out.
Let me tell you, then.
The people I despise the most
in this world
are the people who wait
till the end of the date to kiss.
Unbelievable.
It makes me so angry.
Why does it make you angry?
Because these are people
that are constantly afraid.
Who are incapable of
embracing life completely.
These are people who, confronted
with happiness, they save it for later.
You never know.
What do you never know?
You never know. It might run out.
And they save their kisses until the end.
Then they go back home contented.
But I don't think you can save happiness.
You spend it on the people you like…
right from the beginning.
And once I begin, I never stop.
I've wanted to kiss you
ever since I saw you throwing
that stuff out the window.
And also when I broke into your house.
But now that I think about it,
it would have been highly inappropriate.
Hey, would you mind letting us pass?
- When you're ready.
- What, is this the only street in Seville?
- For God's sake. Okay, come on, go.
- Uh, sure.
- Please. Go ahead, sir.
- Sorry.
- Come on, go.
- That's it.
- Another voyeur.
- For sure.
The dog's just a cover, right?
He's hoping to get a good look.
Follow me.
Lead the way.
Come in. The door's open.
I need an explanation
of this plan Ali Baba.
You've heard the story
about Ali Baba and the 40 thieves, right?
I don't remember that much.
It's the story
about this guy who discovers
where the gang of 40 thieves
keep their treasure.
- Okay.
- In a cave
that opens miraculously
when you say the words "open sesame."
Uh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This way.
- You've never heard of it?
- Fairy tales are not my priority.
Let's get back to plan Ali Baba.
The plan is to discover
where the thief hides his treasure.
But in this case, we're not the thieves.
We are Ali Baba.
- Well, I see you're punctual.
- Uh-huh.
- And where, may I ask, is your boss?
- He's concentrating on the plan.
I'm his right-hand man,
and I handle the financial part.
And also the bag part.
I see you've brought your own.
Yes. There's nothing worse than thieves
who carry cash around in a briefcase.
They make us look like accountants.
I couldn't agree more.
Good morning.
Darling, our chauffeur is waiting.
When I look at you, I have
an irresistible need to be irresponsible.
However, I must see to these gentlemen.
What would they think of me?
- I must attend to them.
- Mm.
My husband is cheating on me,
and he thinks I don't know.
It's exhausting for me to compete
against such works of perfection.
And now, the Leonardo.
Samuel, please accompany my wife.
Gentlemen, my babysitter awaits.
So be it. Shall we proceed?
Uh, yes, yes. Of course.
The money you requested.
I presume you'll want to count it?
Yes. Part of my job is to trust no one.
I know of some esteemed colleagues
who were paid with photocopies.
When you go see the duke at his palace,
it's very important
to bring the money bag with you.
Why? Because you'll hide
all this cash inside.
First 40,000.
Notice anything strange?
They look like regular 100-euro bills,
nonsequential and unmarked.
What's the issue?
The idea is for you to put on a show
so that the duke believes
you're counting all his money.
3,960,000.
- And then at one point…
- Four million and forty thousand.
That'll be fine. Give that one back.
Tell me, Keila, why on earth
would I want to give him back 40,000?
Because it's part of the plan.
We're not giving him back the money.
We're switching it.
The new wad will contain
a high-tech, long-range tracking device.
It's important that you hide it
in the bills you return to the duke.
That way, we can follow the money
and find his treasure.
You don't like my money?
No, not at all. The money's fine.
But for the moment,
four million should be enough.
You asked me for five million.
We asked you for four or five.
The fact that you brought five
says a lot about you as a partner.
And it speaks volumes
about your generosity and your fortune.
Were you testing me?
Assessing me as a partner? Like an audit?
On me?
Our business is entirely built on trust,
as Simón says.
- Should I put them back in the plastic?
- No, no. There's no need.
Okay. I'll leave them here.
Come on.
Your fish look good today.
Psst. Hey.
Are those oranges from China?
Ah.
Oh, amazing.
So what have we here?
The Cave of Secrets.
This private party happens every year
to celebrate
two upper-class ladies' birthdays,
the duchess of Málaga
and the countess of Seville.
Oh, wow.
Welcome. If you want to party,
you have to eat.
- Thank you.
- People from all walks of life come here.
You've got Spanish aristocrats,
epicureans, artists.
The party runs all day and all night.
- Let's party, then.
- Yes, let's do that.
Someone's asking for you on the balcony.
Excuse me for a moment.
Samuel, can you get me
a glass of wine? Godello.
I believe it's your birthday.
Congratulations.
I need to speak with you alone.
I'm being watched all the time.
Go to the bathroom on the third floor,
with the Niña de los Peines portrait.
Keep the door open and the lights off.
Your Grace? One moment, please.
You're good. It's all clear.
Duchess.
Last night I had planned
birthday celebrations with my husband,
and you ruined them.
I apologize.
I'm sorry. I don't accept your apology.
You owe me one. I've got a job for you.
I want you to steal
my husband's paintings. The lot.
I'm pretty sure you'll make a huge profit
selling them on the black market.
It's not that easy, actually.
I'll add a gratuity
for your many troubles.
How about one million in cash?
Personally, it makes me
feel uncomfortable.
The idea of gratuity.
Getting in won't be a problem.
I'll help you myself.
Genoveva, I already know the way.
Yesterday we got in all by ourselves.
You're not very interested.
The problem is you seem
to have overlooked a minor detail.
I am a gentleman.
And I have given my word to your husband.
So, you understand. So has my associate.
I like that man.
He's… pensive and intelligent.
I'm sure he'll understand
that the deal I'm offering
is far more interesting than my husband's.
Infinitely more.
What I'm offering is the real deal.
Duchess, I find this entire situation
to be absolutely intriguing.
So, if you do not mind,
I'd like to ask you a question.
Why would you want to betray your husband?
Have you ever been in love before?
Sometimes I wonder
if I've ever not been in love.
When I was 15 years old,
every day between 5:00 and 7:00,
I would stay to study.
At around 5:30,
the boys from the nearby French school
came to ride their horses.
My school has a long equestrian tradition.
Álvaro was always late
for his riding classes.
- Do you know why?
- Mm-mm.
Before attending class,
he would scale the school walls
to come watch me study.
Maybe an hour.
Or half an hour.
And I never noticed it.
Until one day, one of the nuns
started throwing stones at the guy.
No one ever looked at me like that before.
And he continued to do so for 20 years.
Until now.
And now he prefers his collection?
Precisely why I want it gone.
And once it's gone, what do you expect?
I mean, what if after it is all gone,
even then, he still doesn't look at you
like he did back then?
I don't get it.
What if your husband discovered
this passion for art
because his feelings for you had fizzled?
All things considered, life is not so much
about disposing of one's lover.
Rather, it is about wishing deep down
they'll choose us
ahead of everything else.
Well, that is an elegant way
of rejecting me.
But you've given me food for thought.
I think that you might even
have sparked a light.
But you must understand
that when I negotiate,
I am even more ruthless than my husband.
Trust me, you will not leave this party
until you have accepted my offer.
Because…
with so many armed police
out searching for you,
I believe stealing The Lady with an Ermine
might be beyond you.
Keila, we've just left the duke's house.
Is the tracker working?
Yes. The money has not moved yet.
It's still inside
the reception hall of the palace
Bruce, Roi, once the money
leaves the palace, you follow it.
But don't take any risks.
Stay around 500 meters back.
Keila will guide you.
- What's up?
- Get over here. We have a problem.
- Where are you?
- Stuck inside a bathroom at a party.
The duchess brought me here
to make me an offer.
One million euros if I steal
her husband's art collection
and make it disappear.
- I don't get it.
- He's lost interest in her.
His only passion is art.
- Completely insane.
- No, she's not crazy.
She says I am not leaving this place
until I accept her proposal.
And we can't rob The Lady with an Ermine
with the cops after us.
So she threatened you?
What are you gonna do about it?
- Have you accepted?
- Of course I haven't.
'Cause you're coming over
to work your magic.
And you're gonna get that idea
out of her head.
- What are you talking about?
- Listen to me.
I want you to go to the marketplace,
to the orange seller's stall.
You'll find two women.
You're going to ask
if their oranges are from China.
After that, you--
What's going on? Can you hear me?
Well, hello there.
Candela.
What a surprise. What brings you here?
Were you waiting for me
But of course I was.
Well, I'm here now.
So, is there anything more
that you're not going to leave
for the end of our date?
One more thing.
Can you guess what?
Hmm.
- Think you can handle it?
- Mmm.
You pathetic old cheat.
Do you think I was born yesterday?
When you kissed me in the alley,
that was a commitment,
yet two minutes later,
you're in here with the duchess.
- No.
- With my saliva still on your mouth.
Do not deny it. I saw it with my own eyes.
Standing on the balcony,
waving her hand
like she's some kind of Cleopatra.
And you ran to her like a dog.
Listen, the duchess wanted
to speak with me privately.
And of course, I agreed
because I'm a friend of her husband's.
And I believed that she wanted
to discuss something personal
or important or possibly tragic.
You see, in the end it turns out
that she just wanted to talk business.
Andrés, what are you doing?
What kind of business
could you talk about in the bathroom?
So tell me, what kind of business?
Drop it. What kind of business
could you possibly discuss in there?
Obviously, something illegal.
Were you flirting?
Yes, yes. Say yes.
Take one for the team, Andrés.
You've got yourself stuck in a corner.
- Be careful.
- I admit it. You're right.
The duchess brought me here
under the pretense of talking
about some urgent and personal matters,
but in fact… she tried to seduce me.
And naturally, I refused.
Excuse me, I beg your pardon,
but, um, are your oranges from China?
Are you serious?
I can't believe you're still lying.
You refused? Okay, nothing happened.
Are you some kind of saint or what?
Do you have any idea
who you're speaking with?
Hey, what's going on?
Listen. You're not used
to dealing with a woman like her.
She's nobody's fool.
Well, it looks like you're very
up-to-date on the duchess's movements
and also about my own whereabouts,
and you're obviously set
on not trusting me,
so I'll be blunt with you.
We were in the bathroom
no more than three minutes.
Now, that's just enough time
to reject a woman.
It's hardly enough time
to bring her pleasure.
It's impossible.
The amount of bullshit is unreal.
Were you a lawyer in a previous life?
Let me tell you something
I believe you
because no man finishes that fast.
You'd better not with me.
If you're not going to honor
what happened in the alley,
you should leave me now.
Never call me back.
I can't believe it.
Do you have
what I think you have in the bag?
You must be quite a piece of work
to walk around
with millions of euros at a big party.
Or maybe I'm in the mood for a party,
and I know that the best place to keep
this safe is right here by my side.
Follow my lead.
Samuel, we were just talking,
and we were wondering if by chance
there was something exciting to drink.
Would you find us two gin and tonics
with crushed lemon
and black pepper from Madagascar?
Thank you.
He'll be gone a while,
looking for black pepper from Madagascar.
Can you tell me why we're running?
To escape my babysitter.
I'm a little confused,
and I need time to think.
Follow me upstairs. This way.
I had a sort of epiphany
when speaking with your associate.
Come with me over here.
- Sit down. Relax.
- Okay.
So tell me about this epiphany.
I realized that your associate
and my husband
are exactly the same type of man.
I must admit
that I've had the same impression.
And yet, you and I,
we both accept a back seat
because we want the people
that we love to shine.
And for some reason, we find it sexy.
What is it that you find sexy?
A real man, one who's confident.
He doesn't need to be constantly reassured
and comforted.
He doesn't have to spend his time
trying to surprise you.
He doesn't need to grandstand
about his eccentricities.
Well, I suppose we're somewhat
like those old B-sides
that we find on our favorite records.
Those rare gems.
How about both of us,
we start a revolution.
You and I,
the new revolution of the B-sides?
You want to betray Álvaro?
That was the idea.
The plan was
to rob his entire art collection
so that he'd look at me.
An act born of futile desperation.
But the revolution begins here.
It begins with me.
Don't you agree?
I've always been a faithful wife.
A loving one.
And now that will end too.
Your friend, he got me thinking.
I thought that maybe we were no longer
in love…
and that…
it might… be the right moment
for me to begin a new chapter in my life.
Shall we emancipate each other, you and I?
Together, we make our own music.
We record our own A-sides, yours and mine.
I'm sorry. I'm not exactly
a music connoisseur,
so I'm not sure I understand you.
When you came in, I was asking
the Virgin of Macarena, the Mother of God,
to bless me and to help me find a way
to turn my life around.
That's when you walked in.
A man of refinement, a man of virtue,
carrying a tote bag filled
with millions of euros.
Don't you think it was a sign from heaven?
It was meant to be.
I believe that you are the perfect partner
to begin my new revolution
and to start my life
as an unfaithful wife.
With me?
I think your watch is vibrating.
Ah…
It's, uh…
It's a call from a friend. Excuse me.
"Put in your earpiece."
Talk to me, Keila.
The cash is on the move,
but inside the building.
Maybe he's having it all vacuum sealed,
or maybe he's preparing to ship it out.
No, I don't think so.
The tracker indicates it's underground.
I lost the signal when it was 26 meters
below the surface.
According to the floor plans, that means
that the money's under the chapel.
But according to those plans,
there's nothing under the chapel.
Unless…
Unless he decided to build a vault
underneath the palace.
That would explain why you lost the GPS.
- Roi.
- Holding position.
Go get Keila.
Find out as much information
as you can about that chapel.
Bruce, go with them.
Ten-four. At the boat.
Yes?
Hey.
- Hello.
- I have a surprise for you.
I'm in Seville,
and I'm looking right at your boat.
Keila?
Keila? Good evening, everybody.
And welcome.
Just a few hours ago, while walking
through Seville, I met this goddess.
And yet, in this short time,
I've experienced more
than many married couples have
over a lifetime.
I've been shot at, I've been robbed,
and even though
we're not officially married,
we almost got divorced.
But she's offered me a second chance.
And so to celebrate that moment,
I've asked her to sing a song.
So, a round of applause.
Nice beat.
Ready?
Every breath you take
And every move you make
Every bond you break
Every step you take
I'll be watching you
¡Olé!
Every single day
And every word you say
Every game you play
Every night you stay
I'll be watching you…
Psst. Hey.
Psst.
Every move you make
And every vow you break…
We have the coordinates
for Ali Baba's cave.
Excellent news. So where's the hideout?
On the palace grounds.
It's just underneath the chapel.
There must be a vault or safe
because we lost the tracking signal
about four floors below.
Perfect. Now that we've located the loot,
we just go in there and take it.
How wonderful.
A nightingale
A song so sweet and likes to tell…
Wow.
I think I'm in love with this place.
How did it go with the duchess?
Did you get her to change her mind
about robbing Alvaro?
- That was easy.
- Excellent.
Except now she wants to have an affair,
and she thinks I'm the perfect match.
We've only met three times,
but she told me the Virgin of Macarena
chose me to be her lover.
She moved in close to me
and whispered it in my ear,
and I had to hide the goosebumps
bulging on my arms.
And then she said she wanted
to be an A-side,
and I had no idea what to say.
She got inside your head. Be careful, now.
This is just perfect.
Now you keep her there,
wrapped around your finger.
What are you saying?
The perfect match,
the partner pulling all of those strings.
He loves me, he loves me not.
It's your turn to become a Latin lover,
Damián, a real predator.
Having fun?
- With black pepper from Madagascar.
- Ah.
I hear you've begun working on my order.
Yes, you're right. I came here
because I had a question for you.
Mm-hmm.
We can't continue working from the boat.
It's inconvenient, and we've got
blackboards, sensitive documents,
and material that must remain secret.
Something more private
would be preferable.
We were thinking
about the north wing of the palace,
inside the tower.
Hey there.
- Hello.
- Hello, my love.
Guess what? I've decided
to allow Simon and his friends
to stay with us at the palace
as our guests for a couple of days.
What do you think?
It's a brilliant move, Álvaro.
The timing's perfect.
It looks like I'll need to keep you
on a short leash.
This man is just constantly running away
from me.
I'm sorry, but we're having an affair.
- Coochi-coochi.
- Mm.
Indeed. Well, this… this is Candela.
Happy birthday.
Thanks a lot.
And by the way, Candela,
let me introduce Damián, my associate.
We were talking to the duke
and duchess
about doing some business together.
More business?
Or the same business you guys
were talking about in the bathroom?
No, Candela.
This is a different discussion.
Oh, I get it.
I see that you and your friend here
really love money, huh?
Sorry, I've gotta go.
Was it something I said?
No. No, no.
Have you seen the bag that I left here?
What was in the bag?
You seem to be very anxious.
Lucky
My baby, he says he's lucky
But I know how much he loves me
I know I'm the lucky one
Lucky
As sure as the stars above me
He tells me he's dreaming of me
And so, I'm the lucky one
I promised myself
I was through with love
Through being fooled by a kiss
I guess fortune was smiling
From heaven above
What are the chances
Of a love like this?
Lucky, my baby, he says he's lucky
But I know how much he loves me
I know I'm the lucky one
I promised myself
I was through with love
Through being fooled by a kiss
I guess fortune was smiling
From heaven above
What are the chances
Of a love like this?
Lucky, my baby, he says he's lucky