(Uilhan Brewery)
(1. Malting, 2. Malt milling, 3. Mash tun, 4. Hopping)
(Kim Se Jeong)
(Highly passionate, highly sensitive)
(Lee Jong Won)
(Shin Do Hyun)
(Baek Sung Chul)
(Uilhan Brewery)
(Naro Beer)
(Brewing Love)
(This is a work of fiction.)
(Scenes with child actors and animals were filmed...)
(under production guidelines along with experts.)
Let's have a look.
(Episode 11)
These are the label samples the Design Team sent over.
The drawing of a group of people...
is great at accentuating the name,
but I think...
It doesn't show the taste or flavour and strength...
of the beer that we want to promote.
(Posters)
Shall we call it a day, then?
Yes.
- Bye. - See you.
(Posters)
(Min Ju)
Is something bothering Ms. Chae?
Together went into mass production.
She's worried the taste will shift.
I heard about that term.
What exactly does it mean when taste "shifts?"
Even if the ingredients and recipe are the same,
depending on the maturing, fermenting, temperature and things,
unpredictable minute changes...
can affect the beer's taste.
Yes.
Our first batch is 3,330,000 bottles.
That means all 3,330,000 beers must taste the same.
But something minute could change that.
Industry people call that...
a taste shift.
I panic when I go from cooking one packet...
of noodles to ten at once.
Over 3.33 million beers...
Mr. Yoon must be really stressed out too.
- Is he okay? - That's why Ms. Chae's worried.
(Fermented Liquor, Chapter 1: Beer)
(Craftsman Bartender and Brewery Management)
Hey.
- You said you'd be working late. - Yes.
What's up?
I rushed over after sitting in meetings all day long.
You must be busy with the release.
You should get some rest.
I'm here because I had a feeling our brewmaster...
would be too worried to sleep.
Seeing you wiped away my worries.
- Did it? - Yes.
Goodness.
You're looking out for me when you must be busy?
Looking out for the brewmaster...
is part of my job as head of the team.
It gets to you, doesn't it?
It does.
I've never produced this much beer in one go.
In this field,
a taste shift isn't rare.
But that doesn't mean it's a defect.
It's just a minute change in taste.
But people who drink the same thing all the time...
can tell right away.
They go, "Hey, the beer tastes different."
That's the scariest.
It is.
- Is there anything I can do? - What?
Hang on.
Hi, Beom.
Really?
Schedule a meeting tomorrow with the head of SCM.
Yes, sure. Thanks.
Go home. You have work tomorrow.
I can stay another hour.
Then spend that extra hour on sleep.
Get going.
Get up.
No, wait. I'll drive you.
You can nap on the way.
- You're too tired to drive. - I'm fine.
We have a good recipe...
and we won the contest.
And the chairman's tasting went fabulously.
Our beer is perfect.
I got you worried for nothing.
Don't say "nothing." Of course we should worry together.
That's the name of our beer. Together.
See you when the first batch is out.
- Bye. - Bye.
See you.
(Brewing Love)
Hello, sir.
The first batch is being transported today.
I was thinking about stopping by the factory to...
What did you just say?
Why can't the beer be transported today?
What on earth are you saying?
I'll come to you. I'll be right there.
(Jisang Liquor)
Min Ju.
The first batch of products can't leave the factory today.
- It can't happen. - Hold on.
Were you the one who stepped on the brakes?
What are you saying?
They must leave the factory today...
to be sent to direct-only stores across the country.
What if we can't meet the launch deadline?
Push the deadline back.
I also have authority over the launch of Together.
Yoon Min Ju, what's going on?
This is our beer. We made it together.
This batch of beer...
will be dumped,
Ms. Chae.
Taste both of them.
(Jisang Liquor)
There's a subtle difference to the taste.
Was there a taste shift?
When we produced the first batch,
we used a different fermenting tank.
I think that affected the taste.
I can't have it released in this state.
Give me a little more time.
I'll get the taste back on track. I can do it.
- No. We must ship it today. - Yong Ju.
I'm speaking as the team leader.
If we fail to release the first batch on time,
our credibility will drop in no time.
Don't you know how important credibility is?
Why are you thinking only about this one time?
Consumers can even tell mineral water brands apart.
If word gets out that it tastes different,
they'll turn away from our brand.
Then...
what about the wholesalers waiting for our product?
Who would trust us...
and sell our product if we break our word from the start?
A loss in credibility means a loss in sales.
Who wants to drink a beer that tastes different each time?
Once consumers turn away, we'll have to stop producing this.
Min Ju.
Do you know how much the product in the factory costs?
It costs five million dollars.
Five million dollars.
If we halt production, we won't recover the five million...
that went into the first batch,
but we'll also lose the money we invested in developing it.
That's a much bigger loss.
You said you wanted our beer to do well.
I'm doing this because I want our beer to do well.
It's more important to keep our promise.
It tasting perfect is more important.
- Min Ju! - Yong Ju!
Do you want our beer...
to be a quick hit before it disappears?
Go home.
The directors will have heard about it by now.
I must report to them.
Yong Ju.
We must stop it now.
This is our last chance.
We identified the problem first...
and can fix it so why won't you?
It will come back at us as a much bigger problem.
No company can accept this.
I work at Jisang Liquor...
and have a duty to follow their decision.
Don't you see where I stand?
I'd like you to leave everything to us...
from here on out.
(Jisang Liquor)
It's a precious beer we made together,
so I'll make sure it's a hit.
That being said, you'll properly see me do my work.
I've been eyeing you from the moment we met.
(Jisang Liquor)
Do you want our beer to be a quick hit before it disappears?
Are you kidding me?
Why can't you release it?
You used to work in sales!
Don't you fear the sellers?
(Marketing Director Na Tae Jo)
I'm sorry, sir.
But...
now that I know it tastes different,
it's only right to correct it before release.
I'll apologize in person to each wholesaler...
and ask for more time.
Can't I do that?
Are you out of your mind? Is this a joke?
Sir.
I know very well how nonsensical this is.
But...
it's also a fact that...
a beer that tastes wrong doesn't last long.
All the classic beers that the public still loves...
tasted exactly the same until they took over...
five percent of the market.
Five percent of the market is worth 200 million dollars.
That's the kind of beer Mr. Yoon wanted to make.
This will profit us in the long run.
That means throwing away five million dollars!
Why would you even talk about classics lasting long?
What are you saying?
How would the customers know it tastes different?
No one will know!
We know.
You lot...
You lost your minds...
because the chairman has your backs.
You seem to think you actually have the right to make decisions...
because the chairman said so!
Don't go too far...
across the line.
Get out.
Get out!
My gosh.
You're the factory manager.
What are you doing?
Why would you listen to such nonsense?
Who cares if it tastes a bit different?
That's nothing!
Ship the beer right away.
Right now.
What did he say?
No, of course.
It's hard for a company...
to dump a batch for tasting off.
Still, we can't just ship it out.
I don't know what's right.
I can understand and accept both positions.
He's pretty firm.
The situation isn't ideal,
but if we release as planned today,
we must set a distribution plan for the factory...
and direct-only stores with the SCM Team.
Yes.
I have to talk to Mr. Yoon.
Start the meeting without me.
I need to make a call.
Shall we go?
It tastes wrong?
(Planning Team Director Yeom Jang Goon)
Hello.
Have you heard, sir?
Of course they must go ahead. It's too big a loss.
If it were not just about a slight change in the taste...
but about cloudy beer or yeast floating about,
that would be scrapped for being a defect.
It's a shame.
Did I say something wrong?
No.
- You can go. - Yes, sir.
This is how far you should go.
If you continue on this path,
you'll only be ruining yourself.
I'll ruin myself?
We'll see who hits...
rock bottom first.
(Min Ju)
I thought about it again and you were right.
We're in charge of making it and we realized it tasted different.
We can't release it as is.
I get why you're angry.
So I persuaded the director as best I could,
but the company just can't allow delaying the release.
(Min Ju)
I'm sorry I'm not a good enough team leader.
(I thought about it again and you were right.)
(So I persuaded the director as best I could,)
(but the company just can't allow delaying the release.)
(I'm sorry I'm not a good enough team leader.)
I'm sorry.
(I'm sorry.)
What's the point in making excuses...
when I couldn't solve anything?
I wish he'd reply even if it were to be angry.
How long were you here for?
Have you been waiting since you left?
You should've called me...
I waited because I wanted to talk to you...
in person rather than send you a reply.
What about dinner?
You haven't eaten, have you?
Let's get something to eat first.
Why are your hands so cold?
Are you cold?
Is there anything you want to eat?
You couldn't eat while you waited for me.
I'll eat what you want.
- You like rice. - Not me.
You. What do you want to eat?
I'm okay with anything.
Are you really okay?
- Yes. - No.
We're releasing a first batch that doesn't taste right.
About that.
Are you okay with that?
We had no choice.
I thought only of myself.
Sorry for putting you on the spot.
It's okay to be angry...
Never mind.
You're okay if you say you are.
Yong Ju.
Look at me.
You know, I...
Sorry.
Hello, sir.
You reached the store?
Okay. Take care of everything for me.
Bye.
So I'm...
You should take it. It's work.
I'm sorry.
Hello?
Oh, yes, right. I'm sorry.
I left the office.
I'll email you as soon as possible.
Okay. I'm so sorry.
Bye.
Shall we go if you're done?
Shall we?
(Jisang Liquor's new product Together...)
(1st distribution marketing plan)
(E-mail has been sent.)
I've just sent the file. Please check it.
(SCM Manager Kang Su Jeong)
How about some beer?
I'm in.
Goodness.
- It hits the spot. - Right?
Who's this?
- May I have a beer too? - What?
Wait.
What's this?
Why do you look upset?
Did you cry?
No...
Who was it?
Who made you cry? Tell us the name at once.
Good grief.
I'd rather have him get mad at me.
Or blame me.
Why wouldn't he even tell me he's upset?
I can't get angry at her.
I could tell...
how upset Yong Ju was before I could feel my anger.
That is what upsets me more.
Can't we vent our anger out...
and be upset together?
Yong Ju being in pain...
because of me...
hurts me more.
Min Ju adjusts everything for me.
Even without telling him, Min Ju knows everything about me.
Why are your hands so cold?
Are you cold?
What I want to eat, what I need,
and what I want to hear. He feels everything.
At times, he knows me better than I do.
I don't know unless he tells me.
But Min Ju is fine with everything.
He's happy with anything.
I don't know how Min Ju is truly feeling.
You know, I...
Sorry.
Hello, sir.
Even though I want to open up to Yong Ju,
she has a lot to take care of at the moment.
I don't want to become another burden.
- Bye. - I only wish...
for one thing.
I'm sorry.
Hello?
All I need...
Oh, yes, right.
- is for you to give me a hug. - I'm sorry. I left the office.
- Why is everything so complicated? - Okay. I'm so sorry.
Shall we go if you're done?
Shall we?
Why is it so complicated?
And I mean everything.
(One week later)
Isn't this the beer CEO Yoon...
made recently? Together.
Yes. It has just been released.
The bottle is still hot.
Beer shouldn't be hot.
I'm just saying it's... What? Shall we drink it together?
Together!
- Together! - Together!
(Jisang Liquor)
(Jisang's Globalization)
Granny.
Today is the highly anticipated release date of Together.
But why am I not happy?
I hope there are no issues.
Right?
(Min Ju)
Look at her.
I knew it.
Both of you look terrible.
Your skin feels so rough. Goodness.
It's like you've got no strength.
Why must you make my heart break?
Who told you to look so pale?
- Aunties. - Yes.
My goodness. Really.
Let's go inside. Come now.
- Gosh. - My legs feel cold.
Are these all for me?
I'm touched.
No way. We're eating with you. It has three portions.
Do you think we don't have mouths?
Gosh, you're finally smiling.
- Are you feeling better now? - Yes.
- Here. Try some of this. - Thank you.
- This too. - Wait.
Dig in.
How's Min Ju been doing?
I've been too busy to get in touch.
- That's an excuse. - That's an excuse.
You're right.
I want us to fight over who is more upset like children,
clear up the misunderstanding,
and make peace.
But I've got so much on my plate.
I end up choosing the easiest way out.
And it's ignoring him.
Don't you think he knows you're ignoring him...
and waiting for you even though it's eating him?
Maybe?
It's not just eating him.
Min Ju is sick right now. He looks like a living corpse.
Is Min Ju sick? How bad is it?
He makes beer...
and doesn't sleep all day long.
That fool.
A few days ago,
he was found passed out on the brewery floor.
Min Ju passed out?
- What... Aunties. - Go.
- Go after you have one of these. - Right.
Good. You need energy to run.
- Thank you. - Don't mention it.
- Go ahead. - Chew, okay? Chew.
Why did you mention that? She needed to eat first.
Let's eat. We've done our job.
- This way. - Be careful.
- No, really. - This way.
Leave your body to me.
Why are you roaming around?
- You need rest. - But...
No. I...
Be careful. He might bump into the door.
- Relax. - Be careful.
- Slowly. - Come on.
I'm totally fine, okay?
Stop overdoing it.
I need to get the taste of the beer right.
Have you forgotten already?
You passed out from overworking a few days ago.
You totally did. And it freaked everyone out.
Why do you want to go back into the brewery?
- Lie down. - No, but...
- Lie down. - Lie down.
I think his fever went down.
Doesn't he have a slight fever?
I'm all right. Goodness.
All right, my foot. How are you all right?
You must work while getting some sleep.
Did you contact Ms. Chae?
Right. If you haven't, I'll do it.
That darn big company beer. They're working people to death.
No, don't you call her. Don't, okay?
She'll blame herself again if she knows I'm sick.
I don't want to hurt Yong Ju.
- Come now, leave. Both of you. - Okay.
- All right. Rest. - Can't we see you sleep?
- No. - Is that a no?
- Bye. - Let us see you go to...
- Fine. We're leaving. - Sleep, okay?
- We're leaving. - Get some sleep.
What...
- Let's go straight home. - Okay.
Bye.
Yong Ju...
Why do you look so pale?
And what's with your light clothes? Don't you get cold easily?
A lot has been stressing you out recently, right?
Don't worry. I can get the taste right.
I'm testing it right now.
The second supply will be fine.
I heard you passed out.
How unwell were you?
No, I'm fine. I'm all better now.
What about dinner? Did you have some?
You had something simple because you were busy, didn't you?
And even had coffee on an empty stomach.
I can totally tell.
But I won't know.
- What? - If you don't tell me,
I won't know.
Whether you're fine or not.
How you feel.
I don't know a thing.
What is this?
Is it fine as long as you get better?
Should I brush it off now that you're not sick anymore?
Am I to stay ignorant all the time?
Yong Ju.
This is nothing to me.
I didn't want to worry you.
I don't want to make you worry.
Can't you stop making me indebted to you?
I told you there was no owing each other in love.
How is that true?
Doesn't that mean we each need to love each other equally?
But we're not, are we?
You're already everything to me, Yong Ju.
That's what you think.
Remember what I told you?
I will...
only look at Yoon Min Ju who is before me.
That means...
even if you endured things alone in the past,
I want to be with you from now on.
I'm sincere about being together.
I know.
I want that too, you know?
But why do you always say you're okay?
Why do you not talk about your pain?
You feel my emotions before I do.
You care about my business more than me.
But why won't you let me do it?
I can't let you do it.
Why not?
I know how painful it is to feel...
the other person's emotions.
I can't possibly let you do that.
That hurts me more.
That breaks my heart more, okay?
If you're in pain because of me.
If you're sad because of me.
And when I feel those emotions,
it'll be the end of me.
I'll die, okay?
I'm serious.
Then...
what can I do with you?
What...
are you trying to tell me right now?
You know, don't you?
You felt it.
No, I don't.
I don't know.
We...
won't break up.
Instead, it's a truce.
Rather than having an emotional fight,
let's focus on what each of us must do.
Once we get our emotions sorted out,
let's see each other.
Okay.
We won't break up.
- I know, right? - Yes.
My goodness.
A truce?
What's wrong with him?
We need to get going now.
At this rate, it'll be impossible.
That Ju-Ju couple is so wild.
They get on my nerves.
What is it? You're scaring me!
Why are you doing something out of the ordinary?
Just go to your room on the second floor.
Meditate, will you?
Did he have breakfast?
- Gosh, how frustrating. - I know.
Stop scaring us.
How about fighting it out with me?
This doesn't suit you at all.
Is Mr. Yoon Min Ju doing well?
I don't know. He's weird.
All he does is run every day.
He's dying for the day the truce ends.
Oh Chan Hwi. Put the vinyl down.
Look at her adoring it because it's from Min Ju.
What's the use of a truce?
Remember we must prepare for Together's second supply next week?
You'll have to meet CEO Yoon then.
For the sake of us people stuck in the middle,
please unite...
as soon as possible.
Let's go, honey.
We should worry about us, not them.
What is it? Did something happen?
We're the ones with a big war ahead of us.
But I'm a pacifist.
We're leaving.
- Good luck. - Good luck.
Good luck to you too.
This won't make my mom happy.
Dad won't even step out.
You never know.
I might charm them to come out.
By the way, if your mom says,
"Have you saved some money?"
"It's absurd you don't even own a house."
What do I do?
Why are you worried about that?
I'm Bang Ah Reum. I earned financial freedom.
That's not something to worry about.
What I'm worried about is persuading my mom.
Why are you worried about that?
I'm Oh Chan Hwi.
The guy loved by everyone.
Why must we eat outside?
Please wait a bit. I'll bring Father outside.
Forget it.
He'll never leave the house.
Good grief.
Father!
- What's with you? - I'm Oh Chan Hwi.
- "Oh Chan..." - We're...
having brunch outside. Would you like to join us?
No, I'm good. I always eat alone.
Leave it over there.
No way.
Office workers...
wait outside my truck before it opens to eat my toast.
This is a golden opportunity.
- Doesn't it look amazing? - Well, shall I try a piece?
If you want to eat it, come out to the yard.
My gosh.
There's even beer.
Hey. Goodness.
Look at him.
Oh, my.
Really?
I heard there was beer.
Yes, we have cold beer.
To think I'd drink beer at home.
Nobody drinks with me.
Don't worry. I'll be your drinking buddy from now on.
- Father. - What?
Here. Have a glass.
- Father. - Yes?
Right.
That hits the spot!
Why is this split into two?
Gosh.
No, not that one. Eat this one.
Why can't I eat the piece of apple I want to?
She wants you to eat the biggest and prettiest piece.
This one's the prettiest. Right, Mother?
Acting like you know it all.
Do you think this will make me approve of your marriage?
You're totally mistaken.
I'm going back inside first.
- I enjoyed the meal. - Sure.
We're still here, you know!
You can't go back inside like that.
I think I won him over about 98 percent.
Right?
Let's just go through with it. My mom will never approve.
I can't allow that.
You shouldn't be treated this way.
All that matters is us.
I'm going to win their approval...
and have them bless our marriage.
I'm going to see your father walk you down the aisle,
bow down to your father,
and take your hand from his.
Have you heard that we should make sure...
our everyday items are pretty to look at?
Really? You like songs like this too?
What about now?
How did I ever function without Yoon Min Ju?
It's not him.
Hey, sir.
Is it finally tasting how it should?
What a relief!
Sure, I'll order them to be released right away.
Has CEO Yoon been there...
He never sticks around for a chit-chat.
Well, I should check the progress of Together.
I'm only going there...
since it's my responsibility as a project manager.
Of course.
It is inappropriate to break through enemy lines...
when we called a truce.
That is why I came bearing news.
You probably heard that Together was back to its original quality.
I worked many nights...
to bring you this news.
- What is this? - Isn't it obvious?
I just crossed the line.
Come on. I have something to say.
You prefer rice while I like bread,
so I will alternate when cooking breakfast.
You like scary movies while I can't stand them.
I prefer romance.
I'm sorry to say this,
but I won't go gun shooting with you again.
It was boring.
Also, don't stick to drinking beer only from your company...
and enjoy other brands with me from time to time.
There are so many types of beer in this world to...
And then... Wait, there's more.
Beer and...
I love you, Min Ju.
- What was that? - I said I loved you. Why?
Goodness.
(Beom: Read this!)
Have you tried the new beer from Jisang Liquor?
Does anyone else think it's inconsistent?
(Jisang Liquor's Together)
(Jisang Liquor's Together Has Quality Issues)
- What's this? - There's already an article on it.
Hold on.
Hello. Are you available for an interview?
- It'll be brief. - You haven't admitted anything yet.
- Over here. - Can you say a few words?
- Stop. - Where do you stand?
Could you say a few words?
Yes, this is Jisang Liquor.
- No, that news article... - Thank you.
- Yes, of course. - Absolutely.
Just a second.
Could you hold off on releasing the articles?
- Did you read the news article? - What do we do?
Reporters are calling nonstop.
We're doing our best to hold the articles,
but they're spreading like wildfire.
- First, - We'll call you back.
I have a meeting to attend.
What now?
You should've reported any problems we had!
You should've told me...
that there was an issue with the first batch of beer!
I'm sorry, sir. I was hoping to solve it on my end.
- Unbelievable. - The news must've reached...
the chairman by now.
This is exactly why...
I was against this project from the start.
Let's be honest. Every time we launch a new product,
our competitors slander us using the media...
saying that it's too cloudy and has sediments.
Besides, the product itself was of adequate quality.
The consumers are questioning the quality of the beer.
It tastes different from bottle to bottle,
and they're saying we've been deceiving the public.
First of all, we issued a rebuttal article...
to fight off any rumours...
that have been calling Together defective.
The problem though is that the articles...
are spreading too quickly online via social media.
I'm afraid it's already out of our hands.
Who did this? Who would do such a thing?
Judging by how fast the rumours spread online,
there's a good chance...
that this was set up by a vindictive someone...
who knew about our quality issue.
Find who it is.
Find out who's responsible. Whoever that is.
It was an inside job.
Some jerk either received a bribe from Baekmok Liquor...
or is in cahoots with them.
Finding who's responsible isn't the pressing matter.
Can't you see the mess the company is in?
Shut down the production of the new beer.
That's our best option.
If you don't, this will tank our company image.
Are you even hearing yourself?
This project cost a fortune!
This is one hectic weekend.
I knew something like this would happen.
Hold on.
Did you know what was going to happen?
Be honest, Mr. Kim.
He's a human lie detector.
What are you talking about?
I don't know anything.
I mean it.
That's a lie.
What would I know? I'm being wronged.
- That's a lie. - Why are you on my case...
when it's annoying enough that I had to come to work on a weekend?
I have nothing, absolutely nothing,
to do with what's going on.
Could you describe in detail...
what exactly is going on around here?
Yes, Baekmok.
The news articles will be taken care of on my end.
However, spreading rumours online is what you do best.
We have a deal.
What the...
That's all I know.
Ask Ms. Bang.
Director Yeom never gives me any important work.
He's telling the truth.
We appreciate your candour.
(Planning Team Director Yeom Jang Goon)
(Jisang Liquor)
How do you know his password?
It's the company's start date.
Because he doesn't trust others,
he writes important documents himself.
Since he never knows when he'll need them,
he always stores backup files.
I found it.
(Viral press release by Anon)
(Jisang Liquor's Together Has Quality Issues)
(Consumers complain about inconsistency with beer.)
(Experts question issues during production.)
How dare he mess with Together?
When the TF Team put in all that work?
There's a line one shouldn't cross.
Ms. Beautiful Bang,
I see you care greatly about Together.
The chairman must've heard the news by now.
If we can't explain this,
we will all lose our jobs.
Forget everything else...
and prioritize the search of this traitor.
Find out who it is, press charges,
and receive an apology...
stating that the article was released out of spite.
Only that can save our skin.
The traitor is right here.
It's Director Yeom.
Bang Ah Reum, what is the meaning of this?
I know you a lot better...
than you think.
You were the only one at this company...
that I was inspired to be like.
However, I'm afraid he's no longer around.
(Viral press release by Anon)
(Jisang Liquor's Together Has Quality Issues)
(Consumers complain about inconsistency with beer.)
I have been reporting back to Mr. Yeom of the Planning Team...
about the new beer being developed by the TF Team.
With the information I gave him,
he's been trying to sabotage its launch.
For having a negative impact...
on the company's future and its financial situation,
- I will gladly be punished. - Sir.
I was already aware of Ms. Bang's situation...
and gave her a strict warning.
Since then, she has been nothing but loyal...
to the team and the project.
I hear you.
Director Yeom, can I expect your letter of resignation?
Or should I deal with it in my own way?
This is all your fault!
This wouldn't have happened to me...
if the chairman hadn't brought you along.
Why must I leave this company? Why?
Sir.
Are you all right?
Yes.
I've always been the first to be at work and the last to leave.
While others drank their way to the top,
I climbed the ranks...
by planning the budget and analysing our strategies.
After all the work I did to be in this position?
Who is it?
How dare you enter this office?
(Planning Team Director Yeom Jang Goon)
I know...
how hard you had to work to sit in this office.
Your eyes say it all.
I also know how much you love Jisang Liquor.
- So why must I get fired? - Exactly.
- Who do you think is at fault? - That's...
We all want what's best for ourselves.
To be more successful than others.
We all desire to reach the top!
That's all I wanted as well.
So I worked day and night.
This is unfair.
Not everyone does the unthinkable...
just because they think they've been treated unfairly.
Take a look at where you ended up.
Is there a single person...
who understands why you did what you did?
Who's there beside you?
As if that's important.
There was a time when I thought like you.
I only cared about being satisfied in my own bubble...
and told myself I didn't need others, but...
I couldn't have been more wrong.
I needed at least one person...
to see me for who I am.
Do you know why?
Because that one person...
proves that I lived my life well,
and furthermore,
makes me be more of myself.
If you haven't even tried to find that one person,
apologize to yourself.
As if you know anything.
I didn't come here to patronize you...
or offer words of comfort.
I only came here because I knew I'd regret not saying this to you.
We will recall every bottle manufactured...
and offer refunds to consumers who have already bought any.
Mr. Yoon, in the meantime, you will prepare for its relaunch.
As for me, I'm off to deal...
with the scoundrel at Baekmok Liquor.
Those who spread false rumours and write malicious comments online...
should be taught a lesson.
Then...
All right.
Hold on.
Should any problems arise, call me instantly...
Ms. Chae, don't burden yourself with every task.
Yong Ju, let us carry the burden with you.
We're a team, aren't we?
Exactly. We're a united team.
What do you say? How about we wish us luck?
Sure.
What...
- We still can't get it right. - Just get moving.
Let's get it right the next time.
- Okay? - We should raise our hands, right?
We'll decide on that some other time.
- Go on. I wish you luck. - Good luck.
- I'll see you later. - I wish you luck.
- See you later. - I'll get going.
See you.
- Good luck. - Right.
I wish you luck too.
(Jisang Liquor)
- Want to join me for coffee? - I'm good.
Sir, a glass of soju seems to be in order.
Gosh, your shoulders. They couldn't be stiffer.
- This calls for a manual massage. - I hear you.
Would it kill him to join us?
Mr. Park.
The company chat room is blowing up.
The director of the Planning Team got the boot.
Sure, we should meet up right away.
I'm leaving the office as we speak.
Exactly. Talk about the unexpected.
I'll be right out.
Not a single person...
has called.
(Planning Team Director Yeom Jang Goon)
(Letter of Resignation)
Some things in this world can be messed with...
while some things in this world are sacred.
Together should've been off-limits from beginning to end.
That's right.
What you did was wrong.
(Brewing Love)
I know it was rough, Yong Ju.
You did great, Chae Yong Ju.
- Oh Chan Ran? - My name at birth.
Only my family remembers it.
It's about time you dealt with the closing of the Busan office.
You're coming too, right?
Absolutely not.
It's okay. Do whatever it is you want now.
Not being certain of something is also who you are.
And I even love the indecisive Chae Yong Ju.