(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
[This drama is a work of fiction.]
[Any resemblance to real persons,
places, or events is coincidental.]
[Scenes with child actors and animals
were filmed safely]
[under professional supervision.]
A well-known MeTuber has sparked controversy
by raising shocking allegations
involving actress Chu Sang Ah.
The MeTuber, identified as Mr. Choi,
claims that Chu Sang Ah was the true mastermind
behind the Oh Kwang Jae murder case,
a case that once sent shockwaves...
Good kindling makes for a nice, easy fire.
allegedly using Mr. Park,
the convicted perpetrator, as a front.
He also noted that
the prosecutor in charge at the time,
Bang Tae Seop, is now Chu Sang Ah's husband,
raising the possibility
that the case was covered up.
- If these allegations prove to be true,
- Cheers.
they could have major societal repercussions.
We will continue to bring you updates
as the investigation unfolds.
You
only looked at me as a celebrity
to exploit for your big plans.
Yeah. I know.
It's my fault for marrying a killer.
Damn it...
Hey! You okay?
Hey!
Are you okay?
Are you hurt anywhere?
[Chu Sang Ah, accused of killing Oh Kwang Jae]
Isn't she Chu Sang Ah?
Chu Sang Ah?
[Chu Sang Ah, accused of killing Oh Kwang Jae]
[Chu Sang Ah's two faces... what is the truth?]
No matter how many times you live it,
life betrays you at every turn.
Give me the money!
Hey, where did you hide the money?
Huh? Look at me.
Hey, hey!
Give me the money! Damn it.
You want another beating?
Give me the money! Money!
Money!
You little... damn it.
You crazy bitches, let go!
You...
You go make the money! Make the money!
You bring it in, you hear me?
Let go! I said let go!
Both of you... Damn it, get off!
Shit!
Mom.
What the hell!
I'll use this to pay the interest.
Just lend me another two grand, just this once.
I'll pay you back. Please.
Do you regret it?
If you could go back,
would you return to that moment?
Why would you even ask that?
Because it's a shame.
With all those people watching,
what were you thinking?
You really didn't care
if your life ended right there?
If I could turn back time...
I'd kill that bastard
before my mom dies.
Hey, mister.
Hey.
Boss! They're here!
Cops! Cops!
Grab those punks heading upstairs first!
Secure the evidence first.
- Evidence comes first.
- Yes, sir.
Hey...
Hwang Jeong Won?
Hey!
Hey! Stop right there!
Jeez, what the hell is that guy?
He ain't some goblin or something, is he?
Gosh.
You're here.
[Seong Hye Hair Salon]
Hey, what's wrong?
What the...
Oh my goodness!
Oh no.
What is that?
Oh my.
You guys showed up so suddenly this late,
I didn't have time to make much.
It's fine.
So she's someone you know, huh?
Right.
Hey, she looks rough. You sure she's okay?
She's fine.
Jeez, she's so thin... poor thing.
Want me to fry you an egg or something?
You don't feel like eating?
She's shaking...
Hey, don't be too hard on her.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Eat up.
You should eat up too.
I'm not taking you in.
So eat.
Back then, when I got your sentence reduced...
that was my way of apologizing
on behalf of the man
who did that to your mother,
and this filthy world.
I told you
to live a decent life
when you got out, didn't I?
But, seeing you like this?
Feels like a betrayal.
Drink.
Were you planning to use that pretty face
to play every man out there?
Let it go already.
Stop dragging your life down the gutter.
Hey.
Cut the bullshit.
Did you really think
someone who killed a man
was going to turn out any different?
If you let someone like that
back out into the world,
you should've seen this coming.
And...
What's so wrong with living dirty
in a dirty world?
Right?
You said you wanted to be an actress, right?
My wife once told me...
an actor lies to the audience,
lies to the world.
And in the end,
even lies to themselves to make it.
I'll give you a stage.
Want to work with me?
You're out of your mind.
Hello.
You're really going to
become an actress.
Making it through this as an actress,
reclaiming my spot
and standing tall in this industry,
that's what keeps me alive right now.
Do you understand?
Which means cutting ties with Lee Yang Mi
isn't something I can do!
One more step down this road,
and it's over between us.
Because of Oh Kwang Jae,
I was barely surviving...
You know that.
If he hadn't died, I would have!
This will never be over
until one of us is dead.
You've been living in hell too?
You have to be happy there, Mom.
You were always up there, smiling...
like you were looking down at the hell
I was living in.
Your name was Jeong Won, right?
Yes.
Got a cigarette?
What are you?
I'm asking
why you were there,
at that exact moment.
[Bang Tae Seop]
Now I get it.
[I asked if you found Chu Sang Ah]
I'll tell you everything now.
The number you have dialed is not available...
[So is the Changjo Party nomination over?]
[Is the news about Chu Sang Ah true?]
[Reporter Kim, Today Seoam]
[Chu Sang Ah in the middle of
Gangnam Boulevard]
[Real footage: Chu Sang Ah
in the middle of Gangnam Boulevard]
Isn't she Chu Sang Ah?
Chu Sang Ah?
That looks like Chu Sang Ah.
You really do know everything about me.
If you knew my past,
then you'd know
Bang Tae Seop wasn't the only one
who had people digging into me
and wiretapping me. Right?
So I don't trust anyone.
You don't need to feel sorry, either.
So what was it like?
Listening in on me. Watching me.
It bothered me.
But I still hoped you were doing okay.
My mom...
The day my mom died...
I saw you on TV,
crying with me.
I was grateful for that.
That's why I cared.
Why would Bang Tae Seop
send you of all people to me?
Everyone calls me a murderer.
Aren't you scared of me?
I pity you.
Do you know
why I'm sometimes afraid of Bang Tae Seop?
It's not because he's been following me.
It's because
he seems to know me better than I thought.
Ji Soo.
Sorry.
I'm sorry, Ji Soo.
A well-known MeTuber has sparked controversy
with shocking allegations
involving actress Chu Sang Ah.
The MeTuber claims that
Chu Sang Ah was the real mastermind
behind the Oh Kwang Jae murder,
allegedly using Mr. Park,
the convicted perpetrator, as a front.
He also noted that
the prosecutor in charge at the time,
Bang Tae Seop, is now Chu Sang Ah's husband,
raising the possibility
that the case was covered up.
This is reporter Kim Ji Hyun.
[Mr. Bang Tae Seop suspected of
covering up the Oh Kwang Jae murder case]
[Will this cast a shadow
over his political ambitions?]
It's all fabricated.
Fake news.
It's not so easy to just call it fake news.
This is a big risk for us.
You could
end up a suspect, a former prosecutor
under investigation.
That won't happen, sir.
For now,
let's wait for things to die down.
These days,
even the smallest flaw gets picked apart.
Take a breather,
- and look for the next opportunity...
- No.
I have to run this time.
I'll turn this around.
[WR Construction]
[Bang Tae Seop]
Sir.
Damn it.
Take it.
I said take it.
Hello?
The executive director has stepped out.
Then let him know I'm on my way over.
Today is
Chairman Kwon's birthday, so he is quite busy.
Oh, it's Chairman Kwon's birthday, right?
Then I'll see him there. Please let him know.
Come on. Why would you go there?
I've been saving something
for a day like today.
What?
Before I'm called in,
Chairman Kwon will be summoned first.
Why are you dragging my father into this?
It means the card
I've been sitting on for years,
waiting for the right moment to play...
is a joker.
I'm not going down alone.
I'll see you soon.
We still haven't found Park Jae Sang,
and we're trying to contain
the reports already out there.
But handling the advertisers
and clients seems more urgent for now.
Got it.
I'll call you back.
I should get going.
Thanks.
What are you going to do now?
I don't know.
I guess I'll start by stopping things
from getting any worse...
and just try to get through it.
You should wrap things up
with Bang Tae Seop too,
and find your own life.
And someday...
if you find your dream and become an actress,
I hope we meet again on the same project.
- Yeah?
- Sounds like...
there's a copy of Chu Sang Ah's recording.
Where are you right now?
I don't do this for money.
What drives me is
a sense of duty.
And what kind of duty is that?
People living in
this twisted, hellish world need somewhere
to vent their anger.
A witch hunt.
I just want to find the real witches
hiding among us,
put them on the stake,
expose what they really are,
and deliver justice.
[Director Lee Yang Mi]
Hello.
So what's our next move?
We'll reach out to Park Jae Sang
and release the copy of the recording
by tomorrow.
Okay.
Bang Tae Seop and Chu Sang Ah
going up in flames.
What a sight.
Make sure it turns into a full-blown wildfire.
Wrap it up cleanly.
Understood.
How's the chairman today?
Blood sugar is 252,
and his blood pressure is 170.
Oh, come on.
That old man needs to stay alive
a few more months
if we're going to get those papers sorted.
Gosh.
Oh, there she is, my princess!
Mom, my stress levels
are through the roof today.
Do I really have to put on a show
in front of Dad?
Oh, I see.
But you know your dad loves you
more than anything.
If you celebrate his birthday,
he'll be so happy.
Fine. I guess I have no choice.
So, what are we wearing today?
Since it's the chairman's birthday,
a very special occasion,
I prepared looks tailored
to each of your personal colors,
taking hair and makeup into account.
His blood pressure is 170 today.
Forget personal colors.
Do you really think
something this bold is appropriate?
Please, think about the goal here.
Exactly.
Right. I'll prepare new options right away.
Next. Director Cha.
For Hee Jin today, I pulled some references of
those trendy Hollywood star daughters
who've been winning people over lately,
aligned with our strategy.
What do you think of this cute concept?
Oh no,
not cute today.
Go with something that triggers
a protective instinct.
Yes, ma'am.
Hee Jin,
try what you practiced earlier.
Okay.
♪ I ran to you with the biggest smile ♪
♪ So happy to see you, Dad ♪
♪ But somehow you look a little down today ♪
♪ Did something happen ♪
♪ Is something weighing on your mind ♪
♪ Did things not go your way today ♪
♪ Dad, stay strong ♪
♪ I'm right here with you ♪
I love you, Dad.
Oh, my princess.
That was wonderful.
Oh, my girl is the reason I keep going.
Darn it.
Dragging in a five-year-old daughter
in a power play between the adults?
That's just low.
Maybe you should've treated
your wife a little better.
By the way,
you can't drop Bang Tae Seop, can you?
Yeah.
That's actually what I came to talk about.
What is it?
The Oh Kwang Jae case...
That was you, wasn't it?
Me?
After Bang Tae Seop messed up
the Nam Hye Hoon deal,
you got bitter and stirred this up
to screw them...
and me too,
didn't you?
Stop making things up
and worry about your own mess.
Just tell me the truth!
What is wrong with you?
Of all things, why would you blow that up?
You came in late as the second wife,
so you don't know my father's history, but...
If you mess with the Oh Kwang Jae case,
this whole family blows up!
What are you talking about?
My father was tied up in that case too.
Why would the chairman be involved?
Oh Kwang Jae got screwed over
by my father on that China deal, held a grudge,
and tried to blackmail him with it.
That's how it all went down.
What?
Then the one who killed him...
Bang Tae Seop's probably the only one
who knows for sure,
but doesn't it look like my father?
You're adorable.
What an idiot.
[Penalty for Contract Cancellation]
I'm so sorry.
I'll take care of it. I'm sorry.
[Guess she's been acting her whole life]
Once I added up the penalties
from the ads and the film,
it's just brutal.
I went around asking them
to give us a little more time,
but none of it's working.
You're looking for Park Jae Sang, right?
Yeah. I hired a private investigator,
and we're searching everywhere, but...
They say if he's in Seoam
without any phone records,
he's basically impossible to track.
Could take at least a month.
Even if Choi Ji Ho won't meet,
we have to stop the second broadcast,
no matter what.
I really want that too.
But he's being so hardline about it.
What are you going to do?
I'll find Park Jae Sang.
Sang Ah.
Is this the place?
- Hey, ma'am!
- Oh, sorry.
I told you not to do this here!
I'm sorry.
You're making a mess of the whole neighborhood.
How many times do I have to tell you?
I'm sick of saying it.
Customers are coming. Clean this up, now!
I will.
What is wrong with her? This is so stressful.
You don't look well.
Could this be your last birthday?
You think
I'm that easy to take down?
I'm not dying.
I brought something
I've been sitting on for a long time.
Proof that you're the real killer
in the Oh Kwang Jae case.
[Case Records in 2018]
[Criminal Case Records]
Not bad.
You've slipped through tighter nets before,
but this won't be so easy.
So you're going down with me?
As the prosecutor who twisted the truth?
Go ahead. Do it.
Fine by me.
I've got nothing left to lose anyway.
Where's the chairman right now?
He's over there.
- Is he resting?
- Yes.
Even if you get arrested,
you'll just post bail,
given your age and condition...
- What is he talking about?
- But the reputation WR built...
It'll be your legacy that gets stained.
And your daughter, Hee Jin...
she'll spend her life known as
a killer's daughter.
What do you want?
Those stories about me and Sang Ah...
They all started
with your wife, Director Lee Yang Mi.
Please handle it quickly at your level.
Then I'll destroy these documents
and bury it for good.
Call me when it's done. I'll be waiting.
Oh gosh.
Oh my, Chairman!
Get it together, please!
Useless...
Talk to you later.
Prosecutor Bang!
What is that smell?
Shit.
This is an emergency.
All personnel, move to the annex immediately.
Darn it.
Director.
Should we call 119?
Hey.
Are you insane?
You want to blast it everywhere
that the WR owner is dying?
Do you even think?
I'm sorry.
Chairman.
You know I've done everything I could for you,
right?
When you go...
Make sure Hee Jin's shares are
clearly secured in your will.
Yeah?
You...
Yes?
Whatever you're pulling,
shut it down.
Yeah,
I had no idea, you'd been working yourself
to the bone like that.
Director, is there anything I can help with?
I'm sorry.
We should bury the recording.
Yeah.
We're killing this project here.
Pull everything tied to
Park Jae Sang and Oh Kwang Jae.
And shelve the recording release.
Understood.
With the chairman involved,
it's too risky to keep pushing.
I'll reach out to Park Jae Sang
and put the project on hold.
And
bring me a Plan B.
Got it.
Damn it.
Mr. Park,
we're calling off the recording release.
What?
Are you kidding me right now?
Choi Ji Ho's not meeting Park Jae Sang today.
Looks like Lee Yang Mi pulled the plug.
They just shut down the recording,
and Park Jae Sang sounds pissed.
I'll stay on him.
Why are you doing this now?
It's complicated. Let's meet later and...
"Later?" When the hell is later?
You're the one who dragged me into this.
If you want out, you get out.
I'm not letting Chu Sang Ah go.
Hey, Mr. Park...
Don't do anything rash...
Hey!
Damn it.
The number you have dialed is not available.
Why isn't he picking up?
Leech.
What the...
Oh my,
such a sweet girl helping with this...
It's nothing.
Well...
You don't recognize me?
I feel like
I've seen you somewhere.
About Jae Sang... from before...
Then you're...
Chu Sang Ah?
I'm sorry.
I was just overwhelmed back then.
I never thought it would actually happen.
Just once...
Just forgive me, please.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't do this.
Please forgive me.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, ma'am. I didn't know back then.
I didn't know you can't just walk away
after ruining someone's life.
I'm sorry.
Please don't do this.
Please forgive me.
I'm so sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- Sang Ah.
It's been a while,
Park Jae Sang.
You were with Sang Ah last night, weren't you?
Why are you so on edge?
Let's end this.
I can't end it like this.
I'm going to expose everything.
You know,
if Chu Sang Ah goes down,
so does Prosecutor Bang.
I'll stop him,
even if I have to kill the bastard.
I'll take point on the tentpole.
Make it bold
and hit hard.