Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.xyz or dramacool.club
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Is there any way to help her?
Jet, are you with Master?
Ramphueng's messing with us.
There are 40 subjects of meditation.
But it takes time to master each one.
You came all the way here.
Is there a reason for your visit?
I need your help, Master.
Oh...
You're Pong, right?
Master...
What about breakfast?
I'm not hungry.
I feel like
I've been making him uncomfortable.
I think...
I won't bother Master anymore.
What are you doing?
Prim?
When did you get here?
Don't you have any tutorial classes?
For today, no.
Why are you here?
Did you miss me?
Come on.
My dad wanted to talk to Elder.
I'm just waiting for him.
Is Auntie's tape broken?
This is how you listen to music now.
But that's not my mom's tape.
Found it.
How did you know I like this song?
I just think it's such a beautiful song,
so I saved it.
♫Search your heart and tell me who,♫
♫Who can love you...♫
I miss Auntie.
♫Why keep your secrets?
Give me a clue♫
♫We're not strangers,
tell me what's true♫
Hey,
it's okay to cry sometimes.
Maybe it'll make the longing hurt less.
My grandpa told me that
to be a shaman who everyone relies on,
you can't let them see you cry.
But I'm not them.
Don't tell me that
once you become a shaman,
you'll hide your eyes
behind those glasses like Grand Master.
It's like he's trying to look cool.
I mean, his eyes
are just sensitive to sunlight.
Anyway,
shamans are human, too.
They can think and feel anything,
and expressing it
should be okay, right?
And when you're with me,
don't even try to look cool.
You need to smile like this.
We can get the tape fixed later.
I'll find you a place.
Okay.
♫Please, please save your tears♫
♫If your love's for him,
just erase me here♫
So you can check it out together
'cause you're all seniors now.
I just want it to look better,
you know...
I want this to be flawless.
The team leaders should be in...
Whoa.
Hello.
This is amazing.
They'll even perform a play.
Oh...
Hello, Master.
- Hello, guys.
- Hello.
Hi.
Thanks for giving us a ride.
No problem.
The students are setting up the scene,
so it'll be a while before we start.
Okay.
Then, please take me to them.
This way, please.
Right, Jet.
In the meantime, have your friends
ask the local spirits for permission.
They're outsiders.
Doing something wrong
could cause problems.
Okay.
This is where the massacre took place.
When they crushed
the Holy Man's Rebellion,
countless people were killed.
Whoa,
so they're doing it in the actual field?
The spirits here
were accused of being rebels
and then killed.
They called themselves the 'Holy Man,'
but...
the government of Siam
called them 'Phi Bun ghosts'
before they even became ones.
Oh, I just found out about that.
They don't really teach
this part of history, do they?
You can sense it, right?
Yeah.
It's nothing.
The students are just using the place
to tell the story of their ancestors.
We just need to ask for permission
and let the spirits know
we mean no harm.
Keep this in mind.
You're using their place.
When you're done,
make sure to clean it up
so they don't get bothered.
Good luck.
Alright, you can now dress up.
Since we have some time,
do you want a break?
There's a temple near here.
Come take a break with me there.
I'll be around here,
and you can help out the students.
Professor,
where should I display these paintings
from the fine art students?
Thought you wouldn't ask.
Come with me.
I gotta go now.
Master.
Well,
I just realized that
if there are spirits here,
will Ramphueng be able to control them?
And...
should I leave now?
She can't do anything.
What do you mean?
You'll see.
You're not feeling comfortable
right now, are you?
Yes.
Grand Master Sek's amulet...
Your wrist.
I'm only lending it to you.
Don't ever lose it.
Yes, Master.
Pang!
I told you to use the ladder!
- Are you okay?
- I'm sorry!
Are you alright?
- Whoa...
- Paran!
Is everyone okay?
You should ask yourself.
Let me see.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Please have his wound treated,
Professor.
We'll take care of things here.
It's okay. This is nothing.
Nothing, you say?
It can be infected.
Khem is right.
Let's get your wound treated.
Come on.
Gosh...
What can I do?
Oh, my...
Gosh!
Do you happen to have any photos of it?
I think I can help recreate that.
Thanks.
Thank you so much for saving me,
and I'm sorry
for calling you by your name.
It's totally okay.
We were friends
before I became a shaman.
Okay.
Well,
I wasn't comfortable around you at first
'cause I wasn't sure
if I was making you uncomfortable.
But you're still so kind to me, Paran.
You needed my help.
If that's what a shaman should do,
I'm willing to help.
I wasn't talking about today,
but us.
Found you!
You're actually here.
You could've just sent me a picture.
What? You said you needed it right away.
What is it, though?
Is it important?
Yeah, it's a speech
I wrote for my students.
Give it to me.
Thanks.
Okay.
Hi, Master.
I guess you got yourself hurt
instead of me.
Hey!
Watch your language.
He saved me.
Sorry.
I'll go help the kids, then.
Help them. Don't mess with them.
I know. I won't.
Anyway, please take care of my sister.
Pong just keeps joking around
like he always does.
He hasn't changed at all.
Neither have you, Prim.
Still getting physical like before.
Uh...
after this project,
I have something to talk to you about.
You'll end up sunburned all over.
Sorry?
Oh...
Nothing.
He literally offers help to everyone.
Instead of enjoying our time here,
he's now working on a painting.
Just let him.
Which color do you want to take?
Well...
Just take all of them.
Grab one or two each.
Let's see
if they're all still good, then,
- so we don't bring the bad ones.
- Yeah.
This one's dry.
Why did they bring the bad ones anyway?
But these are the primary colors,
so we can probably mix them.
Let me try.
Hey...
What are you doing?
My glasses are now messed up.
Whoa,
has anyone ever told you that
you look so good without your glasses?
Give me some more time.
You're so gorgeous
without your glasses.
Come on, Jin.
Jet!
I'm not gonna fall for it.
Let's just go.
They're waiting for us.
Jin again?
Jin who?
Jin Carrey?
We are here today
to remind ourselves of the injustice
that cost the lives of people
who fought for equality
through our play,
as we were born and grew up here,
in a place where the bloodshed
has long been buried beneath the land.
Khemjira...
So that is Ramphueng?
Thanks to all of you
for letting me have a fun time.
Master,
you're not gonna do anything?
Master!
How did you do that?
You didn't even cast any spells.
It wasn't me,
but them.
The holy men were once
people of great power.
Any spirit that disrespects them
shall face the consequences.
♫I shall vanquish them all,
the wicked kin♫
♫I shall now rise
to defeat all that's wicked within♫
We sincerely hope
that you will pass this story on.
The honor of the Holy Man
must not die along with them.
We wish you all the best.
Why are you smiling, Khem?
I wish everyone could see what I see.
The play...
must mean a lot to them.
They brought about changes,
but were erased.
To be remembered
must feel really good.
I may have failed this time,
but next time...
I won't let you get away.
Some water, Master.
Thanks.
Today's play was excellent, Prim.
I've already called the driver.
He should be coming soon.
If you have something to say,
just say it.
Consider me a friend.
I've got a question
that's been bothering me for some time.
Do I still have a chance
with you, Paran?
I know
that we're not as close as we were.
You've become a shaman, but I...
I've never stopped loving you.
Prim,
but we've always been friends.
I'm so silly.
I don't want to be this way, either.
I hope you really think this over
and see if you can give me a chance.
At least...
I hope you accept this.
Khem!
Is something wrong?
Uh...
Pong's taking me
to the temple fair tonight,
so I was gonna ask for your permission.
Just the two of you?
Jet and Charn are coming, too.
How are you gonna go?
Well...
Pong's gonna pick us up later.
If you're not okay with it,
you can let me know.
Just go if you want.
You didn't even need to ask me.
- I'm not your guardian.
- But you had so many questions.
You can tell me if you're not okay.
I'll listen to you anyway.
You guys are not kids anymore.
Just go if you want.
- Thank you.
- If anything goes wrong,
Pong will be the first one I blame
since he's the oldest.
Make sure he takes care of you.
Right...
Your amulet.
Don't take it off yet.
Return it to me after you come back.
Khem...
Don't stay out too late.
Come on, Pong.
I thought we'd get to ride
in a fancy car.
As kids of an MP and a village head,
if we drove a fancy car
to the temple fair,
people would think
we were trying to show off.
Well, I thought that was what
you were trying to do.
Come on, get in the car.
Wait, but Khem...
The passenger seat is yours.
Please check the maps for me.
Hey, don't bother him.
Leave it to me. I'm from here.
It's okay.
I'll take the seat.
You should be with Charn.
Could it be that
Khem is giving Pong a chance?
Stop that.
Abandon your ship now.
I'm not boarding that ship of yours.
Come on, just go.
So...
anything you want to try at the fair?
Maybe...
some buttered corn.
Buttered corn?
Ake, keep an eye on them,
and let Thong know what's going on.
- Yes, Master.
If they split up,
who should I keep an eye on?
We've taken a break from this
for too long, huh?
Yummy buttered corn right here!
Jeez, if they're this slow,
it'll get dark before we get it.
Hey!
Let's play the balloon dart game!
Twenty baht for three darts.
Twenty for three?
I wanna try that, too.
Throw it.
- Oh...
- Jeez, Charn!
Let Khem try it.
- I don't know how.
- Come on, give it a shot.
Just throw it. They're all the same.
- Whoa!
- Hey, do you even have any strength?
That was close, Jet!
It's okay.
Wanna get more darts?
How many?
- What about a single one?
- When did you get here?
Let's get some popsicles over there.
Whoa, this boy is too good at this.
Whoa,
they've got nice clothes here.
The length is just perfect.
One set of spring rolls, please.
Here.
Hello to all the fans of
Morlam Sing: the Sounds of Isaan!
Yes, morlam!
Come on, guys.
Let's go dance by the stage.
I'll pass, Jet.
- What?
- I don't like crowds.
I'll pass, too.
Dancing with you is too risky.
You come with me, then.
Hold on, Jet!
I'm introverted.
That's not true.
If you were, you wouldn't be here.
Come on now.
Wait, Pong...
What did you mean by risky?
Why is dancing with him risky?
What should we do, then?
Looks like everyone came as couples.
Yeah, so did we.
We're two individuals, Pong.
I'm not with him.
I don't know him.
We're strangers.
No, I don't know him at all.
Jettana... Wait, no.
I don't know his name.
I really don't know him.
Life is short, man.
Just enjoy it while you can.
Don't blame me
for not telling you, then.
Come on.
Come on, dance.
Like this. Here.
Just kick.
♫Don't know
what kind of spell you cast,♫
♫But it makes my heart beat so fast,♫
♫Losing myself whenever you walk past♫
♫Is this the love
that will forever last?♫
♫Is this love?♫
♫Is this the love
that will forever last?♫
Pong's so scared of ghosts
that he's holding Khem's arm tight.
That's enough.
You're supposed to watch out for danger.
I don't care about this stuff.
Yet you're all ears, Master.
Khem!
Khem, you're okay, right?
We're outside now.
No need to be scared anymore.
Are you shocked?
Khem,
don't be scared, okay?
Pong!
Pong...
Wait...
Oh...
Sorry.
You...
You're not scared of ghosts?
Well...
The ones I've experienced
were way scarier.
Oh...
The haunted houses in Bangkok
must be really well done, right?
Yeah.
Jet and Charn are probably dancing.
Should we find a place to wind down?
Up there.
Uh...
Actually, just strolling around here
feels alright.
Are you tired, though?
- Should we go over there?
- Hey.
Actually,
I have something to tell you,
and I think up there
would be a great place to do it.
Let's go before the line gets long.
Uh...
I mean...
Pong,
I...
Well,
what you want to tell me...
I just think...
it's best if you keep it to yourself.
Oh...
I see.
Already got a no, huh?
We haven't reached paradise yet.
I'm...
sorry for disappointing you,
but I really see you
as a kind older brother.
And right now,
I'm actually going through a lot.
- Also...
- Is that actually the reason,
or is your heart already taken?
So refreshing.
Haven't danced in a while.
I'm surprised you haven't.
By the way, where's Khem?
He's with Pong.
I know who he's with,
but where are they?
I've got a weird feeling
that something might happen.
What could it be?
Ramphueng was just dealt with
this morning.
Forget it. It's okay.
It's none of my business, is it?
Uh...
You yelled so loudly just now.
Your throat must be sore.
How about...
we go get some drinks from that stall?
Come on.
Hey, hey!
Aw, man.
- Kla?
- Hey,
thought it was someone else.
Turns out it's my buddy, Pong.
- Aw, buddy!
Hey, bro.
You're on a date?
I'm busy.
Excuse us.
Hey!
- Come on.
- What's the rush?
What's the hurry, man?
You're enjoying yourself now.
Are you all set and ready to fight me?
- Aw!
- Are you? We're so ready to fight.
I think...
you should save the talking
for the ring.
I'm not interested
in talking to a loudmouth.
I may be a loudmouth,
but I sure can bust
that mouth of yours.
- He can get your mouth busted!
You brave enough?
- You ready?
- Uh...
It might be better if we split up.
Staying here could bother everyone.
Bother everyone?
Everyone who?
Are you a life coach or something?
You think you can boss me around?
I asked if you're a life coach.
What's your problem?
Hey, hey!
- Run!
- You bastard!
Get them now!
Jet, run!
Jet, Charn, come on.
Now!
Hey,
are you the MP's son?
I see.
You're with them, huh?
Oh!
Hi, Kla.
It's been a while, huh?
Get ready to run.
This is Kla,
- Pong's rival...
- You'd better hurry, Jet.
Your buddy's gone.
Gosh...
You're so fast
now that you trust your gut.
See you, man.
Hey!
Turn into wasps!
Hey,
what did you do to them?
They messed with me,
and even with Khem,
so I gave him a punch.
Fuck!
Khem,
are you alright?
Come on, it was nothing.
You guys were too impatient.
Forget it.
They've probably stopped.
They haven't.
Here they are.
What is that?
Phayon.
It's black magic.
Only the intended targets can see it.
Master,
Ake told me
something serious has come up.
Pong,
you still got your Zippo with you?
Clear the way for everyone.
Guys, just go with Pong.
What about you?
Don't worry about me.
My magic is the most powerful here.
Pong,
there's no time.
- Do it now.
- Jet!
- Jet...
Come!
That's sick, boss!
Why did nothing happen?
Hey!
Why didn't you go with them?
Jeez, the MP's son is running away.
- Get him!
- Goddammit.
- Stop now!
Hey!
Hey,
this time, you'll be bedridden
and never get to fight again.
Argh!
Take a look. Are they here?
- I'll make sure to beat them up good.
- You're around here?
- Check under the cars.
- You'd better hide well,
- Come on, hurry.
- or I won't let you go.
- Where are you?
- Stop rushing me.
Just find them!
You should hurry up!
Where the fuck are they?
Hey, where are you?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Master's Lek Lai!
You were almost doomed!
I already checked here.
Are you okay?
Were you stung anywhere?
Oh, no.
I'm alright.
Jet, they're gone.
Wait, you're also here?
Don't worry.
Master's magic is protecting everyone.
I'll be back for this.
- Khem!
- Pong...
- Pong!
Are you okay?
I'm fine,
but Pong's not.
- Pong!
- Hey!
Let's take him to Master
and have the spell removed.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
The spell is already removed.
He just needs time to recover.
So...
you keep an eye on him tonight, then.
Charn and I will sleep somewhere else.
But...
All of us won't fit in here.
Let's go.
Uh...
I actually bought you some spring rolls.
I even got the vegetarian ones,
but I came back too late,
so...
they're all soggy now.
I'll eat them.
Put them on a plate for me.
Okay.
What's wrong with you?
Uh...
I'm not used to
sharing a room with someone.
That's nonsense.
We've been sharing a room
this whole time.
Well...
But this is just us.
Uh... I mean...
Nothing. I mean nothing.
Just say it.
What are you hiding from me?
I'm hiding nothing.
Lately, you've been acting damn strange.
Does it...
have something to do with Jin?
You keep saying that name in your sleep.
Anyway,
who's Jin?
Your lover?
Are you jealous of me?
Don't try to change the topic.
Tell me all of it.
It's ready, Master.
Reach your hand out and catch it.
So this is...
what saved me, right?
Thank you, Master.
What's that?
What, Master?
On your back.
How did you get that wound?
Uh...
Well...
Someone threw a rock at me.
Nothing serious.
Let me see it.
Oh, my God!
So...
we were Khem's best friends
in our past lives,
and we even dated without Khem knowing.
What a typical drama plot.
What are you so worried about?
We're not dating now.
- Worried I'll sleep with you?
- I'm worried about myself.
I'm worried
I won't be able to control it.
I'm not even sure if...
these feelings are from my past life
or this one.
This one?
- Do you...
- I'm sorry.
I can't figure it out myself,
unlike Khem.
If you feel uncomfortable,
I can go meditate outside.
Don't assume things.
Who said I was uncomfortable?
What did you just say?
Well,
I don't really know what I'm feeling,
but you've been helping me.
But I also cursed at you.
But you're still nice to me.
You even mess with me sometimes,
but maybe I started it.
Shit, what did I just say?
I'm sorry.
How was it?
How was...
How was what?
Jeez,
do I have to say everything?
What I did...
Did you like it?
I don't know!
It was too fast.
I want to try it again
to make sure my hypothesis is right.
Is it better this way?
We'll see.
Jet...
Is it this bad?
Master!
Master...
Turn around.
Uh...
It's okay.
I can do it myself.
Turn around.
Uh...
Are you mad, Master?
I am.
I'm sorry.
Not at you.
But at Pong
for taking you
and not keeping you safe.
I'm mad at those who did this to you.
And I'm mad at myself.
What do you mean, Master?
You came to me for help
and are staying under my roof.
That makes you mine now.
I've helped you many times,
not for someone to hurt you like this.
Master...
♫Dear today's breeze, drifting by,♫
♫Dear tonight's moon in the sky,♫
♫Please hear my plea, my tender cry,♫
♫Let me stay forever by your side,♫
♫Through endless time,
may our love never die♫
Hi, guys.
Master, Prim's here.
Are you ready to give me an answer?
I...
Master,
if you lose him,
you'll regret it.
Stop it, Charn.
We're not by ourselves.
Let's just talk about this later.
My face's up here.
In fact, both Jet and Charn
have been bound to you
since your past life.
Perhaps...
it's time for us
to recall our previous lives.
♫No matter how long time's passed,
you still have me♫
♫Through storms and stars,
together we shall be♫
♫Even if nightmares come,
we shall make them flee♫
♫With our hearts aligned,
we'll win gracefully♫
♫You still have me,
we're destined for eternity♫
♫Through storms and stars,
together we shall be♫
♫Even if nightmares come,
we shall make them flee♫
♫With our hearts aligned,
we'll win triumphantly♫