All this?
Can I really take whatever I like?
Of course.
Knowing these were part of
Kuji Yoshiharu-san's collection,
I just want to take them all.
Don't be ridiculous.
Ever since I was in college,
Kuji-san has always looked after me.
The reason I joined the
publishing house in the first place
was because I was
determined to work with him.
Nice, oden!
Go wash your hands.
Alright.
Hey, what's this?
Your mom sent it to me.
Whoa.
Two grown men, how are we
supposed to finish a box this big?
Still, I'm grateful.
Yeah.
She's always been like this.
I understand she wants
to show her appreciation,
but if she just thought
about it for a second,
she'd realize it's
actually a bit of a burden.
Ah...
This will probably keep
happening, won't it?
No.
Maybe the problem is that I've
never addressed this disconnect.
I get it.
When I lived with my father,
I was constantly frustrated too.
Your father was like that too?
Yeah.
I'd often vent to Sawada-san and
Mikami-san, our housekeeper,
in the kitchen.
Oh, you had a housekeeper?
Yeah.
After my mother passed away.
Ah.
I just remembered Mikami-san loves apples.
Can I take a few for her?
Of course.
It's hard to find an excuse
to see her otherwise.
You're a lifesaver.
Delicious.
"Life In Smokey Blue"
(Episode 6: Learning to Let Go)
Those apples look so good.
I'm so happy.
I'm sorry to have made
you come all this way.
Not at all, I insisted on coming.
How have you been?
Can't complain, I'm getting by.
Here you go.
Thank you.
This is good.
I haven't seen you at the
Komaba supermarket lately.
I was wondering if something happened.
The Komaba supermarket?
Didn't they switch to
self-checkout last year?
I'm not very good with those.
Ah...
The self-checkout machines.
By the way, Minoru-san is
finally coming back to Japan, right?
The last time he was here,
he stopped by my place.
Eno-chan has grown so much.
She has.
Minoru-san is going to be
living in this house now, right?
So, where will Kuji-san be moving to?
I'm still looking.
I used to stew apples often too.
And banana cake.
You and Minoru-san both loved it.
Oh, right.
I found this while
cleaning up the other day.
I really wanted to show you.
Banana cake.
I really loved that back then.
So,
Azuma-kun,
why did you translate the
protagonist as 'Mr. Rabbit'
instead of just 'Rabbit'?
Uh...
I just felt
it sounded a bit more whimsical.
Whimsical?
Yes.
Hmm...
Whimsical, huh...
I hadn't thought of it that way,
but 'Mr. Rabbit'
does have that Aesop's Fables feel to it.
I see.
Wait?
You took a highway bus
all the way from Sendai?!
Yes.
And then another hour
drive from Sendai Station.
That must have been exhausting.
Hara-san,
what made you decide to
start studying at this school?
When I was younger, I studied
hard to become a translator,
but I gave it up when I
got married and pregnant.
Though I ended up getting divorced anyway.
I see.
I worked myself to the
bone raising my child alone,
but once they were grown and independent,
a thought suddenly struck me.
I felt envious of friends who
had achieved their dreams,
like I was the only one left behind.
That's how it felt.
Ah.
I understand.
So at fifty, I decided
to give it another shot.
It was mostly just a whim,
but sometimes a whim is all you need.
That's true.
I'm home.
What are you cooking? It smells great.
Candied apples and sweet potatoes.
Mikami-san taught me how to make it.
Here.
It's hot!
It's good.
How's the house hunt going?
Eh.
It's going.
When you said you were moving in,
didn't I tell you?
I'm moving out.
This house was inherited by my brother.
I know, I know...
Is that homework for
your translation school?
Yeah, I'm stuck on this part.
Hey, can I take a look?
Right here.
I'm debating whether to
just use the word 'Lemmings'
or translate it as 'Tabinezumi'.
Why not just use 'Lemmings'?
It's fine I guess,
but considering the target
age group for this book,
I'm worried it might be
too hard to understand.
Ah.
I see.
You have to think
about things like that too?
Yeah.
Doing homework at my age.
I never thought that at this age,
I'd be chasing a dream.
I think that's amazing.
Huh?
It really is.
I've always admired how
straightforward you are, Azuma-kun.
Ah, Tajimi-san.
Aren't you going to eat something?
Ah...
Ah... You're right. I'll
go pick something up.
Yeah.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
It's about to give out.
The damage is pretty severe.
Yeah.
The floor around here
doesn't look too good either.
Oh?
An old dictionary.
That's the English-Japanese
dictionary my father used.
Oh.
It has a lot of character.
Yeah, it really does.
Is this going to get recycled?
Huh? Why?
It's so old, you're not
going to use it anyway.
Can I have it then?
I don't mind.
Great.
Minoru-senpai, where to next?
Ah, could you take the
desk on the second floor?
Got it.
- It's heavy.
- No problem, leave it to me.
What an impressive human chain.
As expected.
It's better to get it all done at once.
That way, you don't get too sentimental.
I guess so...
- See you.
- Thanks, good work today.
I'm glad we finished before dark.
Yeah.
I'm heading back to the hotel.
Mikami-san.
I heard you were back,
and I just had to see you.
- Please, come in.
- No, that's alright.
I'll just drop this off and be on my way.
It's banana cake.
Thank you so much.
- Is something wrong?
- Oh, I'm sorry.
Seeing the two of you together like this,
it just makes me so happy.
Yeah.
Mikami-san probably didn't
expect us to wolf it down like that.
True.
So good.
Ah.
Delicious.
Hey, do you remember?
The first time Mikami-san
made us banana bread?
She put raisins in it.
I really can't stand raisins.
But I was just a kid then,
so I couldn't tell her to her face.
And then,
you secretly
ate all the raisins out of my portion.
Yeah, that happened.
Later, you even politely told Mikami-san
that we weren't really fans of raisins.
I remember thinking back then,
my brother is so mature.
I really looked up to you.
You're exaggerating.
There was that one time,
we asked Mikami-san for the recipe
and we made the banana
bread together, right?
Ah.
Yeah, that's right.
Back then,
I even took some to my father.
But,
he wouldn't even look at it,
just said he doesn't eat sweets.
I see...
Even though I knew
exactly what he was like,
I kept hoping for something different,
only to be disappointed again.
But,
that junior who came by today,
he was so happy to finally
pay off his student loans.
As for me,
I never had to go through that struggle.
I sailed through my student years.
I'm grateful to him just for that.
And I truly respect him for his work.
I've resented him,
and I've even hated him.
But...
I'm also grateful to him.
Shizuka.
I'm going to build a great house.
Yeah.
Is there anything you hate to eat?
Raisins.
If it's raisins,
I won't use them.
So you really hate raisins, huh?
Yeah.
I really do.
Even though I'd forgotten about it.
What the hell...
Ah.
You kept the sofa.
I figured I'd keep it a while longer.
It was expensive, after all.
And it's Chippendale style.
Wait.
For real?
- Just kidding.
- You jerk.
I just had a dream.
A dream?
What kind of dream?
The people who used to be busy
in the kitchen of this house.
My mother,
and Mikami-san.
This house,
was built by my grandfather's generation.
Through constant renovations and care,
it's been passed down
for three generations.
Your mom and grandma,
Mikami-san,
you and your brother.
Thinking that I, too,
once stood in this kitchen,
and was part of this house's history,
I feel honored.
Yesterday,
I signed a lease for a new apartment.
Yeah, me too.
I found one in Nakano...
This house is going to be torn down.
They're going to build a new one.
Huh?
My brother is building a new house.
Torn down?
This house?
Yeah.
Why?
Didn't your brother say
he was going to live here?
I never heard anything
about tearing it down.
It's already been decided.
It's time to say goodbye to this house.
You've done well.
Huh?
Isn't today the day you're moving?
Didn't you take the day off?
I don't have much to pack.
Wow, that's a surprise.
Your apartment was always
packed with stuff back in college.
True.
You two,
you were seniors and
juniors in college, right?
Yeah.
Though that was almost 20 years ago.
It's hard to imagine
that you two were once college students.
It feels like yesterday to me, too,
but at the same time, it
feels like a hundred years ago.
Before I knew it, I was an adult.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Even though we're adults now,
it feels like we're just pretending to be.
Back to that house.
Today is the last time.
Look at you, you're
too old to be this drunk.
Get up, we're going home.
What a pain.
Huh?
It's too much trouble to stand up and walk.
Yeah.
Give me a piggyback ride.
Just so you know,
you're not cute at all like this.
Alright, hop on. Heave-ho.
Amazing.
I'm getting a
piggyback ride from Kuji.
Quiet down, you drunkard.
Shut up.
Kuji.
You know,
I really love that house.
It's old,
beautiful,
freezing in the winter,
but the garden is beautiful in the spring.
It's boiling in the summer,
and the garden grows like a jungle.
Yeah.
In your hair,
I can smell the scent of your house.
And the smell of an old man.
Shut up.
You're the same way.
One day, this old man will
become an even older man.
Kuji.
I thought
you'd live in that house forever.
Become an old man,
in that house you're so used to,
eating in that kitchen,
looking out at the garden,
and finally passing away
peacefully on that veranda.
That's what I always thought...
Don't decide where I'm going to die.
Kuji.
You've worked so hard.
For your family,
for this house.
You've really done your best.
You're amazing.
You've done well.
Kuji.
That house,
it really suits you.
It really does.
Is that so?
I wish that were true.
It rained the next day.
Hungover,
I stumbled out the door.
I heard that after that,
Kuji stayed in that house for another week.
(Next Episode)
Since Tajimi-san is in the hospital,
I bought something for the first time.
I wanted to give it to Tajimi-san.
That was actually
a white lie.
In reality,
I just wanted to make myself feel better.