(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
♪Wandering alone♪
♪Walking far by dusk-lit streets♪
♪Your eyes are as cold as clouds♪
♪Faintly coming into view♪
♪The city lights♪
♪Lit up that single moment♪
♪I can't hide or stop missing you♪
♪I can't forget those moments♪
♪Losing you♪
♪Like the seasons in my memory♪
♪Without winter♪
♪Walking down the long, dark street♪
♪Snow will never fall again♪
♪Our old story was torn♪
♪Into scattered pieces♪
♪Replaying every single scene♪
♪After you left♪
♪As if our documentary♪
♪Lost winter♪
♪The breeze speaks of good times♪
♪Pure white devotion♪
♪Send out a letter♪
♪Carrying my longing♪
=The Double Game=
=Episode 5=
♪This door♪
♪Lets in the sky outside♪
Zhi'er,
Tingyu's still waiting at home.
♪Than how you just greeted me♪
♪I know now♪
♪What the chill in my body means♪
Lu Tingyu
could be with some influencer now.
♪My heart still beats so naively♪
They can be unfaithful,
but that doesn't mean
we have to cross the line.
♪A joy that needs no brave pretense♪
What I hate most is
the mistress and the cheater.
♪Maybe you just passed by♪
♪The tears in my eyes♪
♪You looked like you had nothing to say♪
You act so aloof.
♪Then got so good at being cold♪
♪That's why a smile feels so precious♪
♪Maybe you just passed by♪
♪The tears burned into my heart♪
♪Let's say silence was just for show♪
♪Even if I've grown another year♪
(What is this guy trying to do?)
(So fickle.)
(Is he testing me)
(or...)
Sis.
Sis, something's wrong.
Keep it down.
You want Jianchuan to find out
what trouble you cause?
You just got 50 million in funding.
I even covered it from my private fund.
Xu Wangzu,
how many messes have I cleaned up?
This time, it's not just me.
It's both of us.
About the Lianxin Island funding,
a big overseas investor pulled out.
Some small investors heard
and started pulling out.
They pulled their money.
Why are you panicking?
How can I not panic?
Lu Tingxiao just killed my sweet deal.
If the funding goes wrong too,
do you think we can go back there?
Sis,
you must save me.
Calm down.
It's not the end of the world.
Pulling funding happens all the time.
Besides, this isn't on us.
Actually,
this could be our chance.
Our chance?
Do you have a plan?
I'll invite the execs over.
Right now,
go tip off those small investors
and let them make a real scene.
Isn't Lu Tingxiao so capable?
Isn't he all fired up in his new role?
Then I'll send this mess his way
and make the fire burn even hotter.
Let's see how the new CEO fixes it.
Things are lively today.
Don't forget why you're here.
Call Mr. Lu out here.
He owes us an answer today.
What brings you all here?
Ms. Xu,
we heard
that the Lianxin Island project
was a scam.
Even Xiao Ting pulled overseas funds.
Not a cent of our money
can be missing, right?
Pay it back with interest today.
If you don't,
we're not leaving today.
Is that what's going on?
Too bad.
I no longer handle financing.
The new CEO is in charge now.
Tingxiao,
why don't you explain it?
You?
You still owe me
for hitting me last time.
Perfect timing.
Let's settle old and new scores today.
Return our investment money
with interest.
- Yeah.
- Return it.
Return it.
What's all this noise?
- Chairman Lu.
What's going on here?
This is the Lu residence.
Who said you could cause trouble here?
Chairman Lu,
we're not here to cause trouble.
But you should know
the project is tied to a scam.
You're leaving us investors no way out.
Today,
you have to pay
the money back.
- Pay us back!
- Now, hurry!
Everyone,
let me make it clear.
The Lianxin Island project is lawful.
The so-called fraud
is pure nonsense.
Even Xiao Ting, an expert abroad,
no longer trusts you.
Stop fooling us.
Today, if Luzhou Group
can't give us an answer,
we'll take legal action.
Dad,
I'll handle this.
Tingxiao,
what will you do?
Please stay calm.
Just now, I contacted
Mr. Xiao Ting for Luzhou Group.
He sent me a reply email.
Mr. Xiao Ting said
someone misused the funds,
so he's lost confidence in us.
Mr. Xiao Ting also said
that if he sees our sincerity,
he'll keep investing.
Dad, look.
I hereby announce
that from now on,
Xu Shulin
and Xu Wangzu
are removed from all roles
at Luzhou Group.
All related businesses,
including the Lianxin Island project,
will be handed to the CEO
of Luzhou Group,
Lu Tingxiao.
Jianchuan.
Everyone, please leave.
As CEO of Luzhou Group, I promise
I'll give you a fair answer.
Mom.
What?
We can't leave without money.
Know when to stop.
Let's go.
Bai,
how did you get involved
in the fundraising scheme?
Someone asked me
to handle investments.
Who's the boss behind it?
Don't ask.
It's for your good.
Okay.
How did you get mixed up
with Fei Yifan?
We invested together,
so we got to know each other.
Last time, I checked his pool hall.
I later found out
those honey traps
were all set up by his partner,
not his idea.
That kid
has a bit of a temper,
but he's not a bad guy.
The pool hall folded. Money ran out.
So, he came to recover his funds.
I'll verify it.
If it's true,
I'll clear his name.
Of all the kids from our orphanage,
you are the most stubborn.
Still,
why are you here?
It's a long story.
In short,
I'm undercover.
This is complicated.
Be careful.
Get out ASAP.
Where's Lin Zhi'er? Where did she go?
I'm right here.
Mom's about to faint. Get her meds.
Okay.
Has Fei Yifan been giving you trouble?
Fei Yifan?
(Why does she seem so different?)
(What on earth is going on?)
(Am I seeing things?)
(Lu Tingyu's wife, Lin Zhi'er)
You're finally back.
No, you're the one who's back.
Lin Zhi'er,
why did you fake your disappearance?
And why use me?
You must've felt
how I've lived here
all these years.
Just a decoration.
A punching bag.
A pathetic tool
to keep the two families tied.
As for why I used you,
isn't the answer obvious?
We look exactly alike.
This was my chance to break free
from the cage.
You knew about me long ago?
I saw you once by chance.
I thought it was uncanny,
so I started following you.
I saw you walk into a cafe,
and I sneaked in after you.
Then I saw your work page,
your case notes,
and your work dashboard.
Then I realized
the girl who looked like me
was actually that capable.
You hired me in secret to look
into the fundraising scheme,
led me to that hotel,
and drew me in step by step?
And I know you're digging it
and you're capable of that.
Don't worry.
I wasn't trying to hurt you.
Oh, my God.
We really look exactly alike.
This is insane.
Do you think we could be
like those long-lost sisters
from TV dramas?
What?
Seeing that we look alike,
you want my family fortune now?
No way.
Relax. I'm not interested.
I just think
the fundraising scheme
is about to wrap up.
There's no reason for me to stay.
The fundraising is just a cover.
What's underneath is what matters.
I've been in both families.
I know exactly
what those two dads are like.
The fundraising scheme
must have something bigger behind it.
I hope you won't stop.
Don't you like exposing the dark side?
If there's a hidden secret
behind the project,
I will dig
into it to the end.
Then I'll need you
to stay here
and be me.
(So, she wasn't Lin Zhi'er.)
I'll head off now.
Wen Yan,
thank you.
This is my private encrypted email.
Contact me if you need me.
Take care.
You too.
(Wen Yan...)
(This is getting more interesting.)
Lin Zhi'er, what are you doing?
Come down.
Coming.
♪This door♪
♪Lets in the sky outside♪
♪With a voice even lighter♪
♪Than how you just greeted me♪
♪I know now♪
♪What the chill in my body means♪
♪The moment salt hits the wound♪
♪My heart still beats so naively♪
♪To complete♪
♪A joy that needs no brave pretense♪
♪How cruel sincerity can be♪
♪Like a door with no key♪
♪Maybe you just passed by♪
♪The tears in my eyes♪
♪You looked like you had nothing to say♪
♪Then got so good at being cold♪
♪That's why a smile feels so precious♪
♪Maybe you just passed by♪
♪The tears burned into my heart♪
♪Let's say silence was just for show♪
♪Even if I've grown another year♪