Previously on Seducing Drake Palma.
Would you look at that?
Drake’s your tutor.
You’re really meant to be!
By the way,
don’t you dare seduce Drake.
Excuse me,
why would I have to
seduce Drake Palma?
He’s my boyfriend!
Wow!
I already told
Uncle Steve we’re going!
I told him we’re having lunch with them
because of our group project!
Ouch! Let me do it!
He’s my partner for the
acquaintance party.
Show us.
No, as in I won’t
go to that party!
What if we go together?
Am I not dreaming?
Is Drake Palma really
in front of me?
Follow me.
Am I seeing things?
It is Drake!
Aww...
He looks good in his outfit.
His handsome look
makes me weak.
Are you okay?
What’s wrong with you?
Should I talk to him?
What made you change your mind?
Aya, tell Alys that Drake
might be running late.
Oh, Uncle!
It’s totally fine.
Just let him be so
there’ll be romantic entrance.
Alys thinks she
doesn’t have a date.
But surprise—she does!
Aya, you know everything!
Of course, Uncle. It’s me.
Aya, Drake’s here.
- I have to go.
- Okay, Uncle. Bye!
Drake...
Drake, aren’t you going to the party?
Drake, I know you want
to come with us to Taiwan.
Alright, I’m letting you.
I’ll talk to your aunt.
Follow us to
Taiwan, 5:00 AM flight.
Really?
But go to the party first.
You should pick up Alys.
You can wear this.
Otherwise, don’t expect a ticket.
Ugh!
Hey. Hello?
Answer me!
Don’t you understand my question?
I love you, Drake Palma!
Hi.
Hey.
I’m so awesome!
Well?
My date tonight is
so handsome, right?
What can you say, Kei?
Like I care!
You probably forced
Drake to come.
I know your tricks!
Oh, please.
I can hear the jealousy in your voice
because Drake is my partner.
So, cut it out.
I am the queen of the night.
Next!
Hey, Drake. Let’s take a photo.
Uh, never mind.
He doesn’t want to.
Well, you didn’t say anything!
How would I know
you were up for it?
Closer!
Come on, miss, closer!
Closer still!
This is three inches close!
A little closer, miss!
I can’t believe it.
He picked me up,
helped me up, and
put his arm around me.
What happened?
He’s not allergic to me anymore?
Alys!
Hey, Alys, what’s up?
Why are you ignoring me?
Hey, what’s wrong?
What did I do?
What do you think?
You ditched me!
You gave me false hope!
What do you mean false hope?
You’re right.
I waited for you at home
and you never showed up!
You left me hanging.
Aya said you’re going with Drake.
So I just went with her.
Huh?
Okay, thank you.
Brother...
Bro, your phone’s so cool!
The graphics are awesome!
Here.
Is this okay?
Hey, CB!
Aya Pineda?
She’s that pretty weirdo, right?
Blank message?
Fine.
I’ll be straightforward.
Don’t invite Alys.
Drake is her partner in AP!
Sent!
Wow! All caps? Intense!
What about me?
Should you be my partner?
Fine! You’re my AP partner now!
Yes!
This phone is awesome!
Aya said that?
Seriously, Aya Pineda?!
She’s still pushing this
matchmaking with Drake!
I thought Drake really
came to pick me up!
Ugh! I almost fell for it!
- Had I known that Aya didn’t tell you-
- Oh, whatever!
You didn’t even wonder
why I changed partners?
You didn’t even call or text me?
You’re the worst
best friend, Sheen!
We’re done!
You know that will never happen.
You’re my best friend for a reason.
You’ll be with me forever.
We can’t break up.
You have to stick with me.
It’s hard to be his best friend.
Why did I agree to
be Sheen’s best friend?
I should have been patient
and waited to be his girlfriend.
Why did he become classmates
with Kei last year?
She got ahead of me.
I’m sorry, okay?
Don’t be mad, please?
You’re being silly.
Sheen!
I have to go. Are we good?
Hmm?
I still have something
to do backstage.
- Go ahead!
- Save a dance for me.
Sheen’s so annoying!
He left me here!
What a jerk!
Hi.
Here, allow me.
You’re such a messy eater!
Aren’t you feeling giddy?
Who are you?
You don’t know me?
I’m the Student Council
Vice President.
Okay.
Kent Justin Valdez, at your service!
I just came from the bathroom!
You’re fun to talk to.
Did I say something funny?
Good question!
Actually, I’ve been watching you.
I mean, you just stayed in your seat.
Are you a stalker?
Admirer.
I’m good-looking, after all.
You’re so full of yourself!
Go away! I’m eating!
And it was lovely meeting you, too.
See you around!
Who was that?
So annoying!
This is all Sheen’s fault!
He left me, and now I
had to deal with that creep!
Hey!
Whatever!
You really think I wouldn’t
know about what you did.
Come on, bestie!
Have you eaten?
Main dish is good!
- Let’s eat!
- No!
But I’m sure you already ate.
You’re being judgemental, bestie.
Because --
Where’s your date?
Oh, he’s swarmed
by those “like” girls!
Like dance with me?
Like have you eaten?
Let’s eat together.
Like dessert, Drake?
You like?
Excuse me…
he’s my date!
What’s with the glare?
Do you want me to
poke your eyes and record it?
Like, chill, bestie.
I’ll handle this for you!
Like, bestie, please no.
So they’ll stop.
Recording!
Drake, I’m your date tonight, right?
Tss.
Did you see that?
That was so embarrassing!
Bestie, stop it.
Oops, sorry!
Hey, cut it out!
Drake!
Hey!
Sshh.
Drake, everyone’s staring!
Don’t mind them.
But…
Those were three words.
The longest phrase he said all night.
Can I ask you something?
Why are you dancing with me?
Those girls are annoying.
Am I not annoying?
You’re annoying.
But that’s fine.
No.
He is with Katrina.
This is just a crush. Period!
By the way,
that pink tie looks good
on you.
It’s done.
Hmm?
I’m so sorry!
I finally got away!
Drake is too much!
He’s good at making
my heart race!
Alys!
Forget it, Sheen!
Go back to the stage!
Just because you’re the president,
you’re taking me for granted.
Come on.
That’s not true.
Speak for yourself.
You almost swapped
faces with Drake!
Am I being replaced?
Is Sheen my loves
getting jealous?
Keep dreaming!
Talking to him is useless.
Shall we dance?
Is he trying to make up to me?
Or he doesn’t want
to lose to Drake?
Hmm...
What is he thinking?
He’s giving that death stare.
Whatever.
I’ll just dance with Sheen my loves.
Why does he seem sad?
Isn’t he happy dancing with me?
Alys...
Can I ask you something?
Do you think I should go after Kei?
Do you still love her?
I do.
A lot.
I know, best friend.
Fight for her, you silly.
You love her, right?
Mmm.
Don’t give up on her.
All right.
Thank you, Alys.
I’ll look for Kei.
Wish me luck!
By the way,
that pink tie looks
good on you.
11:00 PM.
It’s going to take awhile.
I can’t go home yet.
Like who the heck
is that Alys Perez?
Like I don’t know.
Girl, she’s a snake!
She’s dancing with Drake,
then now with Sheen?
She is so annoying.
Like I have something
in mind, girls!
Like what?
Let’s lock her up
in the stock room.
She deserves it!
That sounds like so much fun!
I’m in that!
Let’s go!
Maybe if I wear this,
they won’t bother me anymore.
Please!
Give me one more chance, Kei!
I won’t screw up again!
Sorry if I made the student council
my priority over you.
Sheen...
I know it’s cliché, but...
it’s not you, it’s me.
Please.
Kei, just one more chance.
I love you so much!
We already talked about this.
We’re done.
You’re a good guy.
You’ll find someone else, but...
But I’m not the one for you.
You’re the only one I want, Kei!
Only you!
I like someone else, Sheen.
I’m really sorry.
Do you really like Drake?
I love you.
Remember that, Kei.
I’ll do everything to
make you happy.
You want me to be happy?
Then tell Alys to
stay away from Drake.
What, Sheen?
Why does Sheen keep on chasing
someone who doesn’t like him?
Why can’t he just
let Kei be with Drake?
If Drake hadn’t
come into our lives,
none of this would’ve happened.
Especially how I feel.
Let’s go.
Like hey!
What?
Like someone’s looking for you.
Who is it?
Like do we even
look like we care?
Just be thankful that
we even helped him.
Like looking at your
ugly face is so like torture.
Like yes!
Like he even gave us this.
Like thanks!
Meet me inside the stockroom.
Urgent.
P.S. I am your secret admirer.
Is this for real?
Let’s go.
Meet me inside the
stockroom. Urgent.
P.S. I am your secret admirer.
Hello?
Anyone here?
Hey! Wait!
Someone’s in here!
Why did you lock the door?
OMG! How do I open this?!
Hey! I’m stuck in here!
Help!
Where is Alys?
Bee! I found you!
Let’s do a slow dance!
- Slow dance?
- I got this!
There!
This little troll
won’t stop following me!
Bee, what’s with your face?
Stop calling me Bee!
I’m Aya! A-ya!
You are Bee!
‘Cause I’m your honey!
Seriously?!
What is your problem?!
Relax, Aya babes!
You’ll get wrinkles!
Oh my God, Lord!
- You’re so mean to me, Bee!
- Lord!
- Please, Lord!
- I’m not a monster!
Why, Lord?! Why?!
Where’s Alys?
I don’t know!
I’ve been looking for her, too!
She left her phone with me!
Wait a minute.
Why are you looking for my friend?
Who are you?!
So, they really went through
with their plan.
Tss. Now, I need to find her.
Bee?
Bee, wait! Bee!
Saint Collete.
Saint Collete, please!
I don’t mind if you
show up right now.
It’s okay with me.
Just open this door, please!
Thank you!
What’s with these students?
I said close it after!
Not again!
Wait—
Wait—hold on!
Pervert!
Creep!
You touched my boob!
My most precious!
You creep! Perv!
Who are you?
Are you a mascot?
Take that mascot head off.
Come on! I just want to
know who touched me first!
You’re so annoying!
Those like girls are annoying!
And I’m an idiot
for ending up here!
It’s so frustrating!
I’m…
Whatever.
Hi, everyone! I know
everybody’s still having fun,
but it’s 12:00 AM.
It’s time to wrap things up.
Maybe
you're the ugliest in Saint Collete High,
that’s why you won’t show your face.
Whatever! That’s okay.
It’s better to look ugly than
have a personality like Drake Palma!
He’s the one to blame.
If it weren’t for him,
my life wouldn’t get this messy!
Sheen’s life, too!
So, who are you?
I promise I won’t tell.
Pinky swear!
Like such a buzzkill!
True! Like, can we extend?
Sorry.
But the party is officially over.
Thank you for coming.
Like let’s just go home.
I’m…
Neil?
Yeah, Neil.
Do we even have a
batchmate named Neil?
Hi, Neil. I’m Alys.
Ahh!
Creep!
Wait!
Why do you keep hitting me?
That’s strike two!
On my boob!
What did I touch?
I didn’t do anything!
Did I touch the wall?
You’re shameless!
Creep!
Perv! Liar! Thief! Forger!
I’ll tell the whole world about this, Neil!
Whatever-your-last-name-is!
You’re disgusting!
Where could Alys be?
I haven’t seen Drake, too.
Great, maybe she’s with him!
This is exciting!
Bee!
Why are you smiling?
Thinking of me already?
Please, just leave me alone, Kent!
Kent, right?!
You even remembered my name!
So I’m unforgettable?
You’re so full of it!
Leave me alone!
Don’t push me away, Bee.
I’ll only fall harder!
What’s going on here?
You’re the worst date, Sheen!
You left me with this creep!
- Unbelievable!
- Sorry!
I was just dealing with so much!
Whatever.
Hey, Kent.
Why are you with Aya?
I’m courting Aya!
Ugh!
Saint Collete!
Thank you for the light!
Thank you!
Hello!
Anyone out there?!
Please! We’re stuck in here!
We’re here!
Open the door, please!
- Help!
- Don’t bother to open it.
It’s locked.
Neil, do you have a phone?
Do you have it with you?
Let me call Aya.
Low-batt.
I said I’d be home by one.
My parents are probably worried.
I also have a flight.
But I won’t make it
because of you.
I shouldn’t have looked for you.
I was just trying to help,
and now I’m the bad guy.
Let’s just stay here ‘til morning.
Neil, can I ask you something?
Aren’t you already asking?
So rude!
You’re a guy, right?
You want me to prove it?
What the—?!
You’re not worth it.
Keep dreaming.
He’s acting like Drake!
But that’s impossible!
He should be asleep by now.
Hey!
For your information,
I’m beautiful.
You know Drake Palma?
The arrogant and handsome guy
all the girls are chasing?
He’s my boyfriend!
He’s with me because I’m pretty!
Why are you laughing?
You don’t believe me?
Why would I believe you?
We’re legit!
I know Uncle Steve, his dad!
And Aunt Katrina…
his secret rel—
I mean, stepmom...
His future stepmom!
So, about Drake.
Do you like him?
Uh…
A little.
He’s really handsome.
Even if he always
looks like someone just died.
He’s smart, too.
He sleeps a lot but
still aces everything.
Tss. I’m right.
Everything she likes about me
is superficial.
My good looks and perfect grades.
She’s no different from those
annoying “like girls”.
Or maybe worse.
And just between us, okay?
Even Aya or Sheen don’t know.
But…
I have a crush on Drake.
So you like him?
Because he’s brave.
Yes, he’s handsome and smart,
but there are a
lot of guys like that.
But Drake?
There’s nothing more to say.
Drake is Drake.
He’s the real deal.
Even if he’s perfect, he’s still human.
I know behind that tough exterior,
there’s a lot of angst in him.
I can see it in his eyes.
I thought everything she likes about me
was only superficial.
I was wrong.
Other than Katrina,
Alys is the one who gets me.
Thanks, Neil.
Why am I moving?
- Drake?!
- Shhh!
How did I get out?
Why are you carrying me?!
Where’s Neil?
Sir! What are you—?!
Shhh!
What happened?
Why are you carrying me?
How did I get out?
Where’s Neil?!
Ouch!
That hurts!
Why did you drop me?
You’re noisy.
You could’ve warned
me before dropping me!
Tss.
Hop on.
What the hell?
Are you trying to kill me or
are you trying to suffocate me to death?
You’re weird.
What are you talking about?
You’re weirder.
Tss.
Hop on.
No!
No way!
You might drop me again!
I can go home on my own!
Bye!
Stop following me!
Go home!
I said stop!
Why can’t he go home?
As if he’s really concerned!
If he hadn’t dropped me,
I’d be home by now!
Just go! I’m fine! Go home!
Why can’t he –
go home!
Are you really not going home?!
Go home!
Why are you still here?!
Leave!
My coat.
Huh? Isn’t this Neil’s?
Alys!
Uh…Mom…Dad...
Why are you home just now?!
We’ve been trying to reach you all night!
We couldn’t sleep!
We were so worried!
Why do you look like that?
What happened to you?
Sheen…
You want me to be happy?
Then tell Alys to
stay away from Drake.
Even if he’s perfect,
he’s still human.
I know behind that tough
exterior, there’s a lot of angst in him.
Am I not annoying?
You’re annoying.
But that’s fine.
I can see it
in his eyes.
On the next episode of
Seducing Drake Palma
Didn’t we already
talk about this?!
I thought you wanted
me to be happy?!
Then tell Alys to back off!
Alys!
Sheen.
Excuse me.
Can we talk after dismissal?
Alys,
dad wants to see you.
I’ll see you after dismissal.
You’re my girlfriend.
Act like one.