Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.xyz or dramacool.club
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
You're from Shanxi, right?
Yes.
Have you ever been to Dayun County?
My grandma is from Dayun County.
From Yunlai Village.
Dayun County now,
has developed really well.
It's changed a lot.
Hello, Mr. Shen.
This is our business representative,
Qiao Jianbin.
Hello.
By the way, Uncle,
did you stay a few extra days on your trip?
No.
I just went for the ribbon-cutting.
It was a quick trip.
Stop watching the news.
I want to watch cartoons.
Dad.
Do you have time now?
I want to talk to you about
the old town renovation.
Sure, that's fine.
Let's go talk over there.
Chenchen.
How many times have I told you?
Do you want to ruin your eyes?
Old Qiao,
it's time to eat.
I'll finish these two big rolls
and then I'll come.
Yazhen is here.
Sister Sha, got your hair done?
Yeah.
Yazhen.
Old Qiao in your family is really popular now.
On TV,
he speaks so well.
He even outshines the county chief.
That's true.
With so many stores,
they made me the merchant representative.
Of course I had to say something.
Right?
No wonder your daughter turned out so well.
I remember the younger one,
she went to work.
But what's the point?
She never even calls.
Only on holidays
she sends a message.
Our Linlin is still the best.
She stays peacefully
by her parents' side.
That's our little sweetheart.
By the way,
your Linlin
is she getting married soon?
Soon, very soon.
My son-in-law
is a future banker.
Miss,
I work in Dayun County's
largest fertilizer factory as a buyer.
All the holiday group purchase benefits
are managed by me.
Let's add each other on WeChat.
If there's a good deal,
I'll let you know.
If you need anything,
just come to our counter.
Please take this.
You're so by-the-book,
how do you make money?
Many sales ladies want to add me,
but they can't even get through.
Your hand is so pale,
are you sick or something?
I'll pick you up after work tonight.
Are you sick?
You...
Stop right there!
Did I say you could touch me?
Honey!
She hit me!
Why did you hit her?
Why did you hit me?
You... you bitch!
Are you crazy?
Let go of me!
What's going on here?
Let go!
I'm going to report you!
Linlin!
You promised to come to our house
to discuss the wedding.
Dad, Mom,
we're back.
Troublemaker!
You still have the nerve to come back.
Auntie, I'm not—
Linlin!
Dad
Come
Have some fruit
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.xyz or dramacool.club
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Dad
This is from you and Mom
for Qiao Lin and my wedding
After the bride price for Qiao Lin's family
the rings
and all the other miscellaneous
expenses are deducted
there's ninety-eight thousand
six hundred fifty-four yuan left
Let me ask one more thing
The wedding gift money
will go to you
Qiao Lin and I discussed it
I'll go through each item
The wedding photos cost
nine thousand five hundred eighty-eight
The wedding planner
I picked a mid-range one
eighteen thousand eight hundred
Out-of-town guests' lodging
I booked twenty standard rooms
Each room is two hundred eighty-eight
Total is five thousand seven hundred sixty
Cigarettes, alcohol, candy, tea
We'll provide ourselves
Fifteen thousand yuan is enough
I booked twenty banquet tables
Each table costs
one thousand two hundred eighty-eight
Twenty tables for the banquet
How is that enough
Mom
Our bank has rules
for weddings and funerals
must be within twenty tables
can't go over the limit
Otherwise, my boss and I
will be affected
Did your work ever say
family often goes to the police station
or precinct
if that affects you
Auntie
Just say what you want
Don't be so sarcastic here
Okay?
I'm being sarcastic?
You, a young woman
always so reckless
Why do you never
think before you act
That police station
do you think it's your own home
You go there several times a month
Auntie, this
isn't my fault
Today it was that guy
He started acting obscene
Enough
Say less
Qiao Lin
You're Lin Tao's fiancée
Our county isn't big
If you keep causing trouble
if word gets out
it'll affect Lin Tao's job
Do you know that
If his job is affected
will you be happy
My son
graduated from a top university
with a master's degree
He's a bank client manager now
He'll be promoted to section chief
branch manager
and eventually bank president
Look at what you're doing now
Aren't you ruining my son's
bright future
If you want to blame someone
we shouldn't have agreed to your marriage
Qiao Lin
I've calculated it
There's still
seventeen thousand eight hundred sixty-six
Should be enough for us
to go on our honeymoon
Go by yourself
Qiao Lin
What are you doing
Working
What's wrong
Nothing
When will you visit home
Qiao Lin
Have an apple
Thank you, Dad
Dad
The bride price Lin Tao gave our family
Did you use it
Yes, we did
Didn't we agree that
this money would renovate the new shop
and after selling the old shop
we'd pay you back
What's wrong
Lin Tao's family
said something
No, they haven't
I'm just asking
Your wedding
How's the planning going
He's too busy at work
I've been busy too lately
Yeah
I might have a business trip soon
The company is sending us
to Jingzhou for training
To Jingzhou
How long will you be gone
Did you tell Lin Tao
Not yet
No
Qiao Lin
This business trip
You should let Lin Tao know
Lin Tao works at the bank now too
He's a key employee
He cares about reputation
You two need to get along
Exactly
You're about to get married
Can't always think of yourself
You know
Whatever it is
discuss it with Lin Tao
Did you hear
I heard
Yeah
From now on, you two should
live your own lives
peacefully
stay close to Mom and Dad
Don't be like your sister
This daughter
is as good as not having one
The guest list and schedule for the family dinner
must be triple-checked.
If there are any issues,
you can always contact me.
Don't worry.
Sis,
tonight
our department is having a dinner.
Do you want to join us?
I won't go tonight.
My boyfriend is picking me up.
Boyfriend? Really?
Isn't he actually our brother-in-law?
Get home early tonight, okay?
Okay.
Enjoy your date tonight.
I'm heading out.
Yan Yan,
Qiao Yan.
Do you think I'm lucky today?
I just happened to catch you after work.
Otherwise, I wouldn't know
where to find you.
Why are you here?
I called off the wedding.
Now I'm totally free.
I thought I'd come to the big city
and see what I can do.
But I haven't found a place yet.
I'll crash at your place for a couple days.
There's a café across the street.
Let's go talk there.
Alright, alright.
Why go to a café?
That's a waste of money.
Let's go.
We'll talk at your place.
It's fine to chat there.
Yan Yan,
Is that your boyfriend?
Then he's my brother-in-law.
Hello, brother-in-law.
And you are...?
I'm...
My cousin.
She came to see me.
Hello, cousin.
I'm picking her up for dinner after work.
Why don't we all go together?
My cousin just arrived.
She's a bit tired.
I need to find a hotel
so she can settle in.
Alright.
Okay.
That restaurant tonight
will have to wait for another day.
Is that okay?
Sure.
Get home early then.
Once I'm home,
I'll call you.
Go ahead.
Bye, cousin.
Be careful.
Drive safe.
This place is pretty nice.
The transport is convenient too.
Qiao Yan,
Why did you say I'm your cousin?
There's a fridge too.
You can buy whatever you want at the store.
I can see it now.
It's because your boyfriend
is too good for you.
So you look down on
your useless sister like me.
Is that it?
Just stay a few days and go home.
What do you mean by that?
You called off the wedding and ran away.
You didn't tell Mom and Dad, did you?
They'll be looking for you everywhere.
Yeah.
I'll wait until I'm settled
then I'll tell them.
It's the same thing.
No, don't change the subject.
I'm asking you,
why can't you
tell your boyfriend
that I'm your real sister?
Grandma and I
are on the same household register.
My surname is Xu.
Not Qiao.
So from the start,
you should've known
my only family
is Grandma.
Yes.
I know you weren't close
to Mom and Dad growing up.
But I never thought
we weren't family.
That's just how you feel.
Qiao Lin,
You showed up without warning
and came looking for me.
I've done all I can.
I've gone above and beyond.
When your money runs out,
just go home early.
Don't make them worry.
But if you want to stay, that's fine.
But I have no obligation
to take care of you.
Qiao Yan,
If I'd known you felt this way,
from the start,
I wouldn't have come to you.
Do you know that?
My surname is Xu.
Xu Yan.
You—you're called Qiao Yan.
You're Qiao Yan, Qiao.
This is the price of your coldness.
Stupid Qiao Yan!
I shouldn't have saved you back then.
Wild child, wild child!
Wild child!
Move aside, I'm going home!
Little Qiao Yan, no one praises you.
Wild child, no parents.
Who are you? How dare you push me?
None of your business.
Who dares bully my sister?
Do you dare?
We don't dare, we don't dare!
You are my sister.
Qiao Yan is here.
She's old enough for elementary school.
Her studies can't be delayed.
You must find her
a school in Dayun County.
All these years,
as her parents,
you haven't fulfilled
your parental duties at all.
But when it comes to her schooling,
you both must
do your best
and take responsibility, understand?
Yes, Mom.
We came this time
to bring Qiao Yan
back home for school.
All these years,
you've raised her alone.
It's been so hard for you.
Alright, alright.
No need for nice words.
Do you know
Qiao Yan tells
the neighbors' kids
what?
She says her parents
are abroad.
She's so little, she
How did she learn to lie?
When you had Qiao Lin,
you insisted on having a boy.
You knew
Yazhen wasn't healthy.
All these years,
her health has been ruined.
Now you have a girl,
and you don't like her.
She has a congenital heart disease.
Will you not even
save her life?
As parents,
don't you feel any guilt?
Mom.
We know we were wrong.
We'll take Qiao Yan home this time
and treat her well.
We'll make up for what she missed.
Mom.
Slow down, slow down.
Alright.
We're home.
Come in.
This is Mom and Dad's home.
It will be your home too.
From now on,
you'll live with your sister
in this room.
Alright?
Dad will take your luggage
inside for you.
These pretty clothes
Grandma packed for you.
At Mom and Dad's house,
be sensible and obedient.
If you can do it yourself,
do it yourself.
And these things you like,
Grandma brought them all.
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.xyz or dramacool.club
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
At mealtime,
don't fight with your sister.
Understand?
Grandma will miss you.
Come, take a look.
This is home.
Alright, it's getting late.
Let's bathe and go to bed.
Come, Mom will bathe you.
Mom, I can bathe myself.
Okay.
Qiao Yan will bathe herself.
Alright then,
take off your dirty clothes.
Mom will wash them, okay?
Mom, I can wash my clothes.
Why does it smell so much like gas?
Qiao Lin.
Wake up, don't scare Dad.
What's wrong with the child?
Someone, help!
Help! Help!
What's going on?
It's gas poisoning.
Qiao Lin, wake up.
Qiao Lin.
Call 120 for me.
Okay, okay, don't panic.
Qiao Lin.
Wake up, wake up.
Don't scare Dad.
Qiao Lin.
Wake up, wake up, Qiao Lin.
What's happening?
Old Qiao.
Qiao Lin has gas poisoning.
Where did you go?
You left without turning off the gas.
Qiao Lin.
Qiao Lin, are you alright?
Stop shouting here.
Go call an ambulance!
Old Qiao.
Where's Qiao Yan?
Qiao Yan.
Is anyone else here?
Help me out.
It's all Dad's fault.
Dad is sorry.
Sweet daughter.
Come.
Have a banana.
Dad will feed you.
Open your mouth.
Have another bite.
A big bite.
Come on.
Good girl.
When we get home, Mom will make
your favorite braised pork.
Alright?
Qiao Yan.
You came back just in time.
Your sister got into a fight outside.
We need to go quickly.
We'll have instant noodles for dinner.
Old Qiao, hurry up.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthd—
Qiao Yan, is that you?
Happy birthday.
Grandma.
Alright, alright, don't cry.
Come to Grandma's house.
Grandma will make you something tasty.
Okay?
Look at you.
All you do is fight every day.
You even fight with boys.
He's your classmate.
What if you hurt him?
See?
Every day, the teacher
calls us out.
We have to apologize every day.
Keep your voice down.
Someone's sleeping.
We have to pay for checkups.
And treat people to meals.
And apologize again.
See? See?
Your sister is so well-behaved.
But you,
you just fight all day long.
You never let us relax.
Mom, I'm hungry.
Alright, alright.
Hungry, hungry, hungry.
We just apologized to them.
We haven't eaten anything.
Come on, okay.
I'll heat this up now.
Come here.
What do you want for the main dish?
Want noodles?
Noodles, noodles.
Mom, I'm hungry.
Take a bath first.
Mom.
Eat after you bathe.
I'm hungry.
Wash yourself.
I'll hurry and wash these clothes.
You need them for tomorrow.
Wrap up a bit.
Don't catch a chill.
Qiao Yan's recent mock exams
have all been excellent.
She's in the top thirty of her grade.
Getting into Jingzhou's top university
shouldn't be a problem.
As for which major to choose,
go home
and discuss it with her.
Help her make the decision.
For her to achieve
such good results,
we must thank the teacher's dedication.
However,
she won't take the college entrance exam.
The family has other plans for her.
Giving up the exam
with Qiao Yan's grades
is truly a shame.
About this,
have you discussed it with her?
What does she want?
Children can't understand
the family's difficulties.
Family matters
are decided by me.
What gives you the right
to stop me from taking the exam?
I'm talking to your teacher.
What gives you the right
to stop me from taking the exam?
Because I'm your father.
Because I'm the head of this family.
Sorry, teacher.
Excuse me.
Sorry you had to see this.
This is final.
Let's go home.
Why won't you let me go to college?
Dad.
Why won't you let me
go to college?
Dad, wait for me.
Wait a second.
Wait a moment.
Just wait for me.
Why?
Because our family is poor.
Because college tuition
and living expenses are high.
Our family can't afford
to support two college students.
So we had to decide
to let your sister Qiao Lin
take the exam.
Dad, what about me?
Then... what about me?
After you finish high school,
we'll help you
find a job.
That way, you can stay
with Mom and Dad.
If anything happens,
we can take care of you.
No.
I...
I want to know why.
Why have you always
been so biased?
Why does Qiao Lin
get everything good?
Am I...
Am I not
your real daughter?
Why do you
keep telling me
my parents don't love me?
I thought
if I kept lying to myself,
if I studied hard,
tried to be sensible,
and obeyed you,
you would like me.
Why do you make me
lose even the right to lie
to myself?
I...
What did I ever do
to let you down?
You've grown up,
never lacking food,
clothes, or anything.
Why can't you
be a little understanding?
That's because you never
told me the truth,
and took away my right
to study.
What you did is stealing.
What you did is robbing.
Is this how
you talk to your father?
That's too disrespectful.
You're so unfilial.
Even if you go to college,
you'll still be ungrateful.
Am I really such a bad child?
Did I really do something wrong?
I don't understand.
Why?
Why do you keep proving
how much you don't love me?
Why?
Why did I have to be
your daughter?
Grandma.
I'm here, I'm here.
Yan Yan.
You...
Grandma.
Grandma knows
you've been wronged.
Look at you.
You're all soaked.
Hey, Haoming.
What are you doing?
I'm on my way home.
Can you come by
my studio?
Now?
Yes.
Come quickly.
Okay.
Driver, change the address.
What's wrong?
It's grown a flower stalk.
It's sixty years old
this year.
I think
tonight
it will definitely bloom.
If it really blooms,
this will be the brightest
moment
of its life.
I hope I can witness it
together with you.
I remember you said before
Agave
blooms only once
in its lifetime.
So after it blooms,
it dies.
After blooming,
the plant quickly withers.
Its energy is spent,
its light goes out.
In the end,
it returns to dust.
It uses up all
the nutrients it gathered
in its life,
endures hardship,
just to wait for this
moment to bloom.
This is truly
its life's swan song.
What's wrong?
I just feel
it's heartbreaking.
It spends its whole life
overcoming
and struggling to grow,
just for one moment
of blooming.
Because it has no choice,
it must be stronger
than others,
work harder,
endure more,
to finally achieve
a beautiful result.
A long wait,
enduring wind and rain,
is the price it pays.
Bloom and bear fruit
Grow old, be reborn
The cycle repeats
This is nature's law
But when each agave
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.xyz or dramacool.club
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
blooms
its pollen
drifts everywhere
and meets another agave
they pollinate each other
creating more seeds
These seeds
are what they leave
in this world
the continuation of life
It's just like people
Meeting
Falling in love
Getting married
Having children
After a hundred years
Even though
people may be gone
their love will carry on
When two agaves meet
they go toward each other
with all their might
even at the cost of life
Because they know
this love
is worth it
They never regret it
Just like you and me
Meeting you
Being with you
No matter what I have to give
no matter the cost
I will never
regret it
What about you
Think carefully
I do regret a little
Regret that we're marrying next month
We should have
married sooner
Let's put this agave
in the pond too, okay
So it will have company
Okay