KING THE LAND
I finally got some freedom.
We'll party like each day is a year,
so don't stop me.
Don't even sleep, okay?
You're so thrilled.
Are you that happy?
Don't you miss Cho-rong?
Hey, she needs some time of her own too.
- What's with you?
- "What's with you?"
- Excuse me.
- Yes, sir?
You're never off the clock, are you?
It's not you two. Sit down.
"Yes, sir?" was funny.
I finally got it.
I've solved the mystery.
What mystery?
I get why Mr. Gu said he was a manager
and not the head manager
because that could make
everyone uncomfortable.
But why did he call me
a department manager,
not a senior manager or a manager?
I wonder.
That's because I'm already
a department manager
in Mr. Gu's heart.
So he wants me
to use this chance to get trained
as the department manager.
I don't think it was that profound.
No, it was. Definitely.
- Do you really think so?
- Yes!
I don't think so.
- Mr. Yoo?
- Yes?
I think our tickets were switched.
You're in business class.
Really? Me?
Of course you should sit
in business class, Mr. Yoo.
Mr. No, you've been well-trained.
I'm glad I brought you up
to be considerate of your superior.
Give him a hand.
You should probably go quickly
before I change my mind.
Thank you, sir.
Don't you ever change.
Wow, business class? Take your seat.
I'm off to business class.
Business, man.
I'm here.
What's going on?
What do you think?
I came back to reclaim my seat.
My seat is always next to you, right?
You're in the right spot.
Are you not uncomfortable?
Not at all.
I'm completely at ease.
What?
Why won't this work? Is it out of order?
No, that's as far as it goes.
- It went down.
- It won't go lower.
Excuse me, Mr. No.
Yes?
Are you trying to start something?
Start what?
This.
If you keep pushing back,
I'll kick your seat.
I'll be careful.
So why did you choose to switch seats
and be uncomfortable?
I am choosing to be with you.
It's nice, isn't it?
Is it just me?
No.
Me too.
This is nice.
Hello!
WE GO HARD!
(YOU'RE PRETTY)
We're here.
Please follow me.
Hello.
Of course, this is nice.
I can't believe this.
- My gosh.
- Careful.
Watch the stairs.
What is this?
- My gosh.
- What's this?
No way.
This isn't the end.
Follow me.
- Really?
- There's more.
Let's take pictures.
- One, two, three.
- Ta-da!
- You come too.
- You two look awesome.
- One, two, three.
The pool is a bit small.
How is this small? It's wonderful.
Yes, why can't you be content?
Mr. Yoo, this place is awesome!
Mr. Yoo,
thank you.
Don't mention it. It's not a big deal.
Let's go upstairs. It'll be even better.
- My gosh. Upstairs?
- Another floor?
- Let's go!
- Second floor!
What's on the second floor?
Come quickly!
Second floor!
- No Sang-sik.
- What's on the second floor?
Goodness.
These are the rooms.
Your rooms are to the right.
The right?
- Yes.
- This is it?
- This?
- This is our room.
- What's it like?
- This?
Three, two, one.
There it is. There's the scream.
It's so high!
Where's my room?
Let's go inside, Mr. No.
You little…
What's all this?
Why did you book only two rooms
for all these people?
Two is more than enough.
One room for men, one for women.
- Where are you going to sleep?
- Me?
Of course,
I'll sleep here.
Are you saying
this ridiculously absurd bed
is supposed to be shared by you and me?
Everything about this place is so nice.
Gosh, so comfy.
Lie down next to me.
You idiot.
We're staying somewhere else.
We can't. We already paid in full.
Five people, five rooms.
That's a given.
And let me make myself clear.
I will not share a bed with you,
so either book a new hotel
or pack up and go back to Korea.
Got it?
Mr. Yoo!
Remember.
I'm the head manager.
Okay?
Yes, sir.
WE GO HARD!
- Help!
- Don't do it.
Stop it.
Mr. Yoo!
- This place is wonderful.
- Thank you.
How did you find such a great place?
You have such great taste.
We love it. It's the best!
I think so too.
However, there has been a problem.
What problem?
The problem is that…
Well, the…
Everyone loves it here.
What do you mean there's a problem?
- May we really stay?
- Yes.
- Really?
The problem is resolved.
Luckily the rooster has stopped crowing.
Then get in here, you two!
It's so cool in here!
Shall we? Okay.
- Shoes off.
- I'm fine.
Come on in. Let's all play together.
Please enjoy. I'll join next time.
Next time, my foot.
You look great.
EPISODE 10
Did you have fun in the pool?
- Yes!
I'm glad.
Let me tell you about today's schedule.
Let's find a chance to slip out later.
We'll go to the hottest night market
here in Bangkok.
But we're here as a group.
Can we really do that?
Of course we can.
Vacations are all about freedom.
Where are we going?
You'll see when we get there.
Mr. No?
Mr. Yoo is talking. Phone down.
Continue, Mr. Yoo.
Things may become dangerous,
so I prepared something.
What did I prepare?
Group tour T-shirts!
Amazing.
But we all have our own tastes.
We don't need a group--
Thank you, Mr. Yoo.
We'll wear them well.
Here.
Let's get changed,
and we'll meet back here in 30 minutes.
- Yes, sir.
Mr. No.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
I'll tell you later.
Go get changed.
This is wonderful.
Ms. Gang, what's the theme
of our trip again?
We go hard!
Precisely! We go hard!
Go hard for our teamwork!
Go hard for our company!
We go hard.
As you already know,
it's not "Hard go."
People may see it
and think we're not soft.
That was so funny.
Get it? Not soft?
So we'll stay as "Go hard."
- Okay?
- Yes!
Then Ms. Gang will start our chant,
and we'll all shout it out together.
- Go.
- Hard.
- Let's go!
Go hard!
- Go hard!
Why do we have to eat Vietnamese noodles
after coming all the way to Thailand?
We don't complain
when we eat Chinese in Korea.
But still, there must be
many good Thai noodle restaurants.
I have a go-to place
whenever I come here on a flight.
Why don't we go there?
Yes, Pyeong-hwa knows Bangkok really well.
Let's go to her joint.
No, this is a great restaurant.
Take a look.
Trust me and try it.
I'm a Thailand expert.
Please come inside.
We are…
- One.
That was too weak.
We are…
- One!
I really don't like him.
These are all noodles.
Of course. This is a noodle restaurant.
Da-eul doesn't like noodles.
What are you talking about?
I love noodles.
You do? Since when?
I've been craving noodles
since I set foot in Bangkok.
Ms. Gang and I are kind of hitting it off.
If you visit Bangkok,
you must eat sticky noodles.
What's that?
The noodles are…
really sticky.
Oh, because they're sticky.
Everything is great here,
but number one is the best.
- I'll take number one.
- Okay.
- Me too.
Me too.
What about you, Mr. No?
It's a hot day.
Do we have to eat hot noodles?
I'll just have a glass of beer.
Okay. Excuse me!
We'll order five number ones.
I said I wasn't eating.
I'm having two portions.
Do you speak Thai too?
Yes.
Go hard!
- Go hard!
That just hit the spot.
This is it.
This is so good.
This is much better than my joint.
What a bummer.
This would be perfect with soju.
No, this would be perfect
for curing a hangover the next day.
Try the soup. It's insane.
I told you so.
Just trust me and follow me.
Mr. Yoo, you're the best.
It may be good, but it's just noodles.
Mr. Gu…
Mr. No, try a bite.
- I'm fine.
- Just try a bite.
- Just once.
Just one bite.
- I'm fine.
- One bite. Please?
Good grief.
What just happened?
- Why is this so good?
- What?
You just fed Mr. No.
I did? When?
You did.
I did that?
You did what? I didn't see it.
- Right?
- Right.
- This is good.
- I was just sharing.
This place is good.
- Give that to me.
- What?
- It's good.
- That's mine.
Excuse me! One more, please.
This is great.
What's that?
What?
- Nothing's out there.
- Never mind.
Eat up.
- This is so good.
- It is.
It's perfect with beer.
- It's good.
- The dumplings are good.
We're running out of time.
Our next stop is
the hottest spot in Bangkok,
filled with every product
and every kind of food.
- A food heaven.
- We're going to eat more?
I came to Thailand to eat.
I'm so full. I can't eat anymore.
If I eat more, I'm not even human.
My diet completely fell through.
I'm done eating as of right now.
Don't offer me anything.
We're running out of time.
Let's get moving.
Go hard! We are one!
Hurry up. Get moving.
Mr. No.
Pay the tab and come along.
- Shall we?
- Okay.
What's that? That looks good!
Mr. Exclamation Mark.
Go back.
I didn't do this.
What's that?
- That looks good, right?
- What's that?
It's pad thai.
Should we have some?
Mr. Yoo! Buy some for us.
- This?
- Yes.
Mr. Yoo, I want shrimp pad thai.
That looks so good.
Hey, it's ice cream!
TAIWANESE-STYLE PEANUT ICE CREAM
Do you have to eat
Taiwanese ice cream in Bangkok?
I feel so lucky that
I get to eat peanut ice cream
while I'm here in Bangkok.
Thailand is a street food heaven.
Is it that good?
Totally. Do you want a bite?
I'm fine.
- Come on.
- No.
Anyway, I clearly remember you saying
that you were too full.
People visit Thailand for its food.
I haven't even started.
You said you were full.
- That you'll blow up.
- This is dessert.
- Is it a separate stomach?
- Mr. No!
- He's back?
Let's find a seat.
Me?
Yes, you.
What's all this?
We're in Thailand,
so we must try all its food.
We just ate.
How are we going to eat all this,
sir?
We have a crowd.
A bite each won't be much.
What should I begin with?
You should start eating
instead of thinking.
Right?
Let's get started.
Thank you, Mr. Yoo.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
Right, before we eat, let's make a toast.
Shall we? Sounds great.
Okay. Go hard!
- Go hard!
Ms. Gang, you've done well.
Come on.
- Thank you, sir.
- Good work.
You too, Mr. Yoo.
- Mr. Yoo.
- You can't reach this.
Thank you.
And Mr. No, you've done well too.
Mr. Yoo.
- Cheers!
Do you want some?
- Encore!
Is everything going okay?
Everything is going smoothly
thanks to you, Ms. Gu.
Well…
You recently picked out
the best staff of each subsidiary
and sent them on a trip, right?
A trip? I haven't heard anything about it.
Mr. Gu Won took the best staff
of King Hotel, King Air, and King Fashion
and took them on an incentive trip.
- Mr. Choi.
- Yes?
How could something in King Group
be carried out without my knowledge?
And of all things, incentives?
I'm sorry, ma'am. I'll look into it.
Are you asleep?
No, I'm not.
Can we see each other?
Now?
Right now.
Okay.
Why are you so heavy?
Sa-rang.
Do we have beer at home?
At home?
Yeah.
You weren't asleep?
I was waiting.
Me too.
I'm going to kill Mr. No when we get back.
Why?
He prepared a lot for this trip.
That's the problem. It's way too much.
"Go hard"? It's so tacky.
Da-eul is awful too.
"Mr. Exclamation Mark, go back."
Don't get me started.
I'll see them in my sleep.
I haven't been on a trip
with my friends since college.
I've never gone abroad with my friends
or gone anywhere with my grandma.
What have I been doing with my life?
You're here now.
And we'll travel much more.
It'll happen.
It's nice to be here with you.
It finally feels like a vacation.
I thought we were in a boot camp.
Tomorrow will be even better.
I'll make every day of yours
filled with happiness.
I'm more than happy right now.
You coming in?
Come on.
I missed you.
We were together all day long.
Not the back of your head.
Your face.
I missed this lovely face so much.
Why is this so heavy?
PYEONG-HWA,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING THIS EVENING?
Ro-un.
What are you doing after work?
Do you want to get dinner?
I have plans.
Really?
You have plans tonight?
Yes.
Tonight.
What's that sound?
Good morning.
Yes, Mr. Yoo. Good morning.
Let me announce today's schedule.
We'll begin our day
with a tour of the Wat Arun.
We'll eat at choice restaurants
and visit the icon of Bangkok,
ICONSIAM, for some shopping.
Then we'll end the day
with a party on a ferry boat.
Do you understand?
What about free time,
sir?
There's no free time on a group tour.
No.
What sort of a tour
doesn't have some free time?
He's right.
This is tyranny. How awful.
No, you came on this trip
with your free will.
You can't want that here.
Right?
Get ready.
See you downstairs in 30 minutes.
Yes, sir.
See you.
Go hard!
- That's so cool.
- It is.
It's amazing.
It's even more breathtaking in person.
This is the Wat Arun Temple.
Let's go inside.
Isn't it beautiful?
If you see any monks as we walk around…
Mr. No.
Go to the back.
Why? I'm fine here.
The order is off.
When we play, we go hard!
When we eat, we go hard!
Enough with "Go hard."
We're not wearing those T-shirts today.
We may not have the T-shirts on,
but we'll go hard forever.
You're forever an exclamation mark.
Return to your spot.
Mr. Exclamation Mark.
Why aren't you in your spot?
Let's go.
Do we really have to…
stay in this formation as we walk?
Mr. No, how long have you been working?
Six years?
Six months.
Let me share a word as your senior.
Don't get on Mr. Yoo's nerves.
It'll make our lives harder.
Da-eul, I thought you were on our side.
It's because we're a team.
I couldn't care less about strangers.
Exclamation Mark, to the back.
Wait for me!
Come on.
- The three of us.
- Take a picture, please.
I'll take it now. Over here.
One, two, three.
Go hard.
Mr. No, do you want one?
Sure.
I'll take it for you.
Will you really?
- Come here. Take it with us.
- Really?
- Go hard!
One more time. Go hard.
Go hard!
- Go hard!
Not this way. This way.
- No, this way.
- Come on, Mr. Yoo.
- Just a little more.
- Here.
Let's do it here. This is perfect.
Go hard!
- Go hard!
Now the highlight of the day.
I welcome you
to a dinner party on a ferry boat!
This is amazing.
I always wanted to try this
whenever I was in Bangkok.
Mr. Yoo, you're awesome!
Let's get out of here.
- Now?
- In a moment.
Is that possible?
Just follow my lead.
Now go inside.
Now.
What the heck?
Why are you here?
Why are you asking me?
Do you have something to say?
Darn it.
No!
I mean…
We have to line up again.
If you didn't like the ferry,
you could've said so.
Here.
Have a cool drink.
Thanks.
Are you still upset?
I was such an idiot. What am I doing?
Mr. No suddenly came between us.
What are the chances?
He's ruining everything.
But you were so cool.
Mr. No, where are you?
Mr. No!
There you are.
Come quickly.
Thailand looks so beautiful at night.
I feel so at peace too.
Everyone here looks so bright and relaxed.
There's this word in Thai. Sabai.
Instead of always rushing things
and scrambling around,
it tells you to slow down
and relax a little.
Sabai.
Maybe that's why.
That's nice.
But if we went sabai with our sales,
we'd get fired.
If we went sabai on a flight,
we wouldn't finish our service on time.
Hey, the same goes for the hotel.
What a foreign concept for us, right?
Then why don't we
enjoy some free time tomorrow
while we're in Bangkok?
Free time for everyone.
Sabai.
Bye-bye.
We're going hard
until the end of this trip.
If you want to relax,
you can go home and do it on your own.
By any chance, if you wish to go home now,
then feel free to go home and relax.
This is so much fun.
It's so much fun.
Ro-un, what brings you here?
I stopped by in passing.
Hello.
- My name is Lee Ro-un.
- Who is that?
- I had time after a flight here,
- Her junior.
so I stopped by to see Pyeong-hwa.
Nice to meet you.
He's a junior on my crew.
How did you come here?
I asked what you'd be doing later,
and you said you'd be eating here.
It's not that.
Mr. Yoo, can he join us?
Wait, he's too good-looking.
We kind of overlap.
Then you should meet him.
This is Department Manager Yoo Sang-sik
of King Group Headquarters.
And this is Manager No.
This is Cheon Sa-rang of King Hotel.
And I'm Gang Da-eul of Alanga.
Nice to meet you. I'm Lee Ro-un.
We have a new member for Team Go Hard.
Welcome. Take a seat.
Excuse me.
One beer, please.
Let's make a toast for our newest member.
Right, Ro-un.
When I say "Go hard," you say it too.
- Okay.
- Go hard!
This is the icon of Bangkok, ICONSIAM.
A round of applause.
This is the fountain.
Let's take a photo
with the ferry in the background.
- Sounds great.
- Okay.
- Of course.
- Another picture?
- To remember this.
- We need to. Come in.
- Is everyone in?
- Yes, we are.
I'll take it. One, two, three.
I knew this would happen!
I knew it!
I had fun. Please excuse me.
No, you can't go.
You're already here with us.
Stay over.
May I really?
Of course.
He can't.
Flight crew only stay
in designated hotels during layovers.
You don't have to worry.
Mr. No can take care of that, right?
Well, I can.
But there's no room.
What do you mean?
One for women, one for men.
We have two rooms.
And our room has a king size bed,
so it fits three.
It's not a king. It's a queen.
I don't mind sleeping on the floor.
No, you'll catch a cold.
It's huge. It's big enough for three.
In that case…
Sure, I'll stay.
Thank you, sir.
Then let's make a toast
to celebrate the six siblings.
Yes, a toast.
Okay.
Go hard!
- Go hard!
Come to think of it,
I haven't slept together
with a group of guys since college.
I've wanted to do this.
When you travel with friends,
a huge group of guys
end up sleeping in a room half this size.
But it never felt uncomfortable.
- Right?
- Right.
I'm uncomfortable right now.
Let's go to sleep.
Sure, I'm not stopping you.
Ro-un and I have lots to discuss.
I love it.
Then you two can chat outside.
I'm tired.
So go to sleep.
Just imagine you're alone
and that you need to sleep.
You'll fall asleep in no time.
Right?
- Yes.
- What kind of horseshit is this?
You two seem close. You're like friends.
Friends?
I absolutely detest people
who are like Mr. Yoo.
Mr. No tends to be
a little clingy with me.
He has no friends due to his personality.
- Really?
- No.
So I've been looking after him
with my generous heart. Right?
I'm turning the lights off. Night.
- No, don't turn them off.
- Go to sleep.
Turn the lights on.
I'm talking to you, Mr. No.
I'm a department manager
and you're a manager.
Turn them back on now.
I've put up with your nonsense all day.
Wait!
Happy now?
Ta-da, Cho-rong!
Look! Isn't this pretty?
It is. It's totally pretty.
And look.
What about this?
That's really cute too.
Did you only get stuff for me?
What about you?
What? I don't need anything.
You don't have to buy out of need.
Buy something if it's pretty.
Don't just buy mine tomorrow.
Make sure you get something
for yourself too, okay?
Promise me.
Okay, I promise.
Be careful of cars.
And don't follow bad people.
Make sure you stay with the aunties.
Okay, I'll be careful.
Goodnight sweetie.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
- Goodnight.
- Goodnight!
What would you have done without Cho-rong?
I'm not jealous that you're married,
but I am jealous
that you have a daughter like her.
Me too.
You should try having one too.
They're not adorable all the time.
But giving birth to Cho-rong is still
the best thing I've done in my life.
Take this.
What's this?
We picked it up on the way.
What?
What is this?
Girls, come on.
You two are giving me the feels.
Cho-rong tells you to look after yourself,
but you don't listen.
What can we do? We have to look after you.
Thank you. I mean it.
- What's going on?
- No.
- Hey.
- No. I'm not crying.
- You better not be crying right now.
We'll tease you for life if you cry now.
Never.
Come on.
You two are the best.
- Come on.
- You're the only ones for me.
Thank you.
Me too. You two are the only ones for me.
Not you.
You've got Ro-un,
who came all the way to Thailand
just for you.
That's really not it.
"I stopped by to see Pyeong-hwa.
Nice to meet you."
"I don't mind sleeping on the floor."
It's not like that.
It's not. Nothing's going on.
- "Then I'll stay. Thank you."
- That's enough.
- Cut it out.
- Why?
- Hey, just cut it out!
- "Pyeong-hwa--"
- What's wrong?
- My gosh.
- Are you all right?
- Why?
- I'm sorry.
- "Pyeong-hwa."
"Are you okay, Pyeong-hwa?"
"I'm okay, Pyeong-hwa."
I knew you'd say that!
- I knew it!
- "I'm all right, Pyeong-hwa."
So sweet!
"I'm fine, Pyeong-hwa."
- Stop it!
- "I came because I missed you so much."
"Pyeong-hwa."
- "Pyeong-hwa."
- I can't hear you.
"I can sleep on the cold hard floor
if it means I can be with you!"
Make sure you eat before you leave.
Thanks.
Mr. Yoo.
- Is Sa-rang gone?
- She's not there?
No. Mr. No's gone too.
- Over there.
- What?
Mr. No!
Where are you going?
We're leaving to find freedom.
Goodbye, everyone!
Hey, Cheon Sa-rang!
You traitor!
Wait for me! I want to come too!
- Isn't it pretty?
- Yes.
You're good.
No, let's take one. I want to.
- This time, you have to smile.
- I shall smile.
And make a heart.
I shall make that too.
And smile.
Good.
What is this place?
I told you there was a place
I wanted to go with you, right?
This is it.
It's as beautiful as a painting.
I'd be so happy if I could see
a view like this every day.
Should we live here?
Sounds like a dream.
Then we'll live like a dream.
Enjoy your meal.
Are you that happy?
I've had lots of Thai food,
but nothing like this.
It's all so pretty.
And it all looks so good!
Try this one first. Open up.
It's good.
This is so good. Here.
- Isn't it?
- Yes.
Take your time and try the others too.
Did you enjoy dinner?
Yes, it was so good.
And the night view is so pretty.
I'm very glad that you like it.
I never
hoped for anything since my childhood.
I was afraid my hopes and desires
would take away
the things that are dear to me.
But I keep wanting more.
I feel so happy that I begin to wonder
if I'm allowed this much happiness.
I keep hoping that
I'll continue to be this happy.
It's okay to want more.
The things you want to do,
want to have, and want to become.
You can want it all.
You deserve it.
My sister and I have different moms.
My father had me
after he remarried my mom.
She disappeared when I was young.
All of a sudden,
without a word.
I was wailing as I looked for her,
but everyone else
had a smile on their faces.
It was the first time I thought
smiles could look monstrous.
And that in my life…
no one showed their genuine emotions.
Then along came Cheon Sa-rang
with her genuine emotions.
Do you still have no idea where she is?
You haven't heard from her?
No.
I kept looking,
but there was no trace of her.
It's as if
she never existed in this world.
I don't know if she abandoned me
or if she had a reason to leave.
So I'm not sure
if I should miss her or despise her.
I'm sure she's somewhere.
Let's find her together.
You don't have to do that.
I was just curious.
I didn't exactly want to see her.
And I'm not even curious anymore.
The night view is nice. Let's go out.
Thank you for coming into my life.
I prepared something.
Ta-da…
This isn't it.
Well, what can we do?
It's for VIPs.
You're right.
Let's hop on.
Look at that.
Let's make a short stop.
There?
This is great.
You said that about 100 times.
But it really is great.
The full moon! Make a wish.
All done?
Yes.
This is wonderful.
What did you wish for on the moon?
That I would always be
as happy as I am now.
Is this good enough for you?
You should've wished for more.
Then what did you wish for?
Me? Nothing.
Why not?
There's nothing more to ask for.
I have you with me.
I don't need anything else.
Oh, but I did say a word of gratitude
for giving me someone so precious.
Thank you.
I love you, Sa-rang.
I love you too.
KING THE LAND
The guest list for the
100th-anniversary event isn't finalized.
Yes it is.
I just need to make a final decision.
Invite the people on that list.
It's my responsibility,
so I'll do whatever I want.
It must be fun playing the hero.
It hurts.
Are you going to leave Won be?
By any chance…
did you ask him about your mom?
I'm sure he'd know.
Subtitle translation by: Eun-sook Yoon