Look at all these leaves!
Whoa!
Wait, what's going on?
Oh no! It won't go back in!
It's heading over
there! It can't get under!
So noisy.
They always come out more when it rains.
Holy cow!
It's a mole! Look,
it's eating a worm! Whoa!
Can't you guys clean the
yard a bit more quietly?
Oh, Shizuka-san, I'm so sorry.
- No, it's...
- Honestly.
We were having so
much fun, I just lost track...
What are you doing here, Sawada-san?
I was just passing by after shopping.
And then?
"I saw poor Saku-chan being bossed around by
you, and I just couldn't stand by and watch."
So you came to help
him out, right, Chizu-chan?
- Chizu-chan...?
- That's right, Saku-chan.
- Saku-chan...
- If we have to do it anyway,
we might as well have a good time.
Right?
You two are something else...
Shizuka-san, you look tired too.
Why don't we all have some tea?
I'm in!
No, I'm fine...
- Come on, don't be shy.
- What do you mean, "don't be shy"?
- This is my house.
- There, there.
Then I'll help myself.
These are delicious. They're my favorite.
- Wow, Chizu-chan, these are great!
- Right?
Where did you get them?
At a place over in Komaba.
- There's a bakery right next to the fruit stand.
- Uh-huh.
- They make them there. Good, aren't they?
- So good.
I like this heart-shaped one.
The red is cute, isn't it?
- It is.
- I like this one.
So you don't like the heart, then.
(Minoru Kuji: Arriving tomorrow at 2 PM)
So he's finally coming...
Hey.
I should probably get going...
Kuji.
Yeah?
No, I mean...
It's a bit early, but I'm heading out.
Oh.
See ya.
I have to make dinner
for my sister tonight.
In that case,
want to take some
leftovers from the fridge?
That would be a huge help.
Well, I'd love to say yes,
but she gave me a very specific list
of what to buy and what to cook.
She's quite the capable sister.
Honestly, she just doesn't trust me.
Well...
That's probably true.
Ouch. You didn't have to agree so fast.
You two really get along well.
Hey.
What's your brother like?
He's two years older than me.
Straight-A student,
star athlete.
Works for a major corporation.
Lives in Boston now with his wife and kid.
He's basically the perfect human being.
Wow.
He sounds impressive.
You should get going.
It's getting late.
Right.
See you later...
Are you okay?
Huh?
As long as you're doing alright.
This guy never changes.
Just like back then.
Are you okay?
What?
And what about me?
How am I doing?
Ah.
You look much better now.
"Life In Smokey Blue"
(Episode 4: Self-Awareness)
(Career Path Survey)
A career path survey, huh?
Is it that time already?
We're only juniors.
I honestly have no idea what I want to do.
It's normal to be worried.
I was stressed out of my mind back then.
Hey.
How did you decide what
to do after graduation?
Well...
No good.
I have absolutely no recollection.
That's not helpful at all.
I'll tell you if I remember.
I'll ask Kuji for you next time, too.
That might be good.
Thanks.
Crap.
I'm gonna be late for my club.
- Good luck.
- I'm off!
See ya.
Higher education, huh...
I should probably...
Thinking about where
my life is going at 38...
I wonder what Kuji thinks.
When he looks at what lies ahead,
does he feel anxious too?
Welcome.
It's been a long time.
Long time no see.
Good to see you, Minoru, Hazuki-san.
Eno-chan, do you remember me?
Sorry for the sudden visit
after being out of touch for so long.
Every time we're back in
the country, it's a whirlwind.
- Here, for you.
- Thank you.
Please, come in.
Eno-chan, you can wear these.
Thank you.
- Is this Grandpa's house?
- Yeah.
Are we staying here tonight?
Of course not.
Daddy booked a really nice hotel for us.
It even has a pool.
A pool!
Let's go swimming later.
That's amazing, Eno-chan.
You can swim already?
I'm not that good yet...
What are you talking
about? That's not true.
You worked so hard to
learn the freestyle, didn't you?
Daddy thinks you're the
best swimmer in the world.
You worked hard because
- Daddy was cheering for you, right?
- Yeah!
Compared to my brilliant brother,
I've always felt inferior.
Eno, the grown-ups
have things to talk about.
Want to go on an adventure?
Okay!
That sounds like a plan. Go ahead.
The garden is just around that corner.
I haven't been back here
since Dad's funeral two years ago.
Yeah.
Still the same dark,
gloomy house.
Ugh.
It smells like cigarettes
and moldy old books.
What are you going to do with all these?
It'll cost a fortune
just to clear them out.
I doubt any university
would take them these days.
Leaving stuff like this behind
is just a burden on everyone else.
Minoru.
I can't even breathe in here.
Damn it, what's wrong with this thing?
Let me try.
You have to do it like this.
Lift it up a bit before you slide it.
I've never seen this view before...
Daddy!
Hey.
Eno.
What kind of house do
you want to live in here?
Hmm... a white house!
Alright.
Then right here,
let's build a big, white house.
A burden, huh...
When I was a child,
in this room where I
wasn't even allowed to enter,
we sat together and
wove words into stories.
That's where I learned
what it meant to "work."
Living with my father...
This was the only place
where he would finally look me in the eye.
How did the talk with the lawyer go?
No major issues.
Shizuka agreed to everything.
We can handle the rest online
once I'm back in Boston.
That's good.
Sorry for dragging you
along for all this today.
You must be exhausted, Hazuki.
Not at all.
I wanted to pay my respects to
your parents. I'm glad we could come.
I see.
I guess so.
Are you okay?
Hmm?
What do you mean?
I don't know... you just seem a little off.
Being back here...
it's always painful.
Why is it painful?
Because ever since we were kids,
Dad only ever had eyes for Shizuka.
Back in elementary school,
Shizuka was always at the library,
bringing home mountains of books.
Dad would see that and just beam with joy.
He'd say things like,
"You're really something else, aren't you?"
But even when I was top of my class,
or when I won swimming competitions,
he never even looked at me.
Today,
I was reminded of that all over again.
That room with the beautiful view...
In the end, he never once let me inside.
Minoru...
And I know it's not Shizuka's fault...
Memories etched
into the pillars,
into the walls,
into the floors.
In every single corner of this house.
- Thanks for having us.
- See you later!
Goodbye.
Next time we see each
other, we'll be moving back.
Make sure you find a new place by then.
Yeah.
Alright, see ya.
- Shizuka...
- Minoru...
No...
Never mind. It's nothing.
What about you?
Safe travels...
Ah.
Thanks.
Scars of our own.
Coming in!
What is it?
What do you mean, "what is it"?
I'm finished with today's work.
Here, take a look.
Did you actually check it yourself first?
Of course I did, Shizuka.
I'll look at it.
Oh.
By the way,
that book I reserved...
could you go pick it up for me?
Sure, sure.
Oh, this one...
Looks interesting.
I'm back.
I'm home.
That bookstore was way out there.
What now? I thought you
said work was over for the day.
- I just finished checking it.
- And?
- Yeah, it's fine.
- See?
Here.
Oh, and this too.
Thanks for the hard work.
Closing the family grave?
It seems to be happening more often lately.
When there's no one
left to look after them,
families decide to relocate the remains.
Times are changing, I guess.
Wait a second.
Do you really need to
report every single thing?
Is it a relative?
No.
But, well...
I've been visiting the grave every year.
Huh?
Yoshie Kimitsu...
Was that the doctor you
worked with as a rep?
It was Dr. Kimitsu.
I see...
He must have been a very kind doctor,
always putting his patients first.
Yeah.
His motto was always
"Everything for the patient."
He always put himself last.
Even when he was so busy he barely slept,
he would still take the time
to really listen to someone like me.
That's truly rare.
A doctor like that...
Because I respected him so much,
it really hit me hard back then.
Are you okay?
What?
But back then,
I couldn't even let myself feel sad.
At the time,
I couldn't face my own weakness.
In these past eight years,
have I grown at all?
Who knows.
At the very least,
I'm able to let myself feel sad now.
I see.
This guy hasn't changed a bit.
Ever since then,
even when he knows exactly what's going on,
he just pretends he doesn't
and quietly stays by my side.
Thank you.
For back then,
and for now.
You're being way too
honest. It's creeping me out.
I knew you'd say that.
I can't believe you remember
all that stuff from so long ago.
Wait... do you actually
like me or something?
Yeah, I guess I do.
Oh, so that's how it is.
That's funny.
Etched away, bit by bit,
everyone's emotions
remain here in this house.
(Next Episode)
If you go back right now,
Kuji's going to be lonely.
Then I'll stay for a bit.
You're exaggerating.
Winter...?
That's unusual.
Once this glossary is finished,
I'm thinking of quitting.