(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
[Disclaimer:
All depicted events are fictional
and for entertainment purposes only;
viewer discretion is advised]
[Love Upon a Time Series]
After all,
we shall soon be family.
He's about to get married.
Complete the mission and return home.
You'd be better off
quitting the game before it starts, Nakun!
My Lord,
what flower might this be?
My Lord...
Master Klao.
Come now, Master.
You behave like a mere child,
inviting me to play at hide-and-seek.
What are you... gazing at so intently?
Come on!
Oh? Is that...
Meow.
A grumpy cat.
A cat?
Does your manor also house a cat, my Lord?
Indeed, a Khao Manee cat,
pure white from head to tail.
It is at times quite affectionate,
yet at others remarkably playful.
Why am I so emotional and jealous of her?
He doesn't like me. He likes Klao.
I can't afford to fall for him.
Although back at the temple,
Klao's story really resonated with me.
When the fortune teller
talked about Klao's spirit, I even cried.
So what's going on?
Let us be on our way, Lady Varna.
I fear High Lord Soontrapinit
has been awaiting us in vain.
Yes, my Lord.
Master.
What?
May we set forth now?
Why?
Whoa!
What seems to be the matter here?
Uh...
Exercise.
Lesson one.
Up, down, up, down, up, and down.
Allow me to demonstrate.
[Love Upon a Time Series]
Lady Varna
possesses exquisite grace
and refined conduct,
which together form
the very essence of a lady.
Truly, she is most suited
to stand by Phop's side.
- Father.
- Hm?
What about you, Dear Klao?
Have you set your sights
upon any particular lady?
Well, I...
I...
Answer when an elder inquires.
Do not make her wait.
I have yet to set my sights upon any.
Then you must hasten to do so.
You, too, should see to it that
you are properly wed without further delay
before committing yourself
to royal service;
only then shall you be
a man of true credibility.
Royal... service?
What?
You spoke to me of your desire
to enter royal service, even as your father did.
Now that you are fully recovered,
return to your studies
with renewed diligence.
I shall arrange for a master
to guide your studies.
I can guide him, Father.
You crazy guy!
Why did you tell him that?
Very well.
He has already come of age at twenty.
He can no longer afford to
idle his time away so aimlessly.
I entrust you to guide Dear Klao
in all that he ought to know.
Understood, Father.
Committing to royal service,
like Klao's father did?
Why didn't Phop object to his father
about Klao's marriage,
even though he seems into Klao?
Maybe...
Bromance?
Or...
He hasn't realized it yet?
He's bisexual?
Or...
He hasn't come out yet?
If you intend to study,
why have you not sought the study hall?
I have brought you
these volumes of knowledge.
What were you writing just now?
Hey, hey!
Can you not? This one is private!
Have I become a stranger to you?
Am I not being clear? I said no!
Why do you turn away from me?
Is your heart troubled on account of Varna?
No, it isn't.
If so, what then brought you to the garden,
Grumpy Cat?
I was out for a walk,
stretching as I went.
Why?
Are there rules
in this manor that say
I'm not allowed to take a walk
in the garden?
Let it be so.
I shall take your word for it.
Let us now commence your studies.
I can't read any of this.
I think...
Phop, can we learn something else first?
Is this what you wish to learn?
How odd.
You once rowed with the speed
of a flying spear.
You keep saying
I once did this and that.
Things aren't the same anymore, are they?
This isn't the same person, you know?
Deep and steady.
Then lift it upward.
Do not merely skim the surface.
Remember to alternate your strokes.
That's enough. I can row it myself.
Yet you told me to guide you.
You did,
so you should let me try it myself.
This will show how good a mentor you are.
- Hey! Let go!
- Klao, be still,
- lest you capsize the boat.
- Then hands off!
Hey.
Hey!
Let go! Let it go!!
Hands off. Come on.
Be still, Klao!
Phop?
Phop...
Phop!
Phop, don't do this.
This isn't funny.
Phop...
Phop.
Phop! Phop!
Phop!
Phop!!
Phop... Come on,
tell me you're gonna be fine.
Where are you? Phop!
Phop?
Where are you?
Phop!
Phop!!
I am right here.
Phop!
Phop!!
I am more than pleased.
Why are you pleased?
You...
Were you pulling my leg?
I was worried sick about you!
That is why I am pleased.
My concern for you is not unrequited.
[What is this feeling?]
If I can't beat this feeling,
why not just embrace it?
Swoosh!
Whoa.
Whoa...
Did people in the past spar
the way we go to the gym
or work out in the park?
- Argh!
- Whoa!
Ha!
Ow!
Klao,
do kindly come
and enjoy this with me.
Kaew? You're here, too?
You like watching sword fighting?
Not quite.
I am merely here out of concern for Jom.
- Ha!
Whoa!
Whoa...
Alas.
Blood...
Step back. Leave me be.
He never ceases to reprimand me.
Well, Thee is...
I mean, the Physician
is worried about you, Pun.
I mean, Kaew.
You might get hurt while they're sparring.
How would you know, Klao?
Such is his way.
Whenever I try to draw close to Jom,
he invariably pushes me away.
You guys are the same.
Hm?
Oh...
I have friends in Phichit.
They are similar to you...
and the Physician.
The closer one gets,
the further the other pulls away.
Mm...
A bilabial stop
is a sound produced by blocking
airflow with both lips,
such as /b/ and /p/.
That's correct.
And...
what about this sound?
Is it considered one?
Let's continue, Nakun.
What are the alveolar consonants?
Sounds produced with the tongue
close to the alveolar ridge.
Such as
S, Z, L,
N, D, and
- T.
- Yes, Pun?
So you've given me a nickname now?
You're starting to fall for me, aren't you?
He didn't call you.
He was talking to me.
If I write it like this in IPA,
can you read it?
Here it is.
[I like you, you know?]
Thee.
My lips are parched.
Yes, Pun.
A cup of pure matcha,
no sugar!
Thee
is always so clingy to Pun that
he's like a puppy following a pretty face.
His mindset is this:
"Constant dripping wears away the stone."
However, it's not wearing away at all.
It won't budge.
I never imagined that we should sit together,
sharing laughter once more,
even though I have not
the slightest inkling of what you said.
But...
I just want to say
it's not like he despises you or anything.
If he were,
he wouldn't let you follow him around.
Maybe
he's just shy,
or maybe
in this day and age it's not acceptable...
That's why he can't accept your love.
Come now!
I am a man.
How can I give my heart
to one such as myself?
That's fine.
I can tell.
I listen; I don't judge.
Uh, Kaew...
Phop isn't taken?
I mean...
He has not yet taken a spouse?
Or do you think
he likes men,
like you do?
Klao!
You must not speak of him so before others.
So...
he's into men?
That I do not know.
As the rumors go,
Lord Phop
resembles a war elephant
whose strength
is already spent before the first strike.
Uh...
A flame without a spark.
A flag that will not fly.
A sword gone dull.
Noodles without broth.
A songbird gone silent.
A man bereft of his vigor.
That's enough.
Phop...
Despite looking that strong,
his little guy doesn't work?
His brother, do you mean?
He is yet too small.
He cannot undertake any real work.
His is too small?
Too small.
His is small.
Klao!
Ahem!
Klao,
I should like to see
the swordplay of Phichit.
Pray, let me see your art.
- Ow!
- Master Klao.
- Klao.
- Klao?
- Klao?!
- Argh!
- Klao!
- Klao.
Master Klao.
Master Klao!
Fetch him the herbal remedy at once.
The Buddha, the Dhamma, the Sangha...
What ails Master now?
Physician, I beseech you,
lend us your cure.
His internal elements seem stable.
He must be brought to my manor
for closer examination.
Master Klao.
I'm fine.
I just felt a bit uncomfortable.
I need to get some rest.
Wait for me, Master.
Physician, I pray you,
follow him and see to his well-being.
It was but a fleeting ache.
Seeing how he now strides so effortlessly,
there is no cause for concern.
I suspect he was simply too slothful
for swordplay and thus feigned illness.
However, I believe...
it would be best to conduct
a thorough examination once more.
Why such concern?
His condition is far from grave.
When you were whispering and laughing with him,
he appeared perfectly content,
without a trace of illness.
Since when have I shared such jests?
Throughout the entirety of the sparring.
You ought to take up the blade yourself,
that you may safeguard
your wife and children.
Stay out of my affairs. I have never harbored
any desire for a wife or children.
What is wrong with him?
Do you truly not know,
or are you merely feigning ignorance?
The feelings between you and Dear Kaew
are plain as day.
Do not seek to conceal them.
I harbor no feelings for him whatsoever,
only annoyance.
My good Physician,
we cannot know for how long
those who stand beside us
shall remain.
The morrow might bring a parting
we never foresaw.
Once before, I nearly lost
all that I held dear.
I know too well the agony it brings.
I wish for such sorrow
never to strike again,
neither upon myself
nor upon my friend.
Don't get sidetracked.
Continue the mission.
Klao was killed.
This might be the real mission:
who killed Klao?
Mother, Lady Varna,
where did you find such blossoms?
Their fragrance fills the air.
I have only just learned of
Lady Varna's renowned skill
in the art of traditional potpourri.
So exceptional was her craft that
she once served the High Lord of Lopburi himself.
It is said that the craft of perfumery
demands the utmost meticulousness.
As such, your skill
must truly be of the finest order.
You are most kind with your words, my Lord.
I was utterly charmed by the fragrance,
so I entreated her to come
and craft more for us.
We shall soon craft a fragrance
for your pleasure, Phop.
Kindly join me and choose the scent.
I leave the choice to you, Mother.
Having just practiced with the blade,
I must wash
before attending to my duties
with the patrol.
It seems he cares little for me, does he?
Do not speak thus, Lady Varna.
Who could fail to admire one
so fair and accomplished as you?
I believe
he is merely indifferent
to such trifling matters.
Yes, my Lady.
For all his stern demeanor,
the truth is that
Phop is merely a bashful soul.
Pray, do make an effort to visit
our manor more often, Lady Varna,
and we shall become better acquainted.
But...
would such a thing be seemly, my Lady?
Of course.
Should anyone inquire,
say I have asked for your presence
to instruct me in perfumery.
And should there be any malicious gossip,
inform me at once.
I shall deal with it accordingly.
Then I am most willing, my Lady.
Aunt...
Lady Varna...
Can you teach me how to make potpourri?
This is rather a surprise.
I never once imagined
you would take an interest in
such domestic crafts, Dear Klao.
I thought you preferred
your scrolls and volumes.
Well...
I want to make myself useful,
given a chance.
Perhaps I might further
endear myself to you.
My!
My heart is already
so full of fondness for you, Dear Klao.
Oh, you...
Does your stomach no longer trouble you?
Oh...
It has subsided, Phop.
That's why I'm out here with Aunt.
What a relief.
Then I must take my leave for patrol.
Understood.
I must bid you farewell for now, Mother
and Lady Varna.
What's next,
Lady Varna?
Uh...
It is done this way, Klao.
Yes! He's finally gone.
Uh...
The flowers Phop favors
are nowhere to be found here.
But Aunt said
he does not favor such trifling matters.
How come?
Phop
just asked me to fetch him flowers
by the manor
and bring them to his room.
Their fragrance filled the air.
With that said,
let me pick some more flowers for him.
Yes, I've finally made it out!
My plan is working:
wait for Phop to go on patrol, sneak to
the market, and return before he catches me!
Let's complete the mission and return home!
I refuse to be stuck here
just to get married.
Kong!
What are you doing here?
And what of you, Master?
What brings you to this place?
Might you be going to that place?
"That place"?
What do you mean?
Good heavens, there is no need to keep
such secrets from me, Master.
We both know
you visit that place most often,
the House of Pleasure
at the farthest end of the market.
"The House of Pleasure"? A brothel?!
Klao often went to the market
for this place?!
Master Klao,
allow me to accompany you.
I beg of you, Master.
Sure thing.
Let's go.
Yes!
Let's go, shall we?
Yes, Master Klao...
Alright!
Master Klao, I am unable to swim.
It's fine.
Swim after my boat, okay?
Uh... Master...
Be wary.
Thank you.
A multicultural market! Feels like the ones in
Khaosan Road, Pattaya, and Patpong.
No wonder Klao loved coming to this place.
Oh!
I'm sorry, sir.
Uh, excuse me.
This place...
What is this market called?
It is known as a canal market.
You must have only just arrived
from the countryside.
Okay, I'm at the right place,
but where's the brothel?
I hope Kong was just spitting nonsense.
Klao was heartbroken over his father's affair.
He probably didn't enjoy the brothel, did he?
The sweets remain untouched.
He has certainly not set foot in the kitchen.
- Is he not in his bed?!
- Is he not in the garden?!
I searched far and wide,
but he was nowhere to be found.
Argh!
How utterly dim-witted!
A wrong husband,
and a lifetime's regret.
Regret, I say!
The cane shall leave your back
like a tiger's pelt!
I have no interest in sharing
the punishment.
- You fool. What an utter fool.
- Sai! What have I done wrong?
I could not find him anywhere.
Nor could I!
Are you in search of Master Klao?
Do you know Master's whereabouts?
The House of Pleasure.
Gasp!
Good heavens!
Everything has gone to ruin!
A delightful taste.
- Sweet and wonderful.
- You.
You there.
You!
Are you talking to me?
Aha!
Yes.
I am talking to you,
Master Klao.
Where have you been all this time?
I was led to believe your heart
had strayed to another favored place.
This way, this way.
If you would, this way.
Hey!
Hey! Pray, help me!
Too high.
Oh, my.
Master Klao.
Today...
We have the Seven-Headed,
Three-Clawed Dragon herbal liquor.
It relieves body pain
and soreness and helps you sleep well.
Goodness. Were you to taste this,
its potency would far surpass
even that of the Dragon...
The Dragon... That one...
The Dragon Horse, Seared by Fire.
Aha.
Here...
Here it is.
I'd rather not.
I have no taste for herbal liquor.
No taste for herbal liquor?
Last time you had half a jar.
If you did,
I daresay you'd take the whole pot.
Well, I prefer...
Soju!
Jjan!
"Jjan"?
Huh?
Like "jangle"?
So the rumor that
Master Klao has gone mad
is true?
Excuse me.
What is this yellow fruit?
Uh...
This... No, no.
Not that one,
the yellow one.
How much for the yellow fruit?
Oh, God. How fortunate.
Do you speak English, sir?
- A little bit?
- Yellow?
Come again? Yes, the yellow fruit?
Yellow... Mango.
Mango?
I'll have the mango, please.
How much for the yellow mango?
Yellow!
Five...
I'll have five yellow mangoes, please.
How much?
Five? Okay.
I'll give the money to you,
and you give the money to her, okay?
I'll give it to you, you give it to her,
and I'll take the fruit.
Well, I do bid thee a very good day,
and thank thee
for thy kindness, my Lord.
Farewell.
Yellow. Mango.
You are truly gifted, my Lord.
You can even speak
the tongue of the Farangi.
I owe it all to my most esteemed mentor.
I mean no intrusion, my Lord,
yet I cannot help but notice
your cheerful disposition today.
A certain someone has graced my manor with
the scent of potpourri, awaiting my return.
Yellow.
Mango.
Are you intrigued?
That was close.
So, do people here misunderstand Klao or not?
I thought he was heartbroken about his father,
but no, he's simply a sad baddie.
So his visit to the brothel means...
Do I really have to
learn the truth there myself?
Uh, excuse me.
Is this The House...
Master Klao!
Where have you been these many days?
Pim has been murmuring your name
from dawn till dusk.
Come, let us depart, Master Klao.
Pim?
Mother!
Master Klao has returned!
I'm not here to enjoy myself, by the way.
I'm not here to have a good time, okay?
I'm not here to have fun, okay?
♫The flower blooms, its petals unfold,♫
♫String upon string, in layers untold,♫
♫Layers untold,♫
♫By the pool of grace♫
♫The bees caress and gently entwine,♫
♫Their voices echo in a melody divine♫
Your absence has been long indeed.
A very warm welcome back to
the Pavilion of Affection, Master.
Upon your return,
you seem somewhat troubled, Master.
Kindly step inside and allow the maidens
to see to your comfort
and ease your worries.
This way, Master.
Long has your absence been, Master Klao.
We have missed you near unto heartbreak.
It is so, Master.
Pim is occupied today,
so I shall attend to
your comfort myself, Master.
- Or perhaps I might attend to you instead.
- Heavens, you lot!
He has but just returned, weary and worn;
cease this dallying at once.
Master Klao,
pray step into the receiving room.
- Let us make our way.
- I...
I shall go
and fetch Pim for you presently, Master.
Let us be on our way.
Is it too late to turn back?
But I won't get any clues if I do, right?
I don't dislike you guys or anything, but...
Phop, help me!
Has Dear Klao finished preparing
the potpourri yet?
My Lord,
the fault is mine alone.
Uh... Hi, Pim.
Long time no see.
I miss you.
By the way,
when was the last time we met?
And what did I do?
I am
Puang, Master.
Truly, it has been so long
that you have forgotten my face.
Indeed,
a man's tongue is woven of deceit.
Shall we remain quiet, then?
We might as well wait
until the candles have melted away entirely.
For, regardless...
I remain a stranger in your memories.
Uh...
Well, I...
I've lost my memory.
Truly?
Truly.
Certainly?
Certainly.
For what reason
do you neglect your treatment
to come to me instead, Master Klao?
That's a very good point.
I'm here to see thee...
I mean, you...
Yeah, you...
Why am I here again?
Why did I come here?
Indeed, why?
This is
the House of Pleasure.
What brings
a gentleman such as yourself
to a place like this, Master Klao?
No... Please, no...
You have quite forgotten me.
We
have never engaged in such conduct.
Your only intent was to sit with me
and visit me.
Uh, I...
I was only here to talk to you?
Indeed.
You were here simply to speak with me.
Never once have you
overstepped your bounds.
Why?
And...
how did we get to know each other?
I wasn't here to have fun?
No, Master.
You have simply held me in your fond regard
because...
upon our very first encounter,
I was...
Where on earth is Pim?! Huh?!
- Uh...
- Speak!
Well...
So it is you, Klao.
You have snatched her away from me.
You were well aware I had claimed her,
yet you dared slight me thus.
So what of it?
I have never allowed anyone to claim me.
As Master Klao reached me first,
my presence is his.
- Let us return inside.
- You shall not go!
Curse you, Sopha. I told you, did I not?
Pim is mine, and mine alone.
How dare you let anyone else have her!
You...
You said you would go
to the outlying cities.
Yet I have returned, have I not?
Hand over Pim.
Now.
No.
Pim.
Come to me this instant!
Be quick!
Damn you!
Stay out of this!
Do you have a death wish, Klao? Huh?!
Cease this at once!!
Dear Klao.
For what purpose have you come here?
I...
Sopha,
see them inside.
Yes, my Lord.
Make haste...
Make haste.
Now!
Come.
Cherd.
Come with me at once.
Dear Klao,
return to your manor,
lest Lord Phop worry for you.
If Klao does not leave,
then neither shall I.
Cherd.
Stay here if you want so damn much.
Damn, Phop's probably already back
at the manor!
Why should I be afraid of him
being upset with me?
I'll hit back if he gets upset.
But it's getting dark,
so I have no choice but to head back.
Take shelter from the rain with me, child.
Child, come here.
It's okay. I'm fine.
Come in here, or you may fall ill, child.
- Thank you.
- Pray do not fall ill now.
I can wait no longer.
Kong, ready the vessel.
Phop,
the rain is falling.
To set sail now would be perilous.
He lacks experience in handling a boat.
Would that not be a far greater risk?
By now, Phop must be terribly worried.
Hold on a second.
Uncle.
Uncle!
Uncle!!
Uh... Uncle.
I mean, sir...
I can't handle a boat very well.
Can you escort me to my manor?
♫Still thinking of you and only you♫
♫The thought of your tears
is what frightens me♫
♫Wishing rains and skies
never take your smile away♫
Phop, I'm sorry.
Master Klao has been out in the scorching sun,
watching over you all day, my Lord.
By evening, he began to lapse
into delirium, as you see.
I have made myself clear.
I see you only as a brother.
I could never feel otherwise.
I ought not to have fallen for you.
Phop!
- What is the matter?!
- I had a nightmare.
Tonight,
might you share my bed?
♫Still thinking of you and only you♫
♫The thought of your tears
is what frightens me♫
♫Wishing rains and skies
never take your smile away♫
♫Every plea I make, please let it reach you♫
♫Don't leave this heart
lost in worry and plea♫
♫Please take care of it for me♫
[Love Upon a Time Series]