[muffled club music playing]
[footsteps approaching]
Are you Diana?
[door creaking]
[door closes]
You the one Ivan sent?
Yeah.
[envelope rustling]
[club music continues playing]
[Morgan inhales]
-Oh, it's all there.
-Says who?
You? I don't know you.
Okay, says Ivan.
Who says I trust Ivan?
I don't trust
my own fucking granddaughter.
She's a liar.
Okay.
[Diana] Hmm.
[Morgan clears throat]
[envelope rustling]
[whispers] Thank you.
In the future, never hand over the money
till you see what you're buying.
It's a dead giveaway you're new at this.
It's all there, sweetheart?
Why? You got somewhere to be?
[chuckles]
Maybe.
Now click your heels together three times
and get the fuck out of my hair.
Okay.
[Diana] I like your attitude, though.
[club music playing]
[music continues playing]
[indistinct chattering]
[playfully] Hey.
Hi.
Um…
I'm so sorry, I'm not here for that.
I am. So can you show me some respect?
Yeah, of-- of course.
I just don't have any cash on me.
So I jus-- I just didn't want to engage
without the cash.
Unless you take Zelle.
I'm just waiting on my sister
who's dropping off an application. So…
-[heels clicking]
-Wow. Unbelieva--
-[Morgan] Time check?
-Yeah.
Um… Six minutes.
Okay. I told you, you didn't have to
worry for ten. That's four under.
What a skill, Morgan. Congratulations.
Can we leave?
It smells like bleach in here.
-Okay, yeah. Sure.
-[Nicky] Okay.
[doors squeaking]
[both exhale]
You know, for a second there,
I was actually thinking about doing it.
You do understand you can't just sit
at the bottom of the pole
begging people for money, right?
You have to, like, work at it.
I don't know.
I feel like I'm getting good at this.
Running errands for a strange Russian man?
-Yeah. Kind of.
-Okay, Morgan, for sure.
-That's great.
-All right.
It's 6:00 a.m.
-So I'm gonna just get back to bed.
-You're gonna go? Okay.
-[Nicky] Okay?
-I'm up though.
-Did you want to…
-[Nicky] Huh?
-[Morgan] Do you want to get food?
-No.
[opening theme music playing]
[music ends]
[mouths]
[sheets rustling softly]
[glasses clinking softly]
[exhales]
[Nicky sighs]
[Tareq] Where were you?
-[Nicky] Hmm?
-[Tareq inhales]
Where were you?
[inhales]
I had a parishioner in the hospital
with double pneumonia.
[Tareq] Hmm.
-Who was it?
-Uh…
[smacks lips]
Jessica. Do-- Uh, Jessica's uncle.
Do you-- do you--
-I don't know…
-Hmm.
You might not have… met him.
[whispers] Oh. Go back to bed.
[Nicky inhales]
I've really been enjoying
staying over here the past few nights.
[Nicky exhales]
[whispers] Me too.
You're worried she's been judging us?
I like to think she's pretty progressive.
This is the most fun she's had in years.
[Nicky exhales]
Why is it that religion has such a problem
with two people
who are in love with each other?
[inhales]
[smacks lips]
[whispers] Because God is perfect,
but the people who interpret him are not.
[chuckles softly]
-So you're just gonna leave me hanging--
-[laughs]
I'm sorry, did you say something to me?
[Tareq inhales deeply]
[softly] Yeah, I said I love you.
[laughs, inhales deeply]
[grunts, exhales]
[inhales]
[whispers] I love you too.
Now can you promise me you will honor
this moment by having a good day
without twisting it
into some kind of problem?
[Nicky breathes deeply]
You're so much hotter when you're happy.
[snorts]
-Things are good. They're good.
-[exhales]
[inhales] Gnarly rash, gone.
-Why did you bring the rash into this?
-[laughs]
We were having such a nice… moment.
[Tareq] Oh, come here. [kissing]
[both laughing]
[funky music playing]
[objects rustling]
[drawer opens]
[drawer closes]
[mouths] Fuck.
[exhales] Okay.
[breathes deeply]
[music stops abruptly]
[box thuds]
[music resumes]
[marker squeaking]
-[door slams]
-[music ends]
[Nicky] Sure you wanna keep these?
They're her high school yearbooks.
[Linda] Nicholas,
do you want to keep them?
Because I have to check out
in half an hour.
This is like a hotel
for people circling the drain.
-Okay.
-This is what she wanted.
She wasn't attached to anything.
She was a very unromantic,
practical woman.
Okay. I mean, she wanted the necklace.
What necklace?
The necklace she was buried in.
-She wanted that.
-Oh, she didn't care about that.
That was more for me.
I wanted her to have something nice.
Donate.
[loud thud]
[whispers] Holy shit.
[soft thud]
Uh…
[paper rustling]
I don't know.
An old box of tennis ticket stubs?
Oh, she would want Dina to have those.
Let's set those aside for Dina Caputo.
Sorry, you don't want anything,
but you want Dina Caputo
to have an old box of tennis ticket stubs?
It was just something
that they did together.
-I have long suspected…
-Okay.
…that your grandmother was a lesbian.
Excuse me?
And that she and Dina would have been
together if things had been different.
Dina's had that haircut her entire life.
-I saw them holding hands once.
-What?
I think that's why
she was so difficult to deal with.
Dad died so young, she never remarried,
and I think it was because
she was in love with Dina Caputo. Trash.
[Nicky scoffs]
Avoiding intimacy for such a long time
can really harden a person, hon,
to the point where you fear
any semblance of softness.
The truth is, everybody deserves
love and a good sex life.
Yeah, I mean, you know.
I know it's been a while since Dad,
but you… you are
more than welcome to date.
-There's nothing stopping you from that.
-I was talking about you.
-Me?
-You think I'm a hard woman?
No, I don't.
You-- You think I'm a hard person?
I think that you have made
some very selfless decisions in your life,
but if I'm being honest,
sometimes I get scared
that your closest relationship
is with God.
And don't take this the wrong way, honey,
but God isn't touching
your body for pleasure.
All right, Ma. I… I--
No, honey, I know
that it's a sacred relationship,
but you know what I'm… talking about.
[sighs]
I mean, yeah, I do, but…
I have a lot of relationships
that I'm grateful for in my life, okay?
I'm… I'm choosing… happiness.
You know? So you…
you don't need to worry about me.
Okay, well, that's good.
I just felt like
I had to say that out loud.
And you did. So…
And I do have sex, Nicholas.
All right, I don't need
to hear about that.
No, I do. No. But I'm glad
that I come across as some spinster
who tucks herself into bed
and says a prayer and goes to sleep.
-I think you're reading into something.
-I am not my mother.
-Well, all right.
-[knocking on door]
Hi, Mrs. Morelli.
Uh, I just wanted to check in and see
if you had any idea about your ETD.
I do not.
I will come get you when we're finished,
and I would have killed for
this level of attentiveness
when my mother was actually in this room.
Okay.
-[door creaks, closes]
-Jesus Christ.
What?
-What? What are you looking at?
-Nothing. I'm not looking at anything.
-What are you thinking?
-I'm not thinking anything.
-No, I know. Turn it off.
-Okay.
I have my first debate this afternoon.
I have been under
a tremendous amount of stress.
So that's a very different situation.
Yeah. Soft.
Trash.
[objects clatter]
[Max] She's just mean…
[car passing]
…for no reason.
And some of the times,
I think it's kind of hot.
In like a "pain is pleasure" kind of way.
But some of the times, you know,
I just, like, wish that it was easier.
Well, how am I supposed
to tell the difference?
Is that a real question or a reaction?
I don't know. Both.
I mean, he's calling me mean.
I feel the need to defend myself.
[therapist] Defend yourself.
Would you describe the current state
of your relationship as, uh, combative?
-No.
-Fuck, yeah. [scoffs]
[sighs] I would describe it as me having
opinions and Max throwing tantrums.
-[scoffs]
-When you use words like "tantrum,"
can you see how that can be perceived
as an attack on Max?
-Thank you.
-[sighs]
Yeah, you, like, push me for no reason.
Stop saying that. I--
It's not for no reason.
I'm pushing you because maybe deep down,
right, I am waiting for you to push back,
and you never do.
And it is so unattractive.
Like, I want you to get mad.
I'm an only child, Morgan.
I didn't grow up in some
emotional war zone like you did, okay?
This is all that I know.
So if that's unattractive to you, fine.
Trust me, you can be very unattractive
to me sometimes too.
Okay, see, this is what I'm talking about.
-What are you talking about?
-You sticking up for yourself!
Oh! Oh, you want me to talk
to you like this all the time?
-Yell and scream?
-Not all the time! Maybe sometimes.
-I am so bored a lot of the time. And--
-Oh my God.
-Bored. I'm boring. Oh, I'm boring.
-I'm not saying you're boring!
-I'm a boring boyfriend.
-I didn't say you were boring.
Okay! Okay!
This is good.
But I think we have to bottle this feeling
between you two in a way that's…
Well, it's not this.
Look, relationships are supposed to be
a safe place.
And, Morgan, perhaps
if you're looking to be challenged,
finding outlets outside the relationship
might allow for more…
patience and warmth with Max, which…
It's a different kind of excitement.
I just want you to look at me
the way that you used to look at me.
I want that too.
Okay, when she ended things
after high school and moved to New York,
I thought, "Wow,
what a fucking bitch." Right?
But also, like, "There goes the most
interesting person I've ever met."
[exhales] You're saying it like
it's like I did something special.
New York is, like,
a 30-minute train ride from here.
Okay, but people don't just
do that, Morgan.
They don't just, like, oh, leave home
to go pursue their dreams.
[sighs] Yeah--
Then I didn't book any jobs
and I ran out of money, so, yeah…
Who fucking cares?
Who cares?
You have all these worldly experiences.
I want to experience
something worldly with you
that isn't just my mom taking us to Cabo.
-We should go to fucking Burning Man.
-[cell phone ringing]
We're not gonna go to Burning Man,
but I get what you're saying, you know?
Like, I understand. I'm so sorry.
I'm just gonna step out for one second.
I just have to take this,
but I'm-- I'm really sorry.
-[ringing continues]
-I think you both want the same things.
[funky music playing]
[Morgan] Okay, what is up with you?
What do you mean?
Uh, I don't know. Something is off.
You-- you haven't complained once.
You're borderline pleasant.
I'm having a nice day, okay?
I realize that there's no point
in making our situation any worse
than it already is.
We don't actually know
if these people are criminals.
I mean, you know… I… I don't know.
They could just be overextended
and needing a few extra hands.
That's…
We are driving to pick up a stranger
from prison. Are you okay?
-I'm leaning into joy today, Morgan.
-[exhales loudly]
I'm trying to have a nice, happy,
meaningful life today.
-[inhales]
-Don't you find it demeaning, though?
That they send us
on these little gofer errands.
It's like they think
we're not capable of more.
We don't want them thinking we're capable
of more, Morgan. Why would we want that?
I don't know. If you're gonna send me
to the strip club, put me on the pole.
-You know?
-I've never had that thought.
[Morgan] And what even is
a medium-security prison?
Like, what do you even have to do
to be "mediumly" secured?
[Nicky] I don't-- I don't care.
-It's a very organized system.
-[guard] Ma'am.
-Pop the trunk.
-Oh.
-[Morgan clears throat]
-Pop the trunk.
[trunk opens]
[Morgan exhales] It's strict here.
[speaking indistinctly over PA]
-Do you have anything in your trunk?
-No.
[trunk closes]
-[Nicky] Is there anything in there?
-[Morgan] No.
-[guard] Ma'am.
-Mm-hmm.
Are you aware that you have six cases
of Four Loko in the trunk of your car?
[sighs loudly]
-What?
-Fucking Max.
-Who drinks that?
-[spluttering] No, I wasn't aware of that.
I can't let you in
with drinks in your trunk.
-[Morgan] Come on.
-I'm gonna have to walk, then.
Uh, no, I'll go. I'll go. I'll do it.
As much as I'd love
to send you into a prison,
Reverend Dardano is supposed to be
picking up an incarcerated parishioner…
-[exhales loudly]
-…he's been counseling, okay? So.
This sucks.
Say a prayer.
Do I have to go around?
[quietly] Hi, I'm here
to take you to your apartment
and offer whatever rehabilitative--
reha-- rehabilitative services…
-[alarm buzzing]
-[gate creaking]
Okay.
[sniffs, clears throat]
[gate creaking]
-[gate clanging]
-[alarm buzzing]
Hello.
Are you… are you Andrei?
Who the fuck are you?
Oh, I'm, um… I'm Pastor Dardano.
I'm here to take you
to your new apartment, um,
and offer whatever rehabilitative services
you would like for your reentry.
Um, do you have
everything you need, or…?
Where's Ivan?
Oh, right. Um…
[whispers] Ivan thought it would be better
if I came to pick you up,
just optically speaking.
-Why are you whispering?
-I don't know.
I'm not quite sure
why I'm whispering, actually.
Where's the car?
Oh, okay, so we couldn't park in here,
so it's just a quick 10 to 15 this way.
-If you want to come with-- Okay.
-[speaking Russian]
[Andrei clears throat]
[tense music playing]
-[Andrei inhales sharply]
-Mm-hmm.
You must be relieved to be out of prison.
-I don't wanna talk!
-Okay.
-[indistinct chattering]
-[camera clicking]
Linda.
Oh, hi. Hi, Annette.
-Hi.
-You look fabulous.
Oh, thank you, Annette. [laughs]
[moderator] All right, everyone,
settle down, please.
-Settle down.
-[door closes]
First of all, I would like to thank
the both of you for being here today.
-Thank you for having us both.
-Of course, glad to be here.
[coughing]
[moderator] All right, well,
let me begin with an easy question
to get things rolling.
What distinguishes each of you
from the other candidate?
-Linda, we'll start with you.
-Yes.
I know-- Thank you for the question, Jane.
I know this town like the back of my hand.
I was born here. Um…
My family has owned Morelli's Hardware
for over 70 years. [laughs]
I raised my kids here,
and I have watched this town grow,
which is why I have a strong desire
to preserve the Glenview
that I know and love
and to restore
a sense of safety and security
that has long been associated with it.
Just last week, my son was assaulted
on the street for being gay.
That is not the town that I know.
That is not the town that I love.
Now more than ever, we need a leader
who has seen this town at its very best.
[moderator] Tom, same question.
Well, first off, I just want to say
that I find it heartbreaking
that Linda Morelli doesn't seem
to like this town very much. [chuckles]
-[audience muttering]
-[Tom] Hmm?
I happen to love this town.
Always have, always will.
That's not, uh, what I said in the--
Sorry, Linda. It is Tom's time to answer
the question. You will get a rebuttal.
-[Tom] Well…
-But I didn't--
Let me just say… [chuckles]
I am in agreement.
Hate crimes have no place in this town.
-Well, duh.
-Well…
But do we really want
someone's mom dictating policy
based on what happens to her kids?
I mean, if her daughter gets a flat tire,
will we suddenly
have to, uh, repave every road?
Sorry, Tom, but, uh, is that your answer
to what distinguishes you
as a… a candidate?
Because, um, it's easy to critique
somebody else's answer
when you haven't an-- answered one.
Wow, see, I didn't know you were running
for the job of moderator. Huh.
[chuckles] Watch out, Jane.
[inhales] Uh, okay. Well,
as the owner of 38 Jimmy John's,
my employee count is ten times
the size of this city council
and likely 20 times the size
of whoever Linda's got on staff
at her little, uh, shop. [inhales]
I know how to manage people,
and I know how to manage places.
My opponent, who seems very nice,
feels better suited to run
our neighborhood watch programs
than lead our entire municipal government.
[hoarsely] Tom,
you better be careful there,
because you're starting to sound
a little bit misogynistic.
Uh-oh. There it is.
I've awoken the beast. [laughs]
We get it, Linda. You're tough.
I'm starting to understand how you managed
to scare off the chief of police. [laughs]
[tense music playing]
Excuse me?
-[Natalie gasping]
-[audience muttering]
[cameras clicking]
[music ends]
[lighter clicks]
Morgan, he's smoking in the car.
-Put the window down.
-Yeah.
[Nicky coughs]
-[Nicky whispers] Jesus.
-[window whirring]
He put the window back up. Can you--
-What is going on here?
-Okay.
-[window opening]
-[car speeding by]
So, um… [clears throat]
What were you in for?
-It's better you don't know.
-Okay.
-Okay, that's the scariest answer…
-[phone ringing]
…you could've possibly given me.
-Thank you.
-Oh, God.
Yeah, we have him.
We're… We're driving to the apartment.
-No, you're not.
-What do you mean, "we're not"?
-Put him on speakerphone.
-What do you mean? What--
What do you mean, "No, we're not"?
We're… we're in the car with him.
[Yusuf] No, you're fucking not!
The apartment won't be ready
until tomorrow
because someone asked
to have it fucking repainted.
[whispers] Don't put this on me.
Okay. Well, how long does it take
to paint an apartment?
He says two coats.
There's no point in only doing one.
-I've slept in worse.
-[Yusuf] He won't let me in.
-The walls are wet. The room stinks.
-[phone buzzing]
[angrily] Who the fuck asked for paint?
-I'm not in… I don't-- I don't know, okay?
-Hi, Mom.
Morgan, what are you doing
on Nicholas's phone? Put me on speaker.
-Oh, I don't think that works right now.
-Hold please.
No, Morgan, this is a crisis.
I need to talk to both of you.
-What is she saying?
-[exhales] Okay.
The debate was a disaster. We're having
an emergency family dinner at the house.
Hello? Who the fuck is that?
Who else is in the car?
Nobody else is in the car.
Someone else is in the car? Where are you?
Ma, tonight doesn't really work for me,
because I promised Max
we were gonna have a romantic night in.
[Linda] Uh, okay, well, Nicky,
be here in 30 minutes.
-Who is this woman?
-I hear someone's voice.
Who the fuck is talking right now?
No-- Nobody's talking. It's--
Mom, I'm with a parishioner, okay?
I don't think I'm gonna be home,
so I… I… I don't think I can make dinner.
No, Nicholas! This is nonnegotiable.
I got raked over the coals
by a sandwich king at the debate.
-What? What is she talking about?
-[Linda] I need some help here.
If you need to,
bring your friend to dinner.
He's not my friend.
But be here by 7:00. You know
how I hate using the warming drawer.
-Lady.
-Is that your friend?
Tell him I'm making chicken cacciatore.
[Yusuf] I don't know
what the fuck is going on.
But someone take me the fucking off
of speakerphone right now!
He called me an animal.
It was humiliating.
Well, what made him say that?
Were you yelling at him?
[yelling] Was I yelling at him?
No, I was defending myself,
and on top of that,
he added absolutely nothing of value
except that his grandfather
apparently invented the French dip.
But the most disturbing part of it was,
people seemed to side with him.
[Andrei moans]
This is the most delicious chicken
I've ever had.
Every night I've dreamed
of a meal like this.
-[Natalie] Oh.
-[Andrei chewing]
[whispers] I think he's crying.
[Linda] Well, thank you very much.
It was my mother's recipe.
She was an excellent cook
and a notoriously difficult woman,
which apparently, is not a recessive gene
in this family.
-Mom, nobody thinks that, okay?
-Mmm.
You are being way too hard on yourself.
Nicky brought it up this morning.
I never said
you were turning into your mother.
Can you make my life easier
for just one fucking day?
[Andrei] He's scared.
[cutlery scraping]
Excuse me?
This Donaldson.
A strong man would not be intimidated
by a strong woman.
-Now you know his weakness.
-[Linda] Mm-hmm.
Weakness always exposes itself.
Oof.
-Interesting.
-[Nicky] Okay.
I'd like to know more.
Nicky, grab another bottle of wine.
-Okay.
-[cutlery clinking]
-[Natalie] Oh, yeah.
-[Linda] Um…
[Linda exhales]
So,
more chicken?
-[Andrei] Mmm.
-[Linda] Okay.
[plate clinks]
[Andrei moans]
You know, you never actually said
how you know my son.
[smacks lips]
-He picked me up from prison.
-[loud thud]
A-ha.
[laughs] That's fabulous.
I…
Um, which one?
[romantic music playing faintly]
-[Morgan laughs]
-Good day?
[inhales] Yeah, actually.
I DoorDashed from that chicken spot
we went to
on our first date back in high school.
Didn't ask you, just did it.
Wait, I thought they shut down
because of a health code violation.
Yeah. New management.
Fuck, yes!
-[Morgan squeals]
-Yeah. And I lit some candles.
One of them turns into body oil.
I don't remember which.
[laughs softly]
Um, is it weird to eat chicken
with your dick out?
It's just something
you're gonna have to deal with.
[inhales]
-[bag rustling]
-[Morgan exhales]
[music continues playing]
[gasps]
-I see you sprung for the best of.
-Mm-hmm.
That's very generous.
-And two skinny margs.
-[chuckles]
-[Max] Mm-hmm.
-[gasps]
-[Max snaps]
-Ah--
Rude bitches don't get chicken nuggets.
Look again.
Okay.
[bag rustling]
[inhales]
[exhales]
[whispers] Fuck.
[exhales deeply]
-[inhales] Yeah, I'll give you this one.
-Mm-hmm.
[romantic music continues playing]
[keypad clacking]
[Linda] That was a shocking story.
Clearly, you were framed.
It was a setup.
This is the problem
with the judicial system.
-Back in my country, I was a surgeon.
-Mmm.
Oh, I want to apologize to you
on behalf of America.
I am truly sorry
for what we have put you through.
-I had a cab driver just a week ago…
-Hm.
…who was a dermatologist in Mumbai.
-And thanks to that wonderful man…
-Mmm.
…I now have a checkup
on the mole on my neck.
-[Natalie] Okay, um, I should go.
-[Linda] Mmm.
Yeah. Yeah, Kevin's Oura Ring says
he hasn't moved in ten hours.
Uh-oh.
-[chair scraping]
-[Natalie] So…
[Natalie inhales] Um…
I guess we will just discuss
post-debate strategy tomorrow.
Yes, strategy in the morning.
Andrei had some great ideas.
I appreciate you.
Oh, fabulous. That's great.
-Okay.
-[slurping]
[Natalie] Drink some water.
I never noticed how much your skin glows.
[mellow music playing]
[swallows] Jergens.
-[Nicky inhales]
-Do me a favor.
Do not leave Mom alone with a criminal.
[whispers] I got him an Airbnb.
She's having a nice time.
I think it's sweet.
I will take him home
when they start slurring, okay?
Let love in, Natalie.
Okay. I don't know what this
radical optimism is, but I don't like it.
[whispers] Good night.
[breathes sharply] Take care of her.
[door opens]
[chuckles]
-[door closes]
-[inhales]
[keypad clacking]
[music continues playing]
[Linda laughing in the background]
[TV playing indistinctly]
[Morgan chewing, laughing quietly]
[woman on TV] Where is she?
-[man] At home, I imagine.
-[woman] No, she's not.
[mellow music playing]
[snoring softly]
[insects chirping]
[muffled banging]
[muffled moaning]
[Andrei speaking indistinctly]
[banging continues]
Ooh.
Oh.
-[Andrei moaning]
-[banging continues]
Oh my…
[cell phone buzzing]
[smacks lips] What time is it?
-Mom is having sex with Andrei.
-[Morgan] Who?
The man we picked up from prison.
[softly] Oh my God.
Okay, okay.
Put the phone up to the wall.
[Nicky] I'm not… You're sick.
That is a sick, sick… I will not do that.
Oh my God, whatever.
How's it going? Is she having fun?
[Nicky laughs]
From the sounds of it,
he's a very generous lover. Yeah.
[Morgan] Well, yeah. That makes sense.
He just got out of prison.
-She's probably getting railed up there.
-[laughs]
-I can't.
-[phone buzzing]
Why is Natalie calling me?
What is she doing up? It's, like, 12:30.
Doesn't she go to bed at 8?
-Can I help you?
-[Natalie] Check fraud.
-Credit card fraud. Identity theft.
-[snoring]
Forgery. Importing
an illegal flamethrower.
Nicky, tell me that man
is out of our house.
Yeah. Yeah, I dropped him off hours ago.
So, yeah, he's gone.
-[Natalie] Oh my God. Thank God.
-[banging intensifies]
Because, honestly, Nicky, that is, like,
the last thing Mom needs right now.
Nat-- I won't-- And I don't…
We're done, okay?
It's done, Natalie.
So, um, um, go back to bed.
[Natalie] Tell Mom I miss her.
Yeah. Bye.
[Andrei and Linda moaning]
-[Nicky] Hi.
-What did she want?
Well, apparently, Andrei was in prison
for importing an illegal flamethrower.
-A what?
-A flamethrower, Morgan.
Importing an illegal flamethrower.
Whoa. Is he singing?
That's singing.
[Andrei singing indistinctly]
[Morgan] He's good.
["Fuck the Pain Away" by Peaches playing]
♪ Huh? What? Right, uh ♪
♪ SIS IUD ♪
♪ Stay in school 'cause it's the best ♪
♪ IUD SIS ♪
♪ Suckin' on my titties
Like you wanted me ♪
♪ Callin' me all the time like Blondie ♪
♪ Check out my Chrissie behind ♪
♪ It's fine all of the time ♪
♪ Like sex on the beaches ♪
♪ What else is
In the Teaches of Peaches? ♪
♪ Huh? What? ♪
♪ Fuck the pain away, fuck the pain away ♪
[music ends]