WHEN THE PHONE RINGS
He's so handsome.
He looks great in a suit.
Who's that?
Who's that woman?
Is she his wife?
- Is she Paik Sa-eon's wife?
- They look good together.
Don't be nervous.
Those people are looking at me, not you.
Sure, they might be curious about you.
But remember,
there can't be any misunderstandings,
interest, or rumors
about our relationship tonight.
Let's go.
A DAY BEFORE
Heavy rainfall is expected nationwide
this year once again.
With the monsoon season approaching,
we must prepare in advance
for landslides, heavy rain, and typhoons.
- Experts have pointed out…
- What's that?
What's wrong with that?
While unexpected damage is inevitable…
I think there's a lag.
How can it stop there?
It looks like she's cursing!
Inspections need to be strengthened.
Na You-ri, pass it over to the scene!
We aim to review
last year's landslide site
and consider ways to reduce damage.
Reporter Park is on-site now.
This means…
a mountain, right?
The high middle mountain?
You did great.
I'll be honest.
Director Yoon's a superior,
but I can't stand how rude he is.
You really showed him
the peak.
I mean, the high mountain.
What the hell are you doing?
Put up the apology message now!
- Darn it.
- Okay!
…roads have collapsed.
WE APOLOGIZE FOR THE DISRUPTION
Places with heavy traffic
were no exception…
- Breaking news on the abduction incident.
- What?
The emergency briefing is in five minutes.
But…
OFFICE OF THE PRESIDENT
You-ri, breaking news
from the Presidential Office.
A spokesperson briefing?
I keep seeing Sa-eon today.
Hee-joo, we're going live.
- Can you interpret--
- No interpreter. Tell her to go.
That's all for today. You may leave.
Great work.
They keep having the spokesperson do it.
Don't the Chief Security Officer
or Foreign Ministry
usually take turns briefing
for situations like this?
They did.
- They did?
- Yeah.
When the abduction happened.
You don't remember, do you?
That's why they keep
sending out Paik Sa-eon.
Paik Sa-eon overshadows
the Foreign Ministry and the ministers.
Hey, I think he's coming out.
OFFICE OF THE PRESIDENT
I'm Paik Sa-eon, spokesperson
for the Presidential Office.
Today, from 1:48 p.m. to 4:20 p.m.
- Korea Standard Time…
- Good vocalization and a great voice.
What was he like as a news anchor?
The same as he is now.
He ranked first in preference,
trust, and ratings.
Excuse me.
Can you please be quiet?
I can't hear Sa-eon's voice well
because of you.
Being a fangirl even while she's working.
We have made our utmost efforts.
However, the armed group demands
the immediate withdrawal
of South Korean Troops
and payment of a ransom,
warning that they will kill the hostages
if their demands are not met.
- Kill?
I would like to state
the government's position on this.
When it comes to negotiations with
the kidnappers regarding the ransom…
There will be none.
The government considers their acts
as inhumane crimes
that cannot be tolerated
and will never compromise.
We promise to mobilize all
national resources to rescue our citizens,
including cooperation
with international organizations.
We will never compromise
on the principles we must uphold.
Furthermore, the government
will use this opportunity
to address the recent attacks
on third-country commercial vessels
in the Strait of Surmuz.
The illegal use of force
in international waters,
where the freedom of navigation
for vessels is guaranteed,
is viewed as a serious concern.
In the future,
the government will strengthen
safety guidance activities
for citizens in high-risk areas
and implement measures
to prevent similar incidents
from occurring in the future.
As of 5:02 p.m.,
a temporary media control
will be implemented
under government authority.
- An embargo?
- Again?
Why are they trying to silence us?
Excuse me?
HBC, Jang Hyeok-jin.
Foreign media are already reporting this.
If our media stay silent,
sensational fake news
and unreliable personal broadcasts
will take over.
Is that okay with you?
Yes.
Excuse me?
Aren't reporters from our country's
leading media outlets all here?
If you don't mislead public opinion,
the citizens won't believe
what fake news says.
Be honest with us.
The current situation is bad, isn't it?
"Don't be gentle with the government."
You've come this far with that saying,
but I've never seen you
look so scared before.
Yes.
I'm terrified right now.
But am I the only one here
who is scared?
I ask all of the journalists here today.
Come together as one
and pray for the safe return
of our citizens.
I promise that the government
will do its utmost to ensure
not a single life is lost.
Check major headlines,
personal broadcasts, new media,
and comments on community posts.
- Report public opinion to me.
- Yes, sir.
Post live updates
from the negotiation team.
Yes, sir.
SINIL DAILY NEWS,
DONGYUL DAILY NEWS, DAILY TAEJIN
SINIL DAILY NEWS LEE YEONG-JIN
MBS HA JOO-WON
HBC NA YOU-RI
Sa-eon, it's You-ri.
I'm rooting for you! Stay strong!
It's time…
you quit working.
You know the election camp
starts in a month, right?
Put aside external activities.
Focus on supporting him.
Of course.
I was going to ask her to quit anyway.
She never should've started working.
Last year, you suddenly
went on about not being able to breathe.
So I guess he let you work
to give you room to breathe.
But exposing your name
and face was something
that should have never happened.
Put an end to it quickly.
Also,
is there no improvement
in your selective mutism?
Is there really a need for improvement?
It's probably better
to keep her mouth shut.
Don't worry, ma'am.
I'll make sure nothing interferes
with the election…
God, that bitch.
I need to put that hag in her place
one day.
This is all your fault!
If you stole someone else's man,
you should do a better job!
You haven't even been
able to win your man's heart.
Who do you take after?
It certainly isn't me.
Don't forget, you're Chungwoon Daily News
chairman's second daughter
and the future president's
daughter-in-law.
HANNAM-DONG, SIGN LANGUAGE CENTER
PYEONGCHANG-DONG, BROADCAST CENTER
HANNAM-DONG
In an emergency briefing,
the government stated that it will
not compromise despite threats
from the Argan armed group--
…no compromise…
Also, there will be no negotiations…
You've gone off-route.
…kill the hostage…
…the armed group…
…ransom…
…strongly suggested…
…no compromise…
…do its utmost…
…kill the hostage…
…strongly…
…kill…
There will be no negotiation
unless the ransom is paid…
The engine of an unattended car
starts on its own.
The doors lock and unlock.
Malware is implanted
in the vehicle's navigation software.
It's car hacking, where someone
manipulates another person's vehicle.
HACKED NAVIGATION SYSTEM
MANIPULATES ENGINE AND LOCKS
Monitoring results show no signs
of journalists breaking
embargo agreements…
- Mr. Paik?
- What about new media?
Yes, we've reviewed everything there too.
It's a mess.
Netizens have uncovered
your hidden background,
including FBI training
and NYPD hostage negotiation courses.
You're a negotiation expert.
They want you to be sent
to the negotiation team.
It's a mess… What? Excuse me.
So, after a comprehensive review,
it appears that there are no speculative
articles or malicious reports…
There is.
Excuse me?
A very malicious report
that distorts the facts.
Where?
Here. Take care of it.
What is this?
What? Come on.
Jang Hyeok-jin from HBC is at it again.
Yeah.
He seems friendly,
but then he throws in a curveball.
But…
what do we say when we request a deletion?
Emotional distress
caused by malicious distortion?
Hysteria?
- Hysteria?
- Hysteria.
Hysteria?
TAESAN DAILY NEWS
SOCIAL AFFAIRS EDITOR KIM HYEON-WOO
This is the negotiation team's timeline.
- You got a call.
- Who is it this time?
A strange number.
I think it's from abroad.
What shall I do?
Paik Sa-eon speaking.
Please speak.
- I'll hang up if you don't.
- Paik Sa-eon.
So it is really you.
What is this?
What? You don't like my voice?
Where are you?
It's not a domestic number.
Who are you affiliated with?
I'll kill…
I'm going to kill
your wife.
The voice just now…
Get back to work.
Yes, sir.
MOTHER
It's me.
Did you see her today?
What time did you part ways?
With my mother-in-law?
SON-IN-LAW
What?
Goodness. It's my son-in-law.
I thought you were busy.
Your face is on every channel today.
My son-in-law looks amazing on screen.
What? Hee-joo?
Yeah, I brought her home.
I'll send her off after dinner.
Is that so?
Okay, have a good night.
- Mr. Kang?
- Yes, sir?
406-000-1290. Trace this number for me.
- What?
- Did you memorize it?
- It's a phishing scam.
- Four, zero…
406-000-1290. I'll trace it.
Yeah, okay. You do that.
Former journalists
really are a different breed.
They're fast.
Is she dead?
You said you'd kill her.
Did you kill her?
Do you even know who my wife is?
Look here.
Don't you watch the news?
I'm far too busy
for these types of prank calls today.
Don't hang up.
I dare you to hang up on me again.
What if I do?
I have…
a knife to your wife's throat right now.
I'll really kill her.
Well?
- I'll kill her.
- Okay.
- Try it.
- What?
Don't just talk about it, do it.
Not yet…
We haven't talked about money yet.
How much will you…
pay for the ransom?
The ransom?
Listen up.
You can demand however much you want.
But there will be no ransom.
So don't call me again.
Darn it.
I seriously love this expression the most.
Eyes on the road.
Sis, do you get it now?
That this isn't a joke?
But…
why does your husband think I'm joking?
What the hell did he mean earlier?
Why did he ask me
if I knew who his wife was?
It's you, isn't it?
Wait. Or does he have another wife?
I'm just teasing.
Well, it doesn't matter
if he has more than one wife.
It's none of my business,
but the wife Sa-eon cares about the most
better be you, Sis.
That's how you'll survive this.
Now, let's call him again.
PAIK SA-EON
Is he going to ignore me again?
Again?
Paik Sa-eon!
This bastard!
It's okay. It's all good.
Sis.
Do you know what kind of phone this is?
This…
can only call Paik Sa-eon.
The voice modulation
is also automatic.
Also, it…
What was it again?
Yeah! That!
It uses a VPN.
It can't be tracked for ten minutes.
I already prepped this car in advance too.
That's why it moves on its own.
I'm so well prepared.
But this guy,
Paik Sa-eon, isn't picking up the phone!
PAIK SA-EON
- Paik Sa-eon.
- What?
Hello, just a moment.
I'll put Mr. Paik on the phone.
I told you not to answer it. Why did you?
I pressed the button by mistake.
It's a phishing scam.
Listen up, you pathetic loser scumbag.
What did I say?
I told you not to call me again.
I'm sure I was clear too.
I'm going to kill your wife.
Fine, then hurry up and do it.
And…
Call me when there's a corpse.
Mr. Paik, Argan called through the hotline
and requests your presence.
Don't touch my things.
Yes, sir.
What the hell? What are you doing?
You crazy bitch!
Damn it!
Get your hands off it!
Stop the car!
The government announced
at 6:55 p.m. today
that negotiations successfully ended,
and the Argan armed group
agreed to release all Korean hostages.
Here is a statement
from spokesperson Paik Sa-eon.
Thank you to the hostages and the public
for your trust and endurance
and to the media for your cooperation
in ensuring national security and safety.
We also express our gratitude
to the Argan government
and allied international organizations,
and we will take all necessary measures
to ensure the safe return of the hostages.
Can I get an exclusive interview,
Mr. Paik?
Just a moment.
Wait.
Wait! My arm! It's stuck!
Come on, you darn punk!
Why are you heading out so early?
It's not even 9:00 yet.
Let's grab a drink.
Did you wait to see
what time I clocked out?
Are you a stalker?
Yeah, man.
I noticed you took down
all of my pictures.
Why? Didn't like them?
A journalist should report the truth.
You shouldn't distort it.
I didn't distort it. It's PR.
Come on.
- You lack humanity.
- I didn't ask you to do that.
I never will, either.
Hey, Sa-eon? Open the door. Hey!
Stop… Hey!
Hey, Sa-eon! Hey!
Darn…
What?
Hey, what are you doing? Hey!
Darn it.
Hyeok-jin, I have a favor to ask.
What's wrong with you? You're crazy!
Hey, I'm sorry!
I was wrong. I won't do it again.
In front of us! There!
Trace this number as quickly as possible.
What? What is it?
Hey, in front of us!
It's a phishing scam,
but I have a bad feeling.
A bad feeling? So do I.
Slow down, man!
I never assumed my number would be safe
from scammers.
But a voice modulator?
He's pulling out all the stops.
So I just can't let it go.
What? Phishing? Modulator?
Is this a case?
Just look into the number.
406-000-1290?
Get out. We're done.
Okay.
I'm off.
Goodness.
That punk.
Why is he in such a hurry?
You're alive.
I received…
a ridiculous phone call today.
Someone said…
they would kill you.
Well, "my wife," to be exact.
Anyway,
you're alive and well.
By the way, what's with the food?
Didn't you have dinner with your mom?
What happened?
You can't trace it?
It's not using the cell towers.
We can't trace it with just a number.
Hey, 406 is an area code in the States.
And it's a virtual phone number.
Is it because it's a virtual phone number?
So is real-time tracking the only way?
Yes, how did you know?
And to track it in real time,
they have to call again.
So I have to wait for his call?
I'm sorry, sir.
And the call must last
at least ten minutes.
I'm sure you already know,
but we need personal information
to identify--
- It's a man.
- Sorry?
But the voice was modulated.
It's a man. I'm sure of it.
And he was on drugs
or not in his right mind.
He made the threatening call
at the perfect time.
It was clear he was trying
to shake me up
during a national emergency.
Yes, there are many groups
that would be glad to see you fail.
Is your wife okay?
Of course, she's fine.
But just in case,
I want her to be under protection.
Without them knowing she's my wife.
Okay. There's a team I can trust.
I'll call them myself.
Just give me the number.
Yes, sir.
Also, about the event
at the British Embassy tomorrow,
didn't you say we needed
a sign language interpreter?
Did you find one?
Come and sit.
There's an event at the British Embassy
tomorrow at 6:00 p.m.
I'll send someone
to pick you up by 5:00, so be ready.
The ambassador's wife is deaf,
so we need a sign language interpreter.
It's not a couple's event or anything.
Don't get the wrong idea.
MOM
Where are you? Are you at home?
Why won't you pick up?
Sa-eon was looking for you earlier.
WHY WAS HE LOOKING FOR ME?
I don't know.
He asked me if I was with you.
I said I'd send you home after dinner,
so tell him so when he comes home.
MOM
You listen to me.
There's just a month left
until the presidential campaign.
You probably won't need to show yourself,
but just in case, see the dermatologist
and plastic surgeon starting tomorrow.
And another thing.
When did you stop going to the clinic?
No wonder why you're not pregnant!
I'll send the medicine tomorrow,
so be ready to get in shape.
Are you listening?
I can't tell if you're listening
since you're completely silent.
It's just a month left.
I told you to quit your job.
3 YEARS AGO
Take it off.
It doesn't belong to you.
You're just the stand-in.
Take it off.
The wedding will be held in private.
You'll never have to pretend
to be my wife in front of others again.
Are you going to strip naked?
It's our wedding vows.
You don't have to read it all,
just remember this.
One, the bride cannot initiate a divorce.
Two, especially
not during the election period.
Three, you will not publicly disclose
your name or face as Paik Sa-eon's wife.
If any of these is violated,
the penalty will be two billion won.
Get up.
I said, get up.
You're so stubborn.
Forget the illusion that we're married.
You were sent…
as a hostage to me.
PAIK SA-EON'S MARRIAGE
SPOKESPERSON PAIK'S WEDDING
SUDDENLY TURNED PRIVATE
SOME SAY THE WEDDING WAS HELD IN PRIVATE
TO HIDE THE BRIDE FROM THE PUBLIC
SIGN IS A LANGUAGE
SEONGNANG-GU SIGN LANGUAGE CENTER
Come on, asshole! Come at me!
Come!
Come at me if you have a death wish!
You bastards!
Who is it at this hour?
STUDIO
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
We meet again.
Goodness.
What is that?
Didn't I tell you not to run your mouth?
What's she doing?
Do you want to lose your teeth?
You must have a death wish, bastard.
Eyes down!
Hee-joo?
What are you doing?
I was just practicing.
What kind of intense practice is this?
Are you interpreting for the police?
Or did a loan shark ask
for an interpreter? Is the debtor deaf?
It's not like that.
But you've never done this before.
You really startled me.
You scared me.
Just do what you usually do.
Watch the video you practice with.
The one with Paik Sa-eon.
There have been a lot of briefings lately.
Want me to bring you some?
No, I don't need them.
Why not?
You said you liked his videos
because they're like a textbook.
You said you wanted to be on-screen
with Paik Sa-eon
even if it was just a brief moment.
I'm done with Paik Sa-eon's videos.
I've done enough already.
I apologize.
I'm sorry we're late.
It's fine.
Let's go.
Wow. That's so nice.
I didn't know
the spokesperson's wife could sign.
I'm not the spokesperson's wife.
I'm just here as an interpreter.
There's no personal relationship.
To be honest,
my wife has a disability too.
Because my wife…
…is my weakness.
I face attacks from all sides.
In a way, you could say
I'm the government's official scapegoat.
So I don't want
my wife to be exposed
to indiscriminate attacks like I am.
Yes, she's my weakness.
TEXT MESSAGE
We're on standby.
We can track it once you get the call,
so just be mindful of the time.
Are you trying to get drunk?
Or are you already drunk?
I'LL GO HOME IF I'M DONE HERE
You can't.
You just have to stand quietly next to me.
Is that so hard?
Stay.
Go sit somewhere if your legs hurt.
Stop drinking.
Do you think I can't hear
just because I can't speak?
Do you think I can't feel emotions?
You don't want to expose me
to indiscriminate attacks?
Then why am I hurt and torn apart already?
Did you say I was your weakness?
A weakness…
is a wound that's prone to infection.
When someone touches it, you flinch,
tremble, and desperately defend it.
That's a weakness.
But you didn't act like that yesterday.
You despicable jerk.
Did you just curse at me?
But then, I might not be the wife
you were just talking about.
Hello?
Speak, 406.
Should I go first?
My wife is safe.
Did you fail to kill her?
Why won't you speak?
You went on and on yesterday.
Wait.
I didn't have time
to listen to your rambling.
Then let's hear your plan on how
you're going to hurt her in the future.
I've got plenty of free time today.
True,
I guess there's not much to do at a party.
I'm glad you're having a good time.
You're good
at playing the lovestruck fool.
Are you surprised by how close I am?
Yeah.
I've been watching you the whole time,
but you didn't notice.
- Stop bluffing.
- Bluffing?
How could someone like you get in here?
You need an invitation to--
You've hardly eaten anything.
Eat something.
The bruschetta with the truffle on top
was really good.
Who are you?
Are you curious about me now?
Stop laughing and answer me. Who are you?
How did you get in here?
Yeah, I'll answer you.
The answer to the question
you asked earlier.
You asked me…
how I plan on hurting your wife.
Don't mess around.
How dare you come here?
You look flustered.
You should've done this yesterday.
Who are you?
What are you doing?
Hello?
What's wrong? Did something happen?
I apologize.
What was that? You're way off base.
You said I can't be possibly here.
A loser like you is probably hiding
and snickering in your room.
Do you really think someone like you
could do anything to my wife?
Listen up, if you wanted to threaten me,
you chose the wrong hostage.
My wife? Who's my wife?
Have you even seen her?
Yeah, that's right.
The world has no idea who she is.
They don't know who your real wife is.
But I do.
Hong Hee-joo
isn't your real wife.
Your real wife is the one you were
supposed to marry, your real fiancée.
The eldest daughter of the chairman
of Chungwoon Daily News, Hong In-a.
She ran away the day before the wedding,
and I heard no one knows where she is.
But still,
how could you marry her sister instead?
Isn't that outrageous?
But then,
Chungwoon Daily News and your family
are in an inseparable
symbiotic relationship.
You had to go through with the marriage,
so you married her sister as a hostage?
Either way, I bet people
will love that. Right?
It's so shocking.
Paik Sa-eon,
the clean and great spokesperson,
rides both sisters like an elevator.
On and off whenever he wants.
What's wrong? Cat got your tongue?
Don't you want to know how I know
a secret nobody else knows?
Say something, Paik Sa-eon!
What do you want?
Yeah, good job.
That's the correct answer.
Tell me…
what you want.
Then listen carefully.
I'm going to tell you my demands now.
Get rid of Hong Hee-joo
and get back with your real fiancée.
You don't need Hong Hee-joo
in your life anyway, do you?
Listen up, you pathetic loser scumbag.
What did I say?
I told you not to call me again.
I'm sure I was clear too.
I'm going to kill your wife.
Then hurry up and do it.
And…
Call me when there's a corpse.
That asshole.
Call him back.
What?
I have something to say to him,
so call him back now!
This is exhilarating.
Pick up.
Pick up!
Do you understand?
Unless you want your personal life
to ruin your father's election,
return things to what they were.
If you don't,
I'll expose the secrets of your marriage.
Hey, man. Are you scared?
It's funny Paik Sa-eon would be scared
because of a loser like me.
You have until tomorrow to decide.
Or we can settle for two billion won.
You have until tomorrow.
Are you done?
Tell me,
how do punks like you
never change your repertoire?
What?
If you want to threaten me,
you should study up on me first.
There are hundreds of reporters
eager to get me to speak at any cost.
Turning a lame scandal into fake news
is easy for me.
And I can get rid of
a pathetic blackmailer with my eyes shut.
So why would I?
Why did you think
I'd accept the presumptuous demand
to abandon Hong Hee-joo?
Why are you dragging my person into this?
"My person"?
Don't be ridiculous!
Hey, do you know what happened
to your precious person yesterday?
She almost died.
No, I mean, I almost killed her!
I kidnapped her in her car,
choked her, and grabbed her by the hair.
I had a knife to her.
I was going to kill her. Do you get it?
So?
What do you mean? It was scary.
She was terrified!
So she was scared. What happened next?
I was about to kill her,
and she couldn't even beg for her life.
Since she can't speak.
Then?
Then you ruthlessly hung up the phone,
saying to call when there's a corpse!
Yeah, Hong Hee-joo
really could've ended up dead.
The car rolled on the slippery road!
I've never been…
more curious about a man before.
Forget about getting arrested, 406.
I promise,
I'm going to catch you.
Wait…
Am I screwed, or did he fall for it?
WHEN THE PHONE RINGS
Who was he?
Did you see his face?
Paik Sa-eon is scared.
What is this?
It's Hong Hee-joo's thigh.
Have you never seen her naked?
I must be crazy!
What the heck? Why is he coming?
Hee-joo, you're doing well, right?
A man?
Were you close?
Lately, nothing makes sense.
There can't be a Hong Hee-joo
I don't know about.
By any chance,
are you close to me?
Subtitle translation by: Sue Mounce