(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
ALL FIGURES,
INCIDENTS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS,
AND OTHERS ARE FICTITIOUS.
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
WERE FILMED SAFELY
IN ACCORDANCE WITH GUIDELINES.
Na-hyun.
Han Na-hyun!
What do you want?
Mom!
Didn't you say you were going to study?
Where's the Na-hyun that was
too busy studying to run an errand for me?
Mom, let me explain.
I really was studying.
I was. I really was.
I knew you'd get caught.
You should've given me a heads-up!
Why is that my fault?
Quiet down, both of you.
- She started it.
Are you going to keep bickering like this?
Even when you're old and gray?
HAN NA-HYUN, HAN SO-HYUN
AUGUST 20, 1997
IT RAINED SO I WORE MY RAINCOAT…
AUGUST 12, 2008
My dear So-hyun
hasn't grown old at all.
HIGH SCHOOL GIRL JUMPS IN
AT THE MOMENT OF CRISIS
Wow.
The stars are beautiful.
They really came.
Excuse me. Are you…
HAN SO-HYUN'S 19TH BIRTHDAY
ON JULY 7, 2012
What's that?
Those punks.
Oh, no.
This is not how I wanted it to start.
You annoying bastard.
You're just dying
for a good beating, aren't you?
That's enough!
What the hell does he want?
Three ganging up on one?
Hey, that's cheap.
If you're drunk, keep on walking.
You won't be able to hold a spoon if
your last good hand is in a cast, mister.
Mister?
What the heck are you saying?
Looks like this guy won't listen.
A beating might do.
HORANG TAEKWONDO
CERTIFICATE OF COMMENDATION
You can't do this, sir.
Or is this because I'm young?
You do look young for your age.
Those boys were ganging up on the kid!
Keep your voice down.
You're in a police station.
- Have a good one.
- You too.
Officer! Wait!
Shut up!
Shut your mouth, okay?
I can't sleep because of you.
Not again.
This is nuts!
You're here too.
This is actually good.
You saw them beat up a boy, right?
I did.
Did you really fight
those three teenage boys alone?
Fortunately, I practiced tae kwon do
since I was little.
Did you perhaps get those men in here too?
Is he crazy? He's talking to himself.
Yes, I got them all in here
because they broke the law.
You break the law, you get punished.
You don't know when to gloss over things.
You shouldn't gloss things over!
If you make compromises and cut corners,
the world would become a total mess
in an instant, mister.
You see, my goal is
to make a fair and beautiful world
where social order is maintained
by the law
and people respect each other.
That's why you wanted to be an attorney.
For that to happen, I shouldn't be easy
even on minor misconduct.
Anyway,
why do you speak to me so formally?
I'm a whole lot younger than you.
You're Attorney Han's older sister.
What?
I mean…
Okay, I'll be more casual with you.
Of course.
Anyway, I didn't mean
to get you locked up in here too.
I'm sorry.
Later when the officer comes,
I'll talk him into releasing you.
You don't have to wait.
You can get out of here if you want.
What? How?
I'm behind steel bars…
Five fish altogether in one fish tank
Hello?
Is this Mr. Shin I-rang's brother-in-law?
Yes, this is me. Who may you be?
I'm Lieutenant Cho Chi-yeong
from Seocho Police Station.
Police?
Have you settled down now?
No, I'm boiling with anger.
I'm so young! Why did I die?
I know how you feel.
You must be sad and frustrated.
What's worse is
that I can't remember a thing.
You don't?
- That's strange.
- What do you mean?
Ghosts float in mid-air
until they regain their memory.
But you're already on the ground.
Anyway, I can help you regain your memory.
How?
If I tell you your name
and date of birth--
Tell me quick.
Your memory will come back.
Make it come back right now!
Okay, all right.
First, take a deep breath.
- Come on, mister!
- All right.
You've got a temper just like your sister.
HAN SO-HYUN'S 19TH BIRTHDAY
ON JULY 7, 2012
Han So-hyun.
You were born on July 7, 1994.
HAN SO-HYUN
Sister.
HORANG TAEKWONDO
Hey! Get your hands off her!
It's going to be real fun.
Na-hyun!
So-hyun!
Na-hyun…
I…
I saved her.
I saved my sister, Na-hyun.
I see.
I'm dead, but I'm happy.
Mister.
My sister
must be well and happy, right?
Oh, my head…
How much did I drink?
What is Attorney Shin's jacket doing here?
Hello?
Attorney Han,
please help my brother-in-law!
Excuse me?
What year is it now?
It's 2025.
Then,
thirty one…
I wonder if she became a singer.
Oh, my sister's dream was to be a singer.
She just loved singing.
She'd sing and play the guitar all day.
Look.
Your sister isn't a singer--
Mr. Shin,
your attorney is here to see you.
Attorney Han…
Han Na-hyun?
Is it really you?
What the… You became an attorney?
But why?
Wow, it's amazing.
The tiny little girl
turned into this awesome career woman.
Is this how you actually are?
I want you to take this first.
I'm not thirsty.
Don't be so cold to him.
I'm not asking you to drink it.
If I act strange in any way,
splash that water on me.
Why should I?
I'm not like you. I don't use violence.
Yes, I know.
Still, keep it with you.
I'd appreciate it if you could splash
that on me, in case I act weird.
You're doing me a favor.
That's not violence, right?
How are the boys?
They'll take two, two,
and four weeks to heal.
Do you usually have bad drinking habits?
How could you use violence
against students?
Na-hyun, that's not his fault.
I have nothing to say.
You better not.
I wouldn't have taken on this case
if not for your brother-in-law.
And I'm partly at fault
for drinking with you.
Thank you for choosing to be my attorney.
But three boys were ganging up on one kid.
I heard differently.
The boys were just talking
when you attacked them out of the blue.
That's not true!
I swear there were three bullying one.
And they attacked me first.
Three boys were bullying one,
and they attacked me first.
The four victims testified the same.
If you keep denying it, it'll be taken
to both criminal and civil suits.
If you don't settle with the parents
of Sung Min-jae with a four-week injury,
you'll get a six-month sentence, minimum.
Then, you'll lose your law license.
Don't jump to conclusions so easily
without even looking into it.
Don't you believe me?
It's best to reach a settlement.
Settle with them no matter what.
Hey, you don't know anything!
I'll try.
Of course, you should.
Fortunately, the arrest warrant
was dismissed.
Go back home for now.
What kind of attorney are you?
An attorney is supposed to listen
to their client and side with them.
Are you getting worked up at me?
You shouldn't do this to your client!
Are you really the Han Na-hyun I know?
The Han Na-hyun you know?
What do you even know about me?
Watch what you say.
So much for a drunk who beats kids.
Those punks deserved a beating!
That's pretty low,
coming from an attorney.
What made you become this inflexible?
You're darn annoying!
Darn annoying?
Did you say something to your sister?
I said she was darn annoying.
What?
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to.
But why is she so mean?
I'd be mad at someone
who beat high schoolers too.
No.
She isn't one to get angry
without even listening.
It's so weird
that she became an attorney too.
Why don't you go after her
if you're that curious?
What about you?
The arrest warrant is dismissed,
so I'll be released soon.
Go on now.
- Over this amazing blue sky
- Oh, there she goes again.
- Riding on the flying magic carpet
- Magic carpet
- In this amazing
- Dad, focus on driving!
- Blue world
You don't even listen to music now?
DAD
What changed you so much?
Wow.
My neighborhood hasn't changed at all.
That's a relief.
Dad?
He's got so much more gray hair.
And wrinkles too.
OFF-DUTY
Still, it's so nice…
to see you, Dad.
Honey, I'm home.
This cushion is still here.
But the sofa is new.
It's nice.
Something smells delicious.
Welcome home. You must be hungry.
- Go wash your hands.
- Okay.
Mom.
Mom…
Wow.
Your braised tofu looks so good, Mom.
That doenjang stew looks delicious too.
There you go,
drinking straight soju again.
I told you to eat as you drink.
- Okay, fine.
- Here.
Did you try calling Na-hyun?
Yes, but she just wants to dine out.
I see.
What?
Are you sad that you can't cook
for our daughter?
No, it's not that.
I'm wondering if we should move.
I think she's avoiding this house.
No way.
She's extremely busy.
We should be grateful
that she's even making time for us.
- You think?
- Of course.
Don't overthink it.
And don't walk on eggshells around her.
Look who's talking.
Geez.
Oh, the news must be on. What time is it?
Gosh.
Han Na-hyun doesn't like this house?
And you walk on eggshells around her?
Why?
Just why?
- On your 6:00.
- I know. I can hear it.
He's moving.
- I got him.
- Come on. He's fast.
- He's one tap.
- Okay.
- He's going down.
- Get him.
- Four o'clock.
- Where is he?
- Hold on. I'll help you.
- Dang.
- Hello?
- Darn, I'm out of ammo.
Gather up now.
- Where are you?
- Wait. Geez.
It must be nice to skip school,
away from your homeroom teacher.
Who are you?
I'm Attorney Yang Do-kyung.
Attorney? Doesn't that make us the boss?
Yeah, of course.
Mr. Attorney, we're busy right now.
Crazy bastard.
Visit us another time.
On behalf of you busy boys,
your parents hired me themselves.
They're quite angry
that their precious sons got beaten
without knowing what you've done
to Jun-ho for the past year.
What happened that day?
We already told the police everything.
We were just messing around
when that lunatic came and did this to us.
- You're lying.
- No, it's true.
Let me tell you something important.
That bastard who beat you up
got an attorney.
When it comes to relentlessness,
she's number one in this field.
It'll take no time for her
to find out what you've done.
You must be Min-jae.
Your father is
the Vice-minister of Health and Welfare.
Ji-hyeok, your mother is
a professor of law at Hanguk University.
Your parents will be put
in a tight spot if the truth gets out.
They'll kill me.
Right.
So now, be honest with me
about everything.
Only then, I can protect you.
I honestly don't care
about school violence.
What I want to know
is that attorney who assaulted you.
Didn't you find anything weird
about that bastard?
FILES
PARKING
My mom knows about it too?
Oh…
Well, she heard me talk
about the settlement money with Sa-rang…
Even my sister?
Things happened that way.
Mother said she'd find a way
to get the money.
As soon as she heard
you could lose your law license,
she stormed out.
Still, she was understanding
after finding out
that you were possessed
by Attorney Han's sister.
Your sister and I are trying every way
to get the money too, so don't worry.
- Bong-su.
- Yes?
I'm sorry.
And thanks.
Maybe I shouldn't have come.
You're in trouble because of me.
And I've discovered
the uncomfortable truth.
What do you mean?
Something's off
between Na-hyun and my parents.
My family wasn't rich,
but we'd laugh and have fun.
We had the most positive energy.
Now, my parents
walk on eggshells around Na-hyun.
Na-hyun is really off too.
I wonder what happened.
Something huge happened.
They lost you, their precious family.
They must've been devastated.
Oh.
Why would a family drift apart
during sad times?
I wouldn't say they drifted apart.
They're probably being considerate.
Considerate?
Some kinds of sadness
are so powerful that they quickly spread
to people around you.
STORY WHERE HAPPINESS GROWS
Worried that your sadness would spread,
you keep hiding your feelings,
watch how you speak or behave,
and even
make secrets.
Because you try not to hurt
those around you,
you'd rather drift apart
from them little by little.
I don't want my family
to live like this because of me.
It's so sad.
All the ghosts who visited me
had their sad stories.
But they all worked out.
Now that you've come,
your family may be able
to open up to each other.
I'll do my best to help you.
Thank you.
But your situation is more urgent.
My situation?
If your family loses your house
and business because of me,
it'll kill me.
Wait.
Though I'm already dead.
Anyway.
You're
quite sweet.
I can't let go of anything
that feels wrong.
What should we do to clear your name?
If what you saw that day is true,
there has to be a reason why Jun-ho acts
like he isn't a victim of school bullying.
That… is what you need to find out.
- What? Me?
- Yes.
How?
You're a ghost, you know.
- Hello.
Hello.
I'm sorry, but I don't know.
SUNG MIN-JAE
- Hello--
- What took you so long to pick up?
Sorry.
Who did you meet today?
I didn't meet anyone.
If you get caught lying,
I'll kill you for real.
I'm not lying.
Come to Heaven and Earth
by 5:00 p.m. later today.
Don't forget the money.
Okay.
Why are you doing this to me?
What did I do…
to deserve this?
I'm going to kill them.
Who is it?
Hello, I'm Attorney Han Na-hyun.
Attorney?
Are you Jun-ho's mother?
Yes.
Did something happen with my son?
Didn't he tell you anything?
I don't get to see him often
because I work at night.
Did he cause some kind of trouble?
No.
Your son is involved in a small case,
but he's not an assailant.
Do you perhaps know where he may be?
Jun-ho.
I saw it that day.
Those guys were bullying you.
No, they're all my friends.
- We were just messing around.
- They aren't…
your friends.
- You know that.
- I don't get what you're saying.
- Jun-ho.
- I'm leaving.
Hey, Seo Jun-ho!
So what are you going to do?
What?
What's your plan?
Are you really going to kill them?
Long ago,
there was a guy like you
back in my school.
He was harassed by school bullies,
but his parents and teachers
were clueless,
not to mention his classmates.
So what?
Why are you telling me this?
Guess why those guys hang out in packs.
Because they're cowards.
So don't hide.
Fight back when they come at you.
No, I can't do that.
Nothing is impossible.
Only if you make up your--
I can't do it, okay?
I can't!
Don't tell me…
Do they have something on you?
I'm leaving.
Is that it?
What if I do?
Does it give me the right to kill them?
- Hello, Jun-ho.
- Jun-ho, hi!
I'm going to take a super fun video
from now on.
- Let go of me.
- Lights, ready?
- Hey, lights.
- One moment.
All ready now.
This bastard looks awfully pretty today.
- Stop.
- Stay still for a sec, Jun-ho.
They blackmailed you with it.
Yes.
Those scumbags took a video of me naked.
Still, you shouldn't do the same to them.
The guy I mentioned earlier
ended up in juvenile hall
after hitting those bullies with a brick.
No one was there to understand
why he had to attack them.
Your case will be the same.
You'll only suffer more.
So please.
Give me the knife.
Now.
No, don't go!
Don't go to them!
An assailant can't meet a victim.
You know that.
You should've told me
about the situation sooner.
Unbelievable.
Sorry.
Did Jun-ho tell you
where he's meeting up with the boys?
Five o'clock at Heaven and Earth.
That means we have enough time.
Heaven and Earth, right?
Come on, follow me.
POLICE STATION
But this is only
Jun-ho's side of the story.
You're right,
but his classmates and the owner
of his part-time workplace
saw a suspicious sight of school violence.
They also said they'd testify if needed.
I'd really appreciate your help.
Were they unable to help?
It seems like someone has to die
before they take action.
But we're running out of time.
I better take Jun-ho's video away
from them myself.
It's the only evidence to prove
that they've been bullying him,
let alone the day of the case.
Sounds good. Let's go right away.
No, not with you.
They know what you look like.
What if they recognize you and run off?
But I can't let you go alone.
I know you better than that.
There's another reason, isn't there?
Yes.
He can get another knife anytime.
Now that I know, I must stop him.
He's a diligent kid that will be happy
if he can just get over this hump.
A boy's life is on the line here.
I'm going to do something about it.
Don't ever come
inside the Internet café, okay?
Okay.
I'll wait nearby and only stop Jun-ho.
Instead, my brother-in-law
will be there to assist you.
Welcome.
- For two, please.
- You may sit anywhere that isn't taken.
Okay.
HEAVEN AND EARTH PC
UNDER CONSTRUCTION
- Excuse me, the power is out!
- What the heck?
- What's going on?
- I was so close to winning.
Mister.
Just testing things.
- What are you doing? Turn it back on!
- Turn the power back on!
- We're terribly sorry!
- He's so high maintenance.
ATTORNEY YANG DO-KYUNG
What's up?
I have good news for you.
The parents are willing to settle.
I told them they should never settle
with a piece of trash who beats kids.
But an attorney has no power, you know.
I follow what my clients say.
Check the settlement agreement.
I texted it to you just now.
SETTLEMENT AGREEMENT
TOTAL AMOUNT: 150,000,000 WON
Do you actually believe
50 million per person makes sense?
Then, does an attorney
beating high schoolers make sense?
When someone intellectually and socially
accomplished fails to set an example,
they must be held accountable.
Discuss it wisely with the assailant,
and come to Taebaek by 6:00 p.m.
if you don't want I-rang to go to jail.
Hello?
Hello, Ms. Attorney.
The victims' attorney just called me.
They want me to come to Taebaek's office
by 6:00 p.m. for a settlement.
Taebaek called you too?
Yes.
I get what they're trying to pull.
They're demanding 150 million won
for settlement money.
They must've expected
Attorney Shin wouldn't
easily agree to the big sum
and gave you a call too.
I understand.
I'll be there on time.
Could you give me a little bit of time?
How much time?
About an hour or two.
It'll be past 6:00 by then.
Let me think only about my son right now.
I don't want him to suffer.
I understand how you feel, but…
It's okay.
Thank you for your concern.
I'd like you to stay away from me.
I know from experience
that it's better to stay away from ghosts
in dangerous situations.
Should I be with Na-hyun, then?
Sounds good.
I'm gonna take a leak.
- I'm going with.
- Me too.
Hey, just go upstairs.
Jun-ho might run off.
- Wait upstairs.
- Make it quick.
I MADE A GROUP CHAT
THANKS, BONG-SU
One is going in.
One's here.
It's him, right?
Yes, but why is he alone?
Let's stick to the plan.
Hey, kid.
You shouldn't take my picture, gosh.
You really can't without permission.
I have rights to my own image.
Why would I take a picture of you?
Sure, I understand.
It's rare to run into a celebrity
in this kind of neighborhood.
- Still--
- I'm lost for words.
Mister, I don't know who you are.
Wait. You're him, right?
Yoon Bong-su.
He's really famous. Don't you know him?
This guy?
Was it Showboating Squid?
No, Steamboating Squid! Right?
I enjoyed watching that drama!
- Oh, goodness. You watched it?
- I really liked it.
Han Na-hyun, are you really an attorney?
You're a real celeb?
I'd be one too, then.
Anyway, I didn't take a picture of you.
Oh, my. My fans are so shy.
It's okay!
You know what? You're lucky today.
- I'll take a selfie with you. Don't worry.
- No, thanks.
- I'll make you look good.
- Let me do it for you.
Oh, thank you.
What the… You still have that phone?
The attorney told us
to throw away our phones.
Did you guys do it?
Of course.
I got a new one with Seo-won right away.
Score!
It's too good to waste.
I'll toss it after showing his mom.
She deserves to see her son's video.
Don't you think?
You always have a point.
- I wish we edited a little better.
- Let me see.
A masterpiece is a masterpiece after all.
- The video isn't here.
- That can't be.
- Oh, no.
- What are you doing? Give it back.
- She's looking for a camera app.
- Give it back to me.
DID YOU FIND IT?
- Hold on…
- It's my phone.
Damn it.
Min-jae, run!
- You're that guy…
- What?
Fuck! Guys, run!
Ow.
Hey, stop right there!
I got it!
Over there!
Attorney Yang.
I'll send the police there.
Don't worry, and get out of there.
You got a new phone,
so you should be okay.
Send the police to Heaven and Earth PC
at Dream Mall quickly.
Yes, sir.
Did you find the video?
No, both of them got new phones.
- Did you catch the one who ran?
- Not yet.
Taebaek actually demanded 150 million won
for the settlement.
Your mother said she'd go there
to settle on your behalf.
What time are they meeting?
In 30 minutes.
I'll try my best to drag it out.
Call me when you find the video.
Okay. Please do that for me.
I apologize.
My son's assault is on me.
I'm to blame for not raising him better.
This will never happen again.
Please give him a chance.
How shameless of you
after what he did to those children!
STORED
What the fuck?
I had a hunch, but you actually came here.
Why are you so surprised?
This is where you used to beat me up.
What? Did you rat us out?
It wasn't me.
You wouldn't believe me, though.
How dare you talk back to me?
Do you have a death wish?
Why would I die?
It's your turn to die.
Wow.
I see you're quite fearless
now that I'm alone.
But you're no match for me, f*****.
Yeah, I know you can fight.
But I won't simply take it today.
Then what, motherf*****?
Delete my video right now.
You're after this too?
Amusing.
You wanna act tough
in front of me, fucker?
You son of a bitch.
I wish I could beat you up to a pulp,
but I'll stop here
because I'm quite busy today.
- Give me your phone.
- Get off me.
Get off!
Get off, damn it!
Are you out of your damn mind?
Die!
You damn nutcase.
Give me your phone.
Give me your phone!
Jun-ho!
Get off me. Get the hell off already!
No, you're not going anywhere.
Give me your phone.
Then, I'll forgive you.
Forgive me?
You crazy asshole.
Who do you think you are to forgive me?
I said I'll forgive you!
You little…
I took it away from him.
I didn't do it like them.
I did it my way.
How did I do?
Well done.
You didn't ruin your life for them.
I'm so glad.
TAEBAEK
SETTLEMENT AGREEMENT
TOTAL AMOUNT: 150 MILLION WON
Excuse me.
What do you think you're doing?
Sung Min-jae, Na Ji-hyeok, and Lee Seo-won
were arrested
for aggravated assault, illegal filming
and distribution of illegal content.
They also beat Seo Jun-ho up
on the day of the assault case.
And Lee Seo-won confessed
that Attorney Shin I-rang
only tried to stop them.
What are you talking about?
Hello?
The police?
- Hello?
- Min-jae.
I'll be there immediately.
Did you do something again?
Your son will arrive soon.
Please wait for him downstairs.
Thank you, Ms. Attorney.
Don't you have any words for me?
About what?
I heard you told them
to throw their phones away.
Is it true?
Why are you so surprised?
You resort to any means possible
to win a case.
That's your way, isn't it?
I thought
we were the same kind.
You haven't changed.
Is it because of Shin I-rang?
Is he behind your change?
Mind your own business.
Lee Gang-pung, Kim Su-a, and Jeon Sang-ho.
- They're all dead.
- So what?
All his clients were families
of dead people.
Why does he only take on such cases?
Why does he keep getting involved
with dead people?
Besides, he swore like Lee Gang-pung
and acted like Kim Su-a.
How did he find out
where Jeon Sang-ho's body was buried?
Don't you find it strange at all?
His office
was a shaman's house
until a few months ago.
Shin I-rang can see ghosts.
It's dangerous to be around him.
Stop talking nonsense.
THURSDAY, JUNE 7, 2012
I wonder who's more at fault.
The one who hit them with a brick?
Or the ones who bullied him to death?
He had no choice…
If I become the best attorney,
will I be able to understand him?
will I be able to speak
for his resentment?
No one was there to understand
why he had to attack them.
Who's there to understand the victim
who had no choice but to attack them?
His office was a shaman's house
until a few months ago.
And my office used to be a shaman's house.
MY DAUGHTER, NA-HYUN
Hi, Na-hyun.
- How have you--
- Have you been to a shaman's house before?
What?
Have you ever visited a shaman
after that incident?
H-How did you…
Was it in Seocho-dong?
I can see and communicate
with dead people.
This time, it was Su-a.
Last time, Lee Gang-pung's spirit told me.
You shouldn't do this to your client!
Are you really the Han Na-hyun I know?
What made you become this inflexible?
You're darn annoying!
So-hyun.
No way.
PITTER-PATTER BUTCHER-STYLE BBQ
I'm sorry, Mom.
Is Attorney Han aware
that her sister has come?
No.
I don't know what to do.
She'll be shocked if she hears it.
Maybe it's better to keep it from her.
For what she did this time and all,
let's treat her to a meal sometime.
Ask her when she's available.
Okay.
What are you doing here?
Na-hyun.
Attorney Han?
I was meaning to call you.
Do you have time right now?
Why do you ask?
I need you to go somewhere with me.
You want us to ride that?
You don't want to?
Well, it's not that I don't want to.
Good, then.
I'll go buy tickets.
I'm afraid of heights.
You like that?
I go crazy for them!
Hold on.
Does Attorney Han know
that you like roller coasters?
Of course! We came here
so many times on vacation.
Then the reason
she took me here…
Na-hyun.
Let's sit in the last row again today.
- With our hands up.
- With our hands up. Deal?
Na-hyun.
- Is it you, So-hyun?
- It's still I-rang.
Let me be alone with her
without you today.
Don't you worry.
I feel so bad for Na-hyun.
I shouldn't stay here.
Is it right to pass on like this?
I don't want to break her heart anymore.
I see. It was thoughtless of me.
Where's So-hyun?
They all passed on.
- No.
- Take care.
Don't go.
Subtitle translation by: Eunjin Erica Kim