(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
1995, APRIL 26
Minoru, you're so slow!
Makoto!
Wait!
1995, APRIL 26
Hey, Minoru.
What do you want to be when you grow up?
A ninja!
A ninja?
What about you?
I…
don't really know.
Bam!
It hurts!
Mom! Dad! Minoru's…
2010, APRIL 27
-Minoru, hold that side.
-Okay.
2010, APRIL 27
Moving on to our next story.
The Diet has passed a bill today
to abolish the statute of limitations
for heinous crimes, such as murder.
And this evening, it was put
into effect with unusual speed.
Under this bill, crimes for which
the statute of limitations has expired
cannot have this statute
retroactively abolished.
As a result, cases from April 27, 2010,
and earlier, will have
their statute of limitations
considered expired,
while cases from the 28th will have
no statute and remain open.
The amendment bill for the review…
Only two days.
It was just two days…
Now, we can't arrest them.
RELAXED FARM: A COW-RAISING GAME
OTHER RECOMMENDED APPS
CONGRATULATIONS.
IT'S A HEALTHY BABY COW!
SHIORI KUDO: PLEASE GET HERE ALREADY
He always texted back,
he was nice, and we got along.
I thought he was perfect.
-Yes.
-But…
Turns out he had a hidden side.
A hidden side?
I went to his house,
and I ran into his side piece!
She told me,
"Sorry. My boyfriend deceived you."
-She was crying, making a scene.
-What?
Anyway, I didn't get it, so I asked him,
"Which one of us are you dating?"
-And what do you think he said?
-What?
"Neither of you."
What?
Next, we have a coroner from the Kanagawa
Police Department, First Division.
Inspector Tagusari.
PARTICLES FOUND BETWEEN VICTIMS' NAILS
FIRST INVESTIGATIVE DIVISION
My name is Tagusari,
I'm a Medical Examiner.
Regarding the small particles
detected under the victims' nails,
we've limited their possible origins
to a few factories in Kanagawa.
Just to be safe, I have expanded
the search to the Kanto suburbs,
and the list of factories is attached.
Then, the closet suddenly
clicked open, and someone came out.
Who came out?
A girl from my work!
What?
They got friendly while I wasn't looking.
MAKOTO TAGUSARI: I'M ON MY WAY
SHIORI KUDO: WHEN WILL YOU ARRIVE?
MAKOTO TAGUSARI: SOON
Mr. Tagusari.
You don't plan on coming at all, huh?
We got a request for support
from the Section Chief!
No…
I was just about to go.
Then let's hurry.
Oh, hello.
Hello.
The Director was happy.
He said you did great.
He would like to have a meal with you
once the case is resolved.
-Decline for me. Make up an excuse.
-Really?
Tagusari.
An unnatural death in Kanagawa Ward.
Understood.
Okay.
At around 7 a.m. today,
when Ms. Nagisa Kuroki,
who works for a travel agency, got home,
she found the man she was living with
dead from multiple injuries.
The body was identified from his ID card
as Satoshi Makimura, 27 years old.
A part-timer at a restaurant--
The entrance was locked?
It seems only Ms. Kuroki
and Mr. Makimura had keys.
Probably some lovers' spat. Here.
But Mr. Tagusari,
she couldn't have done it.
For the past week,
she was in Paris as a tour conductor
for an overseas tour.
Paris?
If this was a murder,
it would be a locked-room mystery.
What?
Spare me the convoluted tricks…
Thank you.
Hello.
There are no signs
of entry from the balcony.
What about a duplicate key?
No suspicious persons seen
on the apartment security cameras.
It's probably natural causes.
Yeah. Like heart failure.
How do you explain
the injuries on the body?
For now, let's ask the coroner's opinion.
-Okay.
-Oh, hello!
Hello.
I'm Kiritani
from the Medical Examiner's Office.
Thank you for your help
in preserving the scene.
Medical Examiner Tagusari has arrived.
Go ahead.
-I'll begin.
-Okay.
Left temporal area.
Okay.
Left hand palm, an abrasion.
Yes.
None on the right.
Left lumbar area, also an abrasion.
Yes.
Left abdomen…
Discoloration?
Okay.
How long has it been?
Three weeks since you joined us…
Getting used to the job yet?
If you have any problems,
don't hesitate to speak up.
The one having problems is me.
At least be on time.
What?
You'll ruin my reputation too.
Ishizaka, I'm on time, right?
-I think you're fine.
-See?
What?
What is it?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What's the cause of death?
Oh, I don't know yet.
Is it related to the injuries?
I can't say for sure right now.
Any information?
As an Inspector, you must be making
good money. Make yourself useful.
Estimated time of death is between
3:00 p.m. and 6:00 p.m. yesterday.
Is that it?
Is there anything else
that can be identified at this stage?
No.
Please proceed
with the autopsy procedures.
Okay!
MATSUIZUMI MEDICAL UNIVERSITY
No rib fractures.
Diaphragm, left fifth rib,
right fourth intercostal space,
opening the chest.
-Rib shears.
-Here.
-Take a picture.
-Please look properly.
I am looking.
-Your eyes are closed.
-I'm looking!
No fluid around the left and right lungs.
Fluid in the lungs.
Possibly caused by a heart attack?
A heart attack…
There was also cardiac hypertrophy.
Perhaps heart failure
caused the buildup of fluids.
Yoshida.
Mr. Kagura.
It's strange there's no
water buildup in the lungs.
In that case, neurogenic pulmonary edema
is a possibility.
If it's neurogenic,
the fluid in the lungs
might be caused by something
other than heart failure.
The cause of the fluid buildup
was a head injury.
This would be the fatal wound.
Around when was the head injury sustained?
The exact time is unknown. However…
Since no fibroblast infiltration
was observed,
it hasn't been 48 hours.
-Estimated time of death?
-5:00 p.m. yesterday.
In other words, the head injury
was sustained within 48 hours
prior to 5:00 p.m. yesterday.
So the crime scene
may not be limited to that room.
However, we don't know
if this injury was accidental
or if there's foul play involved.
Did he hit his head somewhere,
or was he assaulted?
I'll contact headquarters.
Oh, tell them to check
Mr. Makimura's clothes.
The clothes he wore when injured
should be at his home.
Understood.
Don't do anything unnecessary.
-You're the one who told me to work.
-It's probably an accident.
Investigating that is your job.
I only care about knowing
the truth of how he died.
Mr. Tagusari!
I've got the post-mortem certificate.
-Thank you.
-Yes.
Here you go.
My job is done here.
Inspector Tagusari.
Lend me some money.
-There's a big race coming up.
-Quit it…
Excuse me.
Here.
Oh, wow.
Hey…
This shop is…
Health certificate.
Right, yes.
Well…
Your eGFR is, well, just barely okay.
Oh, right…
About how much for one kidney…
It hurts!
Old man, go to work.
Oh, gosh.
The certificate.
Oh, it hurts…
It hurts.
-You're interfering with my business.
-What is this?
Just be quick about it.
We don't buy this here.
What?
Huh?
I gave you this as a gift
when you first got the job!
I'll buy it back once I win the race.
You're terrible.
Hey…
Just take this and go home.
Haruko.
I can't buy a betting ticket
with dumplings, you know.
They're not for you.
They're a gift for Minoru.
Unlike his tactless older brother,
he's actually well put-together.
COVO REVERIO AOI
I'm home.
Welcome back.
From Haruko.
Okay.
You're not planning
to crash here indefinitely?
FUREASU APARTMENTS
This place is close to my work.
Makoto.
I'll leave if you get
a girlfriend or something.
Not in this lifetime then.
Only because you aren't serious about it!
Oh, wait.
Wash up first!
What?
You were at an autopsy.
Makoto.
The body we found today…
Don't bring it home. Stop.
That body had an abrasion on the palm.
Normally, if you fall,
you instinctively put your hands out.
If you had no time to put them out,
the damage should be more severe.
Under what circumstances
did he get those injuries?
Why didn't you say this earlier?
It's just a guess.
Aren't investigations all guesswork?
What if I guessed wrong?
I've been tossed around plenty
by relying on guesses.
I'm only interested in the truth.
I've heard that a million times.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
-Seven.
-Hey…
Six.
-Five.
-Morning.
-Four.
Three.
Two.
Well, it's true that you are on time.
He's almost late every time. Not good.
Will my coming five minutes early
increase the arrest rate?
It makes a huge difference
in our initial response.
What a pain.
Are you two at it again?
Morning.
I guess having vitality is a good thing.
It would be great if that vitality
caught criminals too.
But this time, we don't even know
if there is a criminal.
I'll go to Mr. Makimura's
part-time job to trace his steps.
Please do.
We'll investigate his girlfriend.
Where in those 48 hours
did he sustain the head injury?
Consider both accident and foul play.
-Yes.
-We will.
If he was assaulted,
we'll have to set up a task force.
A joint investigation with First Division.
Please let it be an accident. Please…
Hello.
Mr. Makimura's family has arrived.
I explained the autopsy process
to the family.
Kudo.
Tagusari.
Hurry along.
Yes, okay.
Such a pain.
Is he your family member?
We'll now begin the procedures
for releasing his body…
Wait…
Is something wrong?
Isn't he your son?
No.
This isn't Satoshi.
Please take a good look.
Perhaps he's thinner than before?
My son is already over 40.
He can't be young like this.
He was using an ID card
to fake his identity.
Do we have his fingerprints?
He was never arrested.
He probably ran away
after getting into debt.
Oh, hello.
Hello.
Mr. Makimura wasn't on shift
at his part-time job during that time.
Then, his whereabouts
during those 48 hours…
I'll check his social circle,
but I hope we get something
from his girlfriend.
Oh, right.
The jacket Mr. Makimura often wore,
I found it in the footage
from the CCTV at his workplace.
Well, our body isn't Makimura, though.
This body…
Now we know even less about it.
Where, how, why it happened,
as well as who he is.
Now I wish
it was just a locked-room trick.
For now,
let's clear things up, one by one.
His girlfriend might know something.
-Can I drop you off at HQ?
-Yes, please.
I'll be home late today.
You won't need dinner?
Yes, you eat first.
But I'm also busy
with examinations this afternoon.
Maybe I'll just whip up some beef bowls.
Beef bowls, huh.
LET'S GIVE THEM A NAME
Maybe I'll eat out today.
I'll get off here.
Thank you very much.
Goodbye.
You two seem more like
a married couple than brothers.
Excuse me.
I'm Kudo from the Aoi Station.
You didn't know?
I started dating him two years ago.
At that time, he said
his name was Satoshi Makimura.
What about before you started dating?
It seems he had several part-time jobs.
Do you know anything about those jobs?
Or anything about his hometown,
family, or background?
I don't.
Suddenly asking me about his past…
I don't even know anymore.
In the end,
I didn't know anything, did I?
Not even his name.
To think I don't even know why he died.
Do you know what he did those two days?
When I'm working,
I hardly ever contact him.
Excuse me. May we borrow that jacket?
Sure.
Send this to forensics.
Yes.
Did you notice
anything different about him lately?
Even a guess is fine.
Just tell me.
I noticed it this morning.
He always used to leave his bicycle here.
Was it gone by the time
you returned to Japan?
Did he use it often?
It's a bit of a distance to the station,
so when he took the train, he'd ride it.
The palms don't touch it.
Between the house and the station,
we found Mr. Makimura… Oh.
I mean, the former Mr. Makimura's bike.
The rear wheel is deformed,
so it's likely an accident.
Yes. Excuse me.
A hit-and-run, huh?
He didn't report it to the police.
He couldn't, right?
Because he was hiding his identity.
Oh, that’s true.
Our case was a hit-and-run,
so we’ll leave the rest to you,
the Traffic Department.
Yes.
Oh, it’s finally over.
Tagusari!
I’m sorry.
We’re a bit short-staffed.
Could you give us a hand?
What?
We got a tip-off,
and are currently pursuing this guy.
It would be great
if the Violent Crimes Division
could search for the car
that hit our former Mr. Makimura.
HIT AND RUN CASE
THE STATUTE IS ALMOST UP!
REQUESTING INFORMATION TO AID ARREST!
CHINESE RESTAURANT
MOCCHAN
-Huh?
-What?
It's closed.
Huh?
Let's just open it.
Heave-ho.
Mogi?
Is he out getting ingredients?
Maybe…
Shall we start first?
Okay.
Go get the snacks.
Got it.
And here I thought the case was over.
You seem really fed up with that body.
Shut up.
Once the car model is identified,
are you chasing the car next?
I wish they'd just turn themselves in.
What are you guys doing?
Don't talk about cases
in a place like this.
There are no customers.
I overheard a little bit.
You're fine, Mogi.
More importantly, lock the door.
I told you before.
Oh, sorry.
I was thinking about
what to buy and forgot…
-Mogi, yakisoba.
-Me too.
Coming up.
Let me through.
Did something happen?
What?
It's rare for you to help
another department out.
The Traffic Department's suspect
was also a hit-and-run.
He has been on the run for 20 years
after causing a fatal accident.
The statute of limitations is almost up.
I see.
1995, APRIL 26
You have to make the noodles
"swim" around a bit.
-Swim?
-Yes.
That's it.
-I think it’s good.
-Is it?
So dinner is yakisoba.
Mom is so bad at making it.
-I wonder if she has been practicing.
-It's really not yum--
Hey!
I can hear you!
Oh, no!
Mr. Tagusari, do you have a moment?
You again? So persistent.
Without your witness testimony,
the proposal won't get approved.
I don't care about that!
Mr. Tagusari.
You were smuggling, weren't you?
From offshore.
Tell us.
I have nothing to say.
Mr. Tagusari, you transported
goods to the port too, right?
Hey.
Let me hear your side. Hey!
-I'm busy, go home.
-No!
I'll come by again tonight.
Here goes…
-What? We'll have dinner soon, you know.
-Who said they were going to quit smoking?
No… Me, smoking?
I can tell by the smell.
Stinky.
Dad! Who were you talking to
outside just now?
What?
Apparently, your dad will be interviewed.
An interview?
You'll be on TV?
-Don't be stupid!
-Will you get money?
-What?
-Buy me a PS1!
-No…
-I want a picture book!
I told you, that’s not it.
Look, it's time to eat.
Let’s eat.
Here you go.
You're using that again?
What?
It's delicious!
You guys want to try some?
No!
-Let me put it on for you! Hey!
-No!
-Please don't!
-Come on, it's good.
It's yummy, you know.
Okay, let’s eat!
Let's eat.
Looks good.
I poured on too much.
Yummy.
It hurts!
-Minoru!
-It hurts!
-Minoru?
It hurts!
Mom! Dad!
-It hurts!
-Minoru's…
It hurts!
It hurts…
Makoto!
It hurts!
Around 11:00 p.m.
on the 26th of last month,
at a residence in Yomogida-cho,
Kawasaki Ward, Kawasaki City,
residents Mr. Sakutaro Tagusari,
and his wife, Yuka, were found murdered.
The perpetrator
has not yet been identified.
Sakutaro and Yuka were killed
by stabs to the chest and shoulders.
Based on the condition of the bodies,
the weapon used was…
Here you go, yakisoba.
Thanks.
I still don't get it.
It’s just sour.
Is the former Makimura's girlfriend okay?
No.
Please find the killer, for her.
Because for the people left behind,
time just stops.
Hey.
These are all fakes anyway.
How rude.
I have the real ones somewhere.
That's great.
So, what do you need today?
I can't lend you money
in exchange for dumplings.
Find his identity.
-This is a pawnshop.
-Before this, you were a reporter, no?
What did this man do?
He died in a hit-and-run.
Can I count on you?
What? Have you decided
to become a detective for justice?
If justice existed,
I'd sell it to you for one yen.
What do you want?
Hello?
I'm looking for someone.
Could you look into it?
From the bicycle's paint,
we found that the car that hit
the so-called Makimura was a white van.
However, after checking surveillance
cameras on Hayase Street…
What, 104 cars?
It's quite a common car model.
Well, makes sense.
Over a span of 48 hours, there should be
that many cars that took that road.
But if we have to check 104 cars,
I don't know how many days it will take.
This should be handled
by Traffic Department,
but we are tied up with another case.
Please do what you can, within reason.
Understood.
The Traffic Department knows, doesn't it?
It's not guaranteed that all the cars
are from Kanagawa.
We have to check a few,
and hope we get lucky.
104 cars…
Seriously?
We got through
just four cars this morning.
This is quite tough.
Go on ahead.
Wait, you'll get off here?
Excuse me, please help.
Thank you very much.
Please help.
Here's 350 yen…
That's 200 yen too much, Mogi.
Right.
Here.
Right, sorry.
Thanks for the meal.
Thanks.
Not picking that up?
No.
It's the Director.
He wants to go for a meal
since the case is resolved.
Is that so? It's a chance for a promotion.
Maybe.
Oh, last time,
you prevented a terrorist attack,
so you got a special…
Special promotion.
Right!
That’s how you became Inspector.
Next is…
I'm not really interested.
Why not?
What a waste!
I didn't join the police for that.
And besides,
I'm not good with living people,
so my current position is just right.
Not going to see Haruko?
You finally found out
where she is, so go see her.
To you guys,
she's like an older sister, isn't she?
So persistent.
FORENSICS
Twelve… Twelve?
Twelve cars?
That's the most we can check in one day.
Guess we have to work hard
until we can hand it back to Traffic.
Let's start checking
tomorrow morning again.
I'm counting on you.
Good work today.
-Bye.
-See you.
You're on duty the night shift today?
See you tomorrow.
-I'm heading out first.
-Bye.
-See you.
The next car is…
Working hard, I see.
Of course.
Why are you here?
Stains were found
on the former Makimura's clothes.
Did you analyze them?
They turned out to be
cast iron rust and some oil.
It's similar to what's found
on screwdrivers or bolts.
So some kind of tool…
ANALYSIS
These stains are too big, though.
Whatever caused them
must have been on Hayase Street,
where the bicycle was found,
during the two days from April 17th.
Traffic Department again?
April 17th…
APRIL 17, 2026
This is it.
It's a pulley
for hoisting heavy equipment.
What's the date and time of recovery?
April 17th, 11:14 p.m.
Two days ago, lucky.
The accident occurred sometime
within the 48 hours
before the estimated
time of death at 5:00 p.m.
In other words,
the accident occurred
between 5:00 p.m. and 11:14 p.m.
two days ago,
when the fallen object was recovered.
That's about six hours.
The search for the white van
will be much easier.
Minoru!
Finding the criminal isn't my job.
Five, four, nine, one…
Two, one…
Not this one.
Good morning.
Kudo speaking.
Thanks to the part that fell off,
we narrowed it down to 31 cars.
All the way to Tateyama in Chiba…
Did you investigate these all night?
There are nine cars left.
The hit-and-run car is among these.
No.
It's seven cars.
MINORU: BOTH MINAMI-KASHIWA
AND FUTAKOTAMAGAWA WERE DUDS
MAKOTO: I KNEW YOU WOULD HELP
Three cars left.
This house?
I'm Kudo from the Aoi Station.
You are Masaya Nogami, right?
Police?
There was an accident
on Hayase Street on April 17th.
May we see your car, Mr. Nogami?
There was a male victim who passed away.
Please open your garage.
Sorry. I have to get to work.
Hey…
-What are you doing?
-Show me your car.
We'll find out eventually. A hit-and-run?
No. I didn't run away.
Then what happened?
Dad, what's wrong?
It's nothing.
Go to your room.
Let's talk outside.
I never thought he would die.
VICTORY
Ow!
After I gave him 20,000 yen
for the bicycle repair,
he left immediately.
The victim had reasons
to refuse the police or hospital,
and you, Mr. Nogami,
thought it was just an unlucky accident.
I tried to contact the police too,
but he really said he was okay.
Even so…
Even so, you're still guilty.
You violated the Road Traffic Act
for not reporting an accident.
And…
negligent driving resulting in death.
There's someone who wants to know.
Why someone important to them had to die.
I'll come again next month.
Okay?
When will you catch them?
Why did my mom and dad die?
When you don't know anything…
The pain just never stops.
What has gotten into you?
Normally, you'd be complaining
about it being a pain.
Hey.
Where are you going?
LOOKING FOR WITNESSES
OF A TRAFFIC ACCIDENT
Please help.
Excuse me, please help.
I'm looking for someone
who witnessed this murder!
It happened April 26th!
I'm looking for someone
who witnessed this murder!
It happened April 26th!
Please help.
That's enough.
I can't give any details yet,
but we have secured a suspect.
Really?
Thank you very much.
The Diet has passed a bill today
to abolish the statute of limitations
for heinous crimes, such as murder.
And this evening, it was put
into effect with unusual speed.
2010, APRIL 27
Under this bill, crimes for which
the statute of limitations has expired
cannot have this statute
retroactively abolished.
As a result, cases from April 27, 2010,
and earlier, will have
their statute of limitations
considered expired,
while cases from the 28th will have
no statute and remain open.
The amendment bill for the review…
Only two days.
It was just two days…
Now, we can't arrest them.
I couldn't do anything.
Thanks for your help.
Our case almost had its statute expire.
-Hey! What are you doing?
-Stop it!
Stop, now!
Stop!
THE STATUTE IS ALMOST UP!
REQUESTING INFORMATION TO AID ARREST!
You look just like it.
What?
Just take him away.
Come on.
The list of unidentified persons
in the Prefectural Police database.
Why didn't they abolish
the statute of limitations for all cases?
I just can't accept it.
I haven't found him in there.
-Please tell me.
-I have nothing to say.
-Hey.
-I'm busy, go home.
No!
I'll come by again tonight.
1995, APRIL 26
Where could he be?
He may not be in Japan.
But…
He might be laughing somewhere out there.
When I think about that…
I can't sleep well.
Why did they have to be killed?
It's been 31 years already, huh.
We’ve been tied to that day,
all this time.
Hello?
Are you still trying to identify
the former Makimura?
Community Safety is handling it.
I reached someone who knows
that former Makimura guy.
His real name is Jun Okochi.
Why did he get a fake identity?
Two years ago,
he was exposed online for driving
a high school student to suicide.
A digital tattoo, huh?
By the way,
the student who committed suicide was…
What’s wrong, Mr. Tagusari?
Where is Nogami?
Since it was a voluntary accompaniment,
I let him go.
The man Nogami killed in the accident
drove Nogami's son
to suicide two years ago!
SAFE DRIVING
WATCH OUT FOR ROAD RAGE
He’s gone!
Search the area!
It wasn't an unlucky accident.
Maybe, from the start,
he intended to kill him.
MEN'S 100M SWIMMING CONTEST
OKI NOGAMI
Hello.
Someone saw a person
looking like Nogami on Asahina Street.
Nogami!
Nogami's motive is revenge.
His moves are too unpredictable.
Did my dad really kill someone?
As revenge, it’s a job well done.
Subtitle translation by: Nix S.