The sea doesn't look beautiful today.
But whether the sea is beautiful
or not doesn't really matter.
Because for me,
it's the same every single day.
But the sky
it's never the same even for one day.
Yet it's still just as mesmerizing.
I wonder if you're looking
at the same sky too.
When I was a kid, whenever
something upset me,
I always came here to hide.
This place was our secret base.
Phoon… Phoon.
Phoon.
Fah is here now.
He was the only one I wished would find me.
Phoon.
Fah is here.
P'Fah.
And he always managed to find me.
- It's okay, Phoon.
- P'Fah.
It's okay. I'm right here.
- You don't have to be scared, Phoon.
P'Fah.
Where have you been? Are you hurt anywhere?
Mom and Dad aren't back yet.
Don't be scared.
I won't tell Mom and Dad.
That you sneaked out to play.
- Really?
- Of course.
Thank you, Fah, for bringing Phoon home.
Then I'll head back now.
Otherwise Mom and Dad
will know we snuck out late.
- I'll get scolded again.
- Okay. Bye-bye.
Come on. Go inside.
I thought we'd get to attend
the same high school again.
What a shame.
Then who's going to tutor me and Phoon?
Fun and Phoon are already good students.
I will study hard.
I'll get into medical school.
And become a doctor like you, Fah.
I'll work hard too.
Let's become doctors together.
Don't forget us once you
have new neighbors, okay?
Aww. I won't forget you.
Phoon.
We probably won't see
each other for a long time.
Take good care of yourself.
Yes.
Alright, kids. Come take a photo.
Come on, stand a bit closer.
Alright then. One, two, three.
Switch places.
Switch left and right, quickly.
One, two, three.
Ms. Theerapa Chaowakornkul Born: 13
September 1996 Died: 10 October 2013.
Phoon came to say goodbye.
Goodbye, Fun.
Yes, Uncle Kong.
Why are you leaving so early?
Isn't your flight this afternoon?
I stopped by to see Fun first.
Why didn't you tell me?
I could've taken you to the airport.
Don't you have to help
my dad with work, Uncle?
I didn't want to bother you.
Bother me? Not at all.
Are you sure you can go
to the airport by yourself?
Yes, I can.
I'll send the rest of your
things after you later.
If you need anything, let me know.
You're going all the way to Chiang
Mai alone. I can't help but worry.
Thank you.
Have a safe trip.
Yes.
Fun.
Phoon is about to go see P'Fah now.
To: Torfun
I've arrived in Chiang Mai.
I just got to the dorm.
The semester is about to start.
I really feel guilty toward you, Fun.
For failing the medical school entrance
exam, even though I tried so hard.
I wanted to become a doctor for you.
But next year, I'll definitely make it.
The weather is nice today.
I'm thinking of going out to take some photos.
Please wish me luck so I don't get lost again.
Lost again?
Excuse me.
How do I get back to the university?
I'm not going that way.
That's a different direction.
Then where are you going?
I'm heading to Tha Phae Walking
Street. Someone called me to pick them up.
The walking street?
Yes.
Then hop in.
Oops.
Sorry.
Phoon.
Do you remember me, Fah?
Yes.
It's been so long.
Almost four years, right?
How have you been,
Phoon? Are you doing okay?
I'm doing fine.
Really?
What are you doing here all by yourself?
Oh—Tonfah. It's been a long time.
I'm doing well. How about you?
We're doing fine too. Are you here alone?
Yeah, but I'm heading back soon.
Phoon. Phoon.
Phoon.
P'Fah.
I saw this little guy running
around in the rain by the roadside,
so you followed it and ended
up getting lost here, right?
Yes.
I'm sorry for causing
you trouble again, P'Fah.
It's not a problem.
What did I tell you?
If you get lost, just sit and wait.
I'll come find you myself.
I found you.
So you're actually studying here?
I thought you were just here on vacation.
The semester doesn't even
start for another two months.
I just wanted to try living here first.
There's still a lot I need to adjust to.
What made you decide to come
study so far away by yourself?
Well.
I just wanted to give it a try.
What faculty are you in?
Veterinary Medicine.
I thought you wouldn't like that field.
No, I actually like it quite a bit.
And…
You're studying medicine, right?
Yeah.
Thank you.
I really thought I'd never
see you again, Phoon.
Yeah…
Oh...
So you came here alone?
Did you come with any friends?
I came by myself.
Really?
That's impressive.
You haven't changed much at all, Phoon.
You look just the same.
It really brings back memories
of when we were kids.
Back then,
we were always together.
You, me, and Fun too.
By the way, how's your dad doing?
I haven't heard anything
since you moved out.
He's doing fine.
- Mm.
- My mom.
I don't really know how she's doing.
What do you mean?
My parents divorced.
My mom moved out after that.
I'm sorry, Phoon.
Are you okay?
How's Fun doing?
Fun's doing fine.
Thanks for driving me back.
Drive safely.
Okay. See you.
Yeah.
To: Torfun.
Dear Torfun,
I ran into P'Fah today by chance.
I was really shocked.
I didn't know what to do.
There were so many
things I wanted to say to him,
but when it came down
to it, I could barely speak.
He looked happy to see me.
He even asked about you.
And I ended up lying,
saying you were doing fine.
I'm sorry I lied to him like that.
I was afraid that if he knew the truth,
he'd be disappointed in me.
He might get angry, just
like Mom and Dad did.
You're not here anymore,
and if P'Fah isn't by my side either,
who would I have left?
You lied to me, didn't you?
- No, I didn't.
- I already know about Fun.
This is really bad—what
you did, and lying to me too.
Is there anything else
you're lying to me about?
Huh?
I'm seriously disappointed in you, Phoon.
You hurt everyone, especially Fun.
If you hadn't done that back
then, Fun wouldn't have died.
Do you even realize
you're the one at fault?
Yes.
Another thing.
I hate liars.
And I can't forgive people
who keep hurting others.
It'd be better if we never
see each other again.
P'Fah, I'm sorry.
- Let go.
- P'Fah.
P'Fah, I'm sorry.
P'Fah.
P'Fah, please don't leave me.
Please don't leave me, P'Fah.
Thank you.
Two pork skewers and
one sticky rice, please.
Alright, dear. Why
are you eating so little?
Are you feeling sick?
You look a bit pale.
No.
Here you go.
- How much is it?
- 20 baht.
Thank you.
My battery's about to die.
- Come here. Now.
- Ow!
I told you to come here!
Get in. Go inside.
Do you even know what you've done?
How many times have I told
you not to go into my office?
Do you know that the vase you
broke is worth more than your life?
Get that through your head.
Stay in here. Don't go anywhere.
Dad… Dad…
- Stop crying.
- Dad, I'm sorry.
Dad, I'm sorry. I won't do it again.
- Don't call me.
- Dad…
You little bastard. Shut up.
P'Fah! Fun! Someone, please help me!
- Phoon, are you inside?
- P'Fah, please help me.
It's so dark. I'm scared, P'Fah.
Easy, Phoon.
It's really dark in there.
Reach your hand out.
Don't be scared. I'll stay with
you until Uncle Kong comes back.
Don't go anywhere, P'Fah.
Hello, P'Fah. Is this a good time to talk?
Is something wrong?
Uh… it's just that at my dorm
the power went out.
My phone battery's almost dead too.
Are you still afraid of the dark?
I am.
What room are you in?
Room 302.
I'll get there before your phone dies,
so don't hang up until we meet, okay?
Okay.
Phoon?
Phoon, are you okay?
I asked the security guard downstairs. He said
the power will likely be out until morning.
Then why don't you stay
over at my place tonight?
Would that be okay?
There's no other choice.
You don't have to feel awkward about it.
Let's go.
Careful.
It's not as dark here. Do you feel better?
Yes.
Do you want to wipe your sweat?
Thank you.
Make yourself at home.
Okay.
Are you sleepy? Want to go to bed now?
I can sleep now.
Then go sleep in the bedroom.
Um… I can sleep on the couch.
You should sleep in the bedroom.
I'll sleep outside.
Come on.
Here.
I'm not sure if it'll fit you, though.
Try it on.
Thank you.
If you need anything, just call me.
Actually.
I really can sleep on the couch.
I don't want to bother you.
It's fine. The bed's more comfortable.
Then...
We could sleep in the same room.
It's okay.
You sleeping there is better.
Good night.
Um...
- P'Fah.
- Yeah?
Thank you.
Yeah.
Sorry. I was just grabbing a book.
I ended up waking you.
It's okay. I wasn't asleep yet.
Is the bed uncomfortable?
No.
Sleeping with the light on
makes it harder to sleep deeply.
Want to try turning it off?
I don't think that's a good idea.
Why not?
Maybe it'll help your fear of the dark too.
I've tried before, but.
I really can't.
Then I'll stay with you. Try your best.
If you're scared
you can hold my hand.
You'll stay with me
until I fall asleep, right?
Yes.
Once you're asleep, I'll go sleep outside.
- P'Fah.
- Yes?
Good night.
You're awake?
Sorry I woke up late.
It's okay.
Mm.
Go shower and get dressed.
We'll grab something to eat.
Thank you.
Hey, Phoon.
Can I get Fun's LINE ID?
We haven't talked in a long time.
I want to know how she's doing.
Uh...
Wait a sec.
I'll send it to you.
Okay.
So Fun's studying medicine near home?
Yeah.
That's surprising. Why did
Fun let you study here alone?
I insisted on coming by myself.
She didn't even come to drop you off?
Did something happen while I was away?
Did you fight?
No, nothing like that.
She thinks I'm grown up now, so
she doesn't worry as much anymore.
I see.
Yeah.
P'Fah.
Yeah?
You haven't heard anything from my family?
No.
Why do you ask?
Nothing.
- Oh.
- I thought
your mom and dad were
still in touch with my dad.
My parents hardly ever talk about your dad.
It's like he disappeared.
So I thought
I'd never see you or Fun again.
Will you ever go back to Phuket?
Probably not.
The old house was sold.
If we hadn't met here
we might never have met again, right?
But we did meet.
What a coincidence.
Out of so many universities
you
ended up choosing the same one as me.
Yeah, I guess so.
Fun, it's Fah.
I ran into Phoon today. He's
studying at the same university as me.
Really?
Is something going on at home?
Why would you ask that?
Phoon seems different.
Different enough to worry me.
Maybe I'm just overthinking it.
No. He's still the same Phoon.
Are you free tomorrow? Let's go out.
You look tired.
Did you have trouble sleeping again?
Well
yeah.
Did you sleep well the
night you stayed over?
I did.
Then
if you can't sleep again,
you can stay over again.
How long has the insomnia been going on?
For a long time.
Have you seen a doctor?
I have.
Did it help at all?
(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
Not really.
Have you talked to anyone about
your fear of the dark or enclosed spaces?
I think they might be related.
No, I haven't.
Then let's go. I'll take you.
It's okay.
Have you eaten yet?
I have.
Don't lie to me.
You haven't eaten, right?
Right.
Do you usually eat this little?
Are you sick?
No.
I think we should make a deal.
You finish your meal,
and I'll take you out.
Deal?
Why?
To fix a kid's bad habit
of not eating properly.
- But—
- I'm not taking you out for free.
Let's call it a fair exchange.
Then you don't get anything out of it.
So, do we have a deal?
Alright.
Finish it quickly so we can go out.
Why are you making that face?
I'm full.
The view here is really beautiful.
Totally worth finishing your meal.
Let's go pay respect at the Buddha first.
Shall we?
Why do you like taking photos of the sky?
Because it's beautiful.
Hmm?
P'Fah.
Wanna play a game?
What kind of game?
We take turns asking one question each.
And if it's a question
you don't want to answer?
Well...
Then you don't have to answer.
Just kidding.
Sure. Who goes first?
Me.
Mm.
I want to ask you something, P'Fah.
While we weren't seeing each other,
how have you been?
That's more ordinary than I expected.
I've been fine.
Nothing special.
Going to classes, reading,
and tutoring on the side.
What about you, Phoon?
Me too.
Nothing special.
Really.
How were your high school friends?
We were close, like normal.
Studied together, hung out sometimes.
Nothing out of the ordinary.
And how about you?
I'm doing okay.
Mm.
What about your friends now?
My friends now…
They're all kind of weird.
But it's fun being with them.
You don't have friends here yet, right?
How's Sri Thong?
Did you get lost?
P'Fah.
Can we keep it?
I think
we should find someone else to adopt it.
But I want to keep it.
It must be really lonely.
If it stays with us, it won't be.
Are you lonely, Phoon?
You have everyone.
My parents aren't with me,
and P'Fah and Fun are both busy.
I think
your dad wouldn't allow it.
Then I'll take care of it.
And you can come play with it often, okay?
Really?
Thank you.
What do you want to name it?
How about “Sri Thong”?
Mm, that's nice.
Sri Thong.
Oh no.
I'm sorry.
Even though you took such good care of it,
but when it was with me...
You don't have to apologize.
I believe you did your best.
Now it's my turn to ask.
May I ask
something personal?
Sure.
Right now,
are you dating anyone?
No, I'm not.
That's strange.
- What about someone you're talking to?
- No.
Oh.
Is that strange?
For me?
Love feels very distant to me.
Why?
I dated someone back in high school.
After a while, I realized
love is complicated.
And I felt like I couldn't really handle it.
So we broke up.
After that,
love wasn't something I
was looking for anymore.
I see.
They even said
that I were like their sky.
I never wanted to be that.
When it rains,
the sky isn't beautiful.
No one wants to look at it.
But people expect the sky
to be beautiful every day.
I
Can't be anyone's sky.
Can't you be
my sky?
A friend? What's his name?
Johan.
- Interested?
- No.
I'm taking the medical exam.
Could you tutor me, Fah?
In Mawsynram, India, rainfall reaches over 10,800
millimeters a year— about nine times more than here.
The sky looks beautiful today.
It's nice that the sky can
make you smile this much.
Phoon,
keep smiling, okay?