=Eight Hundred=
It's not that I'm lecturing you.
(Year 1994)
Going to an illegal coal pit to treat people?
And you got your leg mangled.
To put it nicely,
you accepted a buyout of your seniority.
But to put it bluntly,
you were basically fired.
And who did I do it for?
Wasn't it for this family?
Our expenses are so high now.
Is your measly salary enough?
How many times have I said it?
Don't worry about the money.
I'll find a way eventually.
Songge's dialysis
costs 200 yuan per session.
That's 1,600 yuan a month.
With the salaries we had,
could we even manage?
So what? You bought out your seniority,
and now, you're going
to look for a job like a youngster?
But by taking the buyout,
at least I got a lump sum.
It can keep us stable for a while.
What about when a kidney is found?
The surgery costs 300,000.
How will you solve that? Tell me!
Don't make things difficult for me.
If I'm pushed to the limit...
If I'm pushed, I'll sell the house.
Sell the house?
What right do you have to sell it?
Is this house even yours?
It was a reward for Dad
saving someone back then.
Besides, if you sell the house,
will the five of us live on the streets?
Songge,
I'm going to leave here
to earn money.
I'll see if I can bring back even more.
That way, I can get you cured.
Just be patient for a while longer.
Everything will get better.
Chen Hui, I'm sorry.
Why are you crying?
Songge,
never say "sorry" again.
This isn't your fault.
No one wants to get sick.
Trust me.
I will get you cured.
Songge,
before I come back,
you must take good care of yourself.
It's so late. Where did you go?
And with Songge?
Why are you being so nosy?
What do you mean by "nosy"?
So am I not allowed to have a say?
It's their own business.
- Why do you have so much to say?
- Go up and rest.
What do you mean by "his own business"?
Is he not my son?
Even if he's your son,
he has his own thoughts.
Is it right to come back this late?
Why can't I say anything?
Stop fighting, you two.
Dad, Mom,
I've made up my mind.
I'm dropping out of school.
I'm going to Jin'gang to earn money.
I'll take care of Songge's medical bills.
What did you say?
Let me tell you, Hui.
Making money is for adults.
It's not something
you should be thinking about.
Fengyang is only this big.
So how do you two
plan to earn enough
for Songge's kidney transplant?
I've already told you.
This isn't something
you should worry about!
Right now, you just focus
on repeating your final year
and getting into university.
Otherwise, I'll pull some strings
to find you a job here in Fengyang.
I don't want that.
Does everything
have to go according to your plan?
What's that?
So you're all grown up now, huh?
I'll handle my own business.
I'm not cut out for studying anyway.
And I don't want
to stay in Fengyang anymore.
What's wrong with Fengyang?
Tell me, what's wrong with Fengyang?
Tell me. In Fengyang,
you are my son.
But what are you outside of Fengyang?
You have no experience,
and you have no certificates.
You're nobody. Do you understand?
Can you two please stop fighting?
Just listen to what he's saying!
Can you please just stop it?
You're right.
I'm a nobody.
I'm not here to negotiate with you.
I've already made up my mind.
Anyway, I'm quitting school.
I'll be responsible
for Songge's medical bills from now on.
Hui.
Hui!
=Episode 13=
(Jin'gang)
Why is this here?
Dad, look at your son.
He left such dirty clothes in Hui's room.
Hui wore those back.
How is that possible?
Since when does Hui
wear Hongbing's clothes?
He was taken
to the police station by Hongbing.
He wore this when he came back.
This was the outfit.
What did you say?
When was Hui
taken to the station by Hongbing?
Last week,
on your birthday.
Hui called Songge.
I overheard it.
On my birthday?
It
was the day after we had cake.
Hui even told me back then
not to tell you.
I just forgot.
(Computer Purchase List)
Hui,
you don't need to show me
these accounts.
Just let me know
the final cost.
Mr. Huang,
we're partners.
I have to tell you
all the internet cafe's expenses.
We're opening tomorrow.
I even hired a lion dance
to bring us good luck.
A lion dance?
That's great.
Oh, Hui, after you go back,
stop by my house.
Drive my Benz away.
You can use it.
I don't need it.
If I leave it at home,
no one can drive it.
It'll just rot
if it sits there too long.
You're always in the city,
so driving it
will give you a good image.
At the very least,
it's handy for hauling stuff.
Mr. Huang,
what's wrong?
It's nothing. I caught a cold recently.
I've been coughing.
This won't do.
You need to see a doctor.
It's fine.
Just a respiratory infection.
I'll be fine in a few days.
How is your father?
He
is doing okay.
My mom is there with him.
(Xiaojian Home Appliances)
Boss, I'll take this one.
Alright.
Come pick it up in three days.
Xiaojian.
Mrs. Chen, buying appliances?
No, I wanted to ask you something.
What is it?
Go ahead.
Are you going to take over
Hui's roller skating rink?
Who told you that?
That business of his
is early mornings to late nights
and full of all kinds of rough people,
so I can't handle it.
Well, a few days ago,
Hui
came back to Fengyang.
Did you two have a drink together?
No.
It has been three or four months
since I last saw Hui.
What's wrong?
Is everything okay?
It's nothing.
I was just asking.
I'll let you get back to work.
I'm leaving now.
Take care, Mrs. Chen.
(Yingxiong)
Where should I put this?
Just put it here.
The firecrackers go here too.
It's past mealtime.
Are you hungry?
We've been hungry for a while.
If you're hungry, why didn't you say so?
I thought you could live
on air alone.
Get lost.
I'll go buy some food for you.
Keep tidying up.
Okay.
Mrs. Chen.
Liu Ning,
let's go.
How about we go buy the food instead?
Alright, let's go.
Let's go, Lei.
- Hello, Mrs. Chen.
Mrs. Chen,
anything?
On the night of my birthday,
Hui was caught by his dad
and locked up for the night.
Did you know about this?
Songge,
you've never lied since you were little.
You can't fool me.
I know, Mrs. Chen.
Why?
It was just a misunderstanding that day.
Mr. Chen released him
the very next day.
Chen Hui was just afraid you'd worry,
so he didn't tell you.
My husband
has been a cop in Fengyang for 20 years.
He's never suspected the wrong person,
and he's never arrested
the wrong person.
What did you and Hui do?
Songge,
I was being selfish before
when I didn't want you two together.
But Mr. Chen is different.
He's a policeman.
He deals with serious matters of the law.
You must tell me the truth.
Mrs. Chen, it's really not like that.
It really was just a misunderstanding.
The more you say that,
the more unsettled I feel.
I don't know if I should ask
about this matter
or if I should interfere.
I don't know
if...
If Hui
really did something wrong,
between the two of them,
whose side should I even take?
Mrs. Chen, please don't cry.
Don't be upset.
Isn't Hui doing fine now?
Besides, neither Hui nor I
really knows
the reason for it.
Don't get stressed.
Don't let it ruin your health.
I hope...
I hope what you're saying is true.
I hope my husband
has the wrong person this time.
Mrs. Chen.
I know
I owe your family.
I won't let Chen Hui
come to any harm,
even if it costs me my life.
In this lifetime,
I only have one wish.
I just want this family
to stay together.
Songge.
You're back.
Is everything ready for the opening?
Yeah.
I went to see Mr. Huang today
and talked about the opening tomorrow.
He's let us use his Benz.
We have to work hard.
We can't let Mr. Huang down.
Definitely.
I got you a gift.
What do you think?
Why are you buying me new clothes?
You're the lady boss
of the internet cafe.
Tomorrow is the opening,
so you have to look beautiful.
Besides,
this is a new beginning for us.
Yes.
Tomorrow is a new day.
Everything will get better.
It surely will.
- You're back.
- Yeah.
The food is cold.
I'll go heat it up.
No need.
Forgot to tell you,
I already ate at the station.
That's fine.
As long as you're not hungry.
What's making you so happy?
Look at this.
How is it?
Does it look handsome?
Show me.
What do you mean?
Isn't
Hui's internet cafe opening tomorrow?
If you're not busy,
let's go take a look.
What's so special about an opening?
It's not like we haven't seen one.
How can that be the same?
That's our son's internet cafe.
Besides,
I want to go see it.
I don't even know
what an internet cafe looks like.
If you want to go, then go.
I have things to do
at the station tomorrow.
Get some rest.
Not bad, Hui.
You even brought in the Yue Lion Troupe.
Just for good luck.
Internet cafes like this
are only just becoming
popular in first-tier cities.
You're among the first group
of people to try this out.
Try what out?
I'm just happy to make a living.
Look at you being humble.
It's about time.
Let's start the opening.
Let's wait a bit longer.
Mrs. Chen is here.
Mom.
- Hui.
- Where's Dad?
Your dad has some
urgent business at the station.
Come on, do the unveiling.
No, I don't know how.
- Come on, Mrs. Chen.
- No.
Take a photo, Mom.
It's so lively.
The opening ceremony
starts now.
Three,
two,
one!
(Yingxiong Internet Cafe)
Happy opening!
It's so lively today.
Why don't you say
a few words to everyone?
A few words!
Thank you, everyone.
First, I want to thank
the friends who came to support us,
and also my first wave of customers.
Second, I want to thank my mom
and Songge.
Thank you for your support.
Long story short,
third,
we have a grand opening promotion today.
However much you top up,
we'll match it for free.
Please.
(Yingxiong Internet Cafe)
We double your top-up amount.
Welcome.
Please come on in.
(Year 1994, Jin'gang)
Stay sharp when you go into the private rooms.
Have some situational awareness.
(Jin'gang Karaoke Sales)
Those who come to Jin'gang to spend money
are our gods.
If you piss off the gods,
there will be consequences.
Come on, let's review
the Jin'gang's welcome greeting. Begin.
- Your needs,
- our mission.
- Excellent service,
- never stop.
- Good.
You saw it just now.
My roller skating rink
has great business.
At this time of day,
it's even busier.
If business is so good,
why stop all of a sudden?
I'm not from around here.
I can't handle
the local thugs.
It's different for you.
You're locals.
You don't need to fear them.
Have a seat.
Sir.
Hello, your drinks are ready.
Young man,
this is for you.
Thank you.
Don't move.
Police. Stay still.
What are you doing?
What's going on? What are you doing?
You're Tian Jinhai, right?
Yes.
You should know
what bad things you've done.
I didn't do anything.
Don't remember?
Come back to the station with us.
On what grounds are you arresting me?
Let me remind you.
No. 126 Fanyu Road
looks like an entertainment center,
but you should know what goods
are actually being stored inside, right?
Sirs,
let's talk this out.
Everything
is negotiable.
Negotiable?
Well, we're a bit short
on cash right now.
How much are you willing to pay
to settle this?
What are you doing?
Police business.
What's it to you?
I've already called the police.
They'll be here any minute.
Right here!
I'm the one who called.
Real police. Let's go.
Hai,
let me see.
Wait, let me unlock them for you.
Don't worry, Hai.
They were fake cops.
How do you know?
Real cops
use double-locking handcuffs.
These are clearly knockoffs.
Not bad, young man.
Here.
Take it. Here.
Go on.
Thanks, Hai.
Young man,
what's your name?
I'm Chen Hui.
(Public Phone)
Hello, Chen Hui.
(Jin'gang Telecommunications)
How have you been doing over there?
I'm doing great.
Don't worry.
How are Mom and Dad?
Mrs. Chen still cries
whenever you're mentioned.
Mr. Chen is still a bit angry with you.
I see.
Are you doing okay?
I'm all good.
Chen Hui,
if you have time,
you should still call home.
What happened?
Your parents
had another fight a few days ago.
A really nasty one.
They said they're going
to sell the house.
Tell them they don't have to sell.
Money comes fast for me here.
Right now,
I've saved up another 3,000 yuan.
I'll wire it to you guys in a bit.
Give it to me.
Give it here.
Hello.
Dad.
Think you're all grown up now?
Since the day you left,
you haven't called home once.
Have you ever thought
about how worried we are?
I'm sorry, Dad.
Tell me,
do you have any money?
Can you even afford to eat?
You...
Find some time to call your mom
and let her know you're safe.
Since you left,
she hasn't had
a single good night's sleep,
you know?
You brat,
so you're hiding here.
- What are you doing?
- Hui!
- I'll kill you!
- What's wrong, Mr. Chen?
Hello?
Hui, can you hear me?
- Brat, being nosy, huh?
- Hui!
Ruined my plans.
Wait.
The money.
Don't take my money.
This is my life-saving money.
Brat,
that's for sticking your nose in.
Don't let me catch you
on this street ever again!
Let's go.
(Jin'gang Karaoke)
Take good care of Li and Hai. Alright.
Hui, look what time it is.
Why just getting here?
I'm sorry.
What happened to your face?
I accidentally tripped.
Looking like this,
won't you scare the guests away?
Hui!
Any orders, Hai?
Not you. Go get Hui.
Hui, quick!
Hurry up.
Get over here.
- Hai.
- Drink with me.
Everyone here is a good friend of mine.
Today, you're with me.
Let's have a few drinks.
Come on, quiet down.
Quiet down, please.
Let me give a grand introduction.
This young man here
is the one who saved me the other day.
Applause, please!
Good.
Go have fun.
Come here.
Here.
I don't smoke.
You don't smoke?
Fine. Come.
Have a drink with me.
That day, at a glance,
you knew if the handcuffs
were real or fake.
Were you a cop before?
No.
My dad is the local
Deputy Director
of the town police station.
Where is your hometown?
Fengyang.
It's a small mining town.
But, Hai, you probably
haven't heard of it.
It's a small place.
A deputy director of a small place?
He can do whatever he wants there,
just like Lee Rock.
He's not that powerful.
They say those miners
are all very rich.
Your hometown
must be very lively.
It is.
They all say it's
a "Little Hong Kong, China"
in the valley.
Little Hong Kong, China?
So impressive?
I really didn't expect that.
So you came from
"Little Hong Kong, China" to Jin'gang
to make money?
Yes.
My girlfriend
has uremia.
I need to pay for her treatment.
Uremia?
That costs a lot of money.
Yes.
Relying on this job of yours,
you won't make enough.
By the time you've earned it,
I'm afraid your girlfriend
won't be able to wait that long.
I have no other choice.
There are plenty of ways to make money.
I'll teach you slowly later
how to make lots and lots of money.
We can talk more later.
Come,
have another drink with me.
Cheers.
Hai,
sing a song.
What should I sing?
Anything is fine.
Hai is going to sing!
Clap, please!
(Peidun Cough Syrup)
Sing a song!
♪You're always too soft-hearted♪
♪Too soft-hearted♪
♪Crying alone until dawn♪
Hui,
are you awake yet?
Hai,
why am I here?
You got wasted.
So?
Did you have fun last night?
Last night,
what liquor were we drinking?
It wasn't liquor.
It was Peidun Cough Syrup.
Drink a bit of it, and you'll feel like
you're floating.
Is it a drug?
It's not a drug.
It's medicine.
But
drinking it does feel addictive.
Hui, do you remember
what we talked about yesterday?
Come.
You asked me how to make money.
Yes,
I remember.
I'm here to tell you
to join me
in the cough syrup business.
I guarantee
it will save your girlfriend.
The coal miners
have plenty of money.
They spend all day underground.
It's exhausting and dangerous.
If you sell this to them,
they will love it.
Plus, your dad is the Deputy Director
of the police station.
With him covering for you,
nothing can stop us.
Hai,
I don't think I can do this.
Hui,
I think you're smart enough
and have vision.
That's why I'm willing to help you.
It doesn't matter if you don't do it.
You can just keep working odd jobs
and slowly make money.
Yes,
you can wait,
but can your girlfriend's life wait?
In her condition,
she needs a kidney transplant soon.
Otherwise, the complications
will only get worse.
In Fengyang,
you're my son.
But what are you
once you leave Fengyang?
You have no experience,
and you have no certificates.
You're nothing, you know?
Your parents
had another fight a few days ago.
It was a nasty one.
They said they're going
to sell the house.
How much do you want to make?
380,000 in two years.
380,000?
In two years?
Too greedy.
Hai.
I'll do it.
Can you give me the equipment
from the roller skating rink?
What do you want the stuff for?
If I go back to selling medicine,
I'll need a cover.
Smart.
Hai, what are you doing here?
Hui,
my good partner.
Why did you suddenly
disappear for months?
I had to come see you.
Let's find a place nearby to chat.
Yingxiong Internet Cafe.
Business is booming.
Not bad.
It's a popular spot.
The machines are brand new.
Each one must be expensive.
Hai,
there are too many people here.
Whatever it is,
let's find a place to talk.
I'll buy you dinner.
That's not right.
Aren't you going to invite me in to see?
Hai.
This one.
Try this one.
Hello, Miss.
Chen Hui, is he your friend?
Yes, my friend.
- Hello.
Hui,
your girlfriend
is quite pretty.
Here, Miss.
Happy opening.
Top up 1,000 yuan for me.
Here.
Well, thanks.
Welcome to visit us often.
Sure.
Songge, you take care of the customers.
I'm going to talk with my friend.
Okay.
Let's go.
Bye-bye.
(Ruijin Hotel)
Hui,
why are you so nervous?
You know me.
I am quite easy to talk to.
Hai,
it's like this.
Some things happened here lately,
so I didn't have time to contact you.
I know, you're here for
the payment for goods, right?
Not just the payment.
The interest, too.
Right.
Look, today
won't work.
I just opened.
How about this?
Tomorrow at 2 PM,
wait for me on Hongqi Road.
I'll give you the money.
Can I trust you?
Hai,
my shop is right here.
I can't run away.
Fine.
See you tomorrow.
Take care.
(Pawn)
(Hongxing Pawnshop)
Mr. Chen,
let's get this straight first.
(IOU)
Last time,
I heard Huang Liang mention your dad.
If you're short
a single cent on the due date,
I'll go to the Fengyang Police Station
and ask your dad for it.
Don't worry, Mr. Jun.
When the day comes,
I will return everything,
principal plus interest, for sure.
Two hundred thousand.
In six months,
pay back 240,000.
No problem.
But I need it in cash.
Count the money for him.
Here's the payment I owe you,
principal plus interest.
It's 200,000 in total.
You're really something.
Going to a loan shark
to get cash.
This way, no one can ever trace it.
I wasn't wrong about you.
Hai, let me take you back to the hotel.
Whatever you say.
Hai, I've paid back the money I owed.
From now on, we're even.
Shouldn't you head back to Jin'gang?
What's that supposed to mean?
It means we're done with each other.
Hui,
of all the downline dealers
I've developed,
you're the only one
who hasn't had any trouble for years.
You think you can just quit
whenever you feel like it?
I told you from the start,
once I saved enough for my girlfriend's
medical bills, I'd quit.
You agreed to it.
Hui,
this life isn't something
you can just walk away from cleanly.
Well, I'm quitting anyway.
What are you going to do about it?
If you quit,
I'll report you to the police.
You have no choice.
Your crimes are heavier than mine.
Well, there's
nothing more to talk about.
You just wait and see
if I'm bluffing or not.
Still using this old trick?
You think
I'd come to see you
without being prepared?
(Jiangbin City Kaixuanmen Grand Hotel)
Look at this.
The hotel front desk receipt.
Receipt for a report letter.
If I can't
return to the hotel today,
this letter will be
mailed out tomorrow morning.
(Jiangbin City Kaixuanmen Hotel)
Hui,
do you want to come inside with me
and see if I was
bluffing you?
Hello, sir.
Hello.
I'm staying in room 306.
I left a letter here yesterday.
Could you check
if it has been sent out yet?
Certainly, sir. Please wait a moment.
I'm sorry, sir.
You brought the mail in
too late yesterday.
But the mailman will be here soon,
and it will be sent out shortly.
That's fine.
I'll just have my friend mail it.
Alright.
Thank you.
Go back and take your time reading it.
(Report Letter)
- Hello.
May I know
which organization
this number sequence corresponds to?
This looks familiar.
Hold on, let me check for you.
What's the number?
951127.
9511...
(Jiangbin City)
Here it is. It's the Municipal PSB's.
Yes.
Okay.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
(Report Letter: Yingxiong Internet Cafe's owner,
Chen Hui, sells Peidun Cough Syrup)
♪I always thought
once we see the full picture♪
♪We could understand
each other with empathy♪
♪I always thought
the path we never took♪
♪Must have had more beautiful scenery♪
♪I always thought
once we see the full picture♪
♪We could understand
each other with empathy♪
♪I always thought
the path we never took♪
♪Must have had more beautiful scenery♪
♪Keep moving forward
and don't look back♪
♪The shore is only reached
by the road ahead♪
♪Too much debt has accumulated♪
♪Lit night♪
♪Unfortunately, the breeze in town♪
♪Can no longer catch up to the children♪
♪Times have changed♪
♪Now, everything♪
♪Is no longer what it used to be♪