In the previous episode,
Nankatsu faced
the difficult team
from Shimizu.
Right from the beginning,
Tsubasa was marked
by orders of
the opposite team's captain,
preventing him
from doing anything.
On the other side,
Wakabayashi received
a direct hit
on his injured leg
making him unable
to move freely.
It was a hard blow
to our beloved goal keeper.
Despite all the odds,
all the members
from Nankatsu
did their best to clear
the way for Tsubasa,
allowing him to score
a goal against Shimizu.
At the end, Nankatsu
managed to win the match
and now,
they will be representing
the Shizuoka Prefecture
in the national tournament!
No, Tsubasa!
It's not ready yet!
-Ow!
-Easy!
It'll be ready soon,
so go and take
your bath now.
But Mom, I'm really hungry.
Let me have some.
Ugh!
What a stubborn kid!
This is a typical day
in the Ozora family.
The captain, his wife
and Tsubasa.
This is a warm happy family.
But even if the three
of them agreed...
will it be really okay
to take Tsubasa
with me to Brazil?
A family must stay united.
If I take Tsubasa,
then I'll be the one
tearing them apart.
-Roberto...
-Oh!
What's the matter?
I'm all right.
Okay then.
[opening theme]
Episode 13:
The National Tournament Begins!
SIXTH JUVENILE NATIONAL TOURNAMENT HOKKAIDO FINAL
Hey, what are you doing,
Sapporo?!
Go get the ball!
There's only
one minute left!
Captain!
The Sapporo team attacks
with numerous players,
but can't get the ball!
Captain Hikaru Matsuyama
from the Furano team
controls the ball!
You won't get the ball!
Oh no!
Ah!
This guy is so annoying!
Get the ball
away from him now!
Captain!
Make a pass!
No, he can't!
The captain is
completely surrounded!
What do we do?
Hikaru
Matsuyama keeps the ball!
Can he get away from
the opposing team!?
And now,
we're in over time!
Given this situation,
it looks like our favorite,
the Sapporo, will lose.
Come on, Furano!
Just a little bit more!
Captain, hang in
there a little bit more!
-Ah!
And the referee signals
the end of the game!
Yeah! We did it!
Impressive!
The famous Sapporo team
has lost to the Furano team!
Now the Furano team
will move on to
the National Tournament!
Despite the adversities
and all thanks to
its Captain,
Hikaru Matsuyama!
The team managed
an incredible victory!
We were able to
win this game!
And we did it
without Misaki.
Yeah!
We'll go to
the National Tournament
and we'll complete
against him!
-Yeah!
We did it, Misaki.
I can't wait
to play against you
in the national tournament.
MISAKI
Are you done, Dad?
Tell me...
will we go
somewhere else now?
Yes.
Hm...
Once the national
tournament
and the semester end,
you'll have to transfer
to another school.
You should tell
your friends.
Sure, Dad.
I'm sorry, but I think
you should forget about
the national tournament.
-But doctor!
-Genzo, please calm down!
Listen, Genzo,
you have a bright future
ahead of you.
Don't risk it like that.
If you go into
the tournament,
your injury will
only get worse.
The best is to wait for it
to heal completely.
He's right, Genzo.
You shouldn't risk
your whole future for this.
Please try to understand.
But it's just that...
that I made a promise
to someone
and I must do my part
as well.
I'm sorry,
but Master Genzo
is not home right now.
She says
the captain is not home.
What now?
I wonder if the captain got
better from that injury.
I sure hope so.
He must get better soon,
so we can all play in
the national tournament.
Don't worry, I'm sure
we will win the tournament.
-Yeah!
All right, Son,
did you brush your teeth?
I already did, Mom!
Ugh...
Why do you treat me
like one of your employees?
That's so annoying!
Don't talk to me like that,
young man.
You may have won
the try outs,
but you've barely played
in the games!
But what do you
want me to do, Mom?
All my teammates
are really strong, you know?
Well, that's why
I'm making you work,
so you can become stronger
and you can get to play.
Aw man!
And I thought I was
gonna to take a break
these days.
Why me?
The members
from the Nankatsu team
enjoy their last break
before the national
tournament begins.
Tsubasa,
on the other hand...
Huh?
What's wrong, Tsubasa?
You can't take
that simple pass?
I can, sorry!
What's wrong
with Roberto?
He's been...
acting weird lately.
Tsubasa...
do you really want to
go to Brazil with me?
Of course!
Of course I want to go!
If you come to Brazil
with me...
your mom will be all alone.
Even so,
do you still want to
-go to Brazil with me?
-What?
Again?
I already told you, Roberto,
I do want to go.
These last
couple of days...
I've been thinking
that maybe
I'm being selfish
and self-centered.
That selfishness may break
that bond with your family.
Roberto, stop it.
It's not like that.
I think it's best if...
-Huh?
Genzo!
Can we talk?
It's urgent...
-Oh...
Tsubasa, I won't play
in the national tournament.
What?!
Uh...
It looks like my injury
is more serious
than I thought.
I must wait until
it completely heals.
And that's the reason why...
I need you to do me a favor.
Even if I'm not there,
I want you to win
all the matches
in the tournament.
Until you get to play
against Kojiro Hyuga.
All the matches?
I let him score
a goal that day.
And I failed you
as a keeper and a captain.
I'm sure I must have
my leg healed by then...
I'm begging you...
Please wait for me.
Don't worry about it...
You can count on us, Genzo.
-Let's do it!
-Send it over here!
Run!
Got it!
Yeah, one more!
What's going on?
Put more energy in it!
If you can't stand
this heat,
then you better forget
about winning the nationals!
-Yeah!
It looks like the absence
of Genzo Wakabayashi
is the cause of
their unusual behavior.
-I know.
-It is to be expected.
We have some kids
from the Shutetsu,
without him,
they must be feeling down.
It's true. Genzo is not only
the goal keeper,
he's the captain that
keeps everyone focused.
His absence is very strong
and not having him for
the next matches...
is really affecting
his teammates' spirits.
The only one that looks
to be unaffected is Tsubasa.
Heads up, Taro!
A one-two!
And Taro Misaki has always
been cool headed.
Yeah! We did it!
Idiot!
Even I could've
stopped that!
Genzo is not here now,
so you're the only one
-Now even Ishizaki
-that we've got!
-is strict.
-So put it together!
I promised him that
I would win all matches,
and I will keep
that promise.
Miss Ozora...
If your son
goes with me to Brazil,
won't you be lonely?
Huh?
Why are you so worried?
Please, ma'am.
I need to know.
The truth is...
I would be lying
if I say that
I won't get lonely
sometimes.
But just like
I told my husband,
we parents can't keep
our children
from making their dreams
come true.
But ma'am, Tsubasa
is only in elementary!
I know...
but my son is very mature
for his age.
And his biggest dream
in the world
is to become a professional
soccer player.
That has been his dream
since forever.
And that's why when you
invited him to Brazil,
he was really happy.
I'm his mom.
I want him to make
his dreams come true
without any distractions,
and when he does it,
I'll be very happy.
Well done!
Good job, you guys!
In three days, our trip to
Tokyo will finally arrive,
but before that...
I'll just name the new
captain of the team.
-Huh?
-A new captain?
What about Genzo?
Unfortunately,
he won't be able to play
because of his injury.
And that's why I've decided
to name someone else
to take his place.
I know it will be difficult
without his support,
but that doesn't mean that
we can't win without him.
We're still a strong team.
All right, listen up,
you guys!
The new captain...
of the Nankatsu team...
is Tsubasa.
Me? The new captain?
-Great, man!
-Huh?
Congratulations!
Tsubasa, huh?
I'm sure the atomosphere
will be much better.
From now on,
the Nankatsu team
will play the way
its new captain
says we will play.
-Yeah!
-Tsubasa...
-Huh?
-Some words for the team.
-Sure!
We'll be
the best team of them all!
-Yeah!
We'll be back
with Captain Tsubasa.
AFFILIATION: NANKATSU FC BIRTHDAY: JULY 28 HEIGHT: 145 CM WEIGHT: 39 KG BLOOD TYPE: A
Mom!
I was chosen as
the new captain!
What? Captain?
Really?
Yeah! I can't wait to tell
Roberto too!
Where is he, Mom?
He went out
a while ago, son.
Ugh... That sucks.
Well, son,
now that you're captain,
you'll have to do
even better than before!
I will!
At the end, the three
of them agree, but...
why do I still doubt
myself about this?
I was the one
that proposed
Tsubasa come to
Brazil with me,
then why am I...
why am I...
doubting this?
The national tournament
is about to begin, Son.
Good luck!
Please take care of him,
Roberto.
I'm counting on you.
And finally,
the day had arrived.
The Nankatsu team
embarks on their journey
to Tokyo City to play in
the national tournament.
All right! I want you all to
cheer to our beloved team,
the Nankatsu!
Let's go! Let's go!
Win! Win! Win!
-Let's go! Let's go!
-You will win!
-Hurray! Hurray!
What a good bye, huh?
I didn't think they cared
so much about us.
Even your mom is here.
Take a look.
-Go, Son! You can do it!
-Huh?
You're the best!
Genzo didn't even come
to say good bye.
-Uh-huh.
-Hey!
Don't get
so sentimental, okay?
Genzo...
I will keep my promise.
-Tsubasa!
-Huh?
-Take care!
-Roberto...
-Do you hear me?
-I will win
the national tournament
and I will go with you
to Brazil!
I swear!
Yeah, come on,
that was awesome!
-Let's go! Let's go!
-You will win!
Tsubasa!
Don't you worry!
I'll be there soon!
I'm counting on you guys.
Please wait for me.
TOKYO
WANGAN SOCCER PARK
We're finally here
to participate
in the national tournament!
Always so cheerful,
aren't you?
So, everyone's here?
I hope you didn't
forget anything
because there's
no going back.
Hey, wanna go and take
a look at the field?
Yeah, but we have to
leave our stuff
at the hotel first.
-Hey, you!
-Huh?
What do you think
you two are doing?!
-Huh?
-Got it!
-What the hell?!
Here it goes, Kazuo!
Great pass, Masao!
What's their deal?!
-Are they crazy?!
-Here!
They're passing the ball
between the train lanes!
That was easy!
-Hey!
-Huh?
Don't do that!
It's dangerous!
Jeez, these train guards
are so annoying!
Excuse me.
Masao!
Great pass!
Did you see?
They're twins!
-Here!
-Got it!
Here you go!
Hey, listen, Kazuo!
Masao!
Come here!
We have to go now!
Yeah!
Kazuo, we gotta go!
Sure, but first,
one last time! Go!
I got it!
Huh?
Are you also playing
in the tournament?
Yeah.
My brother Kazuo and I
as well.
We are from Team Hanawa.
Nice to meet you all.
Masao, let's go already!
Yeah!
What's the deal with
those two?
They are very weird.
Weird, but also
very impressive.
Yeah...
Yeah, they are.
This is so exciting.
There will be tons of
players that we don't know.
We have to give it
our best effort!
The National
Juvenile Tournament.
An event where
the young talent
can showcase their worth
against players from
across the country
during the summer.
48 teams participate
in the tournament,
divided in blocks
of six teams
to start the process
of elimination.
The best teams
from each block
will go on to the finals
and only the best one
will win.
JUVENILE NATIONAL SOCCER
TOURNAMENT TEAMS DRAW
This is going to be a heck of a time.
-Taro!
-Huh?
Ah!
Hikaru and all my friends!
How have you been, friend?!
I was surprised to see you
with the Nankatsu team.
They are from
the Furano team
and they were my teammates.
Oh!
My name is Hikaru Matsuyama.
And he's our captain,
Tsubasa Ozora.
Hi, nice to meet you!
We finally meet...
Taro has told me so much
about you, Tsubasa.
We'll be rivals now, Hikaru.
Yeah, we'll be rivals.
Tsubasa! Hello!
How have you been?!
-Hello!
-Quite the lady's man, huh?
I'm so happy to see you.
I want to introduce you
to our Captain.
He is Jun Misugi.
It's my pleasure.
I'm the captain of
Team Mussahi.
Nice to meet you, Jun.
I'm Tsubasa.
I can't wait to
compete with you
on the field,
Tsubasa.
What a pretty girl!
Hey, you're from
the Nankatsu team, right?
You're huge!
I heard Genzo Wakabayashi
is not playing.
-Is it true?
-Yeah, I guess you're right.
I'm Taichi Nakanishi
from Team Naniwa.
If Genzo is not here,
then that means...
...I'm the number one
goalkeeper
of the whole tournament.
Huh?
It's those kids
from before...
If I remember correctly,
they said they're from
the Hanawa team.
It's Kojiro Hyuga!
They are the Meiwa team.
Tsubasa's rivals
have finally gathered!
Now we'll begin the draw
for each block's teams.
From Shizuoka prefecture,
Tsubasa Ozora,
Captain of
the Nankatsu team.
Yes!
Nankatsu will be on Block 1, Slot "A."
NANKATSU SC
Wow!
Great, Tsubasa!
That's a great spot!
We'll be on Block number 1
for sure!
Why is he looking at us
like that?
The Meiwa team will be
on Slot "B" from Block 1.
That... That can't be!
They are on
the same block as us!
That means...
We'll play against
Meiwa first?!
I wasn't expecting that.
I see the first match
is against the Meiwa.
Yeah, but don't worry.
You get better
so you can play with us
at the finals, got it?
Got it.
You have to win.
You must do it.
We will, I promise.
Genzo sounded really upset
on the phone.
I can't believe it.
I really wish I could play.
But why?
Why did they have to
go against them first?
MEIWA
TEAM 3
-Captain!
-Huh?
Captain, this is yours.
Humph.
Here, you keep it.
Sure, but why, Captain?
I don't need it.
Huh, okay.
Oh! Please,
someone take us!
Just forget it, Boss.
No one will come.
That sucks.
We can't get a ride.
Well, if that's the case...
...then you must
sacrifice yourself
and get hit by a car!
That'll make them stop!
-Are you crazy?!
Huh?
TOKAIDO EXPRESS DELIVERY
Hey there, kids,
do you need a ride somewhere?
Yes! Thank you so much!
We're heading to Tokyo, sir.
That's perfect!
I'm heading there as well!
What are you
waiting for? Hop on!
Great!
Hey, everyone!
We got a ride!
-Yeah!
-Cool!
We finally can
go see our friends!
Hey, hold on!
I can only take three kids
on this truck!
What?
But it's okay.
No worrieds.
We truck drivers always
help those in need.
Attention, all units,
I need back up.
I'm in Nankatsu city.
The cargo is
elementary kids
that need to go and
support their friends.
-Please hurry, over!
-Huh?
-Wow!
-Unbelievable!
Well, you need to
get in already!
Sir, thank you
very much for everything.
So tell me,
why are you going to Tokyo?
We're going to
a soccer match.
Soccer?
So you're the cheerleaders
or what?
That's right.
Oh I get it.
I also like soccer a lot.
Huh?
Hold on, young lady,
if you had been
a team manager,
you'd gone with them, right?
It's best not to
mention that, sir!
Huh?
We don't need
a team manager.
It's all because of
that coach.
How dares he tell me
they don't need me!?
Oh well! I'll just go and
cheer the team!
And Tsubasa!
And now,
we present you the teams.
FURANO SOCCER CLUB
HOKKAIDO
Yes. This year's
National Juvenile Tournament
is about to begin.
Teams from the North
and South of Japan
have earned their place
to be here.
48 teams in total divided
into different blocks.
All of them will compete
during the following
six days.
I'm sure we will witness
some marvelous talent
that will no doubt shine
on the soccer field!
MIEWA FC
SAITAMA
NANKATSU SC SHIZUOKA
We're finally here.
The national tournament.
And now,
the Captain
from the Nankatsu team,
Tsubasa Ozora,
will say a few words.
Players!
Let's play this tournament
with honor and respect
of our competing rivals!
Let's play with passion and
a spirit of sportsmanship!
I'm here representing
Nankatsu, and my name is...
Tsubasa Ozora!
Yeah!
Well said, sweetie!
Did you like what he said,
Roberto?
I did!
Sportsmanship...
[ending theme]