[Morgan] I know how this ends.
You drive us to the middle of nowhere,
put a couple bullets in our heads,
probably make us dig a hole,
strip down naked,
bury our clothes,
you fucking sick piece of shit.
Probably blackmail us into some sort
of sexual contract with an arms dealer
or you'll just sexually traffic us.
Probably sexually traffic me, kill him.
Probably can't get a lot for him, can you?
Sounds like you don't know
how this ends, huh?
-I need you to calm down, Morgan.
-I'm literally calm.
-No, you're not.
-I'm really calm.
You know how I know you're not?
Because you've been screaming
for 15 blocks, Morgan!
[Nicky] I was fine when I came in here.
-[Morgan] Bullshit, you were…
-And then you started screaming.
You were not fine!
[Nicky] Oh my God!
-Kick me out of the truck!
-Kick him out. Kill him.
[Nicky] Your voice, I wanna die!
[Morgan] God, you are so selfish.
-How is that selfish?
-You're not alone here!
-How did I get stuck with these two?
-I'm scared to death!
Don't take that literally!
I know you're listening to us!
I'll do anything to survive.
God, I wish for once
that you could take me seriously
and show up for me.
Are you done?
-I'm done.
-Then be done.
-[Morgan] So you can just be on your own.
-[Nicky] Holy shit.
[engine stops]
[phone ringing]
[spits] Fuck.
Hello.
[pleasantly] Yes, they're in the truck.
I'm handling it.
[clerk] No, no, no, I'm dealing with it.
I'm dealing with it, okay?
[suspenseful music playing]
-[Nicky grunts]
-[loud thud]
[groaning] Ow!
Ow! [gasps]
[music stops]
[Morgan] Hey, hello!
What the hell, Nicky?
You're just gonna leave me alone here?
I gave you an exit!
The door is open.
You're just standing there like an idiot.
I didn't see a heads-up!
Get out of the truck!
-Get back in the truck!
Get out!
Get the fuck back in the truck!
Get in the truck. He knows where you live.
I don't know where you think you're going.
I…
I don't know!
Get the fuck back in the truck!
[pleasantly] No, everything is fine.
We are having a great time.
I'm gonna let you know
when everything's done, okay?
[Nicky] Nobody survives a second location
after an abduction like this.
-So we might as well just kill ourselves.
-[Morgan] All right, come on.
-No, I will be doing this. Thank you.
-We got it. We got it.
[door rattles]
[opening theme music playing]
[music ends]
[birds calling]
[quietly] Fuck.
[grunting softly]
[loud pounding]
Stupid people!
Get out.
-[shouts] Get out!
-Okay, all right.
[Morgan] Jesus.
-[Nicky pants]
-[clerk] Huh?
That's what you get
for being a little bitch-ass pussy.
Ow! Fuck!
What kind of man leaves
his sister alone in a truck like that?
Yeah, with a fucking pervert.
Don't be rude to me. I'm not a pervert.
-I don't even find you attractive.
-[Morgan] Please, you would be so lucky.
Fucking Russian asshole.
I'm not Russian. I'm Turkish.
Don't sound anything like a Russian.
[Nicky] Okay.
-Okay, listen.
-[Nicky whimpers softly]
That necklace was for someone
very important, okay?
Someone you don't fuck with.
And you fucked up the whole thing!
Hey! If it was so important,
why'd you leave it
out in the open in the middle of a store?
It was hiding there, okay?
If the cops would come
and they look for, like, illegal jewels,
they're not gonna be suspicious
for, like, a cheap display box.
What are you running out of there?
-I was running your mother.
-[Nicky] Can we keep it clean?
Don't tell me what to do, okay?
You stole from me,
and you're gonna get it back. That's it.
-I don't know how that's possible.
-I don't think so.
What do you mean? What do you mean?
[Morgan] It's around
our grandmother's neck.
Okay, so go take it
from your grandmother's neck.
-Oh my God.
-She's dead.
She's buried under the ground.
You were at her funeral.
[Morgan] You were like,
"Sorry for your loss."
-That was her?
-[both] Yeah!
Fuck! Fuck!
[muffled] Fuck!
[yells in Turkish]
-I don't know what you're saying.
-Sounds Russian, right?
[continues yelling in Turkish]
What?
-No, come on! Come on!
-Turn around! Turn around!
-Get on your knees! Get on your knees!
-Ow! Ow, ow!
-[Nicky yells]
-Listen to me.
[Morgan gasps]
You have one day to fix this fucking mess.
-Oh my God. Please, please, please.
-Okay?
-If you come empty-handed…
-Oh my God!
…I'm gonna blow your brains out!
-Do you hear me?
-[yelling] Yes, you're yelling!
If we find out that you've gone
to the cops, which we will,
I'm gonna personally skin you alive.
-Oh my God, okay.
-Burn you with acid!
[Morgan] Okay!
-Gonna find your family!
-[both] Okay!
-I get it!
-You're being very dramatic!
[footsteps receding]
[footsteps fading]
[both panting]
-Where's he going?
-What's he doing?
-Looks like he's leaving.
-What?
Leaving?
[engine starts]
[Morgan gasps] No, no, no.
[Morgan] No, no. Get up.
[Nicky] Okay, run.
[Morgan] Ow, ow! Ow!
-Where the fuck is he going?
-Fuck!
Where are we?
[funky electronic music playing]
[people speaking indistinctly]
[Natalie] Mom?
-Natalie, what is the temperature in here?
-Yes.
The cheese is sweating.
It's unappealing to the guests.
My mother would hate this.
[gasps] Oh my God.
Is that Maria Sacchetti?
How did she get in?
Oh, I'm not sure.
Um, you did put this in the newspaper.
No. You're gonna have to ask her to leave.
Your nonna specifically requested
that she not be invited.
They had that terrible falling-out.
Nonna requested someone
not be allowed at her own wake?
Well, is that so shocking to you, Natalie?
Speaking of, I specifically said
to the florist no yellow flowers,
and look at this.
Look here, one, two, three, four, five.
Everywhere I look.
Yes, no, I completely understand. Um…
But I'm not sure kicking
an 80-year-old woman out of our house
is a good look
for the family-friendly campaign image
we're planning on
putting out into the world.
-[woman] There you are! What took you--
-[Nicky] Sorry.
Jesus! What on earth happened?
Why do you look like that?
-I'm fine.
-Get in the kitchen.
People aren't gonna wanna look at that
while they're eating quiche.
-[gasps] Mugged?!
-Yeah.
You were mugged
outside my mother's funeral?
Well, I wouldn't say it was right outside.
-Right.
-We were walking home.
Why were you walking home
today of all days?
There were two perfectly good seats
in Natalie's Hyundai.
Okay, well, I didn't know
I was getting mugged. I…
-[woman sighs]
-This guy came out of nowhere.
He was asking Nicky for money,
and Nicky ran away,
and this guy chased after him
and obviously caught up with him. Yeah.
That doesn't feel like
pertinent information, Morgan.
Anyway, I tell this guy that our dad
is the former chief of police,
and that did scare him off but not before
he punched Nicky for crying.
[gasps] So he just came at you.
Well, thank God you're both okay.
See, this is why
this town needs leadership.
-Yeah.
-Right.
It's just crumbling into chaos.
Honey, go upstairs and freshen up.
The girls from
the Facebook group are here.
The last thing we need is for them
to be turning something into nothing.
-Oh my God. I'm sorry.
-Jesus Christ, Morgan!
I'm sorry. It slipped out of my hand.
I'm feeling really lightheaded.
I think-- Do you… do you think
maybe I have PTSD from…
-Oh!
-Oh my God.
You do look pale, so you go upstairs
and lie down just for a little bit.
Actually, maybe I should go home.
Okay.
In the middle of your grandmother's wake,
are you out of your mind?
You really hurt that much?
Because your brother is the one
that got punched for crying.
Yeah, I feel really…
I feel really nauseous. I feel sick.
[woman] Okay, all right.
Well, then you're an adult.
You can do what you want.
Your grandmother is rolling over
in her grave right now.
I'll get the broom.
What is this? What are you doing?
Okay, well, the cemetery closes soon.
Morgan, I told you, I am a pastor.
I can't, in good conscience, exhume a…
exhume a body for a criminal.
That's nuts.
Okay. Well, do you have any other options?
Because it's almost 7:00 p.m.
I haven't heard any.
It's not like we have a buffet of choices.
-Give me a--
-[Morgan interrupts]
Hey, there's glass.
-You might wanna… watch your step.
-[Nicky] Thanks.
If you give me a second, maybe I can
come up with some kind of answer,
but there has to be some other way
of getting out of this.
Yeah, death.
This is your fault, Morgan.
It is entirely your fault, your problem.
[dramatic music playing]
Uh, okay, whatever.
This is really reaffirming
why we live in the same town
and never speak to each other.
-I'll go fix my problem.
-Don't do that.
-[woman] Morgan, honey.
-Come on.
-Look, there's glass all over the place.
-[woman] I'm sick of everything.
-Well, here, let me help.
No, I've got it. You need to freshen up.
-Did you see the Facebook women?
-Okay.
Those girls are all over.
-One look at you.
-All right.
God knows what they're gonna think.
[frenetic music playing]
[Max] Hey.
-Morgan, hey.
-Fuck!
Yeah. Yeah.
Gonna tell me you're going
or leave me alone with your family?
Oh, my bad. Yeah, no, it just seemed like
you were really enjoying yourself.
With your drunk aunt?
Um, I just feel like… I kind of feel like
I'm coming down with something.
I just want to lay in my own bed
for a couple hours.
Totally. I'll grab my jacket.
-I'll come with.
-No, no, no, I think just me.
-Probably one of us should stay, right?
-Fuck. No, Morgan, like…
-What am I supposed to say to them?
-Oh, I don't care. Anything.
They're always screaming at each other,
and you know that really stresses me.
Like, I-- My voice doesn't get that loud.
It's, like, really awkward
if I'm just alone with your whole family.
You've known them for 17 years. It's like…
So?
[sighs]
-Okay, go get your coat.
-Thank you. Okay, yeah.
-Quick.
-Just wait right there.
I'll be right here. I'll be right here.
[frenetic music playing]
[music stops]
-Dad, hi.
-Hey, kid, how you doing? Have you eaten?
Uh… No, but I'm… I'm okay.
[smacks lips, inhales]
-So how's Denise? Thank you.
-It was a nice serv--
-She's good.
-Good.
-Good, thanks.
I have a question for you. If…
If a criminal were to tell you
that they'd know if you went to the cops,
is that a real thing?
Do cops get paid off still?
Is that what he used on you?
These fucking guys watch too much TV.
You don't have to worry about that.
You only have to worry about dirty cops
if it's a higher-end crime.
-Higher-end crimes?
-Yeah.
Like, like what?
Like jewelry theft?
Did he steal your jewelry?
-I, that-- It's…
-Look, Nicky, I don't know.
It's generally high-end crimes,
organized crime.
Those are the ones
that have guys on the inside.
So people do pay off cops?
Sure, sometimes, but not the kind of guys
that are doing crimes
that are, you know, pointed like this.
What do you mean, pointed?
What do you mean?
[exhales] Your mother wants me
to open an investigation.
-She…
-Why?
She's concerned
that maybe you were targeted.
Targeted?
[spluttering] I-- That's impossible.
I don't-- I didn't know the person.
I know, but that's what hate crimes are.
-When--
-Hate crime?
-What?
-What is she talking about?
She's concerned, you know,
about the fact that you're…
you know, sensitive.
She thinks I was attacked because I'm gay?
What, did she think
I was skipping down the street?
You're taking this all the wrong way.
And by the way,
it's one of the things
we all love about you,
but you have a very musical walk.
"We"? The whole family's discussed this?
I'm doing this for your mother.
Would I bank on anything coming from it?
Probably not.
In fact, some of those guys have
roughed up a gay or two themselves.
Okay, Dad, you can't say "a gay."
I'm sorry, a homosexual.
Is gay not okay to say anymore?
"Gay" is fine. "A gay" is different.
I don't wanna have this conversation now.
Okay, I'm gonna go down
to the guys at the station.
-If you want me to mention the jewelry--
-Please don't.
I don't need you to go to the guys.
I don't need you to mention the jewelry.
I got the information I need.
I just-- Don't say anything.
-All right.
-Okay. You promise me?
-I promise you.
-Okay.
[frenetic music playing]
[music ends]
-Were you gonna leave without me?
-[muffled] I can't hear a word.
Then Morgan, roll down the fucking window.
[muffled] Yeah, yeah.
-What is going on with you right now?
-Nothing.
I have like, I have like
an ocular migraine coming on.
It's like I have minutes
before it's sp… sp… splitting.
All the more reason why you shouldn't be
behind the wheel. I'm gonna drive.
No, no, no, babe. I am… Fuck! Fuck!
[muffled] I'm set.
No, no, no, no, no, I'm good.
I'm good, I'm good. No, no, no.
-Wait, get out of the car.
-Mm-hmm.
-Get out of the car.
-No. Babe, listen.
I think I just need a little time alone,
and you're a really cautious driver.
I could have been…
I could be gone already.
'Cause I don't do rolling stops?
-Right now, yes.
-But they're illegal.
You are, like, being so evasive lately.
You're like… I've been really hard to…
[door handle rattling]
Morgan, like, you've been so hard
to pin down emotionally lately, it's like…
I feel like there's, like,
an emotional chasm between us.
There is no chasm.
But you would tell me
if there was a chasm.
Yes, absolutely.
It just feels like you've been lying to me
or, like, hiding something from me,
like an affair or whatever.
-Like an affair?
-Like an aff-- I don't know. You tell me.
[Morgan sighs]
Uh…
Morgan, I'm not leaving this car.
[funky music playing]
Okay.
[music stops]
I had an affair.
Bullshit. I… I don't believe you.
You-- You just accused me
of having an affair.
I'm telling you, I had an affair.
-[pull handle rattling]
-Okay, okay, okay.
Let me out--
Let me out of this fucking car, Morgan.
-Ahh! You're a pig!
-I'm a slutty pig, I agree.
-I'm sorry, but that's the truth. Mm-hmm.
-Yeah, I know.
That's what you are. You're a slut pig.
So…
-[door slams]
-Fuckin'…
I have done nothing but worship you
since we were 16 years old.
And what do you do with all this love
and generosity that I pour at you?
You just… [snorts]
You just gobble it all the fuck up.
Because I'm a slutty pig whore.
[Max] I would never say "whore."
You know how I feel about sex work.
[dogs barking in the background]
[footsteps approaching]
[Max] Give me the ring.
[children playing in the background]
[Morgan exhales]
[electronic music playing]
-[keys jangle]
-[engine starts]
[tires screech]
Hi, I am so sorry to interrupt.
There's a leak, and he's a contractor,
so I'm gonna pull him if that's okay.
Thank you so much.
-Okay--
-Have you taken anything for your eye?
My eye is fine. It's not about my eye.
I just heard Maria telling your father
that the downstairs bathroom
is out of toilet paper,
and she was saying it loud enough
so that people could hear.
-Felt intentional.
-I don't think it was.
This is the way she shows up
to pay respects to my mother?
I put you in charge
of keeping an eye on everything.
What do you want me to do?
Stand outside the bathroom
and pop my head in after every guest?
-[woman] Your eye is getting worse.
-My eye is fine.
You need to put more ice on that
once you replace the toilet paper.
-I'm so sorry for your loss, Mrs. Morelli.
-Tareq, honey.
Just the fact that you showed up today,
it just means the world.
And before I forget, your timber
got delivered to the store yesterday.
Oh, no, that should be
the least of your concerns right now.
One of the last capable men
on this planet.
I know I say this to you
every time I see you.
-How do you not have a husband?
-[Nicky] Ha, ha!
[shouts] Natalie!
I have an idea
that I want to run by you, okay?
What if we booked the cruise
tonight, all right?
Just up and left, quit our jobs,
traveled the world, six months.
-Far, far away.
-Okay.
-Morgan would have to join--
-Nick, you were just assaulted.
-You and Morgan are gonna be fine.
-No, no, no, no.
This is an independent thought.
This is rooted in romance
and… and freedom.
Okay, Nick, we can't quit our jobs, okay?
We're still saving up for it.
I love the enthusiasm, but you were
just involved in a hate crime.
How has this spiraled into a hate crime?
And who fucking stacks
toilet paper vertically?
Whoa, whoa, Nick,
put the toilet paper down.
-[spluttering]
-I-- I'm fine.
You're safe now.
[whispers] You're okay.
I don't know that I am okay.
There is a lot going on
that you don't know about.
Okay.
Then tell me.
[insects chirping softly]
I have to get these inside.
Okay?
["Sleigh Bells" by Riot Rhythm playing]
[tires screeching]
[brakes squeal]
-[car beeps]
-[door slams]
[keys beeping]
♪ You've got a smart best friend
She's okay ♪
♪ Carve you out, start today ♪
♪ Rush the door, take your seats ♪
♪ Our little saints play for keeps ♪
♪ Dear heart, don't stop fighting ♪
♪ Rhythm ride the lightning ♪
♪ It's not hell or heaven ♪
♪ Just like riot rhythm ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah… ♪
[clangs]
[clanging]
[gate clangs]
[car approaching]
[tires screeching]
[brakes squealing]
[insects chirping]
[engine running]
-[Morgan] Hi, hello, sir.
-The cemetery's closed, okay?
-We open first thing in the morning.
-Mm. Okay. Um…
-Okay, thank… thank you.
-You're welcome.
Um, but sir, it, uh-- It's just that my…
This is… This is, like, personal, but…
[inhales deeply] Uh… M--
I… I promised my grandmother
that I would keep her company, okay?
And she's… she's never been
here before, you know?
Are you saying
that your grandmother's lost in there?
No, she… Um… She's dead.
[spluttering] She… We…
We buried her today.
But, sir, she has dementia. I don't know
if that carries on to the afterlife.
I don't know what you know about dementia,
if you have any experience with that,
a loved one in your family, but it's sad.
It's sad, sir. She didn't know her name
by the end. She thought I was her husband.
I'd put on his suits, dance with her,
whatever could make her happy,
because that's how much I loved her
and I'm not giving up on her now.
I will go in there,
I will kiss her on her lips if I have to.
My biggest fear is she's in there,
she's confused.
She doesn't know where she is,
you know? [gasps]
She's a good woman, okay?
And I made her a promise.
There's really no way
you could just give me the keys?
I'll lock up. I promise I'll be so good.
I really want to do it. She deserves it.
You don't know her, but she deserves it.
She's a good-- She was a nurse.
A wartime nurse in Pearl Harbor.
[keys jangle]
-Oh my-- Are you serious?
-Make sure you lock up before you go.
Thank you so much.
This is for the troops, for real.
God will bless you for this gift, sir.
-My brother is a minister.
-[gate opens]
[people talking indistinctly]
-I have to tell you something.
-Okay, what is it?
-[loudly] ♪ Baby ♪
-Oh my God!
-[woman] I don't know. I pressed a button.
-Would you excuse me for a minute?
Just one minute.
Kevin, he works in fintech.
-[guest] What?
-Really, fintech.
I understand.
[shouts] I'm trying to cue up
the memorial slideshow.
Nicky, why did you change the playlist?
-Why do you think I changed the playlist?
-Really, Nicky? Lucky guess. I don't know.
-I need some--
-Is everything okay?
[yells] No, I'm trying to cue up
the memorial slideshow.
-So, there.
-[music stops]
-[Nicky sighs] Oh God.
-All right.
-Honey.
-Yeah. [exhales]
-You're loitering.
-I know.
What did you want to tell me?
[Nicky clears throat]
["Nocturne in E-Flat Major" by Chopin
playing softly]
-[softly] I think I lost a cuff link.
-What did you say?
[normal voice] I think
I lost a cuff link. I think…
I looked down at my shirt and realized
that one of the cuff links had fallen off,
and I realized
that I think it fell off into the coffin
when I went to hug Nonna.
What do you…
want me to do with that information?
I don't-- I don't-- I don't know.
I'm just, I'm-- It was--
-They were a gift from the church.
-Oh…
-They're antique. So, I--
-Nicky, what are you talking about now?
Nothing. I'm just saying… I don't know--
[whispers] I don't know what to do.
[Natalie] Mm-hmm.
I don't know. Get some new cuff links.
Why are we talking about cuff links?
Natalie, I don't recall inviting you
into this conversation. They're valuable.
I believe they were gold.
It was a gold cuff link.
It fell in, and I'm trying to figure out
if there's a way of getting them back.
"Getting them back"? [scoffs]
Honey, it's in the ground.
What are you gonna do?
Well, I guess I don't…
I mean, I guess nothing. I guess nothing.
I just thought,
since she was buried this morning,
the soil might be loose enough to--
-Nicholas!
-[Natalie] Oh my God.
Are you suggesting
that we exhume my mother for a cuff link?
No! Of course not. Of course not!
["Nocturne" playing softly]
-Do they… do they do that?
-You have lost your mind officially.
Natalie, I'm asking a question.
Oh my God. That's my mother's naked back.
-[Nicky] What?
-Mom. God…
-Natalie, what did you press?
-Oh my God.
These are the photos
in the memorial album.
-Honey, fix it.
-Oh my God, no.
You're the one holding the phone.
-[woman] Honey, get it.
-Fuck. I'm so sorry.
-[Nicky] Here.
-[muffled] Oh God.
-[Natalie] Okay.
-[Nicky] I'm turning the TV off.
Morgan was supposed to go through these,
and now she's nowhere to be found.
My mother would be mortified.
I understand. You know what?
I think we could all benefit from being
a little bit kinder to one another.
-[woman] Mm…
-Okay?
Everybody grieves in different ways.
And Morgan…
Morgan is out there somewhere right now,
knee-deep in grief.
-I'm sure she's at a rave.
-Now…
Nonna can't be mortified, Ma.
She's not here.
She's in heaven.
[gasps]
Judging people there.
Okay? [inhales]
So I need you, for the first time
in your life, to just take a breath.
Okay? This is a beautiful spread, Ma.
You deserve to just sit down
and have a drink.
-But we're about to start the slideshow.
-Yeah.
After the slideshow then.
Okay?
Now, I think I have to go.
-My head is hurting.
-[woman] Oh.
And people are staring.
All right, thank you.
I appreciate that, honey,
because your face
is incredibly hard to look at.
All right. So I'm going.
-[woman] Okay.
-Okay?
-I love you.
-[mouths] I love you.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
[Natalie sighs]
[whispers] Are you okay?
[whispers] Did you see
what Bethany was wearing?
[whispers] I saw.
[funky music playing]
[grunts softly]
[panting]
[grunts]
[gravel crunching]
[music ends abruptly]
[man] Hey.
[music resumes]
[softly] God.
[whispers] Morgan.
Morgan.
[music fades]
Maria?
I want to… thank you for coming.
Um… I know that given what went down
between the two of you,
that couldn't have been an easy decision.
What are you talking about?
Your mother was a bitch, but I loved her.
[inhales sharply] Mom always said,
"Indifference is the worst thing
you can receive from a person."
So, I-- Yeah, I don't really know much
about what happened…
[inhales sharply]
…but I think we could agree
that she could be critical. [chuckles]
So you didn't write my mother
a thank-you card 15 years ago.
She sent me a thank-you gift basket
for recommending my caterer.
I'm supposed to send her a thank-you card
for the thank-you gift basket?
-Well…
-I mean, it's insane, huh?
I think that she heard
that you took it to church
and you were handing it out to friends.
Oh, so now she wants to control
what I do with the thank-you gift basket.
I couldn't eat all that cheese by myself.
Listen,
for all your mother's shortcomings,
you're a decent woman, Linda.
You've built a very nice,
honorable family for yourself.
Let's just agree, huh?
To let that be her legacy.
Well, I…
I appreciate that very much, Maria.
Thank you. [inhales]
[both laughing]
-I just want to remind you…
-Hm?
…that I once lent her $18.
-And I never got it back.
-You never got it back.
-Yeah.
-I'm just saying.
[Linda] Mm-hmm.
[door opens, creaks]
[softly] Wow.
This is as far as you got?
Okay, hey.
This is a lot harder than it looks, okay?
I have blisters all over my hands.
-You didn't use gloves?
-No, I didn't use gloves.
I wasn't thinking about my hand health,
okay? I've never dug up a grave.
I don't know what to do
in a situation like this.
-Okay.
-[voice breaking] My back is fucked.
My hands are fucked. [inhales deeply]
We're fucked. And I fucking suck.
-Yeah.
-Ow! [groans]
Jesus.
I'm gonna live my whole life having
never done anything that matters at all.
Okay. All right.
[insects chirping]
Morgan, I'm gonna-- I'm gonna need you
to give me your hand.
-Right now. Okay.
-Okay.
Okay. Let's do it.
-[grunting]
-I need you… to pull it together.
-[Morgan pants]
-Okay. Yes.
-All right?
First of all, you're not a loser.
You are a public school teacher.
And aside from being a mother,
that is the most thankless job in America.
Thank you.
I don't think I said I was a loser.
-And if the two of us continue digging…
-Okay.
…we should hit the casket
before the sun comes up.
I never thought
I would ever say that out loud.
Aw… You're gonna dig?
[Morgan sobs softly]
-I'm gonna dig.
-Aw… [exhales]
Just, like, I've been here
all night, you know.
Okay, okay.
You showed up, you know? And somehow
you're doing the absolute bare minimum.
-Okay.
-You know? It really-- It's kind of just…
It's exactly what I needed right now,
you know?
Morgan.
Yeah.
Who is Alan Botkins?
I don't know. Who is Alan Botkins?
You tell me. You've been digging up
his grave for the past two hours.
What?
No, that's…
-No, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
-Oh my…
-No, that--
-Did you look at the headstone, Morgan?
Or did you just see
a fresh plot and start digging?
This is where the funeral took place.
No, this is where the funeral took place.
[gasps loudly]
Morgan!
No. No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
-What, what, what, what? It--
-Oh, man.
[screams] God!
It is fucking pitch out here.
What are the odds
of two back-to-back fresh graves?
We're in the new part
of the cemetery, so pretty likely.
There's fresh graves
all over the place. There's--
There's one right there. There's…
-There's one over here. Fresh grave!
-No. No!
There's two right here.
I'm being dead serious.
I need you to be nice to me.
Is this the current state
of the public education system?
-Don't do that!
-Just saying…
I knew it wasn't great,
but this is frightening.
[Morgan mutters]
Okay, okay, okay.
Stop it, I am dead serious.
What the hell is this?
It's a little shovel.
No, this is a hoe, Morgan.
This is a hoe.
-What?
-What did you put in this bag?
[yells] Shovels!
["Sleigh Bells" by Riot Rhythm playing]
♪ You've got a smart best friend
She's okay ♪
♪ Carve you out, start today ♪
♪ Rush the door, take your seats ♪
♪ Our little saints play for keeps ♪
♪ Dear heart, don't stop fighting ♪
♪ Rhythm ride the lightning ♪
♪ It's not hell or heaven ♪
♪ Just like riot rhythm ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah ♪