Five million?
[Episode 5: To protect you
from the world's malice]
That amount doesn't make any sense.
May I ask you something?
Mr. He, what do you do?
I run a guesthouse.
With a guesthouse income like that...
Well, it's not really your fault.
You may not know
how
the market works.
Actually, the five million...
It's like this.
Our company
signed a contract with the artists.
There are also upstream
and downstream agreements,
and the cost of the printed materials
that were scrapped this time—
Adding it all up, this five million.
Seriously.
That's already the lowest
I could possibly get it down to.
How about this?
Show me the contracts one by one.
And we'll check them one by one
to see if there really
is such a high amount.
I might not have them with me right now.
But I think
something is more important
for you to check out.
Well...
Please take a look at this document.
Xiangyong signed it.
[Voluntary Resignation Waiver]
I also checked it with him
many times.
It's such a high amount.
And you expect Xiangyong
to take all of it?
Boss.
-Are you…
-Sorry.
I'm the president.
President.
Are you using him as a scapegoat
just because he's young?
Mr. He,
hearing you say that honestly hurts.
To be honest, when I started my busniess,
what I wanted the most
was to be fair and open.
Although our company is not big,
we run
a very principled publishing house.
It's okay.
Mr. He.
It's okay if you don't trust me.
I'll ask Xiangyong's former colleagues
to explain to you.
OK?
This is He Xiangyong's father.
He thinks we misunderstood him.
He really messed things up.
The whole company
was a mess because of him.
Yes.
I've been cleaning up his mess.
Mr. He,
ever since he was an intern,
he's been messing up
nonstop.
We're always cleaning up after him.
That's enough.
What's going on?
His father is here,
and you're talking like that.
If it really is Xiangyong's fault,
then I thank you
for taking care of him all these years.
If you all have a clear conscience,
then I also wish your company
a prosperous business
and flourishing success.
May you don't choke on your food.
May you never trip while walking.
Hope you never run
into another He Xiangyong!
Mr. He,
that was really well said.
I am really moved, really.
For people like us
who come out to do business,
the last thing we want
is an employee like Xiangyong.
By the way,
Xiangyong's friend called
and said they would handle this matter.
But actually, until now,
we still haven't heard any news.
I want to remind you, Mr. He,
if that's the case,
we might have to
take legal action later on.
Don't use the law to threaten me.
He Xiangyong said
he would take responsibility.
So we will take responsibility to the end.
Then sorry to trouble you again.
See Mr. He out.
[Wishing Upon the Shooting Stars]
What kind of heartless company is this?
This is practically workplace bullying.
That idiot kid of mine
came back to the island
and refused to tell me anything.
Of course, he takes after you.
Xiangyong is just like you.
He'd never let you see
how much he's struggling.
And you won't let him know
that something's wrong with your kidneys.
You're the one with an enlarged prostate.
Who has a problem?
Keep it down.
It's just health stuff, nothing serious.
There's nothing to talk about.
Yeah, right.
Every time Xiangyong comes back,
you just sit there drinking.
And then?
You prepare the freshest seafood.
Anyone can see
that you're happy when Xiangyong is back.
You call that a minor matter?
So what now?
The only way is to sell the house?
I went to the bank for a loan.
But the house is too old
and not worth much.
I'm old, too.
And I don't want a day to come
after I'm gone
where Xiangyong
still has to carry my debt.
Fortunately...
fortunately, that David guy
offered just that little bit more.
Sell the house?
Of course, I'll sell it, sell it quickly.
You mean that influencer, David?
He is very sincere.
He's not from our island.
The moment he knows I decided
to sell the house,
he said
he'd take a boat to see it.
I'm grateful to him, too.
Why are you cutting so much?
Don't sneak a bite.
That's for other people to eat.
Look, they're here.
Get it ready quickly.
Stop cutting already.
Snake-style throw.
Mr. He.
Careful.
Be careful.
Nice catch.
This is a gift for our meeting.
This is the crystal I recently released.
A crystal—
It looks pretty good, right?
Good.
This is my good friend,
Mr. Hua.
Hello, Mr. Hua.
Have a seat here.
It's so hot.
This weather is a characteristic
of our Xingpu Island.
It's like a fairy tale world, you know?
Actually, it's quite comfortable.
What do you want to drink?
Bull energy drink.
Xiaoyou, get a can of Bull.
Take a photo.
These are all old houses.
You don't see them much anymore.
They're my employees.
Take a photo of
that dilapidated building, too.
See what places can be renovated.
Film it.
Just film whatever.
What are you doing?
This is my old trade.
I thought if I can't even do this well,
how would I have money
to buy the guesthouse from you?
You're being too polite.
David,
I've heard of your great name
for a long time.
I've watched your videos.
I've subscribed to your channel.
His video content is super rich.
And the view counts are all super high.
Vlogs, diving, food unboxing...
It's all pretty cheap-looking.
Cheerful and sunny
I mean, uh… cheerful and sunny!
But I heard that lately,
you can actually buy views
and traffic now.
I don't really understand it.
So, I thought I'd ask for advice.
Because I don't run a channel.
I have heard about that myself.
But I don't know
how to buy those things.
I've always just done things on my own.
I don't know how to buy them.
Correct.
Just like now I want
to buy the guesthouse,
I'd like to ask Mr. He Xiang for advice
on how to run a guesthouse.
Mr. He, so,
will you be handling the notary work,
or should I take care of it?
You've got more experience
with this kind of thing.
I'll leave it all to you.
Sure.
Then I'll handle it.
Well, excuse me.
I want to ask,
since your channel is so successful,
why get into real estate?
Investing, well,
there are always risks.
And not everything
can be turned into a side gig.
My dad tells me most often:
if a person is too greedy,
it usually doesn't end well.
That's not it for me.
Because for my other jobs,
I make money pretty effortlessly.
So I thought,
for running a guesthouse,
I could get hands-on with it
and really experience local life
for myself.
Where's my Bull?
Where's the Bull?
Haowei, that Bull?
We're out of Bull.
Is that yogurt drink okay?
Forget it, never mind.
Mr. He,
I'm thinking
of tearing the whole place down.
I feel it's a bit too old.
And it's not that safe, either.
So I thought I could
turn it into something like
Greek style,
Turkish style,
Spanish style, anything is fine.
Or is there some—
Or is there some style you want?
You can tell me...
David,
you really don't understand.
Do you know this is a historic site?
Do you know how much history it has?
Do you know how many people come here
because it looks like this?
You really don't get it, do you?
I don't think you should
invest in real estate.
I think you should go back
to filming your cheap-looking Vlogs.
Zhong Xiaoyou!
Don't be rude to my guest.
We'll talk about this later, okay?
Do you really have to sell it?
Is there really no other way?
It's my house. I get to decide.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Hua, it's fine.
You all should discuss it clearly first.
No, it's not like that.
I'm selling it.
I'm definitely selling it.
Okay, okay.
Let me tell you,
I have a rooftop on the second floor, too.
You get a full ocean view there.
I'll take you to see it.
Okay.
Let's go.
This way, please.
You're Zhong Xiaoyou,
right?
Are you afraid of becoming unemployed?
You don't have to worry.
After I buy this guesthouse,
all of you can come and help me.
No, it's not like that.
This way, please.
Let's go.
Turn left ahead.
Take a look.
After turning right,
the view connects
straight out to the ocean.
Haowei, Xiaoyou.
Show them around the place.
Okay.
What's with you?
You're acting very unusually today.
Xiaoyou.
Well,
let's go to the counter.
Come, follow me.
This way.
This is our counter.
No way.
He actually bought it from Yilan.
Hama-chan was actually right.
He said if you have doubts,
just go check his IG stories.
Seeing you eat so happily...
You two have made up, haven't you?
Your son's pretty open-minded, you know.
Friends don't hold grudges overnight.
Are you still just friends?
Don't you like Hama-chan?
I don't like him.
Don't talk nonsense.
Liking someone
is not an embarrassing thing.
I'm telling you—
If you like someone,
just say it out loud.
I don't like him.
It's Uncle Hua's birthday tomorrow.
You have to ask Hama-chan to come.
I'll see.
Li Wanzhe, get on.
-Do you want to eat something first?
-Hurry up.
What?
You're in such a rush.
Mom, I'm going out for a bit.
Are you taking me out to play?
Why are you riding so fast today?
Follow me.
Wait, I haven't taken off my helmet yet.
Hurry up.
What are you doing, being so rushed?
Why are you in such a hurry?
Are you running an errand for a guest?
Do you have your ID with you?
I think so.
Fast.
Go get me a ticket back
to the main island. Hurry.
Hurry up.
Why are you going back to the main island?
Go buy it first.
If you don't tell me why,
I'm not buying it.
My house is about to be sold!
So that's how your debt came about.
It's really infuriating.
Back then, when I called your boss,
I should've chewed him out.
How did it turn out like this?
It's all because
of that stupid shooting star.
I'm completely stuck now.
You can't blame the shooting star, either.
Anyway, it has already happened.
Right.
Since it has happened, I have to face it.
I'll pay my own debt myself.
No one can touch my house.
Are you going to help me
buy the ticket or not?
What can buying a ticket do?
Can you do anything
if you go back to the main island?
I don't care.
My dad is selling the house for me now.
I can't just sit here and do nothing.
I'm going back to confront my boss.
Fine, you want to go back.
Do you have money? Do you have an ID?
That's why I'm asking you
to buy it for me.
Fine, if I buy it for you, and then?
How are you going to come up
with that five million?
Even if you go to a loan shark now,
no one's gonna lend you anything,
you know?
And in what capacity
will you face your boss?
Mr. He,
since you are so reluctant,
why must you sell it?
Well,
there are always times when one is forced
to act against their will.
I'm sorry.
Haowei.
Go take an inventory
of that driftwood for me.
Okay.
Village Chief, we can handle it here.
I already finished this downstairs.
Okay.
How is it?
How is the fire going?
It's fine. It's okay.
You're fanning very slowly.
Let me do it.
Yue, help me check that ice.
-Being a village chief is really hard work.
-You do it.
You've gotta do everything yourself.
I'm afraid there won't be enough alcohol.
If you're not the Village Chief later...
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Thank you.
Wait.
You have to make a wish first.
It's our Xingpu Island tradition.
Make a wish.
Okay, here it goes.
OK.
Alright, alright.
Cheers.
Come, let's have a drink.
To the most handsome Hua of Xingpu Island.
Good.
I wish everyone good health.
And may all your wishes come true.
You young people, get moving.
Tell me what you want to eat.
What do you want to eat?
Green peppers.
Okay.
And what else?
Mushrooms.
Mushrooms?
Right.
Come to think of it,
it seems you've been on Xingpu Island
for 16 years already.
Yeah.
Yeah, about that.
Even
Yang Guo would've reunited
with Xiaolongnü by now.
That's such an old reference.
Have you never thought
about going back to the main island?
I brought this on myself.
Better if I don't go back.
Right.
You are guilty.
Your sin, well,
is that you aren't drunk enough.
Exactly.
Before you get drunk,
you're not going anywhere.
Do you all remember?
Every time he buys a boat ticket,
something always goes wrong.
You and the main island
just don't mix.
Bottoms up.
What's up?
I can't drink anymore.
I was just kidding.
There are still ingredients here.
Xiaoyou, eat with us.
No, thanks.
I don't have much of an appetite.
Then, let's have a drink.
Come on, let's drink together.
I'll help myself.
Drink some more.
Uncle Hua.
Happy birthday to you.
Thank you.
And I wish you all the best
and that everything goes smoothly.
Thank you, Uncle Hua.
What's wrong? Are you not feeling well?
Let me take a look.
No need, I'll be fine
after I go back and sleep for a bit.
Have him take a look at you here，
no charge.
Right.
Your problem is
that you haven't had enough to drink.
Toast the Village Chief.
Let me have a drink with you.
Come.
Drink some more.
Right.
Uncle Hua.
Yesterday...
It's nothing.
Let's talk about yesterday's matter later.
Come, let's drink together.
Aren't you going to drink with Angela?
To Angela.
You drink half.
That's enough, Li Wanzhe.
Stop drinking.
-Village Chief Wang.
-Watch me perform.
Thank you, Village Chief Wang,
for your usual care.
Come.
Village Chief Wang, let's drink.
You're very thirsty, aren't you?
Wait a moment, I need to go pee first.
I'm going to pee first.
Village Chief Wang.
You drink first.
Where are you going, Village Chief Wang?
Are you running away?
Doing your usual bathroom escape?
He's like this every time.
I'm done grilling over there.
I'll come and drink with everyone.
I'll drink with you.
Li Wanzhe.
Where's Li Wanzhe?
Li Wanzhe is dancing over there.
Carp Leaping the Dragon Gate!
Come.
Having a son like Li Wanzhe, I seriously
don't know what to do with him.
Is he really my son?
Of course, he is your son.
-He's good enough already.
-I don't know.
Sometimes I'm not sure.
I'm not sure.
You can be unsure?
I'll drink with you.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
Hua.
Will you forgive me?
He's had these symptoms for a long time.
Do you have any medicine to give him?
Help him.
Don't ignore me.
I have medicine.
Give him a few more drinks,
then he'll be quiet.
Drink more.
Come, drink.
He's still mixing people up.
Dad.
Mr. He, I'm sorry.
Xiaoyou, you're drunk.
Xiaoyou.
Don't touch me.
Luckily, our Li Wanzhe
doesn't just recognize anyone as his dad.
You won't drink with me?
Go to sleep.
I'm not drinking with you.
You want to drink with me, right?
Fine, I'll drink with you.
Xiaoyou.
Let's go.
That wine is quite expensive.
I'll take care of him.
-Take some more.
-Xiaoyou.
Take some more.
Xiaoyou.
Is something wrong with his head?
Xiaoyou, walk a bit slower.
Where exactly do you want to go?
That's enough, don't drink anymore.
You've had too much.
Don't touch me!
If you don't want to drink,
you just go back first.
Don't mind me, okay?
Alright.
Let's go back to the guesthouse.
What guesthouse?
I'm telling you,
if I don't finish the wine today,
I'm not going back.
Do you understand?
You're drunk.
What are you doing?
I'm telling you,
if I don't finish the wine today,
I'm not going back.
What are you doing?
Stop drinking.
Xiaoyou.
Alright, alright.
Don't grab my wine!
You've drunk too much.
Okay, well...
I'll finish this bottle,
and then we'll go back
to the guesthouse, okay?
You said it.
Is there something wrong with his head?
He's possessed or something.
Grab your wine, hurry up.
Let's go over and toast Uncle Hua.
Hurry up!
This must be hereditary.
Hurry up.
Hereditary? From whom?
From a medical point
of view, it's genetic.
Uncle Hua.
Happy birthday to you.
Thank you, everyone.
Happy birthday.
And Mr. He.
Thank you.
Thank you, Home at He's.
I really like it here.
Cheers!
I really can't bear to see it sold.
Okay, you've had too much.
Let's go over there
and watch the dancing, okay?
Let's go, let's go dancing.
Let's go, let's go dancing together.
Let's go.
Let's go, let's go dancing.
Let's go dancing.
I like it here very much.
It's the girls' turn to dance.
The girls' turn to dance.
What did he mean by that?
I sold the guesthouse.
You sold it?
Well, come.
Today is my birthday.
Don't talk about this.
That's not the point today, okay?
But he...
It is.
What about him?
-Aye...
-A, B, C, D, okay?
You're so annoying.
The alcohol is finished.
Let's go home.
You're going the wrong way.
Can you tell me now?
What exactly are you sad about?
Am I sad?
I'm super happy.
I drank the most alcohol in my life today.
Tell me the truth.
I'm happy. I'm great.
Don't grab me.
I can walk by myself.
Chen Haowei.
Don't come looking for me ever again.
What do you mean?
He Xiangyong.
You just turn around
and walk away like that.
You just turned around
and walked away like that.
It wasn't easy for me to find you.
I'm not letting you go this time.
He Xiangyong.
Page eighteen isn't on the exam.
[Epilogue]
Happy birthday to you.
This is the first time
I've drawn a picture for someone.
I hope you don't dislike it.
Dislike it?
This is the best birthday gift
I've ever received.
How could I possibly dislike it?
I like it very, very, very much.
That's good.
How could you forget
the most important part?
The signature—hurry up and sign it.
When you become famous in the future,
I'll show off to everyone
that I was your first fan.
You're so dramatic.
He Xiangyong.
One day,
you will surely become
a world-famous great painter.
You're so hyped
for this year's birthday gift.
What am I going to do next year?
How about on my birthday next year,
you take me back to your home
to see real sea turtles?
Okay, it's a deal.
At that time, we
didn't know
these words...
had no chance to come true later.
[Next Episode]
So last night,
you and Chen Haowei kissed.
So happy.
You said it while holding me like this.
The wish has come true like this.
Don't you feel it's a bit unsettling?
What I'm thinking of in my heart
is He Xiangyong.
I shouldn't use Xiaoyou as his substitute.