(Lee Jae In, Kim Woo Seok, Choi Ye Bin)
(Cha Woo Min, An Ji Ho, Jung So Ri)
(Scriptwriter: Kang Min Ji)
(Director: Im Dae Woong)
(Night Has Come)
(All people, organizations, locations, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
Yoon Seo!
Are you okay? Answer me!
What if something happened to her?
Or should we get more people here?
I'm going in.
If I don't say anything in five minutes, get the others.
Okay.
Yoon Seo.
Where are you?
Say something!
What was that?
I'm on the second floor. Something is off.
Come quickly.
(Message not delivered)
Yoon Seo!
(Voting Status)
(Park Woo Ram: 7 votes, Ko Kyung Jun: 6 votes)
You have six votes.
So if two more people vote, it will be over.
Hey, what should we do?
Isn't it obvious?
We must show them Park Woo Ram, that jerk, is the Mafia.
- Let's go. - Come on.
I'm glad that you two are the last ones to vote.
- Vote now. - Okay. I'll do it now.
No.
Don't force us.
What?
Ji Soo.
I'm not...
forcing you or anything.
I'm just in a tight spot.
Put yourself in my shoes.
It's either you or Ko Kyung Jun.
You barged in here, asking me to help you.
How do you expect me to think clearly with all the pressure?
Don't be like that.
Don't tell me...
you think...
I'm the Mafia.
Who knows?
Can you leave, so we can think by ourselves?
Darn it.
Hey, Woo Ram.
Woo Ram.
How could they do this to me?
How?
Darn it. Come on.
It all happened very fast. Ji Soo must be just flustered.
I'll try to talk to her.
Why don't you stay in the room for now?
Okay?
Okay.
Hello?
(Person-in-charge, Kim Tae Geun, Yoon Hyung Jin)
(Muryeong Retreat Center)
(Sechang High School, May 22)
(Kyunghwa High School, May 17)
(Sihwa High School, September 18)
This is our class.
(Rebuild communication.)
(Park Woo Ram: 7 votes, Ko Kyung Jun: 6 votes)
(Park Woo Ram)
Why...
(Regulations to cut down on using disposable items)
Choi Mi Na.
Where's this jerk, Park Woo Ram?
On the fourth floor.
Wait.
Is he with the others?
No. They're talking on the third floor.
We're on the same boat now.
Let's do it again.
Do what again?
Bring the Mafia to me.
Okay?
Ji Soo, you can think about this more.
Yu Jun.
You should vote for Kyung Jun now.
Okay. I'll do that.
Don't force him.
Give us time to think about this.
What's more to think about?
It's not just anyone. It's Woo Ram.
Why not?
Let's be honest. He badmouthed Ju Young all the time.
This has nothing to do with that.
Woo Ram is our friend.
Please?
Right, Ji Soo. Let's side with Woo Ram.
Cha Yu Jun. Get a grip.
We need to find the Mafia, so we can go home! Seriously.
I don't trust anyone. It doesn't matter if he's my friend.
Besides, who knows? She could have pushed Dong Hyun.
Hey. What did you just say?
That's enough.
This isn't the time to fight.
Park Ji Soo...
I'm seeing her in a different light.
How could she only care about saving herself?
(Room 305)
Besides, Yu Jun is so spineless.
Woo Ram.
Park Woo Ram.
He's not in here?
Where's Woo Ram?
I told him to stay in the room.
Let's go and look for him.
Yu Jun is alone?
Yes.
He wanted to talk to you in private about the vote without Ji Soo.
So...
Hey, Yu Jun.
Darn it. Hey, move him.
Stall a bit more time.
I'll show you how I take down the Mafia.
Darn you.
Hey, turn on the light.
- Hurry up. - Check there.
Darn it.
Woo Ram.
He's not in here either.
That's it. Let's split up and look for him.
Okay.
Woo Ram!
Just tell the truth, you jerk.
Stop it.
Come on.
Say it!
Stop it. Please.
You jerk! How dare you try to kill me?
Hey.
Wake up.
I think he passed out.
Hey. Wake up.
He might be pretending.
Ji Soo, it's past 11pm. Are you going to vote?
Let's just vote for Ko Kyung Jun.
Wait.
I thought you needed time to think.
Why are you in a rash?
We just have to vote before midnight.
Spend some more time to think.
Park Woo Ram.
(Studio)
Woo Ram.
Park Woo Ram.
Jung Won.
Where's Yoon Seo?
I don't know. I didn't see her.
I went all the way, and it was a dead end.
- A dead end? - Yes.
I think we have to look for her outside.
Okay.
Jung Won. Oh Jung Won.
What?
Yoon Seo.
Yoon Seo, I was worried about you.
- Are you okay? - Yes.
I fell to the basement.
Then I found a room with CCTVs.
When I got out, I was suddenly on the second floor.
I walked...
for a long time, but I kept circling around.
I barely escaped.
You fell to the basement, but how did you get to the second floor?
And it was...
a dead end.
I'm telling you the truth.
And I found this.
Are they from our school?
I think they were our seniors.
But I'm not sure.
What happened to their faces?
It's creepy.
I think she is...
the ghost I saw.
What?
Yoon Seo.
Is Woo Ram here?
- No. - He said he'd wait in his room.
He suddenly disappeared.
There's no time.
Spill it out already.
There's no time, jerk!
Look how dogged he is.
He's the Mafia for sure.
Grab him.
Grab him!
Stop it.
Don't do this.
Stop it, jerk.
Stop what? I haven't even started yet.
No!
I never liked your eyes.
Should I shove them out?
So you should've cooperated.
Why did you get on my nerves?
Woo Ram.
Woo Ram!
Park Woo Ram!
Is he on the second floor?
No.
He's not on the first floor or in the basement.
Should we check the other building?
I'm Park Woo Ram.
What's that?
I'm the Mafia.
I killed Lee Ju Young.
What's Park Woo Ram doing?
What's he saying?
- To the studio. - I wasn't...
planning to do that at first,
but I got upset because he humiliated me.
Because he always belittled me,
I wanted to kill him.
He's crazy.
- Park Woo Ram? - What's he saying?
He said he's the Mafia.
Happy now?
Are you happy now, jerk!
You should've confessed in the first place.
Woo Ram. Park Woo Ram!
Hey!
Hey. Open the door.
Hey! Open the door now.
Guys. I'm in here.
Hey!
Move.
Give me that.
Stay away.
Shoot.
Darn it, Kim Jun Hee.
You crazy junks!
Gosh.
You're crazy.
You're lunatics!
Are you okay?
My goodness.
Who's real crazy here?
He's the Mafia. He killed Lee Ju Young.
Cut it out.
Come to your senses, idiot.
Look.
It's over now.
(Park Ji Soo voted for Park Woo Ram.)
(Cha Yu Jun voted for Park Woo Ram.)
Shoot!
I should've killed Ko Kyung Jun first.
I'd be an idiot if I just die.
Shoot.
Hey.
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hey. - Come with me.
Jerk!
Be careful.
Are you crazy?
Do something.
I'll kill you before I die!
Even if it weren't me, someone would kill you.
Die, you jerk!
Voting is over.
Park Woo Ram with the most votes will be executed.
What the...
Oh, no.
Park Woo Ram was the Mafia.
See? I told you.
Get out of my way.
- Go. - Don't touch me.
Hurry up.
Come on.
No.
Stay here.
(Night Has Come)
(Gwangju Information and Content Agency)
(This content was produced through Gwangju Information and...)
(Content Agency's 2022 OTT Platform Content Production Business.)