(reflective piano music)
(inhales)
SUNWOO: This is crazy.
(reflective piano music continues)
(music fades)
(breathes deeply)
(deep sigh)
(exhales sharply)
(sighs)
Do you want pho?
-Sure.
-Okay.
(door closes)
(Eunsoo sighs)
(exhales sharply)
(whimsical music)
(sighs)
(rasps)
(rattles)
(rasping)
(whimsical music continues)
-(rasping)
-(sighs)
(whispers)
This is crazy.
No, that's not it.
(gasps)
This is crazy.
She can't have heard this, right?
Gosh.
This is crazy.
I'm pretty sure she didn't hear this.
(water running)
(sighs deeply)
(whimsical music)
(door opens)
(whimsical music continues)
-It's already here.
-Yes. Come have a seat.
(rustling)
(sighs)
-Let's eat.
-Sure.
(music fades)
(sloshing)
(munches)
This is crazy.
(playful music)
EUNSOO: This place...
-is really good. It's so good.
-(sighs)
-This is crazy.
-Yeah. It's pretty good.
-It's a great place.
-Yeah, it is.
When did we fall asleep last night?
I'm not sure.
(sighs)
I passed out too, so I don't remember.
Oh...
(sloshing)
-It was cold last night.
-I know, it was cold.
-I almost froze to death.
-We were just cold.
It's instinct to seek sources of heat.
-Like how flowers always face the sun.
-Like survival instinct.
I survived the cold, thanks to you.
(chuckles awkwardly)
By the way...
Did you...
hear anything while you were asleep?
-Hear what?
-Anything at all.
Did you fart?
What?
(chuckles)
That...
It was by accident.
It's fine. We're past that.
(theme music)
EPISODE 2
THE DISTANCE BETWEEN YOU AND ME
(scribbling)
SUNWOO: This is better.
-EUNSOO: The...
-Here's dessert.
(in English) Thank you.
-(in Korean) You can have the mandarins.
-(chuckles)
-Can I see what you wrote?
-Sure.
EUNSOO: There's not much though.
(Sunwoo sighs)
Mm...
Ah...
(chuckles)
-You write all kinds of stuff here.
-I have to, or I forget.
And... here.
This is what I'm working on now.
-Do you want to listen to the demo too?
-Sure, why not?
(keypad clacking)
(emotive music plays on headphones)
♪ When I look at you ♪
♪ I don't know what to do ♪
♪ 'Cause you give me butterflies ♪
♪ I wasn't sure enough ♪
♪ Until now ♪
♪ To fall in love with someone ♪
♪ But you came here like destiny ♪
♪ Love is beyond words... ♪
THE CORNERS OF MY HEART TURN RED
♪ It is not as simple as we think ♪
♪ If you really love with all your heart ♪
♪ I will try not to hurt
your tender heart ♪
♪ By any chance... ♪
(music stops)
Good, right?
Huh?
Yeah, it is.
And... these are the lyrics to go with it.
Aren't these lyrics...
too plain for this song?
Is it?
"The distance between you and me.
There's nothing we can do.
Corners of my heart blush."
Yeah, the corners of your heart
are blushing red.
It means they're shy.
That's what unrequited love feels like.
(inhales)
You could feel shy,
but you could also be in pain.
Why?
If all you could ever do...
is barely reach him
with the tip of your finger,
wouldn't it be really sad?
(reflective piano music)
Mm...
With someone I love...
this is all I can...
(reflective piano music continues)
...do. Just grab the hand. Problem solved!
Gosh. How frustrating.
(Eunsoo sighs)
Let's get some air.
This is great. My brain is waking up.
(both breathe deeply)
(reflective piano music continues)
EUNSOO: So...
do you feel that way about Jennifer?
There's nothing you can do.
You can barely reach her
by the fingertips.
Right.
SUNWOO: But what really matters to me
is not about what I can't do with her.
It's about what I can't do for her.
That's what makes me sad.
What do you want to do for her so badly?
Anything. Everything that she wants.
Well, there's something I want.
(music stops abruptly)
What is it?
Chocolate.
(scoffs)
(laughing, inhales)
-What? I've been craving some.
-Chocolate?
-Just one, please?
-Let's go. I'll buy.
(in English) Okay!
(light music)
(munching)
How can you say no to something this good?
I don't like it. It's too sweet.
You loved sweets when you were a kid.
Because you loved sweets.
I was humoring you.
Thank you so much.
(bike bell ringing)
-Wait for me!
-Hurry up!
EUNSOO: They're so cute.
Do you remember when you taught me
how to ride a bicycle?
Of course.
I had to hold onto you every time.
You were such a scaredy-cat.
You know what?
I can even ride scooters now.
I've mastered everything on two wheels.
But four-wheeled is a different story.
What?
(music fade)
A car?
♪ I want to be happy ♪
-♪ I don't want to cry anymore... ♪
-People walk faster than this.
I feel so much more comfortable
having you sit next to me.
I'm glad one of us is feeling comfortable.
(car honking)
Oh, my.
-MAN: Idiot! You think you own the road?
-That scared me.
-MAN: Get off the road!
-Hey!
Is he out of his mind?
It's a school zone up there.
Why are people driving so fast?
Maybe because the school zone
is way up there and not here.
(vehicles honking)
-EUNSOO: Is that so?
-SUNWOO: Yes.
They act like they were never beginners.
Are you cold?
-I'll turn on the heater.
-No! Keep your eyes on the road!
Huh? Okay.
(chuckles)
-I'm not cold. I'm having cold sweats.
-Okay.
Then let's make another round
while we're out.
Oh, I need groceries too.
There's nothing to eat at home.
-EUNSOO: Right?
-Eyes ahead.
I am, no worries.
Do whatever you want.
Oh, hey! Did you hear that?
(chuckling)
You know how people turn on their hazards
after cutting in.
It doesn't mean "thank you",
but more like a way to rub it in.
Maybe I should try it now.
-(laughing)
-(phone chimes)
Is it over here?
PRODUCER KANG WOOIL
ACCEPT CALL
-WOOIL: Eunsoo, it's me.
-Mr. Kang!
WOOIL: Are you out?
Yes, I am. What is it?
WOOIL: If it's okay with you, do you think
you can stop by the studio right now?
I have something to discuss
regarding the song concept.
Oh, right now?
EUNSOO: Uh...
Yes, I can.
(techno music)
WOOIL: Then I'll see you soon.
Okay!
You're going right now?
Sunwoo.
-We're past the school zone, right?
-Why do you ask?
-I'm sorry in advance.
-(tire screeches)
Hey!
(upbeat music)
(music stops)
-(paper riffling)
-(sighs)
I'm sorry to have interrupted your date.
(gasps)
No, we weren't on a date.
He's just a friend. My best friend.
He's been helping me out with the lyrics
because he knows me best.
WOOIL: I see.
Thank you.
-Oh, this was really good last time.
-WOOIL: Right?
The intro for the demo changed a bit.
So the emotional profile of...
Give me yours.
Huh?
You hate mandarins. Drink that.
-(Eunsoo chuckles awkwardly)
-She's sick of mandarins.
-Her parents send them from Jeju.
-Oh.
(chuckles awkwardly)
What are you saying? I love mandarins.
You told me just the sight of mandarins
makes you throw up.
Then you even smashed one with your fist.
(whispers)
When did I?
I'm sorry. You should've told me.
-Would you like coffee?
-No! I'm fine.
Mandarin juice is fine.
I see.
(Eunsoo chuckling awkwardly)
Go stay outside.
Go to a cafe or something.
No. It's okay. Don't worry about me.
(chuckles)
(quirky music)
Please, go on.
Okay.
(laughing awkwardly)
-Have some.
-Okay.
-EUNSOO: Then I think...
-(sucks air)
-EUNSOO: this should be...
(sucking air)
EUNSOO: So the man is ultimately giving up
on the woman?
Should we convey his sentiment
in the chorus?
SUNWOO: Why is this not coming out?
(playful music)
"Giving up" sounds a bit too negative.
So, this man doesn't want to break
the balance for this woman's sake.
He's just gently letting go.
I think that should be our hook.
"Letting go..."
You know,
it's like you're letting go of him,
but not voluntarily.
EUNSOO: Oh, I see.
And you are doing it with a heart
wholly devoted to the one you love.
In other words,
uh... it's like the chilly air
of a winter morning at 4:40 a.m.
(inhales)
Pardon me, mister.
-Yes?
-Is there something on my face?
(scoffs)
No.
-Why do you ask?
-WOOIL: I mean...
You were staring only at Eunsoo earlier,
and now you are staring at me.
(chuckles)
No, I was looking at the TV behind you.
EUNSOO: Don't mind him.
He often got into arguments with strangers
because he would just stare at them.
-I see.
-(Eunsoo chuckles)
Anyway,
I'll put more thought into that part.
Okay. Sure.
-Yes.
-Oh, also...
Try asking your friend too.
WOOIL: About...
the feeling of unrequited love.
(guitar music)
-(scoffs)
-EUNSOO: I will.
EUNSOO: Why were you being so rude?
What did I do?
You told him about me smashing mandarins.
Why would you say that?
You told me to be honest with myself.
And you tell him you like mandarin juice?
-How can you be so undignified?
-Undignified?
I was just being polite.
Wouldn't you have done the same?
-No, I wouldn't have.
-Then, don't.
-I wouldn't have, seriously.
-Fine, don't.
And he wasn't being polite either.
He never asked you what you wanted,
or if there is anything you like.
Who cares? I go there to work,
not to drink juice.
Everything he says is so pretentious.
He's so full of it.
It's his artistic sensibility, okay?
That's how he was able to succeed
in what he does.
Chilly air of a winter morning
at 4:00 a.m. or whatever.
Why would you be out that late?
You should be in bed.
It was 4:40 a.m, Sunwoo.
-He said 4:40 a.m.
-Yeah, whatever.
And why do you hate
all the guys in my life?
EUNSOO: You don't like this,
you don't like that.
-That's because every guy you meet is...
-Every guy's what?
-Hold on a second.
SUNWOO: Oh, hey.
(sighs)
I'm almost there. Okay.
-Drop me off here.
-We're almost there.
Just drop me off. I'll walk from here.
(engine revs)
(tire screeches)
Hey!
-(honking)
-(engine revs)
(rattling)
(hissing)
(rattling continues)
(blows air)
I took care of the deposit on the gallery,
but I'm worried about your reputation.
DONGHYEON: What if
a rumor starts circulating...
(Donghyeon sighs)
...that you don't keep your promises?
Let's make a good statement of apology.
-Okay?
-Okay.
By the way, where have you been sleeping?
My girlfriend left.
Why aren't you coming in?
-I'm staying at Eunsoo's.
-Oh, you're staying there.
Eunsoo...
That Eunsoo?
Is it finally time?
Great. You can skip everything
and go straight to living together.
I haven't asked her out yet.
But I'm planning on telling her
before I leave Korea.
I really want to be honest with myself.
Yeah, you should be.
Wait.
Is this why you postponed your exhibition?
Because of Eunsoo?
Oh, gosh.
Not necessarily... I mean...
What a relief! Seriously!
(laughing)
I was worried that you might retire.
It's a huge relief to know
that it's just about a girl.
DONGHYEON: I'm so glad.
(laughing)
(sighs in relief)
Why would I retire?
Good! Clear things up with Eunsoo.
Just come back when you're all finished.
(in Korean, English)
Back to where you should be. Right here.
(in Korean)
Don't worry about the apology.
It's nothing! I'll take care of it.
Don't worry at all.
(footsteps receding)
(breathes heavily)
(light guitar music)
STUDIO RED
I'm not mad anymore. How about you?
(light music continues)
(clears throat)
EUNSOO: Here, a gift of reconciliation.
What is it?
Something to wear...
SUNWOO: It's an apron.
I support your side job, Sunwoo.
EUNSOO: It's pretty, right?
-Okay, we're good.
-Great, we're good.
You scared me.
I thought you were still mad at me.
Why did you glare at me?
Hey, let's go shopping for groceries now.
You drive. The parking space is so small.
I don't think my car can go down there.
It scares me so much.
(Eunsoo groans)
(gasps)
(exclaims)
Yogurt...
Yogurt sounds nice.
SUNWOO: What should we have for dinner?
(chuckles)
Tell me what you're craving.
I'll make you dinner tonight.
-You're cooking? Really?
-EUNSOO: Yes.
What will you make?
Mm...
We really...
need to get rid
of all the mandarins somehow.
EUNSOO: Can I make mandarin rice
or something?
-Mandarin rice...
-(Sunwoo breathes deeply)
How about preserves?
That sounds good.
Preserves.
SUNWOO: Sounds good.
What else do you want?
Uh...
Make me that dish. The one you're best at.
-You mean, my specialty dish?
-Yes.
The dish we always eat
when we celebrate, mourn, or fight?
Is that what you want?
(in English) Bingo.
Okay.
(in Korean) Since we fought
a little today, we'll have it for dinner.
-Let's go.
-Let's go!
(chill-out music)
Cabbage. This should be enough.
SUNWOO: No, we can't finish all of this.
♪ You're simply beautiful, so beautiful ♪
You're right.
♪ You're mesmerizing... ♪
Let's take both, just in case.
We also need lettuce. So keep it.
-♪ Most beautiful in the whole world ♪
-Here, you like curry.
-We need dumplings, of course.
-♪ Where did you come from, I wonder ♪
-This one.
-♪ Because you're so beautiful... ♪
Hurry up.
Why did you even ask?
-♪ You're perfect in every way ♪
-Oh, my gosh. Oh, gosh.
Let's take these.
There are only four bottles left.
♪ Of all the flowers in the world ♪
♪ Where have you been all my life? ♪
♪ Why are you now swaying my heart? ♪
♪ You're simply beautiful,
so beautiful... ♪
No way.
Use mine.
Let me take care of it.
(sucks teeth)
Listen to me.
This is your pay for being my assistant.
(breathes deeply)
Yes, ma'am.
Hold on...
Did I put this in the cart?
-I did.
-Why?
Because you like these.
-EUNSOO: It's freezing!
-(running footsteps)
It's so cold.
Let me borrow your apron later.
I'll wear it to make an amazing dish.
SUNWOO: Okay...
SEOGWIPO MANDARINS
(Eunsoo exclaims)
(sighs)
Mom.
(chuckles nervously)
-Hello...
-Mom, wait. Just listen to me first.
EUNSOO: You know how
Sunwoo came back for his exhibition.
He just needed...
Can you put that down please?
He just needed a place to stay.
-So that's why he's here. Right?
-Yes, she's right.
-EUNSOO'S MOM: What are those?
-EUNSOO: What are those?
They're just things to throw out.
There were expired foods in the fridge.
He's right.
EUNSOO: Mom.
He and I have been friends for 20 years.
-(whispers) For 19 years.
-Huh?
-(whispers) It's 19 years.
-Yes. We've been best buds for 19 years.
What are friends for?
A friend in need is a friend indeed.
That's what I think.
(chair scrapes)
You two. Come sit here.
-Okay.
-Shall we?
(munching)
EUNSOO'S MOM: Han Sunwoo.
Yes?
(whimsical music)
Think about the woes in your heart,
and choose three cards
with your left hand.
EUNSOO'S MOM: Choose from your heart.
-What's up with these Tarot cards?
-I just learned.
So randomly?
-It's fun.
-Is it?
-(chuckles)
-Try staring at the ocean all day.
You'll start getting curious
about the unknown world.
Well?
Take your pick.
Okay.
-Conviction! Choose with conviction!
-(gasps)
Conviction...
-Choose with conviction.
-Left hand!
(whimsical music continues)
-Conviction.
-Conviction...
(whimsical music)
(music fades)
What is it? What does it mean?
EUNSOO'S MOM: Sunwoo...
you like someone, don't you?
Pure love.
Awesome.
(card riffles)
EUNSOO'S MOM: Sincere to the end.
And that person is...
(suspenseful music)
(inhales)
She's very far away.
(gasps)
Hey, it must be Jennifer.
Jennifer. This is crazy.
-(chuckles nervously)
-Mom, you're pretty good.
EUNSOO: Do me next.
Will my lyrics be a big hit this time?
-What time is it? It's late.
-EUNSOO: What?
-All of a sudden?
-I'm late.
What about me?
Mom, wait. What about me?
Take good care of the house, tenant lady.
I'll come back
any time I get sick of the ocean.
Okay.
-Sunwoo.
-Yes?
-You know I trust you, right?
-I do.
Eunsoo.
-You know I don't trust you, right?
-Yes.
-(chuckles)
-I trust nothing will happen here.
Oh, the pictures from your trip.
Have you tried looking for it?
He doesn't have them either.
He deleted them to make space.
What a shame.
-SUNWOO: I know.
-I was collecting those pictures.
I'll get going now.
I brought some mandarins for you.
Mom, please stop sending mandarins.
EUNSOO'S MOM: I'll send you
three more boxes.
-Three more? No way, Mom!
-(cellphone buzzing)
Stop sending them to me, okay?
Go in.
After I see you off.
(soft chuckle)
Here.
EUNSOO'S MOM: It's a lucky charm.
(chuckles)
-It's cold. Get inside.
-SUNWOO: Okay.
Take care.
(light music)
Let's see. May I try this now?
SUNWOO: You were so confident about this.
(munches)
(chuckles)
Well? Awesome, isn't it?
Has it been upgraded?
Living alone levels you up,
even my cooking.
This is really good. No lie.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Eat up.
(exclaims)
EUNSOO: You must have been surprised
seeing my mom.
Man, why does she keep bringing mandarins?
Am I being punished?
Look at my hands. They're all yellow.
Let me see yours.
(guitar music)
You're still okay.
You can eat more of them.
(chuckles)
I'm sorry about earlier today.
What now? I thought we were all good.
But why were you so upset?
I wasn't upset. I was just...
Just what?
(guitar music continues)
I was just annoyed
to see you drink mandarin juice.
Of all the things to be annoyed by.
-Learn to see who really cares for you.
-(munching)
Okay.
Gosh.
EUNSOO: Anyway,
do you get what Mr. Kang said
about the air of 4:40 a.m.?
-Do you have to get it?
-I have to know to write those lyrics.
(exhales sharply)
(clicks tongue)
I imagine it's being lonely in silence.
The lonely feeling
of standing by yourself.
The feeling of wanting to sleep,
but not being able to fall asleep.
Oh...
Hey, should we step outside at 4:40 a.m.?
(laughing)
Eunsoo, you're just...
(chuckles, munches)
-Are you serious?
-EUNSOO: Yes.
(sighs)
(chuckles)
(chuckles softly)
(emotive music plays on headphones)
Hey.
Here.
-Don't you have any scarves?
-(chuckles)
Please keep your neck warm.
(in English) Thank you.
-(exclaims)
-(scoffs)
So we're really doing this.
(emotive music continues)
♪ My heart flutters whenever I see you ♪
♪ I never know what to do ♪
♪ Just when I thought... ♪
BRAINSTORMING MEETING
WHAT IS UNREQUITED LOVE?
♪ I could no longer love ♪
♪ You came to me, my love ♪
♪ They say love is more than words ♪
(woman crying on TV)
♪ I'll pour out my heart
More than anyone else ♪
-♪ I won't hurt your precious heart ♪
-(breathes deeply)
♪ I'll protect you now ♪
♪ I ponder how ♪
♪ How I can comfort you
When you are in need... ♪
I REGRET OUR LAST MOMENTS
I MISS YOU MORE
♪ As I walk down an unfamiliar road ♪
♪ I buy a flower that reminds me of you ♪
♪ And I hurry to see you ♪
♪ They say love is more than words ♪
♪ I'll pour out my heart
More than anyone else ♪
♪ I won't hurt your precious heart ♪
-(camera shutter clicks)
-♪ I'll protect you ♪
♪ I look at you
And I smile for no reason ♪
-♪ I can't explain ♪
-(camera shutter clicks)
♪ This fluttering heart of mine ♪
(music fades)
SUNWOO: Where are the clean towels?
-In the dryer.
-SUNWOO: Got it.
(sighs)
(cellphone buzzing)
DONGHYEON
-(water running)
-(cellphone buzzing continues)
Hey, Donghyeon. This is Eunsoo.
DONGHYEON: Is Sunwoo there?
EUNSOO: He's washing up.
I'll have him call you back.
DONGHYEON: No, that will be too late.
Can you by any chance
get on Sunwoo's laptop?
Me?
Can't you just ask Sunwoo when he's out?
DONGHYEON: There's a photo that needs
to be sent to the agency right away.
It should be in the "Collection 21" folder
on his desktop.
Can you send it to me right now?
Help me out, please.
Okay, hold on a second.
What's the file name again?
COLLECTION21
All right.
SUBJECT: IS THIS IT?
SEND
FILE UPLOADING
SENDING
EUNSOO: Just sent.
(sighs)
Oh, right. My pictures.
Why hasn't he sent me these?
(Eunsoo chuckles)
When was it?
Year 2020...
2020JEJU
Found it.
Yes.
He didn't delete them after all...
211211_EUNSOO
2020JEJU
Trying to fool me...
(reflective music)
(chuckles softly)
(music stops)
(emotive music)
(emotive music continues)
2013_CHRISTMAS
(emotive music rises)
BONUS TRACK
(door closes)
(sighs)
(dramatic music)
(rasping)
(sighs)
(pensive music)
This is crazy.
"This is crazy"?
(soft music)