(All places, organizations, characters,
incidents, and backstories...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(Final Episode)
(Have a Drink With Su A)
See you later.
("Police Say
Ex-NIS Agent Jeong Planned Murder")
Hello?
- It's me.
- Is that you, Hae Seong?
Where are you?
What happened? You got out?
Su A.
I'm sorry.
I need your help.
Hae Seong. Where are you?
I'll come over. Where are you?
Hae Seong!
Hae Seong?
(Payphone location)
(Find payphone location)
(Payphone locations)
(412 Gilkkeutbyeol-ro, Euihyeon-si,
Gyeonggi Province)
(Have a Drink With Su A)
This is obviously
of Seo Myeong Ju's design.
Clearing Hae Seong's name
is our utmost priority,
- so let's find some evidence.
- Yes, sir.
Damn Gong Jin Sang. I'll catch up.
Why? What is it? I'm busy as is,
so talk fast.
Hae Seong did what?
Excuse me.
(Countryside Store)
Hey.
Gosh, he's awake.
He's awake!
Are you all right?
You should stay where you are.
I'll call an ambulance.
Don't.
You shouldn't move.
You're bleeding way too much.
I'm fine.
I'll get to a hospital by myself.
Hello?
Someone's badly injured.
Please hurry.
Our current location is...
There's a store
called Countryside Store nearby.
But...
Are you all right?
Do you know him?
I'll take him to the hospital.
Thank you.
- Sure thing.
- Let's go.
It was nothing.
Sorry about that.
(Sopoong Motel)
When did you get up?
Just now.
Would you like some tea?
Thanks.
Wait, this isn't right!
You...
You're okay.
What happened to you yesterday?
I escaped while being transported.
What?
It was Seo Myeong Ju
who killed my dad.
(2025, the 2nd
Special Board Meeting Notice)
(Byeongmun Foundation boardroom)
(Agenda A: The dismissal
of Chairwoman Seo Myeong Ju)
Even the directors
who were in your favor...
are now turning their backs on you.
We're grasping at straws now.
What about Jeong Hae Seong?
The police
are still looking for him.
But there's a warrant
out for his arrest,
so it won't be long
before he's found.
Bring him in any way you can.
Ma'am.
Maybe you should get some shut-eye.
I'll bring you regular updates.
(Byeongmun High School)
Your father...
and that murdered NIS agent.
Seo Myeong Ju was behind it all?
She also framed me for murder.
She believes I have the gold bars.
Because of that,
she could go after those around me.
I'm off to arrest Seo Myeong Ju.
It'll be dangerous for you,
so stay home.
Then I'll head to school.
If you're right, the students
could also be in danger.
She knows how much
you care about them.
Besides, I'm a teacher.
(Wanted Fugitive)
Where did you get this?
At the pharmacy
when I went to pick up meds.
What now?
Can you call my team?
Why are you dressed like this?
Don't get me started.
The police
have been monitoring us...
in the hopes
that we lead them to you.
We barely managed to ditch them.
It's all over the news.
- What a scene.
- Goodness.
- Why you... Turn it off!
- My head...
Hey.
I thought you might need this.
Thanks.
Anyway, how do we even begin?
I'm lost as to how
we can untangle this mess.
The recording was our only evidence,
but they took it.
Don't we have another option?
The first option...
is still viable.
Don't you know who I am?
The only female agent
on Domestic Team Four...
and the brains of the team.
I'm Park Mi Jeong.
My leg cramped up.
Wait.
You can go now. Okay?
Guys. Search
the second floor thoroughly too.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
I'm in love, Mi Jeong.
Take the romance outside.
With that flash drive,
we'll be able to take
Seo Myeong Ju down.
I'll go.
The police are probably
waiting outside your house.
You can't go there yourself.
What then?
It'll be the same for you three.
We barely managed to ditch the tail.
It'd be impossible to go there.
I'm always up for a challenge,
but this will be impossible.
What about me,
the team's honorary field agent?
What do you say?
No. It's too dangerous.
This is what we'll do.
The loser of rock-paper-scissors...
will secure the flash drive.
The winner will be the lookout.
What do you think?
What now?
It's dangerous for all of us,
so why does she get a pass?
This stinks of favoritism.
A murder suspect escaped...
while being transported
to a detention center,
- and the police...
- Unbelievable.
revealed his identity.
- Jeong Hae Seong, age 30.
- What?
He's an ex-NIS agent.
Jeong was arrested on scene...
the day before yesterday
of the murder...
of his superior who was in his 40s.
The police
who are still tracking him...
have asked
for the people's cooperation.
- Are you ready? Let's go.
- Sure.
Let's go.
Agent An.
- Yes?
- It's bad.
How so?
Damn it.
- Not that way.
- Damn it!
Go. Get in there.
Shoot.
Open up!
Hae Seong, it'll be over
if you get caught.
Take Ms. Oh and go.
- But we're on the third floor.
- What?
You just had to get a room
on an upper floor, didn't you?
I'm sorry. That's on me.
That's understandable.
- Open up!
- Open this door!
I can't hold them off any longer.
Just get out of here!
Damn it.
You've got to be kidding me.
- I'll leave this to you then.
- Sure.
- Let me.
- Hurry!
Block them.
Are you suggesting we jump?
- Yes.
- What...
I can't!
Are you okay?
Let's go.
What the...
Get out here.
Jeong Hae Seong!
No, don't.
- Get them.
- Yes, sir.
Su A, get going.
- I'll lure them my way.
- But...
I'm an NIS agent.
You said you'd protect the kids.
Go and do just that.
Go.
That way. Get him!
Get him!
What the...
Get him. That way!
Yes, sir.
Damn it.
Shit.
Ms. Seo.
- Jeong Hae Seong...
- Yes?
They weren't able to capture him.
Those incompetent fools.
(Byeongmun Foundation)
(Byeongmun High,
for whom does it exist?)
(Do not crush their dreams.)
(Education is a right,
not a privilege.)
(Byeongmun High,
for whom does it exist?)
Byeongmun High, please.
We'll cut to the chase.
It's about time you stepped down.
The public is outraged,
and the foundation
is unhealthy on the inside.
If you refuse to step down,
we will have to formally bring
this up at the general meeting.
I urge you to make a decision
before that.
It's right for you to step down.
- We need a decision.
- Absolutely.
- I agree.
- She should step down.
- The chairwoman...
- Unbelievable.
- Has she no shame?
- Just step down.
- Chairwoman, step down.
- Come on.
Sure.
I am clear...
with where you all stand.
(Chairwoman Seo Myeong Ju)
Once you pull me down
from my position as chairwoman,
you're planning to dismiss me
from this board.
Aren't I right?
Sure.
Do as you wish.
However, I urge you
to follow protocol.
As stated in the bylaws,
bring me the consent
of over three-fourths...
of the students and faculty members.
Until you do...
- What?
- Has she no shame?
Don't forget...
that I'm...
your leader and master.
(Byeongmun Foundation)
Your tongues.
Be careful with what you say.
My gosh.
- What?
- I can't believe her.
How can she be this way?
Has she no shame?
Does she think she owns us?
- Unbelievable.
- I can't believe this.
Such vermin.
How dare they try
to pull me down from my throne?
Either way, we'll need a way...
to calm the students down.
(Police)
The phone has been turned off.
You'll be redirected
to voicemail after the tone.
Hey. I'm only asking for my phone.
Come on.
Don't be this way
to a fellow officer of the law.
No can do.
But... Hey.
Yeong Hun,
don't you have any connections?
How can we help Yeong Hun
while in here?
My whole life,
I have been led
by my integrity and conscience.
Of course I don't have
any connections.
It's more like
you're not competent enough!
Mi Jeong, what about you?
Don't you know
any police officers...
My gosh.
Weren't you hurt?
Gladly, I wasn't.
What about you?
I arrived at the school
and am doing what needs to be done.
You never know, so watch your back.
Same for you.
Have you found a way
to get into your house?
I think I have...
although it has its flaws.
Hello? Hae Seong?
Hae Seong, is everything okay?
Hello?
Hae Seong.
- Hae Seong!
- Hey, Su A.
Did something happen?
No. I'll call you later.
You do that.
(Byeongmun High,
for whom does it exist?)
(Ms. Seo, rescind recent changes
made to the school.)
(Byeongmun High,
for whom does it exist?)
(Byeongmun Foundation
and Byeongmun High...)
(of history and tradition...)
Scared you, didn't I?
That's for twisting my arm
the other day.
And the flash drive?
I heard the recording.
I hate to admit it,
but you were right.
Don't tense up.
I'm only here to talk.
- I'll have what he's having.
- Sure.
Do you expect me...
to believe that?
It's the truth.
Seo Myeong Ju is behind everything.
Fine.
Let's say that's true.
I could slap cuffs
on your wrists this instant,
but I'll play along.
Where's your proof?
In a flash drive...
that's at my house. Bring it to me.
What's in it for me?
The truth.
The truth?
What if there's no evidence
or that you're lying?
This will be your collar.
That's something important to you.
What's the actual truth?
This is all I can do for you.
It's up to you...
to clear your name.
Senior Agent Gong.
I'm sorry for twisting your arm.
Jeong Hae Seong.
Shouldn't the apology
be more formal?
He's cool, but borderline rude.
(Trustworthy police, safe country)
Excuse me.
How can I help you?
I'm turning myself in.
(Wanted Fugitive)
(Byeongmun High,
for whom does it exist?)
(All subsidies canceled,
Tuition raised by 50 percent)
(Ms. Seo, I strongly suggest...)
(you rescind recent changes
made to the school.)
I apologize.
I'll find out who posted this.
It was me.
I put that up.
Why?
I believe
I already made myself clear.
Because your policies...
will only crush
our students' future.
So?
I only ask because I'm curious.
Tell me. Do you believe...
that this lousy poster...
will change this school?
Historically,
those who shifted the world...
were the powerless majority.
I know what you're thinking.
That I'm a powerless temp.
But that doesn't mean
I'll give up on the students.
I'll squirm.
I'll do whatever it is I can.
Will it be like striking eggs
on a rock?
Then I won't stop
until that rock is shattered.
I am their teacher...
and have a duty to protect them.
I see. How admirable of you.
Fine, then.
The new policies
we were going to implement?
Rescind them all.
Right.
Thank you.
I was about to do so anyway.
On one condition though.
Quit the school.
Why? Do you want
to protect the kids...
but not at a price?
Right now at this exact moment!
Look deep into that heart...
that is hesitating
to give me an answer.
Because that's who you are.
You're...
no better than the rest of us.
I'll gladly quit.
Sure.
But keep your word.
I'm sick of it.
Who is she to pretend
she's kind and innocent...
thinking she's a martyr?
(An Yu Jeong)
Once I beat
the dismissal proposal...
at the general board meeting
next week,
implement the policies
I said I wouldn't.
But...
if you do that, the students
will oppose even harder...
In what way?
As if they ever took action.
Gathering in groups
to speak ill of me...
and gossiping online?
Did you know...
that insects can't hear
people's footsteps?
But we, humans,
can't hear them buzzing either.
Still, gather all the students
in the main hall after school.
I need them on my side
to beat the dismissal proposal.
You killed Jae Hyeon.
What am I supposed to do with this?
You must be thoroughly mistaken,
but I have no interest
in an old cold case.
You.
You're the prime suspect
in Director Kim Hyung Bae's murder.
Should a detective be this clumsy?
- I bet you got bad grades.
- What?
See how long the recording is.
Anyone with a brain
would think there's more on it.
Principal Park, why are you here...
Did Seo Myeong Ju order this?
This is why you should've kept
your mouth shut.
Chairwoman Seo.
It's been handled.
Let's handle it on our end too.
We'll issue the arrest warrant.
But there's a procedure to follow.
How about this, then?
We'll investigate this first and...
Detective Cho Sang Cheol.
Don't make it look obvious...
that you're in league
with Seo Myeong Ju.
Otherwise, I'll crush you.
Shoot.
(Seo Myeong Ju)
Damn it!
(Restricted Area)
(Interrogation Room)
What could the chairwoman
suddenly want to say?
Beats me. Do you know anything?
- Do you?
- I only know what you know.
- So she says.
- She doesn't know.
- Whatever.
- What's this about?
- Who knows?
Let's hear what she has to say.
My beloved students
at Byeongmun High.
I gathered you all here today...
to promise a few things.
First.
As for the school grades scandal,
such a disgraceful event...
Regardless of whether it was true,
I assure you that it will not
happen again at our school.
Second.
As for the new policies...
regarding discontinuation
of the scholarship program...
and the tuition increase,
we have decided
to scrap them altogether.
- Hey.
- My gosh.
- Thank goodness.
- Nice.
- I don't have to drop out.
- What a relief.
- Thank goodness.
- I know.
- I'm so relieved.
- Seriously.
Byeongmun High School
will be reborn, completely.
(Ms. Oh. Enjoy it.)
(Academic Counseling Program)
(Letter of Resignation)
The kind of school where everyone
here can have a true friendship...
while building knowledge and skills
through healthy competition.
I only care about this one thing
and nothing else.
It is your future and happiness.
I, Seo Myeong Ju, promise you this.
To ensure your bright future
and happiness,
I will continue to do my best...
What about Ms. Oh Su A?
Why did you make her quit?
Ms. Oh quit?
- She was here earlier.
- Yes, I saw her too.
You said
our happiness mattered to you.
Then please leave
our homeroom teacher alone.
There must've been
some kind of misunderstanding.
I simply let Ms. Oh decide...
I heard everything!
You made her quit.
- Seriously?
- That's crazy.
- Why?
- For real?
- Is this for real?
- Why?
That is a groundless rumor
you are spreading now.
Your name is An Yu Jeong, right?
Yes.
That's how it should be.
I am here to do the talking.
You are just here to listen.
We know you're the chairwoman
of the school,
but you can't treat a teacher
like that!
That's right. Ms. Oh fought for us.
Would you be happy
if we all told you to step down?
Teachers.
The three students who spoke
just now without my permission.
Write their names down.
She's having them
jot down our names?
I am Lee Dong Min.
I do not agree with you either,
ma'am.
Okay. Lee Dong Min. Write it down.
I am Kang Gi Yeong.
I also think this is wrong.
Okay, Kang Gi Yeong.
Write that down.
I'm Jeong Sang Hun.
I, too, think this is wrong.
My name is Heo Jun Yeong.
We want Ms. Oh back.
I'm Lee Hyeon Jae.
- Me too!
- Bring her back!
- What? State your names clearly.
One person at a time!
We want Ms. Oh back!
- Bring her back!
- We want her back!
- Please!
- Bring her back!
- We want Ms. Oh back!
- Step down!
Please bring Ms. Oh back.
- Ms. Oh couldn't give up on us,
so she fought against you
to protect us.
Ms. Oh isn't the one
who should leave our school.
I think you should step down!
Yes, totally!
Step down.
Chairwoman Seo must step down!
- Step down!
- Gosh, so loud.
What is this?
Cockroaches chanting together?
- Step down!
(National Intelligence Service)
Are you ready?
The arrest warrant has been issued.
Seo Myeong Ju and Park Jae Mun?
They're both at the school now.
Good. Let's go.
Yes, sir.
(National Intelligence Service)
- Step down!
- Hey, Ms. Oh is here!
- Ms. Oh.
- Ms. Oh, please don't leave.
- Ms. Oh!
- Don't quit.
Please don't leave.
- Ms. Oh, please stay.
- We need you.
- Ms. Oh, please!
- Please don't quit.
Okay.
Ma'am, we have a problem.
Arrest warrants...
have been issued for both of us.
- Please stay.
- Yes, please.
- We will protect you.
- We'll do better.
- You can't leave us.
- Seriously.
- Take it back.
- You can't do this to us.
- We have your back.
- Yes, you can count on us.
- Ms. Oh, you can't do this.
- We will protect you, Ms. Oh.
Take Ye Na and head home now.
Then...
you should hide too.
Myeong Ju.
Do as I say.
Please.
- Please.
- Take it back.
- Yes.
- Ms. Oh, please.
- We'll get through it together.
- Seriously, don't leave us.
- Don't leave us, Ms. Oh!
- Please stay!
- Ms. Oh, don't leave us!
- We need you!
(Seo Myeong Ju)
You are impatient.
You'll see me shortly anyway.
I'm not sure if I'll get to
see you guys before I go.
In life,
there is only one thing
that is fair to all.
Do you know what it is?
Death.
Seo Myeong Ju!
Hey, what's with him?
(Motion to Dismiss
Chairwoman Seo Myeong Ju)
(Lee Ye Na, Ryu Su Hyeon,
Kim Seung Hyeon, Park Sang Hyeop)
- Just sign here.
- Okay.
Where is Ye Na?
Principal Park took her home.
- What?
- What is this?
- What's going on?
What is this?
What is going on?
- What's happening?
- What's this?
- Oh, no.
- What's going on?
- My gosh!
- What is this?
What is this smell?
Some kind of oil, I think.
- Oil?
- Yes.
It's gasoline.
This gasoline will burn
you rowdy cockroaches to death.
What do you think you're doing?
Don't move.
I'll drop this
the moment anyone tries to get out.
You guys like it
when things are fair.
So, let's all be fair...
and die together.
- No!
- Ms. Oh!
- Step aside!
- My gosh!
- You came a little too late.
- Put that down.
Put your gun down first.
Put that down.
- No.
- Stop!
Turn the car around.
Turn the car around now!
Let the kids go.
- Why should I?
- They did nothing wrong.
Let them go.
It's too late.
You ruined everything already.
How many chances did I give you?
Every time you took away
what was precious to me.
But now, what?
Let the kids go
because they did nothing wrong?
I didn't take away anything.
You are obsessed.
You are...
gnawing away at yourself right now.
What truly matters to you?
Think about that for a moment.
Mom!
Ye Na.
Don't do it, Mom.
Please.
You... Why are you here?
Mom.
You can still keep her safe.
Please...
Please don't cause any more pain
to others.
Ye Na, go home.
- Mom.
- Go home.
- Principal Park!
- Mom!
- Go home. Now!
- Go home!
If you stop now,
everything can go back
to how it used to be.
So, please...
Please put that down now.
Go back?
Go back, where?
Back to when?
No!
- He caught it!
- Nice catch!
- He caught it.
- He caught the lighter.
- Thank goodness.
- Oh, my.
- Hae Seong!
- Yes!
- Amazing!
- Go, Hae Seong!
- Oh, my!
- Thank goodness!
- My gosh.
- Well done!
Hae Seong.
- Get them.
- Yes, sir.
Thanks, Hae Seong.
- Yes!
- Go, Hae Seong!
That was nuts.
Good work.
You saved the school...
- and Yu Jeong...
- Bye.
- Take good care of them.
- What will happen now?
And everyone else.
You saved all of them.
So? Do you want to head straight
to the office now?
No, I want to talk
to the kids first.
All right.
They must've been terrified.
Check in on them with Ms. Oh.
Hey.
What's wrong with you?
Hey, look at me.
Your face... What happened?
I'm just a little tired.
- Let me go talk to the kids.
- All right, then.
- Hey, let's go.
- Yes, sir.
- Hae Seong!
- Jeong Hae Seong!
Dad!
- Hae Seong!
- Hey.
- Hae Seong.
- Hae Seong!
- Call 911.
- Call 911!
- I need my phone!
- Hae Seong!
- Oh, no!
It's the Big Dipper.
Oh, my.
You know about the Big Dipper?
You're so smart.
Dad.
What about the North Star?
The North Star?
If we have the Big Dipper,
we need the North Star too.
Where is the North Star?
Si Hyun, the North Star
you are looking for...
My goodness, look.
- You woke up.
- Hae Seong.
- Are you all right?
- My gosh.
- Are you okay?
- What happened?
They said you had a mild concussion.
It would've been bad
if you'd come any later.
Hey, how could you not tell me
until this...
Goodness. Don't yell at him.
He's still recovering.
Hey! Stop, seriously.
You really need to
take better care of yourself.
As your teammate,
I'm always so anxious and worried.
Oh, right.
Let's wake Yeong Hun up.
What happened to him?
He wanted to stay by your side.
He didn't sleep for a few days
and collapsed.
I must say, he's loyal.
Although he can be dumb at times.
What about Seo Myeong Ju
and Park Jae Mun?
The case is being tried.
They're on trial now.
The problem is, Park keeps insisting
that he did it alone.
Everything from the incident
22 years ago.
I made the decisions...
and did everything on my own.
Let me meet him.
I must say, this is awkward.
To see you
without Seo Myeong Ju by your side.
I did some thinking.
"Who is Seo Myeong Ju
to Park Jae Mun?"
"How could he be so devoted
to one person?"
So I looked into it and learned
you go way back.
You were an orphan,
and her family took you in
when you were nine,
which means you've known her
for over 40 years.
She's family to you. Am I right?
You'd risk your life to protect her.
I'm sorry to say this,
but you ruined her.
Care to explain?
Seo Myeong Ju.
In your eyes,
did it look like she was doing okay?
What about Ye Na?
How do you think Ye Na felt
as she watched her mom like that?
If you take the fall for everything,
then what?
Do you think she'll be happy?
What are you trying to get at?
The choice is yours.
What would truly help her?
Think about it.
Don't make her any more miserable
than she already is.
Witness.
Do you have anything to say
about Ms. Seo Myeong Ju,
the accused?
Witness,
answer the prosecutor's question.
(Lee Ye Na)
Witness.
You said you had something
to tell us about the murders...
of Jeong Jae Hyeon, Kim Hyeon Ho,
and Kim Hyung Bae.
Am I right?
Please answer. Am I right?
(Witness)
Twenty-two years ago,
Chairwoman Seo Myeong Ju...
killed Mr. Jeong Jae Hyeon,
who was an NIS agent at the time.
- What? Seriously?
- So, it is true?
I did...
as Chairwoman Seo Myeong Ju said.
Not only did I murder Kim Hyeon Ho,
but I also...
took the life
of NIS Director Kim Hyung Bae.
I killed him too.
What?
- For real?
- Is this true?
For all I did,
I put the blame...
on Jeong Hae Seong.
You traitor!
- Defendant! Be quiet!
- Damn you!
- You!
- There's a commotion,
so I'll sentence the defendant...
- after a short recess.
- You!
You traitor!
Case number 2025-KH-9606.
I'll deliver the sentence.
Despite the cruel nature
of the crimes...
and the clear evidence,
the defendant made excuses...
that were impossible to believe,
and refused to show remorse.
The defendant, Seo Myeong Ju...
is sentenced to life in prison.
Wait.
Ye Na.
I dropped out of school.
I want to start over.
On my own, without help.
I love you, Mom.
I love you so much,
but I need time...
to be able to understand you.
I'll visit you again.
It's time for morning assembly.
You have a visitor.
He thought he didn't say goodbye...
and wanted to actually do that.
Come in.
So...
I'm here too often...
considering I got expelled, right?
Okay.
The time...
I spent with you meant a lot.
They'll be fond memories.
I'll miss you.
I came to say this.
Study hard...
and listen to your teacher.
Bye.
Guys.
Excuse me.
(Byeongmun High School)
Hae Seong.
Hey.
They're in shock.
It was a scary evening.
They're all pretty sensitive.
Don't mind it too much.
Are you consoling me?
Look after them.
It hit them hard.
See you.
(Thank you for being my friend.)
Jeong Hae Seong!
- Bye, Jeong Hae Seong!
- Bye.
- Take care!
- Thank you!
- I'm proud of you!
- Good job!
- Bye!
- Look after yourself!
- Thanks!
- Thank you!
- Bye, Hae Seong!
- Take care!
- I loved you!
- Buddy!
- Bye!
- I'll miss you!
- Bye, Hae Seong!
- Stay safe!
- Thanks a lot!
- Take care of yourself!
- Bye.
- I'll be in touch!
- Bye!
- Don't push!
- Bye.
- Hae Seong!
- Bye, Hae Seong!
- Thank you!
- Take care!
- See you!
- I'll miss you!
I like his smile.
(Recreation Forest Field Trip)
He must've had fun
with the students.
Like you did?
Keep it safe for me.
What for?
He wanted to keep it
as a fond memory.
I have a feeling...
your father left this
as a message to you.
The title.
It's another word for "comet."
(2003 Byeongmun High School
Student Council, "Stars That Write")
It's so good when it's warm.
Can I have one more after this?
One more?
Eat all you want. Lots and lots.
Thanks.
Goodness.
If we have the Big Dipper,
we need the North Star too.
Where is the North Star?
Si Hyun, the North Star
you are looking for...
I hid it.
Why would you hide a star?
For you to find later on.
A star that's always
in the same place.
That star always shines bright.
It's a star
that shows people the way.
If you follow that star,
you'll find the answer.
Si Hyun.
I hope that one day,
you will complete this mission.
My darn father.
What about me?
You're really something.
My gosh.
Senior Agent An.
I completed the mission.
That's the end of my story.
How are the others doing?
(5 years later)
("Undercover High School")
- Ms. Oh.
- Hey.
You like web-novels?
I taught the guy who wrote this.
(Lee Dong Min)
Take a look.
Ta-da.
(Teaching Certificate, Oh Su A)
At last.
Congratulations.
I kept my word.
- Let's go eat.
- Sounds good.
Su A did what she set out to do.
It took her a while, though.
Ms. An Yu Jeong.
Why do you want to join the NIS?
I grew up with a vague curiosity
about what it meant...
to protect something.
Yu Jeong...
is working hard
to achieve her dream.
The thought that we could
become colleagues...
- Save me, please.
- It gave me a positive influence.
Ye Na's working on
what she actually wanted to.
(My love Yu Jeong)
Yu Jeong. How did the interview go?
Of course, she's cool with Yu Jeong.
Director.
(Director An Seok Ho)
Uncle became way cool.
It's true that a title maketh man.
Good job.
Mi Jeong.
I think they opened
the accounts overseas.
Yeong Hun finally gave up
pursuing Mi Jeong.
If you look at this...
But the funny thing is...
Let's call Interpol immediately...
to catch...
Mi Jeong.
Come with me.
I might become an uncle soon.
(Have a Drink With Su A)
- What is this?
- You don't know anything.
This is how they dress.
Honey. Where's Hae Seong?
If you think about it, treasures...
aren't that far away.
- What took you so long?
- Hae Seong!
- Hae Seong.
- Get over here.
- Hae Seong!
Sit down.
- You're late.
- My treasure...
It took him so long.
- are these people.
- Sit down.
- You made it.
- Have a drink.
- We were waiting.
- Here.
No, wait. Mi Jeong's glass is empty.
- Wait.
What is it?
- My gosh.
- No way!
How could you?
- You took your sweet time to tell.
- My goodness!
Let's celebrate. Cheers.
- Congratulations!
- Thanks.
The past I spent with them.
The present I'm spending with them.
And the future I'll spend with them.
Every moment...
is sparkling.
I hope you find your own treasures.
Even if it takes time,
I hope you find
the warmest and the brightest light.
I really do.
(Have a Drink With Su A)
They're the same stars,
but they look different from here.
They're pretty.
I think you're prettier.
You've changed a lot in a few years.
- Su A.
- What?
Close your eyes.
- Why?
- Do it.
(Undercover High School)
(No food,
No students from other classes)
(Teacher's Note)
I'm your new homeroom teacher,
Jeong Hae Seong.
I hope we get along.
- No way.
- He's cool.
- I don't believe it.
- He's cute.
You're so handsome.
(Special thanks to Im Chul Hyung
and Oh Eui Sik for the appearance)
(Thank you for watching
Undercover High School.)
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)