[suspenseful music]
[MAN] According
to eyewitness accounts,
the victims were attacked
by a sudden swarm of eyeballs
that flew through the air.
[whimpering]
[INK] Aw.
Is she not coming?
[crying]
Flum?
Flum.
Hi, Flum.
What's wrong?
Are you OK?
[FLUM] Your face!
Do I have something on it?
No. It was earlier.
When I came in, eyeballs were
falling out of your face, Ink.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
You must have been having
some kind of bad dream.
It sounds really scary.
Anyway, where's Milkit?
[FLUM] I wasn't dreaming
or seeing things!
I remember the sounds,
the smells!
You turned into a monster!
That isn't true.
Why would you say
something so mean to me?
Because I know what I saw!
You weren't human.
It was awful.
But I am human.
The Church's
tinkering changed you
into something abnormal,
into some sort of creature.
And that's...
why you
don't have a heart.
What?
No heart.
That must be why they had
you taking that medicine.
It wasn't to keep you healthy
or make you better,
but to suppress your powers.
And when you stopped taking it,
things spun out of control.
Those eyeballs,
they hurt people,
and then they even
went after Sarah.
No!
I-- I didn't.
You're wrong.
I wouldn't hurt anyone!
I love Sarah,
and the rest of you!
I love all of you!
Love us?
Ed, Jonny, and Ottilie
are all gone!
And now Eterna and Milkit
are missing too!
I can't find them.
[crying]
No!
I never do bad stuff
to people I care about.
You would, and you did!
Don't you see?
Friends don't do that!
[suspenseful music]
So I guess I'm not a friend.
Then I guess there's
only one place I belong.
[FLUM] Why?
Why is all of this happening?
[glass breaking]
[DEIN] Flum Apricot!
Get out here.
[theme music]
Dein, what are you
doing here?
This poor little guinea pig
ran away from home.
I came to take it
back where it belongs.
Hold on.
Did you abduct Milkit?
Mummy girl's
probably being tortured
by the lady as we speak.
If she isn't dead already,
that is.
The lady?
Can't figure it out?
I'm talking about the mummy's
former master, Satils Francois.
What?
Is that why--
I see.
Hm.
All right.
Come and get me, Flum.
You want to save
your friend, don't you?
That's what you call
each other, right?
You're so angry.
I like it, Flum!
[melancholic music]
What's wrong?
Don't you want to fight?
[DEIN] Hell of a job keeping
up with me, attagirl.
[FLUM] Ugh! Dein!
I didn't think you'd
follow me so closely.
As much as I'd love
to stay and play,
I've got to get this one home.
If you want the girl,
you'll have to fight for her.
[FLUM] Come back!
[grunting]
Their teamwork is perfect.
It's like they're
moving as one.
How?
Let's see.
Godin Torres, 2,482.
A C rank?
Is he the leader, then?
Godin again?
I know this guy,
Grimmie, Dein's lackey.
So why's it say Godin?
They all have the same name
and the exact same stats.
What's going on?
Something's weird
with their eyes.
The Church must have
messed with them.
Here he comes.
[grunting]
Reversal!
That's one down.
[groaning]
[screaming]
[suspenseful music]
Am I supposed to beat
this group by myself?
[suspenseful music]
No.
I will not die.
Not here.
[GADHIO]
Flum, you know what to do.
Strike the ground
with your prana!
[NARRATOR]
A technique
that overwhelms enemies
with a barrage
of sword slashes,
cavalier arts, prana storm.
Stay alert.
There are more on the way.
Got it.
[music playing]
[heavy breathing]
Thanks, Gadhio.
You came to help.
Yeah.
Some girl named Sarah
asked me to.
Does that mean
she's alive?
Yes.
[NARRATOR]
Flum had been
shrouded in despair,
certain that she'd lost
everyone she held dear.
But with those words,
a ray of hope
broke through the darkness.
Right, then.
Let's move.
Link up.
Connection.
[GADHIO] Flum!
Leave me.
Run.
I'll handle this fight.
[suspenseful music]
My, my.
You're quite the beast.
[GADHIO] One of the children?
Ink must have
blabbed about us.
That useless idiot.
Oh, well.
Now, spiral monster,
you will die.
It's your funeral, mister.
Connection.
Just hold on a little longer,
Milkit, Ink.
Interesting.
There's a hidden passageway.
You can get inside by going
through the stable in the yard.
A Church lapdog.
[DEIN] I thought you'd
never show, Miss Apricot.
I welcome you to the mansion
of Satils Francois.
Take me to Ink and Milkit.
Don't know where they are.
You should worry more about
keeping yourself alive.
Ha.
You're the one
who's gonna die!
Hyah!
Prepare for an early grave,
Dein.
[DEIN] Your powers
are so annoying.
Yeah. Right back at you, Dein.
Did you get
those gross abilities
for joining
the Church of Origin?
Yeah, sure did.
Like 'em?
So that's the reason
you sold out your friends!
You'd do the exact
same thing.
Imagine to be offered
absolute power
that money and influence
could never match!
A power that could
change the very laws
that govern this world!
Huh?
[DEIN] Admit it.
You'd make the same choice.
[suspenseful music]
[cackling]
So how do you like
the Francois mansion?
Mummy girl's former master
has some nasty proclivities,
wouldn't you say?
Those tentacles bat away
any regular attacks,
which means...
Prana shaker.
[laughter]
Not your lucky day.
You're too slow.
Come on!
You usually have more guts
when you face me!
Nowhere to run.
About time I got
my hands on you.
My friends are dead.
My humanity is gone.
A situation like that
really makes you think
about what you've got left.
But today
I finally get to cross
one big regret off of my list!
Your life is mine, Flum.
Sure, the lady told me
not to kill you.
I just don't care
about her orders.
And I don't think
I can hold myself back.
Your death is the start
of my comeback.
I'll rule
the West District again.
Actually,
with my new strength,
I'll take over the entire
kingdom this time.
I'll rule everything!
[WOMAN]
Create a picture in your mind
and say the words
that come naturally.
Re-- Reaper.
Your time's run out.
Goodbye.
[STRAINING] Reaper Soul.
What did you do?
Damn it!
Ah!
The tentacles are rotting away.
[NARRATOR]
Flum had only to picture them
loosening their grip on her.
Reversal!
No.
This can't be happening.
You cannot defeat the divine!
Isn't this the Great Origin's
power that I'm wielding?
Pathetic.
That's what you deserve
for relying on the gifts
of others.
You're still nothing!
I won't let you beat me!
[FLUM] Prana shaker, reversal.
Amazing.
Even Origin's power
can be reversed.
[gasping]
[VOICES]
It's a voice
of corruption.
Flum Apricot,
you mustn't listen
to the voice of corruption.
It's a voice of corruption.
Flum Apricot, you musn't--
Damn.
Those voices again,
the lady and Origin.
Why are they so scared
of the slave girl?
Stop mumbling your excuses.
You're weak.
Do you really think
you've beaten me?
The battle's just
getting started.
I've barely begun to fight.
Behold the power
Origin granted me,
fueled by the dark crystal
embedded within my body!
What?
Ink shows no signs
of having a heartbeat.
But there's something
that's keeping her alive.
Does Ink have a dark
crystal in her body too?
The power
of the core gives me
the strength to slaughter
any fool that stands in my way!
[FLUM] The core?
[WOMAN] You broke its core?
[laughter]
Take her body.
Make it painful.
Become a mindless ball
of meat, you bitch!
Scream for me and die!
[screaming]
You think that'll help?
Ink didn't know eyeballs
were falling out of her face
or attacking people.
So this power--
Hey. What gives?
Why did you stop?
Defend me like you always do!
Take Flum!
Save it.
These eyes, they belong to Ink.
She's the one
that's in charge here.
This is how
she protects her friends.
Ha!
This power is mine.
Origin told me so.
They tricked you.
It made you easy to control.
You seem desperate.
I'm with the Church, child.
And I'm willing
to lend you a hand.
[NARRATOR]
In that moment,
Dein understood
that he had been fooled
and that he would fall
for the same ruse again
even now.
[VOICES] [murmuring]
[DEIN] It can't be!
This power belongs
to me, not her.
Defend me, damn it!
I said such awful things
to Ink.
And yet, despite that,
she's protecting me.
I have to apologize to her.
Now, where is Ink, damn it?
[melancholic music]
[DEIN] It makes no sense.
How could someone like
me lose to a slave?
I was a ruler.
We lost our nobility.
I had to struggle
in those damn slums.
I clawed my way up
with my own two hands.
I-- I am a champion
of the people.
I spent years
building an empire.
Then, out of nowhere,
these monsters show up
and destroy
all that I've built!
It's no fair.
It's not how my story
is supposed to play out.
Screw the Church.
Screw the children.
Screw Origin.
Fuck 'em all,
and fuck you!
What the hell?
No way.
How could you beat me?
You're pathetic.
The people I used to know
are all dead,
every last friend of mine.
So what am I
supposed to do now?
You're the one
who betrayed them.
They believed in you.
They followed you.
But you took their wills
away and made them pawns.
You have no right to complain
after what you did!
[DEIN] Why are you
getting mad at me?
Wait.
You're pretending that you're
a noble hero again, aren't you?
I allowed my old friends
to make themselves useful.
They should thank me.
Yeah.
Keep telling yourself that.
Try to pretend you
didn't abandon them.
I had no choice.
I didn't plan it
this way either.
Blame Carnis.
That oaf is the one who
turned on his own partner.
Don't look at me like that.
Imagine you had to choose
between your life
and your friendships.
If you were forced
to pick one or the other,
I'm sure you'd make the same
decision that I did!
[FLUM] I'm not like you.
There's no way
I'd ever sacrifice
the people I hold dear to me.
How can you cling
to such idealistic nonsense?
Did you forget your friend
sold you into slavery?
You're this close to ending up
exactly like me!
[melancholic music]
[FLUM] You're seriously trying
to get me to take pity on you?
To coddle you?
Disgusting.
Disgusting?
Forgive me.
[NARRATOR]
Dein had lost everything--
his power, his fame,
his friends,
his place in the world.
All he had left
was a fragile ego
and his obsession with Flum.
And now, even that ego
was in tatters.
No, no.
What drove me, what
made me do this was--
[VOICES]
You want to do this.
No.
Please, stay out of my head!
Stop-- get it under control.
[VOICES]
You want to do this.
What's the next?
You want want to be this.
[FLUM] What's going on?
I will kill you.
[melancholic music]
Flum,
if only you hadn't shown up,
my dream would--
Dein said he had
a core inside of him.
If that's so, he can die.
I will end this!
Reversal!
[melancholic music]
[shrieking]
So much misery.
How many people did you
sacrifice for your dream?
Wallow in regret as you die.
[theme music]