[insects chirping softly]
[metal door rattling]
[cat meows]
[snaps fingers]
["Tole Galva"
by Jkevlar, Tency & Titis playing]
[upbeat rap song continues]
[song fades]
Let's get out of here.
- It's a bust.
- Come on, that's nothing. We got this.
You have no idea what's even in there.
Drop it.
I'll tell you what's there.
Full tank of gas.
And that fancy-ass buggy
for your son, bro.
You ain't fed up carrying him around
in that baby sling?
He ain't a bag of potatoes!
There's nothing.
You check the old boxes?
[man on intercom] Hey,
you fucking masked assholes!
Get out of here!
- Let's go!
- Hell no! We still got five minutes.
[man] You steal from Milord, you're dead.
"Milord"?
[expectant music playing]
Fuck you, Milord!
BEREKYA GROCERY
[man] You see?
The bastards took everything!
That's why I can't pay you.
How much?
I don't know, around 2K and some product.
2K, some product,
locked up with only a bike lock?
It's not that--
Fuck you, Milord!
I'll give you two more weeks,
but with interest.
Milord?
I need a refill.
[man] What should we do
about your brother?
It's happened a few times now.
If we let him slide, we lose credibility.
We're not letting him slide,
but I gotta be sure.
[darkly intriguing music playing]
[sighs] Fuck.
[darkly intriguing music continues]
[women chatting and laughing]
[drone buzzing]
The hell is that?
[upbeat music playing in background]
[upbeat music playing loudly]
Hey!
- [man 1] Hooray!
- [man 2] Happy birthday!
[woman 1] Happy birthday, Kiki!
[man 3] Happy birthday, dawg!
- [woman 2] Here he is! Birthday boy!
- [man 4] Yo, man! Come get a drink!
- [man 5] Happy birthday, my man.
- [woman 3] Happy birthday!
Looking cool.
What up, Fatso? Like your present?
- What, the drone?
- Hell yeah, dawg!
Hey, Marvin's got something to show you.
[woman] Hey! Happy birthday,
my favorite little brother!
So the big day is finally here. [laughing]
Happy birthday, bro.
You're late. Where were you?
[Kylian] Uh, I got detention.
Even on your birthday, you got detention?
Damn history teacher hates my guts.
- Have a seat.
- [upbeat music continues]
How old are you?
Sixteen.
[Marvin] Sixteen!
You know what that means?
[Marvin] It's a lotus flower.
It symbolizes purity.
All things good.
The Lafleur family ring.
[emotional music playing]
So, anyway, it's open bar tonight.
Go get something.
And bring the champagne!
King, can I talk to you a minute?
Let's go.
Where'd you get the drone?
I pulled in favors.
The party was also favors?
Man, what's with the questions?
Tell me it was legit.
Yeah?
When it's for the family,
everything's legit.
Don't mean it's not insane.
Come on, bruh!
It's your birthday, chill out a bit.
Just because you're
on that purity ring bullshit
don't mean you get to jerk me around.
Go have fun, man.
Yo! So I lost
a bet to my brother, Kingsley.
So I've got for you a bit of freestyle.
Since I'm embarrassing myself already,
might as well embarrass my brother too.
Chain reaction.
Go take it out on King, he's expecting it.
Lafleur is the flame.
[upbeat rap song playing]
♪ First verse
Things about to pop off ♪
♪ Open your ears wide
I dedicate these lines to you ♪
♪ It comes from the heart
Big love for you ♪
♪ Long life to you
You're on my radar ♪
♪ Bound by blood
This life, there are no coincidences ♪
[freestyling continues in background]
IT WAS KING
IT WAS KING. DO IT AT DAWN. NO HOSPITAL.
[all] ♪ Lafleur is the flame ♪
[all] ♪ Siblings are in the soul ♪
♪ Lafleur is the flame
All bound by the heart ♪
[all] ♪ Ain't no stopping it
[freestyling continues]
- [freestyling fades into background]
- [emotional music playing]
[man] King. King.
- [Kingsley groans]
- There's a guy here for you.
Yo.
- I'm hearing you got some party favors.
- [sighs]
The time for fun is over, brother.
Go home, okay?
I have a bud who wants seven bills
worth of dope, it's easy money.
Where is he?
Down below.
Bring me to him.
This your guy?
So dope goes for--
Ahh! The fuck your problem?
[grunts]
That's from Milord.
- ["Yo pa Méchan" by Shannon playing]
- [groaning]
[song continues in background]
Annabelle's still not answering her phone.
That girl's gonna be the death of me.
We'll have to make a cake.
I mean, I guess so.
Mama!
I made some plum juice for Ms. Janine.
[Mama] That's great.
I brought in your groceries.
Fantastic.
Nolan?
Nothing.
The toilets.
Marvin gave me this.
[song fading]
Whoa, is this real?
A Glock 19.
This is Mama's, isn't it?
You've lost your goddamn mind!
Put it away.
If Mama catches you, you're in deep shit.
How come Mama keeps a gun anyway?
To protect us from Dad, idiot.
- [Kingsley] Hey, you good?
- [Nolan] Kingsley! Yay!
- [Marvin] Doing well, boys?
- [Nolan] Did you bring me any candy?
- [Kingsley] Of course, sticky hands.
- [woman] Hi, Marvin.
Let's go.
I'm home!
- How are you?
- Mmm-hmm.
- [Marvin] Hey, Mama.
- Hi, sweetie.
I fixed up my friend's motorcycle.
Two hours plus travel, the tools.
- You know.
- And your busted face, that's bonus pay?
'Course not.
Pfft. You know these guys.
They're jealous, that's all.
Ow!
Mama! Let me go!
I already told you I don't want you
showin' up looking like this.
- What did you do this time, Kingsley?
- Nothing, Mama.
I'm not lying.
Ahh.
Cassandra, go make
a healing balm for your brother.
[kids laughing]
[pensive music playing]
What up?
Hey.
Gave some math lessons.
Come here, my boy.
Happy birthday, my darling child.
You like it?
Is it the right size?
You know the significance of the lotus?
Sure I've got the right flower?
We're all sure.
It's you.
Kingsley here yet?
He is. With the kids.
Boom! Heard a loud crack!
- [kids laughing]
- Then I showed him.
I kicked him right in the knee.
Bam! Another crack!
All his bones were snapping.
I kept going, though.
Crack! I broke some legs, broke some arms.
Even punched him in the throat.
And another crack! Right in the jaw!
- Crack!
- [kids] Crack!
- In the chin!
Gave everything I got.
Hey, what's up, bro?
Who did that?
Ah, forget it.
Just be glad you didn't see their faces.
[laughing]
Appreciate you caring, man.
Then I went straight for his head!
- Crack!
- [all] Crack!
Kylian was always an extra talented boy.
He will go far,
because he is serious, honest, and tough.
He just floats above everyone else.
Just like the lotus flower on murky water.
Follow his example, kids, you hear?
Not Mr. Cock of the Walk over there.
In any case,
where'd you get this cash, King?
- I mean--
- [scoffs] Well, I already told you.
- Whoa, what are you doing?
- Hang on, Mama.
- Knock it off, for real!
- You can't burn up all his money!
Over my dead body
are we eating with drug money.
No, no, no, Mama, I swear.
It's not from drugs, I swear to you.
Anyone here uses drug money,
you're through.
Remember that?
[door creaking open]
[Mama] Annabelle?
This is when you get in?
You might as well
not have come home at all.
Sorry.
That's it?
Come on, Mama.
We were out late last night.
So were they, but they all made it.
Hey, so where's the cake?
[laughs]
Good thing we weren't waiting up for it.
As a mother, you give life to your kids,
and even then they take more and more yet.
What ingrates.
[chuckles softly]
Should've quit
at just two or three ingrates.
- It's overflowing in here.
- [Mama] Mmm-mmm.
This family sitting here?
Ain't nothing in the world
more beautiful than that.
Grab each other's hands.
- [all complaining]
- Take each others hands, now!
[Kingsley] Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[gentle music playing]
Do you all feel that?
Going through your arms.
Through your body.
You feel that heat?
Your cheeks warming up.
You feel it?
That's the life force.
Ow, stop squeezing me.
It's the life force.
As long as it circulates…
we will be strong.
We'll be protected.
We'll be together, united.
United by this force within us.
That's a Lafleur.
Amen.
[all] Amen.
[rain pattering loudly]
[pot clinking softly]
Annabelle? What are you doing?
Nothing, I have a headache.
Are you kidding me?
You think I wouldn't notice
the smell of arada?
You'll vomit all night long.
You'll just make yourself sick,
but it won't stop anything, you got that?
At some point,
you're gonna have to bite the bullet
and take the damn morning-after pill.
That's something we don't mess with.
You know, you're being harsh.
I'm worried.
You're going down the wrong path.
What do you mean?
It means you have a lot of problems
and you're counting on me
to fix them for you.
But you're my problem.
You make things worse.
I'd be much better if you let me be.
- I'm going to work.
- [somber music playing]
- [objects clatter]
- [car honking]
- [brakes screeching]
- [loud crash]
[somber music continues]
[phone ringing]
[teacher] No? Okay.
Well, don't forget that next week
we're having a test
on modal auxiliary verbs.
I want all of you to succeed.
- Okay? Yes?
- [knock on door]
[somber music building]
- [somber music continues]
- [crying]
[somber music fading]
[knock on door]
- What are you doing?
- Talking.
About what?
Can we come in?
Go to your rooms and wait.
Where's Mama?
Go to your rooms.
- We're hungry.
- We'll eat soon.
[sighs heavily]
Gotta tell them.
Who?
King.
You do it.
- Any of you got some weed?
- [Annabelle] Yeah.
- Want me to tell you a story?
- [kids] Yeah!
And Dark?
We gotta tell Dark.
[Kingsley] All right, guys.
The story I'm gonna tell you all today
is about something not fun.
It's… the story of life.
When life gets bad.
[line ringing]
[on voicemail] You've reached Nathanaël.
Leave a message and shut up already.
- [voicemail beeps]
- Call me back, yeah?
[knock on door]
[mournful music playing]
[mournful music swells and fades]
[man] We've got room at home for the kids,
you know.
That's why we came.
It'd be good for them to be spoiled a bit.
Don't worry. We got this.
It's too much for you alone.
After that allowance check.
[woman] You'll have to kill me
before they get the kids.
Dark.
[breathes deeply]
You all chose to put her there?
We didn't have a choice, bro.
Just be happy she has a spot.
So Mama would rather join the dead
than forgive the living.
No way. I'm not forgiven.
[spits]
[woman] Would you like to come
back to the house for a bite to eat?
[indistinct chatter]
We'll bring them straight home.
It's okay, Auntie.
We're fine with the bus.
No biggie.
Let's go.
You won't be able
to take care of them on your own.
Marvin, children need stability.
- Hey! We're fine with the bus, we said.
- It's better if they're with us.
Give us a few days, all right?
That one's a real witch.
Let's go.
Come on.
Find me a dock worker.
Seriously?
We're moving to phase three.
[intriguing music playing]
Are you Milord? Thought you'd be older.
Are you Jean-Claude?
Just call me JC, man.
JC. That's fine.
Okay.
The basic rundown.
I know who you sell to,
and who sells to you.
I can see…
you ain't got no chains, no jewelry.
Dressed casual.
Incognito mode.
That's good.
That's how I roll.
And you?
What's your deal?
Nobody above and nobody underneath.
Like Putin.
[chuckles]
Still got a long way to go, buddy.
Phase one.
Sell locally. I got it.
Phase two.
Homemade goods traded all over France.
Mules and shit.
That's for them idiots
who wanna get caught.
Phase three. Exports on a larger scale.
That's what I'm after.
Okay. You're ambitious.
Top-notch reputation, but you need more.
From this point on…
I've got my eyes on you.
Nothing gets past me.
I've got eyes, in town, in the city.
You won't be able to fart
without me knowing what you ate.
Got it?
Not a peep about you.
Not from the cops, or your little buddies.
I'm not about risks,
so you better stay invisible.
Milord is invisible.
Knock off the nickname.
I want your real name.
Unlock your phone and give it to me.
What is it?
My family has got nothing to do with this.
What, you think we gonna torture them?
No one gets in bed with an alias.
["BB Compte (feat. Akiyo)"
by Meryl playing]
Uh, 230 for water.
We got one month to settle it.
We're two months behind
on the scooter's insurance.
- [Marvin] How much is that?
- Uh, 55 euros.
[clicks tongue] Damn.
That's the third late notice.
They've reduced our power.
I turned on the microwave
to reheat the muffins from yesterday.
[sighs]
[Marvin] We've got just enough
to keep the fridge on.
How much do we owe?
Mmm, 314, including the late fees.
And the home insurance is 102.89.
And the groceries too.
Mama was paying for all this?
How'd she manage?
She had her stand.
As well as the services, the allowance…
You know what the last thing
I said to her was? "Let me be."
"I'd be better off if you'd let me be."
[crying]
[darkly intriguing music playing]
- We can't make it without Auntie.
- [woman] Oh hell no.
Auntie? No way.
What do you propose?
Well, um, Cassandra
could run the stand on the weekends.
I'll go back to work at Burger King.
And how do much you make?
- 1,600?
- Yeah, barely.
What about me? What should I do?
Annabelle, you gotta get your diploma.
No way you're dropping out again, come on.
Okay.
And you, Kiki?
What do you suggest?
Uh, I have no idea.
I can do some tutoring after school.
With these numbers,
without Auntie, it's impossible.
Okay, stop, stop.
You're giving me a headache.
No one's gonna pay,
not Belle, nor you, Marvin.
I'll tell you what we're gonna do.
We won't end up on the streets
if we know how to work 'em.
What does that mean?
Let me deal with it.
- Do you trust me?
- No.
- The street won't put food on the table.
- It will more than potted plants, Marvin.
King, you've lost it. For real, though.
Mama didn't want us touching that shit.
- So don't touch it.
- Drugs isn't how this family does things.
And having a dead Mom is?
You got a better idea? I'm all ears.
Till then, I'm an adult.
I can do what I want.
Are we gonna live with Auntie?
[Kingsley] No. Go to sleep.
[gentle music playing]
- ["Bien sûr" by Jkevlar playing]
- Okay! The beast is loose!
Okay!
El SherKhan, rolling up!
Yo! How are you, man?
- You all good, bro?
- Yeah, dawg. All good.
You know it.
You know it, son.
Look at you, all thinned out.
- 'Sup, dawg?
- Damn.
Yeah, you got skinny.
I leaned out.
I'm built for speed like a cheetah.
[laughing] Yo, is that some new bling too?
- Asked for gold, but they ain't have any.
- [man laughing]
- Here, cousin.
- Hell yeah, my cousin. You get it.
[man] You'll see, we went all out.
[man] Damn, bro. It's good to see you.
For real, son. We gonna party.
- [SherKhan] Damn straight.
- [man] Let's go, guy.
- [rap song continues]
- [indistinct background chatter]
Ooh, this is bad!
Welcome back, dude.
- Gotta show respect.
- So business is moving up, huh?
Damn straight, it's all going great.
We get shit done.
Hell yeah, seems like it.
Damn good. It's going great without me.
Just doing our best.
Your best is a lot, Vince.
That's what I like about you.
Champagne.
Hell yeah, the cousin's out! Hell yeah.
- [bottle thuds]
- [Vincez] Oh!
- [bottle thudding]
- Ahh! Stop!
[groaning]
You really thought you could
skim off my business and not get caught?
SherKhan, stop, man.
Vincez wanted to surprise you.
He kept it all, look.
[woman] You're late.
Yeah, I know, sorry.
But look what I picked up.
Smells burnt, though.
What's wrong, sweetheart?
Look at her feet.
Look at this. Thaïs has been wearing shoes
that don't fit her for weeks now.
She didn't tell us, no one noticed.
And that's nothing compared
to everything Mama did for us.
Have you guys looked in--
The only ones that don't have holes
are Marvin's old SpongeBob socks,
but she won't wear them.
Go to sleep, princess.
Be right there.
We can't make it like this, King.
We won't manage.
Cassandra and I gotta stay up all night
to finish our homework.
I know it's a lot. We are in deep shit.
But we're gonna get out of it, hmm?
I know what to do.
I know how to make us money.
I swear to you.
FOR SALE
CALLING MARV
Yo, why did you do that?
The drone doesn't belong to you, dude.
Show some respect, man!
Kiki asked me to sell it.
- It'll pay the electricity bill.
- [clicks tongue]
- [Vincez] Yo, is King here?
- Yeah, over there.
Okay, thanks.
Yo. I'm sorry about your mother.
Mine used to buy herbs from her.
Looking for your next play?
Who did that?
My cousin.
SherKhan, man. [clicks tongue]
He'll have to pay and he's good for it.
Mmm-hmm.
What's the plan?
I know where he hides his dope at.
[expectant music playing softly]
No.
[Kingsley] You won't have to do anything.
Just drop me off, I do my thing.
It'll take ten minutes, tops,
and we're flush.
No!
[sighs] You don't want to help me,
for real?
No, I don't want to help you. No.
You're gonna fuck shit up.
You'll fuck it up for all of us.
Man, this is-- [clicks tongue]
Whatever, man. It's fine.
- Marv said you were up to something.
- You in?
- Robbing someone again?
- What do you mean? I didn't rob no one.
Don't worry 'bout it.
This Milord is gonna
have to watch his back.
I'mma show him what's what.
But forget that.
You're making enemies, bro.
So what?
Well, those enemies
could go after the family.
That's beside the point.
I need to know if I can count on you.
No. I'm sorry, it's a bad idea.
Man, where do you get off
judging my ideas?
[clicks tongue]
Voice of purity over here. God damn.
JC
YOUR BROTHER KINGSLEY…
YOUR BROTHER KINGSLEY WORRIES ME.
YOU'RE RESPONSIBLE FOR HIM.
[sighs and clicks tongue]
[dog barking faintly]
[commentator on TV] So much excitement
happening here tonight.
And another missed goal by Martinique.
The fans are not happy.
[TV continues indistinctly in background]
Hey.
See that bar over there?
Keep an eye out, okay?
You see him come out of that bar,
and walk down this way,
call me immediately, okay?
So how will we know which one?
He's got two big chains
and a monitor around his ankle.
You'll see it.
So if we see him walk by us,
we'll call you?
Yep.
He won't be out for a minute.
There's a game on.
In 20 minutes, I'll message you,
tell you it's over, and you can peace out.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
- All right, kids.
You got this.
Don't do anything dumb.
King?
Hmm? Yeah?
If he sees us?
Well, so what if he sees you?
Just a girl and some kids, that's all.
Whatcha think he's gonna do?
Just don't look him in the eye.
And tell them not to look at him either.
Okay.
[suspenseful music playing]
[commentator on TV] They've withstood
the Lillois offense.
Though poor Martinique
is still trailing three-zero.
In the second half of the French Cup final
and it's been an ordeal for them.
The Docks are
monopolizing the ball yet again.
Lille, on the attack,
are they gonna score another goal?
It doesn't look like Martinique
has what it takes today.
- Oh! And Lille scores!
- Come on, ref! What you doing?
Bringing their total to four
against Martinique's zero.
At this point, any chance of Martinique…
[suspenseful music playing]
[Kingsley] It's me.
- Who's this?
- It's my brother.
Okay.
- Got eyes on my cousin?
- Of course, son.
Come on, where is it? We've gotta go.
Over there.
[commentator continues] Fans are growing
increasingly frustrated
with this embarrassing performance.
Can Lille bring their goal count to five
before halftime?
Lille was on fire tonight…
- [men grumbling]
- They're playing like bitch-ass amateurs.
Fans are surely baffled
with Martinique's pitiful playing tonight.
We can see fights breaking out.
Look at this.
You bring your family…
Hey.
[suspenseful music continues]
He's got a chain.
He's getting closer.
Sick of this damn team!
Doesn't have a monitor.
[indistinct chatter]
Okay. Keep looking. Next.
[man in background] I gotta decompress.
I can't sit and watch a game like that.
[suspenseful music continues]
How many are there?
[commentator] Martinique
regains possession of the ball.
Maybe they're starting to wake back up.
We can certainly see panic is setting in…
- [fans clamoring]
- No, they're finished. It's stupid.
Not yet. One half still left.
Even with four half-times,
there's still no way they'll make it up.
[clicks tongue] Come on, man.
[commentator]
…at this point will not happen.
There's no way
they're gonna be able to come back…
[suspenseful music continues]
Is that him?
Could be.
Don't look at him.
I'm peacing out, dawg. This is bullshit.
[man] Where you going?
To Bel'hair. Damn messed-up my night.
[suspenseful music continues]
- That's all.
- More than I expected.
Leo, go look under the seat,
should be bigger bags in there.
Well?
Yeah.
[suspenseful music continues]
Yo, help me.
- Pick up, King.
- [line ringing]
Normally when you invite a girl over,
you gotta leave the door open, right?
- You want it open?
- [girl laughs]
No, I'm kidding.
[laughs] You wanna be Tony Montana?
No. He's a loser.
I'm sorry? How come?
Because he always made bad choices.
He's a show-off, he's impulsive.
Why have a poster of him then?
A reminder to not end up like him.
[suspenseful music continues]
Can't carry all these on a scooter.
You got a car here?
[clicks tongue] Seriously,
ain't you prepared at all, dude? [sighs]
Damn it.
- [line ringing]
- [Ambre] Hello?
- Ambre?
- Yeah.
We're in deep shit.
Kylian, gotta talk to you.
Kingsley's about to do something stupid.
He took the stash
of some guy named SherKhan,
and that guy's on his way back.
- SherKhan?
- You know him?
I've heard the name before.
Well, he's about to get his ass busted.
- And Marvin?
- Can't reach him. Kingsley, neither.
Fine.
Go back to your room, I'll call Fatso.
His brother's connected.
It could help out.
That's the most I can do.
God damn.
[suspenseful music continues]
Oh, come on.
Damn, you got any tape or shit?
Man, for real,
you guys are pissing me off! [exhales]
- [suspenseful music continues]
- [phone vibrating]
Yeah, baby, what's going on?
- There's someone here.
- What? Who?
I don't know, they're in the living room.
I can hear them.
- Hmm?
- I locked myself in the bedroom.
Damn it, what do I do?
Who are these guys?
Tell 'em I'm coming! Tell 'em!
Yo, some guys are at Coco's!
My man is coming!
Yeah, SherKhan is coming!
He finds you here, he'll kill you!
- [man] He's coming now?
- Right now! And he's gonna kill you!
You sure?
Oh, you will find out
soon enough, assholes!
[suspenseful music continues]
CALL FROM SK
- It's my cousin.
- Let us out.
[SherKhan] Go to Bel'hair!
- Huh?
- Go to the salon! Now!
Right now?
Yeah, I was gonna go, but I can't.
You go, tell me if everything's okay.
I'll be there in 20.
- Yeah, sure, but is there a reason?
- Just go! God damn!
Come on, open it.
He wants me to check out the salon.
Something's off.
And so what? Let us out!
What are you doing?
You gonna let us out?
[clicks tongue]
Hey, get off me!
- [dramatic music playing]
- Look at you!
- Give me the key!
- Get off!
- Get off! Get off me, asshole!
- [dramatic music continues]
[both grunting]
Ahh!
- [groaning]
- [dramatic music continues]
- [slicing]
- [groaning]
[gun fires]
[both groaning]
- [music fading]
- [Vincez groaning and whimpering]
[door rattling]
[Vincez groaning]
- Let's go, let's go.
- [groaning continues]
[gun clatters]
[Thaïs] That was so cool.
I hope we do it again soon.
Annabelle?
Let's tell Kingsley,
so he'll use us again.
Annabelle?
We're really tough!
["Bienvenue aux antilles"
by Jozii playing on headphones]
continues playing]
YOUR BROTHER KINGSLEY WORRIES ME.
YOU'RE RESPONSIBLE FOR HIM.
IN MEMORY OF LIONEL LEPAGE
["Bienvenue aux antilles"
by Jozii continues playing]