(Lee Jae In, Kim Woo Seok, Choi Ye Bin)
(Cha Woo Min, An Ji Ho, Jung So Ri)
(Scriptwriter: Kang Min Ji)
(Director: Im Dae Woong)
(Night Has Come)
(All people, organizations, locations, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
Get your phones!
It's not mine.
Na Hee!
I found it!
- Are you okay? - Yes.
- Do you have your phone? - No.
- What about you? - Not yet.
Are you okay?
Where is it? Darn it.
What now?
Get your phone.
- What about you? - I got mine.
Let's hurry up and find hers.
For breaking the rules,
Oh Hye Seung will be executed.
Oh Hye Seung was a Citizen.
(Participants must vote and identify the Mafia.)
(Vote now.)
For breaking the rules,
Kang Ye Won will be executed.
(Welcome to Muryeong Retreat Center)
Kang Ye Won was...
- a Mafia. - Guys, hurry!
You must vote. Vote or you die!
Who should we vote to kill?
Who?
For breaking the rules,
Lee Hyun Jun and Park Jung Eun will be executed.
Lee Hyun Jun and Park Jung Eun were Citizens.
I found it!
- You got it? - Yes.
Vote for Myung Soo now. I'll keep looking.
What?
- Screw it. - I got it.
Hyun Ho!
Your phone.
- Give it to me. - Get lost, punk.
Darn you!
The scumbag.
For breaking the rules, Kim Yeon Ju will be executed.
Kim Yeon Ju was a Citizen.
(Will you vote for Baek Eun Ha?)
Kim So Mi voted for Baek Eun Ha.
Baek Eun Ha?
Baek Eun Ha voted for Kim So Mi.
Park Woo Ram voted for...
- Baek Eun Ha. - Darn it. Why?
Choi Mi Na voted for Baek Eun Ha.
- No, I didn't. - Shin Seung Bin...
voted for Baek Eun Ha.
- Kim Jin Ha... - I didn't.
Ahn Na Hee voted for Baek Eun Ha.
Hyun Ho!
Hyun Ho, I'll do it.
Jun Hee, your phone. Vote fast.
Hurry.
What about the others?
We must find Yoon Seo's too.
I'll look so you just vote already!
Cha Yu Jun voted for Baek Eun Ha.
You must vote fast.
There's no time.
It's Baek Eun Ha. Don't vote and we die.
If we vote for her too, she'll die.
What else do you want to do?
We'll scatter the votes.
So we all get one vote.
Vote for each other.
Kim Jun Hee.
We'll vote for each other, okay?
- Jin Da Bum... - Be quick.
voted for...
- Oh Jung Won. - Oh Jung Won...
voted for Jin Da Bum.
Lee Yoon Seo voted for...
- Kim Jun Hee. - Kim Jun Hee...
voted for Lee Yoon Seo.
Im Eun Chan voted for...
- Nam Yeon Woo. - Nam Yeon Woo...
voted for Im Eun Chan.
For breaking the rules,
- Jang Hyun Ho will be executed. - Hurry up.
Hyun Ho!
Jang Hyun Ho was a Citizen.
(Welcome to Muryeong Retreat Center)
Voting is over.
With ten votes, Baek Eun Ha...
got the most, and she will be executed.
Baek Eun Ha was a Citizen.
I said I was a Citizen.
I said it wasn't me!
I said it wasn't me.
Why vote for me?
Why?
Why me?
(Assembly Hall)
Night has come.
Ju Young.
Ju...
Hey.
Ju Young.
Lee Ju Young.
- What is it? - Ju Young's weird.
Why?
During the night, Lee Ju Young...
was executed by Mafia.
Lee Ju Young...
- was a Citizen. - Ju Young.
Before the last vote closed,
the Doctor nominated who to Heal.
They nominated Cha Yu Jun.
I don't know.
- Morning has come. - Ju Young.
All participants, identify the Mafia...
and begin to vote.
I think she was strangled with this.
I said I wouldn't hand in my phone.
I said I didn't want to!
If we hadn't turned in our phones, we wouldn't have slept here.
And they wouldn't have died.
You killed them all, Jun Hee.
- It's on you! - Stop it.
If only we'd voted sooner.
Then they wouldn't have died.
They're not wrong.
We survived by pure luck.
You and Ko Kyung Jun, what'll you do about it now?
Did I suggest we hand them in?
Kim Jun Hee you scumbag,
you said we just had to give up our phones!
This happened because of you.
It's on you.
I'm sorry.
The game must take place within the boundaries.
Whatever.
The class president got us into this.
Let's vote for him today.
You said it was a good idea...
and took everyone's phones.
Why change your tune now?
You looked pretty relaxed last night.
Why did you take your phone in secret?
You're the most suspicious here.
Hey.
Isn't it obvious?
How are we to trust Jun Hee?
He could be Mafia.
(Jin Da Bum)
Guys!
Our lives depend on this game.
Why entrust someone else with mine?
I just used my brain.
If not,
I could've died.
Hey.
Stop it.
Please.
Do you want to fight in this situation?
How long must we fight over a game that kills?
Won't you go home?
How can we go home?
We can't leave.
The Mafia Game.
If we figure out...
who started it and why,
we can find a way out.
Then we can all get out without anyone else dying.
We'll figure out a way later.
Let's move the others.
Move what?
We can't leave them like this.
We must move them to the freezer.
Hey, Ko Kyung Jun.
Let go, psycho.
Don't leave.
Stay and help.
If we do it, we do it together.
You're being cheap...
and sneaking away again?
What did you say?
I shouldn't have collected the phones.
It wasn't your fault.
We didn't know about that rule.
No.
It's all my fault.
Kim Jun Hee.
Until the game's actually over, people will keep dying.
If you really want to be responsible,
think of how to find a way to get everyone out safe.
Okay?
Okay.
(Frozen hairtail)
(Main Menu)
Yoon Seo.
- Yoon Seo. - Yoon Seo.
What's wrong?
Yoon Seo.
Are you okay?
Hey.
- Breathe. - Are you okay?
Breathe, Yoon Seo.
Go on. Slowly.
It's okay.
Are you all right?
Yoon Seo.
(Lee Yoon Seo)
Are you okay?
What happened?
You don't remember.
You passed out.
I was so scared.
I'm fine.
Let me wrap the bandage for you.
Why do they have to die?
Na Hee.
Hyun Ho was trying to help me.
Why do we have to suffer like this?
Let's not drag this out. Just turn yourself in.
If you're Mafia, tell me.
Do you think they will if it were you?
Darn it.
Okay. Let me try again.
"This jerk is 100 percent Mafia." Anyone who thinks like this?
Reveal yourself if you're Police then.
Police!
Are you not going to reveal yourself?
I don't think they would do it either.
They won't.
Why the heck won't you cooperate?
Hey, Class President.
It's you, isn't it?
Only Citizens died because you didn't allow us to vote.
It was the Mafias' plan to kill all the Citizens, right?
What are you talking about?
Did you not read the notice?
It wasn't just Citizens. A Mafia died too.
At least, we can be almost sure about who the Doctors are.
It's not me.
It's not me either.
It's you two.
Who would save Yu Jun other than you guys?
I don't know why the Doctor saved me either.
But it's really not me.
(Baek Eun Ha: 10 votes, Im Eun Chan: 1 vote,)
(Oh Jung Won: 1 vote, Jin Da Bum: 1 vote)
Hey, So Mi.
Eun Ha said you were a Mafia yesterday.
Did you pick her because she caught you?
Hey, I...
I voted for her because she was going to vote for me first.
What about you? You're a Mafia, aren't you?
What? I'm not.
Ju Young...
and you had a big argument yesterday.
We had an argument,
but why would I kill her because of it?
You lick her boots in front of her as if you're her maid,
but you badmouth her that she's a jerk behind her back.
I guess you wanted to kill her.
No.
No wonder.
Ju Young did treat Min Ha like a maid.
That's really not true!
Darn it, you talk so much.
Turn yourself in, or you'll see blood.
Kyung Jun.
Why did you do that?
What the heck are you talking about?
Why were you hiding your phone yesterday?
You knew they would die if we don't vote.
You didn't tell us on purpose so that they all die, right?
I told you.
How can we trust that punk?
If you didn't believe it, why did you force us to do it?
It's you who killed Ju Young, you punk.
Do you think I don't know that?
What?
You told her how you felt about her, but she rejected you.
And it got spread on the Internet only for you to get bashed.
- I was just joking. - Don't try to fool me, idiot.
You kneeled and begged her...
to delete the post.
Everyone here knows that.
Mi Na. You say it.
You took the video.
Yes.
It has nothing to do with this.
It has everything to do with this because you're a darn Mafia!
You talked behind her back and called her a fox.
You killed Ju Won first because it would've been obvious...
if you had killed Ju Young first, didn't you?
No.
How can I be a Mafia? It's you.
Screw it.
Darn it.
Ko Kyung Jun voted for Park Woo Ram.
(Ko Kyung Jun voted for Park Woo Ram.)
No, I'm not. Don't vote for me.
I can tell from his eyes. He's 100 percent Mafia.
Hey.
(Will you vote for Park Woo Ram?)
(Shin Seung Bin voted for Park Woo Ram.)
Shin Seung Bin and Kim Jin Ha...
voted for Park Woo Ram.
You jerks.
Hey.
You punks should vote for him too.
Mi Na.
He holds so many grudges against you too.
Since Ju Young is dead, it's your turn.
Hey.
Kyung Jun.
Get out of my way.
How dare that piece of trash try to kill me?
But...
they won't switch the target and accuse us, will they?
What are you talking about?
There are 15 of us.
The three of us voted for Woo Ram,
but there are a lot more people who didn't vote yet.
Darn it. Should we get some insurance?
Where are you going?
Hey.
Guys.
Where are you guys going?
Hey.
Hold on.
We should talk before you go.
We can meet again after a break.
What?
(Will you vote for Park Woo Ram?)
Choi Mi Na voted for Park Woo Ram.
Mi Na.
Why did you do that?
Why?
Come to think of it, Kyung Jun has a point.
I knew it.
I had a bad feeling when I saw his eyes looking at Ju Young yesterday.
- What? - This crazy witch.
Woo Ram.
Don't. I'll persuade them.
Aren't you hungry?
Ji Soo.
(Room 302)
You're not really a Doctor, are you?
Because I'm not.
I know. I believe you.
- But who on earth... - I'm really not.
- Please trust me. - Yu Jun.
I'm so confused right now.
What's going on?
What happened?
I fell prey to Kyung Jun's plot.
I shouldn't have let them vote.
Do you think they would've listened if you had stopped them?
Instead of talking here,
don't we have to go...
and tell the other guys to vote for someone else?
Who should we ask them to vote for?
How would I know?
Anyway,
it'll be fine as long as it's not us.
If we only know who the Mafias are.
(Swimming Pool Cafeteria)
If you don't vote for Woo Ram,
do you think those punks will save you?
They will do anything to save themselves.
Understand?
Everyone voted for Eun Ha.
Woo Ram and So Mi are behind it.
You should get revenge.
We should team up.
You can use the cafeteria too. How nice is that?
Right?
Woo Ram has to be a Mafia.
He got all worked up because he has so many dirty secrets.
Eat.
Hurry up and eat it. The noodles will get soggy.
(Im Eun Chan, Nam Yeon Woo, and Jin Da Bum voted for Park Woo Ram.)
What's this?
- Why did they do this? - These jerks...
How can they do this to me?
Right.
Ji Soo and Yu Jun are on our side.
It'll be fine. Don't worry.
I'll find a way.
Okay?
A way?
Screw it.
I have no choice.
It's me or Kyung Jun.
It will not end before one of us dies.
Don't you think so?
Let's do the same thing he does.
Let's vote for Kyung Jun.
What?
He always bullies others.
That scumbag deserves to die.
That jerk...
will do anything to survive.
Yes. Let's say he kills me today.
What will happen tomorrow then?
Who do you think he's going to vote for tomorrow?
It'll be one of you.
Is it me or Kyung Jun?
Make a choice.
Woo Ram is right.
I'll vote for Kyung Jun.
Me too.
I saw what he did today. We should stop him.
I'll vote for him too.
Guys.
If you don't help me, I'll die.
You know it.
Are you going to kill me?
Please.
Please help me.
(Kim Jun Hee voted for Ko Kyung Jun.)
(Kim So Mi voted for Ko Kyung Jun.)
(Park Woo Ram voted for Ko Kyung Jun.)
(Will you vote for Ko Kyung Jun?)
(Park Woo Ram, Lee Yoon Seo, Ahn Na Hee, Kim So Mi,)
(Kim Jun Hee, and Oh Jung Won voted for Ko Kyung Jun.)
Look.
I knew it.
That crazy jerk must have a death wish.
Only Yu Jun and Ji Soo are left, right?
Yes. They should be in their room.
Their room?
You guys aren't feeling well. You should rest.
I'll go with them.
Do you want to go to the infirmary?
It's a little scary here.
Okay.
Do you want to go in?
We don't even know what this is.
That's why I should go.
I'll be back quickly.
Yoon Seo.
Be careful.
I will.
Yoon Seo.
- Yoon Seo. - Are you okay?
(Night Has Come)
(Gwangju Information and Content Agency)
(This content was produced through Gwangju Information and...)
(Content Agency's 2022 OTT Platform Content Production Business.)