LOVE NEXT DOOR
- All right, thank you for waiting.
- My goodness.
I made some doenjang stew with clams,
but I'm not sure how it'll taste.
- It looks so good.
- I feel bad we're always eating for free.
Let's grab a drink later.
Well, you're retired now,
so you should sleep in and relax at home.
From now on, he insists
on cooking at least one meal a day.
He's looking for a way to survive.
Can't you say things in a nicer way?
My wife's been through a lot,
so I should take good care of her now.
Goodness.
Why do men act like they come
to their senses when they get old?
He must be scared you'll leave him behind.
I'm terrified.
Aunt Mi-suk, I'll never do that.
I'm ready to prostrate myself right now.
Hey, that's something
you should do quietly.
You can't fawn like that
in the presence of your mom.
Gosh, forget it.
I'm immune to it now.
My goodness.
I'll peel perilla leaves for you forever.
No need for any debates.
Honey, I can't reach
the greens over there.
Which ones? The bean sprouts? Chamnamul?
- Bireum?
- Chamnamul.
- I see.
- Honey.
- I can't stand it.
- Honey?
- Yeah?
- I want some soy braised beef.
Go ahead. It's right near you.
You're closer than I am.
What are your hands for?
- Is this for me?
- I use them for this.
Do you have hooks for hands?
That hurts so much!
It's supposed to hurt.
You think it's supposed to tickle?
Why can't you use your chopsticks?
Jeez, all that fuss.
Why have you been so busy lately?
We haven't had a date in days.
I mean, I just have too much work.
Can you wait just one more week for me?
One week is too long.
One week's going to feel
like a thousand years for me.
Did you use my razor…
My eyes! Mom, Dad!
They're doing weird stuff in her room!
Hey, Dong-jin. It's not…
It's not weird stuff.
We legitimately have official approval
from both families now, so get lost.
I can't approve of this.
Seung-hyo,
it's not too late to rethink this.
Who are you to decide if we can or can't?
She's totally like Bigfoot.
She keeps stealing my razor.
Have you lost your mind?
I'll kill you!
I'm telling you for your own good.
It wasn't me.
The blades dull as if she has a beard!
- You better shut up.
- I don't care.
What?
I don't care if Seok-ryu
is Bigfoot or an alien.
Choisseung.
I've heard this line before.
That's right.
You must've really enjoyed Coffee Prince!
Seung-hyo, get a grip.
That's a TV show, and this is real life.
Dong-jin, you said your exam
is coming up soon, right?
- Grab something to drink while you study.
- What a waste.
Okay. I'll call you
my brother-in-law from now on.
Sure thing, my brother-in-law.
On second thought, this…
I mean, my sister
isn't that much of a mess.
Even if you put lipstick on a pig,
it doesn't look so bad, you know.
- Get out.
- My razor…
I told you I didn't use it!
But the hair…
I swear it wasn't me.
I swear I didn't use it!
Are you crazy? I said it wasn't me!
Hey, I didn't do it.
THE END
See you tomorrow.
What should we eat?
Mr. Kang.
What brings you here?
Hello, how have you been?
Not great.
You said you'd come back in the summer,
but you didn't show up.
I'm sorry.
I've been busy lately.
I'll reschedule for next month
and definitely come then.
Forget it. You don't have to.
Ms. Jung won't be around by then.
Why won't she be around?
She was assigned to the South Pole.
The research station's…
What was it? Safety officer?
She really wanted to go
and carved out time
to diligently prepare for it.
She achieved her dream in the end.
She's truly amazing.
Dan-ho!
You didn't tell me you were coming.
I wanted to give you a ride home
right when you got off work.
What? I'm so touched.
You must be really tired.
You should go home and get some sleep.
I don't want to.
I'll sleep in your car.
Let's go on a date.
We haven't had a proper date.
What would you like to do?
You weren't joking
about the Wolmido Island amusement rides.
Well, if you don't like this,
how about the pirate ship ride?
I'll stick with this one.
- Let's go.
- No, it's this way.
Okay, let's go.
- Wait.
- We have to line up.
Thank you.
But is this ride actually safe?
I'm worried about my hips,
shoulders, and knees…
Won't my glasses fly off?
Come to think of it,
I've never seen you without glasses.
I'm extremely nearsighted.
Even with glasses on,
my vision isn't good.
Then, you can't see me now?
I can see you, Mo-eum.
No matter how far away you are,
I'll be able to see you.
It's about to start soon.
Hold on tight to the bars.
And…
don't worry.
You'll be safe next to me.
Mo-eum!
- Thank you!
- Thank you.
This duck is mine.
- Are you tired?
- Nope.
My gosh!
What? Seok-ryu and Seung-hyo are together?
Yeah.
What? So you two are becoming in-laws?
Hey, why are you laughing so much?
I think rather than
Seung-hyo and Seok-ryu,
Mi-suk and Hye-suk
were destined to be together.
Gosh, if these two had never met,
their kids would've never gotten together.
Hey, maybe you two were married
to each other in your past lives.
Hey! Why would you say
such an awful thing?
I should be the one saying that.
While we're at it,
we don't need wedding gifts.
No designer bags, diamonds, or cash.
Not even a set of silverware.
As long as the kids are happy,
I don't need anything.
I wasn't going to.
Giving away
my precious daughter is enough.
What are you talking about?
These days, sons are the ones given away.
That's just what they say.
In reality,
daughters-in-law have it worse.
I won't give her trouble, so don't worry.
I won't interfere in their affairs at all.
Same here.
Hey, let's have the wedding next spring.
Maybe mid-May
with nice weather and flowers?
Why? Strike while the iron's hot.
Just do it before the year's end.
That's not enough time to prepare.
It'll be quick with a wedding planner.
Let's hold it at a hotel.
Are you crazy?
Meals at hotels are expensive!
We can't afford that.
How about a small wedding then?
A cozy gathering with those close to us.
We can't do that!
We've given so much money.
We need to receive ours.
You don't want this or that!
What do you want me to do then?
- Let's talk about it!
- Come on!
What are you doing in front of Yeon-du?
- Jeez.
- Seriously.
Yeon-du, make sure
you get along with your friends.
Don't fight like these two, okay?
Okay.
At least there's a lesson in this.
We're actually very close.
We're just talking.
CERTIFIED PERSONAL TRAINER WRITTEN EXAM
Hello.
Are you studying?
My exam is coming up soon.
I see.
Right. I'm thinking of signing up
for personal training sessions.
Who should I ask about that?
Mr. Go, our client wants
a consultation for personal training.
Hello, Na-yun.
- Come this way.
- Okay.
Have you received
personal training before?
Briefly in the past once.
Wait.
Has he always looked like that?
ROOT DINER
NOTICE
NOISE MAY OCCUR DUE TO CONSTRUCTION
WE ASK FOR YOUR UNDERSTANDING
It looks like the next shop
is starting renovations.
Hey, Mo-eum.
I'm outside right now. Why?
What?
Really?
Congratulations, Mo-eum!
What's this?
Are you a peddler or something?
I'm here to celebrate.
You're leaving for the South Pole,
so how could I come empty-handed?
I prepared some things
with a bit of color.
Hey, when did you find out
you were going to the South Pole? Today?
No, last week.
What? Why are you only
telling me this today?
You weren't itching to tell us?
I would've hung a banner
in the street myself.
Look at this. Isn't it so cute?
Should I do that?
Then, Dan-ho would see it too.
I can't bring myself to tell him.
The words just won't come out!
Gosh.
I don't get it.
Even with all this sugar,
why isn't my brain working?
I don't know
where to even start or what to say.
I think I know.
Really?
Hey, can you tell me then?
"Do it with sincerity."
Is this your revenge?
That's what I told you.
Well, you were right.
For big things,
be honest and straightforward.
Tell him it's something
you really want to do,
so wait just one year.
Jeez.
I wonder how he'll feel
after hearing that.
Was this how Seung-hyo felt
when I went to study abroad?
CHOISSEUNG
Go.
What do you mean?
I'm sleeping over.
Jeez, just sleep at your own house.
Why are you sending me away?
I want to comfortably sleep alone
in my own bed.
It's more comfortable if I leave?
Seriously?
Yeah, seriously.
Okay, then.
I'll leave.
But this doesn't count.
To me, this isn't a farewell party.
We'll do this again.
I'll throw a huge feast for you.
- Okay.
- I mean it.
I'll make it more extravagant.
- Just you wait.
- Okay. Just go.
- Got it? This doesn't count.
- I got it.
I'm really going.
Bye.
I love you, Mo-eum.
Please, just go.
Choisseung!
Slow down. You're going to fall.
I wanted to see you a second sooner.
Me too.
Just so I could have more time to see you,
I worked like crazy today.
Hurry and praise me.
You worked so hard. You did great.
Let's go.
Did you have dinner?
No, not yet.
Want to grab some udon on the way home?
I'd love that.
I feel queasy after eating half a cake.
Cake? Why?
Mo-eum was picked for the South Pole.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Wow, Mo-eum really
follows through on what she says.
She's no joke.
As expected, she's so strong-willed.
Jeez, you suddenly told me to come over.
Was it to show off this bracken?
No.
You promised to teach me how to cook.
- You were serious?
- Of course.
Look. I got dressed
to be fully prepared for this.
Look. Do you see?
Well, I don't think this is a real apron.
Did you go
to the department store to buy this?
Yeah.
Come on. Teach me.
- Quickly.
- Wait. Hey.
What?
I will teach you how to cook.
Right.
So teach me something too.
Teach you what?
English.
English? Why all of a sudden?
Well, I don't know when it'll be,
but I want to travel abroad.
I want to try ordering food
and chat with locals in foreign countries.
Okay.
Then, let's be fair
and teach each other.
I'll save on academy fees.
Come here quick.
What should I do? Where do I start?
We need to soak this.
You have to soak
dried bracken a day in advance.
But if you don't have time,
you can boil it in the rice cooker.
I see.
What are you doing? Press the button.
Right. I'll do it. Okay.
Brown rice, nutritional porridge.
- White… Quick cook.
- What? What do I do?
What's happening?
Hey.
You've never used
this rice cooker before?
I just got it recently.
It's totally brand new.
- Hey.
- Hey, that's scary and dangerous!
You're taking forever.
You've had green onions before.
Cut it right down the middle.
Look at me.
I can chop it without looking
or even while looking at you.
Close the book.
We don't need any of this.
Then, how are we going to study?
Let's jump right into action.
Conversation is key in English.
Converse… What?
Conversation and speaking.
Conversation.
It's been so long
I've forgotten all the words.
You're right. I just need to communicate.
Then, what should we talk about first?
Okay. What are you
going to do in the afternoon?
I'm going to go to the supermarket.
Noon… Can you repeat the last part slowly?
No, it's not "the." It's "the."
With a few exceptions,
the definite article
is pronounced as "the" before vowels.
Right. I knew that.
It's been so long I've forgotten it all.
All right, then.
"I'm going to go to the supermarket."
That's easy.
I used to memorize
old comprehension books well.
No, not "super." It's '"super."
Don't twist your tongue like a pretzel.
Just keep it straightforward. "Super."
Super. You can't do it?
I don't want to go anymore.
Our wives are over at your house.
And we're here.
This grouping worked out pretty well.
Let's do this regularly.
I felt like I'd been leeching off of you,
so I brought something.
My goodness!
Wow! It's blinding!
It's brilliant! My gosh!
Wow, this is…
Gosh, the bottle itself looks so fancy.
It screams, "I'm expensive!"
But…
We only have soju and beer glasses here.
We can just use regular cups.
- Hold on.
- Like those ones.
Well, these are
the prettiest cups we have.
All right. And this too.
Isn't that a camera bag?
It's not new.
It's just something I've had.
But it should be easy to use.
Giving two things at once?
That's not fair.
And isn't the camera
way more expensive than this alcohol?
You said you wanted to learn photography.
You can't go into battle without a weapon.
Well, if you put it that way,
thank you very much.
Then, should we…
Wow, that's great!
You must've done this a lot before.
Okay. All right.
I think I'm done.
I think I have a knack for this.
Again!
You need to have it properly leveled.
Look. How about this?
The subject is tilted! Do it again!
Here.
- All set?
- You can't cut it off at the knees.
- What?
- The legs look short! Again!
Okay.
Look at this!
The proportions are all wrong!
Instead of centering it,
put it slightly off to the side.
To make them look tall and slender,
bend down and lower your point of view!
You take pictures like this?
Lower! Get down more!
Think of it like boot camp!
Didn't you serve in the military?
I did! I was a defense serviceman.
Stick to the floor!
Become one with the camera!
- Hey, this is…
- Stick to the floor!
- Please let me go!
- Stop whining!
One, two…
Hi, Mo-eum.
I stopped by before work.
This is a gift for you.
Come on in.
How did you know it was me?
You're the only one who visits us.
- It's a T-shirt.
- Yeah.
I told you I'd get you one.
Am I still not allowed
to wear the mudflat shirt?
Of course not!
You look the best when you wear that.
I don't look bad in other clothes either.
I can't help it.
Mudflat Man is my first love.
My first love was actually Spider-Man.
And then, there's Iron Man, Hulk,
Thor, and Captain whatever.
The competition is so tough,
it makes me lose my fighting spirit.
But my favorite is Mudflat Man.
Try it on and see if it fits.
Okay.
Couple T-shirts?
Well, you're half right.
Check underneath.
Ta-da! This one…
This is for Yeon-du.
And this is for my mom.
Matching group shirts.
No. They're matching family shirts.
I have something for you too.
What?
What? Why is there so much?
They say the temperature at the South Pole
drops to minus 25 degrees in the winter.
Put all of these on,
stay warm, and have a safe trip.
Dan-ho, how did you find out?
When I went to pick you up last time,
I heard it from your colleagues.
I…
I'm sorry for not telling you.
You should be, Mo-eum.
You thought of me as someone too selfish.
I'm…
I'm not some pathetic guy who holds back
his successful girlfriend.
No, it's not like that.
We just recently confirmed
our feelings for each other.
I was worried it would be too sudden.
I also don't know
how to break it to Yeon-du.
Mo-eum.
I heard everything.
Yeon-du.
Send me pictures of emperor penguins
when you go to the South Pole.
Emperor penguins?
Yes. While emperor penguin mothers
go off to find food,
the fathers keep
the eggs warm until they hatch.
Just like my dad.
We'll patiently wait for you.
Come here, Yeon-du.
All right.
I'll be sure
to come back in style
with plenty of snacks.
Bring back lots of snacks.
Got it.
What?
Thank you…
for coming into my life.
For coming into our lives.
I can't breathe, Mo-eum.
I can't breathe!
LENTIL VEGGIE SOUP FOR VEGANS
LOTUS LEAF WRAPPED RICE
I hadn't been feeling well lately
and was looking for healthy food.
- I'll give it a try.
- Thank you for watching.
I hope you enjoy
a healthy and delicious meal.
The instructions were made
so easy to follow.
The eggplant pizza was really good.
I'm glad you found it helpful.
You can try it with zucchini
or potatoes instead as well.
STIR-FRIED TOMATO AND ACORN JELLY
I'm currently sick, and I saw your video
while searching for healthy food.
It looks so good.
But I don't have the energy to cook,
so I can't make it.
It'd be nice if I could try your food.
Choisseung.
- Want to go out?
- Okay.
I'll get ready.
Choisseung!
Are you done with your work?
Can you be out during the day?
Yeah.
Should we take a walk
around the neighborhood like old times?
Sure.
Remember this spot?
It used to be a stationery store.
Of course.
There was a capsule toy
vending machine here.
And all the junk food
was laid out on the stand there.
Every time I got some money,
I'd spend it all here.
It was mostly from my piggy bank.
I was mostly like that.
Let's go, my baby!
My baby!
Call me that one more time,
and you're dead.
Hey, baby!
Let's go to sing karaoke!
Hey! I told you not to call me that.
Come on, let's go!
I'll let you sing the entire bonus time.
Forget it.
You always pick duet songs anyway.
I'm for real this time.
I don't want to.
I'm scared someone might see us
go into a room together alone.
I can't let any more misunderstandings
ruin my life.
You little jerk.
You treat me like I'm contaminated.
- My goodness!
- Get back here.
- What's with you?
- Come here!
Stop right there.
- Hey!
- No!
Come on!
They must be finished with renovations.
I guess so.
I wonder what will come in.
Want to go inside?
What?
Hey, are we allowed
to just walk in like this?
I wanted to hate whatever came
in place of my dad's store.
But it turned out great.
I guess the new business
will be a restaurant too.
The kitchen looks so cozy and cute.
- Take a look inside.
- No way. it's someone else's kitchen.
Who cares? It's only a quick look.
- You think so?
- Yeah.
Excuse me.
It's your kitchen.
What?
This…
is your shop.
What?
Hello?
- Uncle Geun-sik!
- Hey, Seung-hyo.
You were busy.
Am I disturbing you?
Of course not.
Come in.
Wow, Seung-hyo! This is…
I don't think I've ever been here before.
Feel free to look around.
Okay.
Wow, this place is amazing.
Is there something you need though?
Well…
Seung-hyo.
I have a favor to ask of you.
You want to renovate Root Diner?
Yeah.
I want to open a restaurant
for Seok-ryu there.
Uncle Geun-sik…
I haven't been able to do
anything for Seok-ryu.
When I was younger,
I thought by the time I retired
I'd have a pile of money
to pass down to each of my kids.
But still…
I think I can at least
do this one thing for her.
Seok-ryu will be really happy about this.
You think so?
Well, we never had many customers,
and it was in a shabby location,
so I wonder if I'm doing the right thing.
She'll love it more than any other spot.
She gets to continue what you started
and begin something new.
Really?
So you'll take charge of it?
Of course.
I'll handle it in complete secrecy.
Okay.
So this is why you've been busy lately?
You were secretly preparing all of this?
Yeah.
I couldn't compromise on anything.
It's a collaboration between the two men
who love you the most.
Thank you.
Here, you can create dishes
that truly reflect who you are.
And provide comfort and healing to people.
Okay.
You're incredible, Seung-hyo.
You fixed my room,
my heart…
and now, the restaurant.
I haven't even started yet.
From now on, I'm going to create
every space you'll be in.
Wow.
I guess I'm the one who hit the jackpot.
I…
I love this space so much.
What a relief.
Dong-jin.
Your exam's tomorrow, right?
Yes.
Have you prepared well?
This is the first time
I've read this book from start to finish.
I feel so proud of myself.
You'll pass this time.
Here, take this.
What's this? You want me to shine this?
It's for you to keep.
It means
I officially recognize you
as my apprentice.
Shouldn't you ask me first?
Hang it up in your room with sincerity.
Where am I going to put
this smelly and ugly thing?
Just give me a raise instead.
Gosh, this is really heavy.
It looks good on you.
What are you talking about?
- Are you here for a session?
- No.
I decided not to sign up.
Why?
Did you not like something?
I decided to sign up later.
Good luck with your exam.
And after you get certified,
be my personal trainer.
What?
Last time during my run,
you seemed to be a good coach.
So I'll be your first client.
That one doesn't work.
Use the one on the left.
That one's broken.
- Have a seat.
- Okay.
All right.
I'm so upset.
I wanted to have a feast. A farewell party
at a convenience store's ridiculous.
Hey, I'm upset too.
You won't be back for a long time.
This is so underwhelming.
Gosh, it's fine.
Hey, if we prepared something big,
Seok-ryu would go…
Should old acquaintance be forgot
And never brought to mind?
And she'd obviously cry her eyes out.
Bye, Mo-eum…
Stop! Will you look at her?
Hey, Dan-ho.
They had a lot of these today.
Why are you drinking that?
I wanted to recreate
exactly how it was back then.
It's like our beginnings.
I'm still amazed when I think about it.
We don't have anything in common.
How did we all end up as friends?
I think if our moms weren't friends,
we would've never been together.
I still liked our group.
It felt like I was flanked
by the Azure Dragon and the White Tiger.
Hey, what are you doing?
Then, what about me?
The Vermillion Bird? The Black Tortoise?
You are…
You're my love.
You're my love too.
I love you, Mo-eum.
Hey, let's leave.
I don't think I can sit here
any longer either.
I've watched you two act
like damn idiots for decades.
Sit back down.
Yeah, I think I should sit here
since my leg was hurting.
Just wait one year.
We'll get together like this again
and paint the town red.
Cheers!
- Cheers!
- Come back quick.
- Got it.
- Yeah, you better come back.
What do you mean?
My boyfriend will misunderstand.
I think that was a bit harsh.
Hey, why are you two ganging up on him?
- My goodness.
- We're not. It's just what he said was…
You'd always been unique
since you were a kid.
Now, you'll finally set foot
on the South Pole.
Thanks, Mom.
You never put limits on my dreams,
so I grew up well.
You should be getting married instead.
Why go to that cold place--
Again with the marriage talk!
Way to ruin the mood.
When you get there, send me some salt.
In-suk says
Antarctic sea salt is really good.
Seriously.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll give some
to all four Lavender members.
Mo-eum, take care.
Watch out so you don't get
laryngitis, tonsillitis, or pneumonia.
Okay.
Yeon-du, I'll video call you
as soon as I get there.
Call your mother too, you brat.
Of course!
As if I'd forget you, Mom?
I'm not sure if I've said this before,
but come here.
What's gotten into you?
I'm proud of you.
Of course.
I'm your daughter.
Dan-ho.
Yes.
Hurry and take her. She'll be late.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll take her safely to the airport.
Have a good trip.
Yeon-du, let's head inside and eat.
Mo-eum.
Bye.
How can I leave her like this?
- Yeon-du, let's go together.
- Hey.
Go on in.
Hurry and take her away.
Should we go now?
Okay!
- Thank you.
- Please get in.
Have I ever told you
how much I like you, Dan-ho?
What?
I love you as much
as all the glaciers in Antarctica.
But the glaciers are melting
because of global warming.
That's why I'm going
to the South Pole! So I can stop it!
I love you as much as all the snowflakes
that will fall at the South Pole
while you're there.
I'M CURRENTLY SICK
IT'D BE NICE IF I COULD TRY YOUR FOOD
I'm opening a restaurant soon.
The name of the place is…
Rainbow Kitchen.
How do you feel?
Your place will open soon.
I can't sleep.
Did you know?
There are over 1,300 stars
on my room's ceiling.
Wow, you counted all of them?
That's insane. It's so you, Seok-ryu.
As the one who stuck each of them on,
you're not exactly ordinary either.
My neck got cramps a few times
while sticking those on.
I'm here!
I'm here too!
Hello.
- Hey!
- Wow!
Honestly, when I see this place,
it's like Seung-hyo read my mind
and made it exactly how I imagined it.
Dad.
Thank you. I'll really give it my all.
Seok-ryu.
Don't work too hard.
Just enjoy it as you go.
That would probably
be harder to do though.
Would you like some coffee?
It's okay. I already had a cup at home.
I'd like one.
Fill it with ice, so it's nice and cold.
Iced coffee, not hot.
So hot coffee?
Iced Americano!
Goodness.
It's beautiful.
Getting the ice ready.
Here is your coffee.
It's nice and refreshing.
Seok-ryu, are you sure
you'll be okay on your own?
You have to cook, serve,
take bills, clean…
There's so much to do.
I just have to give it a try.
If you need help,
just call your dad.
Dad, I need to ask you for a favor.
Dad.
Can you be my advisor for Rainbow Kitchen?
You're not going to torture me
with work, are you?
I just need to give advice, right?
Yeah. You have more experience than I do.
I want your know-how on developing
the menu, running a business,
and dealing with risks.
Give me your guidance and support, okay?
Yeah, instead of bugging me while I cook,
get paid to nag her.
Come on, I just retired not too long ago,
and you want to put me to work again?
Don't be like that. Help Seok-ryu out,
Mr. Advisor.
- Mr. Advisor!
All right, then.
Because it's not a full-time job.
- He loves it.
- He really does!
Gosh, I'm suddenly thirsty.
Seung-hyo, give me some coffee.
Would you like instant coffee?
What? You think I'd only drink
the instant stuff?
I like Iced Americanos too!
- Iced Americano is the best.
- Okay.
For a moment,
you resembled Steve Jobs… No.
Mark Zuckerberg.
This is who I really was.
I love seeing this other side of you.
I love it, but…
This isn't a date.
This is burning the midnight oil.
I have no choice. I need to get
everything ready before the opening.
So this is an app for Rainbow Kitchen?
Yeah, isn't it cool?
Later on, I can take reservations
and custom requests with this.
According to customers' tastes,
preferences,
and most importantly, health conditions,
they'll be able to make
requests or changes to dishes.
My goodness.
A chef who can write code?
I bet no one would see that coming.
I feel pretty proud.
It feels like the life I lived
in the past wasn't in vain.
Of course. Every experience you had
on the path you traveled piled up
and made who you are today.
I've lived a pretty good life.
I'm proud of you, Seok-ryu.
By the way, you remember
what we're doing tomorrow, right?
Yeah.
Does it look bad?
Why aren't you saying anything?
I was trying to think of…
the right word to describe it,
but nothing came to mind.
You're just
so beautiful.
I better look good! It's so uncomfortable.
It's tight around my waist,
and it's squeezing my chest.
I can't breathe either.
It's so uncomfortable.
Well, with that dress on,
I bet you can't put me in a headlock.
I'll buy you this dress.
Wear it every day.
It'll be expensive.
We'll get our money's worth.
You can wear it at the grocery store
or to the bathhouse…
Choisseung, come here for a second.
Is something wrong?
- What is it?
- It's pinching me here. It's bothering me.
- Let's see.
- Over here.
Hey! You thought I couldn't do it
in a dress, didn't you?
I told you not to put your guard down.
You really want to do this
while buying a wedding dress?
So why did you doubt me?
It doesn't matter what I wear!
Mom, are you ready?
Honey, they're ready outside…
How do I look?
A wedding dress at my age?
Isn't it a bit foolish?
You're beautiful.
You're radiant.
I can't look directly at you.
Stop saying nonsense
in front of our child.
Mom, I'm 34 now.
You'll forever be a child to me.
Aunt Hye-suk.
- Hey, Seok-ryu!
- You're so pretty!
Thank you so much.
I get to wear a dress thanks to you.
- It's nothing.
- Thank you.
- I'm so embarrassed.
- You're so pretty!
Right?
Okay! I'll stop!
I'll stop!
Jeez.
I didn't do it that hard.
So is this going to be my life soon
where I'm threatened
like this every day?
Maybe not soon…
Can we…
postpone our wedding by just a year?
What?
I still have so much to do.
I need to build up the restaurant,
and it's ridiculous if Mo-eum
can't come to our wedding.
Also…
most importantly,
I want to catch up on the 30 years
of romance we've missed out on.
Please?
Are you upset?
Yes.
Why are your reasons so valid, right,
and highly reasonable?
It's impossible to say no to that.
So you'll wait for me?
But you look so beautiful in that dress!
You're telling me I have to wait a year
to see this again? You're so mean.
There is someone else
who might look better in it than me.
Did you know?
I wanted to hold a bouquet
of lily of the valley at our wedding.
Yeah, but since we got married
in the winter, we couldn't find any.
That's right.
But now, I get to hold one
as we renew our vows.
Do you know what this flower symbolizes?
They say it symbolizes
a return to happiness.
We're ready now.
Okay. Look over here, please!
Give us a slight smile!
Seung-hyo!
Yeah, let's get one with our son.
Gosh, you look so nice.
Your son is very handsome.
Right? She has a good eye.
- One step this way, please.
- Okay.
Okay, that's great.
All right, smile!
Amazing.
We finally have a family photo now.
Not yet. Seok-ryu!
- Yes, Aunt Hye-suk?
- Hold on.
Do you need something?
Should I get your lipstick?
No, let's take a photo together.
- What?
- We're family now.
- You're right.
- Right, honey?
- Come over here.
- Stand here.
Gosh, what a beautiful family.
All right, here we go!
Great.
Hey, why is a family picture
taking so long?
- Goodness.
- Come here.
- Yeah, I'm about to pass out from waiting.
- Hey.
She said she hadn't eaten
for two days to take these photos.
This is my first time
wearing a dress at a wedding.
My wedding was
a traditional one at a hyanggyo.
Right, in hanbok.
Hello! I'm here to take your photos.
We should step aside now.
- Right.
- Over here, Lavender!
Honey, pose!
Thank you! We look so good!
- Throw your bouquet!
- Let's yell, "Lavender!"
- Okay.
- Good idea.
Now, look this way.
Ready, set, go!
- Lavender!
My mom and her friends are so adorable.
They are.
They look so happy.
- You're right.
- They're not 57.
They're like 17-year-old girls.
I know, right?
Seok-ryu.
Thank you.
Without you,
I wouldn't have even thought of this.
Honestly, sons just don't get their moms.
Look at this.
Why did you follow me in here?
You should be by her side.
I've been her son this whole time.
Now, it's time…
to be your partner.
There's no time to waste if we want
to catch up on 30 years of romance.
Like what?
Something like this?
Yeah.
That's right.
I've…
thought of another dream.
Just like our parents,
I want to be with you
for as long as I can.
You only thought of that now?
I've felt that way for ages.
No, I probably felt that way
before you did.
I'd been ignoring
my feelings for far too long.
Looking back,
I think it was my very first dream.
I'll take good care of you.
Let's take
a picture like that in 30 years.
Yeah, I'd like that.
Affectionate, warm,
and full of love.
10 MONTHS LATER
Don't be ridiculous.
This is more impressive!
What are you talking about?
This was way harder to do.
Seung-hyo was appointed
as a public architect for Seoul
even with his busy schedule.
Jeez.
He said he's working
on an urban redevelopment project.
Even when clients line up
with bags of money,
gosh, he still puts public interest first!
Instead of removing the factory equipment,
it's best to leave them as is.
He said it was an architect's duty
to preserve history and culture.
Seung-hyo should be an elected official.
Hey, what about Seok-ryu?
She's already earned an Orange Ribbon
six months after opening.
And you all saw the article
about her restaurant
in The Chungwoo Daily.
They said it was a restaurant
that heals both body and soul
with not only delicious
but also healthy food.
She pulled off that difficult feat!
Hey, do you see this scarf?
Seung-hyo brought this back
from his overseas business trip.
It's from a famous luxury brand.
- Hey.
- Hey, what?
- This.
- What about it?
Seok-ryu said this shade suited me
and gave it as a gift.
She says I have a cool summer skin tone.
- Girls.
- I have a warm tone.
Are you two bragging
about your in-laws now?
You two sure find
creative ways to act like fools.
Gosh.
Hey, Yeon-du won an award
at her kindergarten coding competition!
- Wow!
- She wants to work for NASA later.
NASA?
My goodness, that's so amazing.
Right? We don't stand a chance
against bragging about granddaughters.
Ki-hoon got a job!
- Really?
- That's great news! What kind?
He's a sales rep for a copier company.
- It's been a week now.
- Why didn't you tell us sooner?
At first, I wasn't sure if he made
the right choice. I had mixed feelings.
But the other day, Ki-hoon told me
it was always his dream to wear a tie
and take the subway to work.
When I heard that, it really woke me up.
Passing exams isn't the only path in life!
Exactly, he's a people person.
I'm sure he'll do great.
Of course, he will. That's great news.
Our copy machine at the office
is on its last legs.
I should give Ki-hoon a call.
I'll buy him a tie!
He got a job,
so his aunt should give him a gift.
Okay.
- Buy one for him right away.
- Of course.
Get him an expensive one.
Hey, I'm the only one
with just well wishes.
Tell him I'm so happy for him.
- What great news.
- Thank you!
- Should I? A barbecue at my office?
- Do it!
Fifteen.
Great.
Sixteen.
Seventeen.
BAE DONG-JIN
CERTIFIED PERSONAL TRAINER
Breathe in.
Eighteen.
Nineteen.
Okay, one last time.
Push off both feet
and keep the barbell straight.
Keep your eyes straight ahead.
Na-yun, your hips keep going too far back.
Engage your back muscles
to keep it straight.
Let's do ten more.
Hey, can we take a break?
We can't. There's still a lot to do.
Want to grab some chicken and beer after?
Na-yun, after all this exercise,
you want to drink beer?
Don't you feel bad for your body?
- No, I meant…
- All right, grab the barbell again.
Steady upper body, lower your shoulders,
and engage your lats!
Okay, one!
Two!
Great. Three!
Focus! Four!
Seok-ryu wants to add vegan options.
So I've been researching vegetables.
What's good for preventing cancer?
Glucosinolates have cancer-fighting
and antioxidant properties.
I see. What kind of foods
have a lot of that?
Vegetables like broccoli
and cabbage have a lot of them.
But they're sensitive to heat,
so it's better
to eat those raw than cooked.
I see. Then, she should make a salad.
That's the best way to do it.
- No!
- Okay!
Jeez.
You're so cheap.
It's just technique.
Technique, my foot.
Then, what should we…
do tomorrow?
I have to go to work.
Come on. Just retire already, will you?
How long are you planning
to work at that hospital for?
Am I your only friend?
Gosh.
Tomorrow, collect samples for research,
we'll conduct a marine survey.
Ms. Jung?
Yes, sir. There will be
a safety briefing beforehand,
so I'd appreciate it if everyone
could arrive an hour early.
- Yes, ma'am.
And next week, we'll have fire drills.
We'll be simulating
a fire outbreak at the base,
including rescue operations,
first aid, and fire suppression.
It's going to be super realistic,
so be ready, everyone.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Is that the end?
That's the end.
Okay, then. Meeting adjourned.
- Thank you.
Dan-ho! Yeon-du!
- Mo-eum!
- Mo-eum.
Wait, isn't that my house?
You're right.
Where's Mom?
She's at a Lavender gathering.
Wow, people might think you live there.
You're right. I do practically live here.
I had a sleepover with Grandma last night.
I see. Is that so?
She said there was no point
in having separate houses.
She wants to put ours
on the market right away.
What? Are you all becoming
a real family while I'm gone?
I guess so.
Yeon-du.
I miss you so much.
Me too.
So I'm going to send you a very big gift.
A gift?
Dad, hurry and tell her.
That gift is me.
I'll be visiting you next month.
What are you talking about?
I'm officially going to the South Pole
for a feature article about my experience.
I got the approval.
Then…
We'll get to see each other soon?
Yes.
At the beautiful ends
of the Earth where you are.
Was the food all right?
Yes, it was so delicious.
Thank you for the food.
I should be thanking you.
And here are the recipes
for the dishes you had today.
Is it okay to just give
these out like this?
Aren't these trade secrets?
I posted them
on my vlogs anyway, so it's fine.
As long as our customers enjoy good food
and stay healthy, that's enough for me.
I'll definitely try making it. Thank you.
Have a nice day.
- You too.
- Thank you.
Please come again!
I'll make it for you.
- Really?
- Yeah.
POMEGRANATE TREE
Mr. Choi.
You hear that Greip's flagship store
starts construction next week?
Yeah, I'll keep following up on it.
Don't worry.
Jeez, you're not even looking at me.
You're working on that again, aren't you?
TERRACE, LIVING ROOM, STUDY
OUR HOME
Hey, you swore
you'd build my house for me.
But how can you build yours first?
Seung-hyo.
Help me out, Myeong-u.
I want to get married too.
You're right. Welcome to Hell.
- You mean heaven.
- Okay. I was joking.
Gosh, look at the time.
Man…
HYEREUNG-DONG MUSIC CONCERT
BADMINTON TOURNAMENT
When you suggested
opening up the first floor,
I had no clue what you meant.
I can't tell if this place
is an architectural firm,
a daycare, or a senior center.
What? I like it.
We tore down the stereotype
that architectural firms are intimidating.
I think I worked out too much…
What? Mom!
- So you were here.
- Aunt Mi-suk!
- Good afternoon.
- Hello.
- Hello, ma'am.
- Hello!
Wow, you and Seung-hyo
still resemble each other so much.
- Thank you, Mr. Yoon.
- You're welcome.
Right.
I have something for you.
I heard from Seung-hyo
that you published a book.
- I did.
- Yes.
It's a memoir about my 30 years
as a diplomat.
I have a book signing
at a bookstore next week.
- Really? Can I come?
- Of course.
- Yes, I'll be there!
- Hey, you should come too if you can.
How about you treat us first
to celebrate your book coming out?
To beef, not pork.
Just sign the card receipt instead.
- Jeez.
- Hey, Seung-hyo.
Can I stick this up here?
Of course. Here, I'll do it for you.
Over here.
NA MI-SUK'S FAIRY TALE CLASS
"Fairy tale class"?
Yeah. You know I'm good
at telling stories.
I want to inspire the young sprouts
in Hyereung-dong.
I liked it when you read
folk tales for us too.
I'm still learning English from your mom.
Next year,
I'm going to hold
an English fairy tale class here too.
Go ahead.
Chase your dreams, Aunt Mi-suk.
NA MI-SUK'S FAIRY TALE CLASS
EVERY WEDNESDAY AND THURSDAY AT 3:00 P.M.
Hey, kids.
I'm starting a fairy tale class.
You'll come, right?
WE'RE OPEN
WELCOME
BREAK TIME FROM 3:00 TO 5:00 P.M.
STIR-FRIED TOMATO AND ACORN JELLY
I'M CURRENTLY SICK
I DON'T HAVE THE ENERGY TO COOK
IT'D BE NICE IF I COULD TRY YOUR FOOD
After battling my illness for a year,
I went to eat at your restaurant today.
I was too shy to tell you this,
but your food gave me
warm comfort and encouragement.
Thank you for the recipe as well.
Are you coming?
That's right!
Choisseung!
Why are you so late?
I'm sorry for making you wait so long.
When I contacted you, I'd already
been waiting for 30 minutes.
So it was a total of 45 minutes.
I'm sorry.
You seem to have changed a bit though.
Back then,
you'd tell me it was okay to be late
and be careful on my way.
Now, you're getting mad in the street.
I wasn't mad. I was just asking.
You're frowning.
And your voice has lowered too.
You're the one who's changed.
You thought our plans were so trivial
that you were nearly an hour late.
Do you know how important today was?
I had to cancel the meeting
with our house's contractor.
You could've gone alone.
- What?
- I mean, you're the expert.
You can handle it alone.
I'd be of no use.
Seriously, I'm fine with anything.
Wow.
"Fine with anything"?
That's how you regard our new home?
Come on. That's not what I meant.
Hey--
If a customer walked into your place
and said to you half-heartedly,
"Just give me anything,"
how would you feel?
Well, I wouldn't think much of it.
I'd just recommend a dish.
I see. So I'm the only one
being sensitive here?
You're right. I'm the petty one.
I'm the small-minded one.
Stop it. Why are you
acting like this? It's tiring.
As tired as I am after looking
at blueprints all night?
For crying out loud! Hey!
Did you always hold grudges like this?
Do you always nitpick what people say?
Are we having a fight right now?
It doesn't seem like we're on good terms.
Then, we should create
some official rules for when we argue.
Whenever we argue,
we should always hold hands.
If that fails,
add "honey" to each sentence.
You can only let go
once the argument is over.
Should we go?
We should.
What are you thinking about?
Our new house…
even though you don't care.
Just say one more thing…
Honey.
You could end up living there
all by yourself, honey.
After I waited for 30 years
and another ten months,
how could you even say that to me, honey?
I have another request.
Honey.
- Two single beds in our bedroom, honey.
- No way.
We have to go with a queen size.
Not a king either. Make it a queen.
Just look at this.
Why even ask for my opinion
on things like this then?
I'm going to stay right next to you,
like when I'm sad, hot, annoyed,
or even when we argue.
We should add another clause
to the rules when we argue.
No separate rooms and no separate beds.
Give the contractor a call.
Ask if we could still meet now.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I'm just as curious and eager
to see our house as you are.
What if he says we can't?
Hello, sir. How are you?
If it's not too much trouble,
would it be okay if we stopped by now?
Yes.
Really? You're available?
Okay. Thank you!
- It worked? What a relief.
- Wow, what a relief.
Gosh, I thought it was going
to be canceled today.
I was panicking earlier.
I know. Things were so hectic today.
THE END
THE END AND THE BEGINNING
Subtitle translation by: Hye Min Eom