So today, I met the campus's finest.
Heard you're heartbroken.
Do you believe in prophecy stones?
Oh, so you've arrived,
Ritt, the Prophecy Stone Master.
You know I was drunk last night.
What? I don't know about this.
If I want to have my fortune read,
how much do you charge?
He used to have a sweetheart.
They were very close back then.
Always side by side.
I'd like to know
if I'll ever see him again.
Do you remember me?
I'm Ritt.
[Disclaimer: This series is entirely fictional
and solely for entertainment purposes
with no association or reference
to any individuals, places, or events;
there may be inappropriate behaviors
and vulgarity based on the character's persona;
viewer discretion is advised]
♫Is it pure coincidence?♫
♫Or is it destiny that decides?♫
♫Is someone above drawing all these lines?♫
♫Or playing matchmaker in disguise?♫
♫What if the stars shift in their place♫
♫Slightly out of line,♫
♫Will our orbits still align?♫
♫Try answering if your world
will cross with mine♫
♫Though the destiny between us
is differently defined♫
♫And I believe our love has power♫
♫I believe the love of us♫
♫Will realign the stars back
to the line where they should be♫
Actually, I can find my way home.
No need to give me a ride.
Judging from how much you drank,
I'm concerned you wouldn't make it.
It's nothing.
Are you a heavy-drinking fortune teller?
It's part of the job.
It's better that I give you a ride.
I'm worried.
Thank you.
Like something out of a series...
How so?
Well...
You're reaching over
to fasten my seatbelt...
and your face is so close to mine.
Do you want to be
the lead or the love interest?
Uh...
I'll just stick to an architect.
Here's the dolphin.
What?
He wants your echolocation
so he can take you home.
Uh...
I'll give you the direction.
Why do you have to make things complicated?
Here.
Hm?
Motif-ated to ask if I can text you.
I've sent you the location.
Mm.
Are you ready for the ride?
Let's go.
Who do you live with?
I live alone, of course.
So, no lovers?
Not yet,
just a sweetheart.
Here he is.
So...
Are you gonna invite me
up there to Netflix and chill?
Doesn't seem like a good idea.
Why?
We just might go from
childhood sweethearts
to something real tonight.
Shouldn't we take things slow?
Okay.
I'm going upstairs.
Thank you for the ride.
And...
Nice to meet you again.
So are we gonna meet again?
Totally.
You know where to find me.
I'm available every night at Magic Move.
Drive home safely, and good night.
Mm.
Wait.
What's the matter?
A hug.
A hug...
Mm.
Just like when we were kids.
Good night.
So, how's it going, little sis?
Like hot cakes,
crushed, going everywhere,
all over the place!
This means we're on the right track.
Ritt is amazing at saying random stuff
and still getting the customers to buy it.
It's not all that random.
He's writing a thesis on this topic.
He knows some balls about those stones.
Mm, I really thought he made it all up.
Well, not all of it.
Maybe 90% is, and the rest is real.
How is that any different?
Where there are fortune tellers,
there are guessers, Ploy.
That's insulting
to the authentic fortune tellers.
My apologies!
Come on, close up
the bar so we can go home.
Help me out, then!
Hello to you on Tuesday.
Itthi, come have breakfast.
Come on!
No, thank you. I'm on a time crunch.
- What?
- Ugh...
What's the rush?
Alright, take some desserts
to eat in your car.
Thank you, Grandma.
Now, go.
- I'm heading out.
- Alright.
Oh! And drive safe, Itthi.
Alright, just let him go. He's in a rush.
Have you left your condo? When's your class?
I'll come pick you up in 5.
I'm about to head out.
Are you really gonna pick me up?
Count from 1-50, and I'll be there.
Sir,
can we make a detour back to my condo?
Sorry, I forgot some stuff back there.
What number are you at now?
I'm almost there.
At 35 now, pushing the elevator's button.
Just make it before I count to 50.
If I'm late, I'll let you punish me.
48, 49, 50.
I'm in front of the condo. Are you here?
Exactly at 50, right?
58.
You lost.
Then...dinner is on me.
Just in time, right?
I thought you'd already left.
You're in luck.
I left later than usual.
Please get in the car.
Your chauffeur is ready to serve you.
Hey!
What is Itthi from the Faculty of Business
doing here at the Architect buildings?
He's like an angel incarnate.
How handsome.
He's top-tier,
yet he's here with Ritt?
Well, seems like the ace
is here with a background character.
It's giving random villager.
Quiet down. They could hear you.
Everyone's got their eyes
on you, Master Ritt.
I think they’re on you.
They're probably wondering
why Itthi just showed up at this faculty.
Aren't you just exaggerating?
Who would even know me?
Gosh...
That'd be the entire campus.
Don't you realize
how popular you are?
That much?
Totally.
Here, look at those girls.
They’re all blushing.
They probably have a big crush on you.
What about you?
Do you?
Uh...
I'll...get into this building.
Thanks for the ride.
This evening,
you get off at 5 PM, right?
I'll pick you up.
Quick!
Come on, we have a class to attend.
Are you hungry? Let's go grab a bite.
Same place?
Oh!
Same place...
Mm, let's go.
So you remember it?
Who'd forget?
Do you remember this place?
We used to eat here
after school when we were kids.
Oh!
Of course.
It's been a while.
I still come here every once in a while.
Though the cooking never changes.
I...barely get to pass by this area,
so I never stopped by.
Then...
I'll have my usual.
Go ahead and jot it down
since there's no menu.
Right...
What do you feel like?
Tell me, and I'll write it down.
The same dish we enjoyed
having together back then.
Oh...
The dish we enjoyed...
That one, right?
Let me test
if you can still remember it.
Omelet...
With chopped shrimp.
Whoa!
How can you still remember it?
It was always an omelet
with chopped shrimp.
I just can.
And...
Omelet...
Omelet soup with no cilantro.
Whoa!
That was so precise.
It was our childhood dish,
how could I forget that?
Then...
The last one is...
Is...
Stir-fried...
What was the dish? Finish the name.
Stir-fried mixed vegetables, of course!
Are you sure?
You didn't like veggies.
Well... I do now.
Come on, let me write it down.
Let's just settle on these.
Come on, what do we have here?
Omelet, stir-fried mixed vegetables,
and omelet soup.
Wait at your table.
This is nice.
Familiar place,
familiar someone,
and familiar feelings.
It's never changed,
no matter how many times I come back.
Some relationships
don't need to start over
since the connection lingers.
Never once has it disappeared.
Did you smell something?
Omelet?
No,
it's the smell of our memories.
Please don't put
too much sugar in our food.
I think he's sweet enough as it is.
Sure!
Flavorful, huh?
Sweet,
but second to none
when it comes to spiciness.
I'm so stuffed.
Oops!
Sorry.
I got carried away.
Okay.
I just burped.
Guess we're even.
Do you have any plans after this?
Wanna watch a movie?
When are you gonna come to the bar,
you rascal? I'll get the tribute ready.
Let's do it. I'm free today.
No plans, whatsoever.
I'm still caught up in some work.
Not going in today.
Shall we?
Bill, please.
50, 50, 50, 20, 20.
That'd be 190 baht.
Hey!
I'll cover our meal.
You pay for the movie.
Keep the change.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Phew...
I'm not gonna have any more meals tonight.
Ritt bailed on us.
He said he wasn't coming in tonight.
What?! Why?
He said he was caught up in some work.
So what are we gonna tell the customers?
Just that Ritt's not coming in.
We've never told them
that he's open for business every day.
Pitcha, a Thai youth who was given
a chance to be a trainee in Korea at JJV,
has returned to Thailand today
after missing his flight due to an injury.
Let's listen to what he has to say.
Right now, I'm back
to make a recovery in Thailand,
and for the doctor to
monitor my injured ankle.
As for when I'll get to go back,
we'll have to wait and see.
For now, I'll spend this time with
my mother and reunite with my friends
because it's been five years since
I left the country without returning.
That's adorable.
Just the nicest and the most grateful
Who in the world
could be so handsome and talented?
He can dance, he sings beautifully,
and he's all natural.
Just perfect.
He's totally my bias!
Get well soon. I'll be your support!
Pure, I was watching that.
Don't get too invested. Get back to work.
It's almost time to open.
Go check the kitchen.
Jeez, Pure. What a cruel brother.
You've hurt my little heart and soul
when I'm just simply loyal to Pitcha!
I can't believe
my sister could be so precocious.
It's time to work. Chop-chop!
This is a horror film.
Of course, it is.
It doesn't mention this on the poster.
Are you afraid of ghosts?
Big time.
You weren't when we were kids.
All you wanted to watch were scary movies.
I just got scared just a little while ago.
Then...
If the ghost appears,
you can cover your eyes.
Argh!
I'm sorry, but I'll have to wait outside.
I can't do this anymore.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know...
you were that afraid of ghosts.
It's all good.
The poster says, "First Love."
[First Love on the Final Night]
I didn't think
there would be any ghosts.
Well, it's the first love on
the final night before one of them dies.
After that,
the spirit haunts the other person...
Hey, cut it before
I can't fall asleep tonight.
Then...
I'll take you to this place.
Whoa...
Boo!
Just you wait.
I never knew about this side of you.
What side?
Like, the side of you that
enjoys making merit and stuff.
I like to make a casket donation,
both when I feel uneasy
and when something nice
gives me peace of mind.
For today...
is it the former or the latter?
Are you okay?
About what?
Eating at the same restaurant,
seeing a movie,
and making merit together.
I'm not okay...
with only the movie.
Are you still scared?
Can you sleep alone?
I can spend the night.
Not that scared.
I'm fine on my own.
But I think...
I'll have to sleep with the lights on.
When do you want me
to pick you up tomorrow?
To where?
To the university, of course.
I don't have classes tomorrow.
Then...I'll pick you up at 11.
To where?
To go on a date
and see another movie.
This time, I'll let you pick
what you wanna see.
Make up for today.
Do you have time?
I can make time.
Okay.
See you at 11.
♫I believe our love will change our♫
♫Destiny, rewrite prophecies♫
♫Even if they are against our destiny♫
Text me before you go to bed.
Why?
In case someone here is so afraid
that he will have nightmares.
I can wish him
a sweet dream before that happens.
You're so extra.
♫I believe the love of us♫
Wear blue tomorrow.
Why?
I want us to wear matching shirts.
♫We're gonna try… try… try!♫
Is Ritt gonna come tomorrow?
The customers were all complaining
that they didn't get their fortune read.
He has to come in.
We've made a promise to many customers.
If he's a no-show,
we'll be absolutely chewed.
Are you asleep?
I'm about to be.
So your work is done?
No, I'll have
to pick up the work tomorrow.
Alright.
But you have
to come to the bar tomorrow night.
Why?
The customers were all complaining
that they didn't get to see Ritt,
the Prophecy Stone Master.
Alright, alright.
What time do you need me?
How about 11 at night?
Hold up until we get the tabs going
and reach the sale's goal.
Okay.
See you.
Okay, bye.
[Kenaz: Opening up, Warmth]
Give me a confirmation
for tomorrow. No bailing.
Alright!
Sweet dreams, from someone who's scared
of ghosts and leaving the lights on
The fuck's wrong with you?
Why did you just wish me a sweet dream?
Whoa, whoa...
My bad. I sent it to the wrong person.
You did?
So...who was that meant for?
Hey! I'm hanging up. I'm getting so sleepy.
See you at the bar tomorrow.
Yeah, that's not strange at all.
Are you sure you can sleep alone?
Beware of a ghost creeping by the bed.
Wish me sweet dreams.
Nope.
Please? Please.
I wish a ghost haunted you
right in your own bedroom.
What now?
Say it first.
Dreams.
Not like that. Say it properly.
I'm going to bed. Bye.
Okay, I give up. Sweet dreams.
That's bitter.
Give it a taste.
Is it good?
You're moving so fast, my friend.
Have you hooked up?
Pure!
What can I get you, Itthi?
How did Ritt trick you into this?
Did he cast a black magic on you?
I want to be here.
My friend is quite charismatic.
Apart from the prophecy stones,
are you also a master of love potions?
Enough!
You're supposed to be my friend.
What drinks can I get ya?
I'd rather not drink.
I drove here today.
Hello, Ritt.
Hello...
It's Itthi.
Oh, the one from the other day where...
Uh... Ployplern.
Can I see today's schedule?
I wanna see which tables I have to visit.
Sure, I'll bring it to you.
Then I'll have to steal him
to get him ready as the Master.
I'll sit with you.
Haven't you told him yet
that you're not the real sweetheart?
Not yet.
So he still thinks that
you're his childhood sweetheart?
He sure does.
Hasn't he suspected anything?
Or do you really look like him?
I have no idea.
I just go with the flow
like I am that person.
How is that even possible?
Can someone really forget
what their friend was like?
Can you remember
every face from high school?
Almost,
excluding someone
who looks different after they grew up.
There you go.
Maybe I'm that person in his case.
What about your names?
Don't tell me
you two share the same names?
You're right.
But he's not suspicious or anything.
I think
this whole thing is strange.
I thought so,
but everything feels like a dream,
so I just accept its strangeness.
How so?
- Well... Ever since...
- Ritt, there you are.
Your first customers are at Table 3
by the door; they've been waiting a while.
Okay, I'm coming.
Take care of Itthi for me.
Don't say too much.
Okay.
Right now, there might be some obstacles.
But trust me
when I say it will all be fine.
It'll get better in the future.
You mean it?
Of course.
Just have lots of conversations.
Three stones.
Your love looks good!
It's going well, right?
I can tell from your eyes.
Love
is like a wooden bridge.
Sometimes...
the squeaks it makes when you walk across
don't mean that it will fall apart,
but it's reminding you not to forget
to hold each other's hands even tighter.
There you go!
Amazing job.
Are you drunk, Master?
I'm all good.
Are you not gonna drink?
I have to drive for the Master.
Ployplern,
which table
would you like me to visit next?
Just a sec, Master Ritt.
That's everything for tonight.
Get as wasted as you want.
I'm done.
I'd better go back to work on my project.
Well, well, you've taken on so many roles:
a master,
a final-year Architect student,
and probably someone's sweetheart
if I have to guess?
Pure,
that's every customer for the night.
Can I leave now?
Help me close up the bar first.
Don't you think
you're overworking him, Pure?
She's right.
How much you made me work
might as well exceed the legal limit.
Then, be my guest and leave,
my absolutely honorary dude,
No.1 fortune teller at Magic Move,
- an angle of a man...
- Enough!
So, how are you gonna go home?
Want me to call you a cab?
It's fine.
I'll give him a ride.
I see that my friend here
has his own chauffeur.
It's on his way home.
So where do you live?
Bang Na.
Huh?
Bang Son and Bang Na...
How are those ares crossing paths?
What?
We don't live in the same direction?
I can just turn the car around.
Easy as pie.
Then...
We're heading out.
See you, Pure.
We're heading out, Ployplern.
Make sure Ritt gets to his condo.
I'll leave you to it.
They are made for each other, Pure.
Sure, they are.
One of them is good at tricking,
and the other one buys it completely.
I think it's their compatibility.
They are soulmates to the bone.
I'm curious to see
how long you can give me a ride.
How about every single night from now?
If people see it,
they're gonna think we're a thing.
Well...
Isn't that a good thing?
I wouldn't dare.
Itthi, the hottie,
the jade-faced,
the Business graduate,
the finest of the campus,
that's far beyond reach.
What if you don't have to reach?
I'll bow down.
Wow...
Aren't you gonna be a little humble,
Prince Charming?
Be serious,
if I bow down,
will you have me?
Hm?
Pick one.
What does that mean?
It's a secret!
A secret?
Is it your secret
or mine?
Something with a spiritual connection...
isn't told for free.
The booking is closed for the night.
If you want it read,
contact Ployplern to get in line.
Don't I get to skip the line
as your VIP customer? Hm?
Can we leave now?
Otherwise, I'm gonna call my own ride.
You just changed the subject, huh?
Let's go.
What?
Why aren't you getting in the car?
Open the door for me.
Please.
That's the fee.
Do you want me to buckle you up, too?
Here.
That's a payback.
Do it one more time
so it's a gain.
Whose gain exactly?
You...
are quite something else.
We were playing around and pecking
each other on the cheek back then.
Can't we do it now?
Of course.
No sweat.
Playing around, huh?
Don't you think that's enough?
Your cheek is gonna bruise now.
Is Ritt, the Prophecy Stone Master, here?
What do I do
if I want my fortune read by Master Ritt?
I can smell chaos ensuing.
The real one
has come back to claim what's his.
You're scared
to meet his real sweetheart,
and if they eventually meet?
Hey, I have to go.
If we weren't sweethearts,
it would've been hard
to approach you, huh?
Are you Ritt, the Prophecy Stone Master?
Do you mind taking another customer?
[Watch Magic Move Uncut version online
only on iQIYI and iQ.com]
♫Is it pure coincidence?♫
♫Or is it destiny that decides?♫
♫Is someone above drawing all these lines?♫
♫Or playing matchmaker in disguise?♫
♫What if the stars shift in their place♫
♫Slightly out of line,♫
♫Will our orbits still align?♫
♫Try answering if your world
will cross with mine♫
♫Though the destiny between us
is differently defined♫
♫I believe our love will change our♫
♫Destiny, rewrite prophecies♫
♫Even if they are against our destiny♫
♫(But we're gonna try… try… try!)♫
♫And I believe our love has power♫
♫I believe the love of us♫
♫Will realign the stars back
to the line where they should be♫
♫(And we're gonna try… try… try!)♫