NO TAIL TO TELL
Get off me.
Sorry.
Are you…
okay?
Do I look okay to you right now?
- Of course I'm not okay.
- I see.
By the way…
you just saw
that strange thing too, right?
It's not strange. It's mystical.
Anyway, it looks like I have
more urgent matters to attend to.
What?
I'll deal with you later.
What are you doing?
Damn it.
Just how much spiritual power did I lose?
I can't even do this all of a sudden?
Darn it.
What's with her? Is she an actual lunatic?
But why did you come to see me…
WARD 22
NURSING STATION
Where did she go?
STORAGE ROOM
Are you kidding me?
We need to talk.
I said, we need to talk.
I told you.
I'm not that naive fox I used to be.
All this wood will burn nicely.
You're still wicked and irreverent.
What do you think you're doing?
I don't expect you to honor the deities,
but you should at least be reasonable.
I just lost a huge chunk
of my spiritual power.
Out of the blue.
But no matter how much
I think about it, I just don't get it.
You've made quite a mess.
Was it this iron rod
that smashed the statues,
or was it you?
What are you talking about?
I didn't come all this way
to listen to your cryptic nonsense.
Just tell me why!
I've already given you the answer.
You're just being stubborn
instead of seeking the truth yourself.
I'm done cultivating myself,
so go ahead and do it as much as you want.
- Tell me why!
- You've sinned,
so you've paid the price.
Don't be ridiculous.
How is this an appropriate price?
I said I lost a huge chunk
of my spiritual power.
What did I do that was so wrong?
A human has died.
Because of you.
What?
What are you talking about?
Because you twisted human fate recklessly,
someone who wasn't
supposed to die has died.
EPISODE 2
THE HOUR OF TRANSFER
TRANSFER
1. A BIZARRE EVENT THAT DEFIES REASON
2. AN ATHLETE MOVING
FROM ONE TEAM TO ANOTHER
URI GARAM HOSPITAL
The next bus to arrive is number 360.
Hi.
You…
You know,
I think you'll need to make a wish.
What?
Hey, wait. Please stop!
Oh no! That was the last bus.
- Did you even hear what I said?
- Just a second.
Man, that really was the last bus.
I don't even have money for a cab.
- Hey.
- Seriously, hold on a second.
HOME
FASTEST ROUTE: 4H 24M
It takes over four hours
to walk home, jeez.
Hey.
Where do you live?
If I take you home,
will you actually listen to me?
What?
Have you heard of earth-folding?
It's similar to teleporting.
Like in martial arts novels?
Yeah, that.
I'm telling you now
so you don't freak out.
Let's go.
What the heck was that?
We're in front of my house.
I told you it was earth-folding.
I used sorcery to fold the earth.
Fold… the earth?
Wait, could you even travel
to Europe like this?
Like to Germany and Spain?
I guess not,
since they're across the ocean.
Of course I can!
That's not even an issue.
Back in the day,
I'd wake up and go to New York for bagels,
then go to France for lunch.
I was a regular
at a restaurant over there.
And after that,
I'd have my coffee in Italy.
But after a year or two,
you get sick of it.
That's insane.
You know…
that thing you just did.
Could you do it one more time?
Do I just need to hold
your hand like this?
What… are you doing?
Oh, I…
I'm sorry, I just found it fascinating.
Well…
I only showed you this
to make up
for embarrassing myself earlier.
Okay.
Anyway, that's not the point.
You're going to help me.
It's nothing big. Just make a simple wish.
A wish?
Yeah. I can't just interfere
in human affairs without a human's wish.
So you have to make a wish for me.
You want to catch that hit-and-run driver
and make him pay, right?
Hey!
Stop!
I said stop!
Wish for it.
I'll grant it for you.
No smoking in here.
We could've done
this witness interview over the phone.
Why drag someone so busy
all the way here?
Oh, this isn't a witness interview.
Mr. Lee has just been named a suspect.
Wait,
the real culprit for that hit-and-run
has already turned himself in--
Well, the security footage…
suddenly got restored last night.
Strangely, all the cameras
in that area malfunctioned,
so we hadn't been able
to confirm anything.
Isn't that fortunate?
Damn.
Damn it.
Okay.
What the…
Why aren't you showing up? Are you hiding?
Damn it.
What's she doing?
After messing up a job like this,
why aren't you showing up?
Why?
Disgusting. Shit.
…SERVING THE PEOPLE, GOWON POLICE
He's here! He's out!
Is it true that you caused a hit-and-run
and had someone else take the fall?
Any thoughts on the added DUI allegations?
Do you think this will affect
your inheritance of the Geumsu Group?
Just a word, please!
Just a quick word on how you're feeling?
- Please give us a statement!
- Just one statement!
It's really nothing, Father.
I'm telling you, I can handle this.
Father… Father!
Damn it, that senile old geezer.
Shit.
Did you take care of things last night?
I took care of it
so it wouldn't cause any issues.
There's no way
- that they'll suddenly find Bong-chang.
- Good.
If that blows up too,
I won't be able to handle it.
Yes, sir.
Of all the damn luck…
What's happening?
What's… wrong with this thing?
In other news,
a body was found earlier today
in the mountains near Gyeonggi Province.
The victim has been identified as Mr. Ko,
- a chauffeur for a construction company.
- Hey!
- Police are investigating…
- Is that…
- …treating it as a homicide.
- That's impossible.
Hey! What are you doing?
- I didn't do this. I swear!
- What the hell are you saying?
It was me.
You.
You kept summoning me earlier.
Too bad for you.
You can't be my client anymore.
Don't tell me you did all this?
Hey…
Pull over, you bastard.
I told you I'd pay you.
- So why are you doing this to me?
- I don't want to be doing this either.
But…
have you ever heard
of the butterfly effect?
Everyone on the left side…
I helped you.
And that night, you got carried away
and drove home completely wasted.
Then you caused an accident.
And while trying to cover it up…
- How dare you…
- …you ended up killing someone.
I don't really get it either,
but this is
what the ones above are saying.
I helped you.
And because of that, someone who wasn't
supposed to die is dead.
What?
Don't bother trying to understand.
I don't get it either.
Anyway, one has to clean up
their own messes, right?
Since I started this,
I'm going to sort it out myself.
And that'll help me recover
some of my lost spiritual power.
That was just a mistake.
No, it was an accident.
From now on, you won't be able to lie.
And you won't be able
to hide anything anymore.
Every single wrong you've ever committed,
even that pen you stole
from the stationery store as a kid,
you're going to confess to it all.
Oh, right.
I'll be taking this
since you're no longer my client.
Is he trying to say something?
I want to turn myself in.
What? Turn himself in?
Are you confessing
to the hit-and-run incident?
It's alleged
that you attempted to switch drivers.
Is there a reason
why you decided to turn yourself in?
I…
killed
someone!
- Oh my God!
- What?
I can't do this.
You bastard.
The victim died on the spot.
And to cover up the crime,
I ordered the body
to be buried in the mountains.
- Come quickly.
- Yes, sir!
All this time,
I've been building slush funds
- worth tens of billions of won…
- Hey, wait a minute!
…through offshore tax evasion
using overseas subsidiaries!
- Just a second!
- Was it intentional?
FAIRNESS UNDER THE LAW
SERVING THE PEOPLE, GOWON POLICE
This is a gift.
What is this?
It's a suitcase.
You'll probably need it soon.
I'm sure you saw the news.
It all worked out thanks to you.
I've even recovered
some of my spiritual power.
Gosh…
Was that really all you?
Wow.
You know, I've been wondering.
Who exactly… are you?
You want to know my name?
Well, that's too bad.
I don't usually tell humans my name.
No. That's not what I meant.
I mean, what are you exactly?
Not your name, but what you are.
Oh, that.
Take a guess.
Well, I'm not sure.
A demon?
What?
- Satan?
- What?
No?
Try again. Think of something more Korean.
Well…
- A maiden ghost?
- A nine-tailed fox!
Can't you tell just by looking at me?
This beauty.
And this mystique.
A nine-tailed fox?
Like an actual fox with nine tails…
Wait!
So I wasn't just seeing things back then.
Yes, just like in Return of the Legend,
except I have no interest in livers.
And I definitely have no interest
in becoming human.
Wow.
Anyway, that's not why I'm here this time.
Take this. You'll need it sooner or later.
What now…
I WILL GRANT YOUR WISH
Nine-tailed foxes do
this sort of thing too?
Times have changed.
Think of it as a business model.
You're going to be quite wealthy soon.
Wealthy enough to be my client.
Seriously…
Are you messing with me right now?
What?
I mean,
last time, you called me a nobody
and told me not to dream big.
You said all those mean things
about my future.
What changed?
Oh, that?
I guess I misread things at first.
Fate doesn't just change like that.
Whatever, it's fine.
I didn't care about what you said anyway.
I told you.
In a few years,
I'm going to be a really famous athlete.
What I'm talking about
is nothing like
your childish wishful thinking.
I'm telling you
what I saw in your actual future.
Whoa, it's hot! What was that?
I had to show you how to use it.
I'll appear whenever you burn that.
Why couldn't you just say so
instead of scaring me like that?
- Give it back.
- I already did.
But it's gone.
Well, I'll be away for a while
for personal reasons.
And more importantly,
it'd be annoying
if someone who's broke kept summoning me.
So it'll appear naturally
when the time is right.
You can go now. We're done.
Seriously though…
Are you really
not going to tell me your name?
What?
Eun-ho.
My name is Eun-ho.
You should feel honored.
I don't tell just anyone.
I see.
Eun-ho.
Kang Si-yeol?
You must be tired.
I'm Hong Yeon-su,
Team Leader at the Soccer Association.
Remember me?
Oh, right.
It's nice to see you.
Did you already hear the news?
Pardon?
You've been selected
for the youth national team.
Me? On the national team?
Do you have a passport?
You have to leave next week
for overseas training.
Wait a second.
Why am I all of a sudden…
I guess you haven't heard the news yet.
You're a replacement for Hyeon Woo-seok.
As you know, Hyeon Woo-seok is injured,
so there's no clear starter
for that position right now.
I see.
Be prepared. I'll see you then.
You realize
this is a big opportunity for you, right?
- Are you okay?
- Of course.
My face is everything to me,
and I'm scar-free and still handsome.
Whatever.
How long will rehab take?
I don't know. Maybe about a year.
Hey, whatever you do, don't get injured.
This rehab stuff is brutal.
After rehab,
you'll still be able to play, right?
Of course.
What else would I do besides soccer?
Don't worry about me.
Just go and do your best, you punk.
Finish your rehab
and get back as soon as you can.
A year on your ass in rehab?
Total overkill.
"My ass"?
Fine. I'll be back in exactly six months.
Until then,
keep my spot warm
till I'm back, all right?
Whatever, man.
Hey, I came up with a new move.
Since I'm right-footed,
it doesn't matter if my left gets injured.
So, if I do it like this…
Yeah, real good.
Kang Si-yeol?
Hello.
NINE YEARS LATER
What do you think?
It's nice. I like it.
Right?
Islands like this
rarely come on the market.
And it can also be developed.
So, if you build a few villas over there
and bring in tourists--
No need.
I'll be the only one using this island.
Pardon?
I'm going to turn this whole island
into my private retreat.
I see.
But if you're the only one
using such a large island,
how do you plan
on traveling back and forth?
If a typhoon hits,
you'll be stranded all by yourself.
I won't be traveling by boat,
so you don't need to worry.
Anyway, how much was it again?
Right. It's 12 billion won.
It is a high-end property,
but with a bit of negotiation,
we could maybe get it down to 11 billion.
Forget it. It's just a billion won.
What's the point of haggling
over pocket change?
Go check. The money should be in.
Okay, sure.
Excuse me.
Not a single won has come in.
What?
Hold on.
Does that mean
I don't even have 12 billion won left?
Just because I took a few years off?
What would you like to do?
Give me time. I know I can get the money.
But…
can't you make it
a clean 10 billion instead of 11?
Premier League star Kang Si-yeol
signed a massive contract extension
with Thames FC today.
Thames FC announced through their website
that they successfully
re-signed Kang Si-yeol.
They expressed great joy and gratitude
for being able to continue
their journey with their team leader
and franchise star.
Kang Si-yeol's new contract
will last for five years,
making him one
of the highest-paid players in the league.
Becoming the first Asian player
to lead the league
in both goals and assists,
Kang Si-yeol achieved
a career high last season.
This sparked speculation
and media reports about his next transfer.
Amid the growing interest,
international media outlets rushed
to report on his contract renewal.
Officials from several clubs
that had pursued Kang Si-yeol
have expressed their disappointment
following the news.
As Kang Si-yeol has emerged
as a global sports star
beyond South Korea,
soccer fans around the world
are eagerly awaiting his next move.
NICHOLAS: HEART OF VICTORY
Do you know what time it is?
Why are you still in bed?
It's time you started living
like a normal person!
Seriously, it's just soccer.
Just because you quit
doesn't mean your life is over.
Don't try to stop me.
I'm throwing all this out today.
OUR ETERNAL LEGEND
COACH CHA BUM-KUN
This is the Cha Bum-kun Soccer Award.
Why would you throw it away, you crazy…
There's more inside.
HYEON WOO-SEOK
You don't…
have to throw all of them away.
I'm sorry.
About what?
For not succeeding like Si-yeol.
You never know how life will turn out.
You were better than Si-yeol
when you were younger.
For now,
he might be on top.
But you never know
what could happen in 10 or 20 years.
It all depends
on how you live from now on.
Is it…
raining outside?
I guess
we still need more time.
You and I both.
KANG SI-YEOL'S TOP PICK
Welcome.
KANG SI-YEOL'S CHOCOLATE BAR OF CHOICE
He's basically raking in money.
Oh my gosh!
I finally found the Kang Si-yeol bun.
- Which sticker's inside? Check.
- Inside?
I can't really see it.
Hey.
Yes?
I grabbed it first.
I had to hit five convenience stores
just to find it.
No, that's not it.
Do you guys know a lot about Kang Si-yeol?
LIMITED EDITION BUN
What is all this?
It's all Si-yeol's merch. So cute, right?
This is a fan club item
made to celebrate Si-yeol's Golden Boot.
- And this--
- Enough of that!
There's only one thing I'm curious about.
Kang Si-yeol.
How much does he really make?
Didn't you see the recent articles?
Apparently,
he makes 500 million won a week.
And he's in tons of commercials.
I heard he gets paid
over a billion won for each one.
Really?
Then that means he's finally
successful enough to be my client.
What the heck is this?
I AM KANG SI-YEOL
WRITTEN BY KANG SI-YEOL
An autobiography?
How many times
are you going to read that?
What?
It's a good book.
I've never read a book
that resonated with me
quite like this one.
That's because
it's the only book you've ever read.
I AM KANG SI-YEOL
That's because everything is in here.
The hardships of my youth.
My constant effort, discipline,
and patience to overcome those hardships.
Only to be met by inevitable despair.
Despite the endless
resentment and jealousy,
I rose above every limit to achieve
dazzling success.
All of that fits in a single book?
Yeon-su, do you know
what the theme of this book really is?
"I'm the best."
"There may be arrogance,
but never complacency."
I'm so proud that I am me.
Yeah, and I'm also proud of myself
for being your agent all this time.
I really am handsome.
Put it down already.
KANG SI-YEOL IS KILLING IT ON THE FIELD!
- Kang Si-yeol!
HOLD YOUR BREATH
AND FALL FOR SI-YEOL
- Wow, he's signing!
- Please sign mine too!
KANG SI-YEOL IS SEXY…
Thank you.
Long time no see, Si-yeol.
Excuse me…
Where would you like me to sign?
What?
Oh, for crying out loud.
Thank you.
Wait…
Did he seriously not recognize me?
Excuse me, your suitcase is open!
Excuse me, what are you doing--
Since you went ahead
and signed my back without asking,
I'm returning the favor.
What's with that woman?
INCHEON AIRPORT GOES WILD FOR KANG SI-YEOL
DAEHEUNG CITIZENS FC OPEN TRYOUTS
Keep running!
Hey, Woo-seok.
Hello, Coach.
Yeah, hi.
What are you doing here?
Well…
Wait, you're not here
for the tryouts, are you?
WOW, DAEHEUNG CITIZENS SOCCER CLUB
LET'S MAKE HISTORY!
- Here, Woo-seok.
- Thank you.
You need to stir it.
Woo-seok, why are you doing this?
You were cut from this team
not too long ago.
And you're back for an open tryout?
You really think that's going to work?
Please just give me a fair chance, Coach.
I've still got it.
I took a few months off
and got my head straight--
Do you think I don't know
how good you are?
I coached you for years.
This is the K4 League, kid.
It's the fourth division.
Didn't you see how young those kids are?
And you? How old are you now?
Hey, the club says they won't
even offer you a paid contract
because you'd be too expensive.
More than anything,
playing here for a few more years
won't change a thing for you.
Shouldn't you look for something else
while you're still young?
What, you think training here a bit more
is going to get you into the K League?
Or even the national team?
COACH'S OFFICE
I'm in Korea right now.
If you're free later,
do you want to meet at our usual spot?
SI-YEOL
What are you doing? Busy?
Yeah.
What am I doing?
SI-YEOL
Hey, I'm still waiting.
Seriously, he should at least reply.
DELIVERY KING
As you requested,
we've designed it based on
a private theme park concept.
But if we do this,
the costs will skyrocket--
Don't worry about the money.
A huge sum is coming my way soon.
Hold on. Stop there.
Are those the only
dining chairs they have?
I need a luxurious chair,
worthy of a high-end mansion…
Maybe I should make one.
You signed up
for the workshop today, right?
Yeah, I did.
I've done a lot of things in my time.
But I've never tried woodworking,
so I wanted to give it a go.
Oh, I see.
Since it's your first time,
how about a cutting board or a trivet?
A trivet? Please.
I'm going to make a chair.
Not a boring chair like that one.
A chair that perfectly fits
the curves of my body
and wraps me in comfort
while looking elegant and refined.
A chair that's like a work of art.
It's not as easy as it looks.
So, use holds of the same color,
and at the top--
But that is too easy.
I'm going to climb that one.
- Wow.
- She's fearless.
This is way too easy.
What's so fun about this?
Look at her go.
She doesn't seem scared at all.
- What was that?
- She practically flew!
- How is that possible?
- She flew!
You're going to do what?
I'm thinking of putting together
an idol group.
K-pop is all the rage these days.
Gosh, you created the group FOX9?
It's not "FOX9." It's F.O.X.9!
Don't be so out of touch.
Anyway, hitting number one once
really went to their heads.
So I quit that too.
Anyway, I'm all set.
So, what do I do now?
Shall we try again from the beginning?
I did it!
My gosh, I think I have a talent
for woodworking too.
Well, now that you've finished one leg,
shall we try making the other three?
You want me to do more sawing?
Excuse me.
The chair's almost finished,
and he still hasn't summoned me?
I even made sure
the business card appeared.
START
Man, it's freezing.
My muscles are recovering.
- What's that?
- Jeez!
Gosh, that's cold!
You again.
Who are you?
How did you get in here?
Why don't you come out?
I'm here on business.
No, I can't exactly come out right now…
Wait, you can't just barge
into someone's house.
Are you one of my fans?
Even if you are, this is still a crime.
Then report me.
- What?
- I said, go ahead and report me.
Look…
I won't report you.
So could you just toss me
that towel over there?
I need it to get out.
No.
On second thought, this is fine.
So you can just listen from there.
Come on. Just toss it to me!
Hey, you.
Do you really not remember me?
How should I know who you are?
Wait a minute.
Actually, you do look a bit familiar.
Hey!
Do you remember me now?
Long time no see, Si-yeol.
Congratulations. Today is the day.
The day you've been waiting
and hoping for.
Pardon?
You've become quite wealthy.
I WILL GRANT YOUR WISH
Which means you're finally eligible
to be one of my clients.
Tell me. Whatever it is.
What's your wish?
- Well--
- Wait.
For the record, you should
choose your wish very carefully.
Because my fee
is going to be extremely high.
But I don't have one.
- What?
- I don't have any wishes.
I don't think
you quite understand the situation.
This is an incredible opportunity.
Any human would be dying
to ask me for a wish.
I like my life the way it is.
There's nothing I want to change.
Didn't you miss out
on that undefeated title or whatever?
I can make that happen for you.
What's the point of that?
What matters is doing it myself.
Really? That's unexpected.
I didn't take you for that type.
But I can do much more than just that.
For example…
I can change your body
to what it was when you were 20.
Perhaps you didn't get
a good look at me earlier.
I had a checkup recently,
and my biological age is 21.
What about your parents?
Are they suffering from any illnesses?
Once humans reach that age,
something inevitably starts to break down.
I can heal them for you.
I was raised by my grandmother.
My parents passed away when I was young.
Your grandmother, then!
Aren't you worried about her health?
She passed away a few years ago.
Well, that's quite… unfortunate.
Anyway, think about it.
You might not want anything right now,
but life is long.
You may not know it,
but human life is very fragile.
It can be shattered so easily
by even the smallest of things.
When that happens…
you'll be needing my help.
She's still the same.
She comes and goes as she pleases.
Back when my life was whole,
and everything was in its place…
- Enjoy your meal.
- Thank you.
Woo-seok.
I didn't know then.
Ms. Hong! We've got a problem.
You need to see this.
I didn't know
just how fragile human life is
and how easily it can shatter.
I just got back today,
so I don't really have anything to offer.
It's fine. I have to get going soon.
Hey, man. What's going on with you?
Well…
I…
I quit soccer.
- What?
- Why are you so surprised?
We aren't the same.
It wouldn't have been a surprise
if I'd quit at any point.
Wait, you quit?
What, did you retire? When?
No, it's just…
It's been a few months.
And…
I didn't retire. I was cut.
Hey, why didn't you tell me?
It's embarrassing.
How could I tell you something like that?
And what would that have changed?
We…
live in different worlds now,
and worry about different things.
How could you say that?
Is that all our friendship means to you?
I WILL GRANT YOUR WISH
Anyway,
what's this?
Oh, that.
Hey, Woo-seok.
By any chance,
do you have a wish?
I have regretted this moment
for a very long time.
What the…
Here.
You dropped this, Mr. Hyeon.
Oh, I see.
But how do you know my name?
Of course I know you.
Everyone in Korea knows who you are.
Right.
Wait, what?
What do you mean…
Excuse me?
What the…
Where am I?
FOREVER CARE NURSING HOME
What is this?
KANG SI-YEOL
Did you sleep well, Si-yeol?
What's going on right now?
What happened?
Why am I suddenly here?
You made a wish, so a price must be paid.
What?
Wait, what does Woo-seok's wish
have to do--
Didn't I tell you?
I can grant the wish,
but how I do it is up to me.
Once again, your wish has been granted.
NO TAIL TO TELL
Who are you people? What is this?
Since someone became
a world-class soccer player,
someone else must step down
to maintain the balance.
- Are you kidding me? You…
- I have only one principle.
I avoid doing even the smallest good deed
and only avoid doing major misdeeds.
Just do it.
Unless it's beyond your capability.
Fine. And of course, you'll pay the price.
There's a story
behind this object, isn't there?
Eun-ho, I have a wish.
Could you grant it for me?
When you get out, let's do a job together.
Starting now, I'm going on a fox hunt.
Subtitle translation by Susanna Kim