(Seo Ji Hye)
(Go Soo)
(Kim Jae Kyung)
(Yoon Je Moon)
(Reverse)
(Supported by Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism)
(This drama is a work of fiction.)
(Characters, places, and events are not real.)
(Children and animals were filmed under production guidelines.)
Another bottle over here.
Something on your mind?
You usually can't finish one bottle. What's the occasion?
Must be something to celebrate.
Hold on. The food's ready. Have some with your drink.
Don't drink on an empty stomach.
- Come on. Just give me the drink. - All right.
Slow down a little.
I know what you're thinking.
In your imagination,
you've already killed me, haven't you?
- Countless times. - Imagination?
No. You dying by my hand is going to be reality.
And it's only a matter of time.
Really?
You're just running away.
Hiding in there, hoping you'll just be forgotten.
Like a pathetic idiot.
Scared out of your mind.
Right.
I can see why you'd think that.
I guess I'm too stupid to have thought of that.
Cut the nonsense.
As long as I'm alive, you can't even dream of that.
But here's the thing.
The way the world works...
It's not something you can be so sure about.
Because even you could change.
So don't just go...
Thinking a girl like me can't do anything?
You're just humouring me until I run out of steam.
Isn't that it?
Are you crazy?
Does it feel a little more real now?
All this over a little scratch?
I'll make you a promise.
You are going to die at my hands.
No matter what, I swear...
You think you can pull it off? You?
- What? - You think a little blood...
was going to scare me?
Where'd you learn to do that? Your friends? The internet?
Don't tell me you saw it in a movie and decided to copy it.
- What did you say? - You're right.
I actually love it in here.
I get my meals, a roof over my head.
And I don't have to deal with a psycho like you.
You jerk!
You know, I was uneasy about you still being out there,
but seeing you like this really puts my mind at ease.
Now I can finally get a good night's sleep.
Let go of me! Let go!
You can't even control yourself, and you're threatening to kill me?
Just look at the state you're in!
I'll be waiting.
You and I will definitely meet again.
And I'm going to kill you with my own two hands!
No matter what it takes!
I like the sound of that.
It's nice to have someone waiting for me.
(Descent into Darkness)
She's definitely hiding something.
Please, just listen to me and call the police.
She doesn't belong in this house.
She belongs in a psych ward or prison.
Just hold on.
What, you're not even sorry for locking me up in this dump?
You know, the time I'm spending with Ham Myo Jin...
Another 30,000 dollars, now.
Or else, I'm out. For good.
Are you messing with me right now?
I don't think I was a very good driver.
You were a total pro.
I guess the accident made you lose your confidence.
(Korean Beef Restaurant)
Is it really true? I'm not dreaming, am I?
This is the best news I've heard in my entire life.
I could die a happy man right now.
Honestly, the way you talk.
You'll startle the baby.
Right. My grandchild can hear me. I'm sorry, little one.
Tell our little one Grandpa isn't always this silly.
Of course.
The company's been in turmoil, both inside and out,
but it feels like you have made all my worries disappear.
- Thank you. - Not at all, Father.
You'll need to take extra special care of her.
You know how sensitive young people can be.
Let's treat her like she's made of glass.
So she won't think we're another meddlesome set of in-laws.
Give me some credit. Do you think I'm that clueless?
It's just a figure of speech.
- What is it? - The number dialled is unavailable.
It's nothing. A wrong number.
How many times did you cut it?
(2 years ago)
(Bar)
Done already? Go on, try again.
I did everything you asked for.
So what is your problem now?
Darn it.
How many times did you cut it?
It feels like just yesterday you were raising hell during visits.
Were you just waiting all this time for me to get out?
You want to kill me that badly?
Shut it, you jerk!
I get how you feel, but you're wrong.
- You still don't know the truth. - Shut it, you murderer!
Stop this pointless act.
What you think you know isn't the truth!
Bring it on, you idiot!
Darn it.
Is this really the best you've got?
This is the revenge you've waited all this time for?
Kill me.
If you can't kill me,
you're going to die by my hand today.
What have you been doing all this time...
to end up this pathetic?
Revenge?
Give it up.
You're a lost cause.
Are you done running your mouth?
(No to redevelopment that kills the working class)
(Star Karaoke Bar)
I didn't kill your parents.
I gave the police a false confession.
My confession that it was an accident I committed while drunk...
was a lie.
You won't believe me, of course.
- But listen... - Instead of spewing this nonsense,
you should be thinking about your last words.
A mistake...
Do you really think that I just made a mistake?
Do you?
Is that really the best you can come up with?
Your parents died in a sudden house fire.
It was a terrible and tragic event,
and you believe I, of all people, someone you treated like family,
did it by mistake? You really buy that?
Someone else was behind it.
I was paid...
to take the fall for it.
- You took the fall for it? - I'm not sure how he found me.
I was homeless, just wandering.
But a man named Chairman Choi Young Ho...
paid me off.
What are you talking about? And who is Choi Young Ho?
He's so rich, even heads of major corporations have nothing on him.
People like that, when they do something wrong,
they don't solve their problems the way normal people do.
- Especially when the problem's big. - I don't know anyone like that.
And my mom and dad didn't know anyone that rich either!
Don't you get it?
Neither did I.
Why would a complete stranger kill my family?
I don't know the whole story. I've never even met the guy.
I just took the money he sent and did what he wanted.
Cut the nonsense!
You lied to the police for the man who killed my parents?
And took money from a man you've never even met?
Even if it's true, you'll still die by my hand.
Looking at your wrists,
it looks like you haven't had an easy life either.
So just leave it at that. He's way out of your league.
Be straight with me.
If what you're saying is true, then I have a score to settle.
I've been played for a fool for way too long.
Is that so?
Do you think the world just works the way you want it to?
When you can't even handle me?
We'll just have to see who's right, won't we?
Let's hear it. What's your big plan?
I'm going to see this through to the end.
I'll find every last one of them, Chairman Choi Young Ho included.
And I'll be the one to finish them with my own two hands.
And I'm going to be so ruthless,
you can't even begin to imagine.
Nobody can.
If you think you can stop me,
you might as well just kill me.
It'll be quicker that way.
("To Receive Export Industry Order of Merit,")
("Mono Group Chairman Choi Young Ho Returns to Korea")
Tell me.
Tell me everything you know about that monster.
What's your reason?
I asked you for a reason.
For the first time in my life,
I broke with convention for you, and you know it.
- I have no excuse, sir. - Coming the day...
before we announce to say you're pulling your work...
is an insult not just to me,
but to everyone involved in this project.
And that's regardless of whether they know about us or not.
As a fellow professional,
I expect you to show a minimum of common courtesy.
This was the most important challenge...
of my entire life.
And this decision...
I know I may regret it for the rest of my life.
But if I go through with this, regardless of the outcome,
I wouldn't be able to live with myself.
When I first took on this challenge, the very first thing I did...
was go to Chairman Bae of Taejin Group...
and ask for the list of judges.
My plan was to find the top person and win them over.
And that person...
was you, sir.
I didn't think how I got there mattered.
I lived my life without any sense of pride or shame.
I want to make things right.
I'm truly sorry.
No, I'm the one who's sorry.
Sorry that I'm only now seeing who you really are.
My mistake.
They say a lie of that calibre is a work of art.
A man set to be the next chairman of Mono Group...
wouldn't have been that desperate for success.
And if this is about your so-called "conscience as an architect,"
you wouldn't have visited me in secret at this late hour.
You would have made a public confession.
After all, you didn't just deceive me.
You deceived everyone, including the other contestants...
and the judges.
And you're more than smart enough to have figured that out.
I won't ask you what's really going on.
I'm sure it's something more important to you than this.
If you have nothing else to say, you should go now.
Let's not waste any more of each other's precious time.
Darn it, where is she?
Gosh, I was dying waiting for you.
What's this? Hong Kong?
You should've picked someplace farther.
Why China? It's almost next door.
Do you think this is the same as a mainland China passport?
Didn't you know? With a HK passport, most countries don't require a visa.
Seriously?
Just be careful of one thing.
Guys using bad Korean to hit on you.
What are you talking about?
And don't fall for the women begging with crying babies, either.
It's a human trafficking scam every single time.
You can never tell just by looking at them.
So are you telling me to go or not?
You should be careful.
Someone like you would...
- probably fetch a good price. - Shut it. That's messed up.
If you need anything, let me know. I've got a few friends over there.
Pay them, and you'll be safer there than in Korea.
No way. That's awesome.
You've really come up in the world, An So Hee.
So what's the deal?
You're abandoning your beloved homeland?
What deal? I just love Hong Kong.
I'm so jealous.
You must've hit a big score.
What score? I'm just being prepared, that's all.
"Prepared," my foot.
Hey, just send the money already.
I'm out of here.
All right, I'm sending it.
So, you're going to Hong Kong?
What's all this out of the blue?
Don't play dumb.
Weren't you just raising hell, telling me to bring the money?
Did I?
See what I mean?
It's probably a lot more than you were expecting.
Looks like it.
When it comes to money, I'm not one to disappoint.
I know you're resourceful.
Still no word from that wench Ham Myo Jin?
Hey, if you...
met her behind my back, I swear...
Doesn't it get exhausting?
Living like that, always testing people?
You have no idea what I've been through, do you?
I just came back from the dead. I tried to kill that psycho wench,
and I almost got killed instead.
Anyway, what's your plan now?
What do you think the plan is?
Now it's my turn to make a move.
When?
How?
I'll let you know the time and place.
Just be there.
When on earth is that? We don't have much time, okay?
What do you mean, "when"?
I got the money,
so we're doing it now.
I wonder how you knew I was broke.
I guess we're both suited for life in the big house.
You've lost a lot of weight. And it hasn't even been that long.
Is something wrong?
You're skin and bones.
Are you sick or something?
Sick? No.
I've just been getting harassed.
Harassed? By who?
Those jerks.
Is that it? The property holdout?
The development head got mad when he found out I was interfering.
I was wondering why it's been so quiet.
Looks like they hired some real scumbags.
They're animals.
Tell me about it. At your age, come on.
Holing up by yourself in some abandoned building...
Anyone can see right through it.
I worked like a dog my whole life for that one thing.
You think I'm crazy?
Do you?
You think I'll let them take it for pennies on the dollar?
Gi Cheol. For guys like us, ex-cons,
this is our problem.
We underestimate the guys who live by the knife.
Gi Cheol, you need to think this through.
Those guys play rough.
They're untraceable, so if they mess someone up and run,
they have nothing to lose.
They just put a knife to my throat out of nowhere.
I barely made it out alive.
Already?
If they've already gone that far,
it means they're not messing around.
It's nothing to them...
to take you out and bury you.
You need a plan.
Otherwise, they'll really go through with it.
- You get what I'm saying? - That hit...
I'll do it to them first.
This doesn't end until someone is dead.
Darn, that's cold.
Well,
I don't know if I can help,
but seeing you like this after so long...
- makes me feel bad for you. - Cut the nonsense.
Open this.
Darn. You're really out for blood.
You've really been through it, my brother.
So, are you in or out?
If you don't want to, then forget it.
There's a line of guys who'd kill for this money.
You even have to ask, my respected Gi Cheol?
Reporting for duty!
(Guesthouse, buckwheat noodles)
Goodness. Why do you keep asking such things?
You're putting me on the spot.
But you know them well, ma'am.
You used to go to their villa often to deliver meals.
That's because the Chairman and Ms. Hee Soo have a condition.
They can't look at sharp objects.
So they have no knives or scissors at home.
That's why they can't cook at home. It's because of that phobia.
Are you sure nobody saw anything...
on the day I left my phone here?
Well, the thing is...
I went to the villa to get dishes that afternoon...
and saw an unfamiliar car.
So I was looking, wondering what was going on...
when suddenly, someone just popped out of the car.
I was too far away to get a good look,
but I'm pretty sure it was Ms. Hee Soo's fiance.
No, wait. I could be wrong. I was too far to see well, okay?
But isn't that a terrifying thought?
The accident at the villa happened that very night.
- So, could it be... - No. Don't even think about it.
What do you mean, "no"?
Why come here to ask about that day if you're saying it's nothing?
Well...
I was hoping you could help me.
My memory still hasn't come back.
That's right. You did say that, didn't you?
So, are you asking because you know, or because you don't?
Listen, I'm just telling you this because I'm worried.
A detective from Seoul came by a few days ago.
He asked the same questions as you,
acting like the accident was deliberate.
Of course, I didn't tell him what I'm telling you.
I told him off for making trouble and sent him away, as we're on edge.
I know how to read a situation.
You and Hee Soo were so close.
I'm telling you just in case you know something.
Come on, just hear me out, Chief.
It has to be Ham Myo Jin.
We need a warrant for her right away.
I went to his company and met with Ryu Jun Ho.
I also met with the psychiatrist treating Ham Myo Jin.
Darn it.
It looks like Ryu Jun Ho wants to cut ties with Mono Group.
I heard from a legal team junior. Apparently, he's asking for nothing.
- There's no reason to suspect him. - Hey.
Why do you keep making me repeat myself?
Be it Ryu Jun Ho or Ham Myo Jin, bring me concrete evidence first.
Is this how you investigate? All talk, like you?
Chief.
Ham Myo Jin has a psychiatric record. She's still in treatment.
What are you going to write on the warrant application?
"The suspect is a psych patient, but I'm certain she's the culprit."
Is that what you plan to write? And another thing.
If her people submit a doctor's note stating she's in psychiatric care,
what will you do then?
Nothing to say, right? Get out of my way, you punk!
Actually, I do have something to say.
I consulted with the financial crime investigation team.
They've apparently had cases like Ham Myo Jin's before.
Suspects who obstruct investigations by claiming amnesia.
Is that it?
There's more. The doctors at the National Police Hospital.
Even in treatment, they can give an opinion with enough evidence.
And once we have that,
getting the warrant issued shouldn't be a problem.
After that, it's all up to us.
Chief, let's just bring her in first and figure out the rest later.
If we wait and the hospital officially declares...
Ham Myo Jin mentally unfit,
then it's really game over for us.
And then,
you'll be the one to take the fall. You know that, right?
- The nerve of this punk. - Gosh, come on.
No. Whether we crash and burn, or they do,
we have to move on them now.
Chief, I'm asking you to bet on me just this once.
We're out of time. Please.
Woo Jong Rok. Are you absolutely sure about this?
Yes, sir!
You have two days.
Get the paperwork for the warrant and put it on my desk.
Now move.
Yes, sir.
You're the best, Chief!
(Ryu University)
(Vice Chairman Yu Min Ho)
(2 unread messages)
(Take a good, long look.)
Darn it!
Mr. Yu, you may be the Vice Chairman and my senior in this field,
but I'm all out of patience.
I can't say what I'll do next.
So I suggest...
you watch what you do.
Darn it!
So, is it finished now?
I'm so jealous.
Jealous? Of what?
I wish my memory would come back soon,
so I could get back to doing what I love.
- Just like you. - You will.
Hee Soo...
Did I kill her?
Please, I'm begging you.
It's time you stopped thinking about that.
How long are you going to keep dodging the question?
Have you ever thought about...
what your evasiveness is doing to us?
I thought you knew without me having to say it.
Hee Soo...
I killed her.
Not you.
I was the one who started our relationship.
I came up and kissed you first on the beach at Jebu Island,
and I kept coming to see you even though I knew it was pushy.
That's how it all started.
Hee Soo was bound to find out eventually.
In fact, a part of me wanted her to.
The two of us...
We're cruel and shameless.
More than anyone could ever imagine.
I told you not to schedule anything for the time being.
And that I don't need any reports unless I ask for them.
I apologise.
It was so urgent, it slipped my mind.
The head of the Legal Team at headquarters called us.
The head of the Legal Team?
Yes.
They've reviewed the contract from Mono Architecture was founded...
and will send a settlement agreement.
They've agreed to the separation.
Exactly as you requested of the Vice Chairman,
they'll separate Mono Architecture from the parent company...
and execute all necessary terms as stipulated in the contract.
- And their demands? - There's none. Nothing at all.
Sir, did you know about this beforehand?
No. Not at all.
(Atelier)
It's fine you forgot.
Because I remember it all for you.
Whether it be ten times or a hundred times,
I'll keep filling in the blanks for you.
But I'm only going to fill it with my own memories.
And pretend the rest doesn't exist.
So, what can I do daily to help her?
But whenever I take the medicine, it just makes me feel awful.
They do?
That's odd. It's the exact prescription.
I want to know who it is.
Her name is Hee Soo, isn't it?
I'm not sure.
I don't get the impression she was that important to you.
What happened to Hee Soo?
The investigation is still ongoing. We'll find out in time.
Didn't they tell you at the hospital not to agitate the patient?
It's no trouble at all. I'll be better to you from now on.
What made you think of Hee Soo? Where did you find that picture?
So did you design your house yourself?
Our. Our house. Thank you.
If anything had happened to you, I don't know what I would've done.
Our relationship. It started because of me.
I'll do so much better from now on. It'll be okay, so don't worry.
You know earlier wasn't a mistake, don't you?
You left your girlfriend, Hee Soo, and I betrayed my friend.
Hee Soo was abandoned by scum like you and me...
She had no one to trust but you and me.
Want to hear an interesting story?
If there's something you really want,
there's one thing you need to think about first.
You know what that is?
Don't trust...
anyone.
People like me...
who have nothing but the clothes on their backs...
Do you know what the only thing we can count on is?
Insurance.
You can't trust people or money.
They both lie.
What are you talking about?
I gave you a clear warning.
Just...
leave it buried.
I don't need your stupid mind games.
- No! What happened? - My gosh, it's all burned down.
- What is going on? - What's happening?
It was a bolt out of the blue.
(Under investigation, do not cross)
Your parents were the only people I'd ever really grown attached to.
What's all this?
For such good people to die in a senseless accident...
in the blink of an eye.
In that moment, I didn't even feel sad.
I couldn't think straight for days.
In a nice neighbourhood like ours,
how could something like this happen?
What do you mean, "how"? They're saying it was arson.
Word spread like wildfire that it was arson.
- A fire doesn't start on its own. - The question was who did it.
And that's all anyone in town could talk about.
- Oh, dear. - With no motive or suspects,
if the real culprit was one of us,
everyone thought they'd be caught in no time.
He was always hovering around me.
He knew what kind of liquor I drank, what brand of cigarettes I smoked...
He knew everything about me.
So after hanging out with him a few times,
and we got close pretty quickly.
I was amazed that someone besides your parents...
would buy me a drink and keep me company.
Of course, that's still true today.
I'm not sure how to bring this up,
but you know that fire that happened recently?
I feel terrible asking,
but I'm going to need you to take the fall for this.
I'll make it more than worth your while.
My life is on the line here.
I'm begging you.
- Gosh! - Darn.
- What was that? - He thought I was softened up,
because he finally got to the point.
He brought up your parents' accident...
and asked me to take the fall.
He offered me an insane amount of money,
begging me to do it,
saying his life was on the line.
I wanted to kill that jerk right then and there,
but I didn't want to get my hands dirty.
Myo Jin!
- Myo Jin, stop! Don't do this! - Let me go!
Let me go! Get off!
- Stop it. This isn't the way. - Let go! Get off me!
That jerk.
The one who wanted to pin his own crime on me.
I suddenly had to know who that shameless jerk was.
Even if I had to take his money and the blame,
I had to find out who he was.
Looking back on it now,
the reason for my sudden change of heart...
was because of you that day.
Here, look at this.
At first, I didn't even know his name.
He used a go-between for everything when he paid me off.
The person sending the money,
and the one who brings it...
You can't trust either of them.
They're cut from the same cloth.
I figured I'd need some insurance.
So I paid off the courier to find out.
Chairman Choi Young Ho of Mono Group.
("To Receive Export Industry Order of Merit,")
("Mono Group Chairman Choi Young Ho Returns to Korea")
People like you and me...
would never run into someone like him in our lifetime.
He lives in a different world.
And even in that world,
he's in a special class of his own.
If you keep acting the way you are now,
you won't even get close to him...
before you disappear.
Without a trace.
He's still just a murderer.
One who's about to die by my hand.
You can think what you want,
- but that's not how things work. - No.
My life has been over for a long time.
On the day of the accident,
I should have died with my mom and dad,
and the only reason I'm alive is for one thing.
To kill them.
And every single person responsible.
So you will help me.
If you have a single shred of conscience left,
tell me right now.
How are you going to help me?
Or you can die right here...
by my hand.
I already told you.
I've got myself insured.
(Medical record Name: Ham Myo Jin)
Yes.
- They are here. - All right.
Where's Myo Jin?
Didn't she come with you?
It's fine. You can just tell me.
I've analysed Myo Jin's latest MRI,
and she's recovering faster than expected.
The cortex next to her hippocampus needs to compensate for the damage,
but it's not quite working smoothly yet.
She's showing signs of recovery, but that doesn't mean she's stable.
In cases like this,
collaborating with specialists would yield the best results.
No. I told you this can't get out.
It's absolutely necessary. If we start this therapy now,
we can speed up her recovery.
- The specialists could... - No!
Just do exactly what I asked.
I'll be the one to judge Myo Jin's condition.
And I'll take responsibility for her.
Hey.
Do you even intend...
to help her get better?
Based on her condition right now,
her memories could come back at any moment...
if we just take the proper steps in time.
Did you forget what I said...
about crossing the line?
Just because you put money into this hospital,
you think you can do what you want with a patient?
I'd like to keep working with you,
but if that's a problem, then you have a choice to make.
Either keep your mouth shut, or give up the hospital.
The choice is yours,
but I'd watch your mouth from now on.
(Reverse)
I'll handle this myself from now on. I'm prepared for whatever happens.
A warrant's been issued for Ham Myo Jin.
It's a Kutumin-type drug, used for general anaesthesia.
Ham Myo Jin and Jun Ho are together. Why would they need that?
Trying to dump this on trash like me again?
- Some things you can never forget. - No!
But you knew. You knew, and you still accepted me.
And that's your excuse?
- You will pay for this. - So this is it?