ADAPTED FROM THE NOVEL HIDDEN LOVE BY ZHU YI
Sang Zhi.
Can you come with me to buy something?
So?
Grade 11, Class 1's classroom is empty.
Empty?
Yes.
Can I search inside?
The classes are over.
There are no students left.
Okay.
If you see her later,
can you tell her to wait here?
-Sure. -Thank you.
You're welcome.
XIANGJUAN NOODLES
Wait, Zhenru.
The stationery shop is that way.
I want to visit the one by the alley.
Okay.
We have to hurry up.
I don't want to keep my brother waiting.
Zhenru.
Is something bothering you?
What happened?
Nothing.
Nothing?
Sang Zhi, do you have money with you?
Good.
I was afraid I didn't bring enough.
We should have enough.
I did bring an extra 50 yuan today.
What do you want to buy?
How much does it cost?
Sang Zhi.
Let's go over there.
Over there? Why?
I want
to visit the cybercafe.
But our teacher told us not to go there
because it's dangerous.
Let's not go there.
Just go with me this once, please?
I promise I won't go there again.
Just come with me.
Zhenru, we shouldn't go there.
Let's go to the stationery shop.
Come.
Never mind.
I'll go there by myself.
Zhenru!
Zhenru, wait for me!
Don't go there alone!
Zhenru!
Sir.
Have you seen a female high school student
with an injured leg passing by here?
I think she went into the alley up ahead
with another student.
The alley up ahead?
Thank you.
What took you so long?
We've been waiting a long time.
My teacher kept us late.
Really?
I thought you fled.
And we were thinking
we would visit you at school tomorrow.
I don't have money.
My parents didn't give me any.
No money?
Remember what you said yesterday?
My friend here has some.
How much?
Is this all you have?
Do you have to be so broke?
And crippled at that.
Come. Frisk her.
She has nothing.
You have no money,
but your parents must have some.
Tomorrow, after school,
meet me here with the money.
Did I make myself clear, cripple?
You too.
Understood?
Yes.
That's a good girl.
See you tomorrow.
Let's go.
Gosh. What are we now? Beggars?
Do you know them?
I don't.
I met them in the cybercafe yesterday.
Sang Zhi, I'm sorry.
I have no more money
and my parents wouldn't give me more.
I had no other choice.
Sorry, Sang Zhi. Don't be mad at me.
They just want money.
They won't do anything to us.
Besides, the school break is coming up.
They'll move on once the break starts.
Sang Zhi.
You ignored me
after Fu Zhengchu's birthday.
You didn't care
when I fell on Sports Day.
And I was wondering
why you suddenly talked to me today.
When you get home,
tell your parents everything.
Just tell them the truth.
Tell them to inform the school.
Don't listen to the bullies.
They're just trying to intimidate you.
Your parents will help you, won't they?
Go home now.
Bye.
Sang Zhi, I'm sorry.
Sang Zhi.
-Sang Zhi, sorry. -Don't follow me!
Sang Zhi!
Where were you?
Why didn't you answer your phone?
Didn't Sang Yan tell you to wait for me?
What's wrong?
It's okay.
I'm here.
CHAPTER FOUR, HIDDEN APPROVAL
MY SECRET
Thank you.
Drink something.
-Thank you, Jiaxu. -Don't mention it.
What happened to your hand?
Did someone bully you?
Why didn't you tell me?
I don't want to cause you trouble.
Sang Yan also told me
that you are very busy,
so I shouldn't bother you.
But don't worry, Jiaxu.
I won't hide this from anyone.
I'll tell my parents when I get home.
Don't worry.
Where did they hit you?
They didn't hit me.
Didn't they? Look at your hand.
They only tapped my cheek
and took my wallet.
I hurt my hand on my own.
They told me
to come to them with the money tomorrow.
Jiaxu.
I'll be fine.
Don't worry.
Why would you go to a back alley?
A friend brought me there.
Who?
She was being extorted too.
She was scared,
so she brought me with her.
Instead of telling her teacher or parents
about the extortion,
why did she bring you with her?
She was worried
that those bullies would take revenge
if she told on them.
You don't need a friend like that.
Also,
always tell your parents
when something happens.
They will always protect you.
Understood?
How do you go home
when Sang Yan picks you up from school?
We take a bus.
A bus?
What if someone steps on your foot on the bus?
Give me a moment.
Okay.
Okay, come on.
Where are we going?
I'm seeing you home.
Come.
Get on.
Sit tight.
Hold on tight.
Don't have another fall.
Have you taken this route home before?
No.
Isn't the scenery nice?
Jiaxu.
Where is Sang Yan?
I think he went to an interview.
An interview?
For a part-time job?
No.
Graduation is coming up,
so everyone is looking for jobs.
Are you going back to Yihe
to work?
I haven't decided yet.
I quite like Nanwu too.
Do you feel better now?
You're in 11th grade now.
You will face more and more stress,
so you need to find a way
to decompress.
For example, cycling.
If you're ever overwhelmed by studying,
don't keep it bottled up.
Tell Sang Yan or me.
We have been through this.
I'll be grateful if he doesn't make fun of me.
The next time he makes fun of you,
let me know.
Here.
Take this.
Tell your parents what happened today.
Take it.
Go home now.
Bye, Jiaxu.
Bye.
I have a secret.
I don't want to admit it,
but
I seem
to have fallen for him.
Duan Jiaxu.
I HAVE A SECRET
OCTOBER 27TH, TUESDAY
I SEEM TO HAVE FALLEN FOR YOU
He's so handsome.
Little demon!
Come back.
I'm here.
Come!
Tell me.
Did those extorters tell you to meet them today?
We don't have to do that.
Lead the way.
-We really don't have to. -Lead the way!
Listen up.
They messed with the wrong people.
Go. Lead the way.
Don't worry. We're here.
We'll teach them a lesson.
Come on. This way.
It's not embarrassing at all.
We're here.
Is it here?
Stay here, little demon.
Describe their appearance to me.
One of them
has dyed hair.
Another one
has short hair.
One has long hair.
They are
three girls about this tall.
One is shorter.
Why didn't you tell us they are girls?
You didn't ask.
I told you not to do this.
I can't do this against girls.
Let's head back.
No way.
Girls or boys,
they can't bully my sister.
But four boys going against three girls
doesn't sound right.
Yes.
How about this?
Do you want out?
Stay here with her.
You and you, come.
Let's go!
Wait for me, Sang Zhi.
-Hold this for me. -Okay.
Don't worry.
Junwen, will they get into a fight?
Maybe, if the bullies are boys.
But you said they are girls.
They will probably just talk to them.
Help me open it.
Okay.
Does your wound still hurt?
Did you hear that girl just now?
-She's so meek. -That cripple.
Who are you?
Wait.
What are you doing?
Smoking at such a young age?
I heard
that you extorted money from my friend.
I don't know you guys.
Who are you?
It doesn't matter. I know you, that's enough.
You extorted 50 yuan from my sister
and even slapped and threatened her.
I didn't threaten her.
I only took 50 yuan from her.
I didn't do anything else.
Don't make things up.
I…
I only took 50 yuan from her.
I can give it back.
I must settle this score with you
even if you only took two yuan from my sister.
Give me the wallet.
Hurry up!
How old are you?
Why are you hustling in the street
instead of studying?
You got the money.
Mind your own business and leave.
We got the money.
But there's one more thing.
Which of you
is the leader?
Is it you?
Are you scared now?
Little girl.
Violence cannot solve anything.
Only the weak
bully those weaker than them.
Do you hear me?
Focus on your studies
and don't do this again.
Let's go.
How did you settle it?
By scaring them? Tell me. I'm curious.
Listen, this is what I told them.
I kill ten people every month
and I've hit my quota this month.
I'll return next month to kill them.
Come on. Don't bluff.
-I-- -Yes, I'm messing with you.
Fine.
Kiddo.
The way you eat makes you look like a pufferfish.
You're the pufferfish.
Really?
Give me a lollipop then.
I'll show you a handsome pufferfish.
Please.
Have mine.
Don't tease her. Here.
Save it for yourself.
You can have it.
What? No.
I don't want it.
I have had it before.
Jiaxu.
Get yourself some candy.
I was joking.
Keep it. Buy candy for yourself.
Think of it
as returning your 20 yuan.
Okay.
Then…
Thank you for giving me spending money.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
What do you mean?
You're so annoying.
Who said you could have it?
Hey!
Give it back.
I already sucked on it.
Do you still want it?
Hey, give it back.
Give it back!
I still have one here.
Wait. Give it back!
Why do I get the feeling
that she seems more like Jiaxu's sister?
You can be his sister too.
Come on. Let's go eat.
NOVEMBER 11TH, WEDNESDAY
SANG YAN SAID THAT JIAXU SEEMS MORE LIKE MY BROTHER
If only he really was my brother.
He is the warmest person I know.
In moments of need,
he always gives me care and strength.
I want to grow up faster
and become a better person.
I want to be just like him,
someone who gives warmth to others.
Yin Zhenru
is transferring schools for personal reasons.
She will not come to class anymore.
Sorry for the trouble, sir.
Let's go.
Do you see what you've done?
Many students have fallen victim
to extortion and blackmailing
in nearby areas lately.
The school takes this seriously.
The bullies
have been given disciplinary measures.
The police have also lectured them.
If you find yourself
in a similar situation,
you must notify the teachers and your parents right away.
We will protect you.
Sang Zhi.
-I'm sorry. -One last thing.
You should focus on your studies
at your age.
Do not loiter in shady areas.
The topic for today's written exam
is "My Dream."
Pass the exam papers to the back.
ESSAY TOPIC: MY DREAM
Sit here.
Watch from here.
Zhizhi.
Zhizhi, we want to talk to you.
Sit here.
Be careful.
Come forward.
Here, Zhizhi.
These are the results of your final exams.
Take a look.
XURI MIDDLE-HIGH SCHOOL GRADE 11 FIRST-TERM FINAL EXAM RESULTS
PHYSICS, 66 POINTS
I passed physics!
Do you think you did well?
No.
I don't like physics,
so I didn't pay attention during class.
I skimmed through the textbook before the exam
and I actually passed.
Are you proud of it?
No.
Zhizhi,
you study for yourself
and your future,
not for us.
Have you thought about what you want to do
in the future?
What is your dream?
This was an essay topic during the exams.
What did you write?
I wrote that my dream is
peace and love.
For everyone to care for each other.
Look, Zhizhi.
What your mom and I are talking about
is what kind of career
you want for yourself.
I want to draw.
Can I draw for a living?
Is that all?
Either way, physics will not play a part
in my life.
I think.
Zhizhi.
Before you have figured out what you want to do with your life,
you should get some help with physics.
Your class teacher and I talked and agreed
that you're weak in some subjects.
We'll hire a tutor during winter break
to help you with physics.
No use seeking help.
Ask yourself honestly.
Do you need help with physics?
So you're the tutor that Dad hired?
Yes.
Listen now.
I scored over 270 points in the science portion of the NCEE.
Don't underestimate me.
Snobbish, aren't you?
Rightfully so.
Hey, come on.
You scored 66 points.
How dare you criticize me?
Score 666 and we can talk.
I don't want you to be my tutor.
Bye.
Sit down.
Pay attention.
Let me see.
Okay.
Kepler's laws of planetary motion.
Listen to me.
Do you know the three laws?
No? Okay.
This is the formula of gravity.
What is F? F is the force of gravity.
G is the gravitational constant.
M is the mass.
You have a capital M and a lowercase m.
Both are masses.
What is R? R is the distance between two bodies.
-Next question. -Wait. What is this R?
All Rs stand for distance. Moving on.
Wait. Don't move on just yet.
F is…
This is the third time now!
-F is the force of gravity. -Wait! F and G are different.
Both Ms are Masses.
-What is R squared? -This R is distance!
You didn't explain anything!
You're too dumb.
It's not my fault.
Sang Yan, you'll pay for this!
You're done for!
-Die! -You don't get anything.
Die, Sang Yan!
Mom!
Are you scared now?
Go back and study!
She's too dumb.
He's impatient.
-Get someone else. -Get someone else.
Okay, we'll find another tutor.
I don't want you to bicker all day long
and ruin my wife's mood.
I didn't say anything.
It's mainly because your dad
can't put up with this.
Also, can she be tutored
in her own room
instead of in my room?
-No. -Why not?
I'm not the one being tutored.
I don't want a stranger going into my room.
I don't want a stranger
going into my room either!
Enough. Can you two stop arguing?
Sang Yan.
Do you think your dad and I
will let a stranger into your sister's room?
That's right. I'll be worried too.
Yes, I'll be scared too.
I see.
I'm just human CCTV.
I get it.
Then be good CCTV.
Zhizhi.
I thought you were asleep.
Mom, I drew Sang Yan.
MY NAME IS SANG YAN
You gave him a pair of glasses.
Smell this.
Isn't it fragrant?
I already found a tutor for you.
At 10 a.m. tomorrow,
he will come here to tutor you.
Sleep soon and wake up early.
Drink this oat milk.
Good night.
Sleep soon.
She found another tutor.
She found someone so quickly!
I don't want a tutor!
I don't want lessons!
Silly dog!
Maybe I should sneak out tomorrow morning.
That way,
the tutor will know I'm difficult
and will quit on the spot.
Xiaoduan, this is the 3D model document.
Crosscheck and return it by the end of the day.
Okay.
Li Xun.
Jiaxu.
Your optimization is perfect.
Thank you.
Well done.
It's my job.
By the way,
I remember from your resume
that you're from Yihe.
Yes.
I'm also from Yihe.
-Really? -What was your high school?
I went to No. 2 High School.
I went to Yihe No. 3 High School.
I knew it.
I would have heard
of such a handsome junior.
I know you're graduating soon.
Will you return to Yihe?
I'm still undecided.
-Still undecided? -Yes.
Listen, this decision will determine your career.
Make sure to pick a city you like.
I see.
The company will assign me to the headquarters in Yihe
for the A Dream of Jianghu project next year.
If you're interested in returning to Yihe,
we can work together.
Thank you, Li Xun.
I'll think about it.
Do think about it.
I'll let you work.
-Okay. -You have a bright future.
What's up?
Buddy, are you working late today?
That depends on what you're about to say.
Help me pick up your sister.