Subtitle by Kisskh.Asia Translator [ Admin Qari ]
May I be like the stars
and you like the moon.
As long as the world remains,
so shall we.
I only wish to stay with the one I love,
watching every sunrise and sunset.
I want to be with you forever.
Eternals and demons walk different paths.
You and she are ultimately different.
Have you ever
truly cared for me?
No.
Never.
In this life and the next, through all lifetimes…
May we live and die together,
and share life and death as one.
[Moonlight Mystique]
[Episode 5]
What are you doing?
You have the antidote.
Why didn't you save us?
Why?
Step back!
Step back! Don't push!
[Bai Residence]
Master,
Cold Spring Palace has spread the news
that the Governor's Mansion has the antidote.
All the uninfected people in the city are besieging the Governor's Mansion.
Bai Shuo was sent out of the city by her father.
Bai Xun doesn't know that Bai Shuo is afflicted with Nether Poison.
Without Ghost Grass to suppress it,
won't she go mad?
Uncle Wang,
stop! Send me back!
I said stop!
Stop the carriage!
Lady Shuo!
You can't go!
You can't go back!
I know my father well.
If I leave,
he will die.
-Let go!
-Lady Shuo!
The governor's order was a military command.
No matter what happens,
I must take you away.
Military orders must be obeyed.
I must take you away!
Okay.
I'll go get the horse.
Sorry.
With this horse,
you won't be able to reach Ning'an City before it's destroyed.
Fan Yue?
She didn't go mad?
It seems the Nether Poison doesn't work on her.
Is it because the Desireless Stone is in her body?
If you want to return to Ning'an City,
I'll take you back.
You three,
quickly go and restrain the people who have gone mad in the city.
Yes.
Master Bright Moon?
Fan Yue,
let her go!
Are they the Eternals you've been wanting to become?
The Lanling Eternals?
So this is Bai Shuo?
Yes.
Leave now.
Fan Yue,
there has long been an agreement between the Eternal and Demon Races
to not harm the Human Race.
Yet you not only stole the Desireless Stone,
but also caused chaos among the Human Race.
So what?
Jin Yao,
the Desireless Stone and Bai Shuo are both mine.
If you don't want your Lanling Sect
to be wiped out in Ning'an today,
get out of my sight.
How arrogant!
Shuo!
The city is full of demons.
They all want to take the Desireless Stone.
It's too dangerous for you to stay here.
With Master and Uncle Master here,
they will surely keep Uncle Bai safe.
Come back to Lanling Sect with me.
Let go!
Chong Zhao,
I won't trust
those who have lied to me.
I'm going back to find my father.
I don't have time to listen to your nonsense.
Shuo!
Let her go!
[Peaceful]
Grand Master,
as you expected,
Bai Shuo was brought back by Fan Yue.
The Five Eternals of Lanling have also arrived
and are currently fighting with Fan Yue.
Although the Five Eternals of Lanling can't kill Fan Yue,
they can at least hold him off.
See?
Remember,
the Nether Poison is just the prelude
to the chaos in Ning'an City.
Go.
Bai Shuo will be here soon.
Yes.
I know what to do.
[Bai Residence]
Give us the antidote!
Sheathe the swords!
Governor,
please give me the antidote
and save my baby!
Please save him.
Please.
Please save him!
Please save him, Governor!
Please!
Governor.
There's no antidote
in the Governor's Mansion.
I can't save him.
You don't have the antidote?
It's impossible!
How can you not have the antidote?
You just don't care about us!
Give us the antidote!
We know you have the antidote!
Take it out!
Bai Xun!
Father!
Look at me!
Bai Xun!
Stop yelling.
With the barrier here,
they can't hear
or see you.
What exactly do you want?
Let me pass!
Don't be impatient.
Since you've come back,
how about watching a show?
If you don't have the antidote,
why are you still alive?
Bai Xun!
We've always trusted you,
admired you,
and regarded you as the governor!
You're even unwilling to save a child!
Where's your conscience?
Bai Xun,
you're selfish
and indifferent to the people in the city!
What kind of governor are you?
You're even worse than a beast!
You don't deserve to be the governor!
You're useless!
Give us the antidote!
Are you even human?
You find it unbelievable, right?
From respect to hatred,
it only took one day.
How could you not care about us?
Now that things have come to this,
how about we make it even more exciting?
Governor?
Screw you!
The governor has gone mad!
Governor?
Governor!
He's gone mad! Run!
Let's run!
The outside is full of madmen!
Only the Governor's Mansion is safe!
Where else can we escape to?
Bai Xun is highly skilled in martial arts.
While he hasn't completely lost control,
let's kill him now!
Otherwise, when he completely loses his sanity,
-we'll be the ones who die!
-Kill him!
They are the people Bai Xun wants to protect—
ungrateful,
murderous.
Even I, a demon, can't compare to them.
Bai Shuo,
why don't you stop being a human
and join our Demon Race?
The Desireless Stone is inside you.
If you work for the Grand Master,
he
will surely be pleased.
Shut up!
Detoxify my father!
As you know,
there's no cure for this poison.
It's either death or madness.
Today,
someone has to die.
Kill him!
Die!
Stop!
Stop beating him!
Beat him!
Father, wake up!
What are you doing?
Governor!
Stop it!
Father!
No!
Don't bite my father!
Father, wake up! Father!
Let go of my father!
Don't bite my father!
Go.
Go!
Father, wake up! Father!
Father!
Governor!
I'll kill you!
I swear I'll kill you!
I'm incompetent!
I can't save you.
This maniac condition...
really has no cure!
Bai Yu!
Hurry!
Take the people out of Ning'an City!
Father!
I don't know...
why Ning'an is suffering this calamity,
but I know...
♫Across thousands of miles♫
that there are gods in this world!
Gods!
I, Bai Xun,
♫The pain of parting lingers♫
am willing to offer my life
to seek your mercy!
♫ I light a lamp with no wick to carry me through the rest of my days♫
Please descend upon Ning'an
and save
the people of Ning'an!
♫Flowers in the wind, sand in the water♫
I am willing
to exchange my life
for the peace...
Governor! Governor!
No!
Governor!
Of a city!
Father!
♫May I ask, what do the gods see in the world?♫
Governor!
♫Sadness from infatuation, anger, and parting♫
♫My love brought tears♫
♫Greed for gathering, for holding, and for completeness♫
♫I was never a flower, but I withered on my own♫
♫I fell between your brows and became a good fruit♫
♫The grand dream of life is hard to let go♫
♫Searching for the path, the answers, yet found nothing♫
♫With a heart full of compassion for the people, I let go of my obsessions♫
♫I cultivated myself to be free of desires, offering myself as a sacrifice to the moon♫
♫The daylight burns through, and the stars shine bright♫
♫Through the Buddhist dust, I see the moon in the sky♫
♫I am but a mortal, destined to fade♫
♫But I went through a thousand calamities for a promise♫
♫I severed emotions, desires, and the fate between you and me♫
♫To protect the world for eternity♫
♫The flowers flew away♫
♫My tears are streaming down like rain♫
Don't sleep.
♫Light my heart's lamp, cast away attachments, and ask the world♫
You can't sleep!
I don't allow you to die!
Didn't you say you would wait with me
♫On the vast sea, you and I♫
for Xi to come back?
Xi hasn't come back yet.
You can't die!
It's all your fault!
It's because of you!
I'll kill you!
Father,
I can save you.
I'll find someone to save you.
Hang in there.
I will find someone to save you.
[Bai Residence]
Hang in there.
♫Sadness from infatuation, anger, and parting♫
♫My love brought tears♫
♫Greed for gathering, for holding, and for completeness♫
♫I was never a flower, but I withered on my own♫
♫I fell between your brows and became a good fruit♫
♫The grand dream of life is hard to let go♫
♫Searching for the path, the answers, yet found nothing♫
♫With a heart full of compassion for the people, I let go of my obsessions♫
♫I cultivated myself to be free of desires, offering myself as a sacrifice to the moon♫
♫The daylight burns through, and the stars shine bright♫
♫Through the Buddhist dust, I see the moon in the sky♫
♫I am but a mortal, destined to fade♫
♫But I went through a thousand calamities for a promise♫
♫I severed emotions, desires, and the fate between you and me♫
♫To protect the world for eternity♫
One of the Five Contemplations
was awakened?
It's golden.
Kindness?
The first Contemplation is not killing,
but kindness!
Bai Shuo.
Let's go.
Did you see that?
Are they immortals?
My baby is cured!
Sect Leader.
He's really cured!
They are really immortals!
-Are you okay? Let me see.
-I'm fine.
Great!
We're fine now.
I didn't expect to see you again.
Thank you, immortals! Thank you, immortals!
Put her down!
The Human Race has suffered heavy losses.
How about we call a truce between the Eternals and demons today?
Bai Xun just died.
Aren't you going to let them
say their final goodbyes?
The Lanling Sect always stands by its word.
Are you afraid
that we'll take her in front of you?
Master,
don't believe him.
You're injured.
We should take Bai Shuo back to the Polar Realm as soon as possible.
The road ahead is not yours to take.
Sir?
Is this the Lunar Hidden Sea?
Yes.
And no.
This is your sea of consciousness.
What you see
is just my consciousness.
Bai Shuo,
your father's death
caused you great pain.
Sir,
I'm begging you, please save my father.
You saved me ten years ago,
which was already a great kindness.
I know I have no right to ask for more,
but my father loved the city and protected the people
with loyalty throughout his life.
Until the moment of his death,
he never gave up on being kind.
He is the one who truly deserves to live.
Please, I beg you to save him.
Or...
or give my life to him
and let him live.
You want to die?
I don't want to die.
But I have no other choices now.
Only gods can bring someone
back to life.
No.
You're wrong.
The one who can interfere with life and death isn't me—
it's you.
Me?
Eternals can't save him,
and demons can't save him.
I'm just a mortal.
How can I save him?
As long as you have enough power,
you can.
Enough power?
How can I have enough power?
Gather the contemplations
and reignite the Desireless Stone.
Reignite the Desireless Stone?
Bai Shuo,
remember,
the meaning of your existence
isn't to repay someone's kindness,
nor to live for anyone else.
The Desireless Stone entering your body
is both a serendipity
and a part of the cycle of cause and effect.
When the heavens bestow great responsibilities,
they come with trials.
There's no way ahead.
No destruction, no construction.
You
must carve your own path.
What is my own path?
Sir,
who are you?
One day,
you will know.
Father.
Where is my father?
[Noble Virtue]
[Memorial Tablet of My Late Father, Bai Xun]
♫I remember that moonlit night♫
♫The flowers that bloomed once in a lifetime♫
♫I remember that word of concern♫
♫But unfortunately, I didn't get to answer♫
♫I remember that drop of tear♫
♫It dried in the wind♫
♫The one in the autumn wind♫
♫How many times have I seen you in my dreams?♫
♫That year, that year♫
♫The leaves fell unnoticed after the flowers bloomed♫
♫I'm afraid the autumn wind will stir up memories♫
♫They unfold, one page after another♫
♫That year, that year♫
♫The flowers flew under the moon, filling the sky♫
♫Falling to the mud, burying the memories♫
♫Layer after layer♫
♫Another year passed♫
♫That year, that year♫
♫The leaves fell unnoticed after the flowers bloomed♫
♫I'm afraid the autumn wind will stir up memories♫
♫They unfold, one page after another♫
♫That year, that year♫
♫The flowers flew under the moon, filling the sky♫
♫Falling to the mud, burying the memories♫
♫Layer after layer♫
♫Another year passed♫
Mom.
Ning'an City is in this state
because of the Eternal Race's negligence.
But isn't the Bright Moon Palace also responsible for this?
You're injured now.
And we're not afraid of war.
If the 72 sects of the Eternals unite,
the Bright Moon Palace would have no chance to win.
Do you think
you can use this threat on me?
It's not a threat.
If it really comes to a war,
it's still the common people who will suffer.
This is not what we want.
You must have taken Bai Shuo in
out of compassion, right?
Compassion?
Ridiculous.
Whether it's out of compassion or not,
only you know.
Whether she joins the Eternals
or the demons,
let Bai Shuo decide for herself.
Does it hurt?
Wipe it off.
Thank you, Grand Master.
Do you know
why I punished you?
Because I saved Chong Zhao,
which led to the failure of framing the blame.
Lanling Sect is now targeting
the Cold Spring Palace.
Wrong.
When you first intervened to save him,
I told you
I wouldn't punish you, so I didn't.
What angered me is that
you made the same mistake for the second time.
Do you think I couldn't see through it?
In front of
the Governor's Mansion,
you took the initiative to step in
and lend a hand,
and it was still to save Chong Zhao.
It seems our Lady Fu Ling
has someone special on her mind now.
Unfortunately,
he is an Eternal.
I can accept any punishment
from Grand Master.
But it's not your place to sow discord between us.
That's right.
But I'm also curious,
what exactly
are your feelings
for that Chong Zhao now?
I have no particular feelings for him.
As I said before,
besides repaying his kindness,
I also want him to join our Cold Spring Palace
and work for you.
Great.
Well then,
let's do as you said
and turn him into a demon.
How about this?
I...
will give you some more time.
One month.
How about one month?
Within one month,
make him work for our Cold Spring Palace.
If you fail,
then
I'll have to step in
and end him.
Understood?
Yes.
Go.
I allowed you to kowtow to him
because he deserved it.
But Chong Zhao,
from now on,
you're no longer a member of the Bai family.
Ever since my father was chosen as the governor,
he prepared this coffin.
I know he was not afraid of death,
but I never imagined
he would leave me like this.
The one who always wants to cultivate immortality is me.
The one who was self-righteous
and brought the Eternals and demons upon us was me.
The one who should have borne the consequences was supposed to be me,
but why was it my father?
What did my father do wrong?
Why was he the one who died in the end?
Why was he the only one who died?
It was all my fault.
I failed to protect Uncle Bai.
Shuo,
go back to the Eternals with me.
Now that the Demon Race is eyeing the Desireless Stone,
only the Eternals can protect you.
That day, in the ruined house outside the city,
you said you'd protect my father.
In Ning'an City,
you also said that with your master and uncle master there,
♫What kind of flower would never bear fruit?♫
you would definitely keep my father safe.
The Eternals,
♫What kind of fruit never sees a flower?♫
the demons,
and the humans in this world—
I just realized that I never truly understood them.
♫Withstanding the stillness, you are a broken piece of me♫
I thought Eternals could always save humans,
♫I am the fruit to your flowers♫
but it turned out that it was my wishful thinking.
I was wrong.
Logically,
I have no right to blame you.
But emotionally,
I can't help but blame you.
So, Chong Zhao,
from now on,
we have nothing to do
with each other.
♫Across thousands of miles♫
But there's one thing
♫The pain of parting lingers♫
I hope you'll tell me honestly.
Who cast the demonic poison in Ning'an City?
You want revenge?
♫ I light a lamp with no wick to carry me through the rest of my days♫
Tell me!
The Demon Race, Cold Spring Palace,
Zhen Yu,
♫Flowers in the wind, sand in the water♫
and Fu Ling.
Zhen Yu,
Listen to me, Shuo.
Don't be impulsive.
Zhen Yu is one of the three great Demon Kings.
If you provoke him,
-he will surely…
-Don't worry.
I will live well.
I'll live to the day when I can take revenge
for my father myself.
♫The flowers flew away♫
♫My tears are streaming down like rain♫
♫Light my heart's lamp, cast away attachments, and ask the world♫
[Memorial Tablet of My Father, Bai Xun]
♫On the vast sea, you and I♫
-Governor!
♫May I ask, what do the gods see in the world?♫
♫Sadness from infatuation, anger, and parting♫
♫My love brought tears♫
Governor!
♫Greed for gathering, for holding, and for completeness♫
Beat him!
♫I was never a flower, but I withered on my own♫
♫I fell between your brows and became a good fruit♫
Kill him!
♫The grand dream of life is hard to let go♫
♫Searching for the path, the answers, yet found nothing♫
♫With a heart full of compassion for the people, I let go of my obsessions♫
♫I cultivated myself to be free of desires, offering myself as a sacrifice to the moon♫
♫The daylight burns through, and the stars shine bright♫
♫Through the Buddhist dust, I see the moon in the sky♫
♫I am but a mortal, destined to fade♫
♫But I went through a thousand calamities for a promise♫
♫I severed emotions, desires, and the fate between you and me♫
♫To protect the world for eternity♫
Governor, farewell.
They forced Bai Xun to his death.
How dare they come and see him off?
Humans are so hypocritical.
Jin Yao used magic that day.
These humans have already forgotten about
the Eternals, demons, and the Nether Poison.
In their memories,
Bai Xun simply died of an illness in his prime,
with no connection to them.
These Eternals
sure are good at whitewashing.
Master,
when will we bring Bai Shuo back to the Demon Race?
[Tomb of My Father, Bai Xun]
Father,
I'm leaving.
The Eternal Race erased the memories of everyone in the city.
They don't know what they've done,
yet they're mourning you,
seeing you off,
[Tomb of My Father, Bai Xun]
and weeping for you.
You guarded a city
for your whole life,
and even gave up your life.
Was it worth it?
Chong Zhao asked me to go back to the Eternals with him.
If it were in the past,
I would be so happy.
But now I understand.
The Demon Race is heartless,
the Eternal Race is detached,
and the Human Race is powerless.
No one can be relied on,
and no one can be trusted.
Relying on myself
is better than relying on others.
Don't worry.
One day,
I will be stronger than the Eternals and demons
and I will go to the Cold Spring Palace to avenge you.
[Tomb of My Father, Bai Xun]
If you want to get revenge on the Cold Spring Palace,
you don't need to go through all this trouble.
Who allowed you to come to my father's grave?
Don't you want to get revenge on the Cold Spring Palace?
Join my Polar Realm,
and I'll help you.
The Cold Spring Palace deserves to die.
But what makes you any better?
Did you really have no intention of using me
when you gave me the Ghost Grass?
I remember you saying
it was an equal exchange,
and that gain or loss didn't matter.
The condition for an equal exchange was that my father was alive!
♫No matter if I'm drunk or not, I just want to be reckless once♫
I don't expect a demon to be good,
♫Because love is thrilling♫
but I will never allow you to disturb my father's peace.
Get lost!
♫If you tear open my heart♫
♫I can hold you a little tighter♫
♫This pain will gradually cool♫
I do plan to leave this city.
However,
♫Time withers the moonlight♫
you must go with me.
Why should I go with you?
♫All that's left is pitch darkness♫
You don't have the right to choose.
♫I want to tear apart♫
♫This sky for you♫
Who says I don't?
♫A lifetime of guarding everything with you♫
♫Crossing the abyss to fulfill our vow♫
♫I'll leap without a thought for tomorrow♫
♫This moment feels like forever♫
♫I've missed too much time in my life♫
I told you
not to be disrespectful in front of my father's grave
♫I'll throw myself into this flame for you♫
and disturb his peace.
Fan Yue,
♫Even if I'll perish♫
I am just a human.
♫At least I can still kiss your face♫
In your eyes, I'm as insignificant as an ant.
♫Burn out my waning moon♫
But even ants will bite
when cornered.
♫Exchanging a lifetime of passion♫
If it weren't for your stirring things up
and watching from the sidelines,
my father wouldn't be lying here!
Fan Yue, remember,
I, Bai Shuo, never let my grudges go,
nor let my anger fade on its own.
You never let your grudges go,
and never let your anger fade on its own?
Are you really not afraid of death just to vent your anger?
I am.
But I'm more afraid that my father can't rest in peace.
A heartless demon like you
would never understand what family means,
nor would you understand my father's loyalty.
Father! Father!
Father!
Let her go!
Without strength,
drawing your sword would only be self-humiliation.
Fan Yue,
if you forcefully take her away,
you'll be the enemy of the entire Lanling Sect.
Fine by me.
♫A lifetime of guarding everything with you♫
Go back and tell Jin Yao
I've taken her away.
If he wants to start a war,
♫Crossing the abyss to fulfill our vow♫
I'll be waiting in the Polar Realm.
♫I'll leap without a thought for tomorrow♫
♫This moment feels like forever♫
♫I've missed too much time in my life♫
♫I'll throw myself into this flame for you♫
♫Even if I'll perish♫
♫At least I can still kiss your face♫
Young Lord!
How are you?
I won't die.
Master hasn't punished you so harshly in a long time.
Young Lord,
I don't understand.
That Chong Zhao only saved you once.
Why are you helping him so much?
Haven't you already
repaid his kindness?
That's not kindness.
Then what is it?
It's a feeling,
a feeling
that I can't even explain.
You don't need to worry about this.
Investigate something for me.
What is it?
Everything about Chong Zhao from his birth until now,
no matter how big or small.
Why do you want to investigate this?
I want him to come into my world,
the world of hell.
[Bright Moon Palace, Demon Race]
Where am I?
The Bright Moon Palace.
I didn't say I'd come here.
Don't you want revenge?
Do you really think Lanling Sect can help you?
That doesn't mean
I have to rely on you.
Even if I don't join the Eternals,
I will never submit to the Demon Race.
I'll choose
my path myself.
No one has the right to decide for me.
So, are you going back
to Ning'an City to step right into the trap,
or are you going to live a wandering, fugitive life?
It has nothing to do with you.
I don't want to get involved in your life or death.
In my eyes,
you're just a vessel for the Desireless Stone.
But the Wunian Stone is mine,
so you are mine too.