ظآزThat dayظآز
ظآزNothing stays together foreverظآز
ظآزI've quit romanceظآز
ظآزWho hasn't failed againظآز
ظآزCrying in deathظآز
ظآزAnd in lifeظآز
ظآزEven nowظآز
ظآزWe keep learningظآز
ظآزIt's no surpriseظآز
ظآزBeing happy is so hardظآز
ظآزWeirdly, I became a role modelظآز
ظآزOn the day we met again, we said hiظآز
ظآزIt was a reminder,
a test, and a complaintظآز
ظآزWho can do anything without regretظآز
ظآزI am all rightظآز
ظآزMay you live in peaceظآز
ظآزLet the world roarظآز
ظآزSounds like a carnivalظآز
ظآزBeing alive is never dullظآز
ظآزHow wonderful to be freeظآز
ظآزI became even better without youظآز
ظآزNothing can be perfectظآز
ظآزWe bless each other in painظآز
ظآزWe nod and smileظآز
ظآزMay we both be wellظآز
= Love's Ambition=
=Episode 30=
Thank you.
This is considered
a celebration banquet today.
Of course.
Lin Tao,
do you know how I felt
when the bank notified me
that the loan was disbursed
into the company's account?
I was overjoyed.
That was special privilege.
How did I get such an amazing friend?
A thousand words come down to this.
Thank you.
Thank you for doing me such a big favor
and helping Yan Studio.
This is actually
the first time we're dining
in such a nice restaurant atmosphere
and you're speaking to me
so gently.
For this moment,
I feel
every effort was worthwhile.
Why are you talking so strangely today,
Lin Tao?
Am I?
Stop overthinking, okay?
What do you think I'm thinking?
Then I'm overthinking.
Anyway, now we are just
good colleagues.
Nothing more, right?
Who says nothing?
I worked tirelessly
for you,
creating that perfect
financial report.
I boosted Yan Studio's profits
to 21 percent.
That's what convinced the bank.
Wh-What do you mean?
With Yan Studio's current operations,
we couldn't meet
the bank's loan standards.
It's all because they saw my report
that we slipped through
and the approval went smoothly.
Lin Tao,
this counts as fraud.
This is loan fraud.
Not me.
It was your sister,
Yan Studio's legal representative,
Xu Yan.
What are you implying?
What do you want?
What I want
has never changed.
Break up with Yu Yiming
and marry me back home.
Wait, Lin Tao.
Didn't you let this go already?
What? You were faking it?
You've been acting all along?
I can report you.
I'll go report you right now.
- I'm warning you.
- Go ahead.
Go right now.
I'm just an accountant.
Without authorization
from the legal person,
would I dare to cook the books?
Why would I even need to do that?
Every cent of the company
didn't enter my pocket.
Besides,
the stamp on the report
was applied by you, wasn't it?
The company has surveillance.
I checked it.
Your stamping process
is crystal clear.
If you dare report me,
I'll drag Xu Yan down with me.
The legal representative
bears primary responsibility.
Yan Studio is already crumbling
under Shen Haoming's influence.
Can you withstand
the bank's investigation?
You're truly terrifying.
We kindly took you in
to work at the company,
and you repay us
with betrayal?
Be realistic, Lin.
Call me despicable
or filthy,
whatever you like.
(Balance Sheet)
But today,
you must make a decision.
Right now.
Or else,
it's mutual destruction.
As long as you
promise me
that my sister
and Yan Studio
won't be troubled.
(Balance Sheet)
I'll do it.
So,
when will you break up with Yu Yiming?
No need to rush this.
Can't you give me some time?
Fine.
One week.
Jinsong. Jinsong.
Quick, call the doctor!
Doctor!
Jinsong!
Are you okay?
Hurry!
Jinsong!
How is he?
Family members out please.
Calm down.
Please wait outside.
You'll hinder the resuscitation.
- Jinsong.
- Please leave now.
Prepare for CPR.
(Haoming)
Hui,
please look after Haochen.
Emergency at the hospital.
Okay.
Mom.
You're here.
How is he?
His blood pressure
and pulse dropped earlier.
It took a long time
to bring him back.
He just finished tests.
All vitals are stable now.
It's fine.
How's Haochen?
Same as before.
Haochen can't have any more setbacks.
Yan, I'm counting on you.
Mom.
If you keep pushing yourself,
your health will collapse.
How about this?
You go rest and be with Haochen.
I'll stay here.
Okay?
Alright.
I'll stay a bit longer.
Where's Haoming?
He was here moments ago.
Maybe he went to the nurses' station.
I'll go look for him.
I know.
I know you're hurting.
You know.
Back in England,
with everything that happened,
if my parents hadn't shielded me,
I couldn't
have handled any of it.
But after all these years,
the consequences
and responsibilities
still fall on them.
I understand.
I fully understand
how much Jinda
and Haochen
mean to my father.
Both were nurtured personally
by him from the ground up.
That's why he suffered
such a massive shock.
I know.
Your father greatly influenced you.
You know.
Since childhood,
I've always seen him as a mountain.
No matter the crisis
or challenge,
he could resolve anything.
All these years,
despite constant power struggles
within the group,
he balanced competing interests
and maintained unity.
He did it every single time.
Nothing was beyond him.
But I saw him just now,
lying helplessly in that bed.
He was so weak.
The moment his heart stopped,
I was absolutely terrified.
I was afraid
that this mountain
would truly collapse.
He won't.
Father is strong.
He'll make it, okay?
Not hungry again?
You're eating so little in a day.
Your body can't handle this.
I will worry about you.
I'm sorry.
Haochen.
I apologize.
I spoke out of turn.
But no matter what,
we brought you up bit by bit.
When you're happy,
we're happy.
When you're sad,
we're sad too.
Haochen, you must believe.
Every person in this family
loves you genuinely.
Haochen?
Don't you
like going out usually?
Today, whatever you want to do,
basketball,
skateboarding,
I'll be with you the whole time.
Today, if we get tired
after playing basketball,
we'll have pizza.
And also
your favorite ice cream,
okay?
One scoop, two scoops.
Whatever you want.
After the ice-cream,
we'll have pizza,
steak,
or fried chicken.
It's up to you.
Stop filming me!
Put that away!
Security!
Security, hurry!
Get out!
Out! Out! Out!
Detain him!
Get out now!
You okay?
It's fine. It's fine.
Sweetheart.
Quick. Take him away.
Take him away!
Stop filming! How dare you!
Stop filming!
It's okay, honey.
Haochen!
Handle this now!
Don't worry.
Haochen!
Haochen, open the door.
Open up.
What happened?
You're finally back.
I tried
taking him out
to cheer him up today.
We got snapped right there,
not sure if it was a reporter.
- Take it easy.
- He pointed it
right at us,
filming shamelessly.
Then Haochen got upset,
ran inside,
and locked the door.
Haochen.
- Open the door!
- He...
He was crying. Why is it silent now?
Haochen!
Mom, step back.
Haochen.
Haochen!
Haochen, what's wrong with you?
Call Dr. Wang. Hurry.
Dr. Wa...
Haochen.
Hello? Hello?
Wang,
Haochen fainted.
Come to my place now.
Hurry! Yes.
Haochen!
Dr. Wang.
What's Haochen's
current condition?
Nothing serious.
He fainted
due to low blood sugar
from not eating enough.
You don't know him well.
He refuses to eat anything.
What should we do?
Due to emotional distress,
now Haochen
has had mild autism.
That's why he refuses to eat
and communicate.
Mild cases can be cured.
If it becomes severe,
he might show signs
of self-harm
or aggressive behaviors.
Parents should intervene early.
Are there any solutions?
Haochen is very resistant
to his environment right now.
I think
he needs
a totally new
environment for now.
Understood. Thank you.
Okay.
I'll check on him again.
- Thank you.
Haoming, Yan,
let's follow the doctor's advice
and take Haochen to a new environment.
Anywhere will do.
Mom,
Dad's in the hospital now.
Don't worry about Dad.
His condition has stabilized.
I'm here.
Don't worry. I'm here.
Haochen's situation is urgent.
So going abroad? Somewhere far away?
Good idea.
But not too far.
If anything happens to Dad,
we might not make it back in time.
So where's better?
How about my grandma's house?
Is that okay?
Is it convenient? Because...
Very convenient.
She lives in the countryside.
It's spacious there,
with many animals.
Kids love that.
Let's follow Yan's advice.
The hospital has nurses,
and Hui's at home.
Leave Dad's matters to me.
Haochen's situation really
can't be delayed any longer.
Understood.
I'll call
my grandma right away.
Mom, don't worry.
We leave tomorrow.
I told you
not to wait outside.
Yan!
I missed you so much!
Hello, Grandma.
How are you lately?
Good.
Already in great shape,
and even better seeing you all.
That's great.
This must be Haochen?
What a handsome little fellow.
Haochen, say hello to Great-grandma.
Haochen.
Never mind.
He just arrived. He's shy.
After getting familiar,
he'll call me naturally.
Haochen.
Come on. Give the suitcase to me.
Follow me.
Come on.
Watch your step.
Don't look around.
You'll have plenty to see later.
When we get home,
I will cook delicious meals for you.
Come on.
Eat more, Haochen.
I made this
braised pork knuckle.
- And this beef stew.
- Vinegar?
I spent three to four hours
simmering it.
It melts in your mouth.
How does the commercial say it?
It tastes wonderful!
You like the sliced noodles?
These are special.
It resembles silver fish
diving into waves
and willow leaves
riding the wind from branches.
If you visit Shanxi
and don't eat a bowl
of these noodles,
it's a wasted trip.
Haochen,
all these dishes
were prepared
by Great-grandma.
Come on. Eat up.
Haochen?
Don't.
Sorry, Grandma.
He's usually very polite.
It's fine.
He's just a child.
Don't force him
if he can't finish. He just arrived.
Besides, Yan
already told me before you came.
We adults
all understand
children's feelings,
right?
Leave some for him.
Leave some.
No need.
I'll cook fresh
whenever he's hungry.
You all eat now.
Have some fish.
Let's eat.
Eat up.
Okay.
Yan,
when I was hospitalized last time
and you rushed back to see me,
I realized
something was wrong
between you and Haoming.
But seeing you two
get along so well now
reassures me.
So
let me ask you.
Was your previous conflict
about him
having a child?
Grandma,
I genuinely care for Haochen.
He's such
a smart, loyal and sensitive child.
Before, he'd chat with me
for hours.
But now,
he's completely silent.
It hurts to see him like this.
I brought him here
to give him
an adjustment period.
He's a kid.
He needs some time
to process sudden life changes.
I really don't know
what else I should do.
I just want to care for him
and help him become
his old self again.
Yan,
that's the right approach.
Beyond blood relations,
what matters more
and truly connects people
is mutual sincerity.
Grandma,
don't worry about us.
We're being completely transparent
with each other now.
We'll solve problems
and face them together.
With you as our shelter,
we'll overcome everything.
Mom,
how's Dad?
He's stable in all aspects.
He hasn't woken up yet.
But the doctor said
it is optimistic.
No need to worry.
That's good.
Take turns with the caregivers.
Don't keep staying up late.
Okay.
Don't worry.
How's Haochen?
Same as before.
He still won't talk.
Hopefully after some time,
he'll improve.
Alright.
Take care over there.
Okay.
Haochen, breakfast is ready.
Haochen?
Good morning.
He's out.
Sleep well?
Any mosquitoes last night?
Come on.
Look.
Great-grandma made this for you.
Sesame oil egg.
Smell how fragrant it is.
Let's have it with a steamed bun.
You barely ate last night.
Eat a bit more now.
Haochen,
it's delicious.
Haochen?
Haochen.
Since you're done,
go do some work.
Haoming,
you should finish your meal too.
After eating,
get a big basket from the yard
and take the kid
to harvest corn on the back hill.
Okay.
Understood.
We country folks
have one rule.
Only those too old to work
or infants unable to work
can be exempt from labor.
Everyone else can't rest.
They must work the fields.
You're living in my house
and eating my food.
Labor is mandatory.
Grandma,
don't be like this.
Haochen is just a child.
He...
He can't possibly handle this work.
He's quite temperamental.
Brilliant.
Officail Website : kissasian.biz
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
I'll go too.
You haven't finished yet.
Get one for him too.
Get him one too.
Okay.
Let me show you.
Corn harvesting goes like this.
Press down.
Twist clockwise and it comes off.
Twist clockwise. Off it comes.
Simple as that.
Press down.
Twist.
Comes off.
Press down and twist.
The whole corn comes off.
Try that one.
Press down and twist.
There's more over there.
Go up.
Up higher.
No, no, no.
Catch it. Catch it.
Catch!
Use hands!
Use your hands to catch.
Come out of the coop!
Catch!
Catch it! Catch it!
Got it! I got it!
Haochen, take it!
Quick!
Hurry! Hurry!
You're dragging your feet
on such a small task.
Do you plan
to finish it when it's dark?
Why are you staring?
Let me tell you.
All these corns
must be processed before sunset.
How about this?
You handle that pile.
These two are mine.
Okay.
Here, take it.
Haochen,
do you want another bowl?
Go to the kitchen
and serve yourself.
Farm work
really works.
Second serve already.
Remember to tell Mom
about the good news.
Definitely.
Won't this cause indigestion?
Let me help you.
Let me help.
Come on.
Meat lover should eat more.
Eat more meat.
This kid...
His belly...
Though we've now
removed Shen Jinsong
and Shen Haoming from their positions,
they remain the company's
major shareholders.
The board and department heads
are all waiting to see
when they'll make a comeback.
What's your take?
Due to their personal misconduct,
our stock prices plummeted,
causing massive financial losses.
Legally speaking,
the group has full authority
to demand compensation from them.
We can gather
eligible shareholders
to represent the group
in suing those two
and demand they repay the losses.
Meanwhile, file
for litigation preservation
to freeze their accounts.
A legal battle?
It has lengthy cycles.
The longer, the better.
Once preservation is enacted
and their accounts frozen,
all their stocks
become worthless paper.
Without funds,
how could they come back?
Senior,
the patient in Bed 3
has surgery scheduled Friday.
Lin?
You're back.
Are you going out?
Yeah,
I need to return to the office.
Have you been avoiding me lately?
Why would I do that? I'm not.
Lin.
I know you're busy lately,
but you only text two-word replies.
Calls last less than a minute.
When I offer
to pick you up, you decline.
What's really going on?
You're overthinking.
I've just
been too busy lately.
I'm too occupied.
Look,
I finally left work early today,
hoping to rest,
but they called and dragged me back.
It's genuinely chaotic.
I have much to do.
You go rest first.
I'll update you later.
Go back.
Really?
Really.
It's not too bad.
Just a minor sprain.
Apply cold compress when you go back.
Then use the medicinal oil
and massage the ankle.
It'll be fine in a few days.
Thank you, doctor.
The swelling looks significant.
It's my fault.
I didn't catch you.
No, no.
I just lost my balance.
Maybe you should
take some days off
and work from home.
No need.
It's not a serious injury.
With so many things in the company,
I still need to go.
Lin,
are you okay?
I looked for you
and heard from security.
How did you
end up falling?
It must hurt terribly.
Let me see.
I'm fine. Really.
What you doing?
You're injured.
Why are you carrying this yourself?
Dr. Yu,
thank you.
Leave the rest to me.
Are you out of your mind?
What's wrong with you?
This is my girlfriend.
Lin,
you didn't tell him?
Tell me what?
Qiao Lin is now my girlfriend.
Don't believe me?
Ask her yourself then.
Lin,
let me help you.
Thank you, doctor.
Lin,
let's go. I'll help you.
No need.
Lin,
tell me the truth.
Back off.
Yu Yiming,
this is your workplace.
You'll regret it if you start a fight.
Lin,
are you hiding something?
What kind of nonsense is that?
We're in a proper relationship.
We're deeply connected.
True lovers always find their way.
What do we need to hide?
Get out of my way.
I need to talk to Qiao Lin now.
Lin,
make it clear to him once and for all.
Make him give up completely.
Lin Tao and I
are back together.
That's impossible.
Yu Yiming,
the time I spent with you
was truly joyful.
But marriage and dating
are two different things.
I've thought long and hard.
There are significant gaps
between us.
These are practical realities.
As for Lin Tao,
his devotion
has truly moved me.
After much consideration,
I believe
he's more suitable for me.
I don't believe
anything you just said.
What really happened?
If he threatened you...
Yu Yiming,
if you touch my girl again,
I'll hit you. I swear.
Lin Tao, that's enough!
Yu Yiming,
believe it or not,
I've said everything that needed
to be said today.
Don't come to me anymore.
Lin,
now that everything's out in the open,
return what you owe him.
So he won't bother you again.
This ring was also given by you.
Take it back.
Now we're even.
Haochen,
what are you looking at?
You like animals too?
Great.
From now on, these chicks
will be your responsibility.
Actually, taking care of them
is pretty simple.
You just need
to feed them
regularly every day.
That's about it.
And also
clean their living area
thoroughly every day.
Keep it tidy.
Okay?
Simple enough, right?
Here.
Take this.
Three meals a day
are your job now.
If they get hungry,
I'll hold you accountable.
Get to work.
(Xu Yan)
Yan.
I saw the payment went through.
Yes.
The loan funds have arrived.
Also
the physical store is progressing.
Though it might
not move as quickly.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of both
the company and home.
Okay.
Then I'll count on you.
Thank you.
You too.
Bye.
Be careful
with this mirror too.
Lin.
Thank you.
What is it?
Are you moving out?
Where to?
T-To my sister's place.
No matter how I ask,
you refuse to tell the truth.
Is that so?
There's no truth to tell.
Just...
I told you. I've just
had a change of heart.
I don't care how many times
you've said it
or what I've seen
or heard.
Even if you are with Lin Tao
and push me away,
I'll never believe
you've changed feelings.
If you'd seen
how you looked at me,
you'd understand
why I'm certain of this.
Miss Qiao,
things are packed.
Let's go.
Okay.
We're adults.
Act more mature.
Can you do it?
Yan.
We know
you're staying at Grandma's.
So we came to check.
Well, where is Haoming
and Haochen?
Haoming took Haochen to do farm work.
Farm work?
Can Haoming and Haochen
handle farm work?
They're guests from afar.
We can't make guests work, right?
I'll talk to Mom.
Grandma's made great arrangements.
They're eating well
and sleeping well.
So you don't need to worry.
Also, I brought Haochen here
to leave him
some peace and quiet.
If you want
to see him,
maybe you should come later
when he's in better condition.
Okay?
Okay.
S-Since that's the case,
then we won't
bother you anymore.
I...
Th-These are for your grandma.
These are her calcium tablets
and fish oil.
These are snacks
for Haochen.
Kids love these.
And this...
This is the money
you gave me for treatment.
I didn't use it.
The doctor said the tumor was benign.
After the minimally invasive surgery,
I'm fine now.
We heard what happened
to the Shen family.
Now that you've moved back here,
it's convenient for us
to visit from the town.
If you need anything,
be sure to call us.
We can't help much in Jingzhou,
but in our hometown,
we'll definitely find ways to assist,
right?
Take this money.
If it's not enough,
just call us.
We still have savings.
Thank you.
We're family. No need for thanks.
We're leaving now.
You rest first.
I'll get your clothes.
When water's hot, take a bath.
It's cold. Drink slowly.
(You &amp; Me)
(In 2001, I was four years old)
ظآزSeparatedظآز
ظآزLike the world shook off its dustظآز
ظآزSo simpleظآز
(Old Pagoda Tree Kindergarten)
(In 2003, I was six years old.
I was in kindergarten. Wait for me)
(In 2003, you were 11)
ظآزI realize when I lose youظآز
This looks a bit like you.
So cute.
ظآزI was the oneظآز
ظآزWho chose to walk awayظآز
Can I take a photo like this?
Of course.
What for?
Just to keep as a memory.
ظآزFirst time I confessظآز
ظآزI'm so ordinaryظآز
ظآزLonging to earnظآز
(In 2007, I was 10)
Age 10.
(You were 15)
(We both won awards)
15.
(In 2015, I turned 18.
I arrived in Beijing)
(In 2018, I was 21.
You finally returned. I'm still working)
(You were 26.
It was our first time in the same city)
(In 2023, I was 26 years old)
(You were 31. I met you)
(I met you)
(Today, we got married)
(In 2024, we are getting divorced)
ظآزNow I anticipateظآز
ظآزA future with you in itظآز
ظآزLike fireworks that lovedظآز
ظآزRushing toward the starsظآز
ظآزUndaunted by painظآز
ظآزFearless of flamesظآز
ظآزEven if just a fleeting sparkleظآز
ظآزWe shed tearsظآز
ظآزDeep blue seas turn to foamظآز
ظآزWe regained freedomظآز
ظآزIf you remember meظآز
ظآزThen I'm pleasedظآز
ظآزI just wanna take my time tonightظآز
ظآزTo do all the things I said I'd tryظآز
ظآزI go surfing, go diving, go driving,
and go flying to a different placeظآز
ظآزI go drink, go party, and go danceظآز
ظآزEven if I'm lonelyظآز
ظآزCause I just have been hurt
too many timesظآز
ظآزI'm giving it all to get nothing backظآز
ظآزI was lost in the dark,
and it's too hurt to even seeظآز
ظآزSee the world and how it flows.
We never let goظآز
ظآزSo I'll take my timeظآز
ظآزTo reigniteظآز
ظآزThe love I should deserveظآز
ظآزWhen the time is rightظآز
ظآزYou realizeظآز
ظآزIt will all be alrightظآز
ظآزCause I just have been hurt
too many timesظآز
ظآزI'm giving it all to get nothing backظآز
ظآزI was lost in the dark,
and it's too hurt to even seeظآز
ظآزSee the world and how it flows.
We never let goظآز
ظآزSo I'll take my timeظآز
ظآزTo reigniteظآز
ظآزThe love I should deserveظآز
ظآزWhen the time is rightظآز
ظآزYou realizeظآز
ظآزIt will all be alrightظآز