[plane engine whining]
JC
Call me back, let's talk about it.
Call me, please.
Let me explain.
Pick up.
[sucks teeth]
[exhales]
- Why are you here?
- King sent me.
[Annabelle] Mmm.
He won't leave the house right now.
- Is he okay?
- He's a bit on edge, but he's fine.
I'm going to the address
he gave to deliver the stuff.
Wait, where do we go?
His ex-girlfriend's house, I think.
Is it safe?
I trust his judgement.
So, what, am I heading home?
Yeah, I'll bring your stuff back soon.
[car starting]
[Kingsley] Oh!
The suitcases?
Where'd they go?
[Annabelle] Kylian took them.
Yeah, where to?
I'm not sure, but I thought you knew.
- Wait, wait, Kylian kept the bags?
- [Annabelle] Mmm-hmm.
Fuck! Where'd he go, Belle?
Uh, your ex's place or something.
My ex's place?
Damn it!
What is this, more bullshit? Mmm-mmm.
[suspenseful music playing]
[phone buzzing]
INCOMING CALL
[text notification buzzes]
KING - Pick up the phone
and bring me my presents now!
We can call it off still.
We won't though, man.
It's gonna get real.
No choice.
[suspenseful music continues]
You can go now. It's fine.
[man] Are y'all armed? Stay there.
Pfft.
If you're packing here, you're an idiot.
- I'm carrying a large sum of money.
- [SherKhan chuckles]
That's true.
Who this?
He's here as my apprentice.
[laughing]
Damn, what a dumbass. [chuckling]
300% interest.
We good?
A Lafleur has robbed me
and Milord's paying me back.
- Why is that?
- That's the deal.
[SherKhan] Not my deal.
Then we got a problem.
We already have a problem.
Seriously, you shouldn't push your luck.
[chuckling]
"Lafleur will pay."
That's what Milord said.
Shut the fuck up.
I want him dead.
That's what I want. Nothing less.
The terms are set. It's done.
Kingsley Lafleur
is no longer your problem.
Let Milord manage that now.
So?
We good?
We good.
I'm sorry, boss.
I need to go calm down Jean-Claude now.
[Fatso] Thanks, King.
Right.
[crane whirring]
[container thuds]
[man on radio] Yo, Jean-Claude.
You hear me? Your intern is here.
- I'm busy.
- [radio chirps]
[on radio] I know, but he insists.
He has a note from his homeroom teacher
or something. He's pissing me off.
Why'd you come piss me off at work for?
I've come to say
I've sorted out our issues.
I'll soon receive the merchandise.
It's all taken care of. You in?
You must not comprehend my concern
if you believe it's fixed.
SherKhan was looking to make buzz.
He's full of shit,
but that's part of my job too.
To manage the bullshit.
So I stopped by to see him.
Okay.
So?
So SherKhan is wrong
to prey on your brother.
Is that your argument?
He's been running his mouth all over,
so you paid him.
[sucks teeth]
You piece of shit, Lafleur.
You must take me for a fool.
How can I re-establish
our partnership, for real?
[chuckles] "Re-establish our partnership"?
Just forget about it. It's over.
You're turning down 200,000 euros?
I'm turning down 20 years in prison.
With people like you and King,
it always ends badly.
Always.
What if I gave you double what we said?
Enough. It's pathetic.
I made a deal with the Venezuelans.
They deliver in two days.
I can't revoke that.
You're seriously fucking me over here.
Yeah, or I'm helping you.
No, I'll be stuck with 80 kilos of goods.
It's a disaster.
You'll find a solution.
[Kylian sucks teeth]
That motherfucker.
Hey, Didier.
What the fuck?
I'm supposed to be operating that, man.
[on radio] Seems like you're busy
getting blown by your little boyfriend.
I gotta move the F-23 with this.
Climb out of it.
Don't bust my balls, let me finish.
- [crane whirring]
- Piece of shit.
- You still here?
- I have no choice.
These men never back away.
They will butcher your family
and you before that.
Didn't you want to dominate everyone?
The top dog dominates
and he mauls the other dogs.
I bet all my cards on you.
I'm so flattered. It was a bad call.
You're not at that level. Let me go.
[darkly intriguing music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
Well?
Is it settled?
- It's settled.
- [laughing] My man!
Does it have to do anything
with Annabelle's return?
[sucks teeth] Yeah.
Do you care to explain? Why is he upset?
[Annabelle] Kylian!
I don't know what you did
with the suitcases, but this is bad.
[Ambre] What suitcases?
That's it?
You just come home all calm? Empty-handed?
I called 15 times, Kylian!
- Where the fuck is my money?
- I don't have it.
What do you mean?
I told you to head straight back here!
Where'd you put my cash, bro?
What is he talking about?
I gave it back to SherKhan.
Huh? What are you even saying?
King, I reimbursed him
so you'd be left alone.
- No way.
- You serious, Kylian?
Kiki, quit fucking with me.
King, he was gonna kill you.
Maybe murder the family too.
They knew it was you.
I didn't have a choice.
I don't believe you. Give me the money.
The joke isn't funny.
How'd you do that?
Fatso knows some guys.
And, yeah, SherKhan
was interested right away.
Did you forget
we're in debt to our eyeballs?
What you do with my money, bro?
What is it you want to buy?
Are you a moron?
Give me the money
or I'll fuck you up, brother!
I don't have the money anymore.
Forget it. It's through.
[Ambre] King, stop!
Out of my way! Just stay out of this!
Kiki has a point.
Not possible.
I just don't believe you.
I did all that for nothing?
It wasn't me that sent you there.
You lucky you made it back.
You're going to Auntie Régine's.
Tell your siblings
they won't be coming home to us.
That they're staying put
with those weirdos.
For how much longer? We don't know.
You go tell them.
- I had no choice.
- No one asked you, man!
- You've become real cocky.
- [Ambre] King, back off.
You're a piece of shit douchebag
that thinks he's a genius.
And I will make you pay.
You gonna pay me for that!
[sucks teeth] What a jerk!
Wow. Respect, brother.
[pensive rap song playing]
[pensive rap song continues]
Kibble delivery on the 19th at 4:00 a.m.
It'll be at 4:00 a.m.
on the 19th at Bonneville beach
- [bang on door]
- [song stops suddenly]
[loud banging on door]
How'd you get in?
A room to yourself? Seriously?
Nice, nice.
Treating yourself too, I see.
[laughs softly] This place reeks of money.
This tablet here, it now belongs to me.
- It's the school's.
- Like I give a shit.
How much is this worth?
About two, three bucks?
You've come up short.
Give me all of the valuables you got here,
even the basketball shoes.
They're now mine, man.
Oh, you're pissed?
Got a problem?
Is there money hidden here?
- Hmm?
- There's not.
Fuck this, man.
Let's see what "Mr. Do Good's"
been doing lately… besides jerking off.
You can't be here, King, enough.
I'm in enough shit.
You'll get me expelled.
Oh, that's right.
You've been skipping class.
But what is it you do then, Kylian? Hmm?
Do you hang with your boy Fatso?
Y'all sleep together?
Wait.
Was it Fatso?
Did Fatso organize all this?
Did he give the money back?
- He stole it from you?
- No.
He must work for him.
That can't be possible.
Fuck.
You're both working
for that son of a bitch now? How?
How much did he pay
for you to give him my cash?
A few bonbons? Where the bonbons?
Stop! That was just me. I acted alone.
Fatso gave me his number.
I already told you to stop.
Stop fucking with my head.
You don't want to?
[phone chimes]
[exhales]
[sucks teeth]
Step aside.
- Stay put.
- [lock rattles]
There's nothing in my bed.
- Let me go.
- There's nothing here. Stop.
You stop it! I'm not playing with you.
A-ha!
Kiki, what is this?
It's not mine.
Is it Fatty's?
No, it's Lily's. She asked me to fix it.
Oh, yes, Lily.
The white girl, right?
Why was it under the bed?
Unlock it.
No, you can't do that.
- Do it or I'll mess you up.
- Cut the bullshit.
[both grunting]
I'll break you finger by finger
until you tell me the code.
One.
- [straining]
- Two.
- Three.
- [groaning]
Fucking hell.
This thing's worth gold, then.
I'll keep it.
Stop your bullshit. Give it back.
What do you think you're doing?
- [both grunting]
- [bed clattering]
[loud bang on door]
Fuck.
I'm sorry, I'll keep it down.
[man] Open the door, Lafleur.
What's happening?
- Who is this?
- My brother.
- Why is he here? How'd he get in?
- I don't know.
I only came
to bring him something important.
That's absolutely forbidden
and Kylian knows it.
- I'll report it.
- He came without telling me.
I was about to go to bed.
All right, then. Leave.
[introspective music playing]
[Kingsley exhales]
[Kingsley softly] No way, brother.
There's no way.
- [Kingsley sucks teeth]
- [wood thuds]
I'm gonna smash this phone, I swear.
[exhales]
[Léo] What are you doing?
You see this?
It's Kylian's.
That psycho had two phones.
Meanwhile, we're starving from hunger.
Can you believe this?
No.
What might the code be? You have any idea?
I'm sure that SherKhan gave him this.
SherKhan?
I'm sure that he's running errands
for SherKhan…
or maybe SherKhan has him by the balls.
I don't know, man. [sucks teeth]
[phone clatters]
[sighs]
Should've never let him
have shady pals like Fatso.
Does Fatso also work for SherKhan?
I'm not sure.
I have an idea.
["Ga letaw!" by DLF playing]
[SherKhan] Everyone's gonna say
I'm the villain here.
Well, maybe you should
settle your issue with that man.
Trust, I'm gonna settle it.
I'm gonna shoot these fools for real.
Khan, there's a kid
who wants to talk to you.
- Who?
- He doesn't want to tell us his name.
- Is he clean?
- Yeah.
[rap song continues playing]
Lafleur.
Your brother steals from me
and you show up here all calm?
- What do you want?
- I want to work for you too, Khan.
"You too"?
- Yes.
- Do you know anyone working for me?
As you can see, I'm not hiring right now.
I don't mean here.
Where?
Well, you know.
It's my only business. I'll keep you
in mind if I open another bar.
I mean on the street, you know?
Street, huh? You want
to sweep my yard and clean my house?
You want to be my bitch?
[sucks teeth] I don't employ Lafleurs.
Just ask Milord.
Milord?
Your brother and Milord are like this,
and with Fatso,
and all the guys from Dillon.
They think they saved his ass?
From where I stand, they saved nobody.
You want to work for me?
Go to Dillon,
put a bullet in your brother,
and I swear you'll be my number-one guy.
[scoffs]
Scram, kid.
Thanks for the headache, bro. Damn kids.
Pleasure's all mine.
Ah, press here.
- Here?
- Yeah.
Now press harder.
[sighs and sucks teeth]
He can't just disrespect me like that.
- Did you take any medicine?
- No, I haven't yet.
[knock on door]
Nolan, it's almost your turn.
Are we coming home?
It's driving me crazy, brother.
He doesn't even visit y'all.
But the worst part?
He goes and steals all of my money.
It's bullshit.
[Mathis] Are you okay?
No, I'll take an aspirin.
[grunts] This is really busting my head.
[shower running]
Thaïs, are there any painkillers in there?
[Willy] Uh, yeah. Hold on.
- [dark music playing]
- Thaïs, are you in there too?
- [Thaïs] Yes, I'm almost finished.
- [lock clicks]
- [shower continues running]
- [dark music continues]
What are you doing here, man?
Just freshening up for the day.
We only have one bathroom.
Could you put on some pants?
What's happening here?
What the hell is this about? Get out!
Nolan, Mathis, over here.
Does Uncle Willy
get naked often in front of you?
Does he enter the room when you shower?
- No.
He does with Thaïs.
Get your stuff, we're leaving.
- King?
- Shut up!
- You need to calm down, King.
- Shut the fuck up.
[dark music continues]
- Let's go. Faster, faster.
- What's going on here?
- Faster! I'm taking them home now.
- Have you lost your mind?
Let's go. Come on.
[sighs] Your husband is a fucking pervert!
That's bull.
You only see the bad, don't you?
You also gonna claim
she asked him to be her pimp?
That right? [sucks teeth]
We leaving. Come on. Move.
No! You have no right to take them.
Willy! Call the police!
Be my guest, please!
If you call the police, that damn judge,
the social worker, whatever…
I don't give a fuck. I'll come back here
and burn down you and your damn house.
Understand?
["SO COMAN" by Kalash playing]
Mathis has a CT scan scheduled for Monday!
You're gonna have to pay it upfront.
Keep walking, keep walking.
What's the CT scan for? You okay?
Because I get dizzy sometimes,
usually at night.
Dizzy?
Yeah.
- [Mathis] What's a scan?
- ["SO COMAN" continues playing]
- [song fading]
- [waves lapping gently]
Here.
New phone? Thank you.
- [Fatso] Call Marco, Kylian.
- No.
What don't you understand?
We're not going anywhere.
And if they never appear?
Why wouldn't they appear?
To keep the money
of a punk they don't care about.
- Am I the punk?
- What did you say?
- Isn't the punk helping you eat?
- We work, you pay.
Shut up, Ludo.
The dope we're about to get,
did you work for that?
The shipping containers.
Was it you that found them?
Do you know how much money you'll make?
Nothing. He won't get a damn thing.
Calm down.
No need to get mad like this, okay?
I'm just saying, man.
[emphatically] I'm with you.
[motorboat approaching in distance]
[Kylian] Shh!
[motorboat approaching]
Take this back. We'll sell it locally.
- We need to make money right away.
- Okay.
And…
Don't pay attention to my brother.
He can be idiot, but he's pretty straight.
["AK47" by Mercenaire & Kalash playing]
Don't call me "little punk."
["AK47" continues playing]
JC - I warned you.
It's over. Forget about me.
["AK47" continues playing]
[song fading]
- [dog barking]
- [Ludo] Shut it!
[growls softly]
Damn dog.
[dog barking]
[dog growls softly]
- [barking continues]
- [man] Is anyone here?
- Shut up!
Excuse me, I think we may be lost.
- Where'd you come from?
- The woods back here.
Cross the field over there.
Walk down the path.
It's marked.
- I'm sorry, but do you have any water?
- No, none here.
Is there a problem?
[Ludo] No problem.
We don't mean to disturb. We'll go.
[Kylian] Your passports.
- [gun cocks]
- Your passports, now.
[tense music playing]
[Fatso] Marseille.
Tons of people work for me there.
Sir, please. We just want to go home.
Fuck off.
[dog barks]
When are we moving this to the dock?
[sighs]
In three days.
[Marvin] That's not the subject
of this conversation. It's not.
Kylian.
Where were you?
- I was in the forest with Lily.
- [Marvin scoffs]
Can I take a quick shower?
I don't have time to wait on his highness.
Are they at school?
Given what happened, we don't think
we should send them back to Régine's.
- Do you agree?
- Well, yeah.
[Kingsley] Anyway,
we don't want his opinion.
We've gotta handle this.
It's gonna be tough.
Money problems first.
That scan for Mathis isn't covered.
Gonna be expensive as hell.
You'll pay up, yeah?
Hmm? You've got a plan, I assume.
Or else you wouldn't have fucked up mine.
We had 400,000 euros to live on like men.
What do you propose then, Kylian?
You had it
in your little princess hands, huh?
Only to give it to that asshole?
So you're saying
it's better for you to be killed?
[Kingsley] Yes!
Did you really have to do it like that?
Behind our backs.
What are you looking at?
You know I don't agree with them, right?
Okay, okay, okay!
Just stop!
Kylian just wanted to help, so stop.
But we all have to pitch in
to make ends meet.
Kylian, go pick up the kids from school.
We can begin with that.
Don't forget to tell them
there won't be any school trips.
There won't be any activities,
No costumes, no games, no parties.
No Pokémon.
- Because it's either that or no food.
- [Marvin] You have to help us, brother.
I never said I wouldn't.
Okay, move your ass, then!
- [school bell ringing]
- [kid] Okay, see you later.
[kids chattering indistinctly]
[kid] I've never seen his brother before!
[laughs]
Is that you?
Yeah.
But you don't pick us up usually.
I know, but today I'm here.
Not disappointed, are you?
- [Thaïs] No, it's really great.
- [Nolan] No, it's great.
[Léo] Yeah!
- [Kylian] How you doin'?
- I'm fine.
- [Nolan] Are we going home?
- Yeah, someone's picking us up.
Well, I won't say anything to the judge.
I'll just take back the children.
You've already suffered.
No.
No, I have to bring them back.
Sorry, Auntie.
Kylian, be reasonable, not like Kingsley.
- Come here, children. The car is--
- [Nolan] Mmm!
- Let go.
- Leave, Régine.
They won't be going back with you.
Drop it.
Yeah? Or else what?
You don't want to know, believe me.
[Régine straining]
Poor Marilyn.
You truly are a bunch of thugs.
["Love" by X-Man & Matieu White playing]
[Mathis] So cool!
You two are going with them.
[Fatso] Hop on, Mathis.
[Kylian] Give me the helmet?
[Mathis] So awesome.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
You feeling dizzy?
- You sure you'll be all right?
- Mmm.
Tell me if you don't feel well. Let's go.
["Love" continues playing]
[indistinct chatter]
I have also some avocados.
They're four for the price of two.
And also some fresh tomatoes.
Add them to some fish,
they go with everything.
- Did you see these?
- Yes, thank you.
These aren't spicy at all.
You can use one or two, as you wish.
[song fading]
Today, buy four avocados
for the price of two.
Take a look, aren't they beautiful?
I've got some cabbage here too.
[Ludo] These avocados
look past their prime.
You think my avocados
are past their prime?
What do you mean?
Listen to me, grandma.
Grab the avocados,
the bananas, and these mangos,
and take it somewhere else,
or you'll end up looking peaked too.
[vibrating]
Pick it up. It may be important.
Mama, do what he says.
I'll return tomorrow.
If you're not gone,
I'll put a bullet in both of you.
This stand doesn't belong to you,
and never did, so get lost.
Understand? A bullet in each of you.
Past their prime.
["TEN'N SA" by Vié Couli'a playing]
It's in bad shape. The scooter's too old.
What do you want?
Kids can't be hanging around here.
You have any smokes?
I could buy you some
at the minimart over there.
Listen to him.
[sucks teeth] Bounce!
[Sentinel] Yo, wait, wait.
I'm thirsty.
Buy me two beers and a pack of papers.
Tell Shaylee it's for Sentinel.
I never forget a face.
If you don't come back, I'll beat you up.
I'm a pro, just see.
Okay, buy yourself a Coke with the rest.
- Enjoy.
- Got it.
Forget it, that's too busted up.
That's a liability.
[intriguing music playing]
[intriguing music continues]
[bikes approaching]
- [man] How much you have?
- [Fatso] 250.
[man] Great.
[Fatso] I'll get the rest tomorrow.
- Peace.
- [intriguing music continues]
You want something, Léo?
Did King send you?
[sighs heavily]
[phone ringing]
Hello?
[Fatso] I'm with
Léo Lafleur at the moment.
What?
He's spying on me
for his brother Kingsley.
Ugh, you're kidding me.
You can let him go.
Just be gentle.
Okay, Milord.
[darkly suspenseful music playing]
FROM LEFT TO RIGHT
[dark music continues]
FRETTECH
TRIAL BETWEEN THE TWO FOUNDERS
THE SPLIT BETWEEN
THE TWO FORMER ALLIES
FOUNDERS JEAN-CLAUDE JOSEPH
AND DIDIER SAINTE-ROSE
FRETTECH: NEW TRIAL BETWEEN
THE TWO FOUNDERS
Smile, it's a photo for Insta.
["TANALAND" by SAGE FWI playing]
[Kingsley] Is it not working?
Hey! Why aren't you dressed?
[sucks teeth]
I'll be back.
Don't touch anything. No cheating.
Yo!
Seriously, what the hell are you doing?
I might need a scooter.
[bikes revving loudly]
["KMF, Pt. 2" by Evil P playing]
[indistinct traffic]
[darkly intriguing music playing]
[muted dance music playing in background]
Are you coming in?
I don't know. Who's there?
A ton of people for my cousin.
Let's go.
Let's stay here a bit.
If you want.
[laughs softly] All good?
Just a bit of trouble.
"Trouble" like Tony Montana?
Why do you say that? No.
[chuckles] You can tell me then, Kylian.
I'm superstitious.
I'm afraid of what
might happen to you if I tell you.
Mmm. That's so sweet,
but, you know, nothing can happen to me.
- Why?
- I've got lucky nail polish here.
Give me your hand.
Don't be a chicken, give me your hand.
Let's see it!
There you go.
Oh!
[blows] You're all set.
You oscillate between
the soul of an old man and that of a kid.
Really? When's my soul like a kid's?
Hmm.
When I kiss you, for example.
- [laughing]
- You're the kid.
Okay, let's see if I am, then.
- [door opening]
- [woman] Whatever.
[man] It's the truth.
What a question, dude.
[Lily laughs]
Coming?
[Kylian] Mmm…
Yeah, two seconds.
I'll join you inside.
[woman] Hey, Lily. Do you want a drink?
[muted music continues in background]
[loud hip-hop song playing]
Don't worry your pretty head about that.
What's the intern doing here?
Can we chat?
- About what?
- Something real quick.
Fine, go ahead.
No.
Not here.
All right. Be right back.
[loud hip-hop music continues]
What do you want?
Who are you to offer me a drink?
Do I look homeless or something?
Give me my usual.
Well?
Some people want me
to move a big haul into Paris.
And how am I concerned?
It's a bit special, to be honest.
How is it special?
It's toxic substances.
Like?
They're cooking in a lab
and they want to ship it out.
Just call a damn transportation company.
You're fucking wasting my time here, boy.
We prefer avoiding
a transportation company.
That's bold of you.
Who are these people?
They prefer to be anonymous.
They hired me to be their middleman.
And someone said
that I would do this sort of thing?
Nobody did.
You sure?
Yeah.
I saw you spoke with my colleague.
You forget?
True, but that's unrelated to this.
Why don't you ask him?
I've been informed
that he's not the person to ask.
Who said that?
Here's what you tell
the person who sent you here.
You go tell them to fuck themselves.
If they want my help,
they should just come to me.
Got it?
Hey, Putin!
What was that?
[Kylian] Mmm.
Did you offer him a blowjob?
Is that it? You screwing with me?
Someone put us in contact.
Right. Real romantic.
It's adorable.
- Wouldn't advise doing business with him.
- Really?
Tell me why.
He loves ripping folks off.
It wasn't my Plan A.
["G.T.D." by Marginal playing]
["G.T.D." continues playing]
A SMALL STEP, A BIG IMPACT.
HELP PREVENT CANCER.
[expectant song continues playing]
- Hello there, girls. Hello, Cassandra.
- Hello, ma'am.
[Ambre] How are you?
[Kylian] Burger King
for Jean-Claude Joseph and his team.
[man] Show me.
Okay, that's good.
[expectant song continues playing]
- [song fading]
- [insects chirping softly]
[Kingsley softly] Go, go.
We're good.
Stay there.
Must be something.
[whistling]
What's this?
Go back over there.
It must be there.
And it's not.
INTERNSHIP AGREEMENT
BETWEEN KYLIAN LAFLEUR AND MADAFRET
HOST ORGANIZATION: JEAN-CLAUDE JOSEPH
INTERN: KYLIAN LAFLEUR
What is this?
No way.
It can't be.
This can't be possible.
Fuck…
[sucks teeth]
[darkly intriguing music playing]
FATSO
Now? - 11:00 P.M.
Should we come loaded? - 10K no less
80 Kg - Come to the high school
I'm coming
It'll be at 4:00 a.m. on the 19th
at Bonneville beach
Okay, Milord
[dark music continues]
It'll be at 4:00 a.m. on the 19th
at Bonneville beach
Okay, Milord
[darkly intriguing music continues]
[music continues playing]