[rhythmic beats playing]
[coffee maker rattling]
-What do you mean, you don't know?
-I don't… I don't know.
I went to bed.
I woke up. Yusuf was gone, okay?
He left us the keys to the truck
and directions to the barn.
That's it.
Are you paying attention?
You put this down, boom,
pick one, then you do the cup.
Thank you.
[Morgan] Oh!
[loud crash]
[pieces clattering]
[yells] Who just disappears
for no reason, huh?
Um… All I can think of, uh, is that,
you know, he seemed upset.
Hm? What do you mean, upset?
Upset with whom?
Me? We just proved
a new fucking drug route.
I think he was just upset
about, like, his girlfriend or something.
How do you know that?
-[Ivan] Andrei.
-[Andrei] Hmm.
Find him.
[Andrei] Okay.
[insects chirping]
[inhales sharply]
[inhales] When the fuck did you get
this information?
We talked the night before.
And?
Come on. Come on, spit it out,
you stupid bitch.
Hey, relax.
[chair scraping]
[Morgan] Oh my God.
[Ivan] Yusuf fucking up this whole thing
for a stupid girl? I mean…
See, he doesn't understand
how easy it is for us to find him. Huh?
Might need you two
to… to… to come to Miami
to finish the deal.
Uh… No.
What did you just say to me?
I just said no, okay?
We have done enough for you.
I have been a very good "friend" to you,
and all I've gotten in return
is a fucking slap in the face
and this deep, gross feeling
like I have just betrayed
everything I stand for.
Our father is the former chief of police.
Our mother is a very public person
in this town at the moment, okay?
There are a lot of eyes on us right now.
We are not gonna go running our mouths.
We're not that stupid,
despite what my sister might indicate
a lot of the time.
So we're gonna be walking out of here,
and you are gonna let that happen.
Don't you fucking dare.
[dramatic music playing]
-Hey.
-Morgan, fuck!
-[Morgan] Yeah.
-[Andrei] You want coffee or no?
[Ivan] Hey.
You sure about this?
[Andrei in Russian] Kill him!
[Ivan] Kill him yourself if it's easy!
[Andrei] Come on, give me the gun.
Give me the gun then.
[Ivan speaking Russian]
[Andrei speaking Russian]
[in English] Fuck! Fuck!
[Nicky] Get in the car.
Get in the car right now.
Why wouldn't you have told me about Yusuf?
[Morgan] I didn't think it was important.
[Nicky] Why, because you slept with him
or something fucking messy?
Do you know that you complicate
everything and everyone that you touch?
[engine starting]
I have given us both
a fresh start here, okay?
And I need you to take that
and run with it.
And I would like to kindly ask
that from here on out,
you stay away from me.
[frenetic music playing]
Happily.
-What are you doing? Oh my God!
-I am staying away from you.
-As far as I can go, right now.
-Okay. All right.
-[Morgan] Hope that works.
-Yeah, it does.
-[gravel crunching]
-[tires screeching]
[music ends]
[opening theme music playing]
-[dogs barking]
-[birds chirping]
[exhales]
[Tareq inhales]
-[Nicky exhales]
-[Tareq breathes deeply]
This might be the most uncomfortable
mattress I've ever slept on.
-I wanna be your date to the gala.
-You are my date.
No, I mean your actual date.
Out and Loud is recognizing you
for being great,
and I don't want you standing up there
knowing that we're hiding this away.
-You sure?
-[inhales deeply] Yeah, I am.
It's not fair to you,
and it's not fair to the congregation.
It's time.
It's been time.
I can't believe I'm saying this,
but I am excited to go on a cruise.
-[exhales]
-[Nicky laughs]
[Nicky exhales deeply]
-I'm proud of you.
-Mmm.
-Want coffee?
-Yes, please.
Okay.
[Nicky exhales]
[exhales sharply]
-[door opening]
-[woman screaming]
[woman] Who are you?
What are you doing here?
Rose!
-[Rose] Reverend Dardano, is that what…
-Rose!
-[Tareq] Nicky, come out here, please.
-How did you get into my house?
[woman over podcast] The only thing
keeping you from the life you deserve
is you.
In order to change
the frequency of your life…
-[faucet squeaking]
-…you must embrace positive affirmations.
I know this might sound corny,
but it works.
[Morgan sighs, sniffles]
-"I am a good, decent person."
-[exhales]
"I deserve good, decent things."
-"I am ready to make that change."
-[breathes deeply]
"I am ready to be that change."
"I am not my past. I am only my present."
[whispers] …my present.
[rapid gunfire]
[siren wailing]
-[gunfire in video game]
-[woman screaming]
-Fuck! Max!
-[male voice in game] Godlike!
If you're gonna be spraying bullets
at homeless women,
can you at least put your headphones on?
I woke up at six to bake these, dude.
Our floors are clean, babe.
-[woman in game] What are you lookin' at?!
-[gunfire continues]
[pan clanging]
-[sirens blaring in game]
-[gunfire in game]
I'm going on a run.
Like, to the grocery store?
No, like… like for exercise.
Why?
Uh, I'm trying something.
[door opens]
-[gunfire in game continues]
-[loud explosion in game]
As many of you know,
I was photographed last week
entertaining three women
on an evening boat ride. [inhales]
A personal choice
my opponent Linda Morelli
seems to have taken issue with. [inhales]
But let me reassure you all
that my personal life
has never stood in the way
of my leadership abilities.
[over speaker] "Family first," she says.
What about this town first?
And to that point,
what if you don't have a family?
-Then what, Linda?
-[Linda sighs]
[Tom] Sure, I make bold choices
and take big swings.
But it's that kind of attitude that
gets you the big boats in the first place.
[Linda] Mm-hmm.
[Tom] So while Linda Morelli focuses on
jungle gyms and kindergarten classes,
I'll be out here continuing to take
big swings for the people of this town.
From my family to yours,
I'll see you at the polls.
He was caught with three hookers
on a boat. Suddenly, it's my problem.
They're called sex workers.
People are gonna see right through this.
They're gonna see right through it.
Can you imagine the audacity?
Is this illegal?
Honey, why are you wearing a suit?
The campaign barbecue invite
said family-friendly.
I know, and that's what
I wanted to talk to you about
before you forced me
to watch that insane video.
-Um, I--
-[Linda] Well, what?
I was wanting to wait
until after the campaign to tell you this,
but it can't wait anymore, so I--
You're sick. It's cancer.
Natalie, is it cancer?
I… I don't know.
It's not cancer, okay?
I don't have cancer.
-I… I, um…
-Oh no. Oh God.
I…
met someone.
[Linda gasps]
[whispers] Nicky!
-And I'm leaving the church.
-Oh.
-[Linda] Whoa.
-And I'm… I'm telling you now
because Rose caught us this morning.
So it has sort of… [inhales]
-[quietly] What?
-…expedited the process a little bit.
And I am… I am going to be his date today
to a very important event,
so I'm gonna be late for the barbecue.
And I… I just wanted to tell you this
and… and let you know
that everything is under control, okay?
-And… and I am good and I am happy, okay?
-[Natalie] Mmm.
[inhales] So, this is obviously something
we're gonna need to get ahead of.
That was the support I was looking for,
thank you so much.
-[Linda] No, Nicky, don't do that.
-Do what?
Expect the clouds to part because
somebody caught you with your pants down.
Your sister and I are waist-deep
in fending off political attacks.
So who is this boyfriend,
this man that you met?
[Linda breathes deeply]
[hammering outside]
It's Tareq Rivera.
[inhales] My Tareq?! [laughs]
Well, I don't think--
Yeah, I don't think you can--
-[inhales] Oh!
-He comes into the store.
It doesn't mean
you can claim him as yours.
-Oh, Nick, you have got to be kidding me.
-Yeah.
Choosing this moment when I can't give
this the amount of attention that I want.
How long have you been
hiding this from me?
Finally, a man in the family
who can work with his hands. [laughs]
Kevin works with his hands.
-No, Kevin works with computers, Natalie.
-Ah.
Okay, yeah. I just… I… I did not want
to tell you until after the election
because I didn't want any of this
to hurt your campaign in any way.
It might. I'm an ally, but it might.
Okay. And I also didn't want
the entire town to know
before I was ready to share this.
-What are you implying?
-Nothing.
Donna's son, Anthony,
came home from Mykonos last summer
with a raging case of chlamydia
from a "hot tub." It was a bathhouse.
She pays his credit card bills. That is
a secret that I will take to my grave.
Mm-hmm. [inhales deeply]
So as for Tom Donaldson,
I think you just spend the barbecue
laughing with kids, talking to families.
You are the people's pick.
-Yes.
-[Natalie] Yeah?
So let's just focus on showing that
to the people.
Okay, hun, I hope you're right.
Honey, bring Tareq by the store.
-I want to give him the family discount.
-[Nicky] Okay.
[funky music playing]
Hmm, uh…
[happy music playing]
[children speaking indistinctly]
-[screaming]
-[laughing]
[man 1] She makes a good point.
She makes a great point.
We tip a waitress.
Why are we not tipping stewardesses?
-Mmm.
-It's fucking rude.
I think they're union.
I dated a flight attendant
back in college.
-[knocking on door]
-[door opens]
[door squeaking]
Afternoon, gentlemen. I just wanted
to drop this off ahead of schedule.
You can always depend on Ivan
to bring in just what he owes us.
Never over-delivers.
[paper bag rustling]
Tell me, how does it feel to be so good
at just doing the bare minimum?
You get your money?
Yeah, we're good.
[music continues faintly]
Your shoes stuck to the floor?
Get the fuck out of here.
[Ivan] Uh, we're… we're closing the store
for a few days.
We, uh, need to drive Andrei to Florida
to visit his mother.
Was that a question?
Because I don't think our boss
would respond very well to being told
by two fucking clowns
that they decided to take a vacation.
-You two fucking sweethearts or something?
-We're cousins.
Can we go to Florida or not?
[man 2] I'll tell you what.
Heads, the clown car
gets to drive to Florida.
Tails, Mom, she's shit out of luck.
[coin clinks]
[exhales]
[Ivan inhales deeply]
Two days. That's it.
Thank you. [exhales]
[Andrei in Russian] Dickheads.
[man 2 in English] What did he say?
[Ivan] Assholes.
[in Russian] Disrespect
your mother like that.
My mother doesn't live in Florida.
They don't know that! I can't
wait to get this fucking deal done.
Bring in cheaper drugs,
eliminate those assholes.
[car horns blaring]
[Andrei] Soon, soon.
The two of us trying
to swing this thing on our own,
we will look like clowns.
What's the latest on Yusuf?
Working on it. I'll find him.
We need some muscle in Miami.
Serious, badass.
Show the Brazilians
that we're real players
that can handle this operation.
-And drag Yusuf back here…
-I understand.
…by his stupid fucking Nikes
if you have to.
[Andrei] Motherfuckin'…
[in English] I hate this fucking car.
[Ivan grunts]
[door squeaking]
[people speaking indistinctly]
[door closes]
-Hey! Oh. Whoa.
-Hey!
Oh, hi!
Oh my God!
Hey, girl!
Um, we made cupcakes.
-[woman 1] Oh my God
-[woman 2] Oh my God. Cute.
I will be eating one of those immediately.
-Thank you so much.
-[both laughing]
-I can take that.
-[Morgan] Yes!
Thank you.
Something from the registry, I hope.
Yes. Promise. [chuckles]
It's pink like all your, um…
your pink stuff.
-Yeah, thank you. [laughs]
-She knows me so well.
-It's, like, my favorite color. [laughs]
-[squeals] Yeah.
-[woman 1] Come on in.
-Okay.
[woman 1] Here, can I get you guys
a little bottletini?
What is that?
-[woman 1] So, obligatory shower game.
-[women gasp]
This is called dirty diaper.
-Oh my God, yes.
-[people laughing]
[laughing, clapping]
And Morgan…
-[Morgan clears throat]
-…since you arrived last, you're first up.
-[women laughing]
-Oh, nah, someone else can go.
-Put it on.
-Come on, do it.
Um, I'm really bad at games.
[woman 1] Exactly.
So, we have eight dirty diapers,
and you have to guess what's been left
in there by tasting each one.
-[Morgan] What the fuck?
-[Max laughing]
[women exclaiming, laughing]
-What the fuck?
-[Max] Oh my God.
[woman 2] They're chocolate bars, Morgan.
-Yeah.
-[Morgan] Okay.
-If she doesn't wanna go, I call dibs.
-Oh, he'll do it.
-No, no, no. Mm-mm.
-No. Girls only.
-Exactly.
-[Morgan] I'm just gonna…
[Morgan sniffles] Oh.
-[woman 1] You got it? Yeah.
-Mm-hmm.
[man mumbles]
-Oh!
-[all laughing]
-Get in there. Get in.
-Yeah.
-[woman 1] Big bite.
-[Max] Yeah.
-[woman 1] Come on, come on, come on.
-Okay.
[upbeat music playing faintly]
Oh my God, I can't watch.
-[woman 1 screaming]
-[Max laughing]
[women laughing]
I ate the baby shit. I ate the shit.
-[laughing] I ate the shit.
-[clapping]
[cars horns blaring]
[Nicky sighs] You know, for someone
who works with their hands,
they're awfully soft.
-Okay, you're the worst.
-I'm just saying. [laughs]
-I love you, you're the worst.
-It brings up some questions.
Wait. It says
we're supposed to be here, but…
-I don't understand why we can't just ask.
-Does this harbor have-- No.
-What is the reluctance to ask for help?
-It'll be fine, we're gonna find it.
-He might know. Excuse me.
-No, don't bother him. Nick.
Hi, um, are you going
to the Out and Loud event?
-The what?
-Out and Loud.
It's an LGBTQIA+ organization.
They're throwing a… a charity thing.
"Out and Loud" sounds homophobic.
[car horns blaring]
No, it's not… it's not homophobic.
It's-- It's like, good loud, like,
"raise your voice" kind of situation.
And why are you asking me?
[people speaking indistinctly]
-We were just…
-I don't… He's being--
My boyfriend is being honored
at the event,
and I just-- You have nice jeans.
Honored for what? Including the "IA+"?
Okay, do you know the place or not?
That's New York City.
The whole town is
an LGBTQQIP2A+ event, so…
-[Tareq] Great, thank you. Yeah.
-Thanks so much.
[funky music playing]
[Nicky] Why does our community
have to be so divided?
-[Nicky] What did I do to him?
-You bothered him.
Ugh! Speaking of dirty diapers,
we told you guys
about how we're potty training Barnaby.
Yeah, we're doing the ten-minute rule.
So we're in a Homesense,
and he had to go number two,
so we whip out the potty.
-[woman 3 gasps]
-[woman 2] That's cute.
-Aww!
-That's really cute.
[woman 1] That is so cute.
-Sorry, wait, what am I looking at, sorry?
-[Max] Aww.
[man in video] High five.
Bam! See?
-Is he shitting in the bedding aisle?
-[woman 1] Yeah.
Morgan, he's two and a half. [laughs]
Right, I know, but like, someone's out,
shopping for a new duvet for their bed,
and your kid's just taking a dump?
[chuckles]
-Babe, it's a baby.
-No. I know, but it is fucking gross.
And did anyone ask the kid
if he wants to be on social media
taking a shit in a Homesense?
Like, that kid will grow up someday.
-[Max] Yeah.
- [clears throat]
[woman 1 exhales]
[woman 1] Well, it's, like, really good
to see you guys. We've missed you.
-[woman 2] Oh, yes.
-[woman 3] Yeah.
-You guys would have the cutest kids.
-[woman 3 gasps]
-[woman 2] Yes.
-[woman 3] Aww.
-[woman 1] It's true, right?
-When are you guys gonna go for it?
-Maybe… Maybe someday. Yeah, I don't know.
We know, Morgan.
It's, like, really amazing,
and you would be, like, an amazing mom.
-[woman 3] Yeah.
-[woman 2] Come on. You guys are ready.
-[woman 2] You're ready.
-[woman 1] Yeah.
-You've been together for so long…
-You would love it.
For you guys, it works,
but I think, you know…
-[woman 3] No.
-You are perfect together.
-[woman 3] You'll love it.
-[woman 2] Oh my gosh, yeah.
I can't have kids!
[awkward silence]
[vehicle passing by]
I, uh… [sighs]
I can't have them, so…
Yeah, I would love
to sit around all day, Tara,
and watch your kid shit
all over the place, but…
Uh, it's kinda hard for me right now, so…
[woman clears throat]
Excuse me.
And I'm sorry that I ruined this party.
I didn't wanna do that, okay?
Thank you for having us.
This was really beautiful.
Get the fuck up. Get up,
get the fuck over here. We're leaving.
-[Max] Sorry.
-[women murmuring]
[upbeat music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[music ends]
Is it on a boat?
No, the invite just said Pier 49.
-Okay, well, we're on Pier 49.
-This doesn't look like a gala.
Looks like a bunch of people who don't
know where they're supposed to be going.
Okay.
[chattering continues]
Teagan's phone's disconnected.
[Nicky] Can you call someone else?
Teagan organized this whole thing.
They're the only person I ever dealt with.
Okay. I mean, I… I don't know
what to tell you.
I do see some lesbians, though.
So, worse comes to worst,
they'll figure it out for us.
Nick, stop, please.
Just stop for a second, okay?
This isn't funny, okay?
Okay.
The website's down.
Something's wrong. [exhales]
[inhales] I gotta figure out
what's going on here.
-Do you want my help?
-No.
[funky music playing]
[people speaking indistinctly]
Does anyone know what's going on? Okay.
[music continues]
[bell ringing]
[people speaking indistinctly]
[music ends]
[bell ringing]
-What am I gonna be today?
-It's a surprise.
-Can I get a hint?
-No.
Oh, you're a little firecracker,
aren't you?
Well, I think we're about finished up,
so thank you, Arabella.
-I'm not done.
-I'm done.
-Oh. Whoa. My goodness.
-[Linda laughs]
Great job. Can I-- Ma, can I talk to you?
-Yes!
-Over there.
-Kevin, honey, you wanna take my spot?
-[Natalie] Take it, Kevin.
Yeah.
I… Um…
What?
-What… what did you do? What'd you do?
-Cozying up to the families.
-Why? You're making me nervous.
-Tom is here.
-What do you mean Tom is here?
-He is here right now.
He's walking towards us
and he's pulling focus…
-[Linda] Oh my God.
-…so I would just take the high road.
Natalie, I did not burn my bra
to be talked down to by my own daughter.
I know how to handle him.
-Yeah.
-[Linda] Tom.
[Tom laughs]
Didn't expect you to come out today.
Appreciate the support.
[Tom] Yeah, I just wanted to stop by,
remind people that after they get
their kid a free hot dog,
I'm available to answer
any grown-up questions
they might have
about our upcoming election.
Well, I appreciate you taking
time away from your boat…
-Oh.
-…uh, but these are good people
who have a very clear sense of my values.
And I wouldn't want you
to scare anybody off,
so I'm gonna ask you all
to take this across the street.
Oh, see, last I checked,
it was a free country,
so I can do what I'd like.
-[Natalie] Linda, I think you're needed.
-Okay, hon.
-Well, give my best to your wife and kids.
-[Tom] Oh, yeah.
Well, my wife has been
my biggest supporter, as have my children.
We're a stronger family because of it.
But you wouldn't know what that's like.
You take care, Tom.
-[Tom] Yeah. And speaking of hot dogs…
-[Natalie muttering]
…I heard your son's involved in
a bit of a sex scandal at the church.
Yeah, my neighbor said
he's, uh, stepping down. Oof.
Poor kid. [inhales]
But I guess that's what happens
when you grow up in a broken home.
[inhales] But by all means, kitty cat,
family first.
-[Tom gasps]
-[Natalie] Oh.
-Mom. Run.
-Natalie, get me out of here.
-[Linda] Where do I--
-Legs. I'll carry you.
[Max] Are we gonna talk about it?
About what?
Okay, well, first of all,
you're on birth control.
Why'd you tell Tara that we can't
have kids? That's fucking crazy.
I didn't. I didn't say "we."
I didn't say "we," I said "I."
God forbid anyone think
your dick doesn't work for two seconds.
[inhales] And you know, like,
what if I couldn't have kids?
Okay, but you can.
Okay, but she doesn't know that.
She doesn't know what I'm going through.
-What are you going through, Morgan?
-[sighs]
You're running now.
You're baking cupcakes. Like, this is…
I don't know, okay?
I don't know, I'm trying.
-Trying?
-Yeah, I'm trying. I'm trying.
I'm trying to be a better person,
but I can't… I can't be like those people.
-What's wrong with those people?
-Oh my-- Everything! Everything!
It was a fucking game, Morgan.
It was a game.
Have you thought about the fact
that it actually might do you some good
to eat shit from time to time?
Oh… I would eat shit right now
if it prevented me
from turning into those people.
Who do you think you are, Morgan?
-You are losing it.
-[phone buzzing]
Yeah. Have you ever thought about the fact
that maybe everyone else is
fucking losing it, and I've just, like…
I've just stayed the same.
[buzzing continues]
Natalie, I really don't want to hear it,
okay? We're on our way. We're--
She-- She what?
What the fuck?
[funky music playing]
Do you know how much time
it takes me to look like this?
-I can only imagine.
-A lot of fucking time. Too much time.
I'm sorry, uh, I wish
I had more information.
-Oh.
-I'm just as frustrated as you are.
It looks like Teagan took the money
and ran. I don't know what to say.
Not to mention Out Magazine paid 3K for
a table at an event that doesn't exist.
They're in publishing.
Do you think they have that kind of money?
Look, I know you're not the one
that did the scamming, but you're a chair,
and you're right in front of me,
and a person I can yell at.
[people speaking indistinctly]
[seagulls calling]
You okay?
If I never hear the name Teagan
ever again, it'll be too soon.
[Tareq] Not now, Nick.
Okay.
-It's not your fault.
-But it kind of is my fault.
How?
How is some asshole
stealing money your fault?
Because there were signs,
and I ignored them.
Was Teagan hard to pin down
from time to time? Yeah.
Did I question on a few occasions
if this person was legit?
Was it weird
their bank was in Estonia? Yeah!
But I was so desperate to offset
my guilt that I looked the other way.
What guilt?
This relationship put me
back in the closet, Nick.
And I'm not blaming you for it.
I was a willing participant.
I would make the jokes too. [inhales]
But it doesn't feel good
to hide this away.
I got involved in Out and Loud
so I could stay in this
and not feel like
I was betraying a huge part of who I am.
[indistinct chatter]
Well, there has to be a way
of fixing this, no?
Not unless you know how to get
all those people's money back.
[funky music playing]
[music ends]
[insects chirping]
[Andrei] Former military, ruthless.
Recommendation from a friend inside.
Good. Great.
[opera music playing faintly]
So… you guys think you can handle this?
[speaks Russian]
-Andrei…
-[Andrei sighs]
They… they don't speak English?
So they don't speak English.
They're security.
-[Ivan sighs]
-They don't need to speak English.
You got Yusuf?
Where the fuck is Yusuf?
[breathes heavily]
Istanbul.
-What do you mean?
-He went home.
He use company card to buy a ticket.
[Ivan] He went home?
Business class.
He went home. [chuckles, inhales]
The Brazilians want to meet
our operations team, you fucking moron.
-Can't just be the two of us.
-Three isn't much better.
Well, three is better than two.
Three people who actually speak English,
who know the route.
Do you have any idea
what the Brazilians will do to us
if they don't think we can handle this?
Yes, kill us.
And if I get killed,
I will make sure you know
you were the reason for it.
I'll get killed too, you fucking idiot,
so what difference will that make?
[Andrei yells]
[opera music playing loudly]
[Andrei yelling in Russian]
-[loud thud]
-[screams]
[music continues]
[both yelling, grunting]
[Ivan screaming]
[loud smack]
[Andrei grunting]
[Ivan screaming]
[screaming continues]
[music ends]
[doorbell ringing]
-[grunts softly]
-[Andrei groaning]
-[loud thud]
-[floor squeaking]
[opera music playing faintly]
[door unlocks, creaks open]
[insects chirping]
The fuck are you doing here?
[door slams shut]
-Who are they?
-None of your fucking business.
-The fuck is he doing here?
-[Ivan] Uh…
-You both wanted us to come to Miami.
-[Ivan] Yeah.
Yeah? [exhales]
I am willing to do that for you
if you do something for me first.
And the girl. We need the girl too.
She's tougher than he is.
All right, well…
And what… what do you need from us?
[exhales]
You know people who can track people down,
you know, make things right?
You need a hit.
-A what?
-[Andrei] A hit.
-You need them to disappear.
-No. No, no, no, no.
I-- There's… [inhales deeply]
There's somebody who has just stolen
a lot of money from a lot of people, okay?
I just need you to find them and do
whatever it takes to get the money back.
Okay? But not a hit.
So… so, I don't know, scare them…
-But without the hit part.
-[Ivan] Mm-hmm.
-[Andrei] You have info on them?
-Yeah.
Then both of you
will have to come to Miami.
-Well, I can only speak for myself.
-[phone buzzing]
[Nicky sighs heavily]
Okay, well, if you can let me
take this call,
I could try to convince
"the tougher one" to come.
-[Ivan] Go ahead.
-Morgan, what do you want?
She what?
[funky music playing]
[music ends]
[Annette] Oh, Jesus Christ.
-What is that, an owl?
-It's a fucking possum, Nicky, okay?
It's a goddamn possum.
-You couldn't have washed off the paint?
-Morgan!
Do you not think we thought about that?
It's not water-soluble.
If we tried, it would only make it worse.
Well, there's nothing we can fucking do
about it now, okay? So, enough.
[Linda sighs heavily]
[Annette] Here's what's gonna happen.
I am going to walk you down those steps,
past the press, and into the car, okay?
[Linda] Yeah.
That's what we're gonna do.
Is everybody clear?
-[Natalie] Mm-hmm.
-Okay.
You've worked way too hard
for this to derail you now, Linda.
Yeah.
[inhales] Okay, good, let's go.
Okay, and maybe turn your head away
from the cameras. [inhales]
-[door squeaking]
-[reporters shouting indistinctly]
[reporter] One question!
What do you have to say
about Tom Donaldson?
[cameras clicking]
Mrs. Morelli, care to comment
on the allegations of assault
coming from Mr. Donaldson?
-Bullshit, let it go.
-No, no, assault?
Is that what he's--
Is that what he's calling it?
Okay, sure.
Um…
[inhales] Here's the truth.
[cameras clicking]
There are very few things that
a mother won't do to protect her son,
especially when he's found love
after dedicating two decades of his life
to the church.
You fuck with my family, you fuck with me.
And I'm sorry if that sounds déclassé
or something,
but that's who this mother is.
-See, Tom Donaldson got something…
-Linda, the car's right here.
…very wrong about me.
Yes, my campaign is built on family first,
but the thing is,
I consider this town to be my family,
and I will protect it,
and I will fight for it
with the same maternal instincts
that I did for my son this afternoon.
So if Tom Donaldson
considers a little tap on the nose
from this lowly mother of three assault,
then I'm afraid… [laughs]
…he has totally underestimated
just how powerful my family is.
-[reporter 1] Linda!
-[reporter 2] Linda Morelli!
[reporters clamoring]
[car door opens]
-I need you to come with me to Miami.
-Oh, thank God.
[techno music playing]
[music ends]