"Episode 4"
Don't come here anymore.
Huh?
Why?
Stop joking like that.
Am I a nuisance?
I'm sorry.
I'll stay out of your way.
So please don't stop me.
Rei,
you're not a nuisance.
Then...
You need to manage your time better.
I've told you before.
Before you start designing houses,
you need to design your own life first.
I'm not interested in a fleeting,
momentary relationship.
And do you think you can
expect a good relationship
from someone who is irresponsible
about their own life?
That's just who I am.
If you can't accept that,
don't come back here.
But if I can prove
I can take responsibility...
Can I come back?
Only if you can follow
through on your words.
Prepare to go home.
I'll wait in the car.
Don't dwell on what's already done.
Focus on your next task
and give it your all.
Got it,
troublemaker?
If you don't dry off,
you'll catch a cold.
Taking care of you would be a hassle.
You said you wouldn't comfort me.
"Love in The Air -Premonition of Love-"
(I'll become an architect.
Please let me pass)
(I'll become an architect)
Rei!
If we don't hurry,
the lecture will start soon.
- Sorry, coming!
- Mhm.
Oh, I forgot to bring it.
- Sorry! Go ahead!
- Mhm.
(I'll become an architect.
Please let me pass)
I'll do my best!
First,
I need to design my own life.
Being too confident was the cause.
Mhm.
Rei being the first one here?
Is it going to rain?
Return like this.
Does anyone have any questions?
- Yes!
- Yes, Amemiya?
Which is better, the previous model
or this model?
Haa...
(Rei)
Alright.
- The race is the day after tomorrow.
- Mhm.
Aren't you going to practice?
Don't need it for some amateur.
I heard this guy Fuma is supposed
to be an incredible racer…
Will you be alright?
Sorry.
Just shut up and listen to what I say.
Don't worry.
My hands are great.
Rinka?
Want to grab breakfast together?
Mhm.
You see...
What?
Like him, right?
Arashi-senpai.
Who?
I said Arashi-senpai!
Why? Do you need a reason
to like someone?
At first, I just admired him.
But after we talked
at school the other day,
I realized I really like him.
You're close with him, right?
You'll help me, won't you?
Hmm?
Mhm! This is good!
Oh, it's delicious. Do you want some?
- I'll share some with you. Alright.
- Oh, thanks.
The person you liked
is now your rival, huh?
Huh?
Rei,
I'm asking seriously,
do you like Arashi-senpai?
I don't.
Before answering so quickly,
ask your heart first.
Take your time.
Only you can understand
your feelings.
Man, talking seriously
gives me goosebumps.
Model, check.
Blueprints, check.
Done!
All done!
Haa...
Tonight, unstable atmospheric conditions
may lead to localized
severe thunderstorms.
Stay safe, everyone.
- Good morning.
- Oh!
- You're up early.
No, you Raita-san.
I woke up after that guy.
I heard he wants to hurry up and
finish his other work
for tonight's race.
No matter how busy he was in school,
he never gave up
on customizing machines.
That guy has always hated losing.
- I'm heading back.
- Oh?
Aren't you going to meet him?
We agreed I'd only come back
once I could prove myself.
- Sorry for the interrupt.
- Huh?
Rei.
Good luck.
Mhm.
The concept behind my design is
‘a home that harnesses nature's
power to create comfortable living.'
Opposite the living room
is a Western-style garden
with a meeting area specially
designed for family gatherings,
with a layout that provides space
for each family member
to engage in various activities.
Based on these principles,
I designed this home.
That concludes my presentation.
A well-thought-out concept,
suited to contemporary needs.
It's clear you've gained
a deeper understanding.
Thank you very much!
Presentation went well, didn't it?
Then what's with that face?
Remember when you asked if
I liked Arashi-senpai?
You told me to ask my heart.
Mhm.
I still don't know if it's love.
But
one thing I do know,
I don't want to give up.
But…
I'm still far from being
the kind of person he accepts.
Someone who can take
responsibility for their own life.
Rei, do you know?
I always call you annoying, right?
Well, 90% of the time, I'm lying.
You're not the type to give up easily,
I like Rei the way he is.
Both happiness...
And fortune...
Favor the bold.
Mhm.
So, what do you
want to do most right now?
I want to prove myself to him.
I'm going to see him!
That's the spirit.
Ah.
But
there's one problem.
Rei.
About Arashi-senpai…
- You're going to help me, right?
- No.
I…
can't.
- Huh?
- I'm sorry!
About Arashi-senpai,
I respect him,
or I want to be accepted by him,
and, maybe, like him as a person.
Honestly, I don't even know how I feel.
But...
That...
means love.
Huh?
I understand your feelings, Rei.
I won't ask you to help anymore.
Sorry.
I'll handle my feelings by myself.
I'll be honest about my feelings.
You should do the same.
If you can't accept that,
don't come back here.
You need to design your own life first.
Dammit!
Hey! You cheated, right?
Don't blame me for your lack of skill.
If it weren't you...
It's your fault, you mechanic!
You're the one who chose the bike.
It's your trash tuning job
that's to blame!
If you hadn't rigged it,
I'd have won!
Pathetic.
What did you say?
A real racer doesn't whine like a child.
Aren't you ashamed of yourself
in front of the crowd?
I'll handle the bike next time.
Let's have another race.
The racer...
is you.
You damn mechanic.
You'd better not race.
Okay, I'm on my way.
Where is Arashi-senpai?
He seems to be in a bit of trouble.
- Yay!
Do it!
Hey, they're here!
- They're here!
- Do it!
- So awesome!
- Wow! Arashi!
Awesome!
- Do it!
- Go for it!
Arashi, go for it!
What's going on?
Woo!
Oh.
Ah, is this the famous Arashi's boy?
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
Don't make that face. He'll be fine.
Arashi doesn't do things
he can't handle.
Ah!
Ha!
- He's finished!
- Woo!
Rei?
I'm so glad you're okay!
Were you worried?
Because Raita-san said
this was a dangerous race.
It's just a race.
I...
There's so much I have to tell you.
Something to tell me?
You told me to prove
I could take responsibility, right?
I know I'm not there yet,
but I did my best.
I wanted to be the first to tell you.
Can I stay by
your side?
- Wow!
- Yay!
Hey!
This is rigged, isn't it?
Come here, let's compete again!
Where are you going, you damn mechanic?
I haven't lost yet.
You troublemaker.
You confuse me.
I didn't come to see you for this.
You asked me earlier, didn't you?
Can I stay by your side?
Mhm.
I'm answering that question.
Don't stop me.
I won't hold back anymore.
Are you okay?
Mhm.
Are you going to do another
dangerous race again?
Mhm...
Probably not.
I love the sound of engines,
but I don't need to ride a bike.
It's like building a house,
but you don't need to live in it.
Hmm?
Was that the reason
you aimed to be an architect?
When I was a kid,
my mom would complain to my dad.
She'd say, 'You customize bikes, but why
don't you do the same with the house?'
That's when I thought,
I'll make both bikes and houses
cool.
But when I actually tried both,
it was insanely difficult.
But...
But I can't give up either.
I...
get what I want with my own strength.
It's like the rain on the day we met.
Rei.
Hmm?
The time for you to court me
let it be over.
Huh?
No.
Don't say things like that.
Don't cry.
What I'm trying to say is...
This time, I'll court you.
You're terrible!
You can choose.
What?
Whether you'll become mine,
or I'll become yours.
I...
won't choose either.
I'll have both.
You're a bad child.
You need a punishment.
No!
Kai-kun,
I love you.
No!
Calm down.
It's just a dream.
It's okay…
It's okay.
“Not Just the Rain, but
the Storm Approaches”
"Love in The Air -Premonition of Love-"
Rei.
If you don't hurry,
the lecture will start soon.
- Sorry, coming!
- Mhm.
(I'll become an architect)
(Please let me pass)
(I'll become an architect
Please let me pass)
I'll do my best.