Good stuff.
Lord Cheng,
what would you like to buy today?
I just got a new batch of saddles.
Shall I show them to you?
What were you just looking at?
Well...
Nothing. Nothing.
They are just ordinary ores.
Nothing special.
Lord Cheng,
take a look at these saddles.
They just arrived.
How do you like them?
They are all genuine leather.
Look.
Look, they are all new goods.
Your Majesty.
Due to tax reductions and exemptions,
the army's supplies and soldiers' pay
have become insufficient.
In addition, as the weather turns colder,
we also need to prepare funds
for winter heating.
If this continues,
I'm afraid not only people,
but also cattle and horses
may not survive the winter.
Times are tough right now.
Halve the cost of charcoal for heating.
After surviving the winter,
we'll have the soldiers
farm and herd in spring
to increase grain and fodder supplies.
Your Majesty.
What is this?
This kind of ore is currently circulating
in the markets of Great Yan.
The common people
are using it as a form of currency.
I heard Ximeng has discovered black gold.
I didn't expect
that it has reached Great Yan.
It seems the output is astonishing.
Moreover, Ximeng has risen rapidly
in recent times
and introduced many new policies.
I suspect
it is related to this black gold.
[REBIRTH]
[Episode 29]
Young Master,
over the past few days,
there have indeed been
some people from Great Yong in Ximengcheng
whose movements are suspicious.
Lord Zhuge said in his letter
that he will arrive in Ximengcheng
in 3 days to meet you.
Is it possible
that people from Qingshan Manor
are already in Ximengcheng?
Qingshan Manor inherently carries out
assassinations and investigations
for the royal family.
They have strongholds
in both Great Yan and Biantang.
Since my grandfather could find me here
and send a secret letter,
it means in Ximengcheng,
there must be strongholds
of Qingshan Manor.
Young Master,
then what should we...
Don't worry.
Since grandfather is coming to see me,
he'll make sure I can find him.
Young Master.
I hope you have been well.
I did not expect
that even Ximeng, a land without a ruler,
is still within the reach
of Qingshan Manor's eyes and ears.
There's much you don't know.
[Zhuge Muqing, Chief of Qingshan Manor]
Grandfather?
I just lost my ability
to use martial arts.
I won't die anytime soon.
Why?
What exactly happened?
It was His Majesty.
[Zhan Fu, Spy of Qingshan Manor]
He forced the Master
to take poison
that destroyed all his martial arts.
It was because of me?
Yes,
and no.
The Emperor relies heavily
on Qingshan Manor,
but he also fears it.
With the defeat at Meilin Pass,
he blamed our Zhuge family.
Do you think that clumsy corpse
could fool Yan Xun
and Qingshan Manor?
You couldn't even fool Qingshan Manor.
How could you fool the Muhe family,
or those wolves and tigers
waiting to tear our Zhuge family apart?
To avoid revealing any flaws,
we whipped the corpse
and threw it into a mass grave
to be torn apart by wild wolves.
But even so,
His Majesty wouldn't easily believe it.
So you had to use the excuse
of apologizing
and destroy your martial arts
to quell his suspicions.
Not only that.
The Muhe family advised His Majesty
that it was your infiltration
into Great Yan
that alerted the enemy
and delayed the military operation,
causing the great defeat at Meilin Pass.
Half of the spies of Qingshan Manor
were executed.
Grandfather.
It was my fault.
No.
It was the Muhe family.
They have long been trying to replace
Qingshan Manor.
The defeat at Meilin Pass
was just an excuse.
So, Yue,
that's why
I came to Ximeng in person
to take you back.
You are now King Ximeng.
By submitting to Great Yong
under this identity,
you will become a great asset
to our Zhuge family.
The Muhe family's wishful thinking
will come to nothing.
Grandfather.
Yue.
I have failed you.
I have failed your upbringing.
But I've decided...
to leave Qingshan Manor.
Please forget about me.
Just pretend I really died
in the frozen lake.
Yue,
can you really give up everything
and leave with that slave girl?
Where can you go and hide?
In Ximeng?
Or at the ends of the earth?
Qingshan Manor and Great Yong
will find you eventually.
Yue.
You can find me,
but you can't take me away.
This...
is the grandson I raised since childhood.
Now you have
the power to threaten me.
But does that Chu Qiao
know who personally
sent Yan Shicheng's family
to Jiuyou Platform back then?
Back then,
I had no choice.
Even if she knows,
she will forgive me.
Even if
you can explain the Yan Shicheng case,
can you
explain all the dirty deeds
committed by Qingshan Manor?
Qingshan Manor works for His Majesty.
How many people have we massacred?
Although you didn't kill them yourself,
you are the Chief of Qingshan Manor.
Can you absolve yourself?
Yue,
once you are a member of Qingshan Manor,
you always will be.
I am like this,
and so are you.
This...
is our fate.
What are these?
Didn't we spread the word earlier
that the Queen
loved crabapples and sand dates,
and that King Ximeng
would pay a high price for them?
This led everyone
to plant them.
The people who planted these fruits
have rushed to deliver them
to the palace for you.
That's because Ximeng's climate
is suitable for planting these fruits.
And what is this?
This is a gift from the people of Ximeng
to King Ximeng and Queen Ximeng.
They say
King Ximeng, without his mask,
is exceptionally handsome
and a perfect match
for the beautiful Queen.
I think
Ximeng's...
Stop!
This is King Ximeng's Palace!
No entering without permission!
I am the sister of Queen Ximeng.
[Jing Xiaoba]
My Lord.
A woman outside is asking for an audience.
She was stopped by the guards.
She says she is the Queen's sister,
whose name is Jing Xiaoba.
Say that again. What is her name?
Xiaoba...
Jing... Xiaoba?
Xiaoba!
Qing...
She seems to have stopped breathing.
Qing?
What's wrong with you?
Qing is dead.
Sixth Sister!
Xiaoba!
What are you all waiting for?
Let's go!
Hurry!
Go!
Sixth Sister,
Qing is...
Go!
Hurry, keep up!
Xiaoba!
Get down!
Hurry! Don't let them escape!
Run!
Well, well, well.
You lowly slaves
are really tired of living.
Take them back
and cripple their hands and feet.
Serving the Old Master
doesn't require hands and feet anyway.
Take them down!
Yes!
You really are Xiaoba.
Ever since we got separated,
I've been sending people to find you.
I finally see you today.
It's just wonderful.
Sixth Sister.
Long time no see.
It's so good to see you.
Let's go.
I'll take you into the palace.
Xiaoba.
Your Majesty.
You must be tired
after traveling so far to get here.
Take a hot bath later
and change into clean clothes.
Let's go.
Who is this?
This is the first time
I've seen such a luxurious bathing pool.
Sixth Sister,
you are living such a good life.
Unlike me,
who is as poor as a beggar.
I was separated from you
when I fled from Great Yong to Great Yan.
After I settled down in Great Yan,
I sent people to find you.
But unexpectedly,
before you returned,
I had an accident
and fell into a frozen lake.
I know.
The Universal Harmony Guild
brought me to Great Yan.
Miss Zhong once took me in.
Later, something happened to her,
leaving me with nowhere to go.
I could only wander around Great Yan
in disguise.
Xiaoba,
you must have suffered a lot.
After I went to Biantang,
I had Minglu keep asking about you,
but we couldn't find your whereabouts.
Great Yan has been constantly at war
and in chaos.
You were in Biantang,
so naturally you couldn't find me.
Fortunately,
we sisters finally reunited.
This is truly a blessing from Heaven.
My beautiful sister is back.
These are my clothes.
I will prepare new ones for you later.
Sixth Sister,
I'm a little hungry.
Can you get me some food?
Okay.
I will go arrange it now.
Xing.
Guards!
Help!
Sixth Sister!
-Zhuge Yue wanted to harass me.
-Xiaoba!
Kill him for me!
Zhuge Yue shouldn't be
such a despicable person.
Why are you doing this?
I hate him.
I want him dead!
Eldest Sister,
Fifth Brother—
all my family
died in Qingshan Manor.
Why can Zhuge Yue live so well?
Why?
Xiaoba,
Zhuge Yue has left Qingshan Manor.
But the Qingshan Manor under his command
killed all my family.
Can simply leaving
wipe off all the blood debts?
Xiaoba!
Let me explain.
Brother Linxi's death
was a misunderstanding.
Zhuge Yue had no choice.
Jing Xiaoliu!
How did Brother Linxi treat you back then?
If you really see us as family,
you should kill Zhuge Yue
to avenge Linxi, who's dead!
Why can't you do it?
Because you are not Jing Xiaoliu.
You are Chu Qiao,
Queen Ximeng.
You are not my real sister.
My real sister
already died in Qingshan Manor.
All of my family died in Qingshan Manor.
I came here this time
just to use you
to get close to Zhuge Yue
and avenge my family.
Since I've failed,
it doesn't matter anymore.
Just kill me.
That way, our Jing family
can reunite in the underworld.
Xiaoba,
if you don't want to accept me
as your sister,
I won't force you.
Take this horse
with you.
There is a bundle on it,
which contains some rations and money.
If you encounter any difficulties
in the future,
you can come find me anytime.
I got this scar
while attacking Li'ancheng.
It has already scabbed over.
No need for medicine anymore.
This scar is the same.
It has healed a long time ago.
Then shouldn't the wound
you got at Qingshan Manor
be healed by now?
Let bygones
be bygones.
Why are you following me?
You regret letting me go
and want to kill me now, right?
The dagger in your hand
is made of glazed iron
exclusive to Qingshan Manor.
Its poison is lethal upon drawing blood.
I...
I didn't know
this was a dagger from Qingshan Manor.
Can you tell me
who gave it to you?
Before,
I was wandering around
and almost starved to death.
A masked swordsman saved me.
He told me he was also a slave,
and his family
was killed by Qingshan Manor as well,
so he helped me find you for revenge.
Grandfather?
Yue,
I knew you would find out
and follow her here.
Yes.
I was the one who arranged for Jing Xiaoba
to assassinate you.
It was you?
You used me?
I will kill you!
If you want to save this girl,
come back to Qingshan Manor with me.
She wanted to kill me,
and you're using her life to threaten me?
Isn't it ridiculous?
She is Chu Qiao's sister.
If she loses her life
because of you,
will Chu Qiao forgive you?
I recognized this dagger long ago.
But before I followed her here,
I still held onto the hope
that it wasn't you.
I didn't expect
I was too naive.
I'm using this girl
just to remind you
that you are the Chief of Qingshan Manor.
You can never wash the blood
off your hands.
Jing Xiaoba is not the only means I have.
I have other ways
to uncover the past
and make Chu Qiao see clearly
what you have done
and what Qingshan Manor
has done before.
Why do you have to force me like this?
Yue,
among the 3 branches of the Zhuge family,
you are the only one I carefully raised.
You are the only hope for Qingshan Manor
and the Zhuge family to survive.
I won't let you leave Qingshan Manor.
Grandfather,
am I...
just a piece of your work?
You should know clearly
that once you are a member
of Qingshan Manor,
you can never leave Qingshan Manor.
Not just you,
but also me,
and every spy in Qingshan Manor.
It is the same for everyone.
I can give you 5 days.
Five days later,
I will be waiting for you
at the teahouse with Jing Xiaoba.
What if I don't go?
If you insist on having your own way,
not only will Jing Xiaoba lose her life—
you should know the rules.
Qingshan Manor will definitely appoint
a new Chief.
If this Chief is not you,
your loyal Moon Guards
will all be executed,
and their families will also die.
They are all people
who have risked their lives for you.
Can you really bear
to watch them getting killed
one by one?
Broad beans, have a taste.
Please come in, sir.
Sir!
A pot of tea.
Coming.
Young Master,
this is the news we brought from Biantang.
Sir, your business is not bad.
It's mainly because the new policy
is so good.
In the past, there was always
catching and killing,
[Your Majesty, Chu Qiao is no longer
in Biantang territory.]
[We have confirmed that she is now
in Ximeng with Zhuge Yue.]
which made people panic.
Business around here wasn't easy.
You must have made a fortune
these past few months.
I've been lucky.
Not only are there merchant caravans
coming to Ximeng for business,
but many people
from Great Yong and Great Yan
have also moved here with them.
Your business
will definitely keep booming.
Thank you. I sure hope so.
Enjoy.
Here, sir.
Your tea and snacks.
Sir,
you are from Great Yan, aren't you?
Yes.
We are merchants from Great Yan.
We want to buy some herbs.
Sir,
how did you know?
My stall might be small,
but ever since our King Ximeng
issued the trade decree,
I've seen plenty of merchant caravans.
From your clothes and accent,
I could guess roughly.
Sir,
you dropped something.
Thank you.
Sir,
the woman in this portrait
is very beautiful.
She looks a bit like our Queen.
The woman in this portrait
is the one I love.
You are a lucky man, sir.
Enjoy.
Be careful.
Thank you, General Cheng.
Honey,
I brought some fruit for you to try.
You are so thoughtful.
These are fresh apricots
and Xiangsuguo fruit.
I picked them out especially.
They are very sweet.
Thank you, my dear.
She doesn't look like
the one in the portrait.
Here are the spy leaders
of Qingshan Manor's 4 strongholds
in Ximeng.
They're all here.
I know
you want to use them
in exchange
for your freedom and Jing Xiaoba's.
But you've overestimated their value.
Qingshan Manor lacks anything but spies.
A few deaths
don't mean anything to us.
Of course, it's not just them.
As far as I know,
Qingshan Manor has planted spies
in both Biantang and Great Yan.
Although I have left Qingshan Manor
for a long time,
with the abilities I had
when I was still in charge of it,
within 10 days,
I can uproot all these hidden sentries.
By then,
your years of hard work in Qingshan Manor
will go down the drain.
Master!
Yue,
actually, before I came to Ximeng,
I already expected
the result would be like this.
I raised you since you were little.
I know you best.
Once you make a decision,
you won't change it easily.
But I just didn't want to admit defeat.
I wanted to try again
to see
if I could keep you.
I can't force you to do anything,
nor can I make any decisions for you.
If Qingshan Manor
is destined to end
in my hands,
that is destiny.
I can only watch helplessly
as the Muhe family gets what they want.
I...
have one last thing to remind you.
If Qingshan Manor can find you,
anyone in Great Yong can do the same.
As many people
are watching our Zhuge family,
just as many are watching you,
including His Majesty
and
those who want to ascend the throne
of Great Yong in the future.
If you...
want to leave Qingshan Manor
and live according to your own will,
you can only...
rely on yourself.
Yue.
I...
am already in my twilight years.
I can only...
do this much for you.
You...
take care of yourself.
Zhuge Yue,
don't think that because you saved me,
what you have done can be written off.
One day,
I will eventually kill you for revenge.
This Xiaoba is really ungrateful.
And I even gave her a good horse.
Congratulations to the King and Queen
of Ximeng on implementing the new policy.
This seems
to be some kind of sacrifice.
Let Great Yong and Great Yan fight again!
Let him kill Zhao Che!
Everyone infected with the plague
ends up with their entire body rotting.
What's wrong with you?
Chu, you belong to me,
me alone.
I never thought
I would have a day like this with you.