[Fate Chooses You]
[Episode 39]
Lu Qianqiao...
Lu Qianqiao!
Lu Qianqiao,
don't go!
I'm Xin Mei!
Come back!
Lu Qianqiao!
No...
He forgot.
No!
[One year later]
How did you find time to come see me?
Someone asked me to pass a message to you.
Go ahead.
Close your eyes.
Do you feel it?
Feel what?
The "field."
"Field?"
Taoism often says
that all things are alive with spirit.
Life exists
in forms and states
far beyond
what we can imagine.
In this world,
the things we can see
and touch—
like flowers, birds, fish, insects,
all kinds of beasts and creatures,
you, and me—
are actually all the same kind of life.
What else is there?
There are many more.
The field is one of them.
It is consciousness
detached from the physical body.
It is the thought that can take form.
It is the subtle fluctuations
perceptible only in higher realms.
I don't understand.
What exactly are you trying to say?
Sheng has transformed into a field.
Xia Xuanzi killed his wives and children,
committed endless atrocities,
and had long since become a demon.
But Sheng sacrificed herself
and perished together with him.
By that merit alone,
she earned the right to ascend to godhood.
Sheng has become a god?
Yes.
But unfortunately, the heavenly ladder
had long since broken.
Mortal bodies of the mundane world
cannot ascend to heaven.
So Sheng could only ascend
by transforming herself
into a field.
If the Crazy Taoist's prophecy
is true,
that god must be me.
After all, a demon god is a god,
isn't it?
So,
Sheng is already in heaven.
What divine post does she hold?
She has yet to ascend.
Why?
She still has an obsession.
After transforming into a field,
she's been wandering the mortal realm.
She's been wandering all this time?
Where is Sheng now?
Upon unreachable mountain peaks,
across plains of boundless green,
or in the depths of the ocean
silent for millennia.
Or perhaps
she has become a tree,
a flower,
or a speck of dust
resting in your palm.
A field can be anywhere
and anything.
A field
is everywhere.
She came looking for you, right?
I've cultivated the Path of Detachment
to its pinnacle.
All things are spiritual to me.
Occasionally, I can hear
her voice.
It's just that...
I don't know
if it counts as a voice.
Do you know
why she still lingers in the mortal realm?
She can't let go—
so she lingers still.
She told me you have a wish:
to break the Curse of Five Deficiencies,
free Lu Qianqiao
from the fate of the War Demons,
and allow him to live
an ordinary, peaceful life.
She wants to help you fulfill that wish.
But how can that be done?
Go to the divine realm
and lift the curse
placed upon the War Demons.
This is...
The path to heaven that the field
has opened for you.
The only reason she's lingered here,
bound by this obsession,
is to
open this path for you
and send your primordial spirit to heaven.
Go.
Once your long-held wish is fulfilled,
she will finally be able to let go
and complete her ascension.
Young Deity.
Greetings,
Immortal.
Greetings, Young Deity.
Where are you from, Immortal,
and what brings you here?
I come from the mortal realm below,
and I would like to ask for directions.
May I ask where the Deity
in charge of the archives
can be found?
The mortal realm below?
You must mean
the Penghu Immortal Abode
at the foot of Fanyun Mountain, right?
As for the Deity
in charge of the archives...
Since the heavenly ladder broke,
no new gods have ascended.
So these minor matters
have all been left to me.
I wonder where I might find the archives
concerning the War Demon clan.
Anything with the words "War Demon"
is here.
What exactly
are you asking about, Immortal?
A thousand years ago,
the War Demons violated the heavenly laws
and were punished with
the Curse of Five Deficiencies.
Their entire clan was condemned to
violent bloodlust, insensitivity to pain,
sleeplessness, color blindness,
and the taste of decay
in everything they consumed.
The thousand-year sentence
has already passed,
yet the curse upon them remains.
So,
could you look into
why that is?
A thousand years?
Curse?
Found it.
Done.
Done?
Are you sure the curse has been lifted?
Didn't you watch me
erase it with your own eyes, Immortal?
That's all it takes?
Yeah.
What else would it take?
Immortal,
is there anything else you need?
I...
No.
You've come from afar.
You can visit Zhenghua Palace
while you're here.
The Gods of the Five Directions
are hosting a wine tasting.
If you have nothing urgent,
you're welcome to drink your fill
before you leave.
Immortal, why are you leaving?
Zhenghua Palace is not that way!
Immortal!
[Xin Xie Manor]
Bamboo hats!
Handwoven bamboo hats!
Come and take a look!
Handwoven straw raincoats
and bamboo hats!
Come take a look!
Come on! Straw raincoats!
Bamboo hats!
All handwoven!
Straw raincoats!
Come on!
Cheers!
Sit, sit.
Come on.
The dishes today are pretty good.
Eat more.
Yes, yes.
Come on.
Here.
Have some of this.
Eat up.
Thank you all for coming today.
Come on, cheers!
Cheers.
Mei,
don't just eat!
Drink with us!
It's rare for you to come back!
Come on, let's toast together!
Come on, cheers!
Cheers!
Come on, everyone together!
Bottoms up!
Cheers!
Just take a sip.
Come on.
Okay, okay.
Thank you.
Not bad!
Honey water can sober you up.
Drinking it will ease the headache.
Why did you come out?
Brother said you were in a bad mood,
so we came to check on you.
I'm not in a bad mood.
I've just been thinking about
where I should go
from here.
Can't... Can't you just stay?
Can't you stay here
with us?
Aside from Foster Father and Grandpa Pang,
you're the nicest person to us.
Jiujiu and I both hope
you can stay.
But...
I still need to find someone.
But Grandpa Pang said
you have nowhere to go.
Your sect has no one left,
and neither does your family.
Who said I have no family?
I'm married.
I have to go find my husband.
Isn't your husband
our foster father?
He's already dead.
He's not dead.
How is that possible?
We saw with our own eyes
that he was sentenced
to death by 1,000 cuts.
Blades stabbed into him,
blood everywhere.
Didn't you even burn hell money for him
together with us?
That was all meant to fool us.
He is a War Demon,
very powerful.
That execution couldn't kill him.
But unfortunately,
in order to sever
the Jianmu Heavenly Ladder
and save all living beings from calamity,
he sacrificed all his memories.
That is why he hasn't come to find us.
Our memories are what make us who we are.
If his memories are gone,
he'll become
an entirely new person.
But I don't think so.
Even if he's lost his memories,
his nature,
temperament,
habits, and preferences
will not change.
So I must find him.
But...
But he doesn't remember you anymore.
It's okay.
I remember him.
When I find him,
I'll definitely bring him back
to see you.
It's a deal!
Deal.
Immortal Xin!
Immortal Xin, you also came back this time
for the birthday banquet?
The banquet isn't over yet.
Are you leaving already?
Yes.
I still have other matters to attend to.
I have to leave now.
Then farewell, Immortal Xin.
Come back and visit often
when you have time.
I will when I have time.
Please come in, you two.
Take care.
-Please come in.
-Take a look.
These are all excellent wines.
Excuse me.
Take a look at this one.
Ten-year-aged wine.
Excuse me, coming through!
And this one.
Why do you keep following me?
Here.
It's no use acting all cute with me.
I have a journey ahead of me.
I only have dry food.
No little fish for you.
Stop following me.
Landlady!
Coming, coming!
Look at this mess!
Let me pour you another cup.
I'm so sorry, sir.
I'll get you
a fresh one right away.
Hurry it up.
Didn't you say
you had experience with this?
The last inn I was at had bad business.
Landlady!
Coming!
Take it out and throw it away.
You know where to dump it, right?
Don't worry, Landlady.
All this worrying—
I feel like I've aged another 10 years.
Landlady, where is my food?
I've been waiting forever!
Yeah.
We are short-handed. Please forgive us.
It'll be right out!
Alright, alright, just hurry up!
[Safe Haven Inn:
Your Safety is Guaranteed.
Master.
Master, are you okay?
Are you hungry?
So what if I am?
Can you cook?
I can't.
But the Landlady can.
I'll ask her to cook for you.
Have you found a cook yet?
No.
The Landlady's standards are very high.
Not only does he have to cook well,
but he also needs to know martial arts
and be able to fight.
He also needs to be good-looking,
eloquent,
and skilled at coaxing people.
Then she's never going to find one.
That's true.
After all, people like me,
who excel at everything
and can do anything,
are quite rare.
And which of those qualities
do you think you actually possess?
Which one do I lack?
Never mind.
Get back to work.
Master.
I've noticed
you've been out of sorts lately.
Yeah.
Why have I been out of sorts?
Xin Mei?
Mei!
What a rare guest.
Why are you here?
Just passing by.
Thought I'd drop in.
Why are you here?
I can't manage on my own,
so I asked him to come help.
Not only does she not pay me,
but I also have to help
train the new staff.
Landlady, you hired someone new?
It's me.
Mei,
I'm working as an attendant here now.
Master kept me here
to teach me martial arts.
Attendant!
Landlady!
Coming!
Hurry up and sit inside.
I'll cook some nice dishes later,
and we'll have a proper drink together!
Okay.
Come on, let's go.
Coming, coming!
Your business is good.
The inn has changed.
Changed?
Yeah.
The times have changed.
A new emperor has ascended,
placing great importance on craftsmanship.
Schools are being established everywhere,
with dedicated courses in craftsmanship.
A few days ago,
I even came across Tang You
teaching classes at a school.
Oh, right,
a new city has sprung up
in the south
called Yandu.
It's where master craftsmen gather.
I heard that in a while,
they'll hold
lectures there
on the Unparalleled Secret Magic.
That's great.
It means the choice we made back then
was right.
The Unparalleled Secret Magic
is truly a scripture to save the world.
However,
it's been hard on the Landlady.
Nowadays, nobody comes here
fighting all day anymore.
Doing inn business now
depends on good food
and attentive service.
Just the other day
I even overheard them discussing
whether to rename it the Fortune Inn.
How have you been lately?
Same as always.
I was in seclusion a while ago
and just came down the mountain.
What about you?
What are your plans from here on out?
I have a friend
who has asked me to
help with a tricky matter.
Once I've settled things here for An,
I'll leave.
If it's tricky,
remember not to push yourself too hard.
Attendant, another jin of beef!
Coming right up!
Here.
Are you
a bit reluctant to leave?
Actually...
To be honest,
I've been feeling
very different lately.
Look,
can you tell
what's changed about me?
You...
got fatter.
What are you talking about?
I'll let you in on a secret.
Upon reaching the Great Completion Stage
with my Divine Sword,
it felt as though something within me
had unlocked—
my progress soared.
My cultivation
has been progressing by leaps and bounds.
I can barely gauge
what level I'm even at anymore.
I mean it!
I constantly feel
the sword will surging inside my body.
Now I don't even need to pick up my sword.
The moment I close my eyes,
all those moves
and mental techniques
appear right in front of me.
It's as though all things in existence
have become swords for me
to command at will.
Tell me,
am I about to achieve godhood
through martial arts?
That impressive?
It is that impressive!
And another thing—
lately, I keep feeling like
there's heavenly lightning
about to strike me.
It's gotten so bad that I don't
even dare walk through open spaces.
Lightning is going to strike you?
Master,
did you do something
wicked that defies heaven?
Attendant,
another pot of wine!
Go away. What does a kid like you know?
Don't they say when mortals seek to
ascend to godhood,
they must summon heavenly lightning
to temper their bodies?
Could this be a sign
that I'm about to become a god?
Now that the heavenly ladder is broken,
even if you become a god,
you can't ascend to heaven.
That would mean
you'd be stuck in
the mortal realm forever,
getting struck by lightning every day.
Right,
there's a letter for you.
It was delivered quite some time ago
and said to be from
Heda Snow Mountain in North Xiang.
Lu Qianqiao,
Xin Mei,
I've found a home.
My home is beautiful.
Don't worry about me.
Zuo Yingying.
Who sent the letter?
She's found a home.
Just these few words.
Is it really worth a whole letter?
Why didn't she mention me in the letter?
An!
-To think I treated her to so many meals!
-Come on!
The dishes are here!
Hurry.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
A kitty.
Is this your cat?
So cute.
What a silly cat.
So wild.
Come on, let's eat.
The food is getting cold.
-Here.
-Attendant.
Coming.
Another pot of wine!
Please wait a moment.
A letter has arrived!
There's a letter for her.
Yingying, a letter for you.
"Yingying,
it's been a long time.
As I write this letter to you,
I'm at the Safe Haven Inn,
having just drunk Lord of Rust-Sword's
treasured fake wine.
I feel a bit lightheaded,
but I have an overwhelming urge
to say so many, many things
to you.
Business at Safe Haven Inn
has gotten even better.
Lin Muhan has taken over Lingji Mountain,
along with the remaining disciples
of the Tianyuan Sect,
becoming the new leader
of the immortal sects.
He's matured a great deal.
Under his leadership,
the Immortal Sect Assembly
runs flawlessly.
He said
it doesn't matter
if the heavenly ladder is broken;
he will lead all cultivators
to find a new way forward.
As for the Lord of Rust-Sword,
things are a bit dramatic with him.
He claims he's about to achieve godhood
through the sword path
and keeps feeling as though lightning is
about to strike him.
I told him
that the heavenly ladder is still broken,
so if he wants to become a god,
it will be a bit difficult.
Also...
Lu Qianqiao
has forgotten everything now—
he doesn't remember me either.
But I will find him.
By the way,
I also met Jin Lun.
Since cultivating the Path of Detachment,
he's spoken in even more riddles.
But luckily, he's always been
very patient.
He told me
that Sheng has already become a god
and transformed into
a life form called a field.
Although she can't be seen
or touched,
she can always stay by my side.
Sometimes I can feel
her presence,
and I feel that's enough.
I've also come to understand something.
The old gives way to the new;
the sun rises without ceasing.
Dry riverbeds
will always give birth to new streams.
A withered forest will one day
flourish with life again.
Everything seems
to move in cycles,
turning endlessly.
And we who live in this world
are here to catch one more glimpse
of the sun as it rises anew.
Lastly,
I wish you well,
and may all things go smoothly for you.
Xin Mei."
Yingying.
Didn't you always want to teach me
how to ride a horse?
You're willing to learn now?
Then I'm leaving.
Go on.
Safe travels.
Take care.
Father?
Greetings, Sect Master!
May your might and prestige
shake heaven and earth!
This is
Immortal Xin Mei
from Xin Xie Manor.
This is
Lord Lu Huai.
A strand of dark hair entwined—
bound together in a vow
to share a lifetime.
A vow to grow old side by side,
a perfect union eternally bound.
A perfect match—
truly a union made in heaven!
You knew full well you wouldn't die,
so why did you marry me?
To leave me carrying that burden,
to fill me with resentment on your behalf.
I really want to know:
when I risked my life—
using my meager magic
to seek justice for you
and avenge you—
what were you really thinking?
I was grateful.
Miss Xin,
I'm truly grateful to you.
But I do have
reasons I cannot share with anyone.
They concern my life and safety.
But please believe me,
I never had any intention of harming you.
Even if he's lost his memory,
his nature,
temperament,
habits, and preferences
won't change.
So,
I must find him.
[Yuan Zhong, Youhu Clan]
Yeah, you.
Can I help you, sir?
You scared my fish away.
The current's so strong,
and it just rained.
How could there be any fish here?
There was.
I was waiting for a fish—
a fish I've been waiting for a long time,
finally about to take the bait.
Then you walked by,
and it was
scared off.
I still have things to do.
Then what do you propose we do about it?
Very simple.
Just compensate me.
I heard carp are going for
10 mace per jin these days.
Better-quality bighead carp
can fetch 30 to 50 mace per jin.
My fish was big and fat
and of excellent quality.
Multiply that by 10—
call it 500 mace per jin.
Altogether, you can
compensate me 700 taels.
Are you kidding me?
Even gold and jade
aren't priced like that.
You don't want to pay in money?
Then make it up to me another way.
I waited a long time for that fish.
I wouldn't say
I poured my heart and soul into it,
but I had pinned all my hopes on it.
And now, because you passed by,
the fish ran off.
All my efforts went to waste.
If you can make those lost years up to me,
I'll call us even.
How about that?
How long have you been waiting?
Not long.
Just 40 years.
You, disciple of Xin Xie Manor,
are really unreasonable.
But then again, not just you—
if I were the one doing
this impossible search through the masses,
I wouldn't have the leisure
to waste time with some stranger either.
What do you mean?
Searching for one person
in a vast sea of people.
You know I'm looking for someone?
I not only know who you're looking for—
I know
where he is.
Where is he?
How much money did you say
f-for that fish earlier?
Seven hundred taels...
I'll scrape the money together
and pay you.
Will that do?
That was the price just now.
Now,
it's changed.
Then what would it take
for you to tell me where he is?
As long as you tell me,
I'll do anything.
Anything?
Anything.