=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
(Legend has it)
(that at the end of the East Sea)
(stands the giant Fusang Tree.)
(Beneath it)
(lies the Void Spirit World.)
(Unresolved mortal obsession)
(gathers here.)
(After centuries of cultivation,)
(they become spirits.)
(The one with the highest spirit power)
(becomes the Sovereign of Spirits,)
(ruling all spirits.)
Welcome back,
Your Grace.
♪Forget the form to achieve♪
♪Yet I can't♪
♪Today, a home is granted♪
♪Joy without grief♪
(The current Sovereign)
(was born a spirit.)
(The greatest talent)
(in ten generations.)
(He Simu, Sovereign of Spirits)
(The Sovereign)
(loves roaming the mortal world,)
(watching mortals)
(experience joy and sorrow.)
(Liangzhou)
(is her chosen place to rest and watch.)
(Though immortal,)
(she was born blind to colors,)
(numb to flavors,)
(cold, and warmth.)
(She lacks the five senses.)
(Centuries ago,)
(a Starhaven sorcerer said)
(the master of the Deliverance Sword)
(may be the spell bearer and bring her)
(the five senses.)
(But to this day,)
(words of the past have long faded.)
(Even the Sovereign herself)
(has almost forgotten.)
=Love Beyond the Grave=
=Episode 1=
Save my son.
Save Chenying.
You're begging me?
Aren't you afraid?
Please.
Save my son.
Please save my son.
You are fatally wounded,
but I can grant you
one wish.
By my rules,
I will extract your obsession
and save your son.
Are you willing to let me?
Anything to save my son.
I accept.
Deal.
Such a deep obsession
with his son.
Mortals are so hard to understand.
(Without a sense of touch,)
(I struck too hard.)
(Xue Chenying, Liangzhou villager)
The Great Liang Army is here!
(Liangzhou)
People of Liangzhou, do not panic!
The enemy is defeated!
We, the Great Liang Army,
will take over this city.
(Duan Xu, Commander of Tabai Army)
It's the Great Liang Army!
- You're finally here!
- Great Liang's army!
We'll do our utmost to protect
all citizens in this city.
- No need to hide anymore!
- Indeed!
No need to hide anymore.
The Great Liang Army.
They're here to save us.
They're finally here.
(The Deliverance Sword.)
(My aunt's spirit sword
from 300 years ago.)
(Liang)
(Why would it be)
(in the hands of a young general?)
General.
North Chong massacred the city
before leaving.
Are you here to save us?
Thank you, General.
Thank you, General!
General,
thank goodness you're here.
Miss,
wipe off the blood.
(He really is just a mortal.)
(This body is so weak.)
Please help me.
Save that child.
Take her away.
Take care of her.
Pass down the order.
Reorganize the troops in the city today.
Aside from defensive duties,
everyone must stay in the city
to rescue the surviving civilians.
Anyone caught looting or stealing
will face military law.
- Yes!
(The Deliverance hasn't chosen
a master for 300 years.)
(Could you be its master?)
(Liangzhou Government Office)
Our attack on the North Chong Army
caught them completely off guard.
Out of resentment,
they sacked the city
during their retreat.
This was a man-made disaster.
We were still too late.
How many men did we lose this time?
We lost more than half.
Less than 4,000 men remain.
Xu,
(Xia Qingsheng)
you're new here.
(Meng Wan)
The troops are unsteady.
If the enemy attacks now,
we could hardly hold them off.
How is your rheumatism?
Any discomfort lately?
The weather has been fine lately.
I feel no discomfort.
(It seems sunny weather)
(isn't your favorite.)
(The young general has other plans.)
Father, please don't go.
Father!
Father, where are you?
(This child is truly a handful.)
How are the siblings doing?
The physician said they're exhausted.
They'll recover
after resting for a few days.
Take care of them.
Xu,
don't you think that girl
is very strange?
She mustn't stay here for long.
Father!
Where are you?
Father! Father!
Don't leave me behind!
Father!
Don't leave me!
Don't go, Father!
Father!
Please don't leave me!
Father! Father!
Don't leave me, Father!
Father!
Please don't leave me!
Father! Father!
Father, don't leave me!
Please don't leave me!
For centuries, you're the first
to ever grab my hand.
Father.
Fengyi.
(Hejia Fengyi)
Long time no see, Great Ancestor.
You called for me late at night.
Is there finally a way I can serve you?
Help me look into someone.
Someone from the court.
The one wielding the Deliverance.
The Deliverance has reappeared.
Who is its master?
It's...
♪Cross your legs for three years♪
Hurry up.
♪Tether horse and ape♪
(I'm Duan Xu, Commander)
(of Great Liang's Tabai Army.)
(Enemies retreated
north of the Guanhe River.)
(Today, Liangzhou
returns to Great Liang.)
(The Tabai Army will help you)
(repair the houses)
(and rebuild your homes.)
♪Cross your legs for three years♪
♪Subdue dragon and tiger;
tether horse and ape♪
Thank you.
Thank you, General.
♪Breath soft as silk♪
(As long as I'm here,)
(I'll protect the people of this city.)
(Liangzhou)
(As long as I draw breath,)
(I will keep Liangzhou)
(safe day and night.)
It's warmer, right?
(Liangzhou)
You're awake.
Eat up.
Thank you, Miss.
My name is He Xiaoxiao.
Right now,
my brother and I are weak.
We wish to stay for a few days.
Could you please
ask the General
to make an exception?
By the way,
about the General who saved me,
what is his name?
Something is wrong with you.
You...
Hey, come eat!
Eat slowly.
You are quite scheming.
North Chong's famous Suanxian buns.
Only their people can eat them.
No wonder my brother threw up.
If you suspect
my brother and me,
just kill us.
Since it's North Chong's food,
why did you recognize them at once?
You are definitely up to no good.
Why did you approach the General?
Were you sent by North Chong?
Don't bully my sister!
We are not from North Chong,
nor are we spies.
Why do you keep trying to scare us?
Either show evidence
to prove we are spies
or just kill us right here.
I don't care if you work
for North Chong or Duke Pei.
Whatever you are planning,
you'd better give up soon.
Even if it costs my life,
I will never let you
lay a finger on my senior brother.
Hearing you say this,
the General is quite pitiful.
Stop pretending.
We're very busy.
I'll leave now.
Tomorrow morning,
you must leave.
Keep a close eye on them.
Yes.
What is your name?
Xue Chenying.
Xiaoxiao, don't you like food?
I neither like nor dislike it.
Whatever goes into my mouth,
it has no taste at all.
Hurry up and leave.
(Serene and Clear)
Please take me with you.
Right here.
Start digging.
Please take me with you.
What's your father's name?
Xue Mutou.
Which characters?
I can't read.
Your father is already buried.
Why are you crying for him?
He should be the one crying for you.
(Whittling Wood)
His life has come to an end.
He has no more worldly ties,
leaving you, a little kid,
in this chaotic borderland
to survive all alone.
You're the pitiful one here.
Try throwing a handful yourself.
What is this?
What are you looking at?
It's just a magic trick.
So, Xiaoxiao,
you're a trick master.
Honey.
Let's meet in the next life.
My son must be back.
What an amazing trick.
(The General delivered himself to me.)
Give it back! Give it back!
Let go!
You rob even the dead.
Aren't you afraid of retribution?
Get lost!
Under Tabai Army rules,
for any identifiable corpse,
the belongings on the body
must be fully returned to the family.
You have a death wish!
- Are you okay?
- Kill him!
Yes, sir!
(Draw your sword.)
(Hurry up.)
- Let's go!
- Hurry!
Let's go!
Thank you.
Thank you, sir.
Lay your loved ones to rest.
Thank you.
Thank you, sir.
(Whittling Wood)
Rest in peace.
General.
General, you saved us yesterday.
My brother and I can't repay you.
Please accept our thanks.
Miss, please stop calling me General.
It's best not to alert the others.
General,
are you traveling incognito?
You have a sharp eye, Miss.
We only met briefly yesterday.
Even with my veil on today,
you recognized me instantly.
Of course.
You're highly renowned
and look so heroic.
I've admired you
for so long.
Is that so?
Then what is my name?
No need for flattery, Miss.
If I were truly that renowned,
I should've kept Liangzhou
from being destroyed.
My name is Duan Xu,
as in a supreme martial achievement.
My courtesy name is Shunxi.
My name is He Xiaoxiao.
This is my sworn brother.
He's named Chenying.
Miss He.
Watch out.
(The Deliverance chose him
as its master.)
(Who exactly is he?)
North Chong soldiers!
Catch them!
- Yes!
You aren't the only one
who recognized me.
That was so scary!
You're safe now.
Thanks for your help.
I wish I could say there's no need
for thanks just like you,
but my brother and I
have no family left.
Driven out of the Prefect's Mansion,
we are now homeless,
with no food or shelter.
It's about to snow.
We don't even know
where we'll sleep tonight.
Alright.
I'll help you and your brother
find a place to stay.
Thank you, General.
You just mentioned
it will snow later?
The weather is very odd this year.
Even the Guanhe River has frozen over.
Snowing on a sunny day
isn't that strange anymore.
Though the sun is bright now,
the weather will change soon.
My eyes are very sharp.
Come with me.
(He has no spiritual arts,)
(yet the Deliverance chose him.)
(How is he worthy)
(of the Deliverance?)
Xiaoxiao,
it's snowing.
It really is snowing.
Miss, you were exactly right.
You were out for a day and a night.
If you catch a cold,
I don't want to take care of you.
♪Falling down like snow♪
♪Joys and sorrows of the mortal world♪
♪Swept along by the daylight♪
♪The forms and hues of the mortal realm♪
♪Lingering for a fleeting moment♪
You were unconscious for a day too.
Don't catch a cold.
Don't miss the beauty of the first snow.
Let's walk back together.
♪Dawn and dusk rise and set♪
♪Longing to meet, yet parted by destiny♪
♪Let me wander through♪
♪Light and dark, without turning back♪
(Mortals can be moved)
(by such petty sights.)
♪Accompanied by the abyss♪
(What a pity.)
(I am blind to colors, deaf to music,)
(and numb to cold, warmth, and taste.)
(All beings are like dust,)
(living and dying in a single day.)
(Tianshuo)
(No matter how many)
(deep and fervent desires they hold,)
(they're all but an illusion.)
Great Liang once had a vast territory.
(Great Liang)
Now, it borders North Chong
at the Guanhe River.
(North Chong)
The North and South face off.
North Chong has occupied
the 17 Prefectures north
of the Guanhe River for 60 years.
A winter like this comes once
in a century.
The Guanhe River has frozen over.
The North Chong Army crossed,
pillaging Yuzhou and Liangzhou.
Though we used a surprise attack
to retake Liangzhou,
the North Chong Army
is still lurking outside the city.
The Tabai Army inside the city
is forced into a besieged defense.
The situation is dire.
Duan Shunxi?
Everyone
in the court
knows him.
His family is renowned for scholars
and imperial relations.
Two years ago, he became
the Second-Place Scholar
and became an official,
highly valued by Chancellor Du,
groomed as a future Chief Councilor.
Born to a civil official clan,
why did he take charge
of this border post?
Duan Xu...
He has a sworn foe at court,
the Top Scholar of his exam year,
Fang Xianye, Censorial Counselor.
Duan Xu was impeached by him
and ended up in the army.
Fang Xianye is sharp
and careful in every move,
always outshining Duan Shunxi.
Duan Shunxi fell
from a Chief Councilor candidate
to a general post that may not last.
The one you call
known to all, far and wide,
is that famed unlucky soul.
Who is it?
No one.
Let's go.
Go.
Great Ancestor, Duan Xu...
The Deliverance chose
a dying man.
What do you mean?
In these chaotic times,
he's surrounded by enemies.
How long can he last?
According to my rules,
I'll ask him what his wish is
and grant it.
After he dies,
I'll take the Deliverance.
We won't be taking it for nothing.
It's been 300 years.
The Deliverance finally has a master.
I actually lived to see this day.
No.
(My ancestor is Ji Xi.)
(She's the Great Ancestor's aunt)
(and the best Starhaven sorcerer.)
(She once mentioned in her notes)
(that mortals who bear the spell)
(are extremely rare.)
(Could the master of the Deliverance)
(that appeared after 300 years)
(be the Great Ancestor's spell bearer?)
(Then she can get her five senses.)
Assassins!
Watch out, General!
Guards!
Protect the General!
(This body is freezing to death.)
(How delicate.)
(If not to nourish this body,)
(I wouldn't bother bringing her.)
Xiaoxiao!
Don't leave me!
Xiaoxiao.
Xiaoxiao, where are you?
My child.
Don't be afraid.
Come to Mother.
Stay away!
- Chase! Capture them!
- Chase!
- Yes!
(My Spirits Lantern)
(actually fears the Deliverance?)
(Let me see)
(why the Deliverance
chose you as its master.)
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪