( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
TEN DAYS AGO
HAPPY 70TH BIRTHDAY TO JEON YANG-JA
Their abs are no joke.
Will you look at them?
Your mother's taste
hasn't changed at all.
It has changed a bit.
She's more obsessed
with "defi" than bulk.
"Defi"?
Definition.
Clear outlines.
You don't know?
Whatever. Just give her your present.
She'll like it, right?
Has she ever liked anything?
Even so.
What should I say?
Just hand it to her.
I paid for it anyway.
What did you get?
It's not something small, is it?
Something she can use
to sign contracts with.
A fountain pen.
I had her initials engraved.
There are also diamonds.
Made in Germany.
- Mrs. Jeon.
- Yes?
Happy 70th birthday.
Yes, thanks.
I got you something special
that took some thought.
For when you sign papers.
The chairman is here.
Hello.
Would you like some food?
- What?
- Where's my money?
I have some muscles myself.
Will she pay me if I go topless?
- Yours lack definition.
- So what?
Okay, let's talk outside.
- Ms. Jeon!
- Why would you do that?
Why would you call for her?
I must get her attention
if I'm to ask her for the money.
Her only son-in-law
borrowed from a loan shark
and might have to sell
all his organs.
I asked you to give me a little time.
It's terribly rude
to come here to cause a scene.
- It's rude?
- Yes.
It's rude.
Wait, it hurts.
- Does it?
- Yes.
I'll pay you back.
I'll give you a week.
Tell your mother-in-law, you fool.
Or I'll tell her for you.
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
EPISODE 2
CERTIFIED LETTER REGARDING YOUR DEBT
AND AUCTION OF SE-YOON BUILDING SENT
You may say your last farewell
to the deceased.
We'll take him away now.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Hey, you.
Didn't you say you'd be
at the funeral hall all night?
Yes, but I came by to get something.
Did you?
Get it and go, then.
Wait.
Why is Yi-gyeong...
What happened? Why is she like this?
I abducted her.
What the...
What do you mean?
I kidnapped her.
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
AREA UNDER SURVEILLANCE
MANAGEMENT OFFICE
AWAY ON BREAK
So how much did you lose?
Does that matter?
Will you spot me?
Have you lost your mind?
Do you know what you've done?
It's not too late.
Take Yi-gyeong home.
I'll call you a taxi, okay?
If someone asks about it
say someone kidnapped her
and you saved her.
That's just stupid.
Me, save her?
I'm not like Tom Cruise.
Listen to me carefully.
I'm not joking right now.
This is your last chance.
What last chance?
How long will you live like this?
1 BILLION WON
I'll let you in.
Five hundred million won.
Forget it.
I'll call Gyun's junior officers.
Let them help you
find a legal way out.
Su-jong.
It's not what you think.
I'm just getting the money
I'm meant to inherit.
As long as I get the money,
no one will get hurt.
There's no need to feel guilty
about anything.
- Hey.
- You're being stupid.
Give me my phone back.
- No.
- Give it back.
Give it back right now.
Hand over my phone.
No, I don't want to.
Darn you.
Let go, you punk.
- Let it go.
- No way.
Let go!
Are you all right?
What's this?
Why did you take my phone?
Here. Take it back already.
Do whatever you want.
Struggle in debt
for the rest of your life.
Why would you say that?
You're all brawn and no brains.
What'll you do about this?
Let's wipe off the blood
and clean the cut.
You're so annoying.
I'll take care of everything else.
Just watch over Yi-gyeong
in cold storage.
For just two days.
For two days?
What you have to do
is take this.
Three times a day.
Inject her with this.
Will she be okay?
Hey.
She'll be safe.
She's my wife, isn't she?
Have you made up your mind?
Are you sure it's safe?
Hwal-sung, this lunatic.
What he makes me do.
Oh, dear.
You're cold.
Sorry about this.
MANAGEMENT OFFICE
AWAY ON BREAK
DAD, WHERE ARE YOU?
Shoot.
COLD STORAGE
Hey.
What are you doing here, Da-rae?
There's so much dust in there.
(Mom's not doing well at all.)
She's not?
Let's go home.
PORRIDGE
(Eat, Mom.)
(He got it for you
from your favorite porridge place.)
Gi Da-rae.
I see what you're doing.
Do you have anything to say?
I'm sorry.
Is that it?
I'll make it up to you.
That's not the point.
You know you've been acting weird.
You and Gyun were like brothers.
But you didn't shed a tear
during the whole funeral.
When the coffin was taken away
you stared at your phone
as if you were preoccupied.
As soon as the cremation was over,
you left as if you were on the run.
How could you?
Aren't you sad at all?
Gyun is...
Gyun is dead.
I know you're worried
about the building.
But what's most important?
It's family.
You should look after us.
You should be there for us
when we need you.
Your suit's all dirty.
Go and get changed.
Thank you.
You're following the trend
if you're looking at properties
in this area.
You know this café, don't you?
It's the hottest place around.
Hello.
- Mr. Oh.
- Hi.
Why don't you check upstairs first
then head to the basement?
You said you'd like to use
the cold storage, right?
Yes, I'd like to have a look.
SE-YOON BUILDING
Let's order boiled pork
and tofu with kimchi for you.
REALTOR HEE-JU
This place hasn't changed.
Gyun loved to eat here.
He did.
He loved boiled pork
and always ordered soju.
The landlord isn't picking up.
Should we see the second-floor first?
Have you prepared Da-rae's tuition?
Something more urgent came up.
I'll put it back soon.
(It was truly horrid
of you this time.)
I'm sorry, Da-rae.
I'll pay you back double.
Do you trust me?
From now on,
talk to me about everything.
I'll help out.
Of course. You bet.
IS THE COLD STORAGE UNIT OKAY?
I BROUGHT A PROSPECTIVE TENANT
Who is it?
A realtor.
The woman in leggings?
Yes.
I don't like her.
Why? She helps us out sometimes.
Seon.
I'm done for.
I need to use the restroom.
- This way.
- Thanks.
Check out the rooftop.
Isn't it lovely?
I like the vacant second floor unit
as well as this space up here.
If you want, I'll put in a good word
to the current owner
so you can use this space freely.
The call cannot be connected...
Darn it.
This place is popular even now
but it'll be even more popular
once the redevelopment is complete.
This area will also be redeveloped?
Not this building.
That's good.
Is the cold storage in the basement?
Yes.
Just a moment.
MISSED CALL
SE-YOON BUILDING OWNER
The phone is turned off.
Transferring to...
Would you like to see
the cold storage while you're here?
Sure.
Taxi.
What's that punk's problem?
Excuse me. Sorry.
Something urgent came up.
Can I borrow your phone?
Mine just died.
- Who's he?
- Please?
- Lend me your phone.
- No way.
I'll give you 1,000 won.
Please?
Taxi.
RESERVED
Back off. I reserved this taxi.
What?
Where'd it go?
Watch out.
- Hey.
- Mr. Oh.
- Are you going downstairs?
- Yes.
Does it even work?
Why? It seems to work just fine.
I used to keep coffee beans there
until not long ago.
I had to move everything for repairs.
I haven't heard anything since.
Should we check it out now, then?
Do you have a key?
Of course I do.
I'll come with you, then.
I've been calling the building owner.
The landlord has great foresight.
That's why he set this up.
He knew it would be
of some use to his tenants.
You got lucky.
Doesn't this door
kind of freak you out?
Right?
Let's see...
Is this the right key?
I think I hear something inside.
Why would there be a sound?
Don't be like that, Mr. Oh.
I really did hear something.
Didn't you?
COLD STORAGE
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
I feel like I'm hearing something.
I don't hear anything.
Gosh, seriously.
No?
This is it.
It's open.
Wait up.
My goodness.
The storage doesn't work right now.
- Gosh.
- You scared us.
You can't unlock the door
without permission.
You could get electrocuted
if you walked in there.
Sorry. You didn't answer your phone.
There was a leak
and it short circuited the place.
- Step aside.
- Oh, really?
At least you know now.
Let's go. That was really close.
Was that a short circuit I heard?
I need it taken care of soon.
PYEONGBUKGWAN
(Is Dad constipated?)
I'll check out the restroom.
Is it you, Su-jong?
What? Who are you?
The phone is turned off.
Transferring to voicemail.
You will be charged after the beep.
You could've told me in advance
if you had such an issue.
I'm so sorry I didn't.
I'm really sorry.
What exactly is wrong
with the cold storage?
Well...
A pipe burst and flooded the place.
That's why I mentioned
the short circuit.
Something like that
only happens once a century.
Yes, but if I call an expert
it'll be cleaned up no problem.
You don't have to worry.
I'll show you the basement
another time.
The freezer works, right?
That works fine.
It's pretty cold in there.
If you agree to sign a contract
I'll fix it all up so you have
nothing to complain about.
- Okay.
- He's a great guy.
He takes care of everything
right away.
Last time...
He got a good deal on this café
for being a nice landlord.
Can you excuse me for a bit?
This is perfect for you.
And the landlord...
What's up? Is it all over?
How is Yi-gyeong?
I gave her a blanket earlier.
Oh, no.
The injection.
Hey.
Where are the syringes?
- Get them fast.
- Hang on.
Darn you.
Where are they? What...
COLD STORAGE
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
Darn it.
What the heck?
I can't believe what we're doing.
She's a fighter.
Give her a shot on time.
Are you all right?
When will you take her home?
In due time.
- Hey.
Since you're in on it
do something else for me.
What's that?
IF YOU WANT YOUR WIFE BACK,
PREPARE 3 BILLION WON
I'LL COMMUNICATE ONLY WITH YOU,
MIN HWAL-SUNG
I'll speak with them myself.
What?
Why are you surprised?
Well...
Take a look at this.
They'll communicate only with me.
It's three billion won.
I should hand it over just like that?
That's not how you do a deal.
"A deal"?
Your daughter was kidnapped.
That is why
this deal
is more important than any.
Do you know
what's most important
when making a deal?
- Seed money.
- Seed...
It's spirit.
If they take me for a pushover
then I become a real pushover.
You were a pushover your whole life
and you haven't learned anything.
That might be too dangerous.
I've decided.
It's not hard at all.
Make the call and put on an act.
What act?
Be the kidnapper.
Call tomorrow morning
and tell my mother-in-law
to come to parking lot
of Bugwang Sky Road at 10 p.m.
That's not what we planned.
You said you'd bring the cash here.
Things have changed, friend.
Is that hard?
Pretend you're shooting a film.
What if your mother-in-law
catches me at it?
She's a 70-year-old woman.
That's a burner phone,
so don't call anyone else with it.
You can only call me, okay?
Jeez.
YOU'RE... REALLY... HELPLESS...
Administrative procedures
for this place are complete.
What about those who are holding out?
We're almost done with them.
We sent the certified mail.
The properties
will be auctioned off soon.
What about the courthouse?
We'll contact
the certified public appraiser
and get them to adjust the price.
Next.
Hanmaeum Building
will take a little more time.
This guy lived here
almost all his life
and he refuses to sell
even at above the market rate.
This old woman.
She's tied to the man we just saw,
isn't she?
So, how long will you spend on this?
I told you long ago
to take all the buildings
slated for redevelopment
and you're still at it.
There was an accident recently
and you told me to lie low
and watch out.
The accident?
You killed a policeman.
Do you know how hard it was
to cover that up?
There was a reason for that.
A reason?
Are you blaming me
for giving the order?
Well...
How dare you say that?
I said to do whatever it takes
as long as no one sees
or hears about Real Capital.
Do you remember?
I do. Forgive me.
Did you hear the news
from the head office?
What news?
Singapore.
Singapore?
Don't you get it?
If you slack off
and mess up the redevelopment
both of us are in trouble.
Finish it up.
Get to it, then.
I understand.
What did he say?
Should I handle what's in the works?
No, wait.
He wants us to tread lightly.
We took care of
a truckload of people here already.
Why tread lightly now?
Do I have to go back and take care of
the guy I buried in the basement?
No.
That will be ruled an accident.
Don't worry.
Okay, then.
You're still here?
Well...
We were going to eat dinner together.
Okay, then.
I took your daughter.
ALIEN VOICE
That won't work.
It doesn't sound right.
I took...
What the heck?
Are you Gi Su-jong?
CERTIFIED LETTER
TO GI SU-JONG
REMINDER TO REPAY DEBT
1 BILLION WON
TO BE PAID BY MARCH 20
It states 12% of one billion won.
That's 120 million won.
What the heck?
CANCEL ALARM
I can do this. Of course I can.
NUMBER WITHHELD
Hello?
Put it on speaker.
This is Jeon Yang-ja.
Is anyone there?
Yes.
Nice to meet you.
Where is my daughter?
Where's your son-in-law?
Cut the crap and put my daughter on.
If you just hand over the cash
I'll send your daughter back safely.
Do you actually have my daughter?
How dare you make a joke
like this nowadays?
COLD STORAGE
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
Mrs. Jeon, you can't talk like that.
What's this?
Yi-gyeong.
Yi-gyeong! Yi-gyeong!
Yi-gyeong!
Take the tape off.
- Yi-gyeong!
- Don't touch her.
Don't do anything to my daughter.
Yi-gyeong!
Yi-gyeong...
NUMBER WITHHELD
Hello?
I want three billion won.
Tonight, at 10 p.m.
The Bugwang Sky Road parking lot.
Bye.
Tonight at...
CALL ENDED
NUMBER WITHHELD
Mrs. Jeon.
This guy is serious.
He's not to be taken lightly.
Did he say three billion won?
Yes, Mrs. Jeon.
Prepare one billion in cash.
And fill the rest of the bag
with newspaper.
Can't we do that?
- What?
- You know.
That's what they do in films.
They put the real cash on top
to cover the fake bills.
Wouldn't that be hard to tell?
I don't think that's right.
If we call the police...
If you irritate people like this
then Yi-gyeong's life...
Saving Yi-gyeong.
Isn't that our priority, Mrs. Jeon?
DIVORCE LAWYER HWANG MIN-JEONG
That's how everyone begins.
Sorry?
"I stopped by just to be sure."
"I'm not going to divorce him now."
Is that what you're thinking?
But that's how it begins.
You must be a housewife.
- Yes.
- Any kids?
She's going to college soon.
You'll have to make a living, though.
Sorry?
You must figure out what you can take
before you leave him.
Here's your order.
- Thank you.
- It looks so good.
You love this, don't you?
You remind me of my niece,
so let me tell you this.
Do not let emotions steer the wheel.
First, figure out
exactly what your family has.
It'll be even easier
if your husband is the one at fault.
Se-yoon Building.
SEJEONG-RO, YONGDAEMUN-GU, SEOUL
SE-YOON BUILDING
APPRAISED VALUE 2.4 BILLION
DEBT 1.2 BILLION
BANK LOAN 1 BILLION
We'll have nothing
once we repay the debts.
CAN A HOUSEWIFE OF 15 YEARS
FIND A JOB?
THE REALITY IS THAT
IF YOU HAVE A CAREER GAP
THE CHANCES OF FINDING A JOB ARE SLIM
I SHOULDN'T HAVE LEFT MY HUSBAND
RETHINK YOUR DECISION
LIFE ISN'T A DRAMA
His fault?
You know
like infidelity or something.
Hey, you were good.
All we have to do now
is meet her and do the handover.
I'll be there with the money
so just bring Yi-gyeong with you.
So starting now, don't even call me.
My mother-in-law may come along.
That means
I should pack that mask.
Yes.
- Exactly.
- Right?
- I mean, she knows you.
- Yes.
So don't even say a word, okay?
All right?
And then you'll park there.
I want 1.5 billion.
What?
I want 1.5 billion won.
Don't I deserve that much?
SEOUL YONGDAEMUN POLICE STATION
Ju-ran.
I found Gyun's accident footage.
Do you want to see it?
You did? From where?
It was captured by a dashcam
on a delivery motorcycle nearby.
It's a bit far,
so it's hard to make out.
Stop.
This guy.
Can you zoom in on him?
Isn't this
Gyun's brother-in-law?
He seems like him.
No way.
What are you two up to?
Captain, we were checking
the footage of Gyun's accident
and I spotted something odd.
- This man right here...
- Hey.
I get that you're heartbroken,
but it was a hit-and-run case.
We put out an APB for the driver.
And as I mentioned yesterday
it's Jung Chang-su and Real Capital.
You know, the ones he had been...
You punk.
I told you to drop that.
But circumstances...
Will you take responsibility
if problems arise
after messing with a global entity?
If you want to investigate so badly,
bring me the evidence.
Let me put it bluntly.
Bring me Jung Chang-su's body!
- Captain.
- Enough.
We got another case,
so start packing.
Sorry? All of a sudden? What is it?
Good, you're here.
Come with me. Bo-ram.
Come with me.
Where are we going?
You have to tell me first!
VCU TEAM 2
You're here, Mr. Min.
- Hello.
- Hey.
Put a bug on him.
- Yes, sir.
- Hello.
Please take off your jacket.
- Your jacket.
- My jacket.
- I'll take it.
- Thank you.
Like this.
This is for your safety,
so please excuse the inconvenience.
You'll see the power button here.
You can turn it off
while you're using the bathroom.
But leave it on
when we meet the kidnapper.
We'll protect you.
Can you put this in your ear?
Don't be too nervous.
- Hwal-sung.
- Yes?
Do not grumble and cooperate, okay?
Yes, Mrs. Jeon.
- All done.
- Your jacket.
- Thanks for the hard work.
- Sure.
Why did you call the police?
I thought I had explained.
Do you expect me to hand over
three billion won just like that?
Most cases like these
become more dangerous
once the police get involved.
It's best to leave
these matters to the experts.
Is everything ready?
All right.
Let's get going.
Team One, get there first
and stand by.
Ju-ran, Bo-ram,
and I will go with Mr. Min. Got it?
- Yes, sir.
- Captain.
- Yes?
I appreciate your work.
I hope to see you do good work.
That was so sudden.
Madam, you can't do this.
The times have changed.
I can go with you, right?
You?
I can tag along in your car.
Well, I don't know.
It'll be too dangerous.
She's my daughter,
and that's my money.
I'll sit quietly in the car,
and that's that.
All right.
Do not worry.
We'll be right here.
I need to go to the bathroom.
The police are everywhere.
Do not come out.
SU-JONG
THE P, EVERYWHERE
We must leave now to arrive on time.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Yes, I'm coming.
COLD STORAGE
Darn it.
Mr. Gi.
Hey, Mr. Oh.
You could've asked me
to help you with this.
I thought you'd be busy.
Oh, goodness.
How come this is so heavy?
Well, you know.
I had some stuff left in there.
Your brother-in-law's?
Yes.
He left lots of stuff here.
I thought I'd sort out his things.
- It's okay. I got it.
- Hold on.
My gosh.
How were you going to do this alone?
This isn't going to work.
You have to pull it.
- I'll push it from this side.
- Okay.
Down there.
This makes it harder for me.
I got it from here.
- Just leave it here.
- Here?
Right here. Yes, Mr. Oh.
I got it now. Thank you.
You should go now, Mr. Oh. Thanks.
You know
this thing.
I just helped you carry it up here.
Could you lend me a hand as well?
With what?
That thing.
Can you help me move that plant?
Yes, sure.
Yes, right now.
- All right.
- Okay.
My mom got this 20 years ago
when she went to Vietnam to travel.
No, not here. Over there.
Over there.
Anyway, she bought back the sapling.
Oh, goodness.
That's good.
Then she looked after it
with utmost care for 20 years
then she gave it to me
- when I said I'd open a cafe.
- I see.
She said it needed some rain
to grow more naturally.
What do you think?
It looks nice with the building, no?
Yes, it looks great.
Please excuse me, then.
Hey, you know what?
What?
The restroom is clogged again.
We must unclog it, then.
When will you do it?
I'll do that this weekend.
- The weekend?
- Keep it up, Mr. Oh.
Do you need help?
I'm fine.
He bought a car
without talking to me?
Sir, can you follow that car?
Please lead the way.
We'll be right behind you.
Where is he going?
Where are you going, Mr. Min?
I'm sorry.
I have a stomachache.
Captain.
Mr. Min must use the restroom
for a moment.
You can go ahead of us.
Roger that. Be quick.
I'll be right back.
Let me unplug myself.
I need to power this off now.
I'm so sorry.
PLEASE USE THE FRONT DOOR
THIS IS THE BACK DOOR
What are you doing, man?
Do you have a pay phone here?
What's a pay phone?
The phone you put a coin into
to make calls.
Just use your cell phone.
Let me use yours.
What?
What the heck?
SLOW DOWN
SHARP CURVE AHEAD
Darn it.
Man, that was a surprise.
You can let me off here.
BUGWANG SKY ROAD PARKING LOT
Wait.
Hey, Mr. Kang.
When will Ms. Koh
and Mr. Min get here?
A car just pulled in.
They'll take off soon.
All right. Tell them to hurry.
Is that the car?
That's it.
- There it is.
- What?
Let me put this on.
Shoot. I can't see.
What are you doing?
What are you doing, Su-jong?
I think he's not picking up.
Can I have my phone back?
Let me text him.
- What?
- I want to text him.
- What text?
- Here.
There's no time. Hurry up.
- Gosh.
- Hurry up.
Here.
What the heck?
A young boy using this keyboard?
Hey, you write it.
Hurry up and write it.
What do you want me to write?
"There are police. Run."
- What?
- No, it's not what you think it is.
Hurry up and write it.
I think I'll be home late tonight.
Welcome.
Yes.
No, just...
I'm going to meet the kidnapper.
A suspect.
Okay.
Bye.
It's 5,400 won.
Can I have the receipt?
Thank you.
Bye.
What's he saying?
No, fingerprints.
Gosh, what's he taking so long?
Enter the parking lot slowly.
We'll be hiding behind you.
Don't worry.
ENTRANCE
Captain, this is Bo-ram.
We just arrived at the site.
Will it be okay?
Don't worry.
Hey, Detective Koh.
Tell Mr. Min to move naturally.
Relax and move naturally.
Hurry up.
The police.
What's he saying?
The suspect appeared.
Hurry up and leave.
What? What are you saying?
Hold on.
Don't say anything stupid.
Here. Happy now?
There's no time.
Now, hurry up and bring my wife back.
Put this in your car, and return her.
- Here.
- Why are you using honorifics...
Whatever. I don't want to hear it.
Where's my wife?
- Are you acting?
- My wife...
My wife! Where is she?
- Is your mother-in-law here?
- My wife!
Hurry! My wife!
Where's my wife?
- Seriously, you idiot.
- Where's my wife?
She's here in the trunk.
Yi-gyeong.
Get ready for a raid.
Secure your locations and standby.
No, wait.
Where are you going?
You can't go yet.
We have to catch him now.
What if he runs off with the money?
Hey, what's this?
Hey.
Hey, come here.
- What the heck?
- Darn it.
Hey, let me go.
I'm sorry.
Get him!
- Get him.
- Stop right there.
- Hey!
- Open the door.
- Open the door, you jerk.
Open the door.
- Open the door.
- Open.
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
Did you see the kidnapper's face?
What happened to your hand?
That's enough to suspect you.
You know what happened, right?
Your wife was kidnapped.
What is this?
A backpack for hiking.
So what's inside?
It's three billion won.
He took three billion won for ransom.
- Three billion won.
- Nice.
Is he the culprit you saw last night?
You're under arrest
for robbery and kidnapping.
Let me go. Don't touch me!
Let me go!
Subtitles by Eunsook Youn,
Jennifer Lim, Songmi You