[Young Chu Qiao]
[Nine years ago] [Zhuge Xi's Villa]
Search carefully!
Find her quickly!
-Yes!
Search!
Boss, are you okay?
Get out of my way!
Search carefully.
Even if you have to turn
this place upside down,
you must find that little slave.
When I catch her this time,
I'll skin her alive!
Find her!
-Yes!
-Hurry.
-Let's go.
Hurry.
Who are you?
[Yunniang, Qingshan Manor]
You little wretch.
You've got a lot of nerve.
I'm going to flay you alive.
Take her back!
Stop.
This little slave
trespassed into
the Third Master's courtyard.
She should be handled by us.
Falling into their hands,
you little wretch,
you're going to suffer.
Let's go.
Aren't you going to punish me?
This is not a place you should come.
Don't come back next time.
You can leave.
I've heard of you.
Linxi said
the Third Master, Zhuge Xi,
likes women the most
and likes killing them the most.
Every day in this mansion,
so many women
are sent to the third branch.
No one comes out of that courtyard alive,
except for you.
You've survived in that hell for 3 years.
You know quite a lot.
Go away. Don't come near here again.
Otherwise, even I can't save you.
Do you think this courtyard
is the only terrifying thing?
In the entire Zhuge family
and even the entire Zhenhuangcheng,
isn't it like this everywhere?
Wherever I am,
aren't I just a slave
whose life is as cheap as grass?
Please, teach me.
I want to survive too.
I know you're capable.
You can survive by Zhuge Xi's side.
I want to be as strong as you.
Continue.
Master.
You've made fast progress recently.
Thank you, Master.
You are a slave,
but do you know
there are 2 types of slaves?
Please enlighten me, Master.
One type
is born a slave.
That's their status.
The other type
is willing to be a slave.
They even believe they are inferior.
People can't choose their origins.
But if they abandon their inner beliefs
and completely accept their fate,
then they are true slaves.
As long as they don't give up fighting,
whether under the sword
or in this world,
there is still a glimmer of hope.
Take this.
Why are you giving me this?
Slaves can't accept these.
I'm leaving here.
I don't need this anymore.
Hold on to it.
Don't let Zhu Shun see it.
Where are you going?
Are you going back to your village?
The village has long
been destroyed by war.
I'm going to a new place.
Is it the place you talked about,
where there are no slaves,
and people are not divided into classes?
Can you take me with you?
Remember,
you must survive.
Only by surviving
can you go wherever you want to go.
Wash!
Wash faster!
Steward Zhu!
Something terrible has happened!
What is it?
Have you heard?
Yunniang failed to assassinate
the Third Master
and was beaten to death.
What?
It's true.
The Third Master was furious.
He ordered his men to drag her corpse
to the hunting ground
to feed the dogs.
Whoever slacks off
will be dragged out to feed the dogs!
[REBIRTH]
[Episode 27]
[Chu's Mansion]
This is Chu's Mansion?
Of course.
I'm no longer the noble young master
of the Zhuge family.
I can only rely on you and marry into
the Chu family as your husband.
What are these?
These are colored knots
bought at the market.
They are hung around the house
before moving in,
to pray for peace.
I'll hang them up for you.
Go ahead.
Done.
How is it?
Why do I feel like
hanging them here isn't great?
Young Master.
Put me down.
Y-Young Master,
many Ximeng citizens
have gathered outside the palace.
They tied up their daughters
and said they wanted to offer them to you.
Offer them to me?
-Long live King Ximeng!
What are you doing?
Why are their hands and feet bound?
Your Majesty,
to thank you for your great kindness,
we are offering our unmarried daughters
to you!
I don't need female slaves.
Take them home.
Forgive us, Your Majesty!
-Forgive us, Your Majesty!
I have already issued a decree.
Your own daughters
can't be given to me as slaves,
nor can they be bought
and sold by you with a price tag.
Do you understand?
Ximeng is vast.
There is room for all of us.
Now that all tribes
can put aside their past grievances
and gather in Ximengcheng to develop,
at this rate, in a few years,
herds of cattle and sheep
and a life of plenty
will not be a fantasy.
There is no need
to live by exploiting slaves.
Your Majesty.
This is my daughter.
She just came of age.
She can serve your daily needs
and do some heavy lifting.
Please don't despise her.
Your Majesty.
Xing?
Xing.
What are you doing?
Whose robe is this?
It's what King Ximeng's
personal female slaves would wear.
I've thought of a good idea
to let those commoners
stop sending their daughters
to the palace.
Oh my god!
King Ximeng is getting married!
Getting married?
Is he going to choose female slaves
for the palace again?
No.
It's a proper Queen Ximeng.
The wedding will last for 3 days
for all the commoners in the city
to celebrate for him!
Really?
-That's great!
Everyone, please line up.
Don't push.
-Thank you.
-Give me one.
Don't push. Don't push.
-There's enough for everyone.
Listen to me, everyone.
There's enough for everyone.
These are the wedding candies
of King Ximeng and the Queen.
You can come back for more
when you finish.
-Great!
They said King Ximeng is getting married.
For 3 days, there'll be fairs in our city
and free food for everyone.
I also heard
that after King Ximeng gets married,
he won't need female slaves
to serve him in the palace anymore.
I heard that Queen Ximeng
was also a female slave before.
-Go get another portion!
Freshly baked Queen's cakes!
At King Ximeng and the Queen's
wedding tonight,
these Queen's cakes are what they ate!
Miss, Sir,
freshly baked Queen's cakes.
Crispy and fragrant.
Here, have a taste.
Since King Ximeng
has been fighting everywhere,
he should keep it simple.
I didn't expect him to make this.
For the sake of the Queen, King Ximeng
has even forbidden female slaves
from entering the palace.
Making pastries is nothing.
Miss, try it.
It's delicious.
I'll let him have a taste as well.
How is it, Sir?
Is it delicious?
King Ximeng...
Miss.
-Has a real gift.
-Look at this.
This is Luanfeng Tassel.
King Ximeng and Queen Ximeng
are wearing this pair.
Really?
I'll take it.
Okay.
Is this also
King Ximeng and Queen Ximeng's?
Of course.
Look,
these two are a pair,
threaded with the same string,
symbolizing an endless marriage.
King Ximeng and the Queen
are a match blessed by heaven.
Sir,
-how about...
-I'll have a pair.
Since King Ximeng
and Queen Ximeng have them,
we should have them too.
Just this pair.
Okay.
-Take them.
-Thank you.
You're welcome.
You must put these on each other
for them to work.
Why do you smell so good today?
You didn't scent your robes
with incense before coming out, did you?
How could I?
I never use these things.
It might be from the crowd.
Let's go.
♪ On the water ♪
♪ Countless ♪
♪ Ripples rise ♪
♪ Let the wind shape ♪
♪ Another me ♪
-Zhuge Yue.
-Xing.
♪ How can I escape ♪
♪ All the reflections that hold you? ♪
♪ Behind the illusions
of the moon in water ♪
Young Master!
Everything you asked me
to prepare is ready!
Along with spices and wine!
♪ I wait to sink deep ♪
♪ May fortune smile on all below ♪
♪ Just to hear when you'll come home ♪
Lady Chu, look!
♪ Braving schemes alone ♪
♪ Treading through thorns ♪
♪ Searching for your name ♪
♪ Till storms rise again ♪
♪ Not a single regret remains ♪
Why did you prepare spices and wine?
♪ Melt the ice ♪
To drink.
♪ That fate has wrought ♪
To drink?
♪ Let the night ♪
♪ Forever glow ♪
To drink?
Zhuge Yue,
you're a big liar.
A handsome liar.
Do you think our Young Master and Miss Chu
have made it official or not?
Judging from the sound, probably...
mostly official.
How about
we give him another hour?
In my opinion,
it's definitely official.
Let's all head back.
King Ximeng and Queen Ximeng have decreed
that from now on, regardless of gender,
King Ximeng's Palace
will no longer conscript
any slaves for labor.
The commoners and tribes of Ximeng
will no longer need
to send slaves to the palace.
There is no need to kneel.
I used to be just like you,
a slave
with no status,
no name,
no land, no house,
and no right
to decide whether I could live or die.
In today's Ximeng,
everyone is equal.
I came to Ximeng
and managed to break free
from the chains of power and status.
You can all do the same.
That gate
used to be the place where you
sent away your family and children.
Now,
it is a passage connecting us.
No matter who you are,
if you have grievances
or wishes,
you can pass through that gate
and find us in the palace.
Go to the palace?
Really?
Can we really do that?
Will it help?
Please, stand up.
Everyone, stand up.
Long live the King! Long live Ximeng!
-Long live the King! Long live Ximeng!
-Long live the King! Long live the Queen!
-Long live Ximeng!
-Long live the Queen! Long live Ximeng!
-Long live the Queen!
These are millet seeds.
Register over there first,
then go claim your land.
Remember
to choose a flat land
near the canal first.
Thank you. Thank you.
How many people are in your family?
Three.
No, 4.
Four?
Another one is about to be born.
For 4 people, that's 8 mu of land.
Can you manage it?
The more, the better.
How about this?
I'll give you 2 more mu.
Remember,
if you can't farm it all,
hire someone first.
If you hire someone,
you must pay them first.
Got it?
Take it.
Well...
Hey, come register.
I'm hurrying back to farm the land.
Register for what?
What if you take the seeds
to make porridge instead?
You'll get that 10 mu of land for nothing.
Where would I find you?
I wouldn't do that.
Why are you here?
I've come for land and seeds.
What use is land to you?
To provide for my newlywed wife.
Ximeng's new decree
states that everyone is equal.
Are you going to treat me differently?
Since we're distributing land,
I'll give him my 2 mu.
Then I'll give you my 2 mu as well.
Farm well.
It really works.
The water is here!
-It's here.
-The water is here.
-Let me see.
-There's water!
This solves a huge problem for us!
Yes.
Yeah.
Zhuge Yue!
You know about farming?
I used to think of farming books
as leisure reading.
I didn't expect to use them today.
You're truly a man of striking appearance
and extraordinary bearing.
You are truly our savior.
This awful journey is so hard.
We don't even have a sip of water.
Thankfully, we'll reach
Zhenhuangcheng soon.
You can say that again.
I dream of eating Tengxiang Restaurant's
Lotus Pouch Pork Tenderloin,
Stir-Fried Lamb with Scallions,
Bamboo Shoots with Chicken and Goose,
Lychee-Flavored Kidneys,
and Cured Donkey Meat.
We can't get the other dishes,
but wanting to eat donkey meat
is easy.
Whoever targets this donkey
will get 200 strokes of the cane.
-Yes, Sir!
Your Highness,
this is just an ordinary donkey.
There is nothing special about it.
Why do you care so much about it?
This donkey is borrowed.
Its owner is fierce
and not to be messed with.
Neither of us can afford to offend her.
Fierce? And can't afford to offend?
Who is it?
[Master of the Muhe Family, Great Yong]
By His Majesty's decree,
Your Highness, you deployed troops
without permission
and are suspected of colluding
with the enemy and of treason.
You're ordered to immediately
surrender the military tally,
disarm, and be imprisoned pending trial.
I asked Biantang for reinforcements
and have written
to my father to state the urgency.
As far as I know,
my father has not recovered.
May I ask, Lord Muhe,
whose decree is this?
That's right.
I'm passing on
the Thirteenth Prince's decree.
The Thirteenth Prince
is trumping up a charge,
and he can easily find any excuse!
Wait.
Your Highness,
I have a word of advice for you.
What I represent
is His Majesty's will.
Even with thousands of troops behind you,
if they dare to take
one more step forward,
you will never
clear yourself of treason.
Fine.
I'll go with you.
Your Highness!
You stay here.
Don't do anything rash.
Your Highness.
Please.
It's over just like that?
[Zhao Yang,
the Thirteenth Prince of Great Yong]
How boring.
Father even told me to watch out for him,
afraid he'd make a move.
He worried for nothing.
He handed over
the military tally just like that?
Did he not resist?
Your Majesty, he indeed did not.
His Highness not only didn't resist
but also stopped the soldiers behind him.
After being imprisoned,
he even took the initiative to hand over
all 34 military tokens.
Your Majesty,
Lord Muhe said
since His Highness is a prince,
whether to punish him
for colluding with the enemy
still needs to be decided by you.
He neither resisted my decree
nor clamored for an audience
to argue his case.
He is quite obedient.
Lock him up for 3 days,
then release him.
Yes.
Here is the edict of His Majesty.
Seventh Prince Zhao Che
was arrogant due to his merits
and privately mobilized reinforcements,
which is an unforgivable crime.
Considering his remorse,
he's ordered to be stationed
outside Yanming Pass
to redeem himself.
I've received the edict.
Your Highness.
Rise.
This gold coral hairpin is so beautiful.
My Lady, you've done a great service
for His Majesty.
Why are you still so worried?
Although I helped His Majesty this time,
my brother got mixed up with
the Hongchuan Tribe and the Pale Tribe.
His Majesty has always been deep-minded.
Even if he endures it now
and says nothing,
it's not guaranteed
that he won't settle accounts
with the Helian family in the future.
Please don't worry, My Lady.
Look at the things His Majesty sent today.
They are all what you like.
It shows that His Majesty's not angry
and cares about you very much.
"Love me, love my dog."
He definitely won't blame
the Helian Tribe.
My Lady,
Elder Helian Chuan requests an audience.
I didn't even go looking for you,
and you still have the nerve
to come to me?
Today, Elder Tubu is hosting a banquet.
The elders of the Hongchuan Tribe
and the Pale Tribe are there.
For such a grand occasion,
I want to take you out of the palace
to see the world,
lest you be short-sighted
and casually
be brushed off by Yan Xun
with these cheap fabrics
and jewelry.
Delicious.
After what happened the other day,
the Hongchuan Tribe, the Pale Tribe,
and our Helian Tribe
have all been on the record.
You can indulge in wine,
women, and gambling all you like.
It won't cost you your head.
Now you insist on taking yourself
and the Helian Tribe down with you.
Will you be satisfied then?
If you hadn't helped
Yan Xun bring Huan Huan here,
now,
he would be a stray dog.
You have done him a great service.
At a time like this,
you still dare to say such things?
If you don't know
how to restrain yourself,
when the time comes,
I won't be able to save you.
Ling, Ling.
Ling.
I know I've caused a disaster.
So I want to ask you to do me a favor,
have a casual meal with the elders,
and put in a good word for me
in front of Yan Xun when you get back.
My good sister,
just help me out.
I didn't want to mix with them either,
but in the past half year,
I've gradually
received a lot of jade and fine horses
from them.
It's too late for me to return them now.
You also know,
even Yan Xun is somewhat wary of
the Hongchuan Tribe and the Pale Tribe,
let alone me.
I've given you so much. Isn't it enough?
How dare you do such things?
Ling,
it's too late to say this now.
Besides,
for spring and summer grazing,
our Helian Tribe all counts on them.
Ling, my good sister.
Come on.
Elder Tubu.
Elder Pale.
Elder Yunmu.
My Lady!
My Lady.
My Lady,
why are you leaving so soon?
Do you feel
we haven't taken good care of you?
I thought I came here today
to discuss serious matters
with the elders.
But it seems
the elders haven't had enough fun yet.
Let's talk another day.
What are you doing?
Are you trying to imprison
the Consort of Great Yan?
Do you have a death wish?
We wouldn't dare.
You misunderstand us, My Lady.
If we weren't hosting you,
how could we
be drinking and having fun here?
My Lady, don't be so serious.
That's right.
Speaking of which,
you and I have some history.
Back then, her brother
wanted to marry her to me,
in exchange for 500 of my fine horses.
It's a pity
I wasn't blessed enough to have you.
Now that you've risen to power,
you must be worth at least 2,000 horses.
Elder Tubu, look at you.
Two thousand horses?
My Lady,
please don't be angry.
Elder Tubu was just joking with you.
Yes, just joking.
Elder Tubu, you're indeed wealthy.
Not only can you trade horses for me,
but even the wine for your casual banquet
is the Western wine
rarely seen in the palace.
But no matter how generous you are,
you must be careful with your words.
Insubordination is a capital offense.
Once a person dies,
horses won't bring them back.
Well...
Ling, Ling.
Let's talk nicely
and not ruin the harmony.
My Lady, please wait.
I am clumsy with words
and have offended you, My Lady.
Recently, I've found a rare treasure,
and I'd like to invite you
to appreciate it.
This
is the rare painting
I went to great lengths
to find.
The woman in this painting
is the Queen
of the Ancient Chiling Kingdom.
Just like you,
she reduced taxes
and weakened the power of the nobles,
allowing the local commoners
to live a better and better life.
What a pity.
Quanrong invaded.
They didn't just destroy
the Chiling Kingdom.
The Quanrong leader,
right in front of King Chiling,
also raped the Queen
and had a painter draw this rare painting,
"The Painting of the Subjugated Queen."
So that's what happened.
Elder Tubu, on such an occasion,
talking about such an obscene painting
is probably inappropriate.
My Lady, if you think
this is an obscene painting,
you are too ignorant.
For a man,
insulting his opponent's woman
is a tactic.
The Quanrong leader told the world
that he
trampled the dignity of King Chiling
under his feet.
Today,
I will also trample Yan Xun's dignity
under my feet.
How dare you!
Do you have a death wish?
I dare!
-What are you doing?
-Elder Tubu!
Elder Tubu!
Put me down!
Ling!
-Chuan!
-Helian, Helian.
It's a good thing.
You guys!
Helian, Helian.
Put me down!
You've misunderstood
Elder Tubu's good intentions!
Do you have a death wish?
Today, you only said
you wanted my sister to be a persuader.
Nobody mentioned anything about this.
Helian!
Think about it.
Ever since your sister became a Consort,
who still respects you?
If we don't help you
take her down a notch,
there will be no place
for you in the Helian Tribe.
But she is still a Consort after all.
If Yan Xun hears about this...
You are foolish.
For this kind of thing...
-Helian Chuan!
-If neither of us says anything,
how could a weak woman like her
possibly spread this around?
Scream!
Besides, Elder Tubu
has always known his limits.
In matters of romance,
he definitely won't force her.
To put it plainly,
it's just mutual consent.
Not only has the Helian Tribe
been bolstered
by the title of Consort Helian,
but they can also connect with Tubu.
Isn't this the best of both worlds?
You guys come here
and serve Master Helian well.
Come, come.
Elder.
Let's go, come on.
Keep having fun.
Let me go.
You wretch!
Do you really think you're the Consort?
No!
Tubu,
do you have a death wish?
How dare you assault the Consort!
Consort?
What kind of Consort is she?
Yan Xun offered a high price,
so the Helian family broke the deal
and sold her to him.
In the years she's been a Consort,
how many times
has Yan Xun even looked at her?
If I hadn't graced her
with my favor today,
she wouldn't even have been worthy
to serve me!
Cheng Yuan.
I was wondering why Consort Helian
is different from the rumors.
It turns out I'm a step too late.
General Cheng,
you're quite lucky with women.
Why don't you
share it with us?
Do you dare touch me?
You really are His Majesty's lapdog.
Not only are you like brothers,
but you can even share the same woman.
Elder Tubu!
Go!
Helian.
Cheng Yuan.
I...
I killed him.
Cheng Yuan.
It's okay now.
Zhuge Yue.
Up until now,
how many women have you liked?
Did you specifically call me out
just to tell me this?
You are sinking into an abyss of pain,
but I can let you see
the person you miss.
In the future, you will not only
be the King of Great Yong
but also the King of the world!
Traitor!
How dare you impersonate King Ximeng!