Can I go to your mom's birthday party?
Can you help me with
that? I F... king help me?
Who do you think got me
kicked out from my label?
It's because of you.
Love shot! I She tells me every
day that she doesn't like you,
what more do you want?
I ruined everything.
It's alright.
It will get better.
Are you okay? You can tell me anything.
You and I are f... king nothing. I
have no feeling for you, you hear me?
Pure!
Hey!
You have to be on a set this morning,
you know that? I What time is it?
It's 6.30.
It didn't charge! I You have to shoot
a show and you woke up at 6.30?
Where is Namkhang? I Oh my gosh!
Is he there? I He's there.
How long? I Why did you
turn off your phone last night?
I didn't, I didn't plug the charger.
Get these for me.
Namkhang is there already.
Just perfect!
Pure, Joe is furious I'm telling you.
This is not good.
What, girl? What?!
Sorry for keeping you late last night.
No need to apologize.
I wanted to pick you up.
Don't worry about it.
Thank you. I gotta go.
Too much.
Such a wife material, Japanese housewife.
Hot news alert! Someone
reported that they saw Diesel,
a son of Mr.Thara, head
of Thai Pen Thai Party,
visited a nightclub last night
and he's not even 18 yet.
It's not just that. There's more.
It was reported that he abused a woman
in a nightclub, she's injured
and needed to go to the hospital.
Mr.Thara made a statement
throught social media immediately.
There is a rumor about my son
and I can confirm that it is not true.
I have solid evidence as well as
witnesses about his whereabouts last night.
This is the latest statement from Mr.Thara.
We need to watch this topic closely.
It seems like Mr.Thara
will hold a press conference
about what happened.
Our reporters are ready to follow on this.
Stop causing troubles already!
Do you have any idea
what I did all morning?
I needed to tell someone to
erase all evidence from CCTV.
I needed to call the press to
stop them from stirring this up.
I also needed to hire them to interview us,
just because my son
can't control his anger like an animal.
Should you say something to me?
I'm sorry.
Stop with that sad puppy face.
They're waiting for us.
You said you wouldn't
turn out to be like your Dad.
Can you tell them the
truth? I'm asking you.
You don't have to lie, there're
so many ways to choose.
You said that you didn't like
your Dad, why did you act like him?
You lied to me back then?
I know that you're better than this.
Can you tell the truth?
Diesel?
Are you listening to me?
Mr.Diesel,
your Dad wanted you out there right now.
Damn it! Say something!
Why did you fucking lie?
You can't just stay
fucking still and do nothing!
He's your Dad. You need to talk to him!
It's your life, make your own choice.
I I fucking can't make my own choice!
Listen to me,
stop messing with my life, ever.
And quite preaching me already.
You need to take care
of your Dad's business.
Stop minding my business!
Mr. Thara..
Please answer this question, where
were you during the time of incident?
I was working for people all night
until the next morning.
Can you comment on the
incident? Is it true? I Is it true?
I need to tell you that it's not a fair game.
I can confirm you myself
that what happened wasn't true at all.
It's just a smear political campaign.
Where were you during the time of incident?
Please tell us, where were you?
I'm at home, helping my Dad out.
It was such a big mess last night.
You've been through it already.
You're sleeping in a man's room?
Whoa! I Nothing happened between us.
Stop. It's nothing like that.
About Ms.Duangtawan's birthday party,
is it about bird or something?
To be honest,
you're so bold like
if I were you and I was
being told off like that,
I wouldn't dare to share
the same air as her.
That's true.
But people kept telling me that
she can change people's lives.
I want to give it another try.
If I try so hard this time,
and it doesn't work out,
then I'll give up.
Okay?
I saw this book at Diesel's place.
The book has the same name at the theme.
The Conference of the Birds,
an ancient Persian poem.
Have you heard of a bird called Simurgh?
Hello.
Hello. I You're so grown up now.
Ms.Duangtawan is waiting inside.
Yeah? I Diesel! You have
to watch what I just sent you.
This is bad, damn it!
#DieselTrashMan.
Like father like son, both are assholes.
He deserved to be in jail.
Is it alright to lie on news?
You're helping out your Dad at home?
Erase the clip now.
Are you gonna do it or not?
I'll track down your IP address. I don't
care who you are and I'll make you pay.
I'm not scared of you.
Son of a bitch!
Glamorous climate criminals.
1% of the rich flying private jets
causing more pollutions than
normal people do for their entire lives.
Hi. I How are you?
Look at her.
Didn't she care about the theme at all?
Look! No feather?
You need to be more careful these days.
Hello. I Happy Birthday.
Where are we going?
Diesel! Let me go! What
the f... k is wrong with you?
Who is Anyone?
I have no idea, why did you ask?
You said that your friend asked you
to share the article, Anyone wrote it.
Bambi! Who?
You can get in here because
of me and I can make you leave.
Diesel / Bambi.
What is it?
Who?
Isn't it the life that you want so bad?
Bambi? Who?
No, I can't… / Who?
It's just… I Nothing comes for free.
I can't tell you.
Did you listen to the word I said?
I can let you get in here
and I can make you leave.
What is it?
Choose one!
You're hurting me.
I'm so sorry but I
really can't say anything.
Hello, Daeng.
Come to the parking lot, you
need to take someone home.
Diesel?
I'm begging you.
Get in and leave.
Hello, Jom. Did you find it?
Damn it! Let me know the updates.
Leave!
Bambi!
Anyone is …
Dream, she's my friend
from school.
Dream Danupha?
You know her?
Move! Out of the way.
Get out!
What the heck? I Damn it! Dream, fuck you!
Where are you going?
Where to?
Diesel? Where are you going?
Happy Birthday, Ms.Duangtawan.
I can't join your birthday party this
year but I always think about you.
Thank you for everything.
Wish you all the best. See you in New York.
She starred in my last film. Now she's
so famous, maybe she forgets about me.
No, she won't. How's the
sequence coming along?
Still in auditioning process.
I hope you get the right cast members.
Thank you.. I Thank you for coming.
Have you met Dale? I I haven't.
Hello.
I don't think your name
is on the guest list.
Diesel sent me an invitation.
You look good today.
Thank you.
My friend, Tokyo,
helped putting it together.
I got inspiration of the
outfit from a poem called…
The Conference of the Birds.
Simurgh is a mythological bird
that all the birds are seeking for
it, hoping it to be their sovereign.
But before reaching its palace,
the birds needed to get
through various tough tasks.
When they reached the palace,
they saw a pond
located right in the middle.
When they walked towards it,
they saw their own reflections.
Reflection of birds in
the pond. Good thinking.
It can be interpreted that
the birds that could get
through those obstacles,
they are Simurgh.
Impressive.
I'll have an audition for my new
show and I'll have Jib reach out to you.
Ms.Duangtawan, please
come in for group photo.
A little closer, please.
I'll give 200 baht if you pinch a
cheek of someone next to you.
200 baht.
Can you give us cat's
ears? I Cat's ears, please.
Pure, can you do it too?
Pinch Namkhang's cheeks?
Who's the girl in the photo?
You betrayed on Namkhang?
Who? I Who said that?
Who said it. I You bitch!
Are you delusional?
What woman?
Bambi?
It's his personal stuff.
Please don't go.
Actor from BL series took a
drunk girl back to his place.
Woman? I Who's the bitch? Why
did she hurt my little puppy like that?
They're doing great until the
monster woman comes along.
If you know who she it, let
us know. We'll attack her.
Their company should
take better care of the artists.
Fans need to focus. This
is something personal.
It's his business, give him some privacy.
Joe, I'm really sorry. I didn't mean to.
That's enough.
What happened, Tang?
Joe wanted to suspend you for a while.
But I told him that doing that
would also affect Namkhang.
So we decided to have you
take a break from the play.
No, it's not related… / Of course it is.
I spoiled you and look what happened.
If I hadn't spoiled you, you wouldn't
have came to the set late the other day.
It's an accident. I But the photo wasn't.
Can you see this as a lesson?
After this,
please show me that you're really trying.
Because I see none of it.
I'll call the director of the
play that you withdraw from it.
After this, you need to
care more of your friend.
Damn it,
I'm so sorry.
I
I caused troubles again.
I'm sorry.
You do know
what your problem is, right?
Why do you need to withdraw from the play?
I know that you do realize about
what to do to make it all better.
You didn't forget what.
I've carried all along, did you?
I never forget.
Thank you.
While people his age are busy with games,
football and being teenagers,
Can you check the setting
right here? It didn't fit.
Pure dedicated his life to acting.
It's his one and only dream. I
Put costumes number 2 over there.
I want to quit.
But the world didn't award
someone just because they're trying,
the audience didn't pay for tickets
because of the actors' dedications,
but they did it because they
wanted something entertaining.
Pure was wondering what
could bring his audience
to pay for tickets and watch his play.
Pixie dust!
Hey! Namkhang!
You need to fly, Peter Pan,
Tinker Bell is here to save you.
I don't have enough energy to fly anymore.
If it's not sold out by the opening day,
I'll pay for the rest.
You? A rich kid?
Come on, let's rehearse.
When Pure sees the
reality, he starts to realize that
arts require more than just passion
and dedication isn't everything,
it needs the target audience,
then producers will have
enough energy to serve them.
Everything follows demand and supply rules
like it is in Economics 101.
Are you Pure? I'm Joe from Pastel Bay.
I saw your photos and I'd like to know if
you and Namkhang are working for anyone?
I'd like to invite both
of you to be our actors.
Lost 100M in fire, an owner of
luxurious resort barely made it out alive.
When a friend gave you his
hand when you're in trouble,
he needed to reciprocate the favor.
This path could lead Pure to his dream,
but it caused him to
give something in return.
We're interested.
The question isn't how far he can go,
but it is when he decides to trade this,
will it leave something
for him to be himself?
He's hot so it's all
forgiven. #DieselTrashMan.
Men (not all) use violence to solve
problems. Patriarchy society. Pathetic.
Like father like son, all liars.
Dream!
Are you here?
Come out here and talk.
Dream!
Hey! I Dream!
You're standing right here and
yelling? What's your manner?
Who're you?
I should be the one asking, who are you?
And there's no Dream in this
house, you got the wrong one.
Dream, I saw your jacket right
here. Come out here and talk.
This is too much!
Let's talk! I I'll call the police
and press charges for trespassing.
So what? You think I'm scare?
Keep going and you'll see what I can do.
I know that you are Anyone, Dream.
Can you tell her that
erase the post to end this?
Go!
Don't forget to tell her.
Is this her? They followed each other.
Bambi from DM song? I
don't think so, they're friends.
No one wants to pay
for someone's boyfriend.
It's okay to date but
think about your fans.
Please take care of your artists,
we're waiting to here your excuses.
I don't think I can
support them any longer.
I'm sorry.
I didn't realize it's gonna be this huge.
It's okay. I.
I need to apologize for
dragging you into this mess.
How's the modeling job? It
didn't affect anything, right?
I don't think so.
Are you okay?
It should be better once
we solve the problems.
Don't you worry.
If you're not okay,
just say it.
I'm worried about you.
Now I feel so much better.
Smile.
#BringADrunkGirlBacktoHisPlace.
Woah!
So it is Bambi DM?
Please confirm so the fans can attack her.
Get her out of his life, such a monster.
We received a new clip that the politician's
son tried to attack a person in their house.
How could you let them
film you like that?
You knew that if you had told me, I would
have handled it in various different ways.
Where is this place?
Who are they?
I haven't found out yet.
I went to the wrong house.
You remember the story
about a huntsman and a deer?
Yes.
When hunting a deer,
a huntsman gets only
one chance to shot a deer.
If he misses it,
a deer won't return to the same spot.
The only thing he can do is
to herd it to the corner
until he gets another chance of shooting.
Wait, what are you so mad about?
About those stupid woke feminists?
What the fuck do they want from me?
Didn't you just visit their
place? You told me that you did.
Of course I did.
Why didn't they keep posting about this?
You went all the way to their place
and you didn't fucking do anything?
For real?
Damn it! Such a waste of time.
You're so amateur.
Come on, I'm joking.
Can I use your phone?
Same password, right?
Pheung, you need to get the
clothes inside, it's about to rain.
I'm doing it.
Pheung! I Dream!
Someone hit me in the head.
Is it bleeding? I Who did that?
Who? Did you see it?
It's okay, let me see your wound.
It's alright. Get up, easy there.
Easy, easy. Let's get inside.
Be gentle.
I'm gonna touch it now.
Just a little bit.
I think it's just scratch. Not too bad.
Is it hurt so bad?
It's okay, don't worry.
Where is it?
He came to our house last time,
now he sent someone to throw
rocks, what is his next move?
I'm such a bad luck. I
No, don't blame yourself.
You hear me?
Is it tight enough? I'm
gonna take a shower.
Get up slowly. I I'm okay.
What're you doing?
Did you eat?
Nothing.
I didn't do anything. I
You're not telling me?
Really, I didn't do anything.
You think I don't know you?
It's true. I didn't do
anything. I You're lying.
You're lying. I No!
What? You're on live?
Stop it now.
You ended the live? I need to call Joe.
How is it? Are you okay?
Thank you so much.
No problem.
Don't stress out, okay?
Sure.
Not a problem.
You need to be more careful after this.
Let's go.
I need to get my bag.
Pure.
I'm cool if you want
to be in a relationship.
But what you're doing right now
is not good for any of us.
You've chosen this path already.
After this, you have to be
more committed than this.
You get it, right?
Yeah.
I gotta go.
Let's go.
See you.
See you. I Bye.
I'm trapped by his charm but
I'm stuck here because he's weird.
I like his energy.
I'm here to check our their
love. I'm such a third-wheel.
I've followed you since you were
in a play. I'm glad that both of you
have grown up so well. It'd be
nice if you're in the play again.
Who is Anyone?
Anyone is …
Her name is Dream.
She's my friend from school.
How are you?
I'm sorry that I…
Hello? I Hey,
you need to watch the clip right now.
Thief! Stealing a song from Mhong.
She fooled Mhong to get a
free song. I Look at the boy!
What're you doing here?
- If you're not okay, just say it. I'm worried about you.
- Bambi.
What is your deal? You
just showed up like this.
I'm really sorry. But can
you help me out this time?
Is he an actor? I What're you doing here?
Your company is okay with
that. I I'm worried about you.
If she didn't do it… I I
don't know what to do.
Can you help me?
How can you sleep at night
being a monster like this?