Didn't you want to be Queen Chu?
Haven't you always wanted to replace her?
I'm giving you the chance.
Why aren't you taking it?
I...
didn't...
Your Majesty,
I have nothing but admiration for the bond
between you and Queen Chu,
and no trace of jealousy.
If my death
could make Queen Chu
change her mind and return to you,
I would willingly die before you
right now.
You won't die like this.
Let me tell you...
where to stab...
to kill yourself.
Leave!
My Lady.
You are injured?
I'll go get you some medicine.
Leave me alone.
I didn't betray you.
You don't need to pretend to be kind.
Since I agreed to cooperate with you,
I will keep my promise.
You can go back now.
Since it's a cooperation,
it means we share the same goal.
You are not just doing this for me,
but also to fulfill your role
as Consort Helian.
You chose this path yourself.
From the beginning, you should have known
that life around Yan Xun
is not easy.
If I hadn't become Consort Helian,
I would already have been
the fourth concubine
of Elder Tubu of Hongchuan Tribe.
I am a daughter of the Helian family.
Helian Tribe is the smallest
among the Great Yan tribes.
This is a fate I cannot change.
Ever since I was born,
I knew that all the tribal elders
of Great Yan
had their eyes on us,
always wanting to divide
and swallow Helian Tribe.
And my brother...
He never once stopped waiting for me
to grow up,
thinking of using me
in exchange for
a few horses and grazing lands.
Do you think I had any better choice
than becoming Consort Helian?
Even my maids know
Yan Xun has never truly spent the night
in my room.
You think I don't know?
He just wanted to silence the gossip
by giving me this
pitiful and ridiculous title.
What are you doing?
Don't move.
Your foot is injured.
I'll carry you back.
[REBIRTH]
[Episode 19]
Yan Qing,
is there any news from the person
we sent to Zhan's Mansion yesterday?
Your Majesty,
not yet.
But he is still waiting at Zhan's Mansion.
He said that as soon as there's news
about Lord Zhan,
he will come to the palace to report.
He went yesterday.
Why is there still no news?
Don't worry, Your Majesty.
Today is the 15th.
His Majesty has been ill for a long time.
The officials are all at Xiangtian Hall,
waiting for you to pray for His Majesty.
Recently, His Majesty has been unwell.
I will personally pray to the ancestors
to bless him.
Xiangtian Hall is a sacred place.
You should not disturb it.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Ancestors above,
may you bless Biantang with peace
and stability for generations,
and may our Emperor receive the protection
of his forebears,
enjoying long life and good health.
Nobody move!
It's you.
What exactly do you want?
Why do you have Zhan Ziyu's jade pendant?
Zhan Ziyu is dead.
I want to make a deal with you.
You let Li Ce go,
and I will keep your secret.
Let's each take a step back
and leave each other a way out.
Why would I need a way out?
Zhan Ziyu's identity is not simple.
Back then, when the Biantang Emperor
carried out a purge of the Nanxi Tribe,
Zhan Ziyu survived by a stroke of luck.
You took him in
and used him to train the Nanxi people
as suicide warriors.
The assassination attempt in Qinzheng Hall
on His Majesty that day
was your order.
Yesterday,
Zhan Ziyu attempted
to assassinate the Crown Prince
on his way to Youzhou.
It was also your order.
Your Majesty,
even though the Biantang Emperor
has favored you for many years,
Li Ce is his only bloodline
and the sole heir of Biantang.
Why did you attempt
regicide and rebellion?
Once His Majesty recovers,
he will eventually realize the truth.
So it's better
to pin all the blame on Lord Zhan
before he wakes up to it,
so that neither you nor the Crown Prince
will be implicated.
Your Majesty, if you are willing to clear
the Crown Prince's name,
I am willing to leave the Crown Prince
from this moment on
and take Lord Zhan's place
to work for you.
Raising assassins,
attempting to kill His Majesty,
and framing the Crown Prince?
What are you talking about?
I don't understand at all.
The Nanxi Tribe was wiped out long ago.
Their village back then
was burned to the ground years ago.
The Nanxi people have lived by the water
for generations.
How could fire alone wipe them out
completely?
The wooden houses they lived in
for generations
were located in a valley
backed by the South Mountain.
If the fire was set
in a specific season
and at a specific location,
none of them could escape.
Your Majesty,
how do you know this so clearly?
The secret imperial order
given to Sun Di back then
was issued by you
personally.
You've said so much.
What proof do you have?
Impossible.
The order to annihilate the Nanxi Tribe
was issued by Biantang Emperor.
It had nothing to do with Her Majesty.
You're just saying this
to make me testify against Her Majesty
and admit that it was her
who sent me here.
No matter what you say,
I won't betray her.
Even if you kill me,
I won't say a word against her!
Back then,
Biantang Emperor sent troops
to wipe out the Nanxi village.
But after several deployments,
they still couldn't
defeat them completely.
The Empress,
in order to please her husband,
went to great lengths
and finally found a way
to wipe out the Nanxi Tribe
by exploiting the unique structure
and terrain of their settlements
to set the entire village on fire.
Zhen,
tell me this isn't true.
This isn't true.
Run!
Ziming!
Don't run!
Stop!
A remnant of the Nanxi Tribe?
How dare you offend the Empress?
Step back.
This is for you.
Are you hungry?
This...
Your Majesty.
What are you doing?
Princess Fu!
Do you know that holding the Empress hostage
is a crime of treason?
Step back, all of you!
This is a crime of treason!
Raising assassins,
attempting to assassinate His Majesty,
and framing the Crown Prince
are also crimes of treason.
Move!
This...
Everyone, step back!
Step back!
Zhan Ziyu,
tell everyone here,
who ordered you
to use assassins to kill His Majesty
and frame the Crown Prince?
And who ordered you
to eliminate the Crown Prince
on his way to Youzhou?
Speak!
Zhan Ziyu,
I don't understand what she's saying.
Can you explain it to me?
Do you remember
the scene when you brought me back
from the destroyed village in Nanxi
15 years ago?
Nanxi?
Zhan Ziyu is from Nanxi?
The sky that day
was as bright as today.
Looking at your face,
I secretly swore that
I, Zhan Ziyu,
would only have one woman in my heart,
live only for her,
and love only her for the rest of my life.
That is you.
It's...
What a scandal!
Because of this oath,
I would do whatever
you want me to do.
As long as it's your wish,
I could even give up my life,
let alone bear the mere charge
of assassinating His Majesty.
But do you know my wish?
I want to talk to Her Majesty alone.
Step back!
Nobody move!
For the past fifteen years,
I could only hide in the dark
and peep at you in the corner.
Your Majesty...
The sunlight that day
was as warm as it is today.
This...
The seasons are out of order,
and the universe is reversed!
It's an ominous sign!
What should we do?
Zhen...
I can no longer serve you.
Are you hungry?
Guards! Protect me!
Don't move!
Chu Qiao, a famale slave from Great Yong,
conspired with a remnant
of the Nanxi Tribe, Zhan Ziyu,
to frame me!
Arrest them all!
Stop!
Minglu!
They are all accomplices
of Crown Prince Li Ce!
Show no mercy!
Kill them,
and I will reward you handsomely!
Bad news! Bad news!
Something happened to His Majesty!
An assassin broke into Zhengyuan Hall
and took His Majesty hostage.
What...
What should we do?
Take them away!
Your Majesty!
Who are you
to dare hold His Majesty hostage?
You don't need to know who I am.
Release Princess Fu and her people now.
Then, in front of all the officials,
announce
that you ordered Zhan Ziyu to attempt
to assassinate His Majesty
and frame Crown Prince Li Ce,
and I will let him go.
Empress,
save me!
Hurry up and release Chu Qiao
and the others,
and admit that you did it.
I won't believe it.
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
Saving His Majesty is the priority,
Your Majesty.
Yes!
Saving His Majesty is the priority!
Audacious traitor!
To frame me,
you actually dare to hold His Majesty hostage
to threaten me.
Who ordered you?
The Crown Prince or Chu Qiao?
Empress,
are you really going to save yourself
at the cost of the Emperor's life?
Of course I care about His Majesty's life.
That is exactly why I will not negotiate
with rebels and traitors.
Guards!
Kill the traitor
and take His Majesty back!
Your Majesty!
Do it now!
I am here!
Anyone who makes a move
will be punished for rebellion!
Father!
Your Majesty!
I have come by your imperial order
to protect you!
Good.
I have tolerated you for many years,
thinking you knew your limits.
I never expected that you would not only
move against the Crown Prince,
but also come after me.
Stop acting.
You are selfish, hypocritical,
and always putting on an act.
To me,
to your own brother Crown Prince Maocheng,
and to your people and ministers alike.
You deceived me,
went back on your word,
and killed my child,
yet still pretended to love me.
For the throne,
you even killed your own brother!
You feign mourning him.
Going out of the palace to pray for him?
Your acting is so convincing...
you've almost convinced yourself.
If only you knew nothing
and were a little more foolish.
Perhaps I could continue to favor you
and play this game with you forever.
You shouldn't have seen through me,
and you absolutely
shouldn't have exposed me.
You should have kept playing along.
Did it have to come to this?
Is the favor I gave you not enough?
Don't be afraid.
I never intended to kill you.
Because I never wanted to die with you.
In this life,
in heaven or in hell,
I never want to see you again.
This world—
I don't want it.
Your Majesty...
Your Majesty!
Ce!
Zhen.
The sunshine is so beautiful today.
How is he?
Please forgive me, Your Highness.
His Majesty has a pre-existing condition.
Coupled with years of excess
and lack of restraint,
he was already critically ill.
This incident
has completely drained his vitality.
I'm afraid...
I'm afraid there will be no recovery.
Your Highness,
His Majesty has been unwell for many days,
but a nation cannot be without a ruler
even for a single day.
Please make preparations
in advance.
Please make preparations in advance,
Your Highness.
Mother,
Father is very ill.
After what you did,
he likely does not have many days left.
I know you don't want to be with Father,
so I overruled all objections
and insisted on burying you here.
You will not see him again.
I know you do not want me to come see you,
but I did not come empty-handed.
I brought your favorite green rice balls.
Mother!
Mother,
do you like the flower I picked for you?
I'll put it in your hair.
Mother,
if you don't like it,
I won't do it again.
Ce.
These are your favorite green rice balls.
I know you
had never loved me.
And I know you despised me.
You didn't even want to touch me.
I even know that you
wanted to cut me into a thousand pieces.
But in the dead of night,
I still fantasize
about lying in your arms,
listening to your stories.
Fantasizing about...
falling asleep
to your lullabies
and never waking up again.
His Majesty has arrived!
Li Yan, the legitimate son
of the late Prince of Chang, Heir Luo,
has inherited generations
of loyalty and bravery
and is both virtuous and capable.
He is hereby enfeoffed as Prince of Luo.
He is granted a python robe,
1,000 qing of estate land, 300 houses,
500 bolts of fine silk,
and 100 fine horses.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Prince of Luo.
Leave us.
Truly, one cannot judge by appearance.
You have hidden your strength well.
I did not expect you
to be so calculating and scheming.
If I remember correctly,
the palace prayer ceremony
on the 15th of each month
is handled by the Ministry of Rites.
If it were not for you, Minister of Rites,
making things convenient for Chu Qiao,
how could she have appeared
in Youtian Hall that day?
So you betrayed your allegiance
just for a stupid robe
and a few shabby houses?
Prince of Luo, wearing this python robe
that brings you honor,
you really do look every bit the refined
and upright gentleman.
Chunxing!
Pack my things!
I'm going back to Great Yong.
Chun'er!
Why aren't you packing?
Your Highness,
please don't speak in anger.
Now that His Highness has been enfeoffed,
you will be a princess consort.
In all of Biantang,
no one will dare bully...
Let go of me!
You're hurting me!
You're acting tough in front of me now,
but in front of Chu Qiao and Li Ce,
you're just a coward!
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm going back to Great Yong
to find Zhao Che!
Let go! Let go of me!
Zhao Chun'er, enough!
Let me go!
Don't be naive!
Do you think your Zhao Che
will still want you?
We've been married for days.
Has he ever sent anyone to check on you?
Your title as Princess
is just a toy he gave you
to placate a child.
Let go!
Listen to me!
You're not allowed to go anywhere!
Just stay in the mansion.
You, a deposed princess,
and I, a useless prince,
are a match made in heaven.
I will achieve every single thing
I promised you!
Keep an eye on her.
Don't let her leave this room.
Yes.
I thought you were smart.
I didn't expect you to be so stupid too.
Don't stop me! Let me die!
Let go of me! Let go of me!
Why do you want to die?
Is it for the Empress,
or Zhan Ziyu?
I...
After the Nanxi Tribe was wiped out,
you were separated from Zhan Ziyu
and sold into slavery.
It took him years to find you.
You were a slave.
You should know
the life you're living now
is thousands of times better than before.
You survived back then.
But now you want to die?
Isn't that too stupid?
Ziyu is my only family
in this world.
My clansmen were killed by the Empress.
Even my only family is dead.
What's the point of living?
The child in your womb
is your only family.
The child?
Although Zhan Ziyu is your brother,
he exploited your youth
to work for the Empress.
You are so smart.
And Li Ce is a kind
and affectionate man.
Now he is the Emperor of Biantang,
and you are carrying his only child.
Think about it carefully.
These two swords
represent
that we will be together forever.
What my mother lost,
I'll win back for her.
Kill this witch!
If we offer her to the King of Great Yan,
we'll be saved.
Catch her!
Set off!
Long live Great Yan!
Crush Biantang!