(Previously) Lilly killed your
parents with her own hands!
That's why you need to let me help you.
I'll help you start over with me.
We split into two teams.
Kant and I will dig up
anything we can find on Lilly.
You and Style go after Keen.
Her birthday is coming up.
I want some young things like you
to take care of her and her friends.
He didn't leave you.
Mother put a hit on him.
There's no need to be afraid.
You and I will be fine.
(Let's make a deal.)
(You get me dirt on Lilly, )
(and I'll spare your boyfriend's life.)
(This is why I never trusted
you to take care of these things.)
(I knew I was only
going to be disappointed.)
That's everything I can dig up on Mother.
Financial transactions
and everything about her employees…
That's all I could find.
You're not thinking about
stabbing us in the back, are you?
I'm not!
I want to get away from
her as much as you do.
I just want my boyfriend back.
I was used, just like you were.
Bison.
Go get him.
Nont.
Hold it.
You'll get your hug soon.
But if you're being tricky in any way,
I promise you'll die in each other's arms.
Listen to me.
I wanna live a good, normal life, too.
I want to be with the one I love.
I don't want anything to do
with killing people anymore.
All this time,
I just thought that
if I could make her happy,
she'd let me go.
But as it turned out,
no matter how good I am,
she just wouldn't let me go.
Are you okay?
I'm alright.
What are you going to do to Mother?
What?
Are you still worried about her?
No, I'm not.
I'm just going to say that
if you need my help with anything,
I'm here.
I want to see her downfall, too.
Whoa.
I almost shed tears seeing
how much they love each other.
I'd have done the same thing for you.
What are you going to
do with this information?
I'm going to kill her.
Don't do it.
I don't want you to kill anyone again.
What will you have me do?
Let me watch my parents'
murderer live a happy life?
That's not what I'm saying.
I just think there are other ways.
I want to be sure
that the two of you
have a chance to make it.
What do you suggest?
I'll talk to Captain Chris in
case there's anything he can do.
Will he agree to help?
Doesn't he want us in jail?
This is just a matter of negotiating.
Don't worry.
We'll do anything to keep you out of jail.
"The Heart Killers"
(Episode 11)
How was your bath, Cap?
What are you doing here?
I definitely didn't call for you.
And I sure as hell won't
work with you again.
We have a deal for you.
What deal?
Hurry up and spit it out.
I have to go pick my kid up from school.
Tell him, bud.
If you can keep Fadel
and Bison out of jail,
we'll help you get the
people behind their operation.
And how would you do that?
You couldn't even help falling in
love with them while investigating.
They've agreed to cooperate.
We'll get you the big fish you want.
But right now…
I can only give you the smaller fish.
If you can do what you say,
I'll do everything I can.
Promise is a promise, Cap.
Hey.
This is my friend, Tong.
He works in Khaosan.
He's an expert on fake ID and passports.
What are you doing?
Making you a fake passport, duh.
In case you need to run.
Didn't you say Kant made
a deal with that captain?
I don't trust him.
Cops are always looking for
ways to up their ranks, right?
What would I do if he had you beat?
Where do you think I'll
go with a fake passport?
You can go somewhere close by first.
You just have to cross a border,
then fly from there.
You call me after that and I'll fly to you.
We can fly back here
after everything dies down.
It takes 20 years for
these cases to expire.
We'll be old men by that time.
So what if we're old?
I'll still wanna be with you.
Thank you
for doing all this for me.
I don't think I love myself
half as much as you love me.
Trust me on this.
Just get this done.
We don't know what could happen.
I'll get Bison one as well.
This friend of yours,
can we trust him?
Of course.
We've been friends since high school.
Dude got me into nightclubs
since we were barely 20.
Thank you for coming
with me to pick Babe up.
Of course.
It's me who has to thank you.
I've always wanted a
brother, you know that?
It's boring being an only child.
I'd love you to be my family.
It was difficult, wasn't it?
I'll have to get it done quickly.
Sure.
See you.
Bye.
He's here.
Hey.
How was school?
Are the bullies still bothering you?
Not at all.
Who'd dare after you
kicked their butts that day?
You gotta tell me if the
bullies are back, alright?
What would you do?
I'll just teach them a few lessons.
They gotta know not to
mess with my little brother.
You hungry?
Hey, I'm gonna go to the toilet real quick.
Why don't you and Babe wait in the car?
Okay.
Let's go.
What should we have for dinner?
You decide.
He's a smart kid.
He's also a good basketball player.
Ladies,
let's make a birthday toast
for our Lady Anusara Suthasini.
Cheers.
Happy birthday.
Thank you for hosting
such a fun party for me.
It's been a while since I
last enjoyed myself so much.
I've still got another
surprise for you, ma'am.
You do?
Guys, come in.
These boys are taking
care of us tonight, ladies.
I guarantee you full satisfaction.
Isn't this boy…
the one we met at the golf club?
Yes.
I remember you saying
he's good at what he does.
I asked him to come.
Well…
his friend is quite cute, too.
If you like them,
they're both all yours.
You're the best, dear.
You always know just what's on my mind.
I promise you, after this party,
I'll make sure my husband
gives you a seat at the table.
Thank you.
You two.
Take good care of their lady.
She is my VIP guest.
- Yes, ma'am.
Would you like some wine, ma'am?
Happy birthday to you.
I'm going to make a wish, guys.
I wish you more happy
and sexy years to come.
Thank you, dear.
I guess I don't have to get you a present,
since I already gave you two tonight.
I must say…
The present is definitely to my taste.
Come sit here.
You're good at your job.
Your friend is, too.
He knows just what to say.
It's guys like you who'll
make it in the world.
How so, ma'am?
If you have that lady bewitched,
you'll be well taken care of.
Seize the chance.
You don't know if it's ever
coming your way again.
You're right.
When the chance presents itself,
I have to grab it with both hands.
I won't let it slip out of my grasp.
Style.
Why don't you pour Ms. Lilly
and the lady some more wine?
I'm out of wine.
Of course.
You're really something!
Here you go.
Thanks.
Let's hear it for our lady.
Cheers!
Bottoms up, milady.
Mind if I pick a song?
I'd love to sing with you, Ms. Lilly.
No.
I don't sing.
And don't you dare try to sucker up to me.
You're here for her.
Of course.
Here you go.
You should sing us something.
What should I sing?
How about “I Love You”?
Oh, there it is.
- Sing with me, ladies.
- Of course.
What now?
I told you I wouldn't do
it again after the last guy.
This is the last hit.
You can go your way after that.
Fine.
How do you want me to kill them?
Bullet or poison?
I have to grab this chance with both hands.
I won't let it slip out of my grasp.
Who are you?
Hello.
I'm dating your son, Mother.
Dear.
What is all this?
What did you do?
It's nothing.
It's not “nothing.”
That's you on the screen, isn't it?
I need to go to the bathroom.
That's Ms. Lilly, isn't it?
It's her.
It's her!
Fadel.
Bison.
What are you doing here, my sons?
We're not your sons.
Bison, how could you say that?
I'm your mother.
Mother?
My mother is dead!
You killed her.
You put a hit on the man I loved,
because you didn't
want me to quit this job,
and you still dare call yourself my mother?
You never think of us as your sons.
You only keep us for your image,
so we could do your dirty work for you.
I did it with good intentions.
There is no point getting your heart broken
by some temporary love...
Shut up!
You never love anyone.
How would you know what love is?
She does know love.
But the only thing she loves is herself.
We will finally live our lives
without her.
Listen.
If I don't make it out of this mess,
so won't you.
You kill people.
You're getting locked up just like me!
Don't worry about us.
We have plans.
We're getting out of this profession with
your dead body as our final masterpiece!
Bison.
Can you really kill your own mother?
You're not my mother!
Hey!
Don't do it.
You promised me.
You promised you won't kill anyone again.
Don't fall for her trick.
You said you wanted to live a normal life.
It's going to happen soon.
But if you shoot her,
there won't be an ‘us.'
Fadel.
I want a future with you.
Just forget the past.
You two should go.
We'll deal with things here.
Don't worry.
We'll see each other again.
Take the gun.
Be careful.
Take this car and drive to the border.
Leave the car there and cross over.
I don't think the police
know about this yet.
If you go right now, there's
a chance you might make it.
Your passports.
It's your new identity.
Don't contact us until things die down.
We'll go to you when we can.
Same goes to you.
Don't come see me like you did last time.
It's too risky.
I'll go to you.
Are you two going to be fine?
The cops are going to come after you.
Don't worry.
I'll deal with things on my end.
We should focus on
making sure you two are safe.
Style.
Listen to me.
If they torture you for information,
don't put up with it.
Just confess.
Don't you dare get hurt, you hear me?
Don't worry.
I won't spit anything
out even if they kill me.
Style, I'm being serious.
They really could kill you.
You don't have to worry.
I have a knack for surviving.
Fine.
Kant.
I never told you this,
but thank you for
taking care of my brother.
No problem.
I gotta love you when I
love your brother, right?
You should get going.
You'll get there in the
morning if you leave now.
Stop!
Cap.
Where do you think you're going?
Everyone calm down.
I knew you'd help them run.
Just let them go.
You got Ruerat and Lilly.
You know these two were being used.
That's no excuse.
They killed people.
Just hand them over,
and you'll be spared.
Fine, then.
If I don't make it,
you don't make it.
What are you saying?
You bribed a school administrator
to get your kid into that school.
I have proof, too.
Here's a gift.
I hope you take good care of my son.
Are you blackmailing me?
You dare?
Blackmailing is a strong word.
Let's just say we're negotiating.
If this video gets out,
your reputation as a police captain
and your dream of getting a promotion
are gone.
I can make a big deal out of it, Cap.
I can't let them walk free.
All I can do is help reduce the sentence.
How many years?
Five.
No.
I won't accept anything
less than their freedom.
But we'll take it.
Kant.
I'm done running.
I'm tired.
Fadel and I aren't gonna make it anyway.
Five years behind bars…
That's still better than
running all our lives.
If it has to be like that,
I'll never get to really live.
Hey.
You don't know if these
cops will keep their word.
What'd you do if the
final sentence is death?
He's got a point.
How can I trust you?
I never go back on my word.
If that's your decision,
I'll take it.
You heard them, Cap.
Can I ask you one thing?
What now?
Give me one day.
You can come get them after that.
What are you planning now?
I'm not planning anything.
I just want to spend
time with the man I love
before we part.
Please, Captain.
For the sake of this old colleague.
I'll delete every evidence
I have of your bribery.
Fine.
You bring them to me tomorrow.
If you don't,
the next time I see them, they're dead.
Tomorrow.
Won't you eat something?
It's your favorite dish.
I can't stomach it.
I'm sorry this is all I could do for you.
What are you apologizing for?
You did your best.
I knew how hard you tried.
It's all the consequences
of my own actions, anyway.
I really did all those bad things.
I deserve this.
I'm not sad because I'm going to jail.
I'm just sad because
I won't get to be with the man I love.
God really has some weird
sense of humor, doesn't he?
Right when I met a good guy,
when I finally found a good love,
I'm going to jail.
I think it'd hurt less
if someone just shot me dead right now.
I won't let you die.
You're staying with me.
Five years will go by in a flash.
I'll wait for you.
I'll be okay if you won't.
I said I'll wait.
Don't you trust me?
We only have one day.
Let's not spend it being sad.
Let's do something that
will become good memories.
Right?
Why do you look even sadder?
You tell me not to be sad,
but you look pretty bummed.
Let's eat.
I'm not sad at all.
I just have something in my eyes.
Still bummed, aren't you?
You did your best.
If I found out earlier, you
wouldn't have to go to jail.
Style, listen to me.
I chose to walk down this path.
I knew what was coming
for me from the get-go.
Either I get locked up,
or I die.
Five years in jail is so much better.
I don't want you gone for even a day.
I have to take
responsibility for what I did.
I can't change the past.
This could be a chance
for me to start over.
I want to be a good man
who deserves everything you do for me.
We have one day together.
I want to make the most out of it.
What you want to do,
where to go, what to eat,
just let me know.
I'll take you anywhere.
I don't want anything like that.
I just want to do something simple.
Go where we feel comfortable,
with just you and me.
I'll let you pick
what you want to do.
Okay, then.
Can we start by
hugging you for 10 minutes straight?
Take your time.
'Morning, Dad.
Hey.
Good morning.
Oh, hey.
You're here often now, aren't you?
This ain't no hotel, you know?
He's not here often enough, more like.
We're going to have
breakfast at the market.
What are you talking about?
Just have breakfast at home.
Fadel, sit down.
Oh, but I don't want to impose.
You're not imposing.
You're dating Style.
You're as good as being my family.
Sit down, you two.
You know what, Dad?
This guy makes the most
delish burgers out there!
Oh, you jerk.
Are you saying my cooking
doesn't compare to his now or what?
Next thing I know I'll be
running this place alone.
As if I'd ever leave you alone.
Who's going to annoy you if I'm not here?
Well, Fadel.
What are your plans for the future?
Are you going to flip burgers
for the rest of your life?
It's my favorite thing to do.
I guess I'll keep doing it.
That's good.
Doing what you love is good.
If things go well, just
open another franchise.
No one wants your business advice, old man.
Just focus on keeping
this place up and running.
Hey, you gotta plan
these things out thoroughly
if you want to keep seeing each other.
And since gay marriage is legal now,
you two should definitely do that.
Don't jump the gun, old man.
We just started dating.
Whatever.
If you're getting
married, do it before I die.
Give me five years.
I just want to save up enough money
and I'll come talk to you, Dad.
Hey, look who just called me Dad.
Bold, I'll give you that.
Let's have breakfast.
Hey, this is yesterday's
leftovers, isn't it?
Why are you taking me here?
You said you missed your childhood.
I thought this might help you relive it.
Let's have fun today.
Can you forget for a second
what's happening tomorrow?
Be with me today.
Please.
Let's go inside.
Come on.
♪ I'm gonna risk it all ♪
♪ I might get hurt but
I'll learn it on my own ♪
I wanted to be an archaeologist.
I love history.
My parents always took me to museums.
I love dinosaurs as well.
- I can recite all their names.
- ♪ Just try it once again ♪
♪ One more shot, it's worth the pain ♪
♪ Want to face the lessons ♪
Besides northern lights hunting with you,
I have another place I want to go with you.
Where?
Mount Bromo in Indonesia.
Really?
I want to go there, too.
I'm not sure I'm fit enough
for that hike, though.
If you can't, I'll carry
you all the way up there.
That was where my dad
asked my mom to marry him.
That's so romantic.
What are you gonna do?
Are you following in your parents' footstep
and asking me to marry you there?
Hey.
What are you doing?
You think I'm proposing?
Who knows?
You always surprise me.
I have every right to assume, you know?
What if I… really am proposing?
Will you say yes?
Even if you asked me now,
it'd be five years before we
could have our wedding night.
Can you wait that long?
Well, then, how about we just skip to that?
What are you guys doing?
We're taking a look at this thing.
Don't you guys get hot?
It's hot in here.
You should go before it's erupted.
You don't wanna die
like the people of Pompeii.
Let's go.
Hurry! Run!
What the hell was that?
Alright. Let's go, then.
Where the hell did he come from?
Totally killed the vibe!
Go!
No!
I surrender.
I surrender!
I'm tired.
Let's take a break.
Did you have fun?
Yeah.
I'm really tired.
Hey.
You!
Are you gonna be so
sweet to me like this all day?
Yeah.
Get ready for that.
You'll get a toothache just from this.
Looking forward to it.
It's too bad I didn't get to see
your sweet side from the get-go.
You wasted all that time
being so mean to me.
Who'd want to be sweet
with an annoying guy?
You're just like Bison.
You always find something
good in a bad guy.
I believe people can change.
I love a mission.
You'll be my… Project Boyfriend.
I'll help you turn over a new leaf.
You think this Project
Whatever of yours is gonna work?
You think I can change?
You tell me if it works
when you let me do this to you.
Stop it.
When I was a kid, I wanted to
be an astronaut or an astronomer.
I was so obsessed with outer space.
I could recite all the
names of the planets.
Hey.
You know how there's
zero gravity in outer space?
But if two astronauts who got sent up there
happened to fall in
love and wanted to kiss,
how would they do it?
They would float… into a kiss.
Show me.
Hey, guys.
What now, kid?
Did you know I've been to outer space?
You did?
How did you do it?
I was the dog put on the Sputnik 2.
Don't tell me your name is Laika!
Yes!
But how did you know?
I read, duh.
Did you know Laika died in outer space?
Dad never told me that part…
It's alright.
Laika did the world a great
service in space studies.
You didn't die for nothing.
Dad…
Dad! Dad!
Come on.
Why'd you tease him like that?
It's all facts!
And I couldn't help it.
He kept interrupting us.
I don't have much time, you know?
Let's go.
Hey.
Why is your name on this tombstone?
I had it done for myself.
No one knows this.
Not even Bison.
Why would you do that?
I live my life on the line.
I could die at any moment.
No matter how I die,
I just know I'll be doing it alone.
So I had this done.
I'll write it down later,
but just bury me here when I die.
No need for a funeral.
It's not like I have any
family who'd mourn me.
The only person who would cry for me
would be Bison.
Your boyfriend is literally
standing right here.
I'll be mourning.
I'll make sure your grave is well decorated
with flowers and burgers on the daily.
And when I die,
I'll be lying right next to you.
I won't let you get lonely.
Even when we were ghosts,
I'd still be yapping your ears off.
I'm taking you here
because I want to tell you that…
Ever since I met you,
I've been thinking less
and less about death.
You've made me realize that
I want to keep on living
just to spend time with you.
That's the most romantic thing I've heard.
I make you want to keep living?
When you talk to me like that,
it's totally irresistible, you know?
You're making me feel like I'm being lame.
You're just romantic in
an oddly specific way.
Who the hell takes their
boyfriend to their grave?
I doubt I'll ever find
another one like you.
Don't die on me just yet.
Stay and be weirdly romantic
with me for a very long time.
Do you know why it's called
the “Milky Way” in English?
Why?
Tell me.
In Greek mythology,
Hercules, the son of Zeus who was
born from a mortal, was taken in by Zeus.
Zeus didn't know how to
feed the half-mortal baby,
so he sneakily let the baby
drink from Hera's breast.
While the baby was feeding,
the goddess Hera was startled awake,
puzzled as to what toddler
was feeding from her.
She pushed the baby away in shock
and sprayed milk all across the sky.
That's where the name
“Milky Way” came from.
Are you for real?
I feel like you're pulling my leg.
It's true.
I read that somewhere.
We call it “The White
Elephant Path” in Thai, right?
It comes from the belief that
white elephants are from heaven.
Each culture calls it differently,
depending on what their beliefs are.
Alright, alright.
I believe you now that you used
to be obsessed with astronomy.
I want to go stargazing with you everywhere
and listen to you tell me these stories.
I've got a lot more to tell.
Can you really wait?
Of course I can.
Five years is no time at all.
Time flies these days, don't you notice?
Do you want me to buy a
star and name it after you?
Whenever you look
up, you'll think about me.
I don't need such a grand gesture.
I don't want to be up there in the sky.
I want to be right in here.
What are you doing?
Well…
I gotta make sure no kids
are getting in our way again.
There's no one around.
Show me the Milky Way.
You're funny.
Look at that.
There.
I chose to tell my stories to strangers
because I didn't want to be
an emotional burden to anyone.
What do you mean?
When you don't know them,
you don't really care
about them much, do you?
I don't want anyone to worry about me.
But I just learned what
it's like to share my sorrow.
I don't feel so sad anymore.
I'm happier.
You're way too deep, you know that?
I personally think I have no layers at all.
I'm pretty boring.
No layers?
But you're so sensitive.
You just mask it all under your jokes.
Everyone has their own way
of dealing with sadness, right?
You pretend it doesn't hurt.
I bury it under my positivity.
But I don't want you to think
you're a burden to anyone.
Whatever you're feeling,
I'm here if you need to dump it on someone.
Whatever I'm feeling?
Whatever you're feeling.
If I get sad?
I'll cry with you.
I'll wipe your tears.
If I'm happy?
I'll laugh with you.
If I…
I'll help.
I won't get to kiss you
like this for five long years.
Let me get my fill of it for the future.
Did we come here just so
you can teach me to cook?
It's what I want to do.
I want to cook with my lover.
Do what I love with who I love.
It makes me happy.
I've actually opened so
many different restaurants.
Thai food, Japanese, Korean, Italian…
But as it turned out,
I like this one the best.
I like it so much that I even thought
when I quit being a hired gun,
I might even do this seriously.
Who'd have thought…
Hey.
You want me to run this
place while you're gone?
Just focus on your garage.
I don't want this place to
go out of business just yet.
Oh, you underestimate me.
With a little training,
I can do it, you know?
You don't need to.
Here. For you.
But you love it so much, don't you?
That's exactly why
I want you to take care of it.
Come on.
I'll put it here.
Okay.
Looks good.
It suits you.
It feels really safe
when you're by my side.
What is that, all of a sudden?
Gives me the creeps.
Now start cutting those onions.
Wow.
I want our last dinner to be special.
Don't say “last dinner.”
We'll be together when
you're out of prison.
I don't know what the future holds.
I just want to make
the most out of tonight.
Let's plan our life, then.
What do you mean?
Let's plan how we're
going to make this work
while you're in prison.
How are we going to do that?
You'll be here while I'm there.
Style…
You don't have to wait for me.
Just do what you want to do.
Think of our time together…
as a fun period of your life.
No.
It doesn't have to be a big deal.
I can visit you every week.
I'll just be a burden to you.
What burden?
I'm willing to take it.
At first, you will.
But you won't always be able to.
You're out here, you will
meet a whole lot of people.
Are you…
scared of being forgotten?
What else can I do?
When I'm in there, all I'll do is think…
if you forget me already.
How could I forget you?
You're my first boyfriend.
You dragged me out of this place.
We ran away from gunshots hand in hand.
We slept together in the woods
and kissed in the ocean.
Those aren't something
I'll have with just anyone.
I can't forget you.
I'll believe you.
Let's just eat.
I'm getting hungry.
Alright.
Here.
Let me do it, too.
Is it good?
I won't ever forget the taste.
It's messy.
It's good, huh?
Give me a tattoo.
No way.
How could I?
I only had one lesson.
You can do it.
I trust you.
No can do.
I don't even trust myself.
Do you want an ugly tattoo or something?
I don't mind.
Even if it comes out ugly,
it's going to be something
to remember you by.
You need to give me one, too.
I gotta look menacing
with a cool tattoo in prison.
Sure thing.
What tattoo do you want?
Puffin.
Puffin?
That's not menacing at all.
On the contrary, I think
it'll only attract admirers.
Who knows?
Maybe I'll scare them off.
If you're getting a puffin tattoo,
then I want…
a penguin tattoo.
Don't get mad at me when it's ugly.
I won't.
But I'll get even with
you, even if in prison.
Apply that first.
It's pretty.
You can easily steal my job.
Don't exaggerate.
The lines aren't even that good.
But I love it.
Imperfections are
charming in their own way.
I'm looking forward to making
more tattoo stories with you.
The story of you and me
will be etched on my skin forever.
I'll miss you, Kant.
Get up here.
Hey.
I didn't know 24 hours would go by so fast.
Take care of yourself.
Don't drive too fast.
Don't drive when you've been drinking,
and don't be on your phone.
Eat something nutritious
every once in a while.
I know.
Be patient when you're in there.
Let things slide when
someone tries to mess with you.
There are criminals way
more ruthless than you in there.
They're not kind like you.
Be patient until you get out of there.
Are you telling me not to put up a fight?
I'm not stopping you.
I know I can't stop you.
You're a fighter, after all.
Just don't die in there.
You, too, alright?
Don't get on people's nerves.
Stay alive and come
out of there in one piece.
What?
I've gotten way more mellow
since I met you, you know?
Let me know if you need anything.
I'll send you money.
I'll visit all the time.
You don't have to.
The prison is way too far from your house.
Once a month is often enough.
No.
If I could go every day, I would.
Don't.
Just focus on working and living your life.
No.
You can't stop me.
I've got my future planned out for you.
Alright?
Take care, alright?
Of course.
Time to go.
Take care of him, will you?
Of course.
He's my pal.
I can never leave him.
Take care of Kant, Style.
Make sure he eats properly.
I'll keep an eye on him.
Bye.
We're good to go.
You okay?
It's okay, bud.
It's okay.
(Next Week)
You sure you're alright in there?
Of course.
Don't worry.
I miss you.
Come visit when you miss me.
I can't take this anymore!
I can only see him, but can't touch him.
It feels like he's even further away.
I have an idea.
What?
You want me to put you in jail?
Hey, pretty boy.
You looking for trouble?
We have to be here for five years.
Get used to it.
Seeing you makes me happy.