I think I’d better go take a shower.
What’s up, sis?
What’s with you? Disappeared for a week without a call or update… How’s the internship with Tai going?
It’s fun, but kinda hectic too.
Just don’t go breaking anything, alright?... So, when are you coming home? Dad’s been complaining every day.
Hmm… Probably Monday. I'll stay the night and head back tomorrow.
That’s good. Dad hasn’t been feeling well lately. Guess he misses his troublemaker son—can’t eat, can’t sleep.
You’re exaggerating, sis. Tell him I’m coming home tonight then. And ask him to grill some fish for me!
Ugh, such a foodie! See you tonight then.
Alright, sis. See you!
..Grilled fish, woohoo!
Dad!!
What?
Jun said he’s coming home today. And tonight, he wants you to grill fish for him.
What? He’s interning and Tai’s even giving him a salary. Shouldn’t he be treating me?
Aww, I’ll treat him instead, Dad. Let Jun save his money. You won’t have to worry so much.
I know… but I still worry about him.
Come on, he’s got plenty of people taking care of him over there. Who knows, next time he comes back, he might bring a boyfriend to show off!
Really now? Ooh! (laughs) Alright, alright.
Need help with anything, Dad?
It’s fine. I’ll handle it.
Yo, what’s up, Win?
Jun. Tell me what was up the other day—left me with that weird message and then vanished.
I was thinking about going home.
You better just tell me now or I’ll come storm into your room.
Up to you, bro. If you wanna come, then just come.
Alright then. Let me grab my car keys real quick.
Good. You can crash at my place. I’m staying at Dad’s tonight anyway. Yo, he’s grilling fish for dinner—interested?
Hell yeah. That sauce hits different.
Yeah.
But I haven’t showered yet. Gimme a minute, I’ll come pick you up.
Damn, you always take forever. Hurry up, man!
Hey there, my dear --
Yo Jun.
Oh Hia, Tai! What’s up?
I told Hia Tai I was going to your place, so he wanted to come along.
I’m craving Thai tea from Ko Nueng’s place.
Let’s go, bro. Bet you’re hungry. What about Hia Champ?
Champ’s working at the factory. Couldn’t make it.
Are we heading out yet?
My friend, I’m starving. Can we grab something to eat first?
What would you like to order?
Crispy pork basil with a fried egg, for me.
Make that two, please.
Jun, what are you getting?
Minced pork basil with a well-done fried egg, please.
Two of those.
I’m gonna go smoke. You coming, Tai?
Yeah, I’ll come with.
Alright, man.
Huh?
Did you have a fight with Sorn or something?
Nope, didn’t fight.
You guys work at the same place, and he’s mentoring you too. Talk to him more—might help you guys get closer.
We only talk about work. Don’t really feel like chatting.
And that message you sent me—seriously dude, are you hiding something from me?
Nah. I was just watching my series and got curious about something. You’re overthinking it.
Of course I’m overthinking! You usually tell me everything. If you’re hiding something this time, it’s kinda sus, right?
There’s really nothing, bro. Don’t worry about it. I’m just hungry.
Alright man, I’m gonna hit the bathroom.
Sure, all of you just leave me here alone as usual.
Where’s Win?
He went to the bathroom, bro.
Ah, okay.
Then I guess I’ll go now too.
Didn’t you go earlier?
Nope, didn’t go.
Hey, stop shaking your leg, man.
You know, people who shake their leg a lot are supposed to be super horny.
Nope.
Or… wanna try with me and see for yourself?
What the hell are you saying?
Can you just sit still for a sec?
Then stop shaking your leg, I don’t like it.
Then help me out.
Help with what?
Yo, what are you doing?
Put your leg over mine so I won’t forget and shake again.
Win’s taking forever.
Can we get the check?
Four meals and four drinks, total 240 baht.
Here’s the exact amount.
Thank you!
Thanks for the meal, bro!
Now you’re all comfy, huh?
Dad!
Dad, Sister.
I’m home! Missed you!
Missed you too.
Still as handsome as ever, huh, my son?
Looking sharp, as always!
Sis, give me a hug. Missed you too!
Alright, that’s enough now.
It’s been a while... There’s Dad over there!
Hey!
Good evening, sir.
Tai and Win came too?
And that’s Sorn, right? I remember you! It’s been a while—you’ve gotten so handsome.
Go grab a seat. Order anything you want, I’ll make the drinks.
Dad always flatters everyone. Handsome where?
I’m serious! He really is!
Alright, I’ll help.
Cold drinks coming in! Here, this one’s for Tai—Dad said you don’t like sweet stuff, and he still remembers!
That’s awesome.
And here’s yours.
I’m thinking of checking out our old house. Haven’t been there in ages.
How is it?
Still tastes just like I remember.
Dude, I’m so excited!
What’s with you?
Come on, Sis—it’s rare we get grilled fish at home. Can’t I be happy?
Then go all out! You too, Win—don’t hold back. I’m paying today.
Wait, wasn’t Dad treating?
Sis...
Welp, guess I’m going all in now!
Dig in! Look at Dad today—grinning ear to ear.
It’s rare to have everyone at the table. Of course I’m happy. Ever since Jun left for college, this house got way quieter.
Come on, Dad—I thought Sis’s voice would’ve given you more headaches than me.
Jun, you brat!
How about this, Dad—tonight I’ll talk non-stop so you won’t feel bored. Deal?
All night long?
Can you handle that, Dad?
Bring it on!
Alright, alright—let’s eat!
Hello? What’s up, Piang?
Why’ve you disappeared lately? You don’t even call me anymore. Forgot about me or what?
Been super busy lately... Haven’t really talked to anyone much.
Oof, feels like I just dropped in your priority list or something.
And as for all my other flings—they’re all gone now.
Yup, all done for. Only Jun left, and he won’t even check in!
Aww, sorry. So, what are you up to?
Nothing much, just chilling. Wanna come over?
I’m sleepy… Was gonna crash early.
Then I’ll come sleep next to you. How about that?
Nope. I’ll end up not sleeping at all.
Let’s go out tonight then. You in?
Sure, I actually got something I wanted to talk to you about too. What time?
Same as always—meet at 10 p.m.
10 it is…
Um.. OKay, but can I leave before 1 a.m.? I’ve got work early tomorrow.
Deal. But Jun, dress up tonight—I’m showing you off.
Showing off, huh? Alright, I’ll make sure I look my best.
Alrighty!
See you, Piang.
Bye bye!
Yeah, I’ll check in on that again tomorrow. June isn’t rushing me or anything.
Just give me a call if there’s any update.
I'm going to the bar today. Do you want to come in?
Okay, I'll go now.
Whoa, with all this food, the bill’s gonna be huge for sure.
Not really. Don’t worry when you’re with me—we’ll split the bill.
Saying that, I thought you were gonna treat me.
Wow!
Told you to dress up, and you overdid it!
Look—everyone’s staring at you. I’m getting jealous here.
So, Jun… you said you had something to talk to me about. What is it?
How did you know you were a bottom?
Why’re you asking me that?
No reason. Just curious.
Well...
I used to be a top, but it didn’t feel right. Getting topped felt better.
So you had to test it to know?
What do you mean?
I mean… I feel like my preferences are changing.
Huh? Wait—are you saying you don’t like guys anymore?
No, Piang. I still like guys. It’s just that…
Don’t tell me… you don’t wanna be a top anymore… you wanna be a bottom now?
Um.
Yeah… Aren’t you shocked?
Of course I’m shocked—but it’s not a big deal. Everyone’s into different things. Nothing weird about that.
But how do you know you don’t want to be a top anymore?
Honestly? I don’t even know. I’m really confused.
Who the hell confused you that much? I’ve been talking to you for months and all I got was a kiss.
But this person… he confused you this bad? Must’ve hit you deep, huh?
I’m sorry…
Damn it, Jun.
I thought I was getting a boyfriend—turns out I got a girl bestie.
So this is what’s been stressing you out?
Yeah… I feel like I don’t even know who I am anymore.
Not yourself.
Then how about this—go ahead and prove it.
Like tonight—you already brought a guy here. Just do it with him.
What the hell are you talking about?
I’m not crazy. I’m serious. If you really wanna find out, this is the way.
Hold on, I’ll be back in a sec.
Piang’s been here a while. What took you so long? Aren’t you the owner?
Jun, this is Franz—the owner. And Franz.
This is Jun, Piang’s… guy.
Hi there.
Franz, that’s Piang. What’s with that face, huh? Don’t make me find out something shady.
Just saying hi. That’s all.
Whoa… Jun...
How much have you had to drink?
Just enough to numb my heart.
Trying to heal? So what?
Wait—don’t tell me...
I think I’m gonna try what you suggested… but I haven’t found my target yet.
God, you drive me crazy sometimes.
Just stay right here. Piang will be back. Franz, watch him for a bit, will you?
Gimme a cold towel first. And take good care of him, okay?
Would you like another drink?
Thanks.
Your name’s Jun, right?
Yeah.
That’s a unique name.
My dad says it means “handsome.”
And hey—he wasn’t wrong.
So… Jun, are you a bottom?
I guess I could be. I kinda wanna find out if I can be one.
Well then… shall we head to the back?
Why the hell didn’t he accept it?
Hey, kid.
Yeah?
Franz here yet?
Yeah, he’s in the back.
Go tell him I’m here. Now.
Franz is with someone. I didn’t wanna interrupt.
Fine. I’ll go in there myself.
Franz!
What the hell, Sorn? Can’t it wait? You’re seriously killing the vibe.
Jun!
Sorn?
Wait—hold up. You two know each other?
You can’t mess with this kid!
Whoa… is that really Sorn?
Yeah, it’s me! Who told you to drink this much, Jun?
No one curses like that—yep, it’s Sorn for real.
You’re seriously the most stubborn little shit, Jun!
I swear I’ll smack you as many times as your age—stubborn as hell! Come here!
Didn’t you tell me to wait out back?
You brought me all the way back home?
Damn, just when we were about to do something—you totally ruined the mood, Franz. Classy move.
Fine, you little shit. When you’re with me, you act like you’re with someone else.
Do what you want. I’ll just sit here and say nothing.
You little punk…
Seriously deserve a slap.
Who told you to drink that beer?
Who told you to stock it in the fridge?
You’re so damn stubborn, Jun… unbelievably so.
I’ve never met anyone this hard-headed in my life.
Even Win listens better than you.
Why are you even here? Why do you care so much? Didn’t you say you didn’t like me?
See? You’re confusing the hell out of me again!
Say it! What did I do that confused you?
Just say it!
Is that why you were about to hook up with Franz?
I already told you—don’t go doing this kind of thing with someone else. You can do it only with me!
If you wanna learn something, or if you need anything—just tell me!
It’s you, okay? You’re the one who’s confusing me.
I know I like guys, but...
I don’t know what I really want.
And every time you teach me… I still can’t do it with anyone else.
But when I’m with you… it just feels different.
So that’s why you were gonna try it with someone else?
Yeah. So what if I was?
Then I’ll try it with you.
And I’ll make it so clear.
You won’t need answers from anyone else.
Yes, Mom.
When are you coming home, Sorn?
Can’t right now. Orders from overseas are piling up.
Tai and Champ can’t handle it alone, so I gotta help them out.
You’re working yourself too hard, son. You’ll get sick at this rate.
Your boy’s not that easy to break, Mom.
Alright, my strong boy… Oh right—Uncle Nui asked about buying the land.
I’ll come down during the long holiday.
Alright, I’ll let her know.
What’s wrong?
Tripped over the blanket…
Huh? You clumsy buffalo.
Ouch—don’t curse at me.
That hurt!
I’m naked, you know!
Can you get up? Let’s go eat something.
Just give me a minute.
What are you embarrassed for? You’re built like a damn ox and still acting like a shy kid.
If you can walk, come downstairs and eat.
By the way, James is coming back soon. You’ll have to go stay with him.
Okay…
So… you staying over with me again tonight?
Nah, I’ll head back to my dorm.
But I won’t be at your dorm, you know?
Yo, Sorn!
You’ve been in a good mood lately. Got something going on you’re not telling me?
Nothing.
Yeah right! Ever since Tai’s been gone this week,
you’ve been living it up like some
dude on vacation from his wife! You bastard!
Hey, Sorn—if you’re giving Jun that look because you’re planning something, don’t let me catch you.
Hey Jun, go make me some coffee.
I’m not your barista, bro. If you want coffee that bad, make it yourself.
Wow, can’t even make one cup? So heartless.
What’s his problem?
Delivery for Khun Penny.
Jun, go grab Penny’s stuff.
Hi there.
Oh! It’s you! Sorry about the other day—I ran into you pretty hard.
Ah, it’s you. Are you the new intern?
Yeah, just started two weeks ago.
That explains why I hadn’t seen you before. And sorry as well—I wasn’t watching where I was going.
No worries at all.
Here’s the food for Khun Penny.
Got it. I’ll put it away.
Thanks, I’ll leave it to you.
Sure thing.
Thanks.
Yep.
What were you two talking about?
Just random stuff. Nothing important.
Yo, where you planning to eat?
Why? You treating?
You coming or not?
I was thinking noodles at that spot. It’s good.
Okay then. I’ll take rice noodles—no bean sprouts, no pork, no meatballs. And pack it to go, please.
Damn, bro. This place is packed!
Wanna take it upstairs and eat?
Order in.
Takeout? That’ll be a 20-minute wait.
What’s wrong?
I’m starving.
it’s hot as hell.
Ughh can I grab something to eat first? I seriously can’t take it.
Wait.
Hey! Don’t mess with me—I’ll snitch to Tai for real!
Maybe I should mess with you for once. Fine, do whatever you want, buffalo.
Wait, where you going? Seriously, can we eat first?
Tokyo (pancakes)
What would you like?
Mixed fillings—three pieces, please.
Oh no, there’s something stuck on your face.
Bro! You didn’t tell me I had tissue on my face!
Totally killed my look.
Look at this!
Damn, you complain non-stop when you’re hungry.
I was gonna take it off earlier and you snapped, saying I was messing with you.
Now you’re mad I didn’t say anything?
Get it all off.
Is it all gone?
With all that whining, you wanna be my wife or something?
Who’d wanna be your wife? You’re old!
Old, huh? Still the one who made you moan, Jun.
Oh my god—cut it out, Sorn!
Hmm? You’re not eating the meatballs?
Nah.
Can I have them?
What’re you gonna give me in return?
Seriously? I have to trade for meatballs?
You were gonna throw them away anyway. Just give them to me, please!
I paid for this noodle bowl,
And now you just want to steal my meatballs? Don’t be such
a moocher, Jun.
Won’t even give me a bite… stingy!
Use those skills I taught you.
If you’re my student, you better know how to handle stuff like this.
Get in the car.
Why are you standing there all clueless? Wanna get my dad insulted or something?
I thought you already went home.
I bought a suki set. Didn’t feel like eating alone, so I came to pick you up.
You mean… me?
Well, who the hell do you think I brought into the car? Use your brain, man.
Did I say I wanted to go to your house?
I’m making you.
After we eat, I’ll drop you off at your dorm. Happy now?
Call Champ to join us first.
I didn’t invite him, I invited you.
Besides, I just had western food. Too greasy—I hated it.
Why’d you eat it then?
Can you just shut up until we get home?
Keep talking and I’ll really kiss you.
Eat.
Not hungry.
I’m heading out.
Last bus is gone.
Grab a ride.
Do you always trust people that easily, Jun?
What else do you want me to do?
Want me to take you back?
Why not just sleep here?
Nope.
Why not?
It’s free. Don’t wanna crash here?
Nah, I’m heading back. Better that way.
We’re both guys—nothing should happen, right?
You’re so damn stubborn.
I’ll drive you back.
Thanks for dropping me off.
Jun....
This kiss is one that sticks.
When you kiss like that, the person you kiss will be thinking about you all night long.
Damn, if you’re gonna teach me, just say so. No need to yank my neck like that—you scared the crap outta me!
I’m going now.
Jun....
can I crash at your dorm tonight? Don’t wanna risk driving—might doze off.
You already got there?
Yeah.
You, man...
Just got back from dinner with a client.
Ahh..
I’m gonna shower first.
Mhm, go ahead.
Hey, don’t forget to turn the camera back around.
Shit…
Yo, don’t start judging my room,
It’s… kinda messy.
Mm.
Make yourself at home, I’ll shower real quick.
Don’t trash the place.
You could’ve just told me to carry it—don’t just hold it out like that. You scared me!
Where should I put it?
I saw you tell Tai this model fits great.
Yeah, it does. So, where do you want me to put them?
I bought them but the size’s wrong.
You take them—wear 'em for me.
Bro… are you seriously taking back the shoes? You gave them to me—who does that?
Still got them?
Yeah, I still have them.
You gave them to me.
You’re so dramatic—go write a novel or something,
you’d be great.
Alright, I’m taking this side. You sleep on the inside.
Your room’s hot as hell. I might need to sleep naked.
Jun…
What the hell are you talking about?
I want to.
Ugh—wait, hold on…
Look, I think we need to have a straight-up talk.
Can’t it wait till later?
Nope. We’re talking now.
Say what you wanna say.
Like… about that stuff—we’ve done it once, and that was enough, right? I feel like it’s gone too far now.
If I tell you something… can you handle it, Jun?
Go ahead. Say it.
I like doing it with you… but you’re not that good.
But if you keep practicing, I think you’ll become amazing.
But why me?
From the koi pond back then… to now...
Why’d you believe me anyway?
You sound convincing. And honestly, I thought it was safe talking to you.
Can I ask why you kept teaching me?
Because we already started something. And it wasn’t hard to just… keep going.
Right now, I just want you to focus on one thing—are you happy with what we’re doing?
Honestly… yeah, I kinda like it. It’s not like it’s hurting anyone, right?
Why are you overthinking all this?
How could I not think about it? We didn’t even get along before… and now this?
If your girlfriend sees this, won’t she kill me?
I don’t have a wife. No kids.
What about you? Got a boyfriend? A fling?
Someone I’m talking to… but it’s nothing.
Then stop talking to them. If you’ve got something to say,
say it to me.
Wow… you’re acting like my boyfriend now.
Let me tell you something, Jun… If I were your boyfriend, you wouldn’t be asking me these dumb questions.
So? You and me—are we clear now?
Yeah, clear.
Clear about what?
You and I… we’re just sex buddies. We give each other what we need. No feelings involved.