=Eight Hundred=
Grandpa, Grandma.
(Year 1993)
Songge.
Please confirm if these remains
are your family members,
Gao Peiliang
and Liu Xiwen?
When they left this morning,
they were fine.
It can't be.
That's enough, child.
Mr. Chen,
tell me why this happened.
Songge,
because of the rain,
rocks from a landslide
hit your grandparents' car.
Due to excessive blood loss,
the hospital couldn't save them.
Control yourself.
Songge, be good.
- Songge.
- Don't be sad.
It's okay, Songge.
You're like a daughter to us.
We will take good care of you.
- Songge.
The blood test results are out.
(Fengyang Mine Workers' Hospital Lab Report)
Serum creatinine is already at 1,200.
What does that mean?
It's uremia.
She needs dialysis.
How can Songge
be so pitiful?
No family since she was little,
and now, she has this disease.
This disease is the most draining.
Draining for the patient,
draining for the family.
If things go wrong,
the whole family could be ruined.
Do you know
how much one dialysis session costs?
We have to treat her
regardless of the cost.
=Episode 12=
(Old Coal Washing Plant)
Hui.
Hui!
(Public Security)
Get out of the car.
Director Chen.
Where's the person?
He ran.
Mom, what are you still doing back here?
What kind of birthday is this?
Mom, I'm sorry.
I suddenly realized I forgot the candles,
so I thought about going out to buy some.
But I ran all over Fengyang
and couldn't find any.
What is this?
Turns out I didn't forget.
Mom,
where's Dad?
Same as you, acting crazy.
Mom.
Alright, Mom.
Don't be angry anymore, okay?
Be happy.
We have to blow out the candles
for it to count as a birthday.
Hui, you're back.
Dad.
Something came up
at Director Tong's home,
so he had me cover his shift.
There's a lot going on
at the station now,
and we're short-staffed,
so that's why I'm back late.
Don't be upset.
Happy Birthday.
Are you angry?
Mom,
since Dad is here now,
let's light the candles.
Dad, can you turn off the light?
Right.
Turn off the light.
You paged me just now.
Anything?
What's the matter?
I'm asking if you paged me
just now.
Is everything okay?
I was just asking if you were back.
Mom,
make a wish.
Come on.
What wish could I have?
I just hope
that our family
can stay happy and harmonious.
Mom, our family
is certainly happy and harmonious.
- Happy birthday to you.
- I wish you would never get angry.
Come on.
Okay.
Happy Birthday,
Mom!
This is so wonderful.
Mom, the knife.
Okay, I'll cut it.
(Happy Birthday, Mom)
- Use this one.
- Alright.
Give it to Hui first.
Now, for your dad.
Dad, you go first.
Thank you.
Dad.
Hui, here's a big piece for you.
Thanks, Mom.
Happy Birthday.
This cake is so soft.
It's delicious.
Dad,
Songge bought this cake specially.
It's sugar-free, so you can eat more.
Songge is so thoughtful.
Hui, it's about time.
You still have a long way to go.
You should head back now.
It's fine, Mom.
It's your birthday today.
I'll stay with you a bit longer.
We've eaten the cake,
and I've made the wish.
It's okay, come back next time.
The main thing
is that the drive is too long.
Alright, then.
Mom, Dad, I'll be heading back.
- Okay.
Take it slow on the road.
Hui,
can I hitch a ride with you?
Where are you going now?
Director Tong is still at the station.
I have to go and take over his shift.
It's just a few steps away.
Why are you making Hui drive you?
I'm just too lazy to walk.
What's wrong with having my son drive me?
Is that okay?
Of course, it's okay.
Alright.
Hui,
you come inside too.
Dad, it's getting late.
I still have to head back to the city.
Just come on in.
What's this about?
You'll know once you're inside.
Dad,
why did you have me come in?
Dad, what are you doing?
Why are you locking me up?
Dad, why?
You don't know why?
What should I know?
You asked me for a ride,
and I brought you here,
then you locked me up.
You at least have to tell me why.
What do you mean by this?
Stop playing dumb with me!
You know exactly
what you've done!
(24-Hour Service. Fengyang Town
Police Station, Jiangbin Municipal PSB)
(People's Public Security)
Director Tong,
how is it?
Claims to know nothing.
Director Tong,
where are our men who were on lookout?
When I got to the coal washing pool,
it was pitch black,
and I didn't see
a single one of our people.
There was an emergency.
A home invasion robbery
occurred in the west of town.
The station was shorthanded,
so I deployed everyone there.
I wanted to tell you
when we were on the phone earlier,
but your signal was bad.
Then, your phone was turned off.
I couldn't get through to you at all.
Director Tong,
is there anything in this town
more important
than the cough syrup case?
Don't be so anxious.
Regarding Hui's case,
we need to re-examine the situation.
We have to change
the interrogation method.
Also,
the Bureau's decision on your recusal
has already come in.
While Hui is a suspect in the case,
as a direct relative,
you must recuse yourself.
I'll comply.
Go on home.
Regardless of whether Hui did it or not,
you are father and son.
Things have become
too tense between you,
so how will you face each other later?
Director Tong,
everything I'm doing
is to save him, isn't it?
Who could have thought he'd end up
as the primary suspect?
If he can't understand
why I'm doing this,
then he's a fool.
The main issue now
is that you don't have any evidence
proving it was actually Hui.
Keeping him in custody
based on mere suspicion
is against the rules.
Without direct evidence,
once 24 hours have passed,
you'll have to release him.
Direct evidence...
Maybe I really do have some.
Well?
Can I go now?
Chen Hui,
take off your clothes.
What do you mean?
I've said everything I need to say.
Why make me undress?
Just do as you're told.
I've cooperated with everything.
You can't keep doing this over and over.
This is a police station.
We expect you to cooperate.
Take them off.
Come on.
Help him.
Please cooperate with us.
I'll do it myself.
(Holding Room)
Director Tong, how's it going?
That's it.
Let's wait for the results.
Let's go.
Big guy,
be careful on the road.
I've already called
Liu Na and Kang Limin.
When you get to the municipal PSB,
they'll coordinate with you.
- Okay.
- Fine.
It's so late. Who's calling?
Probably Songge.
Hongbing, you answer it.
Until the results are out,
we can't alert the target.
Understood.
Hello?
Hello, Mr. Chen.
Is Chen Hui there?
Songge,
Hui...
Hui drank too much.
He's not coming back today.
Mr. Chen,
there were too many people
for dialysis today.
I couldn't make it
to Mrs. Chen's birthday.
She isn't upset, is she?
No.
How could she be?
Songge,
just get some good rest.
Okay.
Goodbye, Mr. Chen.
Goodbye.
All right.
Big guy,
get moving.
Be careful on the road.
Right, I'll be off then.
Okay, go on.
Stop worrying.
Give me the office keys.
What for?
To find some clothes for Chen Hui.
It's freezing out.
We can't let him get sick.
Thank you.
Your dad sent these clothes over for you.
Do you know
he's hurting even more
than you are right now.
You can't blame him.
As for what really happened,
you know better than anyone.
If you have something to say,
speak up now.
It'll be better for you.
I'm on duty at the office today.
If you want to talk,
just give me a shout.
Hurry up.
Put the clothes on.
Don't catch a cold.
(Jiangbin Municipal PSB)
Limin.
Big guy.
Officer Tang, could you please
try to hurry?
If we don't have results
within 24 hours,
we'll have to release him immediately.
No problem. We'll have results by nine.
Thank you.
Please come with me
to handle the paperwork.
Hurry up.
Don't worry, Chief Liu.
What's going on?
Director Chen now suspects
that the source seller
of the cough syrup
we've been tracking
is Chen Hui.
Chen Hui?
As for the specifics,
we'll have to wait for the test results
to find out.
How could this happen?
What exactly went down?
Earlier, didn't Officer Tang
detect that substance,
whatever it was called,
on the cough syrup bottle?
Later, following the lead,
we found the place where it was hidden.
It was at the Fengyang Coal Mine,
in an abandoned coal washing pool.
Yesterday, right after Chen Hui
returned to Fengyang,
someone went to the coal washing pool.
So you're saying
it's not certain it's Hui yet?
Not certain.
By the time our men arrived,
the person had already fled.
But he made a mess of the scene
so that there was water
from the coal washing pool everywhere.
If it really were Chen Hui,
the substance
would be detected on him.
If Hui is the person
we've been looking for,
the scarred woman must be...
(Yingxiong Internet Cafe)
Songge.
The boss hasn't picked up yet?
At this hour,
he really should be up by now.
Don't worry, he's fine.
He's just sleeping in.
Hello, Grandpa.
This is Songge.
Songge,
when are you coming back to see me?
I'll be back to visit you
in a couple of days.
Grandpa,
is Hui at home?
You mean Hui?
He left last night.
Hello?
Songge,
what's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm not feeling well.
I'm going to go back and rest for a bit.
Are you okay?
Why the sudden discomfort?
How about...
Songge.
Officer Liu.
Officer Liu,
you don't need to see me out.
Go on back, thank you.
You don't look well.
I'll walk you back.
No need, it's too much trouble.
Not at all.
I don't have anything else to do anyway.
I'm really fine.
I just need to sleep it off.
I can't just leave you alone
at home either.
When I wasn't feeling well before,
didn't you take care of me too?
Let's go.
Officer Liu, please have a seat.
Wait a moment, I'll make you some tea.
Don't bother with that,
go get some sleep.
I'll be fine here on my own.
Thank you.
Aren't you going to sleep?
I'm suddenly not that sleepy anymore.
Songge,
today,
did you call Hui?
He hasn't been picking up.
Is there anything
you want to tell me?
No.
Officer Liu, do you
have something to tell me?
Not for now.
How did it go?
Hello?
Chen Hui,
you're free to go.
Hui,
don't you dare blame your dad.
He's a policeman.
In this kind of situation,
he didn't have a choice, you know?
Mr. Tong,
please tell my dad
to bring all my stuff
when he finishes work.
I'll be waiting for him at home.
(Holding Room)
Chen Hui,
you're an adult now.
If there's a conflict,
just call your dad outside
and talk it through.
Whatever you do,
don't start a scene at home.
You hear me?
This is a family matter.
You little brat...
Hongbing,
you'd better be careful.
I got the feeling just now
that Hui is in a very bad mood.
There's a good chance
he's going home
to complain to his mother.
Grandpa.
Hui, you're back.
I came to see you.
Grandpa,
rest for a bit.
Wearing the hearing aid
for too long isn't good.
Okay.
Come.
Hello?
Songge, it's me.
Are you okay?
Don't worry, I'm fine.
What happened?
Last night,
my dad locked me up at the station.
He's suspicious of us?
But it's fine now.
How are things on your end?
Officer Liu came by early this morning.
She was probably here
to keep an eye on me.
But she left after getting a phone call.
Then, everything's fine.
Chen Hui, when are you coming back?
Later.
I still have one thing to do.
At a time like this,
what else do you have to do?
We can't just sit and wait for death.
I have to strike back.
Chen Hui,
since it's over now,
just let it go.
Listen to me.
Wait for me to get back.
Grandpa.
Ding Yue, you bought so many groceries.
Are you heading out?
Dad.
Are you hungry?
No.
I brought you some soup.
If you're hungry,
I'll get you a piece of the cake
that Hui bought yesterday
from the fridge.
I'm not hungry.
Let's wait and eat together.
Okay, keep an eye on it then.
Will do.
Mom.
Mom,
what's wrong?
Nothing.
When I got up this morning,
I tweaked my back.
I think my herniated disc
is acting up again.
Stop working.
I'll help you inside to rest.
No need.
I'll just sit for a bit.
Take it easy.
I'll get you a chair.
Sit down slowly.
How is it?
It's okay.
Why are you back again?
I never left last night.
You didn't leave?
Then, why didn't you come home?
Don't even ask, Mom.
Just thinking about it
makes me so angry.
What happened now?
It's all my dad's fault.
Your dad?
- Off to work?
- Chen.
Wait.
Is Mom at home?
Yes.
What did you tell her?
I just told her
what you did.
Regarding last night,
did you want to make things even worse?
If you're so afraid of Mom knowing,
why weren't you afraid
when you locked me up?
I've already let you out.
Must you come home to cause trouble?
If you didn't mess with me,
would I mess with you?
Why did you lock me up?
A summons.
A police summons lasts...
Twelve hours for criminal cases,
and twenty-four for complex ones, right?
I'm asking why you locked me up.
What was the reason?
It's your duty to cooperate
with a police summons.
So, there is no reason.
You're even too lazy to make up
some trumped-up charges now?
Save your grumbling.
If you truly don't know why deep down,
then you don't ever
need to know for the rest of your life.
Give me my things.
Move.
Look, you're keeping me here
stalling like this,
(Liusan Mutton Restaurant)
but it doesn't solve anything.
It's the middle of the night.
Aren't you going home?
If you keep stalling,
I can't stay with you anymore.
I haven't figured out yet
how to explain this to Ding Yue.
Anyway, I think
you might really be wrong this time.
If the person who ran away
from the coal washing plant
really was Hui,
not a single drop of water
from the pool got on him.
Is that even possible?
I'm relying on my instincts
from all my years as a cop.
Could it be such a coincidence?
We've been here for years
and handled many cases, big and small,
but never once
has a case been as strange as this.
- Right?
- Enough.
"Big and small cases"...
What kind of big cases
could we have here?
At most, it's brawls,
robberies, thefts,
or unlicensed mining.
Since I became Director,
the biggest case
involved someone
stealing over 400 kg of scrap iron.
Don't forget,
we're the ones
who vowed to the entire city
to get this done.
Isn't the cough syrup case
the biggest
we have right now?
So, this is an opponent
we've never encountered before.
Making a misjudgment
is allowed, okay?
I really do hope
that I'm wrong.
Come on.
Finish your drink and go home.
You're back.
Why are you sleeping here?
Waiting for you.
I fell asleep while waiting.
What's wrong?
It's my back.
I tweaked it today.
Then, don't move. Don't move.
Let me.
- Let me see.
- It's fine.
It's fine.
Is it serious?
Right here?
Or here on the right?
Hui told you
about what happened last night?
You have the nerve to bring it up?
Be a little gentler.
Alright.
You're not feeling well.
Once you've rested,
I'll explain it to you.
It's my fault.
I didn't get a chance to tell you.
What's with you today?
Usually,
you're the tough guy
who only acts out at home.
Why are you so unusual today?
I'm just afraid...
I'm worried about you.
So now you're afraid of worrying me.
But what you and Tong did
wasn't very honorable.
You really put Hui through a lot.
Yes.
We were inconsiderate.
Then again,
anyway, this matter
has nothing to do with us.
Let's go.
Go upstairs to bed.
Go to sleep?
Is that it?
What else should we do but sleep?
Don't you have anything else
to say to me?
My back is hurting like crazy.
I don't have the energy
to talk to you.
Go upstairs. Let's go.
No.
What exactly did Hui tell you?
Why are you being so persistent?
He just told me
you insisted he
transfer the roller skating rink
to Tong's niece.
The classmate of his,
the one selling TVs
at the department store...
What was his name again?
- Wang Xiaojian.
- Right.
It's Wang Xiaojian.
He also wanted
to take over the roller skating rink.
Didn't they run
into each other on the street?
He blamed Hui,
made Hui treat him to a meal,
and made him drink as a penalty.
It lasted all night.
He threw up several times.
When did
Hui tell you this?
At noon today.
He only told you that?
Then, what else should he have told me?
He shouldn't have said anything else.
He's telling the truth.
Let's go.
Chen Hui.
When did you get up?
I haven't been able to sleep.
The fact that Mr. Chen let you go
means he has no evidence.
Besides, we won't be doing this anymore.
Don't overthink it.
Come and sleep for a while.
I originally wanted to tell
my mom about this.
Only by making my mom worry
would my dad's mind be unsettled.
But when I saw
my mom's back hurting like that,
I couldn't bear to make her worry.
I just suddenly felt
like my mom had grown old.
I couldn't say a single word
of what I had planned to say.
♪I always thought
once we see the full picture♪
♪We could understand
each other with empathy♪
♪I always thought
the path we never took♪
♪Must have had more beautiful scenery♪
♪Keep moving forward
and don't look back♪
♪The shore is only reached
by the road ahead♪
♪Too much debt has accumulated♪
♪In this short life♪
♪Between right and wrong,
how to choose?♪
♪Regret is inevitable in the end♪
♪Even so-called love
is repaid with pain♪
♪I hear the laughter
and follow the crowd♪
♪Into the streets and alleys♪
♪On that brightly lit night♪
♪Unfortunately, the breeze in town♪
♪Can no longer catch up to the children♪
♪Times have changed♪
♪Now, everything♪
♪Is no longer what it used to be♪