(Uilhan Brewery)
(1. Malting, 2. Malt milling, 3. Mash tun, 4. Hopping)
(Kim Se Jeong)
(Highly passionate, highly sensitive)
(Lee Jong Won)
(Shin Do Hyun)
(Baek Sung Chul)
(Uilhan Brewery)
(Naro Beer)
(Brewing Love)
(This is a work of fiction.)
(Scenes with child actors and animals were filmed...)
(under production guidelines along with experts.)
We should take shelter.
What's with him?
- Head there first. - Sure.
Shall we get going?
Am I wrong?
Are these emotions...
mine?
Come on. It's already late.
These aren't my emotions.
There's no way I like her.
I guess it stopped raining.
Right.
- Shall we get going? - Sure.
How will you get home?
We can share a cab.
Why? We live in opposite directions.
All roads lead to one, and it's late.
- We should share a cab. - It's fine.
Whatever. I don't mind getting home early.
It's not like I want to take the long way home.
Doesn't he know who he has feelings for?
So much for me being an escort.
As if I need one.
- Mr. Yoon. - What the...
Did that startle you?
- What... - Are you not feeling well?
Sorry?
No, it's just that my heart is beating abnormally.
Your heart? Why is that?
Do you have an underlying heart condition?
It wasn't actually my heart.
I guess you can say I absorbed emotions.
You absorbed emotions?
It's nothing. I'll feel better once you two head off.
Sure.
Where are you staying? We should give you a ride.
No, I'll get back on my own.
- You should get going. Go on. - Right.
- Are you sure you're okay? - Don't come at me together.
Stop.
What's with him? Is he drunk?
Are you asking I'm drunk...
when you don't know who made me feel this way?
Who's causing it?
Hold on a second.
Do you really not know?
Know what?
Well, your...
What?
I think it's best for us to part ways.
I'll see you at the next meeting.
Take care, then.
Sure.
We'll get going first.
- Sure. - Come on.
Stay in touch.
Where I got hit earlier...
Why would you touch it?
I'm worried it might scar.
- I bet it's still throbbing. - Hold on.
Doesn't Kang Beom know how he feels?
But his heart was pounding.
Mind your own business.
How can he not know this?
(Brewing Love)
(Episode 5)
Boss!
Put down your camera and enjoy this with us.
He's an expert at spending time alone.
I guess it's photo day.
Come on.
It's not like there's anything new.
What were you taking photos of?
Take photos of us instead. Make us look good.
I don't take photos of people.
I only take photos of things that never change.
- What... - A jerk.
That's what my late mother took photos of.
Didn't I tell you she was a photographer?
- Now, that's stylish. - Tell me about it.
- She must be so cool. - Right?
(Absorbing emotions)
(A talent those highly sensitive possess)
(Do you wish to manage your hyper-empathy and sensitivity?)
"They confuse their emotions with other people's..."
"and feel the emotions felt by other people."
"That puts them in a unique position to heal others,"
"but that leads to draining their own energy."
There are Mr. Yoon and the ladies.
- Shall we make a stop? - Sure.
- Seriously. - Here you go.
Have some rice instead.
- How do you like it? - I already had my meal.
What? Why didn't you tell us that?
Hello!
- Goodness. - Gosh.
But the meeting is in the afternoon.
We came by early. You must be having lunch.
They always come to us for a meal, don't they?
Are we your lunch ladies?
- Get over here. - Get over here.
Others must be joining us today.
Yes, but we asked them to be here yesterday.
Thanks.
How dense of me.
Eat up if you get our drift.
The bibimbap was mixed yesterday.
Try some. Go ahead.
Exceptional, right?
Goodness.
- It's nice to eat as a group. - I know.
- Goodness. - My gosh.
Mr. Yoon, are you sure you're feeling all right?
- Maybe you should see a doctor... - Goodness.
No doctor can treat what he has.
Exactly. His illness is untreatable.
Because he's a nutcase.
I'll get more water.
Thanks.
Goodness me.
You ate too much too fast.
It's that good.
Let's see.
Do you need something?
Well...
I don't get involved with others' love lives.
I'm hardly ever interested,
but your situation...
My heart is suffering immensely.
Mr. Yoon.
Are you sure there isn't a problem?
Of course not. You're the one with the issue.
- Me? - Well...
What do you think about Ms. Chae?
As in Yong Ju?
- I respect her. - Respect?
- She's admirable. - Is that all?
What more should there be to it?
- Let me get her some water first. - Hold on.
Just a second.
You know how it is. When she's thirsty,
you want to get her water as soon as possible.
What do you call it when you only have eyes for her?
- What's that? - What can it be?
- I'm her junior colleague. - Darn.
It's my duty as her junior colleague.
You like...
Like?
Darn.
Could you have feelings for her?
What?
What on earth?
That's the funniest thing I heard all year.
Mr. Yoon.
What I have for her is respect. I'm a true fan.
Mr. Yoon, I see you're not perceptive.
That was hilarious. Get a grip on yourself.
Oh, no. He has no clue whatsoever.
That idiot.
Mr. Yoon must love to take photos.
- There were many at his place. - Right.
His mother used to be a photographer.
She died young.
I see.
- What has you in a good mood? - Right.
What has you giggling?
Here.
We should slowly get to our meeting.
It's our first one, you see.
- Right. - Sure.
So I heard.
Be good to our boss.
Even if he puts up a wall,
just let him be since that's who he is.
He's actually a kind soul.
I thought I was the boss here.
He already got to know the team members.
We even had drinks together and are now one single team.
We're one team, so don't worry.
- What? - Focus.
No matter how you put it,
this seems wrong.
"The meeting must be held at Mr. Yoon's place of work."
That condition of the contract...
seems like a tall order.
Hold on.
I signed the contract since you agreed to that,
so you can't go against it.
Videoconferencing is a common practice these days.
He's like a roadblock
What do you mean by that?
Thanks.
I understand where you all stand,
so let's focus on the meeting for now.
Here. Thanks.
All right.
This is what we'll be spending most of our time on.
(1st Meeting on Product Development)
A concept. We need one to brew the right beer.
That's right.
That is why I was thinking about holding a two-day workshop.
We'll visit famous breweries and research the market.
Ms. Chae.
The craft beer scene and commercial beer brewing...
are two different markets.
If it's to study recipes,
we can buy well-known craft beer at bottle shops.
A two-day workshop seems unnecessary.
- I agree. - Same here.
I'm afraid I'll be too busy.
There are at least a truckload of ladies who await my toasties...
A truckload...
It's an odd vibe in here.
Gosh, what a great nap.
That was great. I slept like a log.
How refreshing.
Unbelievable.
(Baegok-ri Village Hall)
For 30 years...
I have two X-rays.
For 30 years.
(Hwi's Toast)
Unbelievable.
What is this? Is this a challenge?
Who are you to block the path of a man?
I'm stiff all over and would like a massage.
Don't go in there.
If he wants a massage,
- he should get his massage. - Sure.
I felt like a squid on a grill.
It was hot in there.
Why don't we grill a squid?
- Sounds good. - Good.
Our company already has a signature beer.
As per the chairman's order,
it became our goal to make one that tastes like nothing else.
Up until now, we copied beers that were trending...
and had a brewmaster come up with a recipe...
so that we could release our beer in two months.
To be honest, that's not what I want.
I don't want to do the bare minimum...
and would go on a workshop if one is necessary.
That being said, to do a proper job,
it'll take at least six months...
since I can't sacrifice the operations here at my brewery.
Even that's a tight schedule for me.
Six months to launch a new beer?
- Yes. - Six months.
(D-6 months)
Fine. We give you our word.
All right, then. We'll all be attending the workshop.
Rao, could you book our accommodations?
Ms. Chae, that was unfair for you to ask.
- Sorry? - Well,
I may be the youngest,
but I'm a regular employee at the Seoul office...
and a member of this task force.
I don't get why I of all people...
should book accommodations for the rest.
Yong Ju, I'll do it.
Sure thing.
How about we wrap up today's meeting?
Sure. Good job, everyone.
- Have a good one. - Sure.
Have a safe trip home.
Bye, Ms. Beautiful Bang.
Why that...
That punk's getting on my nerves.
(Baegok-ri Village Hall)
- I'll tidy up inside. - Sure.
It's no walk in the park.
"It's unfair."
- Yong Ju. - Yes, sir.
Come over here.
Can you organize these files today?
Yes, I'll try.
- You can do it, right? - Sure.
Let me do it.
I'll summarize and report to you!
(Safety first)
I should get going too.
- Have a safe trip back home. - Good luck.
Sure!
Ta-da!
What's all this, sir?
It's snacks!
You told me that's what I should do.
That's the right thing to do.
I thought you left.
I mean, you don't need to pretend to be fine.
What are you talking about? I'm totally fine.
You don't look fine,
though you don't seem to know it.
We met for a business. How about focusing on that?
And you don't have to care about how others feel.
If I say I'm fine, then I really am.
I got it.
I should get going now. Take care.
I know you pretend to be cool because of me.
I know you're worried...
your anger might affect me.
That's why you give me the cold shoulder.
I'm thankful for that, but...
Yong Ju!
What a jerk he is!
He's totally nuts, a jerk, and an idiot!
"Unfair"? Really?
I should let him know what unfair means!
Gosh!
Thank you for trying to make me feel better.
- I'm who you can count on, right? - Yes.
Did you say nuts? It's funny.
I think he's out of his mind.
He may have left his brain somewhere.
If I were five years younger, I should've already hit him.
Directly!
That was funny.
- You know how I'm good at it. - Of course, I know.
Darn it.
What? "Thank you for trying to make me feel better"?
Then, what was all about focusing on business?
What was all about the others' feelings she told me?
What a joke.
Was I too cold?
I was worried that he'd feel stressed out.
Yong Ju.
Are you up for a beer?
A beer?
Next time.
I feel suddenly thirsty.
Then, let's stop for a minute to get some water.
Sure.
(Uilhan Brewery)
He came.
I guess Yong Ju just left.
She just left without saying goodbye?
I guess so.
She should've said to you at least.
I thought she was a well-mannered lady!
She just ignored us waiting for her?
That's what I mean.
She's rather ill-mannered!
That's quite harsh. She just...
Just...
We're disappointed.
- Yes, it's disappointing. - I see.
- That's disappointing. - Right.
No! What are you talking about?
I'm totally fine.
- I mean it. - I see.
That's how our boss means it.
Yes. You trust us, don't you?
Yes, it's me.
We have something to work on.
Start moving now.
Yes, sure.
- Hello. - Hi.
- Hello. - Welcome.
Two bottles of water.
Then, it costs...
Why won't it open?
Did somebody lock this?
Then, keep the change for now, please.
We'll visit here quite often due to meetings.
Is that okay for you?
Then, I got it.
- We should get going. - See you.
Drink this.
Thanks, Jjuan.
I mean drink it all.
You mean in here?
I see.
Oh, Chief!
- We should go somewhere. - Where?
Sook and Young Sisters are quite angry now.
We allowed you to use the Village Hall and more.
But how dare you leave without a word?
We weren't thinking that.
- Where are they now? - We'll catch up with our car.
- You, off you go. - Why?
In what world are you now? No overwork!
Yong Ju, you're the only one coming.
Sure. You're good to go.
- Should I get in your car? - Yes.
- This way! - Ma'am, please.
Wait. Please.
Why the pub all of a sudden?
- You'll know the reason soon. - Yes.
Shout it.
- Five, four, three, two. - Five, four, three, two.
One!
Ta-da!
How...
What is this all about?
- Good work today. Take care. - Yes.
I'll go home once I return the car.
- Okay. - See you.
How can she leave without saying goodbye?
She's mean.
I'm leaving!
See you.
She got a part-time job?
- It's been taken care of. - Pardon?
For the next year and a half.
I like being exact with my calculations.
It means you should come back.
Thank you.
What? What are you doing there?
My gosh. Why did you knock this over?
Oh, darn.
My clumsiness is my charm.
By the way, what's with this part-time job?
You work for a big company.
Are you in a bind?
Do you need to make fast cash?
What are you saying?
Boss, I'm sorry.
- You're here. - Yes.
My kid started running a fever all of a sudden.
And my husband said he'd be home late. My gosh.
- Is your kid okay now? - Yes.
I gave my kid a fever reducer, and my husband is home now.
You always help me out when I have an emergency like this. Thank you.
I've worked many part-time jobs,
and a boss like you is hard to come by.
What?
"Boss?"
Ms. Beautiful Bang, are you rich?
This was one of the things I heard the most growing up.
"A girl must be obedient!"
I never held back.
This girl was born, and she threw punches whenever she was provoked.
I just hated losing.
Not the fact that I lost.
I hated letting others find out that I was sad about it.
It made me feel like a real loser.
So I was always like, "Okay, it's totally fine."
I always told myself that.
- You're an orphan - You're an orphan
You have no mom or dad.
I have no parents, but it doesn't mean I have no family.
Hey, you live off welfare.
Does the free food taste good?
You can eat because my dad pays his taxes, so be grateful.
Pass on my thanks to your dad.
I can eat more, right?
Yong Ju! Let's go and sing karaoke.
- Come with us. - Let's go.
Karaoke?
I'm broke, and I have my shift.
Excuse me.
Can we get two more servings of pork belly?
Two servings...
Oh, boy.
- Grandma! - Yes!
Come.
(Corn on the cob, Hotteok)
(Fish Cake)
What?
Oh, it's just... It's very dusty here.
- Oh, come on. - Look at all this dust.
What is with him?
Hello. You can take that table...
- in the back. - I'll have a beer.
- Enjoy. - What a way to ruin the mood.
Dust, all of a sudden? Who cares?
Dust? What is with you?
I feel like your vibe has changed.
Really?
Well, I'm not sure about that.
I wonder what gave you such an impression.
Hey, come on!
By the way, you can't even drink.
How did you get into beer making?
It's not that I can't drink.
I choose not to drink because it gives me a headache.
(In My Name, Naro Beer)
You know, when you drink a lot of beer,
you reach a point when people's voices get muffled.
I know what you're talking about. When you start feeling buzzed.
That's when you start talking louder.
I like it when that happens because I actually feel calm.
I mean, I can block out all external noise,
so I can focus on the sound of my breathing.
In that moment,
I feel like I'm all alone in the world,
and I quite like that.
"All alone?"
You know, while working with us,
if you ever need some alone time,
just let me know, anytime.
I promise you I'll make it happen.
Then if you ever need company,
just let me know, anytime.
I'll make it happen too, right away.
All right. Stay. Try to stay like this. Stay!
Oh, no! You need to use your muscles.
You were doing great.
Okay. When your head hurts,
pull out your phone and press one.
Here, try.
Press it.
- Press one. - Yes, that's it.
You make all this fuss every time you go away for work.
How much longer will you keep this up?
I made side dishes and put them in the fridge for you,
so don't forget to eat them.
I asked the caregiver to stay with you until late,
so have dinner with the caregiver. Okay?
Hold on. How much do I owe the caregiver, then?
Two days and...
Four hours, so...
Stop calling the caregiver here.
I can manage alone.
You're at it again.
What will you do if you faint again when you're alone?
Anyway, I have to go.
When I call you, please pick up right away.
Goodness, you're nagging me again.
Just go. Leave me alone.
Bye.
What's wrong? What is it?
Goodness. What?
I almost tripped. That's all.
Is that all you're taking for your two-day trip?
This is enough. What more do I need?
You don't need to come out. I'll see myself out.
- Don't come out. Just stay here. - Okay.
- Bye! - Bye.
Focus.
Yoon Min Ju, focus.
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
Hey, you're acting so strange these days. Do you know that?
No. Of course, that can't be.
Well, that's just how I am.
When I sense someone's overwhelming emotions,
I get so immersed that I almost feel like...
they're my own emotions and I get confused.
So that said, I will check today and make sure that is the case.
Yes.
See you later.
Does my outfit look lame?
Do I look okay?
I should've gotten a haircut.
What are you doing now?
Mr. Yoon!
My gosh.
Did you look up some restaurants for the evening?
Yes.
There's this amazing place.
Have you been keeping well?
Yes.
We'll have lunch here and go together.
Okay, sounds good.
What's with you?
- Guys, we will... - Look at the sea!
- Oh, my. - Wait...
He's acting like he owns the ocean or something.
- Our itinerary... - Goodness.
I don't like the sea.
Do you like the sea?
I don't like looking at it while working.
We're on a tight schedule today.
This won't be easy.
Beom! Hey!
Look, the sea!
No, I mean, Beom!
- Give me a minute, okay? - No, listen!
Help! Someone is drowning!
Can someone help her? Help!
- Oh, no! - What do we do?
- Hey, look! - Someone is drowning.
What do we do?
What's going on?
Help! Over here!
What zoomed by just now?
- Should we call 911? - What should we do?
Oh, no.
Someone is drowning!
What do we do?
- My gosh. - What?
I knew it. Way to go, Yong Ju!
Oh, my. Well done!
- They saved her. - Amazing.
Are you all right? Can you hear me?
- Beom, call 911. - Okay, 911.
Please...
Please.
Are you all right?
Thank goodness!
They saved her life.
Oh, thank you.
- Are you all right? - Yes, of course.
My goodness.
Hold on.
All right, here.
- No, it's okay. - It's fine. Keep it on.
- Go. Let's go. - Thank you.
What about me?
No one will help me up?
Here, get up.
No! I mean, how come no one will help me up?
My gosh. Are you smitten?
- You are smitten. - What are you saying?
Look at you, you're smitten with me
What's with all the scars on your back?
I'm a man with many secrets.
I'll make a special exception for you and let you in on one of them.
In ten seconds.
Seriously, what's with him?
What?
So, you were both in the special forces?
I was worried you'd find me irresistible, so I kept it a secret.
Goodness.
I didn't say anything.
Mr. Yoon told us to wait here. Where did he go?
Oh, my.
I know that suitcase. The magic suitcase.
What's he doing?
Here, some toiletries. And use this towel.
Thank you.
What about me?
Where's mine?
Wear this.
How could you jump into the sea without a second's hesitation?
We didn't have time to think.
The body reacts automatically.
Gosh, I hate the sea.
If you go into the water in winter...
Gosh, I'm still traumatized.
Hey, isn't it better than the intense one-week training?
That's the word I fear the most. Can you please not mention it?
Okay?
We'll wash up quickly and come back.
Okay.
You were pretty good out there when you hadn't eaten anything.
You know I'm a good swimmer.
Why did you take off your shirt?
Why not?
My gosh.
How can anyone like that exist?
No way. Do I...
Am I the only one seeing a halo around her?
Him too?
Wait.
- How could he just jump in? - Her too?
- My gosh. My heart is pounding. - What...
- Why him? - My boss was in the special forces?
Is it now? Is it the time to hand in my notice?
How am I going to check with them here?
My gosh. Look at this place.
How much volume do you think it can hold?
The volume must be at least 3,000 to 4,000L.
Calling it tasty doesn't cut it.
Hey, your eyes are unfocused.
When you get tired, the first thing...
I guess I got too excited.
They're totally out of focus. I'm certain.
Mr. Yoon. They are...
- Hey. - Wait.
You startled me.
You can't hide in here and drink.
I'm not hiding.
I'm drinking out in the open.
Well, do you want a glass?
This beer...
It's totally my kind of beer.
I'm totally hooked.
You get hooked on beer so easily.
My gosh. You're so clueless.
Go and get some fresh air.
You see, it's so easy to fall for something.
It only takes three seconds. How could you not know?
Besides, those three seconds aren't ordinary.
There's a slow-motion effect on that person's face.
The objects around that person become so quiet.
It gets dead quiet as if they stopped moving.
Then there's a glow behind that person's head.
Ta-da! She starts glowing all of a sudden.
Then it starts. One, two, three.
Only a fool wouldn't know what that means.
A fool?
Well, there are different types of falling for someone.
You have to question if it's a genuine concern...
or if it's because she saved someone's life and so on.
So it could be a temporary feeling from seeing a humanitarian act.
That might be why my heart might be feeling full.
It could be confusing.
Besides, how am I supposed to distinguish...
when a storm of feelings overwhelms me?
My gosh. Mr. Yoon.
You finally spoke to me without honorifics.
- My gosh. - You started to like me, right?
- Goodness. That's not true. - Right?
Come on.
That's not a bad idea.
Then we'll have to listen to other people's opinions.
How come we're the only ones working?
Thank you for your hard work today.
Our lodging is pretty close. Let's get going.
All right. Good work, everyone.
- Good work. - Good work.
- Oh, my. - Goodness.
Yong Ju. This used to be our turf. Right?
This brings back old memories.
By the way,
the atmosphere feels a bit off.
What's this?
What is this?
None of our promotional stuff is properly managed.
They're talking about closing down the branch.
Who would manage them?
But still... This is too much.
What do we do?
I think she's angry.
Come on out!
- What? What do you want? - You!
That's enough, Baekmok.
You know that clearing off the shelf isn't cool.
Listen. I'm buying your company's beer...
when no one wants to drink it.
You should thank me and bow to me.
I heard you guys were closing down.
- So what are you going to do? - Mr. Park?
Mad Dog Yong Ju?
Ms. Chae.
What brings you here?
Let's catch up later.
How dare they clear off the shelf in our turf?
"Clear off the shelf?" What do you mean?
I'll tell you.
- Sir! Three more bottles of Likey. - Yes.
Here you go. Three more bottles of Likey.
- Enjoy. - Thanks.
Nice.
- I'm getting tipsy. Let's go. - Yes.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
It's a method of buying all of their competitor's beer.
It may look like they're increasing their competitor's sales.
Four servings of pork belly...
- But if this continues... - and Likey, please.
Well, we ran out of Likey.
We have Tenns. Why don't you drink that instead?
Come on. They're always out of Likey.
Which company manufactures Likey? This isn't cool.
- Let's drink Tenns. It's better - Give us Tenns then.
- I'll give you Tenns. - Okay.
- Hold on. I'll clear the table. - Okay.
Likey will start to be recognized by consumers as a beer...
that no restaurants carry.
Once they're forgotten by consumers,
the sales will go down.
In the end, the company will stop manufacturing the product.
Beom and I will stay here and take care of this mess.
You can go ahead first.
You said I would take action if a team effort was needed.
I think you need a team effort now.
Gosh, if they stop selling Likey,
it would make our job in the Planning Team harder.
Everyone knows I'm not that devoted to the company,
but I can't let our competitor win.
Then what should we do, Ms. Chae?
Then let's start catching these cheaters.
(Catch the cheaters)
(Handing off)
(Bang!)
(You're all dead meat.)
(Legendary Lady in Black)
Why did you break this precious bottle?
(Fizzing)
Clean this up and come out.
Give us a bottle of Likey.
(Come on, put it in now.)
(Reaching)
- What are you doing? - What's your problem?
(Smirking)
(Who are you?)
(Scowling)
(A lunatic with clear eyes)
(Roaring)
(Why do I feel like we're doomed?)
Baekmok.
Must you play dirty like this?
Are you guys thugs?
Our team managers settled...
that we wouldn't try to clear off each other's shelves.
Come on. What are you talking about?
I heard that your team manager abandoned you and went to Seoul.
Right?
Am I wrong?
Ms. Chae.
Are you going to keep holding that?
Go ahead.
I didn't abandon them.
You have to get your facts straight.
I wasn't going to ask again.
Where's your team manager?
My gosh, Ms. Chae.
I heard you went to Seoul. What brings you here?
Goodness. My guys got greedy again.
What do your juniors know?
I bet they were just following orders.
Clearing off someone else's shelf was the worst sales method.
So I suggested we should never do it...
or even teach our juniors about it. Didn't I tell you that?
Yes, I know that.
It wasn't allowed anymore because you threw a huge fit about it.
Don't be so mad.
What do you want me to do then?
A proper apology...
and an even more proper way of taking responsibility.
Fine. I'll take responsibility for this.
I'll gather up my juniors and discipline them properly.
You jerks. I told you not to do it.
No.
You should personally take responsibility.
Don't you get paid the big bucks because you're supposed...
to take responsibility for your team's mistakes?
My goodness.
- I can get my part-timer to do it. - Gosh, no.
(Today's Pub)
Goodness.
- I'm sorry. - I'm sorry.
Where are the other employees?
Why didn't you tell me things were this bad down here?
How could I?
We already feel so awful that we burdened you...
to fix this problem alone just to save our branch.
I tried my best to fill in your shoes.
But it didn't go so well.
I'm sorry that you had to see this.
Why are you sorry?
I'm sorry that I didn't know things were this bad here.
My gosh, Ms. Chae. Why would you say that?
We're going to do our best to hang in there.
So come back to us.
I'll do whatever it takes...
to save our branch.
So please just hang in there for six months.
Seriously? How can she be so cool time after another?
I'll give out the key cards.
You guys go ahead. I'll go inside after a call.
Mr. Park. Did you get home safely?
No. I felt bad that we couldn't have a meal with you after all that.
Yes. I'll do everything to save our branch.
So please give me a bit more time. Hang in there a little longer.
Yes. Okay.
Hey, Grandma. Did you eat?
Liar.
I bet you didn't eat again because it was a hassle.
Did you exercise?
Come on. You have to move around a lot.
So you can...
Hello? Hey.
Did she just hang up on me?
Come on.
Do you want me to put a Band-Aid on you?
I'd need one if I got hurt.
Seriously?
Right here. Your fingers got cuts.
Gosh, this is...
- Give me your hand. - What...
Did you also get this Band-Aid from your magic bag?
There are more cuts all over your hand.
Those aren't even cuts. They're just some scratches.
I can't even feel pain from them.
What?
But I can.
The first things I notice...
are the small wounds...
you don't even remember.
So...
I don't want you to get hurt.
Even if it's just a tiny scratch.
I won't be okay with that.
Why not?
I...
Well...
All done. You're good now.
- I see. So... - Here.
Thank you.
This is my feeling. This feeling is mine.
- My gosh. - What's wrong?
It's nothing.
- Are you okay, Mr. Yoon? - Don't come near me.
- Wait. No! - I told you not to come near me.
(Brewing Love)
We're so in trouble.
I'll give you three months to launch the new product.
- Pardon? - What do you mean?
Tell him to focus only on our product!
Don't belittle his business like that.
You're making a mistake now.
- What do you think? - They're pretty good.
I agree.
Ms. Beautiful Bang.
Why are you getting nervous?
I don't hold back when I'm certain about something.
I certainly like you.