King Yan has a purpose
Princess Helian of Yanbei was born in Shushun
Diligent and pliable
From now on, she will be canonized as Queen of Yanbei
Shirakawa Minister Hawthorne
Loyalty and bravery from generation to generation
His daughter, Shirakawa, has a gentle nature.
Have both ability and political integrity
From now on, she will be named the side princess.
Make the eldest daughter of Parler the concubine
Granted to the three cities of Manghe, Shazhou, Linchuan
as a fief
Thank you, Your Majesty
Achu
I will definitely marry you and be the Queen of Yanbei
The horse that takes you back to the mountains
Achu
Helian
Thank you for your willingness to help me
Your Majesty
Since I was a child, I have longed for the day
Can become the princess of Yanbei
because of this
It will bring glory to Helianbu
Then I won’t let my brother bully me anymore
It can also prevent Helian’s tribe from being humiliated.
So today
It’s the day when my concubine’s wish comes true
I am very happy
tomorrow
The troops of Parler and Shirakawabe
Will arrive in Yandu
three days later
The lone general sets out to conquer the Western Alliance
Fight against Yong's army
The king said
I hope that I can become an ally of the king
Become a useful person to Yanbei
Did my concubine do it?
Did it
Your Majesty
All 10,000 troops from the Shirakawa tribe were summoned
All nine thousand soldiers and horses of the Parle tribe have been summoned
Helian's six thousand troops have all been summoned
Black Hawk Army: Fifteen thousand men
Yanbei army has 12,000 troops
A total of fifty-two thousand soldiers and horses
All gathered outside the city
Waiting for the king’s edict
Your Majesty
Please bring this sword with you to the battle
Use this sword to protect Yan Bei
This is General Cheng’s wish
General Cheng will also
Bring the king back safely
I promise you
Will take Cheng Yuan to protect Yan Bei
Return safely
Go on an expedition
promise
nononono
Chu Qiao, the daughter of Dayong
Carrying the Jade Seal of the Western Alliance
Now I surrender to Dayong
Never break a promise
Someone coming
Chu Qiao is a witch
Angry the Great Yong Ancestor
Cause fire from heaven
take her down
No one is allowed to move
retreat retreat retreat
stand down
Ministers, there is no need to panic
There is no sky fire at all
the thing that caused the image to burn
It's actually flint powder
What is flint powder
Flint powder is a drug that can spontaneously ignite
As long as the sun is strong and the temperature rises
will cause spontaneous combustion
The fire burning on Jiuyou Platform that day
It's the function of flint powder
Zhao Che
Just taking advantage of the Faceless God Society
Using flint powder to fool everyone
Nonsense
The Faceless God Society is the Yong God Sect
How can I allow you to slander me?
You are using the name of the Faceless Gods
to eradicate dissidents
Mu Helie Wei Guang
And the dead General Meng
All because they are not his party members
Only then was he brutally killed
How dare the prince do such a rebellion against Tiangang?
If you don't believe it
Immediately ordered to search the secret passage under the ancestral temple
Mu Shen had already confessed before his death.
He was ordered by Zhao Che to repair the ancestral temple.
In fact, it is in the secret passage
Hidden a large amount of flint powder
Xing Le
I am here
search
yes
Really flint powder
father emperor
This is Chu Qiao's ulterior motive to frame his son.
Mu Shen is dead
How to prove that this flint powder was buried by my son?
father emperor
Chu Qiao, this girl harbors evil intentions
She colluded with Yan Xun
Intention to disrupt the Great Yong Dynasty
Every step she makes is calculated
Father must not fall into her trap
His Majesty
His Royal Highness the Crown Prince
Border emergency report
The armies of Yanbei and Ximeng were divided into several groups.
Coming towards our border in Dayong
This is bad
father emperor
This is exactly the conspiracy between Chu Qiao and Yan Xun
She is here today to slander her son and ministers
Just to drive a wedge between you and me as father and son
Throw Dayong into chaos
Yan Xun took advantage of this opportunity to send troops
It means that I, Dayong, will fall into a situation of being attacked from both sides.
Now Dayong is in turmoil
Current national crisis
Do you really want to believe this witch Chu Qiao?
Still believe it
I, the future heir of Dayong
Someone coming
Capture the witch Chu Qiao
closet large dungeon
Don't move
If he moves again I'll kill him
The witch Chu Qiao teamed up with General Xing Le
Framing the Prince
deceive and listen
His heart can be killed
Kill me on the spot
His Majesty
Zhuge Yue
you
Your Majesty is already in heaven
From now on, the prince will be the new emperor.
Everyone obeys the prince’s orders
The enchantress Chu Qiao joins forces with the traitorous general Xing Le
Regicide and rebellion
Take it all together
open
Who of you dares to act rashly?
缳缳
Let Chu Qiao and General Xing Le leave
Otherwise I will kill you
缳缳
Don't force me
Do I have to say it again?
let them go
get out of the way
缳缳
you go with us
Chu Qiao
Yan Xun and the Western Alliance Army
They're already on their way here
Do you want us to die here together?
General Chu
let's go
Go quickly
缳缳
Why are you forcing me?
you clearly know
you know better than anyone
I have no choice
As long as you are willing to stop
There's still time for everything
If I refuse to stop
you will kill me
Yeah
yes
缳缳
From the day you and I were in the woods of Yanbei
ambushed
Since you accompanied me to Yanxian County
From the day I gathered with my subordinates
I can never go back
No
you can do it
I know
You are not a greedy person
I know you have good intentions
Dayong's wars are raging
Not what you want to see
Zhao Che
You let go of it all
come with me
We brought peace back to Dayong and Yanbei
We can make peace with the war
Just like your father and old King Yan once did
Then
Let's leave together
ok
good
Prince Zhuge Yuejing listened to the order
Immediately surround General Xing Le's Mansion
The whole city captures the witch Chu Qiao
yes
缳缳
You are still too naive
This world is not suitable for you
General Xing
What happened to Yanbei and Ximeng?
My people just came to deliver a message
It is said that Yanbei's army has come from the southwest
Breaking through the border of Dayong
The Yong army was forced to retreat from Ximeng Pass
Went via Yuanjiang River to support the southwest border
Not only that
Bian Tang also sent troops
General Sun Di led 50,000 troops
United Yanbei Western Alliance
March into Dayong together
our people
Are you all ready?
I've gathered them from everywhere
All the trusted soldiers and horses I can muster
One hundred people in total
Gathered at Shilipo outside the city
at your disposal
one hundred people
enough
This belongs to Zhao Che, right?
We met in Baige Town, Yanbei
I didn't know who he was then
After I returned to Yanbei, I met him and was framed.
Chasing and injured
He asked me to send him to meet up with his old troops
but i didn't expect
He took his troops back to Zhenhuang
Just for this day
Sword for tomorrow
It's inconvenient to wear it
Don’t you regret it?
We have already agreed
See you again
Just an opponent
The sword pierced the princess's abdomen
It happened to be pierced
above the fetus in the belly
The princess is alive and well
only
I can't keep the child anymore
His Majesty
Yanbei's army
Already breached our southwest border
Our troops at Ximeng Pass
We have also rushed to the southwest to provide support.
But then
The border defense in the northwest will be weak
If the Western Allies take the opportunity to attack
I'm afraid we'll be caught off guard
What to do
Pass on my order
Immediately send troops to Ximeng Pass to support
His Majesty
Our troops are already insufficient
The remaining people must defend Zhenhuang City
If we deploy troops from Zhenhuang City at this time,
More likely to cause trouble
Yanbei's army
Where did it hit?
We have already reached Lingxian County
After passing the Luanxi River Channel
It's really too late
Imperial brother
There is only one way now
The Quanrong people in the northwest are tall and strong and good at fighting.
Please ask your Majesty to propose a marriage proposal to all the Rong people.
Use me in exchange for soldiers and horses to aid Dayong
In this way
can calm down the crisis on the Dayong border
Get married
princess marriage
Of course, it can be exchanged for military assistance.
But this is really humiliating
Where is Dayong’s face?
Dayong Sheji
at stake
It's face that matters
Is the country, the country, and the country more important?
Dayong since the founding of the People's Republic of China
never
What a precedent for a princess to marry a foreigner?
precedent
Can't we make an exception?
Absolutely no way
Stop fighting
His Majesty
Are you really planning to let Princess Chun'er
Go to Quanrong and get married
What's wrong
Kameng came from Quanrong
She already brought the credentials of the leader of the entire army and his wife
We are willing to help you with one hundred thousand troops
All Rong people are cruel and unkind
murderous
We've been avoiding it all these years
No more contact
Now we have to exchange the princess for soldiers and horses
Not to mention these 100,000 soldiers and horses
Can you obey our orders?
If they take this opportunity to have evil intentions
By then
Let's take precautions again
I'm just afraid it's too late
Zhuge Yue
You don't agree to exchange troops and horses with Quanrong and his relatives?
you disagree
It was because he was worried that Quanrong would misbehave against Dayong.
Still can’t bear to watch the Western Alliance perish
Watching Chu Qiao die
Zhuge Yue
Do you want Chu Qiao and Yan Bei to win?
I still want to go back and continue to be your King of the Western Alliance
I haven't asked you yet
Yesterday’s ancestral temple
You took the initiative to kill the late emperor
What is the intention?
I'm for
Help His Highness out of trouble
If you hadn't taken action yesterday
Chu Qiao has no chance to escape at all
I don't have to be in public
Carrying the charge of patricide and regicide
you do this
Just to help me?
Or to let Chu Qiao go?
Your Highness
The late emperor has learned of your plan
Pretending to trust His Highness is just a temporary measure
If we didn't take action then
With the late emperor’s thoughts and vigilance
Once he walks out of Tianyuan Palace
He will try his best to make a comeback
By then
We want to take action again
it's too late
Zhuge Yue
do you know
The late emperor was able to successfully inherit the throne
Your grandfather Zhuge Muqing was a meritorious minister
But the late emperor treated him
Not as suspicious as Yan Shicheng
Kill them all
That's because of your grandfather
Know your position
Know you
Always you
It's not his business
Just don't interfere
minister
clear
I want you to help me stop Zhao Che together
Completely change Dayong's world
today
I'll just take a look inside this Faceless Temple
who is the winner
Zhao Chuner opened the border
Attracted the entire army to enter the country
I have decided
Go out to fight