[Disclaimer:
All depicted events are fictional
and for entertainment purposes only;
viewer discretion is advised]
What has he done to you?
Can't you just let him go?
I shall never let him go.
This is Charn,
also a junior.
This is Jet,
my best friend.
We've gone through this bamboo grove
over and over.
My duty
is to take care
of the people in this village.
I'll do whatever it takes
to stop being an outsider in your eyes.
The Peace Treaty
[1937]
between Thailand and France
was signed in Tokyo, Japan,
following the Indochina War.
Mother, Father,
I'd like to let you know something.
Khem and I...
We're engaged, Mom!
Sweetie, mind your manners.
There are people watching.
No worries at all.
We'll soon be one family anyway.
The ring Khem has on...
Wat's grandfather used it
to propose to his grandmother
before he left for military service.
And later, his father used it
to propose to me.
So you can be sure that you're destined
to be my daughter-in-law.
Okay, Father.
Didn't take long, did it?
You're already
calling Colonel "Father," sweetie.
I don't mind at all.
We're just as delighted
to have Khemmika join our son's life.
That's right.
You can speak to me casually, okay?
Okay.
- She's so sweet.
- Right.
Chayod,
I'm officially your sister-in-law now.
[December, 1941]
Some desserts, girls.
Those look fantastic.
Look, now that Khem has her own place,
we can have sleepovers more often,
just like when we were in school!
Calm down a bit, Jin.
This is Khem's place, not yours.
And keep that fascinator on.
It's the leader's
latest fashion, you know.
Alright, Miss Chayada.
I apologize for causing you
any displeasure.
You guys really need to
come hang out with me often.
I hope to keep this place cheerful.
- Khem...
- Yes?
Wat's definitely in a hurry.
He's proposed, has a home for you,
and will marry you after you graduate.
Can you believe that?
I'd say it's our friend...
that's in a hurry.
What made you wanna marry so soon?
To be honest,
I just feel like...
I couldn't find...
a better man than Wat in this life.
- Aw!
The Japanese Ambassador to Thailand
has issued an ultimatum
to the government
[Wartime Draft Notice]
that if the leader does not authorize
the Japanese Navy
to traverse Thai territory
by 10 o'clock today, Japan will initiate
an assault on Thailand...
Does Khem know about this yet?
Our parents still don't know.
Only you do.
This is serious, Wat.
Didn't you catch the news?
They're coming in full force.
Military doctors are scarce in Thailand.
I must fulfill my duty.
What about your wedding to Khem?
My biggest concern is her health.
Her heart valve regurgitation
could worsen at any time.
Yod,
you've known her for a long time,
even longer than I have.
Can I leave her in your care?
What do you mean?
I want you to look after her
and keep her company while I'm away.
I'll try to come back as soon as I can.
You don't need to worry.
I've known Khem
even before you met her.
I'll make sure she's happy.
Make sure everything's secured.
Don't worry, Wat.
I'll come by to see Khem all the time
so she never feels alone.
With someone as talkative as Jin around,
she will be too annoyed
to ever feel lonely.
Ouch!
- Da!
- Thanks, Jin, Da.
I'll come back
before she can't handle you.
Right,
make sure Khem eats
and takes her meds on time.
If anything happens to her
while I'm gone,
you'll be in big trouble.
Come on,
is that how a big brother says goodbye
to his little brother?
Take care of her.
You said you wouldn't cry.
I'm just going to work, not to die.
I tried.
But ever since
we've known each other,
I've never had to be away
from you this long.
I'll write to you every day,
so it feels like I'm always with you.
I'll be waiting for you.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
Promise me
you'll take good care of yourself.
I promise.
It's gonna be alright.
How am I supposed to live after this?
Let's go inside.
Dinner is ready, Khem.
Just a moment!
Whoa, Yod.
What a fancy meal.
Is there some special occasion
or something?
Well...
The head of my department is retiring
and wants me to take over the position.
Really?
Congrats.
At such a young age,
you're already holding
such a high position.
I'm happy for you, Mr. Yod.
Why are you on one knee?
Get up.
Marry me, Khem.
Come on,
stop messing around.
Get up now.
Let's just have dinner.
Come on.
I'm being serious, Khem.
Wat asked me to look after you.
It's been over a year,
and he still shows
no sign of coming back.
But you can't marry me
just because you're taking care of me.
It's not right, Yod.
That's not the only reason, Khem.
Can't you really tell
how I feel about you?
Look into my eyes.
Do you really think
I've been good to you
just because I'm Wat's brother?
Stop it, Yod.
Just find someone better than me.
Khem!
There's no one like that.
And nothing will ever change.
This house is still your home.
My parents will still love you.
Please, Khem.
Please marry me.
Stop it, Yod.
I'm sorry,
but my love is for Wat.
Even if he never comes back,
I'll keep waiting for him.
I've loved Khem
long before she even met you.
He doesn't even know who you are.
This will only bring him more pain.
Let him go.
He's not the Khemmika you knew.
You were part of the reason she died.
You chose duty over her.
I'm taking Khem with me.
Forgive me for what I have to do.
- You think you could've set foot in here
- Let me go.
if I hadn't allowed it?
Spying isn't very nice, you know.
We're sorry, Khem.
You didn't have to go that far, Ake.
But Master told us
to keep everyone else out.
What are you doing?
They're Thong and Ake,
my spirit servants.
- Hello, Khem.
Hi.
Go back to sleep.
Hold on, Master.
Do you know that spirit?
It's none of your business.
How is it not?
You literally said,
"He's not the Khemmika you knew."
You talked about me, didn't you?
And who's Khemmika?
Last time, things went wrong
because you stuck your nose
into someone else's mess.
Now, you've screwed things up again.
Just go to bed
and stay out of my business.
Master!
Can't we talk nicely just for once?
You're crossing the line.
I gave in on everything else,
but don't I have the right
to know about this?
Not everything is meant to be known.
What good will it do,
knowing something you can't change?
I'm begging you, Master.
Please tell me the truth.
It might have something to do
with my family's curse.
Please, Master.
Go live your life
while you still can.
And stay out of my business.
We're not that close.
Alright.
But I'd appreciate it if you'd stop
using such improper language with me,
since we're not that close.
Khem...
Argh!
Please wait for me, Khem.
My deepest respects to you, Master.
It's been a while, Auntie.
Thank you so much, Master.
Tonight is the first time
I've felt safe enough
to let Khem rest
without needing to protect him.
Your soul has deteriorated so much.
Should you continue to do this,
you may never find your way
back into reincarnation.
As long as Khem is safe,
that's more than enough for me.
Take some time to recover.
While he's here,
no harm will come to him.
Thank you so much
for always protecting him.
Please excuse us.
Come on, Khem.
The sermon is about to begin.
What? Isn't this Master's bike?
Won't he be mad that we took it?
Whatever. I'll return it after noon.
He won't even notice.
Come on.
Please excuse us.
Sorry.
(Chanting)
Ouch!
Oh, Grandma Si?
Why did you hit me?
Well,
if you hadn't done that,
would you even remember me?
You left and just went silent.
Do I even matter to you?
Aw, Grandma Si.
Of course you do!
I miss you so, so much.
This is Grandma Si,
a respected elder of the village.
Good morning, Grandma Si.
She's cared for Master
since he was little,
as if she were really his grandma.
Grandma,
this is Khem,
my friend.
You really dragged
some serious trouble over here.
Well, I guess.
(Chanting)
- Sadhu.
Your soul is weak,
but your vital force remains intact.
You've grown up well.
If you ever need my help, let me know.
I'll be here to support you.
Thank you so much.
Well,
what an adorable face you have.
If I had a grandchild,
I'd love to introduce you.
Has anyone here caught your eye yet?
That would never come
to my mind, Grandma.
This afternoon, Master will lead
An Invitation to the Devas.
You need to attend.
It will bring you good fortune.
Holy shit!
Sorry.
His bike!
If he doesn't wanna help,
should we leave?
He's pretty late.
Master's here!
Over there. He's coming.
See? He looks so fine.
- He does.
- He's gorgeous.
Jet, come on.
Wearing those sunglasses again?
The ritual is starting soon.
Is he not gonna take them off?
Just look at the girls over there.
Whenever he looks someone in the eye,
young or old ladies,
or even men,
they all fall for him.
That's why he hides behind those shades.
Seriously?
Seriously.
Someone once fainted
just from making eye contact with him.
That's why he wears them.
It's starting now.
Focus and pray.
May all the devas,
Varuna,
Goddess of the Earth,
and the deities full of divine power,
shield and protect
everyone in this village
from all evils and ill omens.
See? That's my master.
This is full of crap.
Hey, be respectful.
He literally summoned the rain.
Not even Doctor Strange
can pull that off.
Hey!
What?
It's not worth it, Jet.
But they're disrespecting Master.
This place is nuts.
That lady acted like she was possessed,
trying to kill her husband.
I'm done with this damn camp.
Not everything you think
needs to be said,
but it's wise to think before you speak.
Master!
Master...
Your bike.
Tell me where you're going.
Where are you guys going next?
Not everything is meant to be known.
Uncle Chai's taking us to go swimming.
Give me your hand.
Don't lose it.
So many damn bugs. Fuck this.
I should've stayed in
and watched something.
- I think it's gonna be...
- Got bug spray on you?
Nope. I only got cigs.
- It looks so nice!
- Want any?
- No.
- Let's get a picture there!
- Wait, hold on.
- Prae...
- Where are you going?
- What the hell?
Come back here.
Alright,
listen up.
Before swimming,
let's pay respect
to the local spirits first.
Just to be safe, okay?
Here.
One for each person.
Make sure everyone gets it.
Here, a lighter, too.
Let's go.
Seriously?
A whole ritual just to swim?
Everyone just blindly believes
this kind of stuff.
No wonder
this fucking country
never moves forward.
You bastards!
Then you need to respect
other cultures, too.
You're not forced to believe it.
Just respect those who do.
It's called multiculturalism.
Ever heard of it?
Cut the "multi" bullshit, nerd.
You've been getting on my nerves.
I'm only holding back
'cause you're Prae's friend.
You don't need to.
Just think about the point I'm making.
- You're not getting it or what?
- Hey!
You're the one not getting it.
All you do is yap all the time.
What the fuck is your problem?
You think you can do anything
just 'cause your dad is some MP?
Get him.
You're the one who brought us here, huh?
We need a word.
Just do it here.
Stay away, Khem.
You're literally asking for it!
Hey!
Why would you get in the way?
You bastards, get this!
Stop!
- Fuck you.
- I told you to stop!
What are you doing, huh?
Go away.
Go swim somewhere else.
Leave!
Just go already.
- Go!
- Fuck off.
I'm coming for you.
You, too, nerd.
I shouldn't have come.
I'm sorry.
Look,
calm down a bit, alright?
Control your temper.
Okay?
Okay.
Let's go, Khem.
Come on.
Khem!
Come on here.
This spot has really cold water.
- Come on.
- Really?
Come here.
It's really cold.
Join us.
You just took the punch yourself.
I didn't ask for your help.
Yes.
I know.
So...
does it hurt?
It doesn't.
The punch wasn't very hard.
Let me see it.
Ouch...
It doesn't hurt, does it?
It doesn't hurt when you don't touch it.
Anyway,
Praemai told me that...
you carried me out of Worn's house?
Obviously.
You're freaking heavy.
My aches still haven't gone away.
Thank you.
Wait.
Today...
For shutting those assholes up...
Thank you.
Sorry? What did you say?
Thanks for that.
What?
What did you say?
I couldn't hear you.
Come here.
Oh...
Thank you, khob khun, kamsahamnida!
Clear enough?
Charn!
Charn,
are you alright?
I'm okay, Khem.
You should go swimming.
Charn, that's Praemai.
I'm right here.
Charn, how shortsighted are you exactly?
Where are my glasses?
Guys, my glasses!
Where are they?
Have you seen my glasses?
I lost them.
How did you lose them?
Look what you did, Jet!
Gosh.
What were you thinking?
I never said I wanted to swim.
I'm drenched now.
I'm gonna get sick again.
Why did you kick me?
My clothes are soaked,
and so is my body.
I'm gonna catch a cold for sure.
Charn,
you want to show off, don't you?
What a great idea.
Yo, give me a light.
Man, I'm so sick of their bullshit.
I'm so freaking done.
I bet this place is cursed or something.
If Te hadn't been so damn clingy
with his girl,
we'd be off enjoying ourselves by now.
I mean, come on.
We came all this way here,
so we gotta have some fun, right?
Have fun? We're in a fucking forest.
Exactly, man.
See that sign over there?
[Keep out]
It used to be a viewpoint.
How about...
we pitch a tent
and do some stargazing tonight?
Yo.
Sounds good?
Yo,
with...
Te is definitely coming.
He never misses it.
Obviously.
Yo, let's do it.
- Go.
- Hell yeah.
I'll go hit him up, too.
How much beer do we have left?
Man, a lot.
I can find more if you want.
Honestly, man,
since that nerd already took one punch,
[Keep out]
I should've thrown in a couple more.
Hell yeah.
He deserved it.
Damn, I wish I were there.
If I were,
- I'd have just...
- What?
Te!
Come on, Sod...
- Sod Chaeng!
Nice shot.
Hey!
Bro, we barely started.
Going to sleep already?
Sleep my ass. I'm taking a piss.
Wait, I'm coming with you.
Yeah, fine.
Babe,
I'll be right back.
Won't take long.
Okay.
Babe!
Wait up! I'm taking a piss, too.
- What's wrong with you?
- Keep me company.
What's your problem?
You sure this is the right way?
What the hell? You're drunk already?
What the fuck?
I'm not drunk, dumbass.
I just gotta pee like you.
Yo, Phu,
you're aiming way too close.
Check this out.
I've got a long-range rifle, baby!
What's the point, man?
Bro, you sure that is long?
It can even reach the ground.
Mine's not long...
Come on, dude.
But it's right on the spot.
Te!
Te, are you done?
Hey, are you done yet?
Te!
Te...
Korn...
Phu!
This is not funny.
[Keep out]
Help!
- Prae?
- Help me!
- Help me.
- Prae,
- Please help me.
- What happened?
Help me.
Prae...
Everyone,
something's wrong with Prae.
Uncle Chai, Auntie Kaew!
Prae!
- Prae!
- Why is she like this?
- Prae...
- Where are the others, Prae?
What's going on, Mint?
Where has she been?
Uh...
She went camping
with her boyfriend at the viewpoint.
I'm sorry. It's my fault.
- Prae...
- I'm sorry.
- Prae!
- I'm sorry. It's my fault.
- Listen to me, Prae.
Calm down.
Calm yourself down and listen to me.
Take your time,
and tell us what happened.
- Prae!
- Prae...
Prae!
Charn, take her to Master.
Hurry up!
Praemai!
Praemai...
Prae...
She's the only one who got out,
but as we can see,
she's not in the same state.
Aw, sweetie.
Praemai...
Praemai!
At least they let her out.
Where is she? Let me see her.
Mother Si!
Let me get through.
Let me check her first.
What happened to her?
Aw, dear.
Oh, dear.
Her vital force has left her body!
- Really?
- Yeah!
Master,
will they allow us back up there?
We need to get her vital force back.
If we don't, things will only get worse.
Jet,
you're going with Uncle Chai
and helping him
gather the entire village.
Okay.
Split them into two groups.
All able-bodied men,
send them to find those three guys.
Everyone else,
go help Grandma Si
draw back the vital force.
Who's her best friend?
They need to come with me.
You should go, Mint.
I'll take care of her here.
Let's go. We should hurry.
- Let's go.
- Be careful.
- Prae...
- Go.
Come on, Jet.
Khem.
You stay.
Praemai...
Let's go.
Praemai, can you hear me?
- Sweetie...
- We need only men born on Saturday,
Tuesday,
Wednesday,
and Sunday.
Just those four days.
We'll form search groups
to look for Te, Korn, and Phu.
They must be found before noon.
Wait, Jet.
I mean, why before noon?
If they're not found by noon,
we're looking for bodies.
Te!
- Where are you? Can you hear us?
- Te!
- Korn, where are you?
- Phu.
- Where are you?
- Te!
- If you can hear me, make a noise!
- Make sure you look everywhere.
- Korn!
- Don't miss any spot.
- Got it.
- Okay.
- Te, Korn...
- Phu!
Mint,
did you bring what I told you to get?
Yes, I did.
Here you go, Grandma.
These are what Prae uses a lot.
Let this ritual succeed and be blessed.
- Sadhu.
- Phu, Korn!
- Te, can you hear me?
Guys!
- Can you hear us?
- Where are you?
- Answer us if you can hear this.
- Korn!
- Can you hear us?
- Can you hear us, guys?
- Where are you?
- Praemai, come with us.
- Come back.
- May your vital force come to us.
- Prae...
- Come with us.
- Come back, Praemai.
- Come back to me.
- Come on now.
- Come home with us.
- Praemai...
- I'll take you back to your parents.
- Come on, Praemai. Come back.
- Praemai...
- Come to us.
- May your vital force come to us.
- Please come back here.
Praemai, come home with us.
We'll go together.
Praemai...
- Let's go home.
- It's here!
- Really? Is it here?
- Yes!
Her vital force is here.
- We got it.
- Is Prae with us now?
- Yes, she's with us.
- Let's go home.
- Let's head back home.
- Okay, let's go.
- Let's go.
- Come on, let's head home.
Here we go.
Let's go home, okay?
Praemai's vital force is back.
Now, may it find its way
back into her body.
Let's tie her wrist.
Tying her wrist...
with the holy thread.
Praemai's vital force is back.
May it find its way back into her body.
(Chanting)
May her vital force come back,
and may it bring relief
and healing to her.
Sadhu.
Come, tie her wrist.
Kaew, you do it, too, okay?
Let's call her vital force together.
Alright, I'll tie her wrist.
Mother Si...
It's back in her body. See?
- Really?
- Yes!
Praemai...
You're okay now, sweetie.
She is healed
and perfectly alright now.
Master!
How's everything, Jet?
Go and stay at Auntie Kaew's place.
Come on, guys.
Let's take her there to get some rest.
Come on.
- Let's go to my place.
- Go.
Be careful.
I'll take this.
You should go with them.
Let's go.
Why did you tell Khem
to go stay somewhere else?
I'll project my spirit somewhere else.
And you can't watch over him tonight.
It's safer for him
to stay with many people,
so they can keep an eye on him.
Are you...
leaving your body? Where to?
And...
Go take a look around.
Let me know right away
if anything's not right.
Okay.
Khem...
Khem!
Are you okay?
Well,
I just feel like
I can't help them at all.
Please don't think that way, Khem.
I just thought...
if I could be a bit more helpful,
it might be better.
I think you've got
the wrong perspective.
It was you, wasn't it,
who kept holding Praemai
during her seizures?
It didn't really matter.
It felt like I wasn't helping at all.
But it did matter for Prae.
At least,
you were there
to share some of her pain.
Thanks, Charn.
Whatever we could do,
we've already done it all.
Let's go to bed now.
Have you found them?
No, Master.
What about you?
Is he in the cave?
Yes.
But, Master,
he seems quite upset right now.
I need to go anyway.
He's the only one who can help me.
Dear guardian of this land,
forest, and mountain,
if I have committed
any offense against you
whether by action, speech, or thought,
intentional or unintentional,
I humbly ask for your forgiveness.
I have a troubled mind
and humbly ask for your mercy and help.
If my merit is insufficient,
I shall respectfully take my leave.
Had your merit not been sufficient,
you wouldn't have made it here.
You may rise.
You came because of
those three boys, didn't you?
We're in trouble, Master.
Khem's disappeared.
Your instincts are strong.
Focus your mind on Khem,
and follow wherever your gut leads you.
I have cherished and protected you
for over 80 years.
How could I let you be taken
by someone else so easily?
Master,
can you please stay with me for now?
At least until I fall asleep.
♫No matter how long time's passed,
you still have me♫
♫Through storms and stars,
together we shall be♫
♫Even if nightmares come,
we shall make them flee♫
♫With our hearts aligned,
we'll win gracefully♫
♫You still have me,
we're destined for eternity♫
♫Through storms and stars,
together we shall be♫
♫Even if nightmares come,
we shall make them flee♫
♫With our hearts aligned,
we'll win triumphantly♫