(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
ALL FIGURES,
INCIDENTS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS,
AND OTHERS ARE FICTITIOUS.
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
WERE FILMED SAFELY
IN ACCORDANCE WITH GUIDELINES.
Where's patient Shin I-rang?
Are you Mr. Shin I-rang's guardian?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
He was already unconscious
when he arrived at the hospital.
No.
I should've been there.
I should've been with him.
What…
Am I…
Am I dead?
dead for real?
Mister.
Who are you?
Wait.
Who am I?
Mister.
You have to go there.
Where is there?
Mother, he's here!
I-rang.
I-rang, Mom is here.
Doctor, what happened to my son?
Don't go out there.
Mister, don't go.
What happened to my son, doctor?
Please. Please help him, doctor.
We've already tried CPR several times.
-Doctor.
-Please. I beg you.
You said…
you'd find my mom for me.
Patient Shin I-rang is pronounced dead
at 8:43 p.m. on August 16…
What… Did you hear that?
-Get the defibrillator.
-Yes, doctor.
-What's going on…
-Please move aside.
-No.
-Folks, please move back.
-But…
-Come this way.
I-rang.
Clear!
Charge to 200 joules.
EKG has returned!
-I-rang, can you see me?
-I-rang.
I-rang, can you hear me?
Attorney Shin…
…Reporter Park Seong-chan.
We will bring you more updates on Cho
as the story develops.
Next, let's meet the hero
who saved the kidnapped child, Kwon.
-Reporter Kim Bo-ra?
-There it comes.
I'm currently at the hospital
where Mr. Shin I-rang is hospitalized.
Mr. Shin got shot in the process
of saving the child,
-but he's undergoing a smooth recovery--
-He's coming out.
-Mr. Shin is coming out now.
-Mr. Shin!
A word, please!
Lightning…
Uncle.
You're so cool. You're the best!
You think?
If you say so, I guess I really am cool.
What a relief.
-Ouch!
-Oh, no.
-Are you okay?
-Careful.
-That fool.
-Get some rest, okay?
-Thanks, everyone.
-See you later.
Bong-su, power!
I-rang, power!
-Let's go.
-Gosh, you've been through a lot.
Have some time alone. We'll be back soon.
Attorney Han cried?
She cried her eyes out,
saying she should've been with you.
She did?
She cried her eyes out?
What's so funny?
Oh, Attorney Han.
Are you okay?
Why can't you be more careful?
You got shot.
I'm okay. I mean it.
Mister, can I go to your house?
Do that. It must be boring to stay here.
Go have fun with Da-bong and her grandma.
Okay!
Yay!
Si-ho left.
You must've been shocked because of me.
I was shocked and upset.
You should've gone with Bong-su or me
to handle such a thing.
It was dangerous to go there alone.
You're right.
I guess I was in a rush.
I wanted to find out who Si-ho was
as soon as possible.
Oh, right.
The day you went to find Si-ho,
his dad visited the office
for a divorce consultation.
Divorce?
They've been living apart
since Si-ho went missing.
Both of them are struggling with regret
and a sense of guilt.
They don't even know if he's alive.
I bet it's worse for them.
You're right.
A slim chance
can cause more pain sometimes.
Anyway, how's the investigation going?
It's taking place under detention
thanks to Ye-jun
who was rescued from the scene.
But Cho Chi-yeong is pleading the Fifth
regarding Si-ho
who went missing more than a year ago.
Ye-jun and Si-ho are around the same age
and were both in yellow rain boots.
Nevertheless, no evidence proves
that he kidnapped Si-ho.
What are you doing?
A sentence for abduction, enticement,
and confinement of a minor
is only a max sentence
of ten years in prison.
It'll be a much lighter sentence
in reality.
I can't let that happen.
I'll help you like this.
-Oh, gosh.
-I-rang was shot!
Sorry. My bad.
At least, let's walk in step.
Left foot, left foot.
What for? We're not soldiers.
Oops!
Oh, come on!
Are you okay?
"I slept like a baby."
"Did you sleep well?"
I wish I could play too.
"Honey, did you have a good night?"
"Of course."
"We should have breakfast."
"Let's have breakfast and…"
"Honey, do you have an acting gig today?"
"Yes, I play a doctor role today."
"My gosh, that's amazing."
Dad, can you not go to work?
I want to spend time with you.
"Should we go to the amusement park
with Da-bong this weekend?"
"Nice idea. That's my wife, Sa-rang."
I want to go camping.
"Good luck with the shoot."
"Okay, thanks."
Excuse me.
I'm here about the boy named Yoon Si-ho.
Are you Si-ho's father?
Do you know my son?
I heard from the police.
That he went missing a year ago.
You saved the boy named Ye-jun.
Do you
happen to know where Si-ho is?
No.
I'm sorry.
I see.
Hello?
He doesn't know.
Honey? Are you okay?
Do you want me to go there now?
Okay, I'm sorry. I just…
Our Si-ho will be okay.
Let's wait a little more, okay?
He said he'd let you in the police car?
Yes.
He was a stranger.
Weren't you scared of him?
He wasn't a stranger.
That detective gave
a safety lesson at school.
In that case,
it must've been easier to trust him.
And he was really good to me.
He showed me his pistol
and played with me.
But when I wanted to go home at night,
he stopped me, saying he'd take me
somewhere fun the next day.
I still said I was going to go home,
and he got angry.
The truth is,
I had a headache since that morning.
It got worse as he yelled at me.
Did it hurt badly?
Yes.
So,
I took medicine and kept sleeping.
When I opened my eyes,
I was in your office.
I see.
I miss my parents.
Can't I go see them?
Si-ho.
I'm afraid you can't see your mom and dad
right now.
Why?
Your parents are…
a little sick.
Really? How sick are they?
They're heartsick.
Why?
Let's say
your friend tripped next to you.
How would you feel?
I'd feel sorry
for not stopping him from tripping.
Right.
You'd feel sorry
even if it weren't your fault.
Your parents are feeling the same way.
They couldn't protect you,
their precious son.
Thinking of what they could've done,
they constantly blame themselves.
That's why
it makes them more and more heartsick.
That's not good.
How do you treat being heartsick?
I want my mom and dad to be happy again.
If they know that you're this okay,
it might ease their pain a little.
But they don't know.
They can't see
or hear me.
Don't worry.
I'll help you.
Okay.
Then…
Whoosh.
Let's go.
Give me your briefcase.
Wait.
Oh, my! I'm sorry.
-Knock it off!
-Okay, my bad.
Hello. You came early.
-How are you feeling?
-I'm okay. Let's get started.
Cho Chi-yeong divorced his wife
after she had an affair
and raised his son, Gyeong-seo, alone.
Two years ago
while Cho went to the bathroom,
his unattended son climbed on a desk, fell
through a torn window screen, and died.
His ex-wife reported him
for child neglect,
but the court ruled that he didn't neglect
his parental duties despite his busy work.
I don't see anything unusual so far.
I wonder why he kidnapped children
and murdered one after losing his own son.
We're back to square one.
What do we have about the case?
The police took these photos at the scene
when his son fell to his death.
His son must've loved pizza.
He diligently collected coupons
and even drew some.
He drew fake coupons?
It could be more like
he wanted to win a prize.
What were the prizes?
-That's it!
-What?
A six-year-old boy collected coupons
over a kimchi refrigerator?
No way.
Hold on. Let's see. When was it?
Three or so years ago,
a neighborhood supermarket hosted a prize
festival to celebrate their grand opening.
Da-bong won a television, the first prize.
But she cried.
Why?
Because she wanted the fifth prize,
a cartoon-character backpack.
How children think is totally different
from how adults think.
Then, from a child's perspective…
What about this one?
I think that's it.
Children love camping.
I want to go camping.
He stopped me, saying he'd take me
somewhere fun the next day.
Cho Chi-yeong told Si-ho
that they'd go somewhere fun the next day.
It may have been a camping site.
Si-ho said that Cho Chi-yeong
gave a safety lesson at school.
What if he was seeking a target
at the time?
And what if he wanted
to give himself a chance?
To himself who couldn't protect his son?
In fact, he called Ye-jun his son.
And he fed Ye-jun pizza,
which was his son's favorite.
So, in short,
he didn't look for a target of revenge,
but a chance for himself to be a good dad?
He's a total lunatic.
If he was going to take Si-ho
to the camping site
his son wanted to go to,
he may have buried Si-ho there.
It's plausible, but it's a little…
Uncertain. I know.
So, I'm going to ask him in person.
I doubt he'll agree to meet you.
He won't talk to me,
but he'll talk to Si-ho.
CHO CHI-YEONG
TO: SEOUL CORRECTIONAL FACILITY
FROM: SECOND FLOOR OF
PITTER-PATTER BUTCHER-STYLE BBQ
To Mr. Detective.
Mister, this is Si-ho.
The Yoon Si-ho that you said
had a nice, round head.
We played word chain
and cops and robbers together.
You showed me your pistol too.
Do you remember?
Cho Chi-yeong may stay silent
until the end.
Can you look for Si-ho's body
at the camping site with Bong-su?
Okay.
GOOD SLEEPING CAMPING SITE
We have only one person from the police?
I barely got my day off to come here too.
We still lack evidence.
Even so, why can't they
just believe what the hero says?
My point exactly.
This place is so big.
Will we be able to find him?
We must.
Everything is possible with God.
There are just four of us,
but he will give us the ability
of 40 or even 400.
Let me give you some precautions first.
Plant growth is different
at the burial site due to organic matter.
So pay attention to areas
with uneven growth or unusual coloring.
And I sent each of you
a metal-detecting app.
Hold your phones close to the ground
and they react to things
like buttons, keys, or zippers.
Attorney Han and Father,
please search that side.
You and I will search this side.
Okay.
Are you a police officer?
Shall we?
I'll do my best.
It's you again.
Who are you, really?
Who are you
to send me such a letter?
Si-ho is…
here right now.
What are you saying?
Otherwise, how else would I know
what happened between you and him?
Stop lying.
Stop messing around.
You kidnapped Ye-jun and Si-ho.
And you caused Si-ho to die.
Anyone can see
you're a despicable criminal.
But I think…
you as Gyeong-seo's dad…
would be a little different.
Please, Gyeong-seo's father.
Think of Si-ho's parents.
Unable to find their beloved son's body,
they're living in utter despair.
You know how it feels to lose a child.
Shut your trap.
You must've wanted to be forgiven.
After Gyeong-seo died,
you must've had so many regrets.
So you tried to prove that you weren't
a bad dad and ease your guilt
by doing what you couldn't do
to your son with those children.
-Shut up!
-For such an absurd reason,
you gave Ye-jun an unforgettable trauma,
let Si-ho die,
and devastated their parents.
What do you know?
I know…
that parents mean the world…
to their children.
You robbed those children of everything.
I don't know who Si-ho is.
And if his parents really loved him,
they wouldn't have left him alone.
Such parents…
don't deserve to be parents.
Don't say that about my mom and dad.
My parents
loved me.
They did everything for me.
To buy me delicious food,
my mom saved on buying make up.
My dad worked until late at night
to buy me a pair of cute rain boots.
They're the one and only parents I have.
I love them so much.
I wouldn't trade them
for a hundred pizzas.
even for an amusement park.
Mister…
why are you trying to trade him?
I'm not your son.
He must've loved you so much too.
If I were your son,
I'd be sad.
Mister.
Why are you crying?
I…
I wanted to do my best for Gyeong-seo.
It felt like my fault
that he was separated from his mom
and that he was left alone.
If I had another chance…
I thought I'd do better
if I had another chance.
I didn't know you were that sick.
I thought you simply had a fever.
You were dead
when I came back the next morning.
I was utterly shocked.
I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry.
Truly.
If you're truly sorry,
bring me back to my parents.
Where am I right now?
-Check here.
-Yes, sir.
On the right.
What?
Si-ho…
Are you sure about this?
They both said they were ready.
What about Si-ho, though?
He's going to see his parents
on awkward terms.
Still, they're his parents.
Shall we go?
Yes.
Si-ho.
Mommy's late.
I'm sorry.
YOON SI-HO
Have you been well, sweetheart?
Si-ho.
Your mommy's here.
You missed her, didn't you?
Oh, wow.
There are so many flowers.
You must've had a lot of friends come by.
Si-ho…
Mom!
Dad!
-Si-ho.
-Si-ho!
Si-ho!
Si-ho, come here.
Our dear Si-ho's here.
That was a low jump.
It's time for me to go, isn't it?
How did you know?
Your sad face tells me so.
But mister,
don't be sad.
I'm so happy that I got to see
my parents get along.
So
smile, mister.
Thank you so much.
You're a hundred, a thousand times
cooler than Lightning Man.
I am?
What's so cool about me?
You're kind.
You're handsome.
And you're super weak.
What's that supposed to mean?
It's really hard for someone weak
to save others, you know.
Then,
does that mean
I pulled off something that difficult?
Yes.
You're so cool that your dad must
also be proud of you up above.
Thanks, Lightning Man.
You were so cool too.
Si-ho,
I prepared a farewell gift for you.
What?
One, two,
three!
-Lightning power.
Lightning power!
-Lightning power!
Goodbye, Si-ho.
I-rang, I'm so glad you recovered quickly.
I-rang has great stamina. That's for sure.
-I know. Gosh.
-Bong-su.
-Thank you for the meal.
-Help yourself.
Why don't we have a toast
to I-rang's good health?
-Okay. Cheers!
-All right.
-You too, Da-bong. Cheers!
-Cheers!
-What?
-Eat as you drink.
Okay.
Don't just smile, eat.
Why are you only giving I-rang
special treatment?
Well, I…
He's my only colleague.
I should look out for him.
You're hurting my feelings.
I did the best I could to help you too.
You didn't just help us.
You're an irreplaceable asset to us.
You're like a paralegal, so to speak.
-Oh, my.
-Right?
Yes, our paralegal.
An actual paralegal, not a role?
Yes, of course.
Mr. Paralegal, let me pour you some.
Goodness.
Cheers to the first paralegal
of Shin I-rang Law Office!
-Cheers!
I'm a paralegal!
Eat up.
ATTORNEY SHIN
INITIATES A LAWSUIT
ON BEHALF OF
VICTIM YOON SI-HO'S FAMILY
THE VICTIM'S FATHER,
YOON JAE-UK,
FILED A SUIT AGAINST
CHO CHI-YEONG
AND RETAINED
ATTORNEY SHIN I-RANG
AS A LEGAL REPRESENTATIVE
PETITION FOR TORT DAMAGES
TAEBAEK
I need to go to him!
Come in.
Mail for you, sir.
What's that?
It's mail from overseas for the Chairman.
Give it to me. I'll hand it to him.
Yes, sir.
It's where Father got operated.
I'll get going now.
-Be careful on your way home.
-Visit us often.
Pretty auntie, goodbye.
Bye.
Mr. Paralegal.
I'll walk her home and come back.
Don't come back.
Take care.
Bye-bye.
Let's go back inside now.
I feel so good.
Our dear paralegal.
That's right.
Do you have anything to say?
Excuse me?
Like what?
Back at Haneul Park and the hospital,
you tried to tell me something.
What are you doing?
Watching out for ghosts.
They always show up
during important moments.
Then, why don't we meet up
somewhere ghosts don't know?
Let's eat something delicious
and say what we have to say.
Do you also have something to tell me?
Of course.
Did I perhaps make a mistake?
It's not like that.
Wait.
Maybe it is.
Is it?
What did I do wrong this time?
Attorney Han,
it's better to rip the band-aid off.
Can't you just tell me now?
I don't want to.
Come on. Just tell me.
Geez.
I'm late but happy birthday.
I wanted to celebrate it for you
although it already passed.
I finally get to give these to her.
Attorney Shin I-rang?
Hello, Attorney Han Na-hyun.
Are you working outside?
Yes.
I'm on my way to get a signature
on the notice of retention from Mr. Yoon.
What are you up to?
CEO Kang of Ideal Shoes has asked me
to go over a contract.
He's signing a new contract
with an online platform.
I see. That's good.
You still remember our plans
later today, right?
I texted you the address.
Yes, I got it.
I'll be there by 8:00 p.m.
Okay, see you later.
You seem to be in a happy mood.
YOON SI-HO
Attorney Shin must be here.
YANG DO-KYUNG
Come in.
Are you busy?
-No, Father.
-Let's eat together if you haven't yet.
The number cannot be reached.
You'll be directed to voicemail after…
That's strange.
Did he go somewhere?
You were inside.
I was worried
because you didn't answer your phone.
I'm dropping the case.
Leave.
-Excuse me?
-I don't want to talk to you.
So, leave.
Wait.
Mr. Yoon, did something happen?
I'm really grateful
to you for finding Si-ho.
And I know that you've done nothing wrong.
But the thought of your father
makes me shudder.
Because of Shin Gi-jung, my father…
Please just go.
It's been a long time
since we had a meal together like this.
I know.
When I was healthy, I was busy with work.
And when I had time,
I was sick and away from home.
Now that you're healthy again,
let's do this more often.
Okay.
Don't you have to revisit the hospital
in the States, then?
No, since my treatment is over.
Right.
My illness made me realize
what was most precious.
Money, reputation, status…
None of it matters.
In the end,
family is all you have.
Your grandpa…
was never one to commend me.
He always asked
if it was the best I could do.
And every time,
I answered I'd try harder.
I couldn't be a warm father to you
because that was how I was raised.
But I'm sure about one thing.
I will protect you no matter what.
That's family.
I believe you'll do the same.
Do you trust me?
Yes.
I trust my son.
Don't worry, Father.
I'll protect you.
All right.
Let's eat.
SHIN I-RANG LAW OFFICE
PITTER-PATTER BUTCHER-STYLE BBQ
But the thought of your father
makes me shudder.
Because of Shin Gi-jung, my father…
PROSECUTOR KIM HYEON-U
Hello, Prosecutor Kim.
Attorney Shin, are you free to talk?
This is about Mr. Yoon Jae-uk's case.
I don't think
I can take on that case.
Mr. Yoon is dismissing the lawsuit.
He did? Why?
I'm not so sure.
Could you
tell me what his father's name is?
Just a moment.
His name is Yoon Dae-myeong.
He passed away in 2003.
Why do you ask about him?
There's something I have to find out.
Thank you.
YOON DAE-MYEONG,
SHIN GI-JUNG, 2003
EXCESSIVE PUNISHMENT FOR
CHARGES OF CHILD SEXUAL ABUSE
WARRANT DISMISSED
PROSECUTOR SHIN
SEEKS WARRANT AGAIN
FOR YOON DAE-MYEONG
SEXUAL ASSAULT CASE
YOON DAE-MYEONG'S SUICIDE…
CRITICISM OF UNDUE PROSECUTION…
CORRUPT PROSECUTOR SHIN GI-JUNG
DIES IN A CAR ACCIDENT
It's in.
Okay, good job.
I need to know what's going on
if I'm to protect you, Father.
Why didn't you go home?
Why were you spacing out here?
I want to know the truth,
but I'm clueless
no matter how many articles I read.
What happened
to your father?
What did
my father do?
It's too late to talk about it now.
Both our fathers are
already dead.
Even so,
I want to know.
Actually,
I need to know.
Please tell me.
My father was an educator.
He was Teacher of the Year
as many as 4 times in 25 years.
He was a diligent and respected teacher.
But in the year he became vice-principal,
something happened.
There was group bullying at school.
Come on, get up!
My father imposed the severest penalty
possible on the bully, expulsion.
One more time.
It's a dud.
The bully student's parents
sued my father
for excessive and biased punishment.
But the court dismissed it
on presumption of innocence.
The real problem started from here.
The prosecutor in charge,
Shin Gi-jung, conducted
a fishing expedition
and prosecuted my father
for totally irrelevant charges.
PROSECUTOR SHIN GI-JUNG
Yes.
Let's go with it, then.
He prosecuted him for property speculation
over his capital gains.
For the embezzlement of operation funds
over a missing lunch receipt.
Let's see.
INCHEON DISTRICT COURT
TO YOON DAE-MYEONG
And for sexual harassment over a simple
reminder enforcing the dress code.
INCHEON DISTRICT COURT
TO YOON DAE-MYEONG
Most of the prosecutions were dismissed,
but my father could barely go to work
due to the legal battles.
And to pay for the growing legal fees,
he even lost the one house he had.
Why to that extent, though?
Did your father…
have something to do
with my father before that?
I was curious too,
but it all made sense when I heard
what my father's attorney said.
He explained that when prosecutors resign,
they are often recruited by law firms
for their ties to the prosecution.
And that the bully student's father was
the head of Korea's top law firm.
Prosecutor Shin Gi-jung
used my father as a sacrificial lamb.
For his own good,
he drove my father to death.
My father
was found dead in the back alley
of Chinatown in Incheon.
A will and a half-burnt charcoal briquette
were found in his car.
One sentence was written on the will.
"Apologies…
to my family."
Three months later,
my mother also took her own life.
All this time,
I completely turned a blind eye…
to what my father did.
I thought that
my family and I were the only victims.
Now I see that…
I've been selfish.
I've forgotten that
a lot of people are still in pain
because of him.
I know my apology won't change anything,
but…
I'm deeply sorry.
So, did you find the shaman?
Please wait a little.
I'll be able to find him soon.
You need to hurry.
If the shaman summoned ghosts
and Shin I-rang has been seeing them,
he may see him too.
Yes, sir.
Him?
SHIN I-RANG, HAN NA-HYUN
Who are you?
How may I help you?
I didn't mean to surprise you.
I'm sorry.
How…
I'm not sure myself.
Something just drew me here.
Why…
now?
It is a bit late.
I'll come again early tomorrow.
I can't take it.
-Excuse me?
-I…
will not…
accept your case.
SPECIAL THANKS TO CHOI WON-YOUNG
CORRUPT PROSECUTOR SHIN GI-JUNG
DIES IN A CAR ACCIDENT
EPILOGUE
Happy birthday.
A new ghost came?
I guess he isn't
on good terms with that ghost.
Why now?
Do you perhaps know who I am?
You are someone who can never be forgiven.
The prosecutor in charge was Shin Gi-jung.
I know it's late,
but shouldn't we reveal the truth?
I have no idea about myself
except for the fact that I'm dead.
I'm calling about a ghost
who needs to pass on.
-Was I that nasty?
-I'll have to send him off myself.
-He left?
-He left.
Don't resent me.
Subtitle translation by: Eunjin Erica Kim