=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 24=
Chiling Secret Technique
has tempered you for so long.
But you remained conscious
and even slipped out to devour spirits.
You've brought me
quite a lot of trouble.
Your turn.
You truly are someone
even He Simu is wary of.
Chiling Secret Technique
can't completely subdue you either.
Young Master Xu is finally back.
That's right.
Young Master Xu is back.
- He's back.
- Young Master.
You're finally back.
(Duan Mansion)
We missed you.
Young Master looks good.
- Young Master.
- Greetings.
Come on.
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
Go get the luggage.
(Duan Mansion)
Feel unfamiliar?
Scared?
So do I.
I feel the same.
Xu!
He brought back
quite a few things.
Xu.
Leave this to me.
You're finally back.
I missed you so much.
Let me see if you've grown.
I've grown taller.
Much taller.
How nice.
Let's go.
Don't stand here.
We'll go in and talk.
All right.
Hey, you.
Move his things in.
Be very careful.
Move them gently.
Xu.
When I was away,
did you cause any trouble?
Are you kidding?
Without me, this mansion wouldn't be
in perfect order.
(Duan Mansion)
Oh, Xu.
I take care of everything
from family expenses
to the arrangement of servants.
This is my sworn brother,
Xue Chenying.
He'll be living here.
Chenying,
this is my sister Duan Jingyuan.
Call her Jingyuan.
Greetings, Jingyuan.
Xu.
Your sworn brother
looks a little bit rustic.
Leave him to me.
Within one year,
I'll make him
a young gentleman in Nandu.
No need.
He'll go with me
to the battlefield.
Don't turn him
into some dandy in Nandu.
I won't.
Go back to the army?
Father.
Haven't you had
enough injuries already?
Jiang Ai,
are you going to rebel?
You and I
serve our own ambitions.
Let's not
accuse each other.
You colluded with a traitor
and plotted treachery.
By law, you deserve
the death penalty.
You've always been picking on me.
You think you will rule
after I'm eliminated?
Greetings, Your Grace.
Why are you fighting?
Your Grace,
when I led my men
to hunt down Bai Sanxing,
I suddenly spotted him.
I tracked him here,
only to see Jiang Ai
meeting with him
very closely.
I tried to arrest him,
but Jiang Ai
helped him escape.
I told you.
That wasn't Bai Sanxing.
Then why did you let him go?
Your Grace,
I also tracked him
all the way here.
If Yan Ke hadn't interfered,
I would have caught him.
Maybe you deliberately attacked me
just to let him go.
Your Grace,
Jiang Ai acted suspiciously.
She must be involved
in Bai Sanxing's escape.
Jiang Ai failed to arrest the suspect.
She'll be punished.
- No way.
- Yes.
- Stop!
- Yan.
Your Grace,
you can't favor Jiang Ai like that.
She's obviously disloyal.
All spirits in the Void are disloyal.
But I'm not.
If you weren't,
you wouldn't have stayed.
I won't deny
that I chose your side
to seek a wise master
and greater power.
But it's been 300 years.
We suppressed the rebellion
and enacted the decrees.
Through all these things,
you've also become
my obsession.
So?
I'm the only one
who truly cares about you.
I can give you anything you want
and solve all your problems.
Simu,
you should trust me.
It was just a casual comment.
Why are you being so serious?
I certainly trust you.
But do you trust me?
I came here upon receiving
Jiang Ai's message.
Now, we're in need
of capable hands.
If you and Jiang Ai suspect each other,
other lords will grow suspicious too.
Yan.
I don't want
another tragedy.
Sorry, Simu.
I was too thoughtless.
As the Right Hand,
you do everything for the Void's safety.
And you're also my friend.
Beside my throne,
there will always be a place for you.
Don't worry.
I promise
to clear all obstacles for you.
Father, you're coughing again.
I'm simply
in poor health.
It's just a relapse.
Take a seat.
I'm almost recovered
from my injuries.
I can stand.
What plans do you have for the future?
The battlefield is cruel.
When you were there,
you were badly wounded.
Don't go back there.
Now you only have a sinecure.
But Chancellor Du and I support you.
Your experience in the army may get you
into the Bureau of Military Affairs
to work accordingly.
Your two brothers
died on the battlefield.
You must not follow in their footsteps.
Yes.
I'll do as you say.
Shunxi,
when you're back here,
you should get married and have children
to carry on our family line.
I'm not familiar
with ladies in Nandu.
Father,
who do you recommend?
Go get those three scroll paintings.
Suyi, the third child
of Vice Minister Wang.
Changling, the fifth child
of Academician Lu.
Qiuyan, the fourth child of Prince Xie.
Their portraits and birth details.
Take a look
and see if you like anyone.
I heard
there was a lady
who grew up with you
as your childhood friend.
After you married
my mother,
she left.
I also heard
Mother was betrothed
to someone else.
But that man
was implicated in a treason case
and was executed.
You reinvestigated that case
and vindicated him.
Now you want me to get married.
So I'd like to ask you.
Do you still remember
what that lady looked like?
And have you ever regretted
marrying my mother?
You have feelings for someone?
After your marriage,
you may take her
as your concubine.
Then the lady you loved...
Why didn't she end up
as your concubine?
If that's all,
I'll take my leave.
Wait.
When you're back here,
all eyes are on you.
Remember.
Be discreet.
Especially in dealing with Fang Xianye.
He is now
the literary leader of Nandu.
Those haughty censors
in the Censorate
deeply admire his essays and poems.
You must not
confront him head-on.
Yes.
Eavesdropping again?
Xu,
is Fang Xianye
the one
who impeached you
and got you exiled to the border?
Why is he always against you?
Does he have a grudge against us?
Yes.
What's so strange about that?
Now, everyone has a grudge
against someone else.
You and I had one too.
What was that?
In childhood, you stole osmanthus cakes
and framed me.
And you used to claim
that I treated you better in Daizhou.
That was ages ago.
Don't be so vindictive.
Glad you know that.
When you were eight,
you stayed there for three months.
But you still talk about it.
Well, who would know?
Who would know
that gentle boy in childhood
could grow up to have
such a sharp tongue?
I'll keep saying that.
A hundred times more.
Xu,
you turned out different.
will you really get married?
Perhaps.
There seem to be
quite a few puppet soldiers.
Did you summon me
for the puppet problem?
I released the puppets
to mess up the Void
in the name of Bai Sanxing.
We can strike
when the time is right.
"You've worked hard these days.
You did a great job.
You helped me a great deal."
Did you expect
I would say that?
Yan Ke,
what did I do wrong?
Where's Bai Sanxing?
I don't know.
I really don't know.
I...
(Yan Zhang)
You went to Qifeng House.
You cast a spell
on this ledger.
That's so you.
My little tricks
can never escape you.
After Bai Sanxing left
the Nine-Square Maze Prison,
you sent batches of spirits
to Qifeng House
for him to drain their power.
That's right.
Where's Bai Sanxing?
You've regarded him as a mortal threat.
I just tried to help you eliminate him.
Say your name.
That day, I used a spell
to blur Xusheng's memory
and entered the Prison.
I found Bai Sanxing.
He had strong power.
I couldn't fully manipulate him.
I turned him into a puppet
and brought him out.
Surprised?
I managed to take him out of the Prison.
You once suspected
that his soul candle was still burning.
I guess it's true.
I ordered you to kill Bai Sanxing.
But you acted on your own
and released him.
How dare you defy me?
I did all that for you.
You're the Right Hand,
second only to the Sovereign!
You have the strongest desire
for the throne!
How can you stand
being beneath He Simu?
When Bai Sanxing is creating chaos,
you can eliminate He Simu
and become the Sovereign.
If you dare to hurt Simu,
I'll kill you now!
All right.
You can kill me.
If I die,
He Simu will die too!
She's the one
Bai Sanxing hates most.
Now, he has regained
his power.
Only I can control him.
If I'm dead,
he'll lose control.
Then he'll hunt He Simu
without giving up.
However,
I may show some mercy
and keep her alive.
No spirit
can compare to you.
After I use Chiling Secret Technique
to drain all the power
of He Simu...
Yan Ke,
I will make you
the supreme sovereign.
And I...
I'll be your consort.
You...
Want to be my consort?
Yes.
I promise you.
I'll spare her life then.
All right.
What are you going to do?
Just trust me.
I'll handle everything.
Deal.
(Simu,)
(I'm back here in Nandu.)
(The court seems stable,)
(but undercurrents are surging.)
(Before recovering
the 17 Prefectures in north)
(the unrest will not end.)
(Soon, I'll go back to the army.)
Hey, everybody.
Last night, Bai Sanxing
devoured my two vice lords
and three senior officials.
If this continues,
even I will be devoured
by him.
Stop pacing.
- You make me dizzy.
- But...
You're not alone in suffering.
When Her Grace comes,
we'll find a solution.
He's devoured so many powerful spirits.
His own power must have skyrocketed.
This will lead to big trouble.
- Yeah.
- That's right.
Why hasn't Her Grace come yet?
Her Grace ordered us
to call off the assembly for three days.
So everybody,
you may leave.
Our world is in chaos.
We need Her Grace to lead us.
Why did she call off the assembly?
What... What shall we do?
Her Grace has her own plan.
From this day on,
you shall all take orders from Yan Ke
to hunt down the rebels.
All captives shall be executed
as a warning to others.
Yes, Your Grace.
Let's go.
Your Ladyship.
Your Ladyship,
our world is in utter chaos.
But Her Grace keeps herself indoors.
What does she mean by that?
I don't really know.
This is indeed a bit weird.
When Her Grace gave this order,
was anything unusual?
If you ask me that,
I recall she sounded a bit weak
when she talked to me.
These days, she's been hunting puppets.
Could it be...?
Are you saying
Her Grace might be injured?
Did she have a fight
with Bai Sanxing?
Bai Sanxing,
so you really are being controlled.
You're indeed
my strongest puppet.
Well done.
He Simu.
You didn't see this coming, did you?
Don't try to release your power
to destroy my body.
I'm shielded by a magical artifact.
Today,
I will drain
every bit of your power until you die.
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪