(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
[Episode 6]
[He Family Clinic]
His mother died because of the triads.
It's said that just before she died,
her last words were...
"Never let He Chu San
get involved with the triads."
Dad.
Dad, hold on a little longer.
Dad, just hang in there a bit longer.
What happened?
Get in the car. Come on.
- Dad.
- Doctor!
- Emergency! Doctor!
- Where is the emergency room?
- Emergency.
- Come in, what's the patient's condition?
- Prepare for surgery immediately.
- Dad.
Dad.
- The family waits outside.
Please wait outside.
Wait here.
Excuse me.
It hurts so much.
- Hurry.
- Okay.
Thank you.
It's okay.
When I got home,
I found him already lying on the ground.
I couldn't wake him no matter how I called him.
The shop door was open at that time.
But the neighbors were all asleep.
No one noticed him.
Don't worry.
It's okay.
He supported me by working since I was little.
He took care of me.
I just hoped to get into a good university
and find a good job.
Then I can take him away
from Ganglong Walled City.
All of this was about to come true.
But now he's in trouble.
I'm useless.
- I'm so useless.
- It's okay.
Don't worry.
It's okay.
It's fine.
Liu Yi.
It's okay.
Don't worry.
You've done great.
How is he, doctor?
Fortunately, he was brought in in time.
The surgery was very successful.
Once the patient wakes up,
he'll be moved to a regular ward.
Family members can visit then.
- Thank you, doctor.
- Thank you.
You're welcome. It's my duty.
By the way, are you hungry?
- I'll go buy breakfast.
- Xia Liu Yi.
Thank you.
If you hadn't shown up in time,
it might have been too late.
What are you saying?
Mr. He is a good person,
so the heavens will protect him.
I-I'm sorry.
I made you angry yesterday.
But...
I really can't get involved with the gang.
The person who should apologize is me.
Not you.
Cui Dong Dong told me.
Mr. He isn't your father.
I didn't know before.
I even forced you to join the gang.
I forced you to do things
you didn't want to do.
I thought you didn't want to join the gang
because you were scared of dying,
because you looked down on us.
I also owe an apology to Mr. He.
He saved me, and yet I treated you like this.
Don't worry.
I won't do it anymore.
What exactly do you want to say?
If...
If you really don't like the gang,
I will avoid appearing before you and Mr. He.
That's not it.
I don't think my parents were dragged into this
because of the gang.
It just happened that the person my mom liked
was from the gang.
I also know that many people join the gang
because they can't survive otherwise.
But not all gang members are bad people.
Like you.
I'm also living a happy life now.
Dad has given me so much love.
It's just that he got sick this time.
That's when I suddenly realized
my concern for him
was nowhere near as much as his worry for me.
Fortunately, he's okay.
Otherwise, I really wouldn't know what to do.
It's fine.
In the future, I will help you
take care of Mr. He.
Is the family of He Guang Sheng here?
I am.
Here.
Pick up the medication.
You wait here for me.
Mr. Hua.
Let me do it.
Madam Hua.
- You're back.
- Madam Hua.
Let me do it. I'll help Dad.
No need. Hold the bag.
Take it easy.
You don't need to help me.
I'm fine now.
- Dad.
- You two rascals.
You don't need to help me.
Watch the stairs.
Sheng, you're finally back.
Hurry up, come and eat.
You prepared so much.
I didn't prepare this.
It's...
Mr. He, what do you think?
- A television!
- Yes.
This won't do. It's very expensive.
Be careful.
You're amazing. Thank you so much.
Well?
I told you I'd help take care of Mr. He.
I didn't lie to you.
Let me do it.
Dad, let's eat.
Come on, let's eat.
Come on, eat.
Come on, sit down.
Come on.
- Sit down.
- You're really good.
Come on, sit down.
- Come on.
- Why so much?
Let's drink first.
Do you like it?
Xu Ying met Fei Qi before he died.
Fei Qi was unhappy about Qing Long
opening a nightclub on his turf.
The two of them...
I knew about their collusion a long time ago.
Fei Qi and Hesheng gang
will be taken down by me.
Speak about things I don't know.
Xu Ying's two trusted subordinates
seem to owe money.
Their homes are being stripped
because of debts.
Their wives and children
have fled to their hometowns.
But I don't know
if they really went back home or...
I remember someone named Zheng,
who followed Xu Ying for a long time.
He's from Caodong.
Here's the deal. You go to Caodong
and check things out.
See if they are still alive.
Let me know right away.
The reward is doubled.
Goodbye.
We'll leave first.
Bye-bye.
Liu Yi, what are you doing here?
Get in.
Where are we going?
Are you kidding me?
I haven't even arrived yet.
But you guys are already drinking?
Who knew that you'd dress up
to chase girls all morning?
Isn't this the top student
our boss has been thinking about?
He Chu San.
Everyone, this is a financial industry elite.
Here!
Have a drink.
Come on.
I'll drink first as a toast.
Getting bold after a few drinks, huh?
You start talking nonsense after a few drinks.
Why bully a college student?
If you dare, drink with me.
- Come on.
- Bring it on.
Cui Dong Dong, drink!
Tonight, I'm going to
drink you under the table!
I'll drink with you.
- Come on.
- Student, join in.
He doesn't drink, come on.
I'll drink, come on.
You still have the strength
to shield others from drinking,
which means we haven't treated him well enough.
Each of us will drink three more cups with him.
Knock him over
before we go tease the top student.
Drink!
- Drink!
Come on, drink!
Come on, Boss!
- Boss!
- Drink!
Cheers!
Boss, keep drinking!
Aren't you their boss?
Why are they forcing you to drink?
Tonight, we're all on the same team.
Forget about boss or not.
Listen up.
If anything happens to you in the future,
and I'm not around,
you can rely on these people here today.
I brought you here today
to show them that you are one of us.
I'm not part of the gang,
so what could go wrong?
True.
You're so obedient and smart.
Like a fox in sheep's clothing.
You...
What could possibly happen to you?
Xia Liu Yi!
Come out here right now!
Having fun in there with that college student?
Cui Dong Dong!
Could you keep your mouth shut for once?
- Tonight, I'll poison you.
- Keep drinking!
Later, I'll get that student dead drunk.
Don't come out.
They'll force you to drink.
I already told you, Cui Dong Dong!
He can't drink.
Come on, we'll drink with you! Keep going!
I'll drink with you.
I'll drink with you!
Drink, drink!
He said June 1st is Children's Day.
It's a holiday for me and my sister.
So, today is his birthday.
Who told you to come out?
Xia Liu Yi.
Your cigarette butt is about to burn your hand.
Everyone's drunk.
Seems like Cui Dong Dong isn't here.
That scumbag Cui Dong Dong ran off again.
I'm telling you...
That scumbag Cui Dong Dong
can drink more than anyone else
and run away faster than anyone else.
Scumbag.
A bunch of useless people.
If someone comes knocking now,
I'd definitely be wiped out.
Celebrating my birthday?
It's basically my death anniversary.
I'm all alone.
I don't even have a birthday gift.
Not even anyone to burn incense
at my grave next year.
Hey, don't say that.
Don't say that.
I've prepared a gift for you.
A gift?
Show it to me.
I didn't know today was your birthday.
So, I didn't prepare in advance.
I just drew it.
Don't dislike it.
He Chu San.
Come with me to a place.
Sure.
Are you kidding me?
Why is your driving so bad?
I should've driven.
I've only driven at the driving school.
But you're drunk.
If I let you drive, it would be like murder.
Don't move.
I'll go by myself.
Bro.
Sis.
I'm here to visit you.
Big Bro.
I didn't expect this.
I actually became the gang leader.
The gang's affairs...
Everything's been smooth sailing.
It's pretty good.
I'm doing fine, too.
Recently, I...
I met a new friend.
Surprising, right?
Not a brother.
Not a lackey.
Just a friend.
It's the...
drama-loving scholar.
He Chu San.
Sis.
You said you liked him.
You thought he was honest.
But he's actually quite crafty.
But he's still a loyal person.
His family is also very nice.
When I'm with them,
I always think about
the days when you were still around.
Every time my birthday came,
you were always there.
You would always buy a cake for me.
This year...
is the first time you're not
with me on my birthday.
After that day,
you've never come into my dreams again.
Are you blaming me?
Blaming me for only visiting you now?
You...
You're not here anymore.
You were killed.
It's my fault I couldn't protect you.
Xia Liu Yi.
I can't be your lackey.
Because if I do,
you'll always see me as just a lackey.
We've arrived. Go on.
Are you kidding me?
I can only drive at 50?
Might as well walk.
It's the traffic rules.
The speed limit is 50.
What if we get caught by the cops?
And...
you were drunk last night.
All right, stop nagging.
Get going.
By the way, Dad said
you need acupuncture next week.
Remember to come on time.
He Chu San.
Do you believe I'll twist
your head off and use it as a ball?
Bye.
He Chu San.
What was he doing back then?
Mr. He!
[Xiaoqi Trading]
Are you here to see the boss again today?
Yes.
You might not see him today.
Boss left early this morning with Dong Dong.
He's not here?
Yeah. Come back next time.
All right.
Then please pass this to him for me.
Okay.
Boss, Mr. He has left.
He asked me to pass this cake to you.
Don't touch it.
What else did he say?
Mr. He also said you should smoke less.
Change your cigarettes to lollipops.
What nonsense.
Go away.
Don't nag at our boss for smoking.
A lackey who won't even kneel to the boss.
Does he think he's the lady boss?
Ma Ying Long.
What did you say?
Get out.
Go!
Laugh? What's so funny?
Are you so bored?
It looks delicious.
I'll beat you.
What's going on?
The boss was out with that student, right?
Weren't they inseparable?
Did he find out that kid's not a good person?
No, no.
Something must have happened
to change the boss like this.
Something interesting.
What happened?
You said you loved the wrong person!
Your heart is full of scars!
What does that mean?
Dad.
Today, Xia Liu Yi is going for acupuncture.
I'll leave work earlier today.
Tell him we can have dinner together.
Okay.
- Mr. Hua.
- Chu San, let's work out together.
We can work out next time.
Chu San, you're back so early today.
What's making you so happy?
Dad.
Liu Yi.
I brought you some of Yuan Ji's chicken feet.
You're back.
Dad, where is Liu Yi?
He came for acupuncture
in the afternoon and left.
He said he was busy with something.
Mr. Xia, Chu San said he wants you
to stay for dinner tonight.
Recently, he's been eating out a lot
and often doesn't come back at night.
Fei and I both think he's in love.
Don't move.
It's fine.
I don't know what kind of girl he likes.
That kid...
Don't be fooled by his soft personality.
Actually, he's very principled.
He probably doesn't like aggressive girls.
He probably likes fair and demure girls.
But I'm not worried.
This kid has good taste.
He never associates with bad people.
It'll be a little painful.
Hold on, hold on.
It hurts a little.
By the way, what would you like to eat today?
I'll make it for you.
Mr. He, I won't eat here today.
I have things to do, so I have to leave.
Bye.
- You're really busy?
- Bye!
I haven't taken the needle out yet.
This kid, He Chu San.
What's wrong with him?
He's always causing trouble for me.
I treated him as a brother,
but what did he take me for?
Xia Liu Yi.
It's me.
He Chu San.
How did you make the call?
I'm at a public phone booth.
I got paid today.
I bought you some food.
I'm out of town.
I'm busy.
But I see that your light is still on.
[Xiaoqi Trading]