What are you doing, bro?
Oh, I’m making stir-fried basil and Panang curry. Tai and Sorn want to eat.
Need any help, bro?
No, it’s fine.
Jun, go find Sorn for me. No idea where he fell asleep. We’re almost done here.
Okay, bro.
Bro?
Are you there, bro?
What the hell is this?
Damn!
Did you see that?
Shit!
Where are you going?
Aren’t you curious to stay and watch with me?
Nah, you go ahead.
It's so hard already, and you’re still holding onto it?
I heard you have a girlfriend. Don’t you want to try it out with her?
Sit down.
Hold on, bro. Don’t tell anyone about this.
Do you really think I’d blab about this?
Hurry up.
Whoa, what’s up, bro?
Hey, hey, hey! What’s going on?
Why? Aren’t you going to take off your pants?
Hurry up.
No one’s around here, right, bro?
Do you see anyone?
Move closer.
Hurry.
Put your hand on it.
I know already. I can do it.
Oh?
Let me do it for you.
Hey! What are you doing, bro?
Why are you yelling?
You want everyone to know what we’re up to?
How can you just grab it like that?
I’m helping.
Cliche.
Can I kiss you?
It helps set the mood.
Two years later...
Jun, are you out yet?
Yeah, I’m here.
I’m almost there. See you at the office.
Okay, see you.
This floor is for imports and exports. We take and deliver goods here.
Got it.
If you have any questions, just ask me.
We start at 9:30 AM.
P’Puth!
Hey, Jun, my little bro!
How’s it going? You doing okay?
I’m good, bro.
Internship?
Yeah.
Come here. I’ll introduce you to the team.
These are your fellow interns.
Let’s introduce ourselves. One at a time.
I’m Aey.
I’m Phe.
I’m Jun. Nice to meet you.
Huh? What’s your name again?
It’s Jun. J-U-N. Sounds a bit tricky, right?
Jun? That’s a really unusual name.
I’ve never heard it before in my life.
It’s Chinese. It means ‘handsome.’
See? I got a cool name.
Jun!
Wynn!
I missed you!
How are you?
I’m good!
Bro Tai, hi!
Alright, kids. Say hi to Bro Tai.
Hello!
Hey, these are the new interns, right?
Yeah.
Ready to work?
Absolutely!
Wow, so the vice president himself is here to welcome us?
Nah, I’m just another salaryman.
Alright, get to work, everyone.
Let’s go.
Wait.
These are your access cards. You need to carry them to work.
Thanks!
Do you all know your working hours?
Yes!
All noted.
Here’s your card.
Thanks, P’Puth!
Aey, this is yours.
Jun, my little bro.
Thanks!
P’Puth so lovely
Oh, P’Penny! Hi!
Oh, P’Penny! / Hi!
Hey! Everything good?
These are the new interns for this year.
Hi
Nice to meet you!
If you have any questions, ask him.
I gotta get back to work.
Ask anything, okay?
Really? Anything?
Yep.
Wow, you’re sharp.
P’Penny is so pretty. I’m nervous.
She’s the company’s star.
And that’s our company’s tough one, P’June.
She’s super strict. Don’t mess up, or you’ll end up in the ‘cold room.’
Alright, let’s get to work. Let me give you a tour.
Come on, guys. Follow me.
I’m at the coffee shop. You want anything?
The usual.
Okay, okay.
Cool. Want a snack?
Nah, I got grilled pork sticky rice. Brought some for you too.
Okay. Be right up.
One mocha, please. And one mallow mocha.
Wow, two cups? Are you drinking them both?
Nope. One’s for my friend.
A friend? Sure about that?
Bina, helping out?
Yeah, Uncle Champ.
Call me ‘Bro’ outside. ‘Uncle’ makes me sound old.
Got it, Bro.
Your coffee’s ready.
Thanks!
Here, your mallow mocha. Same as always.
Thanks.
Damn, it’s so hot today. Why do you always drink hot coffee?
Because it’s good.
I like it.
Where’s my grilled pork sticky rice?
Here.
Looks good.
Smells amazing.
Wait.
If you want some, ask me nicely.
Oh, come on! I’m starving. Stop messing with me!
Then no food for you.
P’Tai, please. Can I have some grilled pork?
Whoa, dude.
Give it back!
Let me feed you.
What’s wrong with you?
I want to eat first.
Go away.
You’re annoying.
What’s your problem?
Can’t you just let me eat in peace? I’m hungry.
You look funny when I tease you.
You’re a pain.
Nah, screw you.
Screw you?
P’Puth!
What’s up?
How long have you been working here?
Me? Over two years.
I started right after my internship. Applied and got in.
Yeah, interesting.
Which department are you in?
Import-export.
Oh, good choice! James is a pro.
Once you graduate, just butter him up. He’ll take you in.
Guarantee
He hired me.
I don’t know
Trust me.
That’s a relief.
Alright, I gotta work.
Wait. Where’s P’Tai?
He said he was picking up a friend at the airport.
I’m off. Don’t wanna meddle in his business.
Alright, bro.
If you’re free, help me out at work.
Why don’t you help me instead?
Nah, I’m out.
Talking to your sweetheart?
Jun has a sweetheart?
No, just someone I’m talking to. Name is Piangrak.
Don’t wait! Show me how spicy. Let me see.
Wait… do you like guys, bro?
It’s the modern era, dude. Anyone can date anyone.
Sorry.
He’s cute, though. At first, I thought Piangrak was a girl’s name.
Yeah, me too at first.
Honestly, I used to date girls.
I got it.
Where are you guys going tonight?
I’m going to watch Aey practice ice skating.
You can skate?
Let me tell you, she’s on Thailand’s national team.
Doesn’t look like it, but she made it.
Who’s that?
Oh, it’s P’Puth.
Okay.
You shouldn’t be spying like this. It’s rude.
P’Sorn!
Where have you been?
You just disappeared.
Me?
P’Sorn.
But you used to call me ‘bro.’
I only call people ‘bro’ if I’m close to them.
Don’t just smile. Tell me where you’ve been.
I had some family matters to take care of.
I lost my phone, so I couldn’t contact anyone.
Then why didn’t you just say that?
You disappeared just like that.
Why are you so mad?
I’m here now, aren’t I?
About that day… the day you and I…
Two years ago.
Jun!
Give it back!
What do you mean?
I said give Jun’s stuff back!
What are you doing, bro?
He was about to steal from you.
If you’re that desperate, go handle it yourself in the bathroom.
Oh. 0000.
Jun!
Why is it taking so long? Are you not done yet?
Bro… I finished three times already, and it’s still not going down.
Huh? Let me see.
No, no, bro!
Don’t be shy, Jun. Open the door.
Hurry up.
Shit. You were definitely drugged, Jun.
Drugged?
Am I going to die?
Put your pants on.
Get in the car.
What is this, bro?
Take off your pants.
Why? What’s happening?
I’ll help you.
But people might see…
See what? My car has 60% tint.
Either let me help you, or suffer until your balls explode.
Bro, this won’t be a problem, right?
You’ll be fine.
I’ll take care of you.
But don’t go doing this with anyone else.
Yeah, who else would do it like you?
Just… wanted to say thanks.
Thanks for what?
For helping me, bro.
No problem.
I’m heading back to work now.
Where have you been losing sleep?
Sorry, I was clearing a deal with Singapore last night.
I think you’re working too hard. Take a break.
Why? Are you worried about me?
I’m just afraid there’ll be no one to help with work.
Alright, thanks.
Go rest now.
I’m getting back to work.
Okay, cool.
What the hell?
If you’re not going to help, then just leave.
Who said I wouldn’t help?
Press this button first.
Then pull out that drawer.
It’s stuck right there.
Not that one.
This one.
Do you wear cologne? Smells nice.
Why are you sniffing my neck? Get away.
What’s wrong with you?
WhyWhen I try to help, you push me away. When I don’t, you tell me to leave.
It’s too close.
Closer than this? We’ve been closer before, haven’t we?
Don’t talk about that in front of people.
Talk about what?
That day!
Don’t pretend like you don’t remember.
Speak properly.
Damn you.
Speak properly, or I’ll bite your lip off.
Fine.
Just don’t talk about that again. I’m serious. I don’t want anyone to know.
Alright, stop looking so serious.
Give me your LINE.
Why?
So you won’t get mad when you can’t reach me.
My phone’s dead.
Not giving it to you. Bleh.
Oh, hey, Jun.
Piang, how long have you been here?
Just got here.
Hungry?
Yeah.
Let’s go.
Who’s that kid?
I think his name is Piangrak. Probably Jun’s boyfriend.
Wait, he’s dating a guy?
Surprised?
When Jun first told me, I was just as shocked as you.
Why’d you bring me here?
Because Piang wanted to eat here. It’s been a while since we last came.
Been waiting since noon, huh?
Liar! You were texting me at noon saying you were eating crepes.
Crepes are a snack, not a meal.
Whatever.
Order food, please.
Here’s the menu.
Thanks.
What would you like?
Him first. He’s hungry.
I’ll have this one.
Make it two.
Coming right up.
Hey, Jun. I wanted to ask you something.
What’s up?
The guy waiting for you outside the office… who is he?
The one with the tied-up hair. He’s really handsome.
A senior at the office. Why? Do you like him?
Does he have a girlfriend?
Wow, Piang. You’re checking out another guy right in front of me?
I was just joking! Don’t get mad.
You sure?
Yes!
Alright, don’t joke like that again. Got it?
Got it. I promise.
You guys didn’t even tell me you were coming.
Sorn, calm down.
Wow, Jun. You’re so diligent, showing up early.
I brought soy milk and deep-fried dough sticks.
Thanks, bro.
No problem.
Hey, what’s on your face?
Oh, I took a nap just now. Maybe dust from my desk.
Oh, okay.
Can I have some grilled pork, bro?
Go ahead.
Hey, bro, any good food around the office?
At the end of the street, there’s a crispy pork place. They give you a huge portion.
And at the very end, there’s stuffed deep-fried dough sticks. So good.
Gotta try that someday, bro.
Jun, you’re here already?
Good morning.
What happened to your face?
Damn.
What the hell, It stinks!
Did you not wash up?
Yep.
Ew.
You show up early just to use the office bathroom?
Getting your money’s worth, huh?
What are you doing, bro?
Your hair is soft, like a dog’s fur.
And your mouth is as dirty as one.
I’ll slap you, Jun.
With my lips.
Bro Champ, he again.
Damn, Sorn. Knock it off already.
After all these years, you’re still messing with him.
Well, he started it.
No, you started it.
You rolled your eyes at me.
Sorn, where did you disappear to?
I had some stuff to take care of.
You vanished just like that?
And why do you care so much?
I’m here now, aren’t I?
Jun, the dust on your face isn’t dust.
Someone drew a cat on you.
What a cat?
Go wash your hands.
You showed up early, but you didn’t check your face?
Damn you, Sorn.
With a crazy cat face like this, what the hell is up with you?
You’re messing with me, aren’t you?
Who said that?
No one else in this company pranks me except you.
Damn it, it won’t even come off!
Well, at least you're smart enough to know it was me.
Why the hell did you do this?
If you’re going to mess with me like this, just stay out of my business.
But hey, I brought you some facial cleanser.
Do you really hate me that much?
Are you seriously dating guys now, Jun?
Who I date is none of your business.
Why? Are you against same-sex relationships or something?
I was just asking. No need to freak out.
I was just curious because you used to date girls.
Since that time… when I helped you.
Shut up, people will hear.
Damn you, Sorn.
Disgusting.
And about what you’re wondering… that was a long time ago.
I’ll tell you now—Jun from back then is gone.
Now, I’m the spicy Jun.
Look at this. What do you think?
Spicy, right?
This is the real deal.
Pretty solid, huh?
Come take a closer look.
Your muscles are tight too, huh?
I get it, physique-wise.
But what made you change your preferences?
Why do you care? It’s not because of you, if that’s what you’re thinking.
You can’t fool me, Jun.
What are you trying to do? People will see.
If you don’t want me to do this, then just tell me—
It’s because of me, isn’t it?
No, it’s not.
And have you used what I taught you yet?
Yeah, I have.
With who?
Why do you care?
Just tell me—with who?
With Piang.
P’Sorn, I saw P’Champ looking for you. He said it’s work-related. He’s outside.
Oh, Jun! What happened to your lips?
Why are they swollen like a damn octopus?
And who the hell wrote on your face?
Oh my god, I’m going crazy!
I accidentally bit my own lip, P’.
And the marks on my face? Probably a dog wrote them.
Oh, just go wash your face already.
P’Sorn, I’m going to find P’Champ first. Come find me later.
And you, hurry up and wash your face. Move it.
I’m dead. I’m so dead.
What’s wrong?
Praew.
I was just in the bathroom, and Jun and Sorn… it looked like they had a fight.
P’Sorn looked pissed. Poor Jun.
Where’s my order? Bring it here so I can check it.
Documents. Hurry up!
Here, the order sheet.
Hey, Wynn, what’s up?
Man, I’m so bored, there’s no one to talk to.
Damn, same here. P’James, my mentor, went out for errands.
Now I gotta do P’Puth’s work.
Hey, let me finish up work first, then we’ll talk.
Wait, wait. Want to grab drinks tonight? I think I’ll be heading back into the city.
Hell yeah, let’s go! See you there.
Okay, same place as usual.
Done deal, see you.
Okay.
Hey, little bro, do you have my files yet?
Right here, just got them fresh off the press.
Damn, that was fast. Let me see.
Okay, all good. Thanks, but you’re useless to me now. Go downstairs and work.
I want to keep helping you.
Help with what? I just have to submit these papers. Go downstairs.
Why are you making such a fuss? Just go.
Fine, I’m leaving.
Every time I see you, I feel like I want to stomp on your face.
If you called me just to scold me, I’m leaving.
Jun!
You’re supposed to be learning from me, aren’t you?
Don’t think just because you’re Tai’s favorite little bro, I won’t tear into you in front of everyone.
So what if I’m Tai’s little bro?
Oh, P’Sorn, is there a problem?
Is this the order from Singapore?
Oops, not playing this game.
If anything comes up, just call Korn, okay?
Alright, I’ll be going now. Okay?
If you want to teach me, then say it nicely.
I called you here since noon, but did you even bother showing up?
Sort these by company name and year.
You look sleepy. Just go drink milk and sleep.
I’m not a kid anymore.
No matter how much you grow, you’ll always be younger than me.
Be honest, P’. Do you really dislike me that much?
I don’t like kids.
Especially annoying little brats like you.
Well, I don’t like certain old people either.
Especially old people like you.
What did you say?
Hey, you just got here, and you’re already chugging drinks. Calm down.
I’m chilling, bro.
Can me toast?
Yeah.
Mind if I sit here?
Go ahead.
I’m Pop. What’s your name?
Jun.
Are you here alone?
No, I came with friends. But your bag got caught on my arm, and now I’m lost.
What do you mean it got caught?
Hey, Jun, Pop’s talking to you.
Then talk to him.
Hey, pour me a drink.
Sorn’s late.
P’Jun, were you waiting long? My friends dragged me into a drinking session.
P’Jun, slow down. I can’t breathe.
I. We.
Oh. Oh.
You bastard. You dare touch my boyfriend?
Who the hell is your boyfriend?
Him. Right here.