[Episode 6: Yu Lei, I believe in you...]
- What are you doing here?
I'm sorry.
- You...
- "You" what?
- I...
- "I" what?
I already apologized.
I-If there's anything you want me to do
to make it up to you,
just tell me.
Forget it.
We're all adults here.
It's not a big deal.
I didn't take it to heart.
Wait. So we're just going to
leave it at that?
What else?
We just had too much to drink.
Anyway, I'll just pretend
I don't remember anything.
And you should stop pestering me about it.
Who's pestering you?
Yu Lei.
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
I'm just going to go for a walk by myself.
Chen Ke, you...
Excuse me. I thought you were someone else.
Chen Ke.
Where were you last night?
I was looking for you all night.
Why didn't you answer
any of my calls or texts?
Your roommate also said
he didn't know where you went.
Last night,
I just wanted some quiet time alone.
And my phone happened to run of of battery.
You don't have to worry.
How could I not be worried?
If I couldn't find you,
I was about to call the police.
You were that worried
that you couldn't find me?
Of course.
You're my best friend.
Then Ouyang Han isn't your best friend?
He...
I guess so.
But he and I... We're... We're different.
What about Li Ming?
He's your best friend too, right?
Yu Lei.
You have so many "best friends".
Among them, I guess I'm just one of many.
No. It's not like that, Ke Ke.
Let me explain.
- With them, I'm just...
- Forget it.
I don't want to fight with you.
The orchestra has a performance
in a couple of days.
If there's anything,
let's talk about it after the show.
June 2, 2001.
Cloudy.
I thought he would turn back.
But he didn't.
Maybe his world is bigger without me.
If that's the case...
what's the point of keeping the music
that I wrote for him?
Okay. Next.
Let's see what else they have.
Next.
Hey, buddy. It's your turn.
It's your turn.
Ma'am, two chicken legs.
No, no. Just one is fine.
So how many is it?
What's wrong?
Wrestling with yourself again?
Senior. I...
I know the performance is coming up,
but there's no need
to put so much pressure on yourself.
Relax.
Have something to eat.
I'll leave you to it.
Thanks, senior.
What's up with you two now?
Sis.
Nothing's wrong.
Nothing?
Then why do you have to give him food
through me?
I just don't want to
affect his performance.
- Give me the shampoo.
- Here.
Did you bring soap?
You can use mine.
Well... I'm just here to give my sister
some documents.
Is your rehearsal going well?
Yeah.
Hurry up. We're running out of time.
Do you have something else to say to me?
I hope your performance goes well.
Thanks.
Anything else?
- Well, I...
- Chen Ke, it's time for rehearsal.
Okay.
Very good. Everyone's in great shape.
I hope you can keep it up
for the actual performance.
Thanks, senior.
[Olympic Theme Memorial Recital]
Chen Ke.
Senior.
Why are you here all by yourself?
Not celebrating with everyone?
It's nothing.
I was just here to fill in
for the original pianist.
I don't really know everyone that well.
It's better if I don't go.
Ta-da.
We couldn't have done it
without you this time.
Our performance went so smoothly
because of you.
Since you don't want to
celebrate with everyone,
I'll have a drink with you here.
Senior, I...
Come on. Here's to you.
Chen Ke.
Actually, these past few days,
I've been watching you.
Even though you've been focusing on
practicing with the orchestra,
and seem no different than usual,
but I can tell that
compared to when I first met you,
you're in a very different state of mind.
Senior. You're overthinking it.
Your mood has been going up and down
all because of Yu Lei, isn't it?
Chen Ke.
You don't have to answer me right away.
Can you first listen to what I have to say?
From the first time
I saw you play the piano,
I've really admired you.
I felt like I'd met a kindred spirit.
And I wanted to get closer to you.
You're a wonderful guy.
Besides admiration,
I think I might also like you a little.
But I gradually realized
that your heart doesn't open up so easily.
But Yu Lei seems to have done it.
It's rare to find a true friend in life.
I'm happy for Yu Lei that he has you
as such a good friend.
I just wonder
if you two have realized it yourselves.
Maybe the feelings and bond
between you and him
go beyond what it means
to be just good friends.
On your birthday,
I saw all of Yu Lei's reactions.
And you've repeatedly been unsettled
because of Yu Lei.
What does that tell you?
Senior, I don't get it.
This just shows that between you and Yu Lei,
there's no room for anyone else.
Including me.
So even if I used to have a crush on you,
it was one-sided.
It could never be a two-way street.
But you and Yu Lei have a real shot.
But does Yu Lei feel the same way?
He has so many friends.
Am I really the most important one to him?
At this moment,
I've never faced a problem like this before.
I have no idea how to solve it.
Forget about what Yu Lei is thinking.
Right now,
I can't even figure out my own feelings.
Chen Ke.
If you think about it, life is a long journey.
Walking it alone would be far too lonely.
That's why we always hope
to find a traveling companion
to walk with us, step by step.
If you're lucky enough,
you'll meet someone
who can see into the depths of your soul.
In an encounter like that,
you'll feel something
you've never felt before.
A feeling of being cherished,
of being treasured.
It's a feeling like
the entire universe is cheering you on.
And every one of us needs that feeling
of being validated, of being seen,
of being needed.
You chasing Lei Lei, Lei Lei chasing you...
it's all the same.
But...
does Yu Lei feel the same way?
He has so many friends.
Am I really the most important one to him?
Chen Ke.
You have to understand, Lei Lei and I
have been close since we were kids.
He might seem carefree, but deep down,
he's a very sensitive and gentle person.
But when it comes to someone he likes,
he always does things that are thoughtful,
but also completely baffling.
And he only confesses his reasons
at the very end.
And I think you two are quite similar.
So the way you two
keep avoiding each other
and second-guessing everything,
it's just exhausting.
Maybe you could find a way
to let Lei Lei know how you feel.
Like, for example...
Like what?
Like preparing a special gift or something.
Of course, I'm just guessing here.
What you actually do is up to you.
Okay. Thanks, senior.
I know what to do now.
Wait.
Hey, I had a crush on you for a bit.
Can't you at least give me
some kind of reaction?
You're making me lose face here.
July 12, 2001.
Sunny.
My world suddenly opened up.
I wanted to run. I wanted to scream.
I wanted to, in the very next second,
shout my feelings out loud.
But in the next second,
[Countdown to Beijing's Bid for Olympics]
my world turned to gray.
[1 Day Left]
Hello?
Mom?
Lin Wen.
Why did the lunch lady give you
so much meat for dinner?
That's not fair!
Good students get more meat.
What's wrong with that?
So good students get to eat more meat?
Yep.
Yu Lei!
Dude! Why are you in here
with the lights off?
You scared me to death!
Shoot. I overslept.
Is the school orchestra's performance over?
Dude, it ended a long time ago.
Did you guys see Chen Ke then?
Nope.
Ke Ke. You're back. I...
Wait. What's wrong with you?
I... I just got a call from my mom.
She said my dad
had a sudden medical emergency.
Ke Ke, try not to worry too much.
Your dad isn't that old.
He should be in decent health.
They got him to the hospital quickly,
so I'm sure it's nothing too serious.
My dad has always had high blood pressure.
Two years ago, he was diagnosed
with coronary heart disease.
But I was preparing for
my college entrance exams then,
so my family kept it from me.
I only just found out about it now.
For the past six months,
my dad's been having frequent angina attacks.
And now it's turned into a heart attack.
Here, here. Drink some water first.
Ke Ke, when our parents get to this age,
it's common for them to get sick.
Don't blame yourself too much.
How can I not blame myself?
No matter what, he's my dad.
I had no idea his health had gotten this bad.
Hello? Mom?
How's Dad?
For now, he's out of immediate danger.
Son. I need to discuss something with you.
The doctor said your dad
needs another operation.
But for this hospital, I'm afraid they can't
perform such a difficult one.
Then what about transferring him
to the provincial capital?
Or a major hospital in Beijing or Shanghai?
Could they do it there?
They could, but I'm worried.
The long journey would be hard on your dad.
I'm afraid he might not make it through.
Son, I'm so overwhelmed right now.
Can you help me decide what to do?
Why don't we just transfer him?
We have to take the chance.
No. We can't.
Dad's condition...
Mom, let's both think it over some more.
There has to be a way.
Okay. You try not to panic, either.
Don't worry. The doctor said
your dad should be fine tonight.
They'll keep him under observation.
We can wait until tomorrow
to make a decision based on his condition.
Okay.
Ke Ke. My mom used to work at a hospital.
She knows a lot of really good doctors.
I'm sure she can help.
Besides, modern medicine is so advanced now.
I'm sure they can do something.
So don't worry too much.
Yu Lei.
Thank you for being here with me.
I feel much better.
But just standing here and doing nothing
is unbearable.
So, what are you going to do?
I'm going to find my advisor now
and ask for leave.
And book the next flight home.
But final exams are coming up.
I can't worry about that right now.
There's no way I'm letting you go alone.
I wouldn't be able to rest easy.
I'm booking tickets for both of us right now.
Both of us?
I've made up my mind.
I'm skipping the exams too.
I'm going back with you.
[Department of Internal Medicine]
Ke Ke. Talk to your dad.
Dad.
Are you feeling any better?
I'm fine.
I'm perfectly healthy.
What's a little sickness like this?
Final exams are coming up.
And you came all the way back.
Are you just throwing away your grades?
And you.
Always making a big fuss over nothing.
Sir, you shouldn't say that about Chen Ke.
He was just worried about you.
The moment he heard you were sick,
he was so anxious.
He bought a ticket and flew back overnight.
On the way here, he told me
that he felt bad for not spending
enough time with you during winter break.
He really regrets it.
Isn't that right, Chen Ke?
Yeah.
Besides, we've already spoken
to our professor and made arrangements.
He said we can take the make-up exams
at the beginning of next semester.
It won't affect our grades.
Sir, Ma'am, you don't have to worry.
Really?
- Really.
- See?
The boy is just trying to be a good son.
And he's thought everything through.
Why are you still looking so grim?
Alright, alright.
Let's eat first.
The congee is getting cold.
It's not like I can't move.
- Here.
- Mom, let me do it.
Let your son feed you.
Mom, you've been at the hospital all day.
If you keep pushing yourself like this,
you might end up
in a hospital bed yourself.
Don't worry. I'm here.
That's right, Ma'am.
I'm here to help Ke Ke take care of him.
You should go home
and get a good night's sleep.
If only I could actually rest easy.
Hello? Mom?
Son.
I have great news.
A top cardiac specialist in the country
is currently attending a conference
in Qingdao.
He's agreed to help your classmate's father
with the surgery.
Really?
Thanks, Mom.
Don't thank me.
- You should thank the doctor.
- Okay.
It's all settled.
Lei Lei. Thank you.
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Thank you.
No worries.
Thanks.
Alright, class.
Time's up. Hand in your papers.
Of course I'm done.
I checked it several times.
I checked it, like, three times.
I'll grab yours for you.
How'd you do?
It was all basic stuff.
You just had to pay attention in class.
Hurry, hurry.
Xiao Ming. How did you do on the exam?
It was okay, I guess.
At least I filled up the whole page.
Fair enough.
I wonder how Chen Ke's family is doing.
I heard something happened
to Chen Ke's dad.
Yu Lei didn't even take his final exams,
and went back with him.
Tell me, isn't that true love?
Totally.
These days, all the handsome guys
end up with other handsome guys.
Unbelievable.
Right now, Yu Lei and Chen Ke
probably have no idea
that they've been shipped as a couple.
What's with students these days?
Xiao Ming, wanna go shoot some hoops?
To blow off some steam?
Xiao Ming?
- Xiao Ming?
I have something to do. I'm heading out.
Look at you.
Eating like a bird over here?
Better than some people
who only know how to stuff their face.
Are you feeding a pig over there?
I bought too much.
Help me finish it.
Anyway, the thing with Chen Ke and Yu Lei...
Don't keep it bottled up.
If you're feeling down about it,
I'll play ball with you.
You're being unusually nice.
What are you up to?
Aren't you on Yu Lei's side?
Why do you care about me?
I don't know why, but nowadays,
I just can't stand seeing you unhappy.
Why are you eating so fast?
Didn't you say you wanted to play ball?
Let's go.
Not so fast.
You can't exercise right after a full meal.
Lei Lei. This scar on your neck...
That's from when I was a kid.
I was climbing a tree,
and I fell out of it.
You've been a little rascal
since you were young.
Nonsense.
I wasn't the one who was fooling around.
There was this other kid who got my toy
stuck up in the tree.
I was just trying to get it back,
so I climbed up.
Lei Lei.
Was it a model airplane?
I think that might be right.
It was in the summer, right?
The model airplane was made of wood chips.
You were spending summer vacation
at your aunt's house.
And before you left,
you even gave that plane to the other kid.
How did you know that?
- Bye.
It was you.
That other kid was you.
Lei Lei. That boy was you?
Honey, what's going on here?
You don't remember?
He's the little boy that our Chen Ke
used to play with.
So it was you.
That kid, Ke Ke... After that day,
he kept talking about you
for the longest time.
After my aunt moved away,
I never came back here.
It's okay.
We've met again in college, haven't we?
That's what you call fate.
Yeah.
Now that you mention it, after you left,
Ke Ke cried quite a few times at home.
I... I'm not that much of a crybaby.
Oh, yes you were. You cried so hard.
Even your piano playing was all choppy.
Mom...
Ke Ke, you're not a crybaby,
but I clearly remember
every single time you've cried.
There's no way I'm wrong.
Yeah.
So you missed me that much.
You, student. Stand up.
What's going on?
- This isn't mine.
- This cheat sheet was right next to you.
If it's not yours, whose is it?
I don't know.
You really don't know?
I really don't.
Professor, I can vouch for him.
That note isn't his.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
I'm sitting right behind him.
That piece of paper
floated over from the front.
But I'm sure it's not his.
Alright. Sit down for now.
Alright, time's up. Hand in your papers.
Let's go.
Hand it in.
- Stop writing, let's go.
- Alright, alright.
Hey, man. Hand this in for me.
Let's go.
Hey.
Thanks.
For what?
I didn't see anything.
Then why did you...
I just figured that
even with all your faults,
you wouldn't stoop to cheating.
Explain yourself. What kind of person am I?
You're...
all brawn, no brains.
I...
Are you complimenting me or insulting me?
But, you're still pretty reliable.
What are you doing? You big gorilla.
Hey, listen.
In a few days, they're airing the Olympic bid
live at the city plaza.
We should go together.
Who wants to go with you?
It'll be so crowded.
Besides, it'll end so late.
Where would we even stay?
We can stay at a hotel.
It's not like we haven't
stayed in one before.
When this IV bag is empty,
remember to call the nurse.
Okay, thank you.
Lei Lei, at school,
are you and Ke Ke the best of friends?
I... I guess so.
Ke Ke doesn't have any siblings.
And he doesn't have any other close friends.
Seeing you by his side, keeping him company,
I'm really happy for him.
Sir, actually, Chen Ke is a great guy.
A lot of people at school like him.
It's true. You don't have to worry.
When he was growing up,
I was only focused on my business.
I thought that as long as I made money,
I could provide for him and his mother.
But, you see the situation now.
This kid, he's become more and more
distant with me.
Sir, actually, Chen Ke does care about you.
It's just that,
I think it's because you two
haven't had a good talk in a long time.
If you were willing to sit down
and really talk,
maybe things aren't as bad as you think.
It's my own body.
I know it better than anyone.
You're all just trying to humor me,
saying that after this surgery,
I'll be all better.
Actually, I know you're just
trying to make me feel better.
There's no such thing as a risk-free surgery.
Sir, the lead surgeon this time is an expert.
Everything will go smoothly for you.
Really.
Lei Lei, I can tell, you're a good kid.
I have no other wish than for you
to always be by Ke Ke's side,
staying as such good friends.
Together with his mother,
please continue to be there for him.
Sir, don't overthink things.
You're going to get better very soon.
I promise.
Sir, don't worry.
No matter what happens in the future,
I will always be there for Chen Ke.
I'll treat him like my own brother.
[In Operation]
Why isn't he out yet?
It's okay.
Director Wang, how is my husband doing?
You are the patient's family, right?
Well, don't worry.
The surgery went very smoothly.
It was a success.
Doctor, but why isn't my dad out yet?
Don't get worked up.
Our colleagues are in there,
they need to run some checks on him.
Think about it,
he needs to regain consciousness
before we can feel at ease
about sending him to the ward.
Otherwise, something could go wrong.
So, it's going to take a little time.
You all just need to wait a bit longer.
Thank you, thank you.
Ke Ke, thank goodness you helped me
make the decision
of not rushing into transferring hospitals.
Lei Lei, thank you.
Thank you for helping our family so much.
Thank you.
Ke Ke is my best friend.
I treat him like my own brother.
I'd do anything for him.
Thank you.
Mom, now that we're past this hurdle,
Dad is definitely going to get better.
Oh, right. Look at this.
Where did you get these?
My dad said the doctors worked really hard
on the surgery,
so we should show our appreciation.
But it turns out,
they don't accept gifts at all.
Anyway, since your uncle's surgery
was a success,
let's try them.
Let's unwind a bit.
Here.
Do you know how to smoke?
How hard can it be?
Wait. This tastes awful.
Why do adults even smoke?
I don't think we know how to do this.
We should just stop.
Let's go get something to eat.
Okay.
Look at you. You're tearing up.
Ke Ke.
If you need someone to hold, you can hold me.
You don't have to be strong.
It's okay now.
Ke Ke.
It's really okay now.
I know.
It's just... I'm still so shaken.
I was so scared.
What if I'd made the wrong decision?
What if...
What if the surgery had failed?
July 15th.
- What if my dad...
- Sunny.
Many people are probably still basking in
the afterglow of Beijing's
successful Olympic bid.
As for us, we're celebrating
Dad's new lease on life.
Life is truly full of uncertainties.
While in Yu Lei's arms,
I was thinking, if one day,
I were to suddenly die too,
what place would I hold in Yu Lei's heart?
Yu Lei probably thinks
that being "brothers"
is the closest relationship we can have.
But for a long time now,
I've wanted to be more than just brothers.
[Next Episode]
It must be He Jin.
I'm going to settle the score with him.
But if you hit him,
you'll be the one who gets in trouble.
Yeah.
I did it all.
So what?
It's all of you.
One after another, you all look down on me.
You only earn respect
by acting with integrity.
You blame everyone else for your problems.
Why don't you look at yourself for once?
Ke Ke, no matter what happens in the future,
I'll always be by your side.
A lifetime?
That's so unrealistic.