=No Doubt In Us=
(Adapted from the Manman comic No Doubt in Us)
=Episode 3=
(Fengyi Palace)
Good.
Bad.
Beat her hard!
Mother, I was wrong!
Mother!
I won't dare again!
No way. I need to check.
What are you doing?
With so many memorials piling up,
I wonder when you'd return.
Are you worried about me?
Who's worried about you?
I'm afraid you'll anger Empress Dowager
and damage my body.
Are you alright?
Jinming stepped in to mediate.
How could Mother refuse?
I told Mother,
to fulfill my filial duty,
His Majesty
personally taught me all night.
Personally taught...
All night...
To fulfill filial duty...
Your Majesty,
you've worked hard.
Not at all.
See how much the eyes resemble yours.
They also look like yours.
What are you thinking?
Don't talk nonsense.
What filial duty?
I said,
His Majesty taught me
to play the zither all night,
so I could perform for Mother later
to fulfill my filial duty.
Mother was deeply moved
and mentioned
she wished the Empress could
learn embroidery.
Embroidery?
Mother knows well
I'm terrible at needlework.
Alright then.
Let's switch.
I choose embroidery then.
Jinyun.
What new game are you two playing?
Why are you here? Aren't you
with the Empress Dowager?
I came to find my brother.
Jinyun, pay me up.
What is it about?
Small matter.
You promised to repay my debts.
Now I brought back your wife.
Pay me up.
How much?
8,000 taels.
- 8,000 taels?
In gold.
- In gold?
The bet with Third Uncle
is a complete scam.
It was an archery contest against him.
He's a war veteran.
And I've only played cards.
So...
Isn't it about archery?
I'll win for you.
Third Uncle,
what refined taste you have.
Your Majesty.
Your Highness.
What brings you here to play with me?
I heard you competed in archery
against Jinming recently
and won 8,000 taels from him.
Do you dare compete against me today?
If I win,
the debt will be cleared.
Right.
Of course.
(Everyone in Chen Empire
knows the Emperor is bookish.)
Jinyun.
(Daring to challenge me in archery?)
Well shot!
Third Uncle.
Now I owe you nothing.
I admit defeat.
Your Highness.
Xiao Jinyun's constitution is frail.
Since when could he handle a bow?
Go investigate it.
I never thought this pleasure house
would harbor such elegant melodies.
Jinming.
This place you brought me
is truly amazing.
Of course.
Jinyun,
we rarely get to come out like this.
Going back early would be a waste.
Come on.
Let's drink.
Good!
Well played!
May I ask you
what the meaning
behind that piece I just played was?
Well...
It's hard to tell.
Poetic sentiments grow cold
with few who understand.
Yet I rejoice to meet you
by the riverside.
Only Mr. Xu truly comprehends music.
He understands me.
What?
Mr. Xu?
(My elder brother isn't the one
to frequent such places.)
(Could it be...)
Exactly.
Before heading north,
Mr. Xu often gathered friends here.
Many of his friends
were foreign dignitaries,
who only enjoyed drinking and revelry,
unlike Mr. Xu who comprehends music.
(Foreigners?)
(How dare she accuse
my family of treason!)
(I must inform His Majesty now.)
Jinyun, are you leaving?
Jinyun, wait for me!
Everyone, leave.
Inform our master
that His Majesty has grown
suspicious of the Xu family.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
Listen to me.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Your Majesty.
Are you having your period?
I am the Emperor!
How could I have a period?
Your Majesty,
your current body is that of a woman.
As a woman,
you'll naturally have periods.
During your period,
you'll need to use a sanitary cloth.
Relax, everyone struggles initially.
I'll show you.
Wait.
Do not use my body for such acts.
Come on.
Your Majesty.
This water is poisonous.
Your Majesty,
you can't handle cold water, right?
I have a cold constitution.
When I first had my period at fourteen,
I've endured pain every month since.
Hot foods cause irritation.
Cold foods bring stomachache.
How did you endure this?
Just let it be
and get used to it.
I've told Xuan to prepare
ginger and jujube tea for you.
But I thought you disliked ginger.
I personally brought you ice cream,
yet you dismissed it.
It seems you truly don't care for me.
I said I'll only have ginger
and jujube tea today.
Since Consort Zhao and others
have had this ice cream,
I don't need to taste them then.
I've known you since childhood.
How could I not know you dislike ginger?
There are many things
you don't know about me.
What I once disliked,
I now appreciate.
What I once cherished,
I don't quite like it.
It seems I'm not welcome
at your Fengyi Palace.
Prepare to leave!
Go to Consort Zhao's quarters.
Ginger tea dispels cold.
It makes you feel better.
Here.
Rest assured.
The pain will subside soon
after drinking it.
Let's go.
I'll help you rest.
Your Majesty.
I'm okay.
Let me carry you.
No need.
(Just once has left me
in excruciating pain.)
(Xu Yu endures this every single month,)
(but I was never by her side.)
Alright.
This way you won't feel cold.
I'll sleep in the outer room.
Call me if you need help.
♪Parting clouds
to pluck the waxing moon♪
The outer room gets cold at night.
Just sleep here.
♪Brewing a pot of bygone years♪
Fine.
It's your first time having period.
Then, I could care for you.
♪Console my grieving soul♪
♪Drunk through lifetimes
with no dreams returned♪
♪If not for letting go♪
♪How could I bear to shatter this dream♪
- Turn around.
♪Returning to drift
through the mortal world♪
♪Like her, like me, like you.
Hairpins carved♪
♪With endless sighs and regrets♪
Xu Yu.
♪Fate laid bare my deepest thoughts♪
You've been busy
taking care of me all day.
Do you care about me?
Who'd care about you?
I'm caring for my own body.
If this causes lasting health problems,
you can't do anything about it.
♪Like her, like me, like you♪
♪All who believed love would never fade♪
Xu Yu.
Just say the word,
and I'll make it happen for you.
♪The wind scatters countless sorrows♪
Things you couldn't do before,
you can do now?
When have I...
Enough, Your Majesty.
Rest now.
♪No one ferries me
across this sea of pain♪
♪The same joys and sorrows
can't be relived♪
(Xiao Jinyun.)
(You promised me so many things before,)
(but I'm sure
you've forgotten them all.)
(Never mind.)
(I'm used to it anyway.)
(With no expectations,)
(perhaps it's better.)
(Four years ago)
Your Highness.
Why are you here?
Today is your birthday banquet.
Why are you alone out here?
♪Loving to walk behind you♪
Many come to congratulate me,
but none are sincere.
♪Even the night breeze turns gentle♪
I'd rather watch the snow here.
Snow silently nourishes all things.
♪Those drops of happiness I feel♪
Why are you sneaking out of the banquet?
Even without your robe.
♪Time seemed to freeze♪
You are also dressed just as lightly.
Thank you, Your Highness.
♪How I wish to hold your hand tightly♪
Your Highness.
Did you make a wish?
♪Walking with you to the road's end♪
I've never believed in such things.
We have to fight for
whatever we want by ourselves.
How can we leave it to fate?
♪Yet I can't escape fate's tricks♪
You're being too serious.
Just making a wish.
It's just a small ritual.
Think about it.
If this wish actually comes true,
that would be so wonderful.
♪Can we stay silent♪
♪Watching the scenery slowly change♪
If it doesn't come true,
then we'd strive toward that goal.
So what wish did you make?
♪Words have failed me♪
I...
I wish for peace in Chen.
And I wish you and me
will both be happy,
and be ourselves
at any time.
Very well.
I'll make a wish too.
I wish that from now on,
I could remember every wish Xu Yu makes,
year after year.
♪Parting clouds
to pluck the waxing moon♪
♪Brewing a pot of bygone years♪
♪Chill flame, window shade,
console my grieving soul♪
♪Drunk through lifetimes
with no dreams returned♪
♪If not for letting go, how could I
bear to shatter this dream♪
♪Returning to drift
through the mortal world♪
♪Like her, like me, like you♪
♪Hairpins carved
with endless sighs and regrets♪
♪Fate laid bare my deepest thoughts♪
♪Like vows, like remorse, like love♪
♪Loving, hurting,
and regretting our late meeting♪
♪Tell me, after all this entanglement,
who regrets it more♪