(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
Life...
isn't always sunshine and rainbows.
But hey, even today,
the world keeps on spinning.
Good work today.
So, you're out of a job now?
Yeah, just sleeping in until noon
and going out at night.
Man, that sounds like the life.
What did you do before?
You know what an MR is? A medical rep?
Basically, you talk to doctors
and try to get them to use
your company's new drugs.
Oh, sounds like it paid well.
Why'd you quit?
Hmm.
Who knows?
Forget about that.
Let's just go have some fun.
Yeah, let's go.
Let's go.
Come on.
Where to?
Are we still drinking?
Wait...
The world's spinning a little.
Did I really drink that much?
Are you okay?
Want to find somewhere to sit for a bit?
Hey, hold on.
Huh?
Where do you think you're taking him?
Who's the hottie...?
Who are you? Mind your own business.
I'm an old friend of his.
Oh, whatever. Let's go.
Hey.
What?
Everything you just did to him...
I caught it all on video.
Let's go.
Hey, wait up!
Is this really okay?
"Old friend," huh? That's a good one.
Ha, are you trying to kidnap me?
Hey, are you even listening?
Just get in the car.
To Komaba...
Whatever. You're pretty handsome anyway.
So, where are we going?
It's time to wake up, Azuma.
How do you know my name?
You...
Attention, please.
Mr. Kuji.
Thank you for all your hard work.
- Thanks for everything.
- No, thank you guys.
I appreciate all your help.
As his rival from the same year,
you must have mixed feelings, right?
Not really.
But still,
- Now Azuma's the undisputed top salesman.
- No, no, not at all.
What do you mean "no"?
Don't be so modest.
Azuma.
Walk with me.
Huh?
Why?
Is it okay if you skip the after-party?
You're taking over
my old territory, right?
Let me give you a few tips
on how to handle those doctors.
Yeah.
Just like that, he talked me into it.
And before I knew it...
I never expected
things to end up like this.
He was the same way back then...
The next morning,
Kuji was gone.
All that was left was a single flower
that had fallen from the bouquet.
What kind of flower was that again?
That was it. That was all.
I never saw him again after that.
"Life In Smokey Blue"
(Episode 1: Reunion)
You're awake?
Last night, I...
If it were you, what would you do?
Huh?
"Song of Spring."
How would you translate that?
What's with the sudden question?
I mean, it's just "Song of Spring."
Well... normally,
wouldn't you just call it "Spring Song"?
That feels a bit...
So, what's the deal?
Translation.
Translation...?
It's my job.
Oh.
I'm actually kind of surprised.
I figured you'd have
started your own company by now.
And I figured
you'd still be a medical rep.
Is this for kids?
Or like a book of poetry?
Yeah.
"Song of Spring."
Welcoming Spring...
Heralding Spring...
Why not just go with "Spring Song"?
It's simple and clear.
I guess...
But it's too plain. It lacks freshness.
Then... how about this?
"Song of the Skylark"?
Hmm.
Not bad.
It's okay...
but it's too specific.
I want something that feels
more like a "new beginning."
That's tough.
You're...
Kuji, right?
Yeah.
Is this...
your place?
Yeah.
You live alone?
Hey, you know,
you should be thanking me.
If you'd followed that creep...
you'd probably be
an amateur porn star by now.
Ha.
What?
You didn't even realize
you'd been drugged, did you?
No way.
You're as naive as ever.
And that was my reunion
with my former rival, Kuji Shizuka,
after eight long years.
[Life In Smokey Blue]
I'm home.
Oh, Saku-chan's back.
You idiot.
If you're staying out, at
least give me a heads-up.
I know, I know. Sorry.
Don't be mad.
Oh, spicy cod roe!
Did your husband send this?
Apparently, you can only
get this brand in Fukuoka.
He knows you love it, Sakutaro.
Even while he's away on assignment,
he's looking out for his
freeloading brother-in-law.
What a guy.
Well, I'm digging in.
Let's eat.
Where were you, anyway?
Oh...
Just... out.
Thanks for the food.
What a strange day.
Even after returning to my normal life,
I still found myself thinking
about that brief, random encounter.
It was stuck in my head.
Mmm, yeah.
What?
This is just cleaning.
You're just trying to make me clean your...
No, it's data organization.
Same thing.
I need you to match the original books
with their translations
and group them with the relevant materials.
That Kuji Shizuka...
is you?
Who else would it be?
Anyway, start with these books.
Put them in alphabetical order
and keep the sets together.
Why me...?
How about this?
I'll be working in here.
Oh.
You are absolutely
not allowed in this room.
Well, that's rude.
My primary work
is medical translation.
I'm bound by confidentiality.
As a former medical
rep, you get that, right?
I guess so...
Call me if you need anything.
This is pathetic.
All this for a measly ten thousand yen.
Hey.
Geez, you scared me.
You haven't made much progress.
I got a little distracted reading.
You know, translation
isn't just about literal
word-for-word meaning.
It's about...
the context,
the atmosphere of the
story, things like that.
Well, obviously.
I mean, yeah, but...
I guess I just never really
thought about it deeply.
It's interesting.
Like how "awkward" becomes "embarrassing,"
or how "pink" can be
translated as "flushed."
Hey, Azuma.
Um...
Why so early?
Oh, well...
I'm heading out.
Don't worry about dinner for me.
Oh, okay.
Wait, where are you going?
To my part-time job.
A part-time job?
Where?
Wait... what?
I want you to research the background
of the young protagonist's life.
His background?
Hampshire...
That's in England, right?
Exactly.
Look into what the town looked like,
the fashion of that era,
what people did for fun, things like that.
That's a huge range, don't you think?
Read the original text
and use your imagination.
Just find whatever information
you think would help with the translation.
That actually makes it harder.
I'm sure you can handle it.
Well, it's a job, after all.
I'll do it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Reading or sketching...
[Life In Smokey Blue]
Napping in a meadow,
flipping through field guides...
No way, seriously?
This kid's life was way too chill.
Crap, I fell asleep.
You know how to cook?
A little.
Want some?
That's more than just "a little."
Hmm?
You're such a jerk.
Let's eat.
This is really good.
Oh, right here.
It says they took a "train" to London.
But back then, would a "train"
really be an electric one?
If it was diesel, it
would be a "locomotive."
Steam engines might have
still been running then, too.
I didn't even think of that...
Oh, and here.
It says he saw a "cornfield"
through the window.
In British English,
"corn" actually refers to wheat.
Wait, really?
Is that true?
You've still got a lot to learn.
Hey...
I've been thinking...
Yeah?
About "Song of Spring."
How about "Song of the Thaw"?
That's actually really good.
It's been a while since I've
felt this kind of good tired.
And...
What I want right now is...
this kind of comfortable pleasure.
What?
I just remembered.
Your bangs get all curly
whenever you sweat or it's humid.
I used to be so self-conscious about that.
They were curly that night, too.
You know,
isn't playing it cool
and pretending to forget
the grown-up thing to do?
Pretending to forget?
So you do remember.
Who knows?
Well, to help you remember,
should we try doing it again?
Doing what?
Sex.
And...
I also know we're physically compatible.
There's no way I'd forget that.
Not even for a second.
(Next Episode)
It's still...
lingering in some corner of my mind.
The memory of a home shared with someone.
I thought that was the first and last time,
but it's slowly taking over.
Even...
my heart...