[whimsical theme song playing]
[whimsical theme song continues]
[twinkling chime]
-[air hissing]
-[ball pops]
[whimsical theme song continues]
[song concludes]
[fox squealing]
NO TAIL TO TELL
[ambulance siren blaring]
-[somber music playing]
-[EKG monitor beeping]
[sobbing] This isn't happening, Si-yeol.
I know. I saw it all,
and you're not going to die.
So stop making me worry
and please wake up, okay?
[EKG monitor beeping]
[EMT] Patient's BP is dropping.
No, Si-yeol.
[breathing rapidly]
Please, save him.
I'll do anything, so please.
Please.
I don't know what to do.
Si-yeol.
[sobbing] No…
Please, no.
[nurse] You can't come in.
[sobbing]
[wailing]
[music fades]
EPISODE 12
LOVE WITHOUT REGRET
WOOSONG HOSPITAL
[pensive music playing]
[Woo-seok] What is this?
It's a fox bead.
Pardon?
You said the male shaman is after this.
It could be taken from me,
so I need you to keep it safe for a while.
[hesitates]
But is it really okay for me
to hold on to this?
It shouldn't be dangerous,
as long as you don't open it.
It might look like
just an ordinary wooden box,
but an eight-tailed fox used her last bit
of spiritual power to seal it.
So that pathetic male shaman
won't be able to find the bead's energy,
let alone the eight-tailed fox herself.
No, that's not what I mean.
Is it okay to trust me
with something this important?
Why not?
[hesitates] Well, because…
you know everything.
[sighs shakily]
You know what kind of person I am,
what I'm really like deep down.
[scoffs softly]
Don't flatter yourself.
You're not that special.
Do you think it's easy to be a bad guy?
I don't believe
humans are particularly good,
but I don't think
they're purely wicked or selfish either.
Even if you have an ugly side deep down,
I'm sure that's not all there is to you.
[sighs]
Honestly, I don't know.
At first,
I didn't think
I was such a bad guy either.
But at some point,
-I realized I'd become so--
-[Eun-ho] You became pathetic.
That's just how it is.
If you live life showing your worst side,
you'll only sink lower and lower.
Don't worry about this.
I'll keep it safe.
But is there really a way for me
and Si-yeol to get our lives back?
Don't worry. Just focus on getting better.
If you die before I can do anything,
then there really won't be
any way to fix this.
[Sang-cheol] What's that?
[gasps softly]
Oh, it's nothing.
[music fades]
Aren't you bored?
[sighs heavily]
Why don't you watch some TV?
[reporter on TV] The gunshot victim
was transported
to a nearby university hospital.
Police have identified Lee,
a man in his thirties,
as the prime suspect and are in pursuit.
Lee, who was imprisoned nine years ago
for various crimes,
is believed to be
the fourth-generation heir to G Group.
He allegedly committed this act of revenge
immediately after his release,
shocking the public.
[breathes shakily]
-[EKG monitor beeping]
-[suspenseful music playing]
[surgeon] Kelly.
Sponge stick.
-Tie, please.
-[nurse] Yes, Doctor.
[sorrowful music playing]
[doors whirring open]
[gasps] How did it go?
We did our best,
but he was already
bleeding heavily before the surgery,
and the organ damage was too extensive.
I think you should prepare for the worst.
[breathes shakily]
[surgeon] He may not make it
through the night.
[soft sentimental music playing]
Wake up. This isn't funny at all.
[Eun-ho breathing shakily]
Why did you…
Because of me… [sobs]
[sobbing] Si-yeol.
I've never been through
something like this before.
I don't know what to do.
What am I supposed to do?
I'd rather…
I'd rather take the punishment myself.
[sobs] That's what you guys really want.
Si-yeol didn't do anything wrong.
[sobs]
What do I have to do…
What can I do…
[sobbing]
[ominous musical sting plays]
[Pagun] There will come a time
when you must choose.
Whether to become human
or be forever annihilated.
[running footsteps]
[Woo-seok] Si-yeol.
What happened?
[panting]
-[sighs]
-[music fades]
[Woo-seok] Hold on.
Where exactly are we going?
I followed you because you told me to,
-but why are we here--
-[Eun-ho] It's just…
This place holds special meaning for me.
[mysterious music playing]
I should at least get to choose the spot
for my final moment.
[scoffs]
Are you serious right now?
You said
Si-yeol might not survive the night.
[sighs]
Okay, look.
What about that other nine-tailed fox?
I mean, was it the eight-tailed fox?
Can't she do something to help?
She can't.
Saving a dying person
is more than she can handle.
Then are you telling me
to just stand by and watch Si-yeol die?
[Woo-seok sighs]
There's only one way.
But…
I need your help.
How?
[dagger rings]
This is the Sajin Ritual Blade.
It holds the sacred power
to sever and defy fate.
Well, what am I supposed to do with it?
Stab me with it.
What?
I said, stab me.
Then I will vanish
from this world entirely,
and everything that was twisted
and distorted because of me
will go back to the way it was.
Then Si-yeol…
won't have to die in vain like this.
[breathes shakily]
But still…
We don't have time to hesitate.
If Si-yeol just dies like this,
then there's really nothing we can do.
And that means you'll die as well.
[intriguing musical sting plays]
[breathes shakily]
[dramatic musical sting plays]
[exhales deeply]
This is the end for me. My final moment.
[music fades]
[Eun-ho] I never once imagined
an ending like this.
[intriguing music playing]
[Eun-ho] But Geum-ho,
I think I finally understand
your final words.
The ones I spent a lifetime
trying to grasp
and could never make sense of
until this moment.
My end isn't what I wanted it to be,
and my last moment may be tragic.
[dramatic musical sting plays]
[Eun-ho] But even so…
[Eun-ho] I lived my own life,
just like you did.
-[breathes shakily]
-[ethereal voices vocalizing]
[thunder crashing]
[Eun-ho] With no regrets.
[thunder crashing, rumbling]
[faint echoing whoosh]
[faint twinkling chime]
-[echoing buzz]
-[wind whistling]
[twinkling hum]
[music fades]
[wind howling faintly]
[ethereal dramatic music playing]
-[cave rumbling]
-[twinkling whoosh]
[objects rattling, clinking]
-[pot clatters]
-[echoing twinkling whoosh]
[EKG monitor beeping rapidly]
[ethereal dramatic music continues]
[echoing whoosh]
[soft sentimental music playing]
[wind whistling]
[soft sentimental pop song playing]
So this is how it ends after all.
[warbling whoosh]
[gasps]
[breathes heavily]
Oh.
Eun-ho.
[soft sentimental pop song continues]
[breathes shakily]
[yelps, gasps]
Eun-ho!
[hesitates]
Did I really do this…
[weakly] It's not like that.
I chose this.
[soft sentimental pop song continues]
Just hold on.
I'll go get help--
Don't go.
Stay with me.
[breathing shakily]
I don't have much time left.
Why did you do this?
You said you'd choose
the solution for both of us.
But this isn't it.
[Eun-ho] Once I'm gone,
I can't really imagine
what that world will look like.
[chuckles softly]
But at least I can save you
and give you your life back.
None of that matters to me anymore.
I just want to be with you
and live a normal life.
Even if I have nothing,
I just want us to be together, okay?
So please don't die.
Don't leave me like this.
[soft sentimental pop song continues]
Si-yeol, do you remember
the bet we made?
You said you'd grant me a wish.
[trembling] Yeah. I remember.
Once everything went back to normal,
I was going to erase your memory.
So you wouldn't be in pain
or miss me.
So you could live a normal, happy life,
just like before.
But I don't have that power anymore.
Eun-ho… please don't.
Eun-ho.
[Eun-ho] So please forget me.
That's my wish.
[sobbing softly]
-[twinkling whoosh]
-[soft crackling]
Eun-ho, no!
[sobbing] No… Eun-ho!
Eun-ho…
[soft sentimental pop song continues]
I really wasn't going to say this.
I know I shouldn't…
so forget what I'm about to say too.
[breathes shakily]
I love you, Si-yeol.
[soft sentimental pop song continues]
[sobbing softly]
Eun-ho…
Eun-ho!
[sobbing]
[song concludes]
[somber music playing]
RIVER OF THREE CROSSINGS
[panting]
[ferryman] As you can see,
the boat isn't running today.
I don't know whose temper is so damn foul,
but I've never seen
the River of Three Crossings
rage like this.
[exhales deeply]
-[rain trickling]
-[wind howling faintly]
[music fades]
[doctor inhales sharply]
The test results aren't good.
At this rate,
I don't think you'll make it
through the year.
I think it would be best
to prepare yourself.
[sighs]
-I understand.
-[knocking on door]
[doctor] What is it?
[nurse] Well…
I think Mr. Kang's chart got mixed up.
What?
-[twinkling chime]
-Wait, how did this…
[intriguing music playing]
The scan is clean.
There's nothing wrong with you.
You must have been terrified.
I am so sorry.
This never happens. I don't know how…
I really am sorry.
[inhales sharply]
[panting]
[exhales]
[music fades]
[rain pouring]
[sweeping sorrowful music playing]
[wind whistling]
[sighs]
[spoon clatters]
[ferryman] What good
does carrying all that weight do?
It's heavy enough
to sink a ship, you fool.
Who are you trying to drag down with you?
Drink up and forget all about it.
Why are you so attached to this life?
[groans softly]
[music fades]
[traffic honking]
["Geum-ho"] That day, one life ended…
ONE YEAR LATER
…and several seasons passed.
[uplifting music playing]
[reporter] Kang Si-yeol, currently playing
in the English second division,
scored a dramatic winning goal,
leading Thames FC to automatic promotion.
Turning down transfer offers
from the world's top clubs,
he stayed with his relegated team
and showed true dedication as captain.
Just as he promised,
he secured the team's early promotion
in just one season,
making a glorious return
to the Premier League.
I think this match
showed everyone who we are.
We had tougher moments, but…
[crosswalk signal beeping]
["Geum-ho"]
In that place where life ended,
everything that was twisted and distorted
returned back to normal.
The human world just went on
as if nothing had happened.
[uplifting music continues]
[twinkling chime]
["Geum-ho"]
Some regained what they had lost.
They grew older
yet remained free of illness.
[twinkling chime]
["Geum-ho"] Some never died…
-and some never grieved.
-[Hye-rim] Dad!
[Bong-chang] Honey!
[laughs] Did you miss me?
-Wait, Dad. That's not important.
-What?
Do you know who I just saw at the airport?
Kang Si-yeol! I got his autograph!
Kang Si-yeol? What?
Did you get it made out to me?
Hey, you don't even like soccer.
I may not like soccer,
but I like Kang Si-yeol.
TO HYE-RIM, I HOPE YOU'RE HAPPY
But come to think of it,
I don't think I told him my name.
You've got your name plastered
right on your suitcase.
How else would Kang Si-yeol know
my daughter's name?
-Seriously.
-["Geum-ho"] However,
even if it seemed
as if nothing had happened,
it doesn't mean it wasn't real.
-[twinkling chime]
-You know that student from the airport?
[Si-yeol] What?
You just seemed really happy to see her.
Right, you wouldn't remember.
What?
[Yeon-su] Do I know her too?
[sighs deeply]
No.
[music concludes]
Anyway, you've been weird lately.
You rarely smile,
and you don't seem to care about anything.
You don't even seem that happy
about finishing this season so well.
[sweeping sentimental music playing]
[sweeping sentimental pop song playing]
[wind whistling]
[sweeping sentimental pop song continues]
[spoon scraping]
[chuckles]
[sweeping sentimental pop song continues]
Your world is truly chaotic.
Isn't it time you let it go?
[sweeping sentimental pop song continues]
[wind howling]
[birds chirping]
[sweeping sentimental pop song continues]
NINE YEARS LATER
H PUB
[Sang-cheol grunting]
[song concludes]
-We're closed for the night.
-[door bell tinkling]
[Si-yeol] Hello, Mr. Hyeon.
It's you, Si-yeol.
Come in.
Where's Woo-seok?
Hey.
[pop music playing over speakers]
Ordering pizza at this hour? That's new.
I haven't told anyone this yet,
but I'm retiring.
Well, good for you.
Considering your age,
you should've done it long ago.
You've milked it long enough.
Right?
So what now? Are you going to be a coach?
I'm done with soccer,
so I'll take my time figuring that out.
Anyway, how's this place doing?
Ever thought about opening
a second branch?
You? Running a business?
Making a living is no joke.
You look pretty happy, considering.
[clicks tongue]
Well, once I actually started,
it really suited me.
Cooking's kind of fun too.
[both chuckling softly]
[glasses clink]
[Woo-seok] Ah!
[sighs]
You know, when our fates switched back…
Has it already been ten years?
Honestly, I used to think
that had it not been for the car accident,
I'd have ended up with a life like yours.
But even when the damn accident
never happened to me,
I still retired earlier than you.
Isn't that funny?
[chuckles softly]
You've readjusted so well, though.
[humphs]
With my dad's retirement fund
and the money I made as a player,
I put everything into this place.
What choice did I have?
I worked my ass off.
But you know, surprisingly,
I've actually got a knack for it.
[laughs]
What?
It's not just pizza.
Even if I just throw
some veggies together,
it still tastes amazing.
I guess I'm better
with my hands than my feet.
Mm-hmm…
I see.
Then you should've played basketball,
not soccer.
Give me a break.
[chuckles]
Just try it before it gets cold.
[clicks tongue]
[exhales]
[Woo-seok] How is it?
[laughs]
Hey, this is actually good.
Right?
I haven't been here in a while.
[Woo-seok] Now that I think about it,
I think it was all just lingering regret.
"If only I hadn't hurt my leg,
then I wouldn't be living like this."
Thinking like that
just drove me into a deeper hole.
I kept thinking,
"I'm not meant to be living like this."
And that kept holding me back,
so I couldn't see anything else.
[tender music playing]
[sighs]
What I'm saying is…
you need to let go too.
Forget about her.
You said that was her last wish.
[sighs softly]
For me…
it's so strange
that the only people left
who remember Eun-ho are you and me.
[sighs]
[Si-yeol] But if I really forget Eun-ho,
there'd hardly be anyone left
who remembers her.
[sighs]
You said you bought that house, right?
You know, that building
with my old rooftop apartment.
I heard that neighborhood's
getting redeveloped.
No matter how hard you try,
that building's going to be torn down.
And the whole neighborhood's
going to change.
No matter what you do,
some things are just out of your hands.
I know.
But Woo-seok,
I feel like Eun-ho is out there somewhere.
-Si-yeol--
-[Si-yeol] I know how crazy this sounds.
But it feels like someone's watching
over me, protecting me.
Like they're right by my side.
They said I was going to die,
but my chart changed out of nowhere.
You remember, right?
That shouldn't have been possible.
And lately, things have been really weird.
When I got injured last year,
they said I'd need six months to recover.
I recovered in just two weeks.
Last month, I definitely left my passport
-and went to the airport--
-[Woo-seok] Si-yeol.
[breathes deeply]
You need to live your life.
This is no way to live.
[exhales deeply]
[Woo-seok] It's too painful for you.
[sniffles]
[sighs deeply]
[music concludes]
NO REDEVELOPMENT WITHOUT CONSENT
CLOSED DUE TO REDEVELOPMENT
-[stomach growling]
-[soft melancholic music playing]
[timidly] I'm hungry.
[sighs]
[chuckles softly]
[music concludes]
[inhales deeply]
[sighs]
[can crunches]
[lights slam on]
[sweeping tender music playing]
Eun-ho.
[breathes deeply]
[tender pop song playing]
[tender pop song continues]
[Si-yeol] Eun-ho.
You're there, aren't you?
You're really there, right?
[breathes shakily]
I don't know if I've gone crazy or what,
but I still can't believe it.
You disappeared right in front of my eyes…
but it doesn't feel like that was the end.
Even now,
I feel like you're watching me
from somewhere.
[tender pop song continues]
Should I check?
[sighs]
[breathing heavily]
What am I doing?
[tender pop song continues]
[yelps]
[grumbles]
Finally. I thought
I was going to lose my mind.
[sighs]
[song fades]
[panting]
Eun-ho.
-[song resumes]
-What do you think you're doing?
Were you really going to jump?
How did you…
I told you to forget everything.
What good did knowing me ever do you?
Why are you still like this?
You could've just lived your life.
I can't leave your side…
because you keep acting like this.
[tender pop song continues]
[Si-yeol sobs softly]
[sniffles]
[song concludes]
-[birds singing]
-[soft mysterious music playing]
-[wind howling]
-[boards creaking]
Why did you do it?
Heaven is fickle by nature.
Sometimes it's terribly cruel,
but sometimes it's infinitely kind.
Do you trust her?
I heard she's a reckless troublemaker.
[Pagun] I've taught her
everything I could.
She'll find her own way now.
To take on her burden
and defy Heaven's will
is to invite a far greater burden
upon yourself.
Even so…
the rain has stopped.
[Si-yeol] What exactly happened?
I don't really know either.
I don't remember much after vanishing.
It was just raining heavily,
and a long time went by.
My heart felt heavy.
So much so
that I couldn't take a single step.
Next thing I knew, I was back there.
Namsan. Where I faded away.
[chuckles softly]
I don't know what they are thinking,
but it looks like they sent me back
from the River of Three Crossings.
[music fades]
Wait a second.
Then all the strange things
happening around me all this time
really were your doing.
What?
Well, I didn't exactly do all of it.
Some of it was just in your head.
Then when did you get back?
Well…
Like… a year ago.
What? A year?
You've been back for a year
and never showed up?
You just sat and watched me
be a pathetic mess?
Well, you weren't that pathetic.
Winning the last season
unbeaten was really cool.
And that photoshoot last month
came out so--
Didn't you see anything else?
[tender string music playing]
Even when I lifted that trophy…
didn't you see
that I hated myself for being happy?
From eating to sleeping,
every single moment,
didn't you see
that I was barely holding it together?
Didn't you see that I missed you?
I felt like you disappeared
from this world
because of me.
I felt like it was all my fault.
[trembling] Because saving me
is why you ended up like that,
I tried to live my life
as well as I could.
Why did you do that?
Why did you?
Because I was scared.
I was scared
that loving you would change me.
What?
It's been ten years,
but I remember it like yesterday.
[wailing]
How I felt the moment you were dying.
If I could just save you,
I didn't care what happened to me.
I was fading away,
and you became my whole world.
But that isn't right.
-Eun-ho--
-I want to live as myself.
I want to live as myself,
and even if I die,
I want to die as myself.
If I stay with you, if I love you again,
-[music fades]
-I'm going to lose myself forever.
[Si-yeol] Then you shouldn't have cared
if I lived or died.
When I was sick or hurt,
you should've just ignored me.
I'll do that from now on.
I'm going to erase myself from your memory
and never show myself to you again.
Even if you get hurt.
Even if you're sick or dying.
[soft dramatic music playing]
I'm going to look the other way.
This really will be the end for us.
No. You won't do that.
I know you.
If you were okay with erasing my memory,
you would've done it already
because I was in so much pain.
Not for your sake.
You would've erased it for mine.
You promised me once.
That until the very last moment,
you'd try to find
the best solution for both of us.
This is that moment.
Our very last moment.
So tell me.
Is this the best solution you found?
Erasing my memory and living as strangers?
Then what am I supposed to do?
Even if we love each other,
we know how it'll end.
I have no desire to become human again.
Not even a little.
And your time is running out day by day.
In the end, it's goodbye.
Is that so wrong?
If it ends in goodbye,
do the moments we share mean nothing?
You live as yourself,
and I'll keep living as myself too.
I'm human,
so I'll get old and eventually die.
You'll live forever, just as you are now.
So someday,
we'll have a painful goodbye…
but the moments we share
won't be painful for you
when you're left behind.
Because I'll make sure of it.
[soft dramatic music continues]
I told you, didn't I?
I give my all to whatever I decide to do.
-[music intensifies]
-I already started ten years ago.
And it's not over yet.
So…
don't run away.
[music fades]
[sighs]
Did I overdo it?
-[gentle music playing]
-[inhales sharply] This isn't it either.
[upbeat music playing]
[sighs]
[sighs sharply]
Why don't I have anything to wear?
I don't know what to wear
on our first date in ten years.
[upbeat music continues]
[sighs softly]
[Si-yeol] Eun-ho.
Have you been waiting long?
I wanted to get here before you.
No, I just got here.
[clears throat]
-[gasps]
-[Si-yeol] Here.
I realized I've never actually
given you flowers before.
Whoa.
[camera shutter clicking]
-Oh man.
-[music concludes]
[Si-yeol] How did a reporter
find us already?
Eun-ho, let's go somewhere quieter--
Oh, he's not a reporter.
He's a photographer I hired.
[camera shutter clicking]
[Si-yeol] What?
We only ever took one photo together.
Even that vanished
when your fate switched back.
That's always bothered me.
[Si-yeol] But what's that got to do with…
A long time from now,
I'll need at least one more thing
to remember you by.
Besides, I heard kids these days
take a lot of date photos.
We just need to go on our date,
and they'll capture our memories for us.
[Si-yeol] Uh…
But how can we have a date?
It's too awkward.
Don't worry about it.
I put a spell on them,
so they won't remember a thing.
-[quirky music playing]
-[Eun-ho] So we
-can even kiss if we want.
-[fox squealing]
[echoing chime]
[Si-yeol clears throat] What?
Oh, right. We should at least
say hi to the photographer.
You guys have met, right?
Hey, you. Photographer!
Hi, Si-yeol! Long time no see.
Mr. Oh! How did you--
I just loved
how that photoshoot
you did last month came out.
So I specifically hired him
for our couple shoot.
-Wait…
-[camera shutter clicks]
Mr. Oh is shooting our date photos?
But he's the top photographer
in his field.
[echoing squeak]
[chuckles]
-[gong clashing]
-[Si-yeol] What's this for?
I called a filming crew too.
Photos are nice,
but video captures the vibe differently.
From now on, every moment of our dates
will be recorded
by the best staff in the industry.
Jeez, is all this really necessary?
Say hi to the director too.
You'll be seeing him a lot.
-Director!
-Yes!
Hello there, Mr. Kang!
Hello.
He went to Cannes and won an Oscar too.
I thought he'd be good
at filming our dates,
so I booked him specifically.
Since we can't really see your face,
why don't you take off the mask?
Right. Of course, Director.
Cameras are rolling.
See? He knows his stuff.
Let's go.
[camera shutter clicking]
[music concludes]
[indistinct chatter]
Eun-ho.
-[perky music playing]
-[chuckles]
[chuckles]
Mm! This is good.
[camera shutter clicks]
[fox yipping]
-[echoing wobbly clang]
-[camera shutter clicking]
[chuckles]
[camera shutter clicking]
[birds singing]
[Mr. Oh] Hold on. Wait. [laughs]
The background is great here.
Could you two stand right there?
Really? You think it's a good photo spot?
[Mr. Oh] Great!
Si-yeol, big smile!
Make it look natural!
-[camera shutter clicks]
-[laughs]
Could you give me a different pose?
A different pose?
[echoing chime]
Maybe try a kiss or something.
-[music concludes]
-But there are too many people here.
No one will remember.
I'll make sure
there isn't any press coverage.
[whistling whoosh]
Here.
[chuckles]
[soft quirky music playing]
[director in English] Cut!
[in Korean] Okay, that was great.
-[indistinct chatter]
-[soft quirky music continues]
Today was so much fun, wasn't it?
Yeah.
Hold on, let me fix your hair.
-Okay.
-[can hisses]
What should we do now?
Well…
I was thinking
maybe we should go somewhere
without all these people.
[echoing chime]
-[wobbly boing]
-What?
We've got plenty of photos and videos,
so I just want to be alone with you.
Just the two of us?
[echoing twinkle]
[echoing plop]
In that case,
do you want to go to my place?
What?
-[chuckles]
-[fox squealing]
-[music concludes]
-[wind whooshing]
[Eun-ho] Come on in.
Wow. So this really is North Korea.
I didn't know that last time I was here.
Well, it is Myohyangsan Mountain.
[chuckles]
Man, I haven't been here in ages.
I came here once, ten years ago.
So you lived in this huge place
all by yourself?
All that time?
[soft intriguing music playing]
[Eun-ho] Yeah.
I suppose.
[kisses]
[chuckles]
What's this?
It's just
that I figured you must've been lonely.
-Hey, you're home.
-[record scratches]
-[music concludes]
-[fox barking]
[Eun-ho] Hey!
Why are you in my house
when I wasn't even home?
-Wow, that hurts.
-[quirky music playing]
Long time no see.
-[wobbly boing]
-Yeah, long time no see.
-[Si-yeol chuckles]
-[echoing squeak]
For some reason,
I feel like your whole vibe has changed.
-Right, she became a nine-tailed fox too.
-[fox howling]
That day, ten years ago.
[echoing chirp]
When she sacrificed herself for you,
my fox bead accumulated
tons of spiritual power.
I see.
By the way, no need to thank me.
Excuse me?
I'm the one who cured you, Si-yeol.
-[whistling whoosh]
-Hey!
[echoing ding]
What? He deserves to know.
Ten years ago, she asked me for a favor
when she said she was hiding
my fox bead because of those creeps.
If I end up disappearing from this world
and can no longer protect Si-yeol…
What?
If that day comes,
I need you to step in
and save Si-yeol for me.
I'd just become a nine-tailed fox,
so I was low on spiritual power.
So I had to use every bit
of spiritual power I had
to save you from dying
of that heart condition.
I suffered for years because of that.
[sighs sharply]
Are you seriously not going to go home?
Stop coming over here already!
[wobbly boing]
All this time, you've been hugging me,
sobbing your eyes out,
all because you missed Si-yeol.
And now you're saying
you don't need me anymore?
-[echoing plop]
-Your house is huge too.
I swear…
Will you please shut up?
-[fox squealing softly]
-[Eun-ho] Look at her!
-[echoing chime]
-[chuckles awkwardly]
-I don't want it.
-[chuckles]
[chuckles]
[music concludes]
Gosh, I barely got rid of her.
Since she grew another tail,
she's turned into such a sly fox.
I seriously can't handle her anymore.
Really?
I was actually really glad to see her.
It brought back some old memories.
You should be careful if you think
she's anything like she was before.
I think her temper
is even worse than mine.
No way.
That's impossible.
I'm serious.
It wasn't only you and Woo-seok
whose lives were restored ten years ago.
Because of me, that male shaman,
Jang Do-cheol or whatever,
was practically a walking corpse
because of the spiritual backlash.
But he came back to life as well.
[gasps]
[ethereal dramatic music playing]
[gasps, breathes rapidly]
[Eun-ho] I guess since he had
some spiritual power,
he seemed to have woken up
remembering what happened.
[Si-yeol] So?
[Eun-ho] He should've seen it
as a second chance and kept his head down,
but he went after the fox bead again.
Reckless fool.
[bell clangs, rattles]
[twinkling whoosh]
[Do-cheol groans]
[groans, breathes shakily]
[faint eerie wailing]
[Do-cheol whimpers]
-[retches]
-[music concludes]
[Do-cheol sputters, gags]
-[fingers snap]
-[eerie music playing]
[spirits snarling]
[Eun-ho] He went to Seoraksan Mountain,
looking for an easy eight-tailed fox,
but he ran into a pissed-off
nine-tailed fox instead.
So he met the same wretched end
as in his previous life.
-I see.
-[music concludes]
Oh, right.
Then what happened to Lee Yoon,
the guy who shot me?
-[mysterious music playing]
-I saw on the news that he's in prison.
Did she do that too?
-[Eun-ho] No, Geum-ho didn't do that.
-[Yoon] Hey, get off me!
[Eun-ho] He brought it on himself.
We know exactly who you are.
That's why we're here.
-[Yoon yelling]
-Let's go quietly.
Damn it! [yells]
[Eun-ho] Neither Geum-ho nor I
did a single thing.
He managed to land himself
in prison all on his own.
[Si-yeol] Hm…
But… "Geum-ho"?
Yeah, she grew another tail.
So I gave her a name since it was awkward
to keep calling her an eight-tailed fox.
You can call her Geum-ho too.
[chuckles softly]
Anyway, let's talk about you now.
Have you thought
about what you'll do after retirement?
[music fades]
[Si-yeol] Yeah.
[inhales deeply]
I've done enough as a player,
so I'm thinking
of being a club owner for a while.
-For real.
-[uplifting music playing]
Club owner?
Actually,
I bought a team ten years ago.
[Beom groans]
Man.
Coach, the game's about to start.
What's this really important announcement?
What is it?
Why keep us in suspense
without saying anything?
Hey, just wait a bit, will you?
[knocking on door]
[echoing twinkle]
-What the…
-Oh gosh.
Jeez.
-Hey!
-Excuse me.
-Outsiders can't just walk in here--
-Chi-su, wait!
-That's… Kang…
-[gasps]
-Kang…
-What are you saying?
Whoa!
Kang… Si-yeol?
Let's hear it for the player,
Kang Si-yeol, who just acquired our team…
No, wait.
Let's hear it
for our club owner, Kang Si-yeol!
[triumphant chime plays]
[players exclaiming, laughing]
Wait…
So… Mr. Kang Si-yeol,
-No way.
-[Beom] I'm such a huge fan.
And you're my… role model.
Is that right?
I had no idea you thought of me
like that, Seo Beom.
[Beom] What?
Oh my gosh.
How do you know my name?
Of course I know it.
We're on the same team now.
So, how are they all doing these days?
Well,
Beom is still working with the team.
He's our GM.
You know how he's sharp with numbers.
I think he's better at this
than he was as a player.
[both chuckling]
And?
Gyeong-hun finally snagged
the starting keeper spot,
Jeong-bae retired early
and took over his family's restaurant.
-Yeah, their galbi is pretty good.
-[Si-yeol chuckles]
As for Chi-su, he transferred out
and went up to the second division.
And now he's playing in the K League.
He even made the national team.
Well, he was a surprise pick
and only played one game.
[chuckles softly] That's impressive.
[chuckles]
[yawns]
It'd be nice to see them sometime,
though they probably
won't even remember me.
Let's grab a meal together soon.
Okay.
[music fades]
[birds singing]
[exhales deeply]
[chuckles]
He must've been really tired.
-[gasps]
-[tender string music playing]
RIP KANG SI-YEOL
JUNE 10, 1998 - MARCH 20, 2096
[Si-yeol] Eun-ho.
What's wrong?
No… it's nothing.
I think I just saw our distant future.
Is it a bad future?
Not really, just a little sad.
[inhales deeply]
Don't worry too much.
I decided I won't be shaken up
by things like this anymore.
Like I told you before,
I saw the future when I first met you.
At first, I saw your friend succeed,
then in the same future,
it was you who succeeded.
Back then,
I thought maybe I just saw it wrong,
and I brushed it off as nothing.
But thinking back
after everything we've been through…
it was a future that actually happened.
Because I intervened in your fate
and briefly switched
your fate with your friend's.
So from the moment we met 19 years ago,
it was our fate to end up like this.
[music concludes]
[Eun-ho] Yeah.
[serene music playing]
Then this sad future you just saw
is going to happen eventually, right?
And you're really okay with that?
I'm okay.
Just because I know
a moment in the future
and can guess the outcome,
I've learned that it doesn't mean
I know the process or the meaning.
So in our love, and in our lives,
no matter what ending comes,
I'm just going to face it.
I'll only know
what that ending really means to me
after I've lived through it all.
-[music fades]
-[twinkling chime]
[mellow ukelele music playing]
-[waves crashing]
-[seagulls squawking]
What do you think?
It's nice.
Just the two of us on a deserted island.
-It's kind of romantic.
-[chuckles]
Right?
I'm building a two-story house over there,
but I'm currently revising
the floor plans.
It was supposed to be a villa just for me,
but since we're going to live
together now,
the layout ended up changing a lot.
Oh, over there?
Can we go see it now?
[Eun-ho] Of course.
Let's go.
[music fades]
If there's anything you need,
just let me know.
I'll make sure to include it.
Well, from what I heard,
it sounds like we're all set.
Besides,
I just need you by my side.
[exciting music playing]
Stop it.
By the way, where's the dock going to be?
[Eun-ho] What?
The dock.
For the boats to come and go.
Why do we need that?
You can just hold my hand
to come and go like this.
It's way faster and easier.
-No, but still…
-[upbeat pop song playing]
What do I do when you're not here?
Call me. Just burn the business card.
Oh, about that…
How should I put it?
I know it probably won't happen often,
but what if we get into a fight,
or what if you get mad at me?
Anything could happen.
Then am I stuck on the island
until you cool off?
Of course.
Did you think dating a nine-tailed fox
was going to be that easy?
What?
[laughs]
I'm kidding.
I'm going to build the dock over there.
I already ordered a yacht too.
[laughs]
Oh, I see.
That's a relief.
You look genuinely relieved right now.
No, I don't. Not at all.
Don't worry.
Having a boat doesn't mean
I can't keep you here.
Oh, come on, stop it.
That actually scares me.
Then just treat me right,
and you'll be fine.
This is nice.
I feel like we've got nothing
but happiness ahead.
Don't you?
Yeah. I'll be good to you.
[chuckles]
[giggles]
[upbeat pop song continues]
This is nice.
SPECIAL APPEARANCES BY JUNG DONG-HWAN
WOO HYEON AND HONG SU-HYEON
[upbeat pop song continues]
[fox squealing]
NO TAIL TO TELL
[upbeat pop song continues]
Subtitle translation by Susanna Kim