Um...
Do you take digital payments?
Sorry, we're cash only.
- Oh, I see.
- Yes, sorry.
As I prepare to set foot on a path
I never imagined taking,
I find myself
feeling a little shaken.
Thanks for coming.
You saved me from
accidentally dining and dashing.
Don't treat your employer
like your personal errand boy.
Here.
Candy?
That's a first.
I'm trying to quit smoking to save money.
To save money?
It's important, you know.
Saving up...
for tuition,
textbooks...
And commuting costs
really start to add up.
It all comes down to money.
And then,
of all times...
Wait! Dad's coming back?
Not until next spring,
but his time away is finally over.
Are you serious?
Honestly, it feels a little awkward
having him back now.
Hey, don't say that.
Poor Dad.
Yeah.
You know, Sakutaro,
you're welcome to keep living here.
We have the extra room anyway.
- No, I couldn't impose like that.
- Exactly.
Saku-chan, you're not allowed to move out.
We have to stay together forever!
Together forever, huh...
Why don't you try saying that to your father?
Sigh...
(Incoming Call: Tajimi Yasuyuki)
"Life In Smokey Blue"
(Episode 5: A New Step)
Sorry to call you over like this
on such short notice.
The thing is,
I heard you quit your job as an MR.
Oh, yes.
I'm doing some translation work
for an acquaintance now.
It's more of a freelance gig.
- Translation?
- Yes.
I knew it.
You always did have a gift for it.
You're probably the only person
who would ever say that to me, Tajimi-san.
I still remember
that Auster book you translated in class...
- "Ghosts."
- That's it, "Ghosts."
Paul Auster's "Ghosts."
So, the reason I called...
I have something I'd like to discuss.
At the start of a new journey,
unexpected paths begin to open up.
It's taking a shape
that's slightly different from before.
Bright...
Clear.
Weep...
Shedding.
This is from "Song of Spring"...
How's the progress?
You scared me!
When did you get back?
Just now.
Oh. How did the meeting go?
Fine. Same as usual.
Here.
A little something for you.
The person I met with
happened to be a candy-giver.
And you actually took some?
I figured someone I know
usually carries candy around.
You're so sweet, Shizuka-chan.
You've made a lot of progress.
Actually...
Yeah?
I...
I'm going to work as a cram school teacher.
A cram school teacher?
Yeah.
I did it part-time back in college.
An upperclassman I worked with
asked if I'd join him.
Oh...
Is this the one you mentioned before,
the one who studied abroad?
That's the one.
He's the one who praised my translation.
He's always looked out for me,
and he's been checking in on me lately.
So,
thinking about the future,
I think it's best if I go help him out.
I see.
Which means...
regarding my work here with you,
once I finish this glossary,
I'd like to resign.
I know it's sudden and selfish,
and I'm really sorry.
I understand.
I expect to be done by the end of the year.
Okay, got it.
Well, that was straightforward.
It's tight...
[Onboarding documentation for his new job]
Oh.
Azuma, let me introduce you.
This is Ms. Shimada from the office.
I'm Shimada. Nice to meet you.
I'm Azuma. Nice to meet you too.
I'll be in your care starting next month.
Looking forward to it.
Whoa.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
The layout is very clear.
It's finally finished.
Thank goodness.
Well then...
I should probably head out.
Yeah.
Winter thunder.
You don't hear that often.
Huh?
The power's out.
Is the data okay?
The data's fine, but...
I can't do any more work today.
And just so you know,
my deadline is tomorrow morning.
Oh...
That's rare for you.
You're usually so ahead of schedule.
Ah.
Does this have to do with
what happened in Yamanashi?
That has nothing to do with this.
Well,
if you use your laptop...
Sorry, I'm only at 3%.
Oh.
I guess we wait for the power.
Not much else we can do.
They're saying it's a major blackout.
Even the trains have stopped.
I heard winter lightning
carries a much stronger current.
Well, since we're stuck...
Want to do something?
In this freezing weather?
I can't believe you're in the mood.
Huddling together might keep us warm.
It's fine, go ahead and smoke.
I thought you were quitting.
It's not so much quitting
as it is just saving the money.
I see.
Hey, Kuji.
Why did you choose medical translation?
Because there's a demand for it.
That's it?
I wanted to use my knowledge and skills
to actually help people.
It sounds cliché,
but I really mean it.
Yeah.
I get that.
This relationship without a name...
is it ending today, too?
Ah.
The trains should be running again soon.
Looks like you'll make the last train.
That deadline tomorrow...
is it for a book?
Or is it medical?
It's for a publisher.
Then let me help.
I'll make sure
you hit your deadline.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Let me be blunt then.
I'm expecting some serious overtime pay.
Three months have passed since I reunited
with my hated former colleague.
It's been both stimulating
and surprisingly comfortable.
They were peaceful, steady days.
Ah, all done.
Good work.
The sun's coming up.
Are you hungry?
Not really.
More importantly,
give me a cigarette.
Huh?
Here.
Ah.
If I leave right now,
you'll be lonely, won't you?
What are you even talking about?
It's freezing.
Have you ever seen the movie
"Blue in the Face"?
Oh...
That's the sequel to "Smoke," right?
Yeah, I've seen it.
There's this heavy smoker
who decides to quit.
There's a scene where he shares
one last cigarette with the protagonist.
I always loved that scene.
So, is this your last one?
Who knows.
After all the preparation,
it's finally started.
My life as a cram school teacher.
Before the word "human,"
there's actually a hidden "that" here.
And then, this...
Ah.
Yeah.
Can you reach it?
I think so.
A place that once felt so foreign
is slowly becoming familiar.
Here you go.
- Wait, there's dust on it.
- I said I was sorry.
- No, no, stop!
- Let me just get it off.
[Searching for properties in Tokyo with a
veranda with zero results]
I really want a smoke.
(Kuji Shizuka)
This source text has a lot of personality.
"Song of Spring."
How would you translate this?
Hey.
I've been meaning to ask.
Why don't you ever translate
words like "I" or "my"?
You called me just to ask that?
Well, usually,
people would use "I" in the translation.
But your draft doesn't have a single one.
I was wondering why.
Are you talking about "Song of Spring"?
It's been bugging me.
I can't stop thinking about it.
I just felt like having "I" in there
didn't feel right, no matter how I phrased it.
So I decided to avoid the first person entirely.
Does it sound unnatural?
No.
Then why did you translate "Bluebell"
as "little blue flower"?
I was prioritizing the flow of the rhythm.
It is verse, after all.
Do cram school teachers
have to do this kind of work too?
Actually,
I've decided to go to translation school.
What?
It's only once a week,
but I wanted to give it a real shot.
So I'm just going to try it.
I see.
Why do you look so happy about it?
Huh?
No,
well...
It is pretty strange, isn't it?
It's very strange.
Want to go get some curry udon?
Give me one of those.
I thought you were quitting.
I told you, I'm not quitting.
I'm just trying to save money.
That attitude of yours
is the absolute worst.
Between school and everything,
I'm also looking for a new place.
Are you moving out of your sister's?
My brother-in-law is coming back.
I can't just stay there and be in the way.
I see.
But honestly,
it's going to be tough.
I have some savings,
but moving is so expensive.
In that case,
why don't you just stay at my place?
Wait, what?
What?
I mean,
it wouldn't be for long.
Until you find your next place,
you can use the spare room.
Are you serious?
You're out during the day anyway.
And if you want to study translation,
I have plenty of reference books.
Well,
if you don't mind...
I'll be in your care, then.
You're being dramatic.
Um...
Kuji-san?
What?
The curry udon.
Is it ready yet?
Alright, alright.
Let me help.
Stop it.
Cut it out. Get away from me.
No matter the weather,
being in this house
doesn't seem so bad.
(Next Episode)
At this age,
I'm actually chasing a dream.
I'm home.
Go wash your hands.
Is your brother moving in in May?
You didn't say a word about this.
Get up. Let's go home.
That house really suits you.