( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
How have you been, Eun-ho?
After graduating, I started a company
with my college friends.
Do you still do kumdo?
I quit after getting crushed by you.
I should've gone easy on you.
I struggled a lot after you dropped out.
Dropped out?
What happened?
So that's the backstory, huh?
Well…
I had my reasons.
You could've at least kept in touch.
I'm sorry.
So? What have you been up to?
I'm a webtoon producer.
WEBTOON PD
A business card?
I work at a company called Naemo,
near Hapjeong.
That's so cool.
It suits you.
Here's my card.
Producer Seo Mi-rae.
For the first time,
I'm the same person here
as I am in reality.
It feels weird to hear you call me that.
We're here.
This is the place.
So this is your company.
Let's meet more often from now on.
Okay.
I can take you home. Where do you live?
It's okay. You must be busy, so get going.
It's dark out.
I'm not 20 anymore.
I even drink soju at a pocha by myself.
Even in college,
you never drank like most 20-year-olds.
Anyway, I'll get going.
See you soon.
Hello?
Did you make it home?
I wanted to make sure you got back safely.
Eun-ho?
What is this? How is he calling me?
Hello?
Oh, yes. Just a moment.
All subscribers
with a basic plan and above
can send and receive calls and messages
with the characters after logging out.
That's crazy!
Hello? Isn't this Seo Mi-rae's phone?
Oh, yes, Eun-ho.
What are you up to?
I'm having trouble falling asleep.
I'm also wide awake now.
Then shall we talk until you get sleepy?
Shall we?
I've never met anyone who knows it.
Any horror fan would know that film.
The protagonist, being a villager,
was a fun choice.
Right?
Most folk horror films would go with
an outsider who's just arrived.
Exactly!
Want to watch a movie together next time?
-A movie?
-Yeah.
Let's meet near your office.
I'll come to Hapjeong Station.
What?
Are you uncomfortable with that?
No, that's not…
If you're okay with it, I can head over
around the time you get off work tomorrow.
The realism is breathtaking.
Sounds good.
Then…
I'll see you tomorrow.
EPISODE 5
THE CAVEATS OF PERFECTION
Sorry I'm late.
Let me go grab some coffee.
I already made some.
It's cold, though, since you're late.
Thank you.
I was reviewing a submitted file
and lost track of time.
Shall we get started?
I didn't like this piece that much.
It was too imitative of existing works.
Me too.
Is anything ever completely original?
The lines and page layouts
are too amateurish.
Which can be fixed with our help.
Do you think you can also fix
such a childish plot?
Some titles top the charts
despite having a childish plot, you know.
What?
No, I just…
Which titles might you be referring to?
There are plenty of them, as you know.
You're right. There are plenty.
What's his problem today?
Let's take a break.
Did you get to work okay? Good luck today!
When was the last time I received a text
from a guy checking in on me?
Heading out for lunch? Let me come with.
I have a lunch meeting.
Why don't you eat with Kyeong-nam?
Shall we?
We also have plans.
Enjoy your meal.
Let's go.
Sure.
This is so awkward.
Do you like romance?
What?
I'm asking
because we'll be judging together.
No. I don't like it.
Me neither.
So what?
So what do you like?
Horror.
Why is that?
Well, it's just…
I barely notice my heart most of the time,
so I like the way they make it race.
I also like horror. A lot.
Who asked you?
It must be hard for you
to work on The Man to Know.
Yeah, I guess.
I only got assigned that job
thanks to you.
Hang in there.
I'll be there soon.
Take your time, and don't trip.
Eun-ho!
-Am I late?
-No.
The movie is about to start. Let's go.
Don't kill me!
Don't kill me…
Please don't kill me!
Please don't kill me…
Want some popcorn?
What was it they said? That excitement
is not an emotion but a sensation?
It's so sweet.
A bit messy, isn't it?
It's really nice in here.
Everyone is out of the office.
Take a look around. I'll get you a drink.
I miss everyone.
Looking back now, we were really young.
I didn't know back then…
that I'd never…
forget about you.
We have a nice rooftop.
Want to get some fresh air?
What is it?
Are you going to disappear again?
No.
I'm not going anywhere.
On my way to work. Have a nice day.
Anything you want to eat today?
I haven't thought about it yet.
You wanted lasagna last time.
I'll find a place that makes good lasagna.
…I suspect that might be a trace of it.
Like you said, it does have its strengths,
but are they enough
to make up for the shortcomings--
What are you doing?
Why do you ask?
It's nothing.
Please continue.
Eun-ho!
Am I late?
You're pretty.
The few hours of freedom I have
after getting off work.
I've finally found the perfect way
to spend that time.
Look at this one.
Have I ever been on
such a perfect date before?
This is so nice.
Has time ever flown by so fast?
Stop crying, okay?
Hey.
Drink this and forget about it,
or go beg him to take you back.
There's none. They simply don't exist.
What do you mean?
No man in this world
is a perfect match for me.
If I can't find one after meeting 30 guys,
that means no such man exists.
Then what, are you gonna stop dating?
I don't know. Fuck!
Why are you suddenly swearing?
It was all a waste!
If I had put all that time
into something else,
I wouldn't be worn out dealing with kids,
even with a master's degree.
I would've made something of myself!
Hey, don't be so dramatic.
It's not too late.
It's hopeless.
I've had all my energy drained by guys.
Now I don't have the strength
to do anything.
Hey.
You have it better than me.
I should have
just lived like you!
What?
JI-YEON
Hey, how's my profile picture?
Can you tell I'm pretending to be okay?
So obvious.
EUN-HO
Hello.
Are you on your way?
What's up with your friend?
She broke up with her boyfriend.
That sounds rough.
Hey, Eun-ho.
Do you think there's a perfect match
for us somewhere in this world?
Not sure. Why do you ask?
Just curious.
I guess I'm not good enough for you
if you're asking that.
It's not like that.
The weather's gotten really cold now.
Had I found the answer
that Ji-yeon couldn't?
-Eun-ho.
-Yes?
When you're with me, do you enjoy it?
First the call, and now this.
That's an odd question to ask.
Tell me. Do you really enjoy
being with me?
What are you really asking?
Our relationship…
is a good thing, right?
Is being with you
the right choice for me?
Mi-rae.
When I'm with you, I'm so happy.
And when I'm not with you,
thinking about you makes me happy.
What do you think of?
The way you smile.
The way you walk.
The way you eat.
The way you talk. Everything.
So,
put your doubts aside.
Okay.
I'm hurt, you know.
Sorry.
Ji-yeon couldn't find her answer.
But I think I've found mine.
Why would you eat with us?
Where's your team?
They all wanted to go eat sushi,
and I can't eat uncooked food.
I'm glad you're here.
You are always welcome to join us.
Hey, you're all gonna attend
the workshop, aren't you?
Workshop?
-Yes, it's this week.
-You're not going?
I'm not gonna go.
I don't want to.
Do I have to go?
Don't you remember what happened
two years ago when you didn't go?
Huh?
Come on, it's barbecue time!
-Barbecue!
-Mi-rae, it's barbecue!
-Get in!
-Come on, Mi-rae!
It's packed.
I'm full.
It's too much for one person to take on.
Are you sure she'll be okay?
The authors have said yes,
so we can proceed as scheduled, but--
-Let us know if you need help.
-Then it's settled.
Sir, can you take a look at--
-Anything else to add?
-No.
Meeting adjourned.
Hey, are you eating? Eat your fill.
Pretend that I'm paying for it.
Sir, during the last workshop,
I had a stomach bug--
Dong-min, order one stomach bug for…
Get us one aged rib, man!
Mi-rae, you're still here?
First time seeing you here.
The last workshop was amazing.
Workshops are the reason I haven't quit.
That went on for three weeks.
Hwang Byeong-hak is impossible
when he gets sulky.
He's two years older now, so this time,
I think we're looking at six weeks.
Kyeong-nam,
you didn't go back then either.
Were you okay?
Yes. I was okay.
You're not going, are you?
You're going, aren't you?
Well, it'd be awkward
if I were the only one not going.
I'm going.
You're going to attend a two-day workshop?
What's gotten into you? Are you bored?
No.
My parents live nearby,
and I have to see them on Friday.
But it's a weekend.
You should spend time with your family.
I'll take care of it.
FLAMING JJAMPPONG
That devilish jerk.
Wow, this is the scent of nature.
Wake up! How long are you going to sleep?
WORK ALL NIGHT! WORKSHOP ALL NIGHT!
Hey, you guys aren't carrying much.
Boys, come back down here.
Have fun. I miss you.
Okay. I'll be in touch.
Hello.
Eun-ju! Take a picture of me over here.
NAEMO'S 7TH ULTIMATE GEEK CONTEST
All right, this is an old tradition
at our company.
Who's the real deal?
The ultimate geek contest!
The winner will have
the special opportunity to choose
from a variety of collectible items
brought by Director Hwang!
Hey, these are all limited edition!
No improvement at all.
-Since last time?
-We do this every time.
Now then, here's question number one.
Listen to the following line from a comic,
and guess which comic it is.
"I talked to a guy for the first time.
Am I about to get a boyfriend?"
-Seo Mi-rae.
-Mi-rae was faster. The answer is?
I Want to Hold Aono-kun so Badly
I Could Die?
-Correct!
-Really?
Remember the name.
-She's on Team 2.
-Question number two.
Bringing up a classic.
In Dragon Ball,
which World Martial Arts Tournament
did Tenshinhan first appear in?
Hye-bin!
The 37th!
Wrong.
Mi-rae. The 23rd?
-Wrong!
-It's over the 30th.
No, it's not.
-Kyeong-nam.
-Yes?
-The 22nd.
-The 22nd?
Correct!
Kyeong-nam!
In Polar Night, Cha Dong-hwan
served in the air force for--
-Seo Mi-rae!
-Jesus.
-Yes?
-Eight years.
Eight years, correct!
In Villain to Kill,
when Kwon Yu-ri is in danger,
the hotelier helps her and says…
-Park Kyeong-nam.
-Yes?
"Good morning."
Ding ding ding!
In A Bona Fide Killer,
Bona's child carries around--
Kyeong-nam.
-Yes?
-Kongdoli.
Correct!
In Theme Park of Death, Baek Jin--
-Seo Mi-rae!
-Yes?
Rolling Z Train.
Rolling Z Train, correct!
Yup. She got that one right.
In Transfer Student at Apocalypse High,
Geon-u's friend's sister--
Kyeong-nam.
-Class 2-5.
-Correct!
In Abandoned House Diary, how tall
is Oh Seong-chan, who keeps passing out?
Mi-rae.
175 cm?
-Wrong!
-Kyeong-nam.
176.
Correct!
-Mi-rae.
-Kyeong-nam.
-Mi-rae!
Seo Mi-rae, Arapra Garatus!
Arapra Garatus, correct!
That's it! Arapra Garatus!
Our very own Seo Mi-rae
got the last question right.
It was a nail-biter,
with both participants evenly matched!
Now, I will be announcing the results.
Naemo's 7th Ultimate Geek Contest 2025.
And the winner is…
Park Kyeong-nam!
Go Team 1! Go Park Kyeong-nam!
Ms. Seo, which prize do you want
to find the most in the treasure hunt?
An early leave.
I'm so cold!
I can't keep looking.
Who even hides treasures in a stream
when it's this cold?
A centipede!
-Where?
-Oh, it's not.
-It's a twig.
-Hey, your phone!
Oh no! It's going down the stream!
Oh God, no!
-What do we do?
-No!
Dong-min!
Holy!
-I'll show you.
-Just get in there.
-Hurry! It's over there!
-Hold on a sec.
-Hurry up!
-Go after it!
Thank you.
Aren't you cold?
It must have hit a rock.
The screen's cracked.
You're right. I only just bought this!
I'm going to change my pants.
Well done, Kyeong-nam.
Hey, are you okay?
That was a brand-new phone.
Yes, I'm fine.
I feel good.
-Huh?
-Good.
Okay, let's all drink!
-Hey, any song requests?
-Cheers!
Fine, I'll just take care of it.
I never thought
you would be attending this workshop.
Since your parents live nearby,
do they farm oriental melons?
Park Kyeong-nam definitely has
the makings of a star.
You can't be serious.
You saw him.
He went in without any hesitation
when everyone else was standing around.
Then he just left.
Women go crazy for that kind of thing.
Have a drink.
I'll go get soju.
As I turned into the alleyway
The alleyway
My heart was pounding
Was pounding
Curtains draped
Over your window…
Ms. Seo.
Yes?
What?
Is that water?
This?
It's soju.
Oh, it's soju.
Soju's not good though.
Huh?
Soju is not good.
This is also soju. The water's over there.
Thank you.
Seriously? He's a lightweight?
Hot!
Why don't these match?
The bottles and lids don't match.
What are you, a matchmaker?
Why are you trying to match them?
No, it's this bottle.
It's supposed to have a matching lid.
Hey. Look.
-Over there.
-What in the world?
I mean, there has to be a lid.
Hey, look!
Eun-ju, look at that!
This guy has a weird habit
when he's drunk.
Kyeong-nam. Let's get you to bed.
You don't get it. It needs to have a lid.
Yes, it does. God, you're heavy.
-We're seeing so many new sides of him.
-This is important.
Here. Careful.
Did you hear what I said?
Without a lid, something bad will happen.
-Sure, that's important.
-I'm serious.
Sleep, okay? Sleep.
-Hey, you guys. Sing a song.
-It really needs a lid.
-Sing a song.
-I'm okay.
-Well…
-Don't pick it up.
Sing a song!
Go on. Sing a song now.
-I really can't--
-Do it!
But after a long while
I was crying on my own
Feeling the pain
I once caused you
Would you…
The end.
I didn't know this song was so short.
Kyeong-nam's awake.
Feel better? You can go back to sleep.
I'm good.
My ears were hurting.
Your ears?
-What on earth is he on about?
-His ears?
Hey, your turn.
I told her not to date
someone from the office.
Mi-rae, aren't you glad you came?
Wasn't it so much fun?
Director Hwang,
that was the best workshop of my life.
-Don't skip these from now on.
-Of course I won't.
-Guys, wasn't that fun?
-Let's go in Kyeong-nam's car.
Dong-min!
We'll take the bus.
Please take Eun-ju home safely.
You can go in my car.
Yes! It'll be more comfortable.
He's okay with it.
-Come on!
-What?
-Get in.
-Hurry up!
I think I'll sit in the back.
What?
You getting in?
Yes. Okay.
You can drop me off here.
I'll get out here too.
Whoa, don't throw up in the car.
Get out of the car. Hurry!
I'll get out here too.
You don't live here.
I can take the subway. Thank you.
I'll drive you.
I'm headed that way anyway.
Get home safe. Kyeong-nam, thank you.
See you tomorrow.
Your diffuser has a really nice scent.
Just shut up.
I can smell alcohol on you.
You must've had too much.
What?
I didn't though. Did I?
Can I drop you off near Yongsan Station?
Yes.
But don't you live in Seongsu?
I do.
Then why…
I have a meeting with Hwany there.
On a Sunday?
Yes.
I thought you really cared about
work-life balance.
I don't want to get in the way
while he's trying to step up his game.
He's trying to step up his game?
I see.
How's Ms. Yun doing?
Mr. Hwang seemed worried about her.
Worried about what?
Sales, probably.
They dropped a lot last month, after all.
That was just a temporary dip
due to the coin event and her break.
That, and her title has low ratings,
so I suppose it's making him nervous.
I see.
Having said that, it looks like
Hwany will be doing the short story
that Ms. Yun was supposed to work on,
at the advertiser's request.
Can I drop you off right there?
Yes.
Why does Mr. Hwang keep talking to you
instead of telling me himself?
Who knows?
Thank you for the ride.
You don't have anything else to tell me?
I do.
What is it?
I like you.
What?
What did you say?
You heard me.
No, I don't think so.
I might have misheard you.
I said
I like you, Ms. Seo.
What? I mean, where is this coming from?
I should get going.
See you tomorrow.
What is he saying?
Seriously.
Is he actually crazy?
He's messing with me, right?
Wait, besides…
I saw him with Eun-ju last night.
That bastard!
Is he trying to date two girls at work?
I got rejected.
At first, I was just fangirling over him.
But it was late into the night,
I had a buzz going,
and he was right next to me,
so I just took a shot.
And?
He shot me down coldly.
I actually felt shot down.
So, do I just need to be aware of this?
Why don't you give it a thought?
About dating me, that is.
I don't think I can do that.
Do you not like me?
I don't particularly dislike you,
but I don't think
I'll ever come to like you.
Just a moment. Oh, my head…
Wow, he really is just built differently.
My phone broke, and my heart broke.
It was the worst workshop ever.
What?
So he actually meant what he told me?
-Cover me!
-What?
Why? What is it?
Why?
What are you doing?
Are you playing trains?
-I wanna play too!
-Off we go!
Let's get back to work.
I like it.
The readers would really like this part.
I liked the witty homage in the beginning,
and I also liked the art style.
It doesn't follow the trend,
but it has a rookie's originality.
In conclusion,
the readers will definitely like it.
I like you.
Get a grip!
-Take a short break?
-Sure.
Me too.
Push.
This is driving me crazy.
We're not meeting today either?
See you later. I'll leave work early.
Ms. Seo.
Yes?
Did I make a mistake?
Sorry?
I didn't think you'd avoid me.
Me? Avoid you? When did I ever…
Can I wait
for your answer?
Oh God…
Or
should I just give up?
Well, you know, I--
If you're seeing someone,
you can just tell me.
Well, I…
I am.
I am seeing someone right now.
So I'll pretend
I didn't hear what you said.
All right.
What?
I understand.
Asking someone out and giving up.
Why is everything so easy for him?
He's so full of himself.
PRODUCER PARK KYEONG-NAM
I can't tell what he's thinking.
Whatever.
So it's not just kumdo you're good at?
I'm good at everything.
Let me skate with you.
Try to keep up.
Eun-ho.
Someone asked me out.
Is it that jerk you always complain about?
I knew he was going to.
How did you know?
I didn't see it coming at all.
When I told him I had a boyfriend,
he just said, "All right."
Was he trying to feel me out?
Like, to see if I would fall for him?
He's so annoying.
You seem distracted by some other guy
when you're with me.
Are you jealous?
Am not.
I think you are.
You were being jealous, weren't you?
Am I a little prettier?
I like you.
Still got it.
You should try it.
I'm sure it'll look good on you.
Only heartbroken people
treat themselves like that.
I'm completely over it now, okay?
I'm not heartbroken.
I can tell from your spending spree.
You're so not over it.
I need to be prepared
for the new era, you know.
It would be such a shame
to let this face of mine waste away.
Whatever.
Hey, it's Seo Eun-ho.
What? Let me see.
-He's so handsome.
-Did you try this one?
-I did this one.
It's really good.
-Which one?
-This one.
-Did you see the Milky Way?
-Obviously.
-I wanna try this one too.
-The trip?
This one for me.
It starts raining all of a sudden…
He's so good-looking.
What is this?
Seo Eun-ho, in particular,
has been receiving rave reviews.
He's kind but sexy.
Strong, but you still want to protect him.
I got to meet the women
who fell in love with him.
K, an office worker, had this to say.
Reality doesn't matter to me now.
When I go on a date with him
for a few hours after work,
it feels as though
I went on a date in real life.
Scratch that.
It feels way better than that.
College student Eun-ho's
best five moments.
Five. Charismatically tying
your kumdo belt.
Don't you go easy on me.
Give everything you've got.
Four. Running in the sudden rain together,
like a scene out of a movie.
-Three.
-To you, am I still just an upperclassman?
-Two.
-The exam?
The day you first confirmed
your feelings for each other.
I blew it. Because of you.
One. The night of the trip.
The romantic moment of sitting together
and gazing at the sunset.
Office worker Eun-ho's best five moments.
-Five.
-Still as pretty as ever.
Four. Gently tying your apron,
unlike when he was a college student.
Three.
I didn't know back then
that I'd never forget about you.
What?
Where did he go?
You scared me.
Surprise.
Here.
What's with the flowers?
Is it a special day?
I just felt like
bringing you flowers today.
You don't like them?
I do. Thank you.
What's with you today?
You were quiet throughout dinner.
What do you mean?
Is everything okay?
Yeah. Everything's fine.
Mi-rae.
Yes?
I'm scared.
That you might leave me again.
Office worker Eun-ho's best five moments.
Two.
I'm scared. That you might leave me again.
Damn it.
I'm sorry. Let's talk about it next time.
Did I do something wrong?
It's not like that.
Look at me.
One. Pushing you against a wall
unexpectedly to kiss you.
A sexy side hidden
beneath his gentle demeanor.
This is just too much.
Eun-ho.
You didn't do anything wrong.
I'm the one who changed.
Now,
no matter what killer move you pull on me,
I can't get into this at all.
What do you mean by that?
This time, I'll tell you before I leave.
Tell me what?
Thank you for everything.
Take care.
No.
You sons of bitches.
How dare you screw with me like this!
Fine. I've had enough.
I'm canceling my sub right away.
You scared me!
How have you been?
Why are you here?
Tell me. What's wrong?
Do you not like Seo Eun-ho?
Then you can just move on to the next guy.
Are you here because I was about to
cancel my subscription?
Oh my.
What are you talking about?
Goodness! No, not at all.
Are you going to cancel?
I don't know.
Just tell me. If there's a problem,
we simply need to solve it together.
Why would you jump
to such extreme measures?
Tell me.
How many women is Seo Eun-ho seeing?
Do you really need to know that?
Yes. I really need to know.
All right.
Here.
CHOI SI-WOO
SEO EUN-HO
12,432 people.
What?
Now it's 12,434.
Twelve thousand…
Why did you have to ask?
That means he did and said the same things
to other women too.
And there are what, twelve thousand and…
What is it?
What? Did it just go up again?
Now it's 12,45…
I'm good now. Stop.
So are you saying
you don't like the fact that Seo Eun-ho
is available to other women as well?
Yes.
I mean…
My head gets it, but my heart…
But it can't be helped.
And if you think about it, it's natural.
It's not like this is an issue
that can be solved.
There is a solution.
What?
It can be solved.
I can match you up with a guy
only available to you.
As if that kind of guy even exists.
The number of men in Boyfriend on Demand
isn't 900 but 901, to be exact.
I'm saying we can generate
one custom-tailored boyfriend per account.
What do you mean by "custom-tailored"?
We'll generate a boyfriend
perfectly tailored for you and you alone.
Gu Yeong-il.
Gu Yeong-il?
Ms. Seo Mi-rae,
please take the survey to create
a custom-tailored boyfriend on BoD.
To do that,
we need to know you in more detail.
What kind of looks you like,
what kind of personality you like.
Whether you want to take the lead
or be led. We'll analyze everything.
Let's see.
"I like the uncomfortable feeling
of dating a heartthrob."
No.
"I prefer a man who's sexy at times
over a man who's sexy all the time."
"I'm attracted to men who show it
instead of saying it." Definitely.
There are so many of them.
Just how many are there?
"Please describe your ideal man in detail,
within 2,000 characters"?
Seriously?
Why are there so many?
How good is it anyway?
BOYFRIEND ON DEMAND 901
Gu Yeong-il is the champion of BoD.
I'm so proud of my fine taste!
Helped me get through the worst breakup.
A true lifesaver.
901 taught love to a lifelong single.
Gu Yeong-il alone is enough
to make me subscribe.
The man I didn't know I wanted.
He amazes me every day.
Optimization complete.
I don't know where I'm headed,
but waiting at the end of this road
is someone who's a perfect match for me.
What the heck?
Doors opening.
Hello.
Doors closing.
What are you looking for?
God, you scared me.
No, I just…
Ta-da!
It's this, right?
There we go.
Subtitle translation by: Daham Yoon