RTNNJ
GLORY
Good afternoon, madam.
Good. Hurry up!
-Okay,
-Enjoy your lunch.
Thanks!
SEOUL JOO GENERAL HOSPITAL
Yeo-jeong,
I'm not looking for a king.
I don't need a king
but the executioner who will join me
in my sword dance.
Your drink and salad.
Thanks.
CAFE GYODAE
You're not normal.
You call the headmistress as you wish.
Didn't you enjoy the walk in the park?
- Is this your lunch?
-Breakfast.
My heart is breaking.
- No matter how much I worked...
- I'm on a diet.
I need to lose four kilos
to fit in a bikini for Christmas in Guam.
-Good luck.
-Thanks.
Mom, I've decided.
-What?
- I won't be a professor.
That's fine.
- I will open a surgery.
- Great.
Have you decided so now?
Some time ago.
But now I decided to tell you.
RESIGNATION
- You're serious.
- I did.
Then do it.
I'm glad you didn't decide
stay in the army.
This is a better solution.
Where will you be? In Apgujeong? Cheongdam?
No, in Semyeong.
There's a person I'm interested in living in Semyeong.
Are you seeing each other?
Not yet.
Do you know such people?
She is completely calm, as if she is under water,
but for her sake I would go into a storm.
- Is she a fisherman?
- That's a metaphor.
You don't do this to make money
or to heal the sick,
but because of the girl?
And you wrote that here?
Jesus. I will write a new resignation letter.
Holy God, how you shame me!
Are you sure you're on a diet?
I used to believe in all the gods of the world.
I knelt down and prayed
before all the gods who have abandoned me,
like a sick woman who has no help,
so he wanders looking for hope.
I wonder where you are now and what you are praying for.
Sew this into Ye-sola's bag.
Do it yourself. No one can touch it.
Thanks, mom.
Did you just find out now?
that she became a rascal
Ye-sola's classmate?
How incompetent you are!
Come back home.
I'll handle it.
Whose son-in-law was he?
in the Ministry of Education?
Don't.
What if you challenge her,
so gadura tells everything?
What if everyone finds out?
I'm afraid, mom.
Why is that zero so scary?
Not her! I'm afraid for Ye-sol!
If everyone finds out, Ye-sol will find out too.
Maybe he doesn't know now,
but what if he finds out when he grows up?
I'm afraid of that.
Yeon-jin.
Look at me.
I already told you
not to look back.
The solution is never in the past.
It's always in the future.
Such is life.
Do you understand?
FLIGHT SCHEDULE
OCTOBER 31 - NOVEMBER 6
Over time I understood
that God does not exist.
It just pretends to exist.
You should pray to me, Yeon-jin.
Because your salvation depends on me.
He's so handsome.
Is that your boyfriend? He is young.
- Bring the coffee, Mr. Kang.
-What?
Yes, of course.
I wouldn't, thanks.
It's not difficult for me.
That's your problem.
You don't understand anything until someone tells you.
Do you want to tell me something?
No, nothing.
I know you are a great teacher.
I just wanted to have a coffee.
Call me. It is urgent.
Is your boyfriend good?
It sure is.
I don't know why,
but I thought you liked older people.
Yeah, you're cheating on him?
I'm kidding.
- Do you have a girlfriend?
- Do I look like that?
No, not in the least.
Why?
Nobody told you?
Then I won't say anything either.
We don't know each other.
You must be the type of person
which angers others with words.
You make yours uncomfortable.
What?
You know what, Miss Moon?
You're lucky to be a woman.
If you were a man, I would hit you hard.
Seriously?
You look like a man who only hits women.
I'm just kidding too!
It sounded lovely from your mouth,
so I decided to try.
I don't know where Son Myeong-o is.
I knew how to lose him because he drives a motorcycle,
but in a day or two he would appear at home.
But after this day
he wasn't at home or at the golf club.
Was he in a travel agency?
That.
Maybe they gave him a mountain of money,
so he went over to their side.
Maybe he bought a ticket that day
and left the country. That would make sense.
I'll check with the agency.
Let's wait until the weekend.
Good.
If he's not dead,
it is not our goal to find out
where Son Myeong-o disappeared to.
Dead?
Killed?
I mean to say…
Are you saying he might be dead?
It is possible.
- I'll get back to you.
-Wait.
If you are…
by any chance
did it…
You ask if I killed Son Myeong-o?
If by any chance you did,
i should know about it
to be able to prepare…
I didn't.
And if I did, you shouldn't know.
What?
Our deal is very simple.
You will do what I ask,
and I am what you are looking for.
That's how we help each other.
We've gotten too close, Ms. Kang.
Dad has arrived, Luje.
I know dad was gone for a long time.
Sorry.
What is it?
Luje!
Hell!
Why are you like that?
Dad apologized.
I know you're mad that I didn't come home.
What is it?
Hell.
What the hell?
Where are you, cunt?
The cunt was here.
That fucking dog is out of his mind.
I don't mean you.
Let me ask you something.
Where have you been?
Did you bite him?
If you just stood and watched,
I will be disappointed.
SPECTATOR REGISTRATION PAGE
VIOLENCE IN SCHOOL
NO ANNOUNCEMENTS
She is a forecaster,
and he doesn't know how to write a script.
Even novices know that.
Jaepyeong has another commercial.
Are we?
Oh, did you hear that?
You were loud.
They say the truth speaks loudly, Yeon-jin.
Are we in the series Editorial?
Su-mi.
You should listen to the stylist.
He says that my husband is playing the commercial again.
You know what that means?
The station pays me
only 2.2 million won per month,
and my husband spends here
220 million on advertisements.
You are still young.
How long will it take?
Will you be young next year? Or a year behind?
You're asking for trouble!
No matter how much collagen you injected into your face,
you will never replace me.
You drooling bastard.
So, Su-mi,
don't challenge me
because I will cancel your contract with the station.
Have a good time.
What about Dong-eun?
Did you discover anything?
It is not easy to find personal information.
I had to investigate another case
to reach them.
JAE-JUN
That's why I called you.
The world has changed, Yeon-jin.
It's not the same as it was 18 years ago.
That's why I pay you more than 18 years ago.
I hear you bought a hotel
in the name of the younger sister.
Do you have many guests?
Thank you for your concern.
Remember you owe me.
I hired people.
I'll let you know when I find out.
It seems that lately
you have a lot of work to do.
Thank you for your concern.
I checked the map of Myeong-o.
He bought a one-way ticket to Vladivostok.
Nothing more.
But he did not board the plane.
I also checked the hotel
in which he reserved a room. He didn't come.
So he didn't leave Korea.
That's right.
Why are you asking about him? Something wrong?
That.
But I don't know if he just disappeared
or someone killed him.
At least you have enough black, Dong-eun.
Yes, I have.
It means that Myeong-o has cracked.
SD cards are consumables anyway.
Is it time to find the real butterfly
which will flap its wings for me?
Butterfly with silk wings
which will cause a hurricane.
I know who it could be, Yeon-jin.
The wires are installed! I'm turning it on!
GO PARK IN SEMYEONG
On behalf of the city, thank you.
Thank you for staying up late, Mr. Ha.
It's early, not late.
Truth.
Brilliantly done.
I will look around a bit more, to absorb everything.
Of course. Here you go.
Fuck, Myeong-o!
I have no more ice or drugs!
Where are you? Let's meet. Will you come to me?
Shall we meet alone? Why?
Come on, read my message!
Read it!
Which ring is better?
Gad didn't come to work again.
He stole my clothes and watches.
First, second or third ring?
Seriously? What hour?
I paid in advance.
I don't care what you screwed up.
Work is work.
Are you interested in another design?
Big stones
can be uncomfortable to wear.
Not.
I like big ones, I told you.
I love everything big.
Tae-uk!
You said you'd be late. You're early.
They are all beautiful. I haven't chosen it yet.
Leave us alone.
Didn't I tell you?
that you wear high heels when you're with me?
I like it when you're tall!
If you carry you, I will not be taller than you.
You have to accept my height.
My legs hurt from yesterday's flight.
I'll wear them next time.
I'm not going to officially propose to you.
You wanted a bigger stone than your friend.
There. That one is the biggest.
Seriously?
For God's sake, it's even bigger! Great!
That's not all.
I have a message from mom.
My mom loves monastery food.
Don't tell her you eat meat.
I know!
I don't really like meat either.
INVITATION
MRS KANG
You have to turn!
There is a car behind you that is following you!
What are you doing here?
That doesn't matter now!
For God's sake! I do this every day.
I should have known they would try it too.
I will try to remove them somehow.
Leave it to me. Don't expose yourself.
Do you want to die?
It doesn't stop like that!
Sorry. are you ok
My neck! My back! What will you do?
We have work to do.
Call the police
or pay me in cash. Make up your mind.
You gave me the wrong choice.
People usually call security, not the police.
If it is rented, rent-a-car.
Look at you wise men!
He's hired, but I love him!
If you wreck a man's car,
you need to call the police
or give him cash.
First you wrecked my car,
and now you're holding me back.
What the hell is going on?
We both have work to do. I'll give you money.
-Give me your account number.
- It's not cash.
Give me your number.
When I call you, bring the cash.
Are you injured? Let me see.
You were supposed to follow Jae-jun today.
Why were you behind me?
Why did you follow me?
You ask why I followed you?
Do you doubt me now?
I'm just being careful.
You are not scared?
I can tell your husband
that you asked me to kill him.
I can tell him everything.
You must have remembered that.
Jeon Jae-jun was in front of the school.
He looked at Ye-sol then left.
As I followed him,
I found myself behind you.
That's when I saw you.
I was glad.
And then I saw the car.
I probably could
to think so.
But I didn't think like that.
I didn't think of anything.
I have enough to do
with camera and driving.
Get out.
Jae-jun goes to the restaurant regularly
at Mangwon Market.
They sell cabbage from Haenam.
Eat it now.
He was in the car. He has already matured.
Ma'am!
I can tell more people about you.
Yeon-jin, Jae-jun, Sa-ri.
I was happy
when I bought cabbage.
Because of you, I started dreaming again.
I dream of dinner with Sun...
Not about dinner
where you just throw food in your mouth.
About the real dinner,
with jigae  and fried eggs,
which we can eat slowly.
I dream of such an evening.
I cheer up when I think about it.
You're thinking about other things though.
Yes, you are right.
Sorry.
Why am I always like this?
Because you are a good person.
I made a mistake today.
I will make sure your dream comes true.
Thanks for the kimchi, but I won't take it.
"Mrs" and "Ms Kang".
That's what we call each other.
How to call a person differently
with whom am I planning murders?
DOAMSA
Yeon-jin, you must be aware
that we bring you darkness.
We know how dark the end will be.
The person you called cannot answer.
Yeon-jin doesn't answer?
Neither did Myeong-o.
Maybe they are together.
Maybe he sleeps with others.
Watch your language!
I wanted to say
that both do not appear.
- I'm just saying.
- Hye-jeong.
Want to be a badass? Do it right.
That's how you'll become a successful badass.
Now you are sloppy.
I'm leaving. I have a flight tomorrow.
The little one.
Yeon-jin's daughter.
-Ye-salt.
- What about her?
Those are Yeon-jin's shoes.
I bought them in London.
I didn't know she had them too.
What about Ye-sol?
When is his birthday?
Ye-sol?
Do you know or not?
I don't know when her birthday is,
but when Yeon-jin got pregnant,
mom told her
that she must give birth before Chuseok
so that the child would be rich.
Why do you ask?
I wonder if she is my daughter.
You must be joking.
When the sun doesn't set in the summer,
the nights become bright.
It's called white night.
That's right! Nights become as bright as day.
Did you know that it is during the white nights?
polar night on the other side of the hemisphere?
It would be awful if the nights lasted that long.
The opposite of "white night"
is "polar night".
The nights are terribly long,
completely different from white nights.
Did you last week
had white or polar nights?
I hope you get through it wisely
next week. I'm Park Yeon-jin.
I am Hwang Kwang-hee.
Park Yeon-jin is with us,
a wave among prognosticators
and the queen of wicked comments.
We'll be back after the commercial.
The ceiling is high here.
The skylight lets in a lot of light.
It looks even better at night.
It looks great. I'll take that.
It has just been built and is close to the station.
It is beautiful during the day and at night.
Below is the yoga studio, and above is the gym.
People who work out here
they often get injured.
An ideal place for a doctor's office.
What kind of doctor are you?
It would be great if you were an orthopedist.
Plastic surgeon.
Even better!
People who exercise
she'll want to touch up her eyelids!
It's nice. I take it.
- Are you really a doctor?
-Please?
You are so determined, like a con man.
And you're still hot.
So listen.
I don't want to brag,
but my nickname is Beauty.
People are surprised that the doctor looks like this.
I must not tell them that I graduated early
nor that I am a member of Mensa.
I liked you better when you were silent.
Schedule for next week and mail.
And the letter that arrived by express delivery.
Express delivery?
SON MYEONG-O
The mobile device is switched off. Leave…
Who came?
I haven't seen you in a long time.
Three years, right?
Last time I saw you
at the opening of your father-in-law's office.
Looks like you didn't come to play.
I'm curious why you came.
I can't reach Mr. Son Myeong-o.
Where is he?
Are you looking for him too?
I can't get it either.
Why do you ask?
- Do you want a cigarette?
- I don't smoke.
How can I reach him?
You still haven't told me why you're looking for him.
I need to talk to him about something.
Give me his address
or a relative's number.
Did you get something too?
You did.
What did you get? How does the bastard threaten you?
What did you get from him?
This conversation is going nowhere.
Let's let each other know when we find it.
You think you won't be the first to find it?
He's your friend after all.
He's not my friend.
Just an employee.
Well, good. I have some work to do.
The mobile device is switched off.
Leave a message.
Myeong-o, you fucking stink.
I'm not the only one you sent something to
and who are you blackmailing.
But what are you threatening Ha Do-yeong with?
Some woman?
Or a girl?
If you're me and Do-yeong
put in the same bin because of Ye-sol,
I'll kill you, you piece of shit.
What is it?
It's really nice.
Why?
You won? Great!
Play with me.
Come on, come on.
Very convenient.
That's the meaning of goa.
I have to post this.
Check the bumper,
pay at the office and pick up the key.
-Thanks.
-Not at all.
I was thinking about something.
We didn't finish the game properly.
We have to count the points.
What's going on?
are you ok What was it?
Sorry.
are you ok
What was it?
Come in, quick.
What was it? Are you not well?
Come in.
I haven't received all the furniture yet.
I'll get you some water. Sit down.
What is this place like?
What's going on?
Did I call you at the wrong time?
Did you move?
A friend opened a practice here
and makes a lot of money,
so I came too.
At least that's what I meant to tell you.
Did I mess up?
Do you want to count the points?
I don't want to lose without knowing why.
I thought you would come like that.
Cunning.
You asked me where I was going.
And why am I doing all this.
It's a very long story.
There is nothing beautiful about her.
Do you want to hear it?
There are white and polar nights.
My life is made of white.
The sun always shines on me.
Of course.
Why do you say that?
Are you going to a party?
Your mother is going to work.
He is going to an important awards ceremony.
That's so cool!
I can't wait to be like mom.
I will wear such necklaces
and beautiful dresses.
I want to try this one. She is beautiful.
It's heavy.
Expensive jewelry, watches,
handbags and cars.
It's all hard.
Expensive coats, dresses and heels
they are very light.
Good?
Good!
No worries, Ye-sol.
I will not disappear over the horizon.
No matter what.
PATERNITY TEST
PROBABILITY OF PATERNITY: 99.999 %
Well, of course.
That's why she's so beautiful.
Shit.
HA YE-SOL
Good afternoon, Hye-jeong.
Hi.
Someone from Information was here.
- They found my cell phone?
- That's not why he came.
It's thin. Urgent delivery for you.
Urgent?
Now you know.
I dedicated my whole life to revenge.
And you won't stop?
You're better than them, Dong-eun.
I don't intend to be better.
I'm getting worse every day.
When you're done with revenge,
and your world will be destroyed.
I envy you, Yeo-jeong.
You must have had an idyllic childhood.
You grew up and became good and happy.
Sometimes you sound naive,
but you have no problems in life.
You saw my scars.
Can you remove them?
How long has it been?
You made such an expression
after just one hand.
And despite that
do you want me to stop?
The nights were white,
and sometimes polar.
They are guilty?
That's what they did to you?
Those bastards?
I'm already devastated. I have no more dignity.
Come back.
I would like to remain faithful
to his anger and vice.
I will do it.
I will be your executioner.
I will dance with a sword.
Tell me.
What's first?
How do I do that?
Who do you want...
to kill first?
Subtitle translation: Davor Fröbe