(Previous)
There's something I must tell you.
What… is it?
Teh's in love with Fah.
I'm craving a chill barbecue night.
Sure. Just name the date.
P'Toh...
Why is my heart racing?
I think… I'm really into you.
Jimmy likes you.
But I don't like him.
Where's Fah?
He's been out since 4.
Something about catching the sunrise.
How did you know?
I ran into him while I was jogging.
I thought you guys woke up together.
I couldn't sleep. New bed, I guess.
So I just got up to work out.
Hey, there's a court here.
Wanna shoot some hoops?
Let's go.
Damn it, Jimmy. What the hell?
My shirt's ruined.
My bad.
Didn't know my own strength.
What were you staring at?
Nothing.
Bull crap.
You're acting sketchy.
What are you hiding from me?
Come on! I'm not hiding anything.
I'm going to take a shower.
"Love Alert" (Episode 3)
Teh, what happened to your shirt?
I just tripped.
Give it here.
I'll wash it before the stain sets.
You two go shower.
We'll check out when Fah's back.
I've already packed.
Yes.
You can shower first.
Let me help you.
It's fine. I've got it.
You can't win against my strength.
Just tell me... where you want me to...
"scrub" hard.
Need a hand?
What are you after?
Why ask that?
I just want to know.
Well…
I'm just a good friend…
A helpful person…
And someone who has… feelings for you.
There's one rule of mine you should know.
What rule?
I don't…
do “seconds.”
I'll admit, you were great last night,
but a rule…
is a rule.
Understood?
Fah,
let me get that for you.
It's fine.
Where's P'Toh?
In his room.
Okay.
How was it?
How was what?
You and Fah on the very first night.
You heard us?
I knew you liked him,
but I think it was too fast.
Who told you… that I like him?
Jimmy did.
He told me that, so I played
wingman for you at the party.
I even cleared my
schedule just to go on that trip.
I thought you'd used the
chance to flirt a bit.
Didn't expect you to go all in like that.
P'Toh,
are you sick?
You're burning up.
I'm not sure.
I've been having chills.
It's cold indoors and hot outdoors.
You should take meds before it gets worse.
I'll go grab some.
Hang on a sec.
What's your problem?
Did you tell P'Toh that I like Fah?
So what? I just used your name as a cover.
What? You bastard!
- How could you...
- I like Fah.
I had to do whatever it took.
At least…
I made that trip happened.
Even if I didn't get anywhere with him.
Or do you like him too?
Something felt off back at the resort.
That bull crap about not sleeping...
and meeting Fah to take photos.
It was suspicious.
What are you hiding from me?
Well?
Answer me!
I'm not hiding anything.
Just…
don't use me as your excuse again, okay?
Crappy friend.
Fah.
What are you up to?
Testing a new cream
formula for sensitive skin.
And what brings you here?
Looking for my friends.
But I can't find them.
How long are you going to stare?
It's good you're here.
I need a guinea pig.
No reaction. This formula works.
How did you know I have a sensitive skin?
You got a whole rash just from a mosquito
bite that night. Of course I knew.
You're quite observant.
In case you didn't hear me clearly…
I. Don't. Do. Seconds.
Now, leave.
I need to focus on my work.
Leave.
I said I need to concentrate.
Wait,
can I suggest something about the cream?
Go on.
I think…
the texture and properties are great.
But maybe add a little fragrance?
That would be better.
The chemical smell is too strong.
Thanks for the feedback. I'll look into it.
Why isn't he picking up?
P'Toh.
Oh, Jimmy.
How did you get in?
Why didn't you call first?
I climbed over the wall.
I called you like hundred times,
but you never answered.
I took some allergy meds and passed out.
Phone was on silent.
P'Toh! You're burning up!
Let's go to the hospital.
I'm fine.
It's just a little flu.
I still have to check
the orders for the cafe.
Are you serious?
You're sick and still thinking about work?
Jimmy? What are you doing?
Taking you to your bed.
Jimmy!
Hold on tight.
I'm quite okay now.
You're still sick and don't
even go to the hospital.
You're so stubborn.
You're treating me like a kid.
I'll treat you even more like one.
Jimmy?
What are you doing?
Wiping you down.
It's okay.
I can do it myself.
Are you shy?
Come on, we're both guys.
Jimmy!
What the heck?
I'll make this less awkward.
I'll take my shirt off,
and you take yours off.
Fair and square.
Do it.
Bastard Jim.
Even when you're sick,
you still smell so good.
You...
P'Toh.
How are you? Feeling well now?
I took those meds and it
felt like a tranquilizer shot.
Didn't know what happened.
Jim was looking for you.
He saw me burning up,
so he wiped me down.
I feel much better now.
Your brother's so stubborn.
He didn't want to go to the hospital,
so I had to give him a quick sponge bath.
Thanks.
And why are you here?
You forgot your shoes in my car.
I just returned them to you.
P'Toh, your brother's here.
Well… I'm leaving now.
Thanks, Jim.
Get some meds for P'Toh. I'm going.
I'll be back.
Hey.
I put your shoes there.
Jimmy.
What?
Thanks for looking after my brother.
And…
And what?
Sorry for snapping at you about him.
You brother-obsessed freak.
Your brother is like my brother.
I never betray anyone.
You're my best friend.
Yeah.
Get meds for P'Toh, or
he'll do his work again.
You'd better go.
I'm off.
Hey, safe driving.
Yep!
You're too slow for me, traitor.
How's my cooking?
Delicious.
Didn't know my brother was a pro.
Nice work, YouTube chef.
Naturally.
Just order whatever you want.
Why tire yourself out?
And…
don't forget to take
your meds after the meal.
P'Toh.
Did Jimmy just wipe you down?
Where is this coming from?
I'm just worried about you.
You saw it. It was nothing.
Why don't you trust us?
I don't want you to fall for Jimmy
and see you get hurt.
I've been his friend for a long time.
I know exactly what he's capable of.
Why worry about me?
You should worry about yourself.
And what's wrong with me?
Do you realize you haven't
been yourself since the trip?
What do you mean?
I don't know.
But I know you're hiding something from me.
Right?
No! I'm gonna wash dishes now.
So suspicious.
Tell me when you're ready.
“What are you doing?”
(Teh: What are you doing?)
(Teh: What are you doing? (Read))
(Fah: Hanging out with friends.)
“Have fun.
Let me know if you need a ride home.”
(Teh: Have fun. Let me know
if you need a ride home.)
(Jimmy: What are you doing?)
(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
What's up?
I'm thinking of asking Fah out tonight.
Don't bother. He's out with his friends.
How would you know that?
I mean…
It's Friday.
Everyone's out with their friends, right?
True.
I'll try my luck anyway. I messaged
him, but he hasn't read it yet.
Just leave him alone.
He's busy with his friends.
I'm heading to bed. Feeling a bit drowsy.
I might have caught P'Toh's cold.
You started this game, Teh.
Get well soon.
I'm worried about you.
Take care of this little guy.
It's much better behaved than I am.
Jimmy.
Guess who?
What's my prize if I win?
Guess…
Guess first. Then we'll talk.
Plaifah.
Ugh, No fun. How do you know?
I remember your scent.
Did you graduate from the K-9 academy?
Give me your paw.
Happy now?
So, what brings you here?
Remember when you were my guinea pig…
I mean, my victim…
Guinea pig was right.
You're actually pretty funny.
Anyway, I got a perfect
score on that formula.
So I thought…
I'd treat you to a meal.
Pick any place you want.
It's on me.
Deal.
Can I really do that?
Yes, you can.
I'll help you.
I let you choose a restaurant,
but you chose hard labor.
We can go to a restaurant anytime.
But having a meal cooked
by you? That's a rare chance.
True.
You're the first person
to ever set foot in here.
Really?
Usually, I'd go to their place or a hotel.
I don't like people intruding
on my personal space.
They'll get ahead of themselves.
I'm truly honored.
Whatever.
If it wasn't for my cream,
you'd never be here.
I'm so grateful. Thank you so much.
That's my head.
Stop playing around.
Are you going to finish that?
Your chopping is sloppy. Can you even cook?
Keep chopping them.
P'Toh does all the cooking.
I just eat whatever he makes.
If you want my cooking,
you have to earn it.
Get back to chopping.
We're making curry, not mashed potatoes.
Here's your coffee, mister customer.
In the cafe's cup.
Thank you.
The coffee's great as always.
And the cup…
has a drawing of me on it.
I was thinking of drawing the customers
on every cup when it's not too busy.
What do you think?
It's a good idea.
It can be your cafe's signature.
But can your “staff” draw like you do?
That's the hard part.
It's delicious.
Are you flattering me?
I bet it's not as good as Toh's.
It's a different kind of delicious.
Smooth answer.
Actually,
I wanted to say…
It's as tasty as the chef.
Watch it.
See?
I knew I'd get that reaction.
I might not be good at drawing like you do,
but I want them to have a partner.
That…
That was my first kiss…
I'm not sure how to…
It's okay.
I'll take the lead.
What's on your mind?
Remember when you covered my eyes?
I asked what I'd get if I won,
and you told me to guess right first.
Yeah, and I treated you to dinner.
That was for the cream. This is different.
What are you asking for?
Can you drop the…
“no seconds” rule?
I'm really into you.
But I'm a man of my word.
Then…
I'm sorry...
But every rule…
has an exception.
How can I say that I slept with
the guy my friend has feelings for?
Damn it!
Jimmy likes you.
But I don't like him.
Fah doesn't like Jimmy back anyway.
Screw it. I'll apologize to Jimmy
after I can win Fah over.
(Next Episode) I hope you'll do the same
for me. Or at least… don't break my heart.
Punch me if you have the balls!
You bastard!
I also hope that you'll…
stay away from Fah.
If you don't want your brother
suicidal from a broken heart,
you'd better keep your mouth shut.
I'm telling you again.
Jimmy's incapable of loving anyone.