♪I want to hold the hand ♪
♪Inside you ♪
♪I want to take the breath that's true ♪
♪I look to you and I see nothing ♪
♪I look to you to see the truth ♪
♪Some kind of night into your darkness ♪
♪Fade into you ♪
♪Strange you never knew ♪
♪I think it's strange you never knew ♪
♪Fade into you ♪
Here you go.
Hi, welcome to Malone's. I'm Hannah.
What can I get started for you guys today?
Hannah Wells?
Yeah. Yeah, that's me.
Have we met?
Actually, could we maybe
sit in another section?
Uh, we're pretty slammed at the moment,
but I promise I'll take good care of you.
Maybe even throw in
a slice of pie on the house.
I-I-I have a girlfriend, so...
You know, actually, we all do.
Oh, okay. Um...
Look, I was just trying to get your order,
if you need a minute.
Yeah, give us a minute. Thanks.
Sean.
Oh, shit. Uh, hi.
She's not working today, is she?
I mean, I know she has
Movement for Actors on Tuesday.
She's-- She's not working today.
Good. I just really miss
Della's fries, you know?
Yeah, I-I do.
I miss Tucker's salmon.
- Uh, Garrett and I...
- Broke up.
Yeah, I heard.
It's all over Fifth Line.
Plus the...
The what?
Uh, I'm not sure it's real.
It's not real.
Just a thing a guy said to me in class.
- I'm sure Garrett wouldn't...
- Sean.
Hannah.
What are you talking about?
Uh...
- Is Garrett in there?
- Uh, yeah.
But I don't think you should go in there--
Hannah!
Hannah, wait!
Oh, my God!
Well, well, Wellsy.
Have you made a wrong turn, or...?
Um...
Have you seen Garrett?
No, not since this morning.
Uh, Simms says that he's, um...
- Fuck, in here.
- Wellsy?
Okay, you have officially
stepped over the line.
Well, this is gonna be good.
You're so far over the line,
I can't even see this stupid line.
A campus-wide hands-off law?
You broke up with me.
And why are you in a suit?
- Hannah...
- No, sorry.
You cannot go around campus
telling guys you'll beat them up
for speaking to me.
Are you insane?
With that masochist--
Sorry, misogynist...
Sorry, I can't even think straight.
There are too many penises in this room.
- It is a men's locker room.
-  Okay.
Garrett, I really can't have my customers
be afraid of speaking to me.
I work for tips.
I never said any of that.
For fuck's sake, someone obviously
knows what's going on here.
Stuebs said Garrett was gonna
beat anyone up if they hit on Hannah.
I didn't say that, Dean said it.
You gotta be fucking kidding.
I said he'd lose his shit, numb nuts.
Losing your shit is different
than beating somebody up.
He kinda did, though, right?
Just fix it, okay?
Sure, yeah.
Sorry, Wellsy.
Look, I would never tell anyone
to stay away from you.
You should be with
whoever you want to be with.
Yeah, thank you.
Bye.
It's our understanding that Coach Jensen
has already suspended you for four games
following last week's altercation?
Yes, ma'am.
We support that,
and we appreciate you
taking responsibility for your actions.
However, in light
of your past indiscretions,
we simply can't let this slide.
What past indis...?
Like tha--?
Are you familiar with the NCAA bylaw
that requires student athletes to maintain
their amateur player status?
- Excuse me, that wasn't a--
- Just answer the question.
Yes, I'm aware.
According to this video posted on your own
social media account,
it appears you participated
in a professional Bruins practice.
That video was taken after a practice.
Perhaps, but that is not at all clear
in what we see here.
How would it look if we were to bend
the rules for you, Mr. Graham?
The video was posted
prior to the start of your season,
which means Briar University
rostered an ineligible player.
It is therefore our ruling that Briar
forfeits all games played thus far.
- What? You-You-You can't do that.
- Garrett.
- Which takes your current standing
from 13 wins, 3 losses, and 1 tie,
to 0 wins, 17 losses, and 0 ties.
They're gonna fucking hate me.
They're gonna be upset. Yeah.
Why'd you do it, Garrett?
The Bruins invited me.
That's not what this is about.
Not really.
Why did you attack him like that?
It's not my story to tell, Coach.
Okay.
What kind of hockey player
do you want to be?
The hothead who hit Delaney?
I have no interest in coaching that guy.
I want to coach players
who love the game the way I do.
Who go out on the ice because every
fiber of their being wants to be there.
You gotta love it, Garrett.
Do you love it?
Then do me a favor.
Figure that out.
Dead last?
Oh, we can't be dead last.
- Dead last.
- That's it.
That's my senior year down the drain.
Not necessarily.
You explain to me how we make
the Frozen Four from last place.
- Yeah, you're right. No Garrett.
- No Birdie.
Fucking concussion.
- Joe Rogers.
- He's not ready.
- But if he--
- Nope.
Yeah, he's not ready.
How many games do we have to win?
-  Every fucking game.
- Or tie.
We can't win every fucking game.
- With three-fifths of a starting line?
- Garrett will be back.
- Garrett's the reason we're in this.
All right? This is on us.
We have to fix it.
The only way to get a shot
at the Frozen Four
is if we are first in the conference,
and to do that, we need new blood.
Tuck, you and I can hold it down
without a strong center,
but we need a solid D-line.
Dean, you can't do it alone.
We need a new Birdie.
There was this kid
at open tryouts last year.
Remember? Tore up the ice.
Crazy fast defenseman.
Yeah, um... Hunter something, right?
Yeah. Davenport. Hunter Davenport.
Fuck no.
- What?
- No.
Fuck that guy.
Why, because he out-skated you?
- He didn't out-skate me.
- No, he kind of did, bro.
Jensen offered him a spot on the team,
and he turned it down.
Maybe he had a good reason.
Yeah, the reason is
that he's a selfish dick
with a piss-poor attitude,
- and I'm not fucking playing with him.
-  But...
Just drop it.
I'm serious.
I'll talk to Rogers.
I'll get him ready.
It's over.
Work, study, finals,
the semester, all of it.
I'm free.
Okay, is that...
Good? Bad?
Sorry, your line read is so confusing.
It...
I-I don't know.
Ah.
You can't distract yourself anymore.
I can't distract myself anymore.
Yeah, you gotta be sad, babe.
That's part of it.
No. Garrett's not sad.
He's totally fine not invoking
a campus-wide hands-off policy.
Okay, well, gentle reminder,
we didn't want him to have done that.
- It's like wildly problematic.
- I know. I know.
But, yeah, if he had,
it would mean he misses me,
and he's miserable, too.
And I really want him
to be miserable, too.
- Is that shitty?
- No, it's like Breakup 101.
How'd you get over Sean so fast?
You were sad for, like, a day,
and then, you were fine.
Teach me your ways.
I...
started having fun.
- Wait, you had a fling?
- No.
You had a fling, and you didn't tell me?
No, okay?
A fling is like a mini relationship.
It's like a gateway drug.
I... am through with all that.
It's too much pressure.
I am just being single and hooking up.
Both of the things, none of the stress,
and that's what you should be doing.
You've been so focused on school and work
and the showcase and Garrett.
Like, just lower the stakes.
Have fun?
Have fun.
Do stuff just 'cause you want to.
Well, can sleep be fun?
Sleep is self-care. We'll allow it.
Yeah, if I go to bed now,
I could sleep for a full eight hours.
Dream big, Hannah.
You could sleep for nine hours.
Ugh, that sounds glorious.
- Oh, shit. Al.
-  Hey.
Okay.
Oh! Oh, my God.
- Hi.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I, um...
I'm fine.
Just... need you to sit.
I came to say...
Okay, what's-- what's going on?
You may have noticed
that it's been a second
since we slept together.
I have noticed, and let me be
the first to say I'm not crazy about it.
Yeah, it's because I had a revelation.
Uh...
We need to sleep with other people.
We've always said that
we can sleep with other people.
Right, of course. You're Six Flags.
But when's the last time
someone other than me
actually got on this particular
roller coaster?
- Shit.
- Exactly, yeah.
So, um...
Like, this thing between us...
- It's fun.
- Agreed.
But it can't be a relationship.
Sure.
Just need to lower the stakes
a little on us.
Sleep with other people, so we can
sleep with each other, as well.
- I'm not tracking the logic here.
- Just have sex with someone.
Are you in or are you out, Di Laurentis?
A sexy homework assignment.
I'm in, Allie Cat.
I am so in.
Good.
Okay, bye.
- So, we're not...?
- Just text me when it's done.
♪To fall in love with someone else
it's such a bitter taste ♪
♪Too cold to stand I need a hand
in crawling out your grave ♪
♪So I can get up and start living ♪
♪Too busy missing you ♪
♪Too busy missing ♪
♪Page one ♪
♪It's just the prologue ♪
♪Setting the stage
for all that's to happen ♪
♪Then on to the first chapter ♪
♪Everyone's happy ♪
♪For shadowing impending disaster ♪
♪Then girl meets boy ♪
♪It's awkward, confusing ♪
♪Can't tell if it's love or it's hate ♪
♪When hands graze ♪
♪Reaching for something ♪
♪Forgettably dull and mundane ♪
♪Now it's a love story ♪
♪Of epic proportion ♪
♪The likes of which never's been told ♪
♪Two hearts beating as one ♪
♪Ran right into the sun ♪
♪Oh, what would I give to go back ♪
♪Back to page one ♪
Hey, which light came on first?
The squiggly one? I don't know.
The s--
What? Hey, could you show me?
I would, but I can't get oil
on my new favorite outfit.
No.
No way. No, absolutely not.
They sent you so much cool shit.
- I told you to stop opening my mail.
- That box has been in the truck for days.
Days. It's practically
begging to be opened.
And it's a good thing I did.
Because look what I found.
Who says print media's dead?
- Toss it.
- Absolutely not.
Okay, I finally found them.
Ian's little's best friend's girlfriend
is in American Studies with him.
And?
And I really don't think
it's a good idea, bro.
What's not a good idea?
- Don't worry about it.
- Hunter Davenport.
Oh. To take Birdie's spot?
- See what you did?
-  That'll be messy.
- I love it.
- Wait, why messy?
Well, doesn't he hate Dean?
Okay, I'll bite.
What do you know?
Well, they're both bougie bitches
who vacation in the Hamptons,
so it could be any number of things.
All I know for sure is Hunter
went to high school with Dean's sister.
Fuck. Summer?
The one and only.
- That's not good, man.
- Look, okay, I don't care.
If we're gonna have a shot at fixing
Garrett's mess, we need him.
- You tracked him down, yeah?
- Yeah.
Good.
Let's reach out.
♪Spare myself of this ache ♪
♪How could anyone dare
to love again?♪
♪I'm raising my walls ♪
♪So I never fall ♪
♪Into another love story ♪
Hi.
What is that? It's beautiful.
Uh, it's just a song I wrote
in high school.
Okay, Taylor Swift.
Those lyrics are insane.
Uh, yeah, well, they used to be easier.
I felt things.
I wrote them.
Well, some of the best songs ever
were written after a breakup.
Maybe this is what you need
to bust through your writer's block.
Yeah, I...
I-I think it's about more
than that, actually.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Um...
Um, you know when you meet someone,
and you don't quite
get their name at first,
then you start seeing them all the time,
and you've got inside jokes,
and it just becomes really awkward
to ask what their name is?
- My literal nightmare, yes. Go on.
- Um...
Uh...
What if it's your best friend?
And she doesn't know
this huge fundamental thing about you?
Okay.
I'm gonna tell you something.
But I really don't want you
to look at me differently.
Or treat me differently.
Or hate me for not telling you sooner.
Hey, I would never.
You say that, but a lot of people did.
Remember my friend from high school?
The one who was roofied,
and all the stuff that happened after?
You're the friend.
Oh, Hannah, I always knew.
I just...
I thought you'd tell me
when you were ready.
You're my favorite person ever.
Right back at you, babe.
So, what does this have to do
with writer's block?
I... I just haven't been able
to write lyrics since.
Oh.
I didn't want to be the girl
who was raped.
I want to be this girl.
The girl who wrote this song.
The Hannah that I love is that girl.
And this girl.
And all the girls in between.
Because you're not just one thing, babe.
You're everything.
Never forget that.
Okay, you are everything.
And the words will come when they come.
And maybe I might have the beginnings
of an inkling of an idea for a new song.
But I need someone's help for it.
Thank you, again, for all the help.
Yeah, of course.
- Can't wait to hear the finished product.
- Yeah, if it ever turns into anything.
Well, hey, if it does,
I've got some friends
who work at the radio station.
I could call in a favor.
Yeah, I-I-I think this one's just for me.
These hockey sounds
will be so cool in the mix.
All right, totally, we got some good ones.
He's been sneaking in after practice.
Skates these pensive
little circles around the ice.
It's hard to watch.
Almost as bad
as his divorced Tom Brady stories.
- Yeah, those were bad.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I make Allie show me on her phone,
so he doesn't see.
My brother makes me do the same thing.
They aren't speaking?
No. They got in this big fight.
Apparently.
Anyway, send me the song
once it maybe turns into something.
Yeah.
Hey.
Uh, why are you...
Uh, Jules was helping me with a song.
Yeah?
Yeah.
You kind of helped me come up
with the idea, so...
thanks, I guess.
Are you dropping a diss track or...?
No.
No, uh, you just...
reminded me of who I used to be.
Right.
Well...
good luck at the showcase.
Actually, I dropped out.
Oh.
That's too bad.
Uh, you would have been really great.
- Well, I should--
- Hey, can I--
Sorry, what?
- No, it's fine.
- Garrett, I know we're...
You know.
But it's me.
I'm thinking about quitting.
Hockey?
Yeah.
Oh.
I don't know if I'm in it
for the right reasons.
I don't know if I'm playing because
I want to prove that I'm not like my dad
or I want to prove
that I am like my dad or...
...because I'm not good at anything else.
But...
Jensen said I should be skating
because I love it, and...
I don't know.
You once told me
that you'd be relieved
if you couldn't play anymore.
And now, you can't.
And that means you could be anywhere,
doing anything.
But you're not.
You're here.
On the ice.
Skating.
And for what it's worth,
you do have a good reason to play.
It's not your dad.
It's the guy on your right.
Who's always had your back.
Even when you're being an asshole.
Come! Come here!
Right here!
Yes, yes!
Graham and Logan
have been having a blast out there.
We love that for them.
And more importantly, we love it for me.
Two minutes left, it's looking--
...Graham and Delaney meet center ice,
ready to start the--
Hey, get off!
Get off of him!
Hey! Graham!
Hey! Hey!
- Bring him to me! Come here!
- Hey! Hey!
Garrett, look at me!
Hey, I got you.
I got you.
Okay?
Oh, you know Tucker hates
when you do that in the kitchen.
He'll live.
What do you want, Garrett?
The, uh...
St. A's game.
You pulled me off Delaney.
Yeah.
Thank you.
I blacked out.
If you hadn't stopped me...
Listen, Delaney's a piece of shit.
But I don't want to be that guy.
I don't want to be the guy
who loses himself in a violent rage.
I don't want to be...
I don't want to be my dad.
Look, um...
I'm gonna say some things.
I haven't said
any of this out loud before.
Except, well, except to Hannah.
But I think I need to.
Okay.
Yeah.
What's up with the cryptic text, dude?
I'm having a crisis.
Can you keep a secret on your life?
Where's the body?
- This is serious.
-  Okay.
Right.
Sorry.
I've been hooking up with Allie.
- I know.
- You know?
I was in the car with you for eight hours,
and I have eyes.
Oh. Fuck, you're not as dumb as you look.
I appreciate that.
So, what's your crisis?
I've lost my game.
What?
I tried hitting on, like,
three different girls.
Gorgeous girls.
All of them totally into me.
But I just...
I don't care.
Heart's not in it.
- Dick's not in it.
- Whoa.
I know.
Dude, you like Allie.
Like, "like" like her.
- Just tell her how you feel.
- No.
No, that's...
No.
She wants Six Flags.
Am I supposed to know what that means?
She doesn't want anything heavy or real.
Yesterday, she told me
that we had to sleep with other people.
And, uh, evidently I cannot.
"We"? Like, she's supposed to hook up
with other people, too.
- Yeah.
- And...
you're cool with that?
Totally, I mean...
- We aren't...
- No, you aren't.
We aren't at all, like...
But...
Yeah.
You're fucking awesome, D.
I know that. She knows that.
Otherwise, she wouldn't
be hooking up with you.
So, stop being chicken shit
and tell her how you feel.
And you gotta do it fast before she goes
and hooks up with some other guy.
Okay, I'll see you tomorrow.
- Love you, bye.
- Love you.
Carter St. James.
♪Sick ♪
♪Oh, dear ♪
♪You're ringing in my ear...♪
You checking me out?
No.
You sure?
Okay, we got Braun on center, Rogers on D.
Logan, Dean, you look
after those two out there, okay?
We gotta get the puck
to the net tonight.
Okay?
That goes for all of you.
I want shots all fucking game.
Do not let up.
You hear me?
Sorry, Coach. Um, can I...
Go ahead, captain.
Uh, you know I'm not a big speech guy.
Uh, but I figured since I can't, uh...
I thought that being captain
meant I had to do it all.
So...
I was selfish
and angry, and I shut you all out.
I acted like I was bigger than the team.
Yeah, you were a bit of an asshole.
I was.
But even when I abandoned you,
even when I lost my shit
when you didn't deserve it,
when I forgot about the game and the team
and how much fucking fun we have
when we're out there together,
you were there.
You guys backed me up.
That's why I love this sport.
Is that it's about showing up
and leaving it all out on the ice.
Not for yourself,
but for the guy on your right.
For your brothers.
I know I let you guys down.
I haven't been the captain
that you deserve, but...
But until then...
You guys already have a captain
skating with you out there.
That okay, Coach?
I'm good with it.
Gentlemen?
Yeah, Logan!
Let's go!
Let's go, Logan.
Captain Logan!
-  Yes, sir.
-  Yeah!
Yeah, let's go, all right!
- Let's fucking go!
- Yes sir!
Let's go!
Hit it!
Way to lay the body, D.D.!
Tough hit by Di Laurentis.
Wherever he is,
I bet Garrett Graham's proud.
Let's go!
Ha-ha! Yeah! Tucker!
Daveed!
Hi.
I wrote something, and I don't know why,
I feel like it's really good.
And anyway,
I don't even care about winning.
I just feel like I need to share this
and let people into my truth to heal,
like you said.
And I know what time it is,
and I know it's too late,
and I know I said I was dropping out,
but can I maybe drop back in?
Now, girl,
you know they didn't have the budget
to reprint all these programs.
So, you're saying...
I'm saying you better start warming up.
You are on after Bethany.
Thank you!
Yes! Okay!
We can come back from a tie,
but we can't come back from a loss.
- Let's be smart.
- They’re not getting that puck back.
- Let's fucking go.
- All right, get it done! Change! Change!
♪Talking what I′m doing next week ♪
Stall, stall.
♪You really don′t wanna test me...♪
Fuck yeah!
Nice.
- Hey, shouldn't you be back on D?
- They're not getting the puck back, baby.
Fucking right. Let's go!
Don't play it safe, get back to him.
Hey, Tuck! A tie's not a win!
Aye-aye, cap!
Come on, Logan. Go to work.
Take it!
- Yes!
- Yeah!
Yes!
Whoo! Go, John!
Attaboy, Logan! Attaboy!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Let's go!
Whoo!
♪Who cares what you're doing next week ♪
♪You're saying please don't test me ♪
♪Just pass the drinks, I feel sexy ♪
♪Ooh, get messy ♪
♪Baby, get messy ♪
♪Get messy ♪
Oh, my God. She's doing it.
Okay, this has been fun, but I gotta go.
You don't want my number?
No. Actually, I don't.
I could stay, and we could keep up
this cute little banter thing we're doing,
but, I mean, like you said,
the benefit of being complete strangers
is we don't owe each other
anything, right?
I mean, that works for me.
Okay.
I have a best friend to go support.
Hey, we won. You should come to Malone's.
I want to talk to you.
No time. Hannah's doing the showcase.
You have to get Garrett there.
- Why?
- Because they're right for each other,
and Hannah deserves a romantic gesture.
So you want me to...
Yes, now.
G.
We gotta go now.
What's up?
Wellsy's doing the showcase.
You gotta be there.
How do you know that?
I overheard it in the stands.
Wait, Hannah's doing the showcase?
Well, we're going. When does it start?
- Like, now.
-  Then we gotta hustle.
- Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
- Come on, come on.
What's going on?
What if she doesn't want me there?
Fuck are you talking about?
Of course, she wants you there.
- No, she's moving on. I have to let her.
- Jesus Christ.
Look, you guys are perfect for each other.
So, whatever you did to fuck it up,
just undo it.
It's not that easy.
She deserves better than me.
No, don't fucking do that.
You are not your dad, okay?
So, are you gonna fight for her?
Come on.
Please welcome to the stage,
Hannah Wells.
♪Ooh ♪
♪Ooh, ooh ♪
♪I heard the talk ♪
♪I wish I never listened ♪
♪It's so hard letting go of it ♪
♪The sharpest knives ♪
♪Are whispered harsh opinions ♪
♪And what did I have to show for it ♪
♪Like a glass hits the floor ♪
♪My world was shattered and broken ♪
♪Couple years
I was coping and holding in ♪
♪I had no words ♪
♪Couldn't make a sound ♪
♪I took my time ♪
♪But I'm here right now ♪
♪I spent so long inside my head ♪
♪The pain, the tears, secrets I kept ♪
♪In fear one day they'd be the end of me ♪
♪And all at once it all makes sense ♪
♪I had to break, I had to bend ♪
♪ I had to lose myself to finally see ♪
♪I am the girl that I am ♪
♪Because of the girl I used ♪
♪To be ♪
♪Ohh ♪
♪I bared my truth ♪
♪Not knowing what would follow ♪
♪And I would do it all again ♪
♪Time heals all wounds ♪
♪But leaves a pretty scar, though ♪
♪Stronger than I've ever been ♪
♪'Cause I found my words ♪
♪So I'll sing 'em loud ♪
♪Guess all the hurt ♪
♪Got me here now ♪
♪I spent so long inside my head ♪
♪The pain, the tears, secrets I kept ♪
♪In fear one day they'd be the end of me ♪
♪And all at once it all makes sense ♪
♪I had to trust to feel again ♪
♪I had to let you in to finally see ♪
♪I am the girl that I am ♪
♪Because of the girl I used ♪
♪To be ♪
♪It all makes sense
It all-- It all makes ♪
♪It all makes sense ♪
♪'Cause I found my words ♪
♪So I'll sing 'em loud ♪
♪I had to let you in, to let you in ♪
♪To let you see ♪
♪Guess all the hurt ♪
♪Got me here now ♪
♪I spent so long inside my head ♪
♪The pain, the tears, secrets I kept ♪
♪In fear one day they'd be the end of me ♪
♪I am the girl that I am ♪
♪Because of what I went through ♪
♪Partly because of you ♪
♪I am the girl that I am ♪
♪Because of the girl I used ♪
♪To be ♪
Yes!
You came.
I couldn't miss your big moment,
could I?
You are, um...
fucking incredible.
The way you just opened up
in front of all those people.
I want to be more like you, Wellsy.
Like the girl from the green room.
The girl up on that stage.
Fuck.
Everything you are.
Garrett--
Just hear me out.
Please.
You make me want to be better.
To do better, and...
I'm going to.
Just...
give me another chance.
I meant what I said before.
You should be with whoever you want to be.
But...
I really want that guy to be me.
You know, girls really hate it
when guys are too available.
They do?
Shit.
Yeah. You got a lot to learn here, Graham.
Do you know any good tutors?
I might.
♪I wish I could save her ♪
♪But I can't behave her ♪
♪And she's twisting,
shapeshifting on a Saturday night ♪
♪Will she waste into
the kind of woman everyone likes?♪
♪She's an industry professional
at telling you lies ♪
♪Works hard for her money
and still can't get by ♪
♪She's a California keeper
if she just plays pretend ♪
♪And you'll love her 'til you leave her
'cause she's sick in the head...♪
Good game.
Now you just gotta win 16 more.
Thank you for that.
There she is!
The star, the icon.
I still think it was rigged.
They didn't rig the pop showcase.
- Whatever, Bethany paid someone off.
- She absolutely did.
- But second place is the new first anyway.
- Right?
And I got an internship.
Paid internship.
Which deserves a drink. Who wants a drink?
I will accept the drink.
Mm. Four piña coladas, please.
Hey, Walker.
Hey, can I get three shots of tequila, please?
Thanks.
- Hey.
You did a nice thing.
- What?
- Getting them back together.
No, they got themselves back together.
With help from you.
And me.
- You're welcome.
- Mm.
I get it now.
You love love.
That's what you said you wanted, right?
That night at the fire pit.
So, I came here to tell you that, uh...
I didn't complete the assignment.
What?
- Why?
- Because I like you.
I like us.
I know that's not what we said,
but I was hoping--
Hey, no, Dean.
- You can't.
- And yet, I am.
No, I mean, like,
you have to complete the assignment.
- Because--
- Because why?
Because I did.
Okay, somebody tell me
why we aren't drinking over here.
I swear, it didn't mean anything.
I-- Joanna set me up with this guy,
like a total stranger at a bar.
Oh, shit.
♪I don't mean to cause a scene ♪
♪But respectfully, I...♪
Oh, shit.
Allie, is that who you...
♪Looking at your knee-high boots ♪
♪You looked at me and said ♪
♪"I'm gonna make a man out of you"...♪
Him?
No.
Yes.
Do you know him?
♪I think I'm gonna ♪
♪Come to my senses
realize that I'm in...♪
-  Dean.
- The fuck are you doing here?
- I heard your team needs saving.
Yeah? Get the fuck out.
Hey, uh, Logan,
you said this was his idea.
You-- You said what?
Dude, you didn't.
- Hey, what the hell is going on here?
- You weren't there? I had to make a call.
I'm not skating with this prick!
Aw. What, are you scared
I’m gonna dust your ass again?
- You wanna try? Yeah?
- Yeah, I do.
- I'd like to see you fucking try.
- Get the fuck out of my face.
-  Hey! Hey, Dean! Hey!
-  Whoa, whoa!
Come on!
Hey! Whoa, whoa!
- Come here!
- Fuck you! Get the fuck back!
- Fuck you!
- Drama, drama, drama.
I knew this would get messy.
What is happening? Who is that guy?
Great question. Beau, who is that guy?
That is Hunter Davenport.
And that's our new starting line.
♪I got a feeling
they want me in the background ♪
♪I know they need me in the front ♪
♪It doesn't matter
'cuz I know what will happen ♪
♪They won't believe it when it comes ♪
♪Uh-huh, all I ever needed
was to give it all I got now ♪
♪Maybe I'm just in it for the rush ♪
♪Taking my percentage
better give me what I want now ♪
♪Thank you very much ♪
♪I wanna
bad thing rush ♪
♪Gimme
♪I wanna
bad thing rush ♪
♪I got a feeling
I'm 'bout to do a bad thing ♪
♪I know they know that I'm the one ♪
♪Back me up into a corner
I'll come atcha ♪
♪I like to watch 'em when they run ♪
♪All I never needed
was to give it all I got now ♪
♪Maybe I'm just in it for the rush ♪
♪Taking my percentage
better give me what I want now ♪
♪Thank you very much ♪
♪I wanna
bad thing rush ♪
♪Gimme