(Y'all hittin' the bar today?)
(I have a gig)
Being a Brave is a job where
you could get smoked at any second.
A homie who was chilling yesterday
could be a ghost this morning.
Pondering about when my turn gonna come
got me depressed as hell.
In the end,
maybe as a way to gear adrift
from that ate-up of reality,
we end up staying posted to Ed Cyrus' bar.
8,000 yen...
What a rip-off.
No money to carry into tomorrow, so hungry,
getting hit hard (Scum of the Brave)
Playing bossa nova and
earning my day-to-day cash
And the thugs
are running wild in the streets
I'm just standing here,
staring at you with my dead-looking eyes
There's not a single thing I can teach you
Yeah...
Let's just keep surviving over and over,
making fools of ourselves
Since we're both not normal
You can't save with "I-love-you"
This town is sick
Gradually, watching carefully,
get through it all
That single moment in slow motion,
the battle's going good
You and me,
we're so arrogant and so uncute
Telling transparent lies
Do you want to be strong?
Want to be loved?
Stay quiet, you fool!
Too early to say the "last of us"
Today's day will soon be memorial
Gradually, watching carefully,
bite into it and hang on
Let's put on a poker face and go
Still the same, you and me,
we're so arrogant and so uncute
Telling transparent lies
You can't save with "I-love-you"
You can't save a single soul
Telling transparent lies
(#6 Boot Camp of the Brave)
Hey, long time no see, Yashiro.
("Backstreet" Maruta)
(Unlicensed Brave)
It sure is cold today.
Master, can you make it a little warmer?
Damn, you still kickin', Maruta?
Thought you kicked the bucket already!
Heh, been half a year, huh?
Joe and Ishinoo.
Where are those bastards?
Joe's on the grind,
and I ain't heard from Ishinoo.
It's been a while since I did,
so he's prolly got bodied by now.
Hey Ed, give me another glass!
Hey, that's my beer.
I know! Cheers!
So...
Where have you been slacking off
for the last six months?
Hehe.
Well...
I got a job.
A job?!
You ain't even have a fixed address!
Believe it or not,
there was a company that actually
hired me as a contract worker.
The job was lining up with others to
buy rare toys and tickets and stuff.
Heh...
So you finally quit being a Brave?
Nah, actually...
I got fired from that company.
Huh?
My boss told me to scam
some honest old lady,
and sell her some shitty game console.
Like hell I'd do that, right?
So I crushed that asshole's eyeball,
stole anything valuable, and ran.
Whoa...
I see. That sounds just like you.
That's the divine punishment for him.
I know, right?
So today, I figured someone
might buy this thing I stole.
King Rob's coming to Japan!
Seven Medallions Grand Winter Season
finals spectator ticket!
For real?!
You want this that badly?
Of course!
King Rob is our hero!
He's the guy who won three
world championships in a row!
I'll buy it right now!
How much?!
30,000 yen.
If you're not buying,
I'll sell it to Joe or Ishinoo.
Wait, wait!
Can I pay next month?
Nope.
I don't have money for tomorrow's beer.
I got a big lick poppin' next month.
Rather than next month,
how about you make
the money right now?
We've been waiting for you, Master!
I heard you started working
as a private tutor?
Way to go, Yashiro.
(Shogo Imamura)
(The Best Spears and Shields)
In other words, it's practical training!
Master!
Next week at the Academy,
there will be a sparring exam
using swords, held in a match format.
It's an important event,
that will determine whether
we advance or get expelled.
So, I was hoping you could
personally give us sword training!
Not happening! Go home!
I'm asking too.
We'll pay you.
If I say nah, the chairman gonna
smoke me or what?
Even if you refuse, I won't say a word.
My dad only sees us as a nuisance
he can get rid of if we get expelled.
Oh?
Sounds just like a Brave.
Which makes him
the worst scum of a father.
Yeah, he's a scumbag.
That's why I want you to teach us.
You're a strong Brave.
And someone we can trust.
Aki said the same thing.
Did she really?
She ain't wrapped too tight upstairs.
Huff...
Plus, it takes more than
that lil' pocket money y'all got,
to make this
first-rate Brave to...
I'm a Brave, not a mentor.
Yes, we know.
I'm probably trash at teaching.
Yes, we're certain you are.
Tuition is 100,000 yen for y'all three.
Pay up or the deal's off.
We'll pay 50,000 yen up front for now.
The rest after the lesson.
20,000... 30,000.
Aight then, let's get this done quickly.
We need a wide space and training weapons.
Your school will do.
Yes!
Then let's do that first thing tomorrow...
Right now.
Huh?
Entering the school building
at night is prohibited.
Who cares? We'll just break in.
If you can't sneak into a school,
how are you going to sneak
into a Demon King's castle?
Yes.
I think that's a good idea.
It feels like a real boot camp!
(Scum of the Brave)
Heh, wall-to-wall tatami, I see.
They must be swimming in that dough.
Please give us your guidance!
We're hoping for some ultimate move
we can learn quickly or something!
Ain't no such thing.
An ultimate move...
Tell me...
What's that like?!
I told you there ain't one.
Strap on them protectors already.
We'll kick this off with sparring.
I can take y'all three at once.
Yes!
So we just spar with you?
What about you?
Aren't you putting on a protector?
Don't sleep on a pro.
Come on and get me.
Yes!
Then the honor of going first
goes to me, Jogamine!
First, Indo.
She's bold, but...
You're easy to read,
coming straight like that.
Then the star player, Jogamine, is up!
Why're ya doubling down
on that same mistake, you clown?
Second, Jogamine.
A style that parries attacks with
a shield while aiming for counters.
This girl...
You don't pull counter moves on
somebody stronger than you.
You'll break down easily,
and get taken by hand-to-hand moves.
Well, your raw strength on E3
might be higher than mine, though.
Everything else aside.
Take this a bit more seriously.
Huh?
That's cheating!
Throwing swords is forbidden
in real matches!
Oh, that's a textbook amateur talk.
If it pisses you off that much,
try landing a hit on me.
Well, that was a good workout.
Hey, what's with you?!
All you've done is use dirty tricks!
We can't use that in a match!
You're right.
You can't do what I did as a reference.
Huh?
But I figured out the reason
why you girls are falling behind.
The reason?
I see! That's our master for you!
Then please give your honest opinion
to me, your first disciple!
Yeah.
First, Sarah, you're too scared.
What?!
Who are you calling scared?!
That. What you did there.
Pointlessly trying to intimidate others
means you actually wanna avoid conflict.
Anyway, let's talk about
the sparring we did.
You always go third when
it's time to strike, right?
That's why you could always
swing down with full power.
That's because I was trying
to knock you down...
Meaning, you wanna
end it all in one hit.
You don't wanna get hit back,
so you rush to close it quick.
And if it looks like you can't win,
you tap out fast.
Sounds like you were taught
that kind of self-defense.
You were probably taught
not to fight someone you can't beat.
Anyway, you should fix that.
Basically, you gotta fight thinkin'
about forcing a stalemate.
Next, Indo.
Your problem is...
Nothing in particular.
Be honest, your practical
scores aren't bad, right?
Yukine's problem is academics.
She's shaky on multiplication tables.
I can do that much.
Liar.
When I tried teaching you,
you were solving them with some
weird code-like method.
That was a coincidence.
There's no such thing
as a coincidence in math.
So first...
Just shut up and listen to me!
Raise your hand when you want to speak!
Anyway, you don't really have any issues.
But Instructor,
I want to become stronger.
You're stronger than me right now,
so I want you to teach me.
"Right now", you said?
Talk about cheeky.
Well, someday.
Someday when?
Someday.
Lastly, Jogamine.
Yes!
You're so hopeless.
Not even worth discussing.
You can't be serious!
I am dead serious.
How do I put it...
You ain't fightin' to kill
or wreck your opponent.
That's what I've noticed since
the Amber Thorn incident.
Don't tell me you don't wanna kill people?
If that's the case, quit being a Brave.
Your problem is beyond skill.
But Master...
I was taught that a Brave represents hope.
Huh?
If peace can be built without hurting
anyone, wouldn't that be best?
Being a Brave is already a thorny path.
If so, shouldn't we always strive
for the best possible outcome?
This brat is seriously delusional.
Maybe she needs harsher training.
What's this?
That face...
I think I've seen it somewhere...
Hey!
We're done for if we're caught.
Perfect timing.
Sarah, Jogamine...
You two handle the guys
coming now and shut 'em up.
Solve your own issues in real combat...
If you screw up and
get exposed, you're expelled.
Oh?
Maybe I'm actually cut out for teaching?
But Master, even if it's for training,
hurting innocent guards is kinda...
They've let us infiltrate,
so they're not exactly innocent.
Think of it as their training too.
That's one way to think about it...
Don't let him talk you into it, Aki!
Instructor, what about my training?
Huh? You're fine for now.
I don't want to be the only one
with nothing to write home about.
Will you train me again?
If you can follow my orders.
Just go sit over there in the squat.
Got it.
As expected of Yukine!
Even I'm kinda freaked out by how...
Was it really here?
Yeah. I definitely saw a light.
You're so serious.
This is outside the contract, right?
Well, whatever.
Want to grab a meal together after this?
They might be companions of
the man from yesterday.
He seemed quite skilled, didn't he?
Well, yeah.
It still hurts, so how about you nurse me?
See? They've already run off.
No need to go this far.
Don't say unnecessary things, Id.
Huh?
That woman's voice...
Ether hoarse.
It's what happened to Demon Kings
who've had sloppy surgery,
or addicts who use illegal amounts of E3.
And from the way they talk,
they don't sound like teachers or guards.
They might still be nearby.
Let's track them.
Aight. Go!
Argh, screw this!
Damn, she actually goin' on offense.
That's the fruit of my teaching!
Maybe not as ripe as I thought.
That woman's got skills.
Ouch!
You illegal intruders!
Do you intend to oppose the Academy?!
State your names!
Press the attack, you idiot.
Tch, students.
Why are they here?
Indo, get ready.
They don't look like amateurs.
We're retreating! You may use your E3!
Can I kill them?
Idiot. Cover Jogamine and fall back.
Understood.
Hey, don't chicken out! Stand up!
You...
It hurts...
Screw this...!
Is this some kind of trend or what?
Mental rental
As a beautiful girl,
my policy is to be undefeated
Entitled "Invincible Girl"
I'm renting you in my heart
Mental rental
No returns? "A cowardly scumbag"
Who am I?
You have your ideals
Like, super-opposite from me, for real
All flaws and empty inside
My Doppelgänger achieved the pinnacle
Only ridiculous common-sense people
Can wear shoes on the dance floor
Going crazy, bombed out,
how's the water temperature?
I can't end here in a city with no future
Technology is a disaster
Keeping people in brilliant anguish
Everyone has their own
"Why? Why?" complex
My title, loser-exclusive,
is high-spec
Neither talented nor with character
Liar, psychopath?
If that's who I am,
I can never be a match for you
Incomprehensible pretty words
I feel awkward with those eyes
They see through my weaknesses
Let me borrow them
Tell me
Mental rental
As a beautiful girl,
my policy is to be undefeated
Entitled "Invincible Girl"
I'm renting you in my heart
Mental rental
No returns? "A cowardly scumbag"
Who am I?
You have your ideals
Like, super-opposite from me, for real
Bizarre non-delicacy
Take it to the max and it's fantasy?
That mentality will save the earth
Ah, self-searching is not for you
You're dazzling,
with not having much to search for
Oh no, oh no, oh no
Oh no, oh no
Master! There's no reply to
the message I sent to Mr. Ishinoo!
Did he even read it?
Why are you even texting him for...
His hobby is...
Next episode, Episode 7:
"The Death of a Brave."
(#7 The Death of a Brave) Next
episode, Episode 7: "The Death of a Brave."
Hey, listen to me...
(#7 The Death of a Brave)