=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 22=
If that's all, you may leave.
Don't just stand here.
How annoying.
Your Grace,
I heard Her Ladyship took a mortal
to the Nine-Square Maze Prison.
She violated the Golden-wall Decrees.
Yeah, Your Grace.
If you hadn't gone there personally,
that mortal would have died.
Her Ladyship knowingly violated the law
and attempted to kill a mortal.
It's...
It's a grave offense.
- That's right.
- Yeah.
Mortal?
There's only one mortal here.
I heard his soul candle
was extinguished.
He survived anyway.
I wonder if Her Grace
did something in the Prison.
Could she be injured?
Your Grace,
it's not appropriate
to shut us out here.
Come out and make a ruling.
Your Grace,
please make a ruling.
How noisy.
Greetings, Your Grace.
Why did you stop?
Her Ladyship took a mortal to the Prison
and violated the law.
Your Grace,
punish her by law.
What do you think, Jiang Ai?
They want you to die.
I did violate the Golden-wall Decrees,
but that mortal didn't die.
According to the law,
I don't deserve to die.
But I'm guilty anyway.
I'll be punished.
Yan Ke, why are you so quiet?
What's your opinion?
As the Left Hand, Jiang Ai
knowingly violated the decrees.
No serious harm was done,
so she shall be flogged thirty times.
As for other offenses,
please determine
by law.
Starting today,
Jiang Ai will reflect on her mistakes.
Her duties will temporarily
be handled by Yan Ke.
From now on,
no one shall trespass
in the Prison.
The flogging
will be executed by Yan Ke.
Immediately.
Yes.
Her Grace still favors His Lordship.
He won't show favoritism
during the flogging.
Do you have any complaints?
Her Grace ordered you to do this.
I believe
you've figured out what she meant.
So I have no complaints.
Everybody is here today.
Then do it now.
Don't spoil Her Grace's mood.
You tried to get rid of me,
but never expected Her Grace
to openly shield me.
Now that your plot has failed,
doesn't it feel bad?
Twenty-eight more lashes.
Your time for abusing me
is almost up.
What happened today
was far worse than I thought.
Her Grace was usually
dependent on Her Ladyship.
But she showed no mercy
in the punishment.
Because Her Grace has no heart.
As if you had one.
Hey.
Don't get me involved.
All of you,
listen up.
Anyone who violates
the Golden-wall Decrees
will end up like this.
Simu.
It's that mortal's voice.
After the flogging,
you may all leave.
Her Ladyship is really suffering.
After all these years,
I was punished again because of him.
Bai Sanxing, I hate you!
I...
(I'll pay you back)
(a hundred times over.)
(I saved you)
(from evil spirits.)
(You should always belong to me.)
Your Ladyship.
May I see you?
Come on in.
Greetings, Your Ladyship.
This is the Glacial Elixir, a tribute
from the Frigid Land last year.
It heals wounds fast.
His Lordship is too cruel.
His Spine Whip
is made of Thunderous Crystal Keel.
When he flogged you,
he even used spiritual energy.
An ordinary spirit
would be annihilated
after just one lash.
He wished I would be annihilated.
Too bad he couldn't kill me.
Now, he's in charge of Xuling Temple,
but everyone is loyal to me.
He won't get anything out of it.
Don't worry too much.
Now he has new problems
to deal with.
He has no time for me.
New problems?
What brings you here?
The mortal's tonic elixir has arrived.
If you can't go,
I'll fetch it for you.
No need.
The more people think
I've fallen,
the more I have to act as usual.
Greetings, Your Grace.
Why did you come here
instead of resting?
Just minor injuries.
His tonic elixir has arrived.
I've brought it to him.
Simu,
in the Nine-Square Maze Prison,
Bai Sanxing suddenly attacked us.
To save me,
he lost his soul candle and got lost.
There, he had a bet with me.
If he made it back alive,
I would tell him about your past.
When he wakes up,
should I honor my bet?
You can tell him.
Yes.
Do you hate Bai Sanxing?
Of course.
That's why I tricked him
into the Nine-Square Maze Prison
and tried so hard to get rid of him.
If someone's body is confined,
he can break free.
But if his heart is held captive,
he'll just willingly
confine himself.
You should know
what's really in your heart.
Then what about you?
These days, you've been
staying by his bed
and taking meticulous care of him.
You even have the morning assembly here.
But you refuse to accept him.
Can you face what's in your own heart?
Simu,
what on earth are you scared of?
How about
you keep me by your side?
Whenever you want to feel,
you can have my senses.
Simu!
For a mortal, staying in the Void
is even more terrifying
than death.
So what?
(Back then, I was weak-willed.)
(I longed for that brief)
(yet sweet companionship.)
I'll definitely treasure
your smart skull.
Foxy,
let me have a taste.
(I yearned for the warmth)
(and softness of the world.)
(So I brought you back to the Void.)
(The Void with endless nights.)
(But you don't belong here, after all.)
(You don't belong in my world.)
(Even if I could have you for a moment,)
(I would inevitably lose you one day.)
(In that case,)
(what's the point of starting?)
Simu.
Only when I'm sick
can I be treated so well.
I'm really awake.
Great.
This is great.
I can still see your smiling face.
Great.
You still want to see this face.
Simu,
I'm sorry.
You've been
through so many terrible memories.
I knew
you hated parting.
But I still let you
watch me grow old.
Sorry, Simu.
I wasn't there for you all the time.
That was an illusion,
but I believe all the joy and delight
were real.
How nice, Simu.
I'm so happy
that you also have feelings for me.
I love being with you too.
If you still like it,
we can buy a house.
With mountains and water around.
We'll plant fruit trees and flowers
behind the mountain.
You love cilantro so much.
We'll just plant cilantro
all along the stream.
I don't understand
why you like this flavor.
Made cilantro-filled moon cakes again?
You love cilantro-filled moon cakes.
Then we'll put more crushed peanuts
and rock sugar.
Simu.
Stop.
Stop that.
Simu.
You shouldn't have said it.
Duan Shunxi,
I love being with you.
Simu,
I really,
really like you.
You shouldn't remember.
Neither of us should.
Yan,
have some tea.
Simu,
why did you take a mortal
back to our world
and treat him with special favor?
You even let him live
in the bedchamber
that I had built for you.
This is our home.
No one but me
can stand by your side
and stay with you forever.
Yeah, Yan.
Only you'll stay with me.
Without you in the Void,
I wouldn't feel reassured.
(Zhaomu Pavilion, the Void)
Get up and take the medicine.
Simu.
I'm too weak.
Your Grace,
would you deign to feed me?
Take it.
If one day you have my sense of taste,
you'll know
I hate bitterness.
This medicine
even smells bitter.
Open your mouth.
I guess you often take care of me,
so you're good at feeding me.
You're ticklish and hate bitterness.
Did you see someone in the illusion
who tickled you
and fed you medicine?
Simu.
If you want to know
what I saw in the illusion
of the Prison...
If you do,
I'll tell you.
Like I told you,
before I ended my training
in the All-Knowing,
I helped the High Priest
and the Chong court
do terrible things.
Those memories came back.
I had blood on my hands.
Han Lingqiu
executed people too.
I fed him a memory-erasing potion.
He probably won't remember anything.
That's good.
May he never remember it.
Wake up.
The nightmare is over.
It is?
Yes.
You're my spell bearer.
In this world, no one
can make you experience
a nightmare again.
I will never allow it.
Take it.
It's also part of the nightmare.
I said
no one would make you
experience a nightmare.
But I'm a spirit.
I'm not included.
You're looking good, young man.
It seems Simu
has taken good care of you.
Thank you for your concern.
I've heard
you were punished
because of me.
Sorry to get you involved.
You're well-informed.
Just a few
minor reprimands.
Don't worry.
Sorry for putting you through that.
Some small gifts for you.
Are these all you're giving me?
I remember back in the Prison,
we had a bet.
So you remembered.
This time,
you won the bet.
The duty of the Starhaven Sect
is to maintain the balance
between mortals and spirits.
Simu's mother
was a sorceress in it.
To marry the former sovereign,
she gave up
her position in her sect.
On their wedding day,
the red carpet was rolled out
from the Starhaven Sect
to the Sovereign's Hall.
Flowers danced in the air.
That breathtaking scene
is still vivid in my mind
even now.
After that,
Simu was born.
On the day she was born,
there was a once-in-400-years snowstorm.
- The next day, the chill faded away.
- Simu.
It was warm again.
There's a little rabbit.
She's been gifted since childhood.
When she was young,
she was just as powerful as me.
But she seldom came to the Void.
Her parents took her to the Mortal World
- where she lived as a mortal.
- There. The fish.
It swam past.
Yeah. That's it.
Go catch it.
I got it!
Simu, have all my candy.
Thank you, everyone.
- Take my toys too.
- Enough.
All right.
When we have time, we'll come back.
Simu was a bit different
from ordinary mortals.
But they lived a carefree life.
She and her parents
helped mortals as much as they could.
We should go.
They made good connections with mortals.
Why are they so warm?
Because they love us.
These mortals
love their families,
their sweethearts,
and their friends.
They even love
this vast world.
See you!
- At that time...
- See you!
- She had many friends and relatives.
- See you.
See you!
- She thought they would meet again.
- See you.
- She didn't know.
- See you!
There were some people
she would never meet again.
"See you"
means "never see you."
Father,
so this is death?
Your mother...
Her destiny is sealed.
She did everything she could
to stay with us until now.
In the end, you and I have no one
but each other.
This is quite sad.
But Father,
you broke your promise too.
After the former sovereign passed away,
the Void fell into chaos.
All the spirits here
coveted
the throne.
♪Spirits are intoxicated♪
♪With obsessions♪
♪Forget the form to achieve♪
♪Yet I can't♪
♪Today, a home is granted♪
♪Joy without grief♪
♪Lanterns light the empty delusions♪
♪All are ferried across♪
♪Spirits are intoxicated♪
♪With obsessions♪
♪Yet I can't♪
♪Today, a home is granted♪
♪Joy without grief♪
♪Lanterns light the empty delusions♪
♪All are ferried across♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪