What is it?
P'Korn and P'Praew said you
guys are really close to P'Champ.
I wanna ask him out.
So I was hoping you two
could give me some advice.
P'Gorn.
I've got a question about Champ.
Yeah? What is it?
I wanna know…
Is Champ single?
Hmm?
Tos, why do you ask?
Well…
Champ's just cute, that's all.
What do we say?
Single or not?
But if you really wanna know…
Ask P'Sorn and P'Tai…
They're close with him.
Sorry if we don't know!
Yes - Just try it! Ask P'Sor and P'Tai…
No need. This is enough.
Good luck
I'm rooting for you!
I heard…
You just started at the office…
And you're already hitting on coworkers?
No work?
I do work.
But Champ matters to me.
I wanna know
what type he likes…
So I can try love at work...
You should get back to work.
It's business hours
not personal time.
We'll chat later.
Alright.
But if you guys can't help…
No worries.
I've never failed at flirting…
Just don't block me,
that's all.
Dude's being hell a
annoying—pursuing Champ again!
What are you gonna do?
Hello all—big group
today. What can I get you?
What's everyone having? I'll treat.
Jun and I will have green tea.
Then… I'll take one Americano.
Got it two green teas, one
Americano, and one mocha.
Sure. But hey! Isn't Champ
skipping his usual… mallow mocha?
Um… what's a mallow mocha?
It's hot coffee with marshmallow.
He usually drinks it daily.
Bro.
Don't you usually just drink iced coffee?
Then can I switch to a mallow mocha?
Nope!
Why not?
I just wanna drink what Champ drinks.
Champ only drinks iced mocha.
Then whose mallow mocha is this?
It's for my friend.
One mallow mocha and one espresso, please.
Got it.
Make it quick!
Champ!
Huh.
I saw Jun just calling
you and that Tos dude.
Right now?
Yeah.
Me too?
Go ahead.
Let's go, bro.
Tos, don't meddle with Champ!
You just joined, right?
I saw your late reports.
I think you need to change how you work.
Bro.
I'm grown and I've got this job.
I don't need anyone telling
me what's right or wrong.
And my uncle said I'm definitely staying.
Don't worry about my work.
Tos, he is not being nice.
He shouldn't act like this.
What we heard earlier…
Don't mention it to anyone.
Grab your coffee and
go eat before break ends.
Before break ends.
What now…
Nothing.
We've gotta follow what the boss says.
You're calmer than I thought.
So why the hell did you call me here?
That bastard! Isn't he hitting on you?
And you're just letting him? I don't get it!
If we weren't at the office,
I'd've knocked him out!
But I don't like him, man.
But if you start liking him!
I'll deal with you…and him!
Deal with what?
What are we?
You want me to spell it out?
What we are?
You're my wife!!
Tai...
You belong to me.
I'm so jealous, it's driving me crazy!
And that bastard thinks who he is
flirting with you in front of your husband?
I'm not your wife!
We're not even dating.
You got amnesia?
Need me to refresh your memory?
Because you never said anything.
You never defined us.
And how you treat me…
It's no different from anyone else.
Not special, right?
It's not true!
Do I not feel that way?
I love you, Champ.
I've loved you all this time.
Until now.
I didn't even realize
how important you are.
But our relationship…
It's definitely more than friends.
Why are you this adorable?
I could die of jealousy!
You asshole.
I love you, Champ.
You love me too, right?
Mmm.
Then…
Love with me.
But here…
No worries…
Doing it here…
Feels thrilling!
Yeah…
P'Champ.
Our senior at the company.
He's super handsome.
If I could win him over, that'd be slick!
Guys-liking-guys is trending now, right?
Might be good to hop on the trend.
Yeah.
Champ's easy to talk.
And kind.
Totally.
My profile's no joke
who wouldn't like it?
Oh… P'Tai,
Where are you going?
You worthless moron
from work to your brain.
All you think about is low‑blow stuff!
You having fun with this crap?
Do you think you're cool
doing this shit?
And you!
Who the hell are you to judge me!
Who are you to speak up…
You're just Champ's friend.
If Champ wants me,
You don't get to interfere!!
Why shouldn't I have a say?
Hey!
Don't you!
P'Champ.
Help me.
Tai is going to hurt me.
Just let him go.
Tai!
Get out.
I'll handle this.
But damn!!!
Yeah
I'll take it from here.
Got something to say? Spit it out.
P'Champ.
I wanna know
are you seeing someone?
I
I like you.
Huh.
If you feel uncomfortable,
it's okay.
Or if it's because of P'Tai,
I can get my uncle to
kick him out.
I appreciate your kindness,
but keep it.
Use this time to better yourself,
so when your uncle's gone.
You can survive on your own.
And one more thing
I already have a partner,
and they don't like it
when someone flirts with me.
Who's your partner?
The boss's son.
The boss's son?
Damn!
Hey you!
You think he's dumb or insane?
Can't he tell…
Tai is the chairman's son?
Yeah, same.
I don't really know,
but he's overly confident for sure.
That, I agree with!
Right? You agree?
I don't know how powerful his backup is,
but Tai's got that aura, man.
When we see him—damn—we almost
wanna somersault and bow at his feet.
Show us then. How would you do it?
Like this! Just like that.
Gosh… P'Tai's not just hot, he's cool too!
So high-class no one can afford him.
Whoever dates him is super lucky.
True that.
Hey P'Put,
So what's Champ gonna do now?
Tos openly declared he's chasing him.
I mean, Champ probably has a lover already.
Handsome, kind,
super sweet
he doesn't seem single.
What do you think?
I'm sure he's taken.
Someone at his level being single? No way.
And… what about you and P'Vee?
Have you two patched things up yet?
Right!
You gossip about others,
but what about you?
Spill it.
I think
letting her go is the best.
Even if we got back together,
I couldn't be her peace.
Better she meets someone better than me.
Back to work.
Let's go.
Don't be sad.
It's gonna be okay.
Jun,
I'm heading out to meet a client.
Want anything?
Umm…
Can you get me Tokyo pancakes?
Yes, sir.
Hey Jun,
you did my laundry the other day, right?
Yeah.
Didn't you see the stain?
I'm going to see clients
it's so unprofessional.
For real?
Where's the stain?
Right here.
What the hell are you playing at?
Something stuck on your forehead?
P'Sorn, you jerk!
I'm off!
Coffee to cure the hangover.
Honestly, you should've stayed 3 more days
till my day off.
I'd take you around.
I know
you wanted someone to take your IG pics.
Don't act slick.
Just post the old ones first!
Why?
You jealous?
I'm just protective of what's mine.
P'Thanu!
That bad, huh?
How could you eat that much?
Hey! P'Sorn.
Did you hear?
Tos resigned.
Said another place offered him more pay.
The other place offered a higher salary.
Hmm…
One more thing…
Can I go chill with Win?
He called—said he's lonely.
Please…
Please, P'Sorn?
Where?
Just a local hangout nearby,
not far.
Please?
No.
I won't get drunk.
I don't believe you.
I swear.
I won't drink too much.
I'll come back safe.
No drama.
Please… P'Sorn…
Please.
If you're going.
Then I'm going too.
But if I can't go with you,
then you're not going either.
Ah… Jun!
This table's for our friends.
Oh! P'Jun!
Yo! What's up, my man?
Hey P'Fran, Hello.
Hello, Jun the hottie.
Whoa, you're exaggerating, bro.
Haven't seen you here in forever.
Thought you forgot my place already.
Nah, never forget this place!
Good thing Piangrak
called to reserve a table.
I picked the best spot and
threw in a free bottle for you.
You gave us a whole bottle?
Yep.
Thanks a lot.
You're a really big-hearted shop owner.
With generosity like that
aren't you scared of going out of business?
Not at all.
My business partner
totally gets it.
Jun!
Yeah?
Didn't you say you
wouldn't bring P'Sorn here?
Honestly, I wasn't gonna tell him.
But if I didn't,
he wouldn't let me come at all.
Hey, cheers!
Come on!
Cheers, P'Fran!
Let's clink glasses!
Cheers!
Mmm…
Hey.
You.
Wanna head near the stage?
Let's go, let's go!
Let's move.
Hey, did you come with friends?
You look familiar
are we following each other on IG?
Mind typing it for me?
What are you doing?
Uh… dancing, duh?
Your charm's on full blast tonight.
What?
So what's the deal?
Are you dating P'Sorn?
Wait
what?
You two are a thing now?
So he's not your “Bro” anymore, huh?
You messing with me?
Hold up...
P'Fran, you know P'Sorn?
Yeah…
Sorn's actually my business partner.
What?!
P'Sorn's a partner here?
He never told me!
Don't change the subject.
That girl just now
did you give her your number?
No, I didn't!
Didn't you see? I was
literally trying to get away.
Good.
Now you going home or what?
It's almost 1AM.
Come on, bro…
We've still got a full table.
You're the co-owner anyway
can't you treat us?
Give you an inch, you take a mile, huh?
Bro!
Come on,
pour us another round, please?
Please, bro…
Hurry up!
Fine!!
Want a drink~?
Today's your last day of internship.
I wanted to bring you here.
Why'd you bring me?
Do you know?
The office fire escape...
What is it for?
I don't know.
They're for this!
You okay?
You sure I can do this?
Yeah.
Jun wants “Hia” to do it.
What did you just call me?
Hia Sorn...
Go easy on me.
Was I being too rough on you?
No… don't say stuff like that.
Why is that?
So what if I say it, huh?
It feels so intense.
Jun
you're too damn cute.
Hey.
You guys still here?
If me and Champ weren't here,
would you two even get a
moment alone, huh Sorn?
You're corrupting my boy!
You do that stuff somewhere private!
Were you spying on me?
Damn right we were!
Fine!
I won't use the fire escape next time.
Okay, that's good...
It's hot and exhausting anyway.
If it's were a rooftop sounds... better.
That's nice, Sorn. Real nice.
P' Tai, P' Sorn, stop fighting already.
Jun.
Tai kicked me!
You're talking nonsense.
I'm honestly creeped out, man.
I'll take that bastard Jun home later.
You guys coming?
Sure. Win probably wants
to go with Jun anyway.
Let's camp in your
grandma's backyard again
with the koi pond.
Yeah.
I want your dad and sister
to know we're together,
like my mom does.
And if my dad doesn't approve?
I'll fight for it.
Because I
want his son as my boyfriend.
Here's some water.
Hi, Dad!
Oh, hello!
Hey sis!
Hi, Dad!
Hi, hi.
I brought some fruit for you.
You took Jun in and brought gifts?
Wow, this guy's not bad at all.
Dad, let me help.
Busy day at the restaurant, huh?
I'll help serve.
Sis, which table?
He's pretty slick. Maybe we
should hire him as an employee.
Not an employee
I'm gonna be your son-in-law.
They're good. Maybe you could hire them...
Hey, did you see Dad's face?
Here's water. And for dad… and sis.
Thank youuuu.
So Tai and the others aren't here?
Haven't seen you in ages.
Oh, they're waiting at Tai's grandma's.
We're camping on the lawn tonight.
So, Jun staying at Sorn's place—any drama?
Sneaking girls in?
Or… does Dad need to go propose for a wife?
Eh?
Or... a guy?
Sis, what are you talking about?
Drink your water.
I am.
And how's your boyfriend search going, sis?
Dad, look at what he said.
He's teasing you—just kidding.
Hey Sorn, if... we're sleeping
together, you sleep on the floor.
I never planned to share the bed with you.
Your place isn't soundproof…
Sex won't be as fun if we do it now.
What are you saying?
Aren't you worried that people will see?
Hey!
So you're flirting with my brother?
Or are you already together?
Sis.
I ask Sorn.
I like your brother.
We're dating.
I'm here today.
I'm here to tell you.
I will another one person
who comes to love Jun.
And ask your permission to date openly.
Oh dear, sis!
How long have you been together?
Just recently.
We've been together longer than that.
What are you talking about?
Better now than later, right?
Since when?
When you stayed at Sorn's house, or before?
You mean when did I start liking him…
When we were dating or after...?
Hey!
I felt it when I went to his place.
I liked him first.
He takes good care of me
just too stubborn to say it.
He didn't say he like me.
We argued, but he apologized,
so I softened.
Alright, you're dating then.
Sis, you're the best!
You're the cutest.
But with Dad…
Maybe we should go slow?
Do you think...
If dad finds out, wll be mad?
No idea.
But I don't think he's that old-fashioned…
Finally you have someone real.
Stop teasing.
When's it your turn?
I will tell dad.
Don't squeal yet.
How's it? Do you like it here?
I love it.
I've been coming here since we were kids.
Before, my parents didn't have time,
So I come to playing with you often.
Made us close, this feels
like my second home.
From now on, this place will be yours too.
This ring came from Grandma.
She told me to keep it
until I meet someone I love.
I think... I love you now.
I don't know since when.
But when I realized
it, I already loved you.
So this ring it's yours.
But I didn't bring a ring
to give you in return.
Consider it reserved.
When we get married,
you can bring a ring to exchange.
Mmm.
You like it?
I do.
The ring?
Yeah.
Need any help, Dad?
I've never seen Jun bring
anyone home, except Tai and Win.
I'm glad Sorn got along with him.
I thought wouldn't get along.
Do you remember how mad Jun was before?
When he said Sorn invited him over.
I was shocked and happy.
Jun's a sweet guy.
Everyone likes him.
Please take care of him.
He can be a tease, but he's kind.
Besides Tai, you're someone he cares about.
Thank you for looking after him.
Thank you for trusting me, Dad.
Just… be respectful, that grabbed his butt.
New Caption.
I don't want him getting calluses.
Consider it Dad's request.
Got it, Dad.
Huh?
How did dad figure it out?
Hia!
Ah, sorry—it just slipped.
But how did Dad know?
He just knew.
How?
I didn't say, You didn't say.
Sis, didn't say.
Dad defintely wouldn't have noticed.
With so many customers
every day, today is the same.
How'd he notice?
Do you think someone
who raised you all your life...
Wouldn't recognize you?
Huh?
I visited your place,
and slept with you.
Adults notice these things.
And when you said no one saw,
Dad did. I even grabbed your ass.
F♪♪king P' Sorn!
What the hell, man?
You're all over the place!
What are you dramatizing?
Do you think I didn't notice Dad watching?
Fine!
But don't do anything
flashy like that again.
Especially in public.
No this, no that.
So many rules.
Maybe I'll forbid you from
leaving the house instead.
Why would you lock me in?
I'll keep you in bed
no sun, no moon.
P' Sorn…
You're,
so damn cute.
Awww!
Hurry up.
Tai, Champ, and Win have been waiting.
Let's go.
P' Champ...
That ring on your finger looks familiar.
No wonder
you've seen it before.
Where?
Grandma's.
Bro?
Have you greeted your brother-in-law yet?
Whoa.
I'm shocked.
We've been best friends forever.
But Champ's a great bro,
so kind and sweet.
Wow, thanks, man.
I don't want to brag,
but if it was P' Sorn.
I swear, stop imagining.
Everyone's got someone.
Tai dates Champ,
and Jun's with Sorn.
I want a boyfriend too…
For that, you should ask Sorn.
Why me?
Aren't you an expert?
You're his bro—teach him.
Bro
they say you're good in bed…
Is that true?
Win, why are you staring at me?
Jun's good too
I taught him self-care when he was young.
Sorn!
Damn, Sorn!
Fuck!
What the hell are you saying?
Yeah,
I know I was wrong
I was young and didn't know.
But don't follow that, Win!
I forbid it.
Hey, bro..
Where'd you teach Jun that?
That's none of your business.
Why not?
What's with that koi pond?
What? Nothing.
Just eat, guys.