(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
(Previously) Why didn't
everyone else get paid, but I did?
I'm the one who hired you.
I like you, Rome.
If we do it in the car, would you mind?
Pete and I didn't do anything that night.
It's nice though.
Seeing you jealous.
We're not back together yet.
How many times do I have to tell you that?
You know why I have to do this.
Can I stay over tonight?
So you can punish me however you want.
(Episode 7: Point of No Return)
I'm glad we're on good terms again.
Mm-hmm.
I'm still waiting if you want
us to get back together.
Give me some time.
Hey.
I think I'll pick up where
Rome and I left off on this trip.
Mm.
If you like him that much, go for it.
Hey, I…
Guys! Listen up!
Before we head out,
let's take a group photo.
Come on. Off the bus.
Move it.
Let's go.
Come on.
FINE ARTS OUTING
Camera's over there.
One, two, three!
FINE ARTS OUTING
Whoo!
"Only Friends: Dream On"
Gather round!
Grab your keys, everyone.
Stick to your assigned tents.
Some are for two, some for three.
[The sound of Fine Arts
students' displeasure]
What?
And don't go switching tents
as you please, okay?
Come on, take your keys.
This one's yours. This is yours.
And this is yours.
This one's yours.
Gosh, I'm having a headache.
Timmy, a word?
What?
What is it?
Why is there not enough room this year?
We're cramming people in.
Last time, it was two per tent.
This is the budget we've got.
Hold on.
Didn't we already get sponsor funding?
If we're really short on money,
we shouldn't have gone on this trip.
We should've saved it for the play.
No way.
Food, drinks, and trips are essential.
Besides, we do have enough money.
Someone just embezzled it.
Huh?
Is someone stealing from the play budget?
Um…
I'm gathering evidence.
Let me make sure first.
I'll take care of it.
You just enjoy the trip.
Leave the headache to your producer.
Hey, this one's for Jack and me.
Tua, that one is yours.
Who am I sharing with?
Probably Timmy.
Where is he, anyway? Why isn't he here?
I think he's sorting out
the accommodations.
Yeah?
Hey, Arnold.
Which tent are you in?
This one, I think.
Good.
We're neighbors.
Dean.
Hm?
Can we switch?
I want to talk to Jack about the script.
Besides, I'm not sure
I want to play the role anymore.
Hey. Is it really that bad?
Arnold, let's talk later.
You can share my tent.
If he stops talking to me completely…
I don't think I can handle it.
Well, well.
What a coincidence.
We're sharing a tent.
Did you plan this, hon?
Hey, Rome.
You're in this tent too?
Mm.
But I can move to another tent,
so you guys can be more comfortable.
Uh… hey.
You can stay here with us.
The more, the merrier.
Besides, I think the other tents are full.
Yeah, just crash here.
No one's going to do anything to you.
Unless…
you're planning to do
something to my friend.
Hey, Raffy.
What are you saying?
You're going to scare Rome off.
He's not scared.
He likes it.
Fine. I'll stay.
Hey.
He's not going to quit.
Jack will talk him out of it.
You know what?
He's not saying a word to me.
He doesn't read my messages.
Nothing at all.
I really messed up.
Come on. He's not going to
let your friendship end like that.
Look at Jack and me.
We had a huge fight,
but we ended up talking again.
I think Arnold might
give you another chance.
But you guys are ex-boyfriends.
You've been connected for so long,
you can't just cut ties completely.
But I'm just…
just a faculty friend who helps him out.
Exactly.
You've always been there for him.
And this time, you helped him too.
Even if your method… was money.
Sugar daddy much?
You'd be mad too if you were him, right?
I think the real reason
he's upset is that you lied to him.
Hey, Tua.
After every content shoot
with him on this trip, I'll whisper,
"Arnold, Tua loves you so much.
Please give your sugar daddy a chance."
"Next time, sugar daddy Tua
will pay even more."
When you said you'd quit earlier,
were you serious or
just trying to hurt Tua?
Don't worry, Jack.
I know how important this project is to you
and to everyone in the faculty.
I won't let my personal issues
affect the work.
Saying that means you care about Tua a lot.
I've known Tua for four years.
He's the best person I know.
And he means no harm to anyone.
I think you know that too.
When I was falling apart because of Dean,
he was the one who helped me.
I get it, Arnold.
The way he handled it was foul.
But you can just tell
him not to do it again.
Try to see his intention.
See why he did it.
Arnold…
you're more capable than you think.
You got me the lead actor I really wanted.
And the person who made you realize that…
is the one who paid you.
I just don't like liars.
Sincerity is the first
step in any relationship.
I don't know what else
he'll lie to me about.
Jack, don't you think
you've taken us a bit too far out?
If this thing tips over,
no one's coming to save us.
You know I can't swim well, right?
I can.
Don't be scared. I've got you.
Right.
You're the smartest person in the world.
You can swim, you can direct plays…
Is there anything you're not good at?
There is.
I got an F.
Wait.
When was it? I didn't know that.
What subject?
Friendship 101.
I failed.
Seriously?
I don't want to be your friend anymore.
I want to be your boyfriend.
Wow.
Just like that?
So you planned this kayaking
just to ask me to be your boyfriend?
This feels like a movie scene.
You're such a director.
So, what do you say?
Yes or no?
Okay.
But…
I want to announce to everyone that I won.
What are you talking about?
I bet Timmy and Tua
you'd be the one to ask first.
Now they owe me drinks at Pink's bar.
Whoo!
So I just walked right into your trap?
Yep.
Jack asked me to be his boyfriend!
Yay!
Careful.
What is this, a music video?
I'm waiting for you.
Don't you miss our first year?
Yeah.
When you asked me to be your boyfriend.
Big mistake.
I should've smacked you
into the water with a paddle.
Oh please. You couldn't do it.
You were infatuated with me.
Want to go kayaking?
You hoping for something?
No.
I just want to film some
content with you too.
Come on.
Let's go.
Ouch.
Damn it.
Are you feeding the ants or what?
You've got red bite marks all over.
I'll put something on them
when we get back to the tent.
Please don't quit, Arnold.
This is my fault. Don't let
everyone else suffer for it.
What do you take me for?
I'm not quitting.
This project helped me
discover another side of myself.
I never thought I'd enjoy acting this much.
And I got to experience it…
because of you.
But I'm still disappointed in you.
You lied to me.
So from now on, whatever it is,
just be honest with me.
If you need help with
anything, just tell me.
Don't forget.
You and I…
we're more than just friends.
Am I forgiven?
Of course.
I can't stay mad at you for long.
You didn't talk to me at all.
It was torture.
Hey, I had to act with nonchalance.
Come on. Stop looking so sad.
I thought you'd never talk to me again.
Getting bitten by a whole nest of ants
hurts less than you ignoring my messages.
No more of that.
We're good now.
Smile.
Come on, smile.
Let's go.
Let's join the others.
I just wanted to see him smile.
It's better than that sad cat face.
The wait for his forgiveness felt endless.
I'm relieved now.
I won't make him angry again.
Hey.
Wanna go for a swim?
No. It's too hot.
Why don't you ask Pete?
Hey, knock it off. That's not funny.
I'm not into Pete.
He's crazy about you.
Why not give him a chance?
Think about yourself.
You chased me nonstop until I gave in.
Now he's doing the same to you.
You'll cave eventually.
Maybe I should find
somewhere else to sleep tonight.
Here, Rome.
Got you a beer.
Thanks.
Let's celebrate.
It's going to be a long night.
Cheers.
Let me know if you need anything.
I've got you.
Sleeping bag…
or some other kind of protection.
Why aren't Tua and Arnold here yet?
Don't tell me they're fighting harder?
Don't think so.
Here they come.
So, have you two made up?
If you have…
Come here!
Let's hit the water.
Come! We've been waiting for you.
Get in the water.
Let's go.
Come on, Tua.
Guys!
Why didn't you wait for me?
Come.
Jeez!
So hot!
Alright, everyone!
Let's pause right here.
Attention, attention!
Stop talking and stop
drinking for a second.
We've got a special performance
from the heads of our faculty play.
Jack, Tua, Dean, and Timmy!
Whoo!
Yay! Come on!
Look at them. They're like a boy band!
♪ Really liked when
you said the love word ♪
♪ Haven't heard it in a long time ♪
♪ Is it so hard to say it out loud? ♪
♪ Just say you still love me now ♪
♪ I know your love is true ♪
♪ I know that you still care ♪
♪ I know it's not too hard to share ♪
♪ Where's that same old word?
Wanna hear it again ♪
♪ Let's bring back the good old days ♪
♪ Can you say, can you say,
Say it one more time? ♪
♪ I've been wanting
to hear it for so long ♪
♪ Can you say, can you say,
Say it one more time? ♪
♪ Remind me that
your love is still strong ♪
♪ Ja da da ja da da da da da ja ♪
Awesome!
I'm beat.
Do you want to spend the night with me?
I'll have Raffy wait outside.
No idea when I'll be done tonight.
You should find someone else, Pete.
I have solid evidence
of who embezzled the money.
The sponsor gave us 200K.
Why is there only 100K in the account?
What are you talking about, Timmy?
[Screenshot of a bank
transfer for 100k baht]
This is one hell of a crappy job, Pete.
How can you be this shameless?
We busted our asses securing this sponsor.
You didn't help at all,
and you're dragging us down.
I'm reporting this to the faculty board.
You'll be expelled.
You won't graduate.
And I'm taking this to the police.
Let's not involve the police.
Timmy, please.
Don't go to the police.
Please, Jack.
Then return the money soon.
Or you're kicked out of the project.
We should rename
Romeo &amp; Romeo to Prison Break.
And remember this,
I won't let this play fail,
no matter what the fuck happens.
Jack.
What are you doing here?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
And right now…
I'm feeling just right.
You said you'd go running with me tomorrow.
I don't think you'll be able to.
I will.
With you, whether it's an obstacle race
or a marathon, I can handle anything.
But right now, can you spend time with me?
No.
I don't like myself when I'm drunk.
And you are too.
You should get some sleep.
Hey, if I wanted to sleep,
I could've stayed home.
You don't look like you can go on.
Come on, I'll walk you back to the tent.
No.
I'm fine. Don't worry about me.
I can find my way back.
Besides, it's our last year.
I want to enjoy it while I can.
Mm.
If you want to go all in, that's your call.
But are you sure you've got this?
I am.
I knew it.
Sorry.
Hey.
Thanks a lot, Arnold, for forgiving me.
I know I w as wrong,
but I don't want you to think that way.
I did it because I truly meant well.
And…
I wanted to spend time with you.
Tua, you've said that
like a hundred times already.
I get it. You don't have to say it again.
You keep repeating yourself
when you're drunk.
And I'll keep saying it.
Because I'm happy to have you in my life.
Yeah, you're totally drunk.
Let me take you back to the tent.
Tua! Arnold!
Dean!
I'm so glad you guys made up.
Don't fight again.
Got it?
Yeah, we're good.
Love each other.
Yeah, we love each other.
You're drunk, Dean.
Drunk? This much alcohol can't touch me.
It's nothing.
Whoa!
Let me show you.
Hey!
Jeez!
You're awesome.
That was nothing.
Dean, what are you doing here?
Come.
Are you going to throw up?
I'm not throwing up.
Come with us.
Hey, you two. Love each other.
Love each other.
Oops.
You almost let me fall.
Dude, it's just grass.
Come on, bottoms up.
Then I'll take you to bed.
Whoo!
Come on.
Yay!
Come on. Down the hatch.
Yep.
No.
I don't want it.
Just for fun. Come here.
Oh, gosh.
Whoo!
Tua. Hey.
Why don't you change first?
You'll be more comfortable.
Look at you.
Fine, I'll do it.
After this trip,
it's your turn to take care of me.
Buy me a meal.
I'm glad to have you in my life.
My phone…
MEET ME OUTSIDE.
I saw you.
You still haven't given up on Jack?
I'm sure Jack and Dean
will definitely get back together.
Damn right.
Dean made that very clear.
But stay the hell out of my business.
Now what?
Want me to call Pete over?
Go ahead.
You've been pushing us together all day.
Call him.
I'll take him.
Fine. I'll go get him.
If I really do take
him, you'll get jealous.
You already like me.
Why play games?
So?
I'm annoying like that.
If you can handle that, stay.
If not, walk away.
Someone like you…
is exactly my type.
The harder you play,
the softer you'll be for me.
You're all talk.
Do it already.
See?
You and I both want it.
Arnold!
Oops, sorry.
- Dean.
- Sorry.
You okay?
I'm good.
Where's Tua?
Asleep.
Gosh. Such a lightweight.
What about you?
Hope you're not a lightweight like him.
Here. Let me test that.
Yeah?
Bring it on.
Come on.
Whoa, Dean!
That's so strong.
That's right.
My Romeo's got to be this strong.
Yay!
Cute moment.
Can we get some photos? We need content.
Make everyone smile so wide it hurts—
They'll be searching #DentalClinicNearMe.
Alright then.
A cheek kiss.
Please.
Okay. Snap it.
One, two, three.
Aww!
Wait.
I didn't press the button.
One more.
No!
No more.
I'm not doing it.
No!
Let's go, Arnold.
Hurry up.
Where are we going?
Hey, you know I'm really glad
Tua suggested you act with me?
I think we have great acting chemistry.
I should be thanking you too.
You're so talented.
You set the bar high, so I have to keep up.
Of course. I'm top-tier in this faculty.
Wow, the drunker you get,
the more confident you are.
Naturally.
I'm Dean, Prince of Fine Arts.
Gosh!
Alright, Prince of Fine Arts.
You almost collapsed.
I almost did.
Is this for content too?
Where's the camera?
No camera.
Just me.
Okay.
Romeo, I want to stay with you tonight.
Can I?
We should head back
before someone sees us, Romeo.
When we get to the tent,
you go in first. I'll follow after.
Why?
So Pete doesn't get suspicious.
Hey, where are you going?
Jack, Jack, hold on.
Let me catch my breath.
I'm tired.
Are you alright?
I told you I'd wake up to run with you.
You've really changed.
The old you wouldn't even get up.
I told you I'd change.
Hello?
(Hi, son.)
(Have you talked to your sister lately?)
Not at all, Mom. Why?
(Her boyfriend hit her again.)
(It was a bad fight this time.)
(I'm really worried.)
(But I can't leave work to go to Bangkok.)
(If you have time,
can you check on her for me?)
Sure.
I'll go check on her.
Is something wrong?
My big sister.
She moved to Bangkok with her boyfriend.
At first, everything was fine.
But later, whenever they fight,
it turns physical.
Mom and I have been telling her
to leave him, but she won't.
This time must be serious.
Otherwise, Mom wouldn't have called me.
If there's anything I can do, let me know.
It's okay. It's a family
issue. I'll handle it.
Dean.
Your issues are my issues.
Let's keep going.
Guess I have to admit it.
I do want to take care of him.
Look at you. Are you good?
You should have something hot.
It'll help with the hangover.
Hey, they have congee too?
I asked the staff to make it.
It should help you feel better.
Thank you.
Eat with me.
It's okay. I don't want to take your food.
You're hungover too.
Besides, it tastes better
when we eat together.
Guys, look at that!
The old place brings
together the old flames.
They can't cut each other off
because they're meant to be together.
Because they're what?
Meant to be together!
Don't overthink it.
They're just teasing.
Dean and I…
we're getting back together.
Yay!
See?
You heard that?
Watch out for the ants over there.
It's getting way too sweet.
I knew it.
You two can't escape each other.
If this play flops, I'm
cursing you two for life.
It's alright.
Right now, the whole
mountain is still pink.
Let's do it.
Call it a fresh start.
(Next Episode) You exposed Dean
as a host before, did it even affect him?
So you're just going to
let those two off the hook?
Don't think nobody
notices what you're doing.
You'd better be careful.
I really want to know
how Jack would see you…
if he found out.
Happy three-year anniversary.
Will you marry me?
Will you quit playing around?
If we're still together in the future,
I'd want to get married.
Now it's clear to you
how we feel about each other.
But I want to make it clearer.