LOVE IN THE CLOUDS
ADAPTED FROM BAI LU CHENG
SHUANG'S "LOVE IN THE CLOUDS"
A FEW MONTHS AGO
Ming Yi.
What talent.
Truly one of a kind.
All these years at Moonlit Blossoms,
I've never seen
a dance as unique as yours.
You've practiced it countless times!
How can you still not
remember a few simple moves?
Madam, go easy on her.
It's my fault.
I taught her the wrong steps last night.
Zhang Tai,
you've always been the best dancer here.
You never make mistakes.
You're saying this
just to protect the newcomer, aren't you?
Do you think I won't punish you
because I favor you?
Go. Both of you.
Pour a bucket over yourselves.
I just recovered from illness last month.
If I fall sick again,
Immortal Xue,
Immortal Hao, and Immortal Liu
won't get to see me.
Don't blame me if
you lose business because of it.
You're getting
far too bold for your own good.
Don't push your luck.
MOONLIT BLOSSOMS
Madam,
I'm a bad dancer and
haven't practiced enough.
It's my fault.
Moonlit Blossoms has
always rewarded and punished fairly.
Don't break the rules because of me.
EPISODE 9
- Immortal Ji.
My apologies, fairies.
I'm here today for…
Who?
Her?
I'm here with
Fairy Ming Yi to get something done.
How dull.
Take this.
- Eat it yourself.
- Here.
I got my hopes up for nothing.
Seriously?
Even if there's no deal,
we can part on good terms.
Not even a word to make me stay?
Want some snacks?
MOONLIT BLOSSOMS
So pretty.
How lovely.
- Zhang Tai, you're so kind.
- What a big pearl.
And these jade pieces are so exquisite.
I'm getting married.
General Xun Ming said you could
pick whatever you like from these gifts.
Zhang Tai,
you're marrying General Xun Ming?
Why didn't you tell me?
Immortal Ji, what are you holding?
Some snacks for you.
Thank you, Immortal Ji.
You're welcome.
Now that I'm engaged,
I shouldn't visit
Moonlit Blossoms anymore.
But since we've
been sisters all these years,
even if we won't see each other again,
I want to say goodbye properly.
Zhang Tai,
your general treats you so well.
No wonder you fell for him.
Yes. He's learned, courteous,
honest, and loyal.
Since when do you praise men like that?
You used to say things like,
"He's so handsome."
- "He's so tall."
- "He's so rich."
"I wish he'd do my eyebrows."
Take your time choosing your gift.
I must return to serve the general now.
Wait.
Zhang Tai, how's your wrist injury?
Have you been using
the medicine I gave you?
It's much better. Thank you, Ming Yi.
Ming Yi, what's wrong?
Her injury isn't on her wrist.
It's on her back.
She is not Zhang Tai.
There's a puppet
mark on the back of her neck.
That wasn't the real Zhang Tai.
It was a puppet made in her likeness.
Then where's the real Zhang Tai?
To make a puppet
move like a certain person,
one has to extract
the seven senses from the person.
Only then can the puppet look convincing.
Once the three souls and
seven senses are extracted,
the person will die
within 15 days.
Ming Yi, Immortal Ji,
is there any way to save Zhang Tai?
She was always so kind.
Every time the Mistress punished me,
she took the beating for me.
When Xianxian's family was in trouble,
she gave her money.
The Jingwei Tribe is wiped out.
Zhang Tai has no family in this world.
We must help her.
Yes, please help her.
A bit higher.
No… I'm exhausted.
Hungry?
How could I not be?
I haven't eaten in days.
Why haven't you eaten?
I ran out of money.
How's that possible?
You always get the biggest tips.
I just lost my appetite. That's all.
You're lying, aren't you?
Last time at the Huansha Market,
you bought me an eyebrow pencil.
It was so expensive.
Did you spend all your money on it?
You're overthinking it.
You liked it, didn't you?
Come on. It's no big deal. Stop pouting.
You could hang an oil bottle off that lip.
Not cute at all.
- Are you ticklish?
- No.
Then what are you afraid of?
Stop it! Stop!
- I'm ticklish!
- You call this not ticklish?
I am!
Ow…
- My back hurts… It hurts.
- Are you all right?
- Does it really hurt?
- Just messing with you.
- What's this?
- Scallion pancake.
I don't want it.
Then what do you want?
Roast duck.
You're a bird. You can't eat roast duck.
Dreams are free.
Here, I'll share a duck leg with you.
- I'm starving.
- Me too.
How I wish for a proper meal.
Lord Ji, I have a favor to ask.
To be honest, I still feel a bit wronged
about being tied up
and punished last time.
Did I give you all
those jewels for nothing?
Of course not.
But I was hoping
for a little more in return.
Say it. What do you want me to do?
Lord Ji, you're clever.
You must have guessed it already.
If we are to save Zhang Tai,
we'll be facing
the strongest fox in Jixing Abyss.
I won't be able to
protect you at all times.
Xun Ming could tear you apart with ease.
Are you sure about this?
It sounds
like you're not
refusing to help me save her.
Thank you, Lord Ji.
It's just a friendship.
Is that really worth so much to you?
Yes.
To me, friendship weighs
more than a thousand mountains.
My wife said
that since she was married to me,
she no longer wished to
meet anyone from her past.
But since you requested it, Immortal Ji,
I can't say no.
General, I'm just too
worried about Zhang Tai.
Once I see her myself, I'll stop worrying.
This way, please.
- Zhang Tai!
- We have guests.
Zhang Tai, it's us.
I'm not receiving visitors.
Look up. It's me.
Again, I'm not seeing anyone today,
no matter who it is.
- No, I have to talk to her.
- Ming Yi, what are you doing?
She's ignoring me.
She must be angry with me.
If she won't see you,
she must have her reasons.
Don't cause a scene.
- Lord Ji…
- My wife has cut ties with her past.
You insisted on seeing her,
and I allowed it.
Are you still not satisfied?
General, that's not what she meant.
Lord Ji, please
persuade the General for me.
- Enough, Ming Yi.
- I just want to talk to her. Please…
Quiet.
General, perhaps she's simply hungry.
She hasn't eaten.
That's why she's being so difficult.
Would you be kind
enough to grant us a meal?
We'll leave once we finish.
Right?
All right.
Please, enjoy. Once you're done,
please see yourselves out.
Thank you for your hospitality, General.
Go on, Ming Yi.
Ming Yi, aren't you hungry?
Eat up.
Try this.
You won't eat a thing yourself,
but you have no problem making me eat.
Try this.
Here. Let me feed you.
How about some chicken?
Easy. Stop feeding me.
Do you like it?
Open your mouth.
Go on.
Fire!
Look, it's huge!
General, what's going on?
Spit it out.
Lord Ji, that was impressive.
It's just a natural fire.
You should be quite familiar with it.
- The illusion is in place.
- Let's go.
Zhang Tai.
A puppet loses awareness when separated
from its master for too long.
Isn't it dangerous to cast spells
at a place so close to him?
Xun Ming isn't easy to deal with.
Do you have a solution in mind?
This puppet
retains only two of
Zhang Tai's senses, strength and vitality.
Xun Ming has separated
her three souls and seven senses.
Illusion Trap. A fox tribe technique.
You know about that?
Our mistress comes
from the Yousu Fox Tribe.
I've been worried about Zhang Tai.
Of course I know
something about the tribe.
Xun Ming used Zhang Tai and lured her in,
trapping her within his Illusory Realm.
Travel with your primordial spirit,
and I can use her two senses
to let you see her.
But you won't be able to bring her back.
Only by finding and recreating Xun Ming's
most cherished memory
can you truly enter his Illusory Realm
and save Zhang Tai.
I can find out what that memory is
from Zhang Tai.
But let me warn you,
traveling with
your primordial spirit is dangerous.
I'll set up the array here.
You'll only have one incense stick's time,
barely enough for a few words.
If Xun Ming comes,
I'll go immediately and leave you behind.
I'm counting on you, Lord Ji.
Be careful.
Zhang Tai…
Zhang Tai.
That's Ming Yi's voice.
Ming Yi, is that you?
Zhang Tai.
Ming Yi.
Ming Yi, where are you?
I can't see you.
Zhang Tai, stop struggling.
Xun Ming trapped your primordial
spirit in his Illusory Realm.
I can only reach
you through your two senses.
But I can't pull you out.
Only by recreating what
the Yousu Fox Tribe treasures most
can I break the Illusory Realm
and free you.
So tell me,
what is Xun Ming's most cherished memory?
Tell me everything between you two.
All right.
Back at Moonlit Blossoms,
Xun Ming wouldn't let go of my hand.
He wouldn't look away from me.
He was different from all the other men.
And as you know,
he was tall, handsome,
and seemed rich.
I naively thought
I'd finally found
someone to spend my life with.
But after marrying him, I realized
he really was different from others.
He's insane!
Officail Website : kissasian.be
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
He kept performing
fox-tribe wedding rituals with me
again and again,
never skipping a single step.
We've done it at least 20 times.
And every time,
he made me play music with him
until my fingers hurt,
and he still wouldn't stop.
He even forced a new name on me:
Mu Xinliu.
- Mu Xinliu?
- The more I thought about it,
the weirder it felt.
Maybe he had a lover by that name?
But how could I resemble her?
No, impossible.
I don't believe it.
No one could be as beautiful as I am.
Get to the point.
What's his most cherished memory?
His most cherished memory?
I… I'm not sure.
It probably has something
to do with that woman he loved.
Do you remember how you got
trapped in this Illusory Realm?
Well, I kept talking about going
back to Moonlit Blossoms to see everyone,
and it upset Xun Ming.
To cheer him up, I gave him wine
and tried to get him to talk
about that woman he loved.
He got drunk
and kept saying,
"Whether you have
true feelings for me or not,
you're the only one I love."
Then he tried to kiss me.
Xinliu…
If it'd been only once or
twice, it would've been fine.
He's not bad-looking,
so I didn't really mind.
- But after 20 kisses, I went numb.
- Zhang Tai!
We're running out of time.
Once the incense
burns out, I have to leave.
Get to the point.
I'm getting there.
We held another wedding ceremony.
The same ritual. The same steps.
I'm tired of playing music.
He walked toward me,
and I suddenly fainted.
When I woke up, I was here.
Here? In this forest?
Forest?
What forest?
From what I see,
you're trapped in a forest.
Where are you really?
I'm in Xun Ming's Dengxian Cave.
He… he locked me in what was supposed
to be our bridal chamber.
You are just like her.
Zhang Tai, listen to me.
You are probably trapped
inside an Illusory Realm Xun Ming created.
Think carefully.
Is there anything strange around you?
Ming Yi,
I hear strange sounds.
Women's voices.
I don't think I'm the only one.
Before me,
he probably married many others
who resembled the woman he loved.
They might all be dead now.
And I might also…
Ming Yi,
I don't think I can hold on much longer.
There's no time left.
I haven't eaten this much in a while.
Why did you eat so much?
You kept feeding me.
Here.
Are you full now?
General, you're back.
Is the house all right?
Thank you for your hospitality.
We've finished our meal.
We'll be leaving now.
- Thank you, General.
- Let's go.
The fox tribe sure makes good chicken.
Little glutton.
Zhang Tai didn't know
what Xun Ming's most cherished memory was,
but she thought
it would be about his unforgettable love,
Mu Xinliu.
Someone from the Mu clan?
I know where we might find clues.
So one can enter the Langhuan Pavilion
simply by registering during the day.
Then last time, why did you…?
It was theft last time.
This time, we're borrowing books.
Not the same thing.
Not this one either.
GENEALOGY OF THE MU CLAN
You found it?
It's the royal genealogy of Jixing Abyss.
Good job, Lord Ji. Let me see.
So only Judgment Hall officials
can touch this book?
Wait, Lord Ji.
If you open it by force and damage it,
how will we explain that?
This flimsy seal is nothing to me.
Greetings, Immortal Situ.
He's here.
Hide. Trust me.
Hurry…
What a coincidence.
Sister Yi?
Greetings, Immortal Situ.
Sister Yi, what are you doing here?
- "Sister Yi."
- Is there something you want to know?
I can help you.
I can even make it seem
like the Judgment Hall is behind it.
It's nothing special.
Immortal Ji often
takes me out to socialize,
and there's a lot I don't know.
He said the Judgment Hall's archive
has plenty of books I can borrow and read
to avoid making mistakes.
But I just can't open this one.
You're in charge here.
Surely you can open it, right?
You're keeping Ji Bozai company.
He should be bearing the consequences.
He has no right to
make you do anything for him.
Thank you in advance, Immortal Situ.
Please, help me this once.
Fine.
I'll help with whatever you need.
However,
could you not
mention Ji Bozai in front of me again?
All right.
Thank you, Immortal Situ.
MU QIBAI
Are you investigating Lord Hanfeng?
Investigate?
That sounds harsh.
I only mean to learn more about him,
given his high status.
This royal genealogy
is all about the Mu clan.
If they marry outside the clan,
does it go unrecorded?
By custom,
once two people form a heart imprint
and carve their names on
the Marriage Stone at Mengyuan Pond,
their names are
entered into the genealogy.
MU XINLIU, MARRIED TO XUN MING
Mu Xinliu married Xun Ming.
Jixing Abyss really excels
at making artifacts.
Even this book has
more than meets the eye.
Sister Yi, don't say things like that.
If anyone overheard,
they might suspect
you're not from Jixing Abyss.
I suddenly feel a chill.
It is a bit cold here.
What a coincidence.
Immortal Ji, you've been here all along.
Why did you hide?
I wasn't hiding.
We were on a tryst.
But someone intruded unexpectedly.
By the way,
I heard you call her "Sister Yi" just now.
Since you are so eager to be her family,
why not drop the formalities
and call me "Brother-in-law"?
Why so shy all of a sudden?
We still have matters to attend to.
We'll be going now.
Again, thank you for
your help today, Immortal Situ.
Let's go. Come on.
Come on.
Hurry…
Thank you.
Your Lordship, didn't you find any clues
about the Golden Millet Dream
in the archive?
So far, there are no new discoveries.
I only know the Bo clan's old residence
on Zhangwei Mountain was exposed,
and Mu Qibai took the chance
to seize the "Bo's Medical Classics."
But the formula of the Golden Millet Dream
was only found in fragments.
Even the Sunken Abyss
failed to reproduce it.
If I can't find the Golden Millet Dream,
I'll never have
spiritual veins in this life.
Even without them,
you mastered the Thousand Insect Spell.
But I can hardly compete in
the Qingyun Tournament with that.
Don't lose heart.
There's still Ji Bozai.
They all say he has
the Golden Millet Dream.
It vanished from the Six Realms long ago.
How do you think
he gained spiritual veins all of a sudden?
He's probably connected to the Bo clan.
He might even be one of its descendants.
- Why is he always brought up?
- What?
Nothing.
Anyway, since Jixing Abyss has been
refining medicines in the Sunken Abyss,
they must have the formulas.
I was hoping to find clues in
the Judgment Hall's archives,
something to help me make
the Golden Millet Dream myself,
but I found nothing.
The fastest way
is still to steal it from Ji Bozai.
Fuyue,
that makes me feel so useless.
Then I'll go steal it.
I'll be the useless one. Is that better?
By the way,
I checked for you.
After Ming Xian lost
the last Qingyun Tournament,
she vanished from Yaoguang Mountain.
Some say she defected.
As for why she reverted to her female form
and is now staying by Ji Bozai's side,
I haven't been able to figure it out yet.
You looked into her?
Wasn't it you who wanted
news of her, Your Lordship?
But I never said to investigate her.
Fuyue,
you must not hurt Ming Yi.
This is the first time you've scolded me.
I'm sorry, Fuyue.
I will follow your orders, Your Lordship.
I…
Lord Ji.
Are you close to Situ Ling?
You've known him a long time, right?
Jealous again.
Of course not.
Immortal Situ rescued me and Ruo Shui
from a netherbeast.
I only stayed in contact with him
out of gratitude.
We're not close.
Then why is he so willing to help you?
Earlier,
he used Mu Qibai's artifact
to search Jixing Abyss,
causing a huge scene,
but then he let it slide so easily.
Maybe…
maybe he took a fancy to me.
Stay away from him.
I'm worried he'll trick you
into saying things you shouldn't.
I didn't ask for an explanation.
Lord Ji, you were right.
Mu Xinliu really was Lord Hanfeng's cousin
and Xun Ming's late wife.
According to Zhang Tai,
Xun Ming made her reenact
the Yousu Fox Tribe
wedding again and again,
and she entered the Illusory Realm
during the ceremony.
So I think
Xun Ming's most cherished memory
must be his wedding to Mu Xinliu.
To enter Xun Ming's Illusory Realm,
you must recreate his wedding.
If we are to recreate
a Yousu Fox Tribe wedding,
we can't use an outsider to play along.
It would be too unpredictable.
You have a point.
Why don't you and
Granny Xun stage the wedding?
That way, we can respond quickly
if something goes wrong.
But if Granny Xun and I hold a wedding
and invite Xun Ming,
will he really attend?
You're actually willing to do this?
Has it occurred to you
that Granny Xun might refuse?
She would?
In that case,
the only people suitable
to stage this fake wedding
are Ming Yi and you.
But you don't trust her, do you?
All this time,
Ming Yi has had no
contact with the outside.
Besides, with her weak spiritual power,
she poses no threat.
When you enter the Illusory Realm
and get rid of Xun Ming,
even if she notices something,
we can deal with her quickly.
But Your Lordship, I must warn you:
when the time comes,
you must be ruthless with Ming Yi.
If she must be sacrificed,
do not hesitate.
Fine.
I know what to do.
It's settled then.
Your acting has never been better.
You can go to Ming Yi now.
Ask for her hand and
trick her into marrying you.
What a plan.
Go.
Let me think.
Lord Ji, didn't you say we should check
Moonlit Blossoms
for any missed clues about
the Yousu Fox Tribe? Hurry…
Are you really worried about Zhang Tai?
Of course.
Before I left the Illusory Realm,
Zhang Tai said she could barely hold on.
You also said
that once someone's three
souls and seven senses are taken,
they won't live more than 15 days. I…
Your acting has never been better.
You can go to Ming Yi now.
Ask for her hand and
trick her into marrying you.
No fighting or bloodshed needed.
Just get married and it's done.
Ask for her hand and
trick her into marrying you.
So simple. I believe in you.
Just get married and it's done.
Ask for her hand and
trick her into marrying you.
No fighting needed.
So simple. I believe in you.
- Ask for her hand…
- It'll be a piece of cake.
- And trick her into marrying you.
- Just get married and it's done.
Marry me, Lord Ji.
We'll separate afterward.
That will be easy.
Let's get married and save her first.
- Besides…
- All right.
Officail Website : kissasian.be
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
I know
you only want this wedding
because you want to save Zhang Tai.
Rest assured. This marriage will be fake,
and I will only invite Xun Ming.
We will not carve
our names on the Marriage Stone.
Nor will we form a heart imprint.
Your reputation
won't be affected in any way.
Lord Ji, you needn't worry about me.
As for carving names
and forming a heart imprint…
You have sacrificed
enough for your friends.
You must not sacrifice any more.
Trust me.
You always think things through.
You refused to marry me before.
Why are you willing to make
such a sacrifice to help me now?
Do you have some other plan in mind?
Must I always have some scheme?
Thank you for helping me.
You're helping me out of a sense of duty.
I will not let you suffer for it.
After we save her, we'll part if you wish.
Although I like you,
I will not cling to you.
All right.
After we save her, we'll part if you wish.
Although I like you,
I will not cling to you.
Is Your Lordship plotting
how to make Xun Ming attend the ceremony?
I already know how to make him come.
Then what are you thinking?
INVITATION TO JI
BOZAI AND MING YI'S WEDDING
How dare Ji Bozai hold his wedding
at Xinliu's burial site?
Luosheng Forest.
It was also the place
where you and my cousin pledged your love.
If they chose that place,
they must expect you to show up.
Go if you want.
I will not stop you.
But remember this:
do not lose your composure because of it.
Don't worry.
I'm not that useless.
INVITATION, MING YI
JI BOZAI