I've never thought
that the legendary prodigy,
Young Master Zhuge
of Great Yong's Zhuge family,
would fall to this point.
Wasn't he
the most feared spy master?
How could he end up so badly wounded?
Xing,
I know you have many questions,
and I should give you some explanation.
But I have my reasons not to.
Wait for me to settle everything.
Zhuge Yue,
can you stay for me?
Yes.
You're right.
But this is my business.
It has nothing to do with you.
I didn't even notice
your forbearance and pain.
And I've been resenting and blaming you
all this time,
never once thinking about
how much hardship you've endured.
If he intended not to tell you,
fearing you'd worry,
you naturally wouldn't know.
This poison in him is very strange,
twisting along his heart meridians
and limbs,
yet it moves like thread.
I've tried my best but couldn't remove it.
For now, I can only use needles
to seal his acupoints
to protect his organs,
but how long this will hold
depends on his own strength.
Your Highness,
what should we do with our plan
to rescue General He?
We don't have much time left.
At this point,
we can only wait for He Xiao
to be handed over to the Black Eagle Army
and look for an opportunity
when they're on the way back to Great Yan.
Tomorrow, I'll go with Fang Miaomiao
to gather information first.
[REBIRTH]
[Episode 15]
[Lincheng]
Once the Yong Army opens the gate,
and the Great Yan prisoners of war
walk out through it,
we'll be able to locate
He Xiao.
Open the gate!
They're coming.
He Xiao!
Oh no, it's a trap!
Close the city gate!
Hurry!
Charge!
What's that sound?
Something must have happened.
Don't get up. I'll go help.
[He Xiao, General of Xiuli Army]
General Chu!
Get on the horse!
Yes!
Stop those three!
Don't let them escape!
He Xiao, Miaomiao, you go first!
I'll cover you!
My Lord, you can't do that!
It's an order!
Your Highness!
Go!
Run!
Young Master! Young Master!
Young Master!
Young Master,
it's me, Shiyi!
[Yue Shiyi, Moon Guard of Qingshan Manor]
Shiyi?
Young Master.
Shiyi.
Why are you guys here?
Chu.
Come back with me.
Let's go back to Great Yan.
Yan Xun,
it's over between us.
Chu,
we've faced death together,
sharing both joy and sorrow.
I don't believe there's anything
between us that can't be resolved.
Why are you being so resolute?
Yan Xun,
we used to walk side by side,
and we were each other's only comrades
and family.
The path we once walked
has already come to an end.
Look behind.
We've long since gone our separate ways.
I was born a slave,
with only one goal in mind—
to abolish slavery and stop the wars,
so that even those with lives
as worthless as grass
could have the right to live.
But all that remains in your eyes
is revenge.
You want to use fresh blood
to wash away the hatred of your family
and Great Yan.
Chu,
this world is inherently
a survival of the fittest.
There's never been such a thing
as justice or fairness.
There was no justice
when the Yan clan perished tragically
at Jiuyou Platform.
When we were imprisoned
in the Yingge Courtyard,
with no one to depend on,
no one was there for us.
When I lost everything and was in despair,
the only person by my side
was you.
Chu,
to me,
the world
and justice
are nothing compared
to the bond between us.
Yan Xun.
I was wrong.
I thought we shared the same ideals.
Because we depended on each other so much,
I saw you as my closest person.
But now we no longer walk the same path.
Please, let go of yourself,
and let go of me.
Chu.
I can guarantee that,
on your own,
you won't be able to fight your way out.
Zhuge Yue?
Yan Xun,
I didn't expect us to meet like this.
Xing.
You said yesterday
that you wanted me
to stay by your side forever.
I promise you.
I want you to stay by my side forever too.
To the ends of the earth,
we live and die together.
Zhuge Yue.
You shot an arrow at me
outside Zhenhuangcheng.
I paid you back at the frozen lake.
Now we are even.
If you leave now
and stop interfering between Chu and me,
I can pretend you were never here.
What happened between us
can be left in the past,
but if you persist in your ways,
even your father...
Shut up!
You have no right to judge my father!
Attention, everyone!
Whoever brings me Zhuge Yue's head
will be made
a Marquis of a Thousand Households!
Yes!
Let's go!
Retreat!
His Majesty is wise and brave.
He is the one chosen by the gods
of Great Yan.
Yes.
I knew it.
Under the guise
of a prisoner exchange, His Majesty
captured Lincheng
and completely deceived
those from Great Yong.
Soon, we'll be able
to march all the way to Zhenhuangcheng
and avenge our fallen brothers.
Yes, avenge them!
Come on!
Let's raise our glasses
to Great Yan
and our new King!
To His Majesty!
Your Majesty.
I heard you led the Black Eagle Army
and took Lincheng.
I'm here to congratulate you
and Great Yan.
We won a great victory at Lincheng.
Your Majesty, why aren't you celebrating
with the soldiers?
Did you see Chu?
What?
I saw her.
She also came to Lincheng.
She rescued He Xiao.
Your Majesty, you saw her?
If you see her next time,
bring her back to me.
If she can't be brought back alive,
dead is fine.
Your Majesty.
Haven't you always wanted her dead?
It should be fine, right?
It...
It should be fine.
Should?
You think I don't know?
An hour after taking the Huiyuan Pill,
one's vital energy is restored,
but it shortens lifespan.
And you tell me it should be fine?
Don't...
Don't blame me.
It was Young Master Zhuge who insisted...
Xing.
I forced him.
I had to save you at that time.
Xing!
Xing.
It's me.
What do you want?
I came to tell you
everything that's happened
during all this time.
I don't want to know anymore.
Leave.
Come on.
I never thought
I'd still be alive
to drink such fine wine.
After Young Master
fell into the frozen lake,
Qingshan Manor sent us Moon Guards
to the front line.
Some of us died, some were injured,
and those captured suffered greatly.
Who would have thought
we'd see the Young Master again
and be here alive,
eating meat and drinking wine?
To us being alive.
Cheers.
How can you be here
drinking such fine wine without me?
How did you do it?
I didn't even notice,
and the glass is already in your hand.
I just witnessed it.
Miss Fang's nickname is "Master Thief."
Looks like there's nothing she can't take.
You...
Tastes good.
This is what happened
after I fell into the frozen lake.
I was saved by King Ximeng,
took the deadly poison Blood on Snow,
and became his shadow.
I promised to do 3 things for him
in exchange for the antidote.
Zhuge Yue,
why are you only telling me this now?
Are you mute?
Why are you only saying it now?
Tell me! Why?
Why? Why?
Zhuge Yue, promise me
that from now on, you won't hide
anything from me anymore,
and you won't avoid me.
Did you hear me?
Remember,
you are not allowed
to hide anything from me anymore.
Considering your injuries,
I will let you go this time.
Your Highness.
I...
Young Master Zhuge!
I went through a great deal of trouble
to save your life.
At the very least,
you should follow medical advice—
no alcohol, no intimacy,
and avoid meat and heavy food.
This...
[Zhuge Yue] [Yan Xun] [Li Ce]
You don't understand.
Yan Xun and Her Highness
have known each other since childhood
and have gone through many hardships
together.
Even though they have now
turned against each other,
the scar in Her Highness's heart
is still there.
She can't forget him even if she wants to.
If Yan Xun keeps pushing like this,
the embers could easily reignite.
If you ask me,
our princess will eventually
return to Great Yan
as its princess consort.
She's not stupid.
Why would she go to a desolate place
like Great Yan
to be a princess consort?
It's better for her to stay in Biantang
and be the Crown Princess.
Our Crown Prince is wealthy
and quite romantic.
She has suffered so much before.
Only by staying with him
can she live a good life.
What do you think?
I... I choose Zhuge Yue.
I think
Miss Xing will definitely choose our boss.
Why Zhuge Yue?
Because our boss
is both talented and handsome.
Yue Shiyi,
your boss is not even here.
Why are you still flattering him?
Be honest,
who are you really betting on?
I...
You've left out an option in this bet.
I saw everything.
I bet on the fourth one.
The fourth option?
Xing will not be anyone's
princess consort.
She will only be herself.
Why do I feel like
he's cursing our princess
to stay unmarried for her whole life?
Lady Chu,
it's so dusty outside.
We'd better close the window
so the dust won't come in.
Stop!
General Chu.
I'm getting a bit tired riding.
And the scenery here is not bad.
How about we switch?
Sure.
I was just feeling a bit stuffy.
Let's switch.
I get carsick easily.
What do you mean, Yue Shiyi?
-Don't meddle.
-Alright.
Yue Shiyi, Fang Miaomiao,
get in the carriage.
I will ride the horse.
Don't you think
Zhan Ziyu has been a bit strange lately?
Ever since the incident at the inn,
he hasn't caused any trouble.
He doesn't even come near our carriages.
Isn't that a good thing, Your Highness?
Didn't he buy an eagle for a high price?
He's been playing with it all the time.
I think
he was probably
scared out of his wits by you last time.
I don't think it's that simple.
Rest assured, Your Highness.
We will arrive in Tangjing
in the blink of an eye.
As long as we enter the city safely,
this hurdle will be behind us.
No matter how he tries to cause trouble,
it won't work.
[Tangjing]
Slow down.
Your Highness.
Since you have returned safely
from this trip,
I will now return to the palace to report.
I won't disturb Your Highness
and your distinguished guests any further.
Thank you for your hard work, Lord Zhan.
Give this to Lord Yu of the Ministry of Personnel's
Supervisory Department.
Tell him it's Her Majesty's will.
Yes.
I came especially to thank Her Majesty
for arranging the marriage
between the Prince of Luo and me.
[Linrui Palace]
Please wait a moment, My Lady.
Beauty Hu is inside
paying her respects to Her Majesty.
I will go and announce your arrival.
[Beauty Hu]
Let her in.
You must be the girl
the Prince of Luo is about to marry.
Your Highness, you are...
It doesn't matter if you don't know me.
I know you.
You are the famous Princess Chun'er
of Great Yong,
who almost married the new King
of Great Yan, Yan Xun.
Pardon me.
I shouldn't have touched a sore spot.
But it's all good now.
You will soon be the Princess Consort of Luo
in our Biantang.
However, there is one thing
that surprises me.
You don't look...
like Princess Fu at all.
The Prince of Luo has been deeply in love
with Princess Fu for years.
Why did he suddenly
have a change of heart?
What did you say?
Don't tell me you don't know.
The Prince of Luo and Princess Fu
were once engaged.
The Prince of Luo has remained unmarried
for years because of Princess Fu.
Now that Princess Fu
has been brought back,
we all thought
the Prince of Luo would resume
his engagement with Princess Fu.
Is the Princess Fu you're talking about
the one in the Crown Prince's Mansion?
The Prince of Luo was once engaged to her?
Beauty Hu.
Her Majesty?
Your Majesty.
Come here.
What did you just say?
Your Majesty,
I...
I was wrong.
Servants.
Beauty Hu has behaved improperly
in words and actions
and slandered a prince.
According to palace rules,
slap her 20 times.
Your Majesty,
I was wrong!
Please forgive me!
Your Majesty!
How could this be?
Chun'er!
Chun'er.
You misunderstood.
This portrait is...
It's Princess Fu in this portrait.
You were engaged to her, weren't you?
Then do you know that
the Princess Fu in the Crown Prince's Mansion
is an impostor,
and that she is Chu Qiao,
a convicted slave from Great Yong?
I know.
Her Majesty had suspected it long ago
and called me to identify her.
She and the Crown Prince
privately asked me to help cover it up.
You actually testified
for a convicted slave?
Yes.
So you like Princess Fu.
And because she looks like Princess Fu,
you like her too,
don't you?
No, Chun'er.
I don't.
I did like Fu before,
but I know very well that she is not...
Then burn it!
You claim that you like me!
You liar!
Li Yan,
you don't have to love me.
You can have someone else in your heart,
but it can't be her.
It can't be Chu Qiao!
My Lady, your wedding is coming up soon.
The crowd here is quite mixed.
We should head back early,
or His Highness will be worried.
Why go back?
He won't worry about me.
I'm just a substitute.
The person in his heart is Princess Fu.
Your Highness,
you shouldn't think like that.
Since His Highness met you,
he has changed a lot.
Miss, have you seen this person?
No.
I'll take this.
Miss,
have you seen this woman?
[Prince of Luo's Mansion]
Your Highness! Your Highness!
Your Highness,
this is the nuptial wine
for you and His Highness.
You can't drink it all by yourself.
I want more!
Bring more wine!
Your Highness, you are really drunk.
You can't drink anymore.
Your Highness,
this wedding fan can only be removed
when His Highness comes.
Otherwise it would bring bad luck.
Chunxing.
Do you know how many times
I've been married?
Three times.
This is the 3rd time.
The first time, on my wedding day,
snow was falling heavily.
My groom rebelled
and led troops against my father.
I begged him,
but he wouldn't listen.
Instead, he threw the wedding robe
I made for him
onto the ground,
letting horses trample over it.
Your Highness!
He walked past me so coldly,
so decisively.
He walked past my body
and shattered my heart.
The second time,
I carefully arranged
a fake wedding for myself.
Your Highness, you are really drunk.
Here.
Chunxing.
You know what?
I finally got married.
What else is there for me
to look forward to?
Your Highness, be careful!
Your Highness, your foot...
Chun'er!
Chun'er, are you alright?
Chun'er.
If you don't want to get married yet,
we can pretend
today's wedding never happened.
I can keep waiting for you,
until you fall in love with me,
until the day
you truly want to be my wife.
I heard Her Majesty likes jade,
so I specially found a fine piece.
Her Majesty is not in the palace.
Princess Consort of Luo, please follow me
to the hall and wait for a moment.
Your Highness, please have some tea.
[Qifeng Palace]
I have already handed the evidence
obtained from the trip to Qiongzhou
to Lord Yu of the Ministry of Personnel.
That King Ximeng is a fake.
He was sent by Ximeng to Biantang
to obtain Director Zhang's
manufacturing compendium.
I just don't know how he
got involved with the Crown Prince.
This son of mine is quite something.
I really underestimated him.
There is another thing
that I also find very strange.
What is it?
In the team
of the Crown Prince and Ximeng this time,
I didn't see Princess Fu,
that Chu Qiao.
And as far as I know,
she is not
in the Crown Prince's Mansion either.
Are you saying Chu Qiao is missing?
Yes.
I worry she will affect our grand plan.
Then let's strike first
and do it quickly
to avoid any complications.
As long as we solidify
the Crown Prince's charges of treason
and collusion with the enemy,
even 10 Chu Qiaos
won't be able to save him.
Today is the 6th, right?
Today is the 6th.
Are the carriages ready?
Your Majesty,
the carriages are ready outside.
But today is the Greater Heat.
For years, you've gone to chant sutras
for Crown Prince Maocheng
on the sixth of every month.
But it's exceptionally hot this year.
I'm afraid your body
can't handle the journey.
It's fine.
Let's go to Tianlong Temple.
Your Majesty!
I have something important to report!
Don't you know what day it is today?
Rushing into the palace so recklessly.
Beauty,
what happened to your face?
Your Majesty,
I know very well
that today is the day
you go to Tianlong Temple
to chant sutras for Crown Prince Maocheng.
Your devotion
is known to the heavens and the earth.
But do you know
what Her Majesty has been doing
every time you're away?
What do you mean?
Greetings, Your Majesty!
Greetings, Beauty Hu!
Where is the Empress? Why isn't she here?
Her Majesty...
Her Majesty is resting.
You lowly servant!
Empress.
What are you two women doing?
I...
I'm keeping Her Majesty company
in the bath.
Today isn't a festival.
Why did you release so many sky lanterns?
Zhuge Yue,
what's your plan?
I will never willingly
an incompetent coward!
I am not!
Her Majesty orders
that the Queen of Lingyue
and the false King Ximeng
be arrested immediately!
Since you have moved on,
how could I be dwelling on it?