Previously on
Seducing Drake Palma.
Hi, Drake!
Mind if I join you?
Wait!
What about Shaira?
What if she gets mad?
I can handle her being mad at me.
I can’t handle you
not talking to me.
- Seriously.
- You know what?
Drake?
I just had so much fun
with you, Drake!
Here.
Is this really my role?
The one who hands you a handkerchief
whenever you cry.
You can talk to me, you know.
I’m willing to listen.
I’m waiting.
You don’t know
anything about love.
You’re really underestimating me.
Come on.
Maybe I can actually help you.
Why is he like that?
I am his girlfriend, right?
I’m probably entitled...
And I have the right to ask, but…
Then again,
he doesn’t even ask me
anything.
Maybe
I shouldn’t ask him either, right?
Drama doesn’t suit you.
You’re an Amazon!
Ouch!
You’re hitting me again!
You’re annoying, you know that?
Why?
I’m telling you my problem and
you’re just saying all sorts of nonsense!
Well,
you said I don’t know
anything about love problems,
so I’m making do with
what I’m actually good at.
And what exactly are you good at?
Make you laugh.
Why are you looking
at me like that?
I know it’s weird because
we’ve only known each other
for a week.
But in that one week,
I’ve seen you cry twice.
I don’t know, but…
can I be the one instead?
I promise I won’t make you cry.
Kidding!
You’re so carried away!
Ouch.
Where are you going?
Wait up!
Alys!
I was kidding!
I love you, Drake Palma!
Hey!
You’re sulking again!
My god!
Can you get out of my sight?
I’m still pissed about what
you did last weekend.
I’m sorry.
Bad joke.
Do you want some?
- No!
- I already took a bite out of it!
No!
Is that College Algebra, Zy?
That’s so easy!
Well, okay then, smart-ass!
And stop calling me “Zy”.
Please, we’re not close!
Wow, “we’re not close.”
And why not?
“Zyril” sounds cute.
And I don’t like “Alys”.
It’s like your name was cut short.
I’ll tell my mom on you.
You’re in trouble now.
How do you do it?
What’s so funny?
You. What’s all this tattling about?
You sound like a kid.
Whatever.
Oh, Alys,
he’s your only friend
in Brenford,
so just bear with
him when you can, okay?
- Just bear with him.
- Give me that.
Give me that!
I’ll do it.
Oh, so now you’re
the smart one again.
Thanks!
Go ahead, then.
It’s done.
Mmm.
Give me that!
Such a show-off.
Do you want me to teach you?
No, thanks!
Keep dreaming!
Come on!
I’ll teach you, it’s easy.
I said no, give that to me.
You’re going to be a forever
nuisance in my life, Marco!
Oh, wow.
I think you’ve got a
crush on me.
Ugh, will you stop
saying things like that?
That’s disgusting.
Then, why did you look so disappointed
when I said “kidding”?
This girl’s disgusting,
you’re making a mess.
Hey.
That suits you, ugh!
Because you’re a bully!
But you were disappointed!
I wasn’t disappointed!
I said sorry!
Apology not accepted!
Why are you so mad?
Because you fooled me!
Sorry, Zyril!
The way you’re talking,
it’s like I’m your boyfriend
who just cheated on you.
Wow, you’re really
full of yourself!
I’m sorry, Zyril.
I was only joking because
you wouldn’t stop crying.
So, you’re going to mess
with me every time I cry?
I just panicked.
I never thought
you love Drake that much.
You know Drake?
Uh, you mentioned him once.
Didn’t you?
I told you about him?
Maybe I just forgot.
Yes, you’re just forgetful.
Look who’s here again!
So you’re just going
to stay quiet now?
What? Cat got your tongue?
Why are you
ganging up on me?
You’re funny!
You’re really asking that?
Uhm...yes?
‘Cause you’re so selfish, missy!
You already took Drake,
and you’re involving Tripp, too.
Don’t you think that’s
a little too overboard?
You all know Drake?
He’s our batchmate.
But unfortunately,
he transferred to SCA
for some unknown reason.
And for some very
ruinous reason,
you became his girlfriend.
Oh, right.
Drake is from Brenford High,
no wonder the girls
here always stare at me.
Sorry.
Your “sorry” won’t fix anything!
Watch your back.
Did they just threaten me?
Why did I even come to
the lair of Drake’s admirers?
Alys!
Am I ready to see Drake?
What am I even going to say to him?
Ugh, Alys, why did
you even come here?
What to do?
Fine. I’m already here.
1-1-3-1.
Drake?
Why did I...
Why did I even go
to his condo?
I should’ve just gone home.
You’re so stupid, Alys!
You’re so stupid!
I can only tolerate you
crying five times, Alys.
That’s your third already.
When you reach five,
I’ll make my joke real.
Have some coffee.
You need it.
Try some milk.
It’ll taste better.
It’s been two weeks
since I last saw Drake.
Who would’ve thought I’d
get tired of visiting his condo?
It hurts that I’m
the one making the effort,
but then I always see him
with Shaira.
Oh, hey!
Do you have a class?
My class just ended.
How are you?
Tired, but happy.
Really?
You know cooking’s my passion.
I know.
You make me your guinea pig.
I mean, I’m your food taster.
I’m sorry!
You get free food,
yet you still look at a loss.
Are you complaining?
Not really.
Just right.
Whatever you say.
- Zy…
- Mmm?
How about we go to
SCA’s sem-starter?
They rented the
nearby theme park.
What do you think?
Oh right, it is
SCA’s sem-starter.
It’s open to outsiders.
What if we visit Aya, Kent and Sheen?
But… Drake’s there.
So?
I don’t want to.
If you want to go,
you can go by yourself.
Why?
You’re such a buzzkill!
Come on!
Annoying! I said
I don’t want to!
Wow, really?
I thought we were
friends forever?
Tss.
Oh wow, you’re
guilt-tripping me?
That’s not going to
work on me anymore!
You already tried that before!
Come on, you don’t
have classes, anyway.
Keep your voice down!
There’s a lot of rides, too!
Hey, keep it down,
we’re in the library!
There’s a lot of rides.
We’re in the library,
don’t be noisy!
Come on.
Please!
You’re not going to stop,
are you?
Oh my god...
no wonder so many girls
pick fights with me here –
Marco’s smile is deadly.
I know you’ll say yes.
What else can I do?
You’re so persistent!
I know you won’t
stop bothering me.
Yes!
- Sssshhhh!
- Hey, don’t be noisy!
- Sorry, sorry!
- We’re in the library.
- Peace, peace, peace!
- You’re so noisy.
Thank you for letting me
use your locker.
Come on, it’s no big deal.
143.
That’s the code, 1-4-3!
- Ah, got it!
- In case, you might use it.
Okay, thanks.
Whoever put that
dead rat in my locker,
I hope they get boils!
That’s just mean!
It smells so bad, even
air freshener can’t beat it.
Hey.
Can I have this?
Let’s not put your
secret admirer’s effort to waste.
Hey, wait up!
Wait for me!
After you ask for chocolates,
you’ll leave me behind?
- Whatever!
- You’re hurting my feelings, you know?
Tripp! Tripp!
- Let’s ride that one, come on!
- Huh?
- Let’s do that later.
- Let’s ride that one!
Let’s go.
Come on! You invited me here,
then you don’t want to ride anything?
You’re just scared of heights!
No, I’m not!
So, why don’t you want to?
You’re just scared
and won’t admit it!
Cut it out, Zy!
You’re reckless with your motorcycle
but you don’t want to go on rides?
What kind of person are you?
You’re weird!
- I’m not scared!
- Then come on!
- I said later!
- I want to go on rides!
That's for later.
See that ride over there?
That’s basic, that’s so easy.
There’s a wedding booth!
You know what,
my mom told me
that when she and my
dad were in high school,
they went to a wedding booth
and they got married there.
It’s annoying, you know?
If things were okay
between me and Drake,
I would’ve dragged
him here to marry me.
How about you, Tripp,
who would you want to—?
- Thank you!
- Hey, Tripp!
Wow, so you’re just
going to ditch me?
I called you.
You were the one
busy daydreaming.
You want some?
Then, buy some.
You’re so annoying!
Miss, I’ll buy one.
There’s so many!
You know what, in the month
we’ve been together,
I’ve learned to bring
a lot of money.
You’re so stingy,
I’d starve because of you.
You’re rich, anyway.
Whatever, that’s
such a lame excuse.
Hey!
Yuck!
Seriously, you poked me with
the finger that had spit on it?!
Gross!
You’re so fussy!
You really are gross!
- Fussy!
- Hey, man!
Long time, no talk!
How are you?
I’m good. You?
Acting all snobbish!
Well, I feel pressured.
It’s hard at SCA, too.
What about you?
You’ll stay forever in Brenford?
Wow, the audacity of this guy!
He’s not even that handsome!
Excuse me, mister!
That’s fine, at least we’re still rich.
How about you?
How’s business?
Are you going bankrupt soon?
Nice one, Marco!
You’re still arrogant, Palma!
Wait…
Palma?
At least I have
something to brag about.
Anyway, we’re leaving.
Let’s go, Alys.
Hey, what did I just hear?
- Alys, let’s go.
- Did I hear that right?
- Alys, let’s go!
- Palma?!
Huh?!
Just wait a second!
- Just a second!
- Come on!
Tripp Marco.
Is “Marco” your last
name, or is it “Palma”?
Why are you asking?
I know someone with
the last name Palma.
Who knows, you might be related.
Why, are we both handsome?
I’m seriously asking!
Ouch!
Fine.
Tripp Marco Palma, 19, single,
and ready to mingle with you.
How’s that?
Look at you,
you’re pretending you’ve never
had a girlfriend,
but you’re such a flirt!
Oh, wow!
So, is it my fault I’m
this good-looking?
You’re so full of yourself!
But seriously...
So, wait...
do you know Drake Palma?
- He’s my cousin.
- No way?!
Yes!
But of course, I’m
more handsome.
Hey!
Seriously?
You’re cousins?!
Yes. You’re unbelievable.
You asked me and I answered.
Now, you don’t believe me!
You’re so confusing, you know?
Shocks!
You and Drake are cousins?
- For real?!
- Yes.
He’s my cousin.
Our dads are brothers.
We’re both Palmas,
and both handsome –
it runs in the blood.
All right?
- Ouch!
- Damn you!
- After all the crying I did—
- Ouch!
you turn out to be cousins!
Ouch! That hurts!
- You’re so annoying!
- Ouch, stop!
So you actually
knew that Sebastian?!
- Ouch!
- You’re cousins!
You and your cousin
are both annoying!
Okay, stop, stop.
Stop, it hurts!
Why are you even mad at me?!
Of course, because
you’re his cousin!
Blood is thicker than water.
Of course, you’ll take his side.
Ouch!
But love is the
thickest of them all.
Don’t worry, I’ll
always take your side.
You said it.
You better stand by it.
Yes, I will.
My whole body’s
hurting from all your hitting!
You deserve it!
I’m sorry.
It’s your fault, anyway.
So…
You want to try some rides?
- Are you ready for it?
- Of course!
- Yeah, right!
- That’s easy!
- Oh, yeah?
- So, let’s go?
- Let’s go!
- That’s basic!
Basic, huh? Really, now?
“Basic” your face!
Can I back out?!
Why would you back—?
I’m scared, I don’t
want to anymore!
Why are you getting off?! Hey!
Now I’m getting scared, too!
- Alys, I don’t want to be here!
- Come on!
Hey!
Mom!
Hey, I’m going down!
Wow, look at my props!
Mine’s better – shining,
shimmering, splendid!
Why are your shades like that?
- Can I see yours?
- Mine looks cute.
- Mine looks cuter.
- Okay, let’s swap.
What? Okay.
Selfish.
- Here it is.
- This is big.
Alys, I don’t want to!
- Tripp!
- I can’t do it!
Alys!
Okay, go!
Come on, Tripp, do better!
Alys! Alys!
Hey!
Smile.
Is it working?
- It’s not.
- It isn’t.
Excuse me, we’re
sorry, the SD card’s full.
Would you be able to wait?
We just need to dump some files.
What?
Uh, it’s okay. Never mind for now.
We’ll just come back later.
Sir, stop!
Hey!
Stop being a basher,
it just makes my skills show.
Tripp! Tripp!
Zyril! Zyril!
It won’t shoot!
Hey, wake up!
Wake up! It’s over!
We’re done!
You can get your prize now.
Can I get the
strawberry keychain?
It’s not enough.
One ring, candy.
Two rings, keychain, and
then three or more, plushies.
Let’s take a picture!
- Smile!
- Wait.
Smile!
I feel dizzy.
Too bad, I want to get
the strawberry keychain.
Can’t we just buy the
strawberry keychain instead?
Sorry, you can’t.
I’m Tripp!
I’m dizzy!
I’m not scared!
Stop it!
I didn’t say that!
Miss!
Come in here
with your boyfriend!
Huh? No!
You don’t want to
marry your boyfriend?
He’s not my boyfriend.
So, you’re available?
Available...
Oh, so you’re available!
Move over!
Hey, available!
Bestie?
Bestie!
- Bestie!
I’ve been looking for you!
Uh, excuse me, I have class!
This girl doesn’t cut classes anymore,
that’s why we only came here now.
- Hi, Sheen! I missed you!
- Hi, Alys!
I don’t think you missed us at all!
Hi, Kent!
- Just a little.
- “Just a little.”
She missed me a lot,
but she missed you guys just a little.
Oh, wow!
You’re still so in love, Kent!
Of course!
Right, bee?
I bet he waited for your class to end
so you could come here together.
So cute and fluffy, my KenYa!
It’s annoying,
I’m a little jealous.
- Bee!
- Thank you, Alys!
You mean clingy!
Bee, stop!
Oh, sorry!
I wish someone
would wait for me, too.
And then we’d walk
together while people stare.
And we wouldn’t care
because they’d just be looking.
But of course, that’s just a dream.
Why don’t you tell Drake
about that fantasy of yours?
Bestie? Oh my gosh!
You lost weight!
Really?
What happened
to you in Brenford?
- She seems to have not eaten yet.
- Don’t you have food there?
Turn around!
Spin!
Then, give me a hip shake.
Shake it, like this.
One more spin!
One more, turn around.
That’s it.
What the— stop it,
I’m getting dizzy!
You’re so easy to trick!
Of course I’ve been eating,
there’s a lot of food in Brenford!
I’m studying Culinary
Arts, remember?
It’s because the buildings there
are far from each other.
So between classes, I keep
walking from one place to another.
Well, that’s true,
she walks far.
But bestie, you’re blooming!
You look so pretty today!
You’re absolutely inspired by Kent!
You know, it’s a good
thing your friend’s nicer now.
She doesn’t punch
me anymore.
Ouch!
See, that’s what
you get for jinxing it!
Sorry, bee!
Is that Tripp?
Oh, yes! Come here!
Hi, Tripp!
Tripp, this is Aya, the
one I always tell you about.
And this is Kent, and this is Sheen.
Hi, bro!
I know Sheen.
- Huh?
Sheen.
- You guys know each other?
- Mmm.
We were batchmates before
in Brenford.
Ahhh...
So, what?
Are we just catching up here?
Oh, bestie, treat me some drinks!
Why am I always the one
treating you guys?
- Do I look like an ATM?!
- Yes!
Come on, treat me! You’ve got
more money than me, anyway!
Come on, bestie, I
want that – hotdog!
I want hotdog, and
drinks, lots of drinks!
I want lots of drinks!
I miss you!
Thank you!
Oh wait, I don’t
want to eat anymore!
Here.
Come on, bestie!
Let’s just look outside.
Look at you, you’re the one
who dragged us there.
Well, I changed my mind.
And just let them be,
they’re already adults.
You’re right.
Let’s leave them be.
Let’s go, let’s do girl bonding.
Let’s go. Over there!
Oh, wait!
You’ve got a lot to tell me!
Yes, let’s go!
One question, one answer –
what’s going on with you and Tripp?
Wow, those eyes
are so judgmental!
Nothing, we’re just friends!
Friends?
Yes!
Really, “friends?”
Just friends?
You’re not just friends!
Fine, we’re best friends, if you
don’t believe we’re just friends!
You know what, fool Kent
all you want, but not me.
And I feel there’s something
between you and Tripp that I can’t explain.
You are such a
gossip, you know that?
And anyway, who would like a guy
who’d let you starve and not even treat
you because “you’re rich”?!
It still annoys me every
time I think about it!
I thought you said
there’s nothing?!
There’s really nothing.
Nothing!
Bestie, spill it, I’m
your only girl best friend!
Fine, I’m sulking
now, there, I’m sulking!
Now you have to
make it up to me!
Make it up to me!
- Come on, let’s go!
- What am I, Kent?!
What am I, Kent?! Go there!
Okay, fine!
“Make it up to me!”
Just tell me already!
There’s nothing,
you’re so persistent!
What happened
between you and Drake?
Come on, spill!
What exactly do you
want to know?
Everything!
Aya, I keep thinking
why didn’t I just go to SCA?
I wish I had done better.
That way, we
could’ve been together.
- Hey.
- What?
Why do you look
uninterested in my story?
Because that’s not the
story I’m talking about.
Then what story are
you talking about?
Look at my best friend,
you’re so impatient!
We’re just getting
to the exciting part.
Okay, so guess what – Drake and
Shaira actually live in the same condo.
Same floor and everything.
They’re literally neighbors.
And that clingy octopus
keeps latching onto Drake.
She’s even calling him “husband”.
Oh, wow.
See, I knew it!
Nothing good will
come from that Shaira.
Why do you say that?
You know what, Shaira and Drake
are always together.
At first, I was annoyed.
Of course, we’re BFFs!
And CB keeps telling me,
“That’s just how Shaira is,
don’t get annoyed.”
But still—
- they’re so irritating!
- They’re always together?
The way Drake acts, you’d
think he doesn’t have a girlfriend!
You know what, just
break up with him!
Is Aya right?
Should I just break up with Drake?
Just break up already!
Thanks, bestie.
I’ve missed this.
In Brenford, I have
no one to talk to.
You know I don’t
have friends there.
Why?
I’ve got no one to talk to,
since it turns out Drake
and Tripp are cousins.
I can’t rant to his cousin, right?
But you know, bestie,
I’m just one text away.
“Friends forever,” remember?
I’m really lucky
to have you, Aya!
Of course, we’re soulmates!
Come on...
we’re soulmates!
Then Sheen’s second,
and next is Tripp.
You know, even if I have
just a few close friends,
I’m thankful because I
know you all love me!
Of course!
I’m always here for you.
Bestie...
Who’s this?
Who’s that?
Let me just get
this, bestie, okay?
Go ahead!
Hello?
Good thing Tripp dragged
me here. I missed Aya!
- Bestie...
- So? What’d they say?
- Sorry!
- What?
There’s a problem with our design.
I have to go back to SCA.
Wow! New life, bestie!
- Stop teasing me, bestie.
- I’m so proud of you!
Kent’s such a great
influence on you.
- I’m so proud of you, bestie!
- Kent?
- I forgot Kent!
- What?
Ah, never mind,
I’ll just text him.
I’ll tell him I really need
to get back to school.
Okay.
They’re probably
still catching up there.
Alright, bestie!
- Bye!
I’m so dramatic!
- Aja!
Alright!
- Bye, bestie!
- Take care!
- I love you!
- Bestie!
Bye!
- Bye!
- Love you, bestie!
That’s so sweet!
Who would’ve thought
she and Kent would last?
It’s been months now and counting.
Imagine that – they’re still together?
I’m so proud!
Where is he, anyway?
How do I get back there?
This theme park’s so big!
It’s confusing!
Oh, Alys!
You really have a goldfish memory!
Who’s this?
Unknown number, probably just a scammer!
Ugh! Where are you guys?
So annoying!
Hello?
To your right.
Huh?
Tss.
Turn to your right.
Drake.
Come to me.
Oh no, is Shaira here?
I think I’m developing
Shaira-phobia – fear of the octopus!
- Drake.
- Sit.
How long have you had my number?
A month ago.
Huh?
That long?
Why didn’t you call me?
Should I have called you?
Lord, I’m really having a hard time.
I miss my simple life,
when Math was my only problem.
Of course not.
Who am I for you to call, right?
My girlfriend?
“My girlfriend”?
See? You’re not even
sure if I’m your girlfriend.
Why are you crying?
Nothing.
I’m crying for no reason.
It’s not because my
boyfriend ignores me.
It’s not because he
prioritizes the girl who
claims he’s her first love.
It’s not because he
could call me but didn’t.
There’s really no reason to cry.
I’m sorry.
I knew it. It was not a good idea
to go here.
This is your fault, Tripp.
You brought me here.
Now, where are you?
Let’s get out of here.
You’re sorry, but
you’ll just do it again?
Drake, I’m getting tired.
If you don’t want me,
can you just say so?
Don’t make me look like a fool.
Please?
That’s so unfair.
I’m really sorry, Alys.
I didn’t know
that’s how you feel.
You didn’t know
because you never asked –
that’s why you’ll never know!
I did my best, Drake,
but I think this is where we end.
Are you breaking up with me?
You know, sometimes your
intelligence actually has a use.
Yes, I’m obviously
calling it quits, Drake!
You’ve inflicted too much damage!
Please…please…
please, let me go.
Alys Zyril Perez,
breaking up is a
mutual decision,
and I don’t wanna
break up with you.
Drake, what do you really want?
We’ll fight...
then apologize, then text me?
Then I give in again.
Four down, one to go.
Just one more, and you’ll
get a feel of my joke.
I did my best, Drake,
but I think this is where we end.
Are you breaking up with me?
You know, sometimes
your intelligence
actually has a use.
Yes, I’m obviously
calling it quits, Drake!
You’ve inflicted too much damage.
Please… please…
please, let me go.
Alys Zyril Perez,
breaking up is a
mutual decision,
and I don’t wanna
break up with you.
Am I really that
bad of a boyfriend?
Should I apologize?
- “Stop it!”
- I never said that!
- Hurry up!
- No!
I’d only do that
if you won earlier,
but you didn’t, you
only won candy!
- Come on, just one!
- No, whatever!
No!
- Whatever!
- I don’t like you!
Fine, then I’ll never
treat you again!
Fine, if you win— no!
Can I get the
strawberry keychain?
It’s not enough.
One ring – candy.
Two rings – keychain,
and then three
or more, plushies.
Too bad, I really wanted
the strawberry keychain.
On the next episode of
Seducing Drake Palma.
Hello?
Why are you calling?
Do you know Shaira?
Shaira?
He’s asleep!
Why would I wake
him up for you, duh?!
This is Drake’s girlfriend, Alys.
Why are you with him?
Are you accusing me
of cheating on you?
Why, are you not?!
Tell me in the three weeks
we weren’t together, Drake,
did I even cross your mind?!
Even just once?
Let’s go home.
What?