(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
[The entire content of this drama is fictitious, for entertainment only. Please watch wisely]
[Previous Episode]
My name is Aerie.
Bambi.
Prim.
We've made up.
No matter who approaches in any way.
No matter what happens, I will choose you.
Shasha, listen to my explanation.
I have to find a new manager.
Just search slowly.
Surely it can be found.
Broke up with you because of your mouth, right?
How could I put up with such a bad guy all this time?
Why I don't know
is there a good person like you waiting for me?
Did you give my father money?
Of.
Even though we've made up,
doesn't mean you can decide everything for me.
OK, but can you edit the photo?
It seems like my face is a little swollen.
Shouldn't have eaten too salty last night.
The swollen face is also very cute.
No need to edit, Preaw.
Why do you keep opposing me?
Only married once.
I want the prettiest.
Don't worry, Sis, I'll take care of it.
I will make you two the most beautiful brides.
- Tiny. - Really good.
When you get married,
I'll let you guys hold it
free follow-up party at Blossom.
You promised yeah.
Good.
OK, come on, go get changed.
There are still several models.
Why do you want so many models?
So fussy.
Will we be like them when we get old, Sis?
Don't think that far ahead.
We just started dating.
But, feelings are not calculated based on time.
Or
You can't see our future?
This is not what I mean.
We're just getting started.
We still have to understand each other.
Don't plan that far ahead yet.
There are still many things to consider in life.
Family,
work
and society.
I know.
I understand everything.
But, I don't care about that.
I only care about the two of us.
I don't want to date carelessly.
Not casually dating.
Our wedding party
I'll make it bigger than Ant, okay?
Really?
Good.
♪ Rules of love, no falling in love with you ♪
♪ I know, but I don't want to hear ♪
♪ But, I want more ♪
♪ Just thinking about you ♪
♪ Girl, girl, girl ♪
♪ Forbidden to love you ♪
♪ Because I like girls ♪
[Girl Rules]
[Bird in a Cage]
Hey.
He must have argued with Prim.
So, so sad on the dance floor.
So,
Is this why you pulled me here?
What do you want?
Go help him wipe his tears?
Prim will beat you up.
It could be a double battle.
You are crazy?
Bambi and I are just friends.
Then, how are you and Gorya?
Let's discuss it later.
I don't want to have a headache anymore.
I'm already annoyed with the manager's business.
It's not hard to find a new one, right?
It is not easy to find people who can be trusted and competent.
Everyone wants to benefit from me.
Are you okay, Bambi?
I'm fine.
Very happy.
Come on, join me in dancing.
You are dancing.
But, it seems like your heart is not in it.
How about continuing dancing in your apartment?
What do you want?
Don't want to do anything.
Only want
with people who don't see me as a problem.
How?
If you're not willing, I'll find someone else.
Thank you for letting me come to your house.
No problem.
Someone accompanied me to drink quite good alcohol.
I didn't have any friends after returning.
Not friends drinking and having fun.
What about your college friends?
Basically friends drinking and having fun.
Not someone who understands me.
The only person who understands me,
I chose to date him.
Now we are fighting, friends and girlfriends, everything is gone.
Why is it so difficult to change yourself?
Then, why do you want to change yourself?
If it is for the sake of satisfying him, it will be endless.
Are you going to keep changing until he's happy?
Wouldn't it be better to change for your own pleasure?
Have you ever met someone who made you want to change?
Never.
I'm not ready to change for anyone.
Maybe go back to being the Bambi that used to be pretty good too.
Doesn't love anyone.
No need to take care of anyone.
Only care about your own happiness.
Do whatever you want.
No need to worry about hurting anyone.
You are sure?
Maybe a kiss will change our relationship.
Not sure.
But, I just want to forget the things that are on my brain.
Min.
I can't contact Bambi.
Did something happen to him?
I'll go report the police.
Calm down, Prim.
Maybe he was with friends.
Do you know his friend?
Do not know her.
Do you think he has other friends?
Only I can survive it.
Your words are a bit outrageous.
He did it for your good too.
If someone lent my father money, I would be very happy.
I know, I understand everything.
But, you know what? My father is my problem.
Sis Prim is looking for Sis Bambi?
Can.
I saw him at Blossom last night.
I work there.
Really?
Who is he with?
I saw it with Kak Shasha.
They go together.
Min, do you have Shasha's address?
Don't have.
I contacted Kak Woonsen about work.
No problem, I'll help you look for it.
Eh...
I think I know
people who know Shasha's address.
Who?
Gorya.
Thank you for helping me.
Actually, I don't want to help.
But, feel sorry for you.
He always bothers you.
But, that's not his fault.
I was wrong, my words were too cruel to him.
You really love him.
So, blame yourself like this.
Go quickly.
While I haven't
changed his mind because of jealousy.
How?
Did you sleep well last night?
Of.
My head doesn't hurt so much anymore.
I made breakfast for you.
Is there anything you want to eat?
This trick of yours...
Taking women to bed at home,
then make breakfast.
If you want him to come again,
so you have to take good care of it.
I'll go down first.
Where is Bambi?
He should be taking a shower.
Can I come in and talk to him?
Up to you.
Shasha, is breakfast ready?
You guys just chat.
Gorya and I waited upstairs.
Can you?
Don't worry.
Why are you looking for Shasha?
Then, why can't I find it?
He is my friend too.
Probably my best friend now.
I'm really worried about you.
My phone wasn't answered either.
I'm worried something happened to you.
No need to worry me.
I can take care of myself.
In the future, I will just mind my own business.
Let's not fight anymore, okay?
I won't interfere in your business anymore.
What else do you want?
I'm sorry about my father.
I know, what I said was too much.
However, if you sleep with Shasha to annoy me,
I think you are too cruel.
Do you think I'm that kind of person?
Bambi.
In the past, I thought I understood you best.
But sometimes,
I feel like I don't understand you at all.
Don't anymore.
If further,
I will definitely miss you as a friend.
I still want someone to understand me.
That is true.
We're too similar, not suitable for dating.
You can sleep here tonight.
Thank You.
Nothing happened
between me and Shasha.
No matter how angry I am with you,
I will never hurt you.
I know you did it for my good.
But, I have limits too.
After all, I am your girlfriend.
Is the friend who understands you the most too.
I want to show you something.
Bambi and I didn't do anything last night.
So what?
You don't need to explain it to me.
I just want you to know.
He just needed a place to rest because of Prim's problems.
You're quite reliable.
Good at giving emotional value to others.
You also came looking for me before.
Halo.
What?
But, this is not on my schedule.
One o'clock?
OK, I'll be right there.
What is it?
Kak Woonsen.
Accepted the job but didn't tell me.
Don't write a schedule either.
I haven't done my hair, I haven't made up and I don't have clothes.
He took care of it for me first.
Need me to help?
Can you find clothes that match the theme concept?
What about the details of the activities?
What's the concept?
Tell me.
I'll help you find clothes.
You just make up on location.
I've called my makeup artist friend.
Can be done in 30 minutes.
The rest should be no problem.
Thank You.
I'd be in trouble without you.
You thanked me many times.
I'm not used to it.
You better keep talking harshly.
How did you grow up?
Why don't you like me being gentle?
Release your hand.
Too much.
Already.
The car is waiting for you below.
I go first.
Wait.
If it's like this,
can you accompany me to go together?
I don't want to go to big events alone.
No.
I'm a stylist, not a manager.
You don't need to do anything.
Just accompany me.
Just smile next to me.
I need support today.
Look, is there a chair or sofa that you like?
I know the boss, can get a discount.
Sis, this one is very soft.
Beautiful too.
It should match my room perfectly.
It's your style.
I'll buy it for you if you like.
As a new home gift.
No need, Sis.
Too expensive.
If you want to buy it, I will pay you in installments.
But, my interest rate is very high.
What if I don't have money?
Can you pay it another way?
How do you want to pay?
Preaw, what are you doing?
I paid the interest first.
You like being spoiled too much.
When I like someone,
must be revealed so that he knows.
Sis, actions are more important than words.
Min.
Hello, Uncle.
Halo.
Long time no see.
You rarely come home.
Oh, I've been busy lately.
As it happens,
I brought...
My friend to buy a new sofa here.
This is Preaw, my friend.
Are you still dating Park?
The one you brought home to eat.
It's broken up.
Oh, dear.
I thought you two would date until you got married.
No problem.
You are young and beautiful.
You can still search for more.
Don't delay too long in getting married and having children, understand?
Then, I'll go first.
Remember, go home and see your mother.
Hopefully there will be a chance to eat at your house in the future.
You just met my uncle earlier.
Still want to meet my family?
You will be more depressed after meeting him.
Don't go.
You don't want to do anything?
Do what?
You want me to take your hand and introduce you as my girlfriend?
Can't.
Too much.
I understand you.
No problem.
We just live our lives like this.
Just go with the flow for future things.
I can.
Look here.
Look at the camera.
A little closer.
Smile for a moment.
Did you come alone today?
Yes, isn't Brother Woonsen coming?
Reportedly, you fired him, is that true?
Is it because of money fraud?
Yes, is that a misunderstanding?
- Please answer. - Yes.
- What happened? - Is this true?
What happened between you?
Sorry.
Sorry, Everyone.
He still has another schedule.
Sorry.
There weren't any journalists following, right?
There shouldn't be any.
You can keep holding me.
I know it's hard to refuse.
Hey.
I'm helping you.
This is not the time to flirt.
Anyway, thanks.
I'm not ready to answer all those questions.
Good.
Discussed after discussing it with a lawyer.
Maybe he wants to trap you.
You are very thorough.
Very suitable to be a manager.
Will you be my manager?
Don't want to.
Not my job.
You better take care of yourself.
You've seen it, I can't take care of myself well.
I really want to
asked you to take care of me.
Don't want to.
I can't stand being with someone who asks to be beat up all day.
Could be crazy.
Too much.
I guarantee that trying won't bother you.
Can't.
I can't even take care of my own life.
Don't want to let your life bother me anymore.
Don't forget to think about me when you sleep.
Don't want to.
Look, what my father bought for my mother today.
Tadaa...
- This is a surprise for you. - Wow, thanks.
- Thank You. - This is what you want?
- I also have a gift for you. - You just bought me this bag.
- I have one too? - This.
Is that your father?
How does Dad know what I want?
Of.
Him and his new wife and new son.
Ha?
My mother realized he was having an affair and got her pregnant.
So, divorce.
He abandoned me,
my mother and my sister.
Ignoring our lives.
I really don't understand.
He hurt my mother so deeply,
why does my mother still help him and give him money?
He never felt guilty about us.
Come ask for our help if you have any problems.
Then, spend money on his wife and children.
When living well,
he pretended we didn't exist.
That's why I try so hard
managing the company.
To prove that we can still live well without him.
Wait for me here for a moment.
I'll be right back.
Where are you going?
Bambi.
Wah.
Little Brother, I'll tell you.
This cell phone you are holding
is my money.
What?
This my father bought for me.
When will you return your 200,000 debt to me?
Didn't you say it doesn't need to be returned?
That's because you tricked me.
When borrowing money,
You said you were having trouble and were sick.
Isn't it a shame to leave your own family and daughter now?
Bambi.
OK, let me take care of it.
Hey.
You're the one who told your little girlfriend to come asking for money?
No.
If you borrow money, you should be responsible.
From now on,
don't come to borrow money again.
I'm not responsible for raising someone else's wife and children.
Give me my money back this month.
If not, I will ask a lawyer to look for you.
Beware of falling into my hands.
How dare you talk to my mother like that, come back!
Hey Bambi!
200.000 baht.
Bambi.
Fuck.
Since dating you, I've only been to your house once.
I don't dare bring a big lady like you home.
Why?
Do you think I'm dating you because of my family background?
I'm dating you because of you.
Ssttt.
- Mother! - Aah!
Prim.
You surprised me.
I thought the house was burglarized.
Where can there be a thief as beautiful as this?
Huh.
Mother.
This is Bambi.
He once came to our house when he was in college.
Do you still remember?
Hello, Auntie.
Halo.
I remember.
But, isn't it said that you guys have broken up?
Isn't it better to make up again?
I have to cook a delicious meal today to celebrate you getting back together.
Let's eat together, Bambi.
Or you can also stay here.
If Prim sleeps here, I'll sleep here too.
Come on, come inside.
I am hungry.
What delicious food did you cook today?
Let me think about it first.
This is my favorite food.
This is Prim's favorite food.
Want this, son?
That's it, Mother, Bambi didn't have time to eat.
It looks very delicious.
Eat a lot.
Thank You.
Baipor.
You know? They get back together.
I know earlier than Mom.
This couple is very popular on social media.
"A new director and a noble's daughter" fits perfectly.
Is it very popular on the internet?
Sorry, Sis Bambi, I was kidding you.
Please make it a joke, I'm not embarrassed.
Because this is reality.
It's enough.
Reduce use of social media.
The more you say the more it makes no sense.
This is true, Sis.
Thank You.
This place is still cool and comfortable as before.
Of.
I like it too.
But, Prim says the house is old.
Want to buy a new one.
Mom, move and live around town instead.
So I can take care of you.
After all,
he will work in the city in the future.
No need to have too much trouble getting back and forth.
Too wasteful of money, son.
Mother.
Even if I don't have money, my girlfriend will pay too.
He has money.
I even planned to stop and let my boyfriend take care of me.
Not a problem, Auntie.
This money is not a problem.
OK, then I have a new goal.
I'm not looking for work anymore.
Just look for a rich partner.
Hey, enough.
I am kidding.
Remember, relying on yourself is the most appropriate.
Why talk so much today?
Eat, eat quickly.
Open your mouth.
Eat
Eat quickly.
Bite every bite, one, two, aaa...
Can't be bribed.
Two.
This is too coincidental, right?
What if I told you, I did it on purpose?
If you want me to be your manager,
you just dream.
Why?
Don't want to help me?
How many times do I want to say it?
I don't want life to become more chaotic.
More unwilling to be a manager who sleeps with celebrities.
I didn't hire you to accompany me to sleep.
Or do you want me to hire you to accompany me to sleep?
Manager
just need to take care of work and daily life.
I don't like dealing with people.
Usually it's Kak Woonsen who helps me talk.
Be it payment or serving reporters
or if I need something, I don't want to talk to myself either.
Afraid that other people will think I have a lot of problems.
What if your parents did it?
Many celebrities use their mothers as managers.
Don't want to.
Let them relax, just have to wait to receive the money.
Besides, my family is not as warm as yours.
Too much.
I'll just handle it myself.
If you mess up, you'll probably just get scolded.
I can be a manager.
But, can only be a manager.
There can be no other relationship.
Why?
What do you mean?
That is, we will not sleep together,
won't hug,
not kissing,
there is no physical contact whatsoever.
But, you can get a salary and you can have me.
Be a little professional.
Do you actually want to or not?
Too much.
Just do what you say.
After all, you will change your mind sooner or later.
Get out, I don't want it anymore.
I haven't hired you yet.
Don't rush to resign.
♪ I'm forever yours ♪
♪ Only you, this is real ♪
♪ All my life and my whole heart is yours ♪
♪ You are that person ♪
♪ Stand before me ♪
♪ It doesn't matter when I'm awake or in a dream ♪
♪ I'm so happy that person is you ♪
This is not the final version yet.
What do you think after seeing it?
This is clearly our life.
You still dared to say no at that time.
Because every one of my works
all the material comes from you.
Be it sad or happy,
you are always in my story.
Look.
What's this? So cute.
Do you remember the day we broke up?
Your birthday.
I prepared this.
But, in the end it was not given.
I saw it was a small deer.
So, I remember you.
Although it's not an expensive item.
Maybe you don't need it anyway, so just save it.
Why?
So cute.
Your gift
not related to price.
It becomes valuable because you think of me.
Look, it looks like me, doesn't it?
Like it or not?
Of.
Maybe I can't immediately change myself for you.
But, I will try so that your heart is not too tired anymore.
You don't need to change yourself, Bambi.
Just communicate with me more if there are problems.
There's one more thing.
You don't need to try to make me happy.
Because we should be happy together.
Understand?
I understand.
Auntie can see it later.
What is it?
This is my house.
I can do anything.
You said it yourself.
Do you like it or not, Little Bambi?
Really like it.
Look, you can still put things in it.
Can this contain the love I give you?
You're so cute.
Thank You.
I really like.
This is Fiona's business proposal.
It focuses on different customers than the main brand.
Next, it will launch a whole series of bags and shoes.
However, his style is definitely different from Yanin's.
Did you do all this yourself?
Of.
Mother sent me to school abroad,
not in vain.
I'll consider it first.
But, you have to consistently do it.
This is not a toy that can be thrown away if you get bored.
Have to invest millions of baht.
Do you understand?
I will not tarnish the reputation of your only daughter.
Thank You.
Become a wealthy woman.
The money has been earned.
Not rich yet.
But, it's enough to take your girlfriend out for a big meal.
Save the money first to buy things for the new house.
No need to treat me to a meal.
But, I want to take care of you.
Because I'm already dating,
must look after each other.
How is it okay to always let you take care of me alone?
I'm just worried about you.
You need money for many other important things.
Don't always act like a big brother.
It's okay to act like a boyfriend.
I'm being a girlfriend.
Because I'm your boyfriend, I should help you with your finances.
What do you want?
Preaw.
People can see it later.
Aren't couples just like this?
Don't just talk.
Must act.
Preaw.
Pleases me.
Sis Min, I have...
Sorry.
I'll come back later.
I told you not to be like this in the company.
But, you are the boss in this company.
After all, most people here like women too.
What are you afraid of?
That's true, but I have to maintain my image.
Sis, are you sure it's just for image?
Don't you want to publish me?
Not like that.
This takes time.
Don't let today be too long, Sis.
I feel like a secret lover now.
My mother is preparing to open a shop for me.
Then, it will continue to expand its branches slowly.
After stabilizing in the market,
then opened branches abroad.
Sounds really great.
But, maybe you will be very tired.
But, if you are serious,
I think you can definitely reach international standards.
But,
maybe we can't see each other often for a while.
I'll be very busy.
Besides, I want to stop partying.
So you can focus on this.
I have to prove myself to my mother and you.
No need.
I always knew you were serious.
Just say if you need help.
I want your dreams to come true.
Just like you who continued to support me at that time.
Until I can open this production company.
So,
You don't plan on giving a reward to the person who made this effort?
Just like this?
This is just a "deposit" paid up front.
So,
don't you want a “deposit”?
No way, there's still an interview later.
Just let them wait.
Too much?
We will continue after the interview is finished.
Good.
See you later.
Bambi.
It's really you.
Do you still remember me?
We met on the badminton court.
Remember your face, but forget your name.
My name is Aerie.
Oh, Aerie.
What did you come here for?
I applied for a job here.
You came to look for Sis Prim, right?
How did you know Prim works here?
When we met that day,
I checked Sis Prim's social account.
I just found out
he is the director of several MVs and commercials that I really like.
So, I applied for a job here.
Want to work with great people.
Wish you luck.
Thank You.
Bambi.
This shirt is very nice.
What's the brand?
Fiona.
My own brand.
I'll buy it too.
Maybe I could be beautiful like you.
It was unexpected that we could meet here.
What a coincidence.
That timing was just a coincidence.
But, this time it was intentional.
I want this job.
So, why apply for a job at Lady Bird?
We are just a small production company.
I like Sis Prim.
Eh, I mean I like Kak Prim's work.
Not like that.
Startled me.
I guess expressing feelings.
Actually, I secretly found out.
I know Sis Prim and Sis Min
opened this company to make women's work.
Additionally, most of the employees here are women.
Because Sis Prim feels
women don't get many opportunities in this field.
Really looking for good information.
It's estimated that everyone has been interviewed, right?
Don't say it is the fans who come to chase the artist.
Oh, no.
I just focus on work.
Guaranteed there is no personal intention.
Your resume looks very good.
I think we can work together.
I will not disappoint you.
Why come to the furniture store?
Is there work here?
There isn't any.
Just walking around.
Ha?
Then, why did you bring me here?
I have to take care of other things too.
What do you want to take care of?
Try saying it.
Can't answer.
That means it's not that important.
Just come around with me.
As a manager,
You must understand me deeply.
You know? I could be here all day.
Every time I touch this used thing,
I can always imagine that old family.
For example, the dining table that was once used by parents and children.
Looks very warm.
Then, why don't you buy a house?
This way there is space to put furniture.
Why buy it?
After all, it will end up being left alone.
Ha? Your family doesn't come home and live with you?
What family?
My mother already has a new family.
Now, I just need to work and send money.
Sometimes, I wonder too.
What am I actually working hard for?
In order to buy pleasure for yourself.
Now, the single rate is getting higher.
The birth rate is getting lower.
Almost everyone in this world is single.
Then, you want to be single?
Single or not.
But, seeing his parents making out in the kitchen,
really very cute.
Once, their "main topic" of the day
is to put capri beans in phat kaphrao or not.
There is one more thing that makes them fight a lot.
Should you call it sambal fish or fish sauce?
Fighting so childishly.
I just want to have an atmosphere like that too.
Anyone can fight with me over nonsense.
I can accompany you to fight.
Funny.
Don't take advantage of the opportunity there.
Just seeing you so sad,
want you to feel more meaningful.
Is this what you say as a manager?
Nope.
I just feel sorry for a model who pretends to be lonely.
What do you want?
Dance.
Dancing what? I want to go home.
Come on, the atmosphere is right.
Whose atmosphere?
Your own atmosphere, right?
Ayo.
Don't want to.
Just a moment.
Like this.
Walk slowly.
Glide.
Turn.
Correct.
What are the rules?
Can't you forget the rules first?
Can't.
How is the company lately?
Good enough, Mother.
The work never stops.
Prim is great.
The idea is very good.
Prim.
Does he still like women?
Of course still, Mother.
How could something like this be changed so easily?
How about you?
Quite like women too?
Huh, why is this so hard to peel?
Don't want to be eaten by people, huh?
Come on, I'll help you peel it.
Mother, did you hear something?
What did Uncle say to you?
He says,
saw you cuddling with the woman in the furniture store.
Broke up with Park too.
Why didn't you tell me?
This is not important.
Just a bad man who left my life.
Mom should feel happy for me.
Is that woman your girlfriend?
Do you still remember Aunt Joo?
No matter when it's Grandpa's birthday or during the pilgrimage season,
no one invited him.
Because his family felt embarrassed.
Because he is looking for a woman as a girlfriend.
I don't think he's bothering anyone.
He is great at work.
Very rich too.
It is true.
But, Grandpa and Grandma didn't accept it.
Do not accept?
But, always received the money he sent every time.
Min.
Must consider all actions, decide carefully.
Should think more about Mom too.
Don't be the person who disappoints everyone else in the family.
Woonsen's older brother.
How did you get in?
Don't forget, I know all your passwords.
Everything you own is in my hands.
But, this is called breaking in illegally.
I can call security.
Are you sure you want to call him?
Where did you get it from?
You want to blackmail me?
It's better called "business negotiations".
What do you want?
You should let me go back to being your manager.
But this time,
I want to take 50 percent.
You are crazy?
If so, just try it.
I want to know too.
If everyone saw how you entered the world of entertainment,
do they still dare to hire you?
Maybe someone sympathizes with you too.
However, you will have a digital footprint that cannot be erased.
Your heart will carry scars forever.
You just decide for yourself.
One more thing, fire the stylist.
He's not helping your career at all.
[Next Episode]
Could you please revise this?
I'm afraid the client will misunderstand.
Here, right?
You don't need to come to work tomorrow.
In my opinion, you are not suitable to be a manager.
Your easily bored nature hasn't changed one bit.
Just throw it away if you have won.
- Oh, halo, Oil.
- Halo.
Have you also "changed sides"?
I want comfort.
Not a fuss because of unclear things.
Don't say things that make me feel guilty.
Obviously you alone cannot give me a clear connection.
I really admire your efforts.
But, you have to differentiate clearly.
He likes or is just being "kind".
♪ Because I like girls ♪
♪ Girl, girl, girl ♪
♪ Forbidden to love you ♪
♪ Because I like girls ♪