(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
Welcome!
Hey! We finally got to the restaurant.
It's packed!
Now that we made it, let's start asking
the customers about their meals!
Hello. Whatcha eating?
The Momo-chan Ramen
that they're famous for.
That's right.
It's the store's top-selling item.
It's Momo-chan Ramen! Smells great!
Huh? Did you pick that ramen too?
That's what the place
is famous for after all.
Ah, I wanna eat one too! Looks good!
This is Momo-chan Ramen.
And believe it or not,
it was a South Korean chef
who came to Japan and developed this dish.
Kim Yu-jin.
Here you go.
Wow, looks great!
What was it that brought a chef
from a prestigious hotel
in South Korea to Japan?
The answer?
His beloved wife, Eiko.
Mmm. Delicious.
My wife and I are constantly trying
to develop new flavors.
My husband's dream is to open
a Momo-chan Ramen branch in Korea.
Thank you very much.
I KNOW THE CHEF, HIS EX IS A CELEB
WHO?
YOU TROLL, DON'T LIE
DO RA-MI
HE'S CHA MU-HEE'S EX? FOR REAL?
RECEIPTS OR IT DIDN'T HAPPEN
Careful.
This is where I was staying.
Nice and quiet here.
When I swing by Italy,
I try to book this place.
Lucky. Key was still here.
I didn't know you were staying here.
Seems a lot nicer than the hotels.
Oh.
The key was in the lockbox,
so this is how you left the place
when you checked out.
But everything's clean.
Guess you keep things neat.
I feel better keeping it simple.
I wouldn't know how to do that.
I spill stuff. I'm messy.
I know.
It's all right.
I can clean for two.
If you don't dry your hair,
you'll get sick.
This place is old.
It's gonna take some time to heat up.
I think, um, I wouldn't impose and stay
if it wasn't so hard to find a cab.
I'd just go back to the hotel.
Italy really doesn't play around
with cabs, huh?
I'll grab a cab in just a sec.
Shouldn't be too long with the app.
Not now.
Uh…
My hair.
I can't leave
before I've dried my hair properly.
Otherwise, I'm gonna catch a cold
like you said.
Or I
could go.
Uh, n… no.
Hold on. Let me make you
something warm to drink.
Coffee or hot cocoa?
Do you have a preference?
Uh, whichever's sweetest.
I'd really appreciate that.
All right.
Mu-hee, where you at?
Seems like Ho-jin never got on a plane.
You guys together?
Yeah.
It's snowing outside,
so Ho-jin is keeping me company
at his place.
I'll be back when it stops snowing.
You crazy?
Whatever, just stay.
Congrats, Mu-hee.
Hey, Ho-jin.
I, uh…
I was…
I've noticed this is right across
from the café we met at.
Why did we never talk here?
Well, it would've been
so much easier to meet up here instead.
Maybe not.
You said you remember everything,
so you know what she did to me.
I want a reward since I passed.
The things I've done to you.
Does the… bite still hurt?
You okay?
Uh… Yeah, your bite hurt a lot for sure.
It was painful.
I'm so sorry.
She was kinda aggressive.
Thanks to her, I know everything.
I know all about your issues
and what troubles you.
With all of that, you still want me?
You know what type of girl I am.
If I say I get you
and that I totally accept you,
would you believe it?
I wish I could say I'm comfortable too.
I wonder if that
places pressure on you though.
I'd also feel miserable if I said no.
If I said I completely,
wholeheartedly believe you,
it would be a lie in itself, I think.
I'm a professional interpreter.
You're harder to understand
than Chalcatongo.
Chalca…
tong, what?
You see, it's a language considered
as the most peculiar in the world.
Gotcha. What I say
is difficult to understand.
That's true.
Do Ra-Mi showing up
basically allowed me to understand you.
None of this really matters.
We're gonna break up eventually anyway.
Whether I get sick of you
and end up going,
or you feel disappointed in me and leave.
This, too, will end.
Start with that in mind so we don't expect
to understand each other completely,
you know?
Uh, that could be true.
Look, Ho-jin.
Are we really destined to break up?
You mean it?
Then pick a date.
Oh.
I'm…
I think that
we can last for at least 30 days or so.
What do you think, Mu-hee?
Yeah, me too.
I do see us lasting at least that long.
Um, let's try this for a month, for sure.
- Huh?
- What?
Uh…
What happened?
Crap. The power went out
'cause we had too many heaters on.
Well, the building's almost
a hundred years old,
so the wiring's not up to date.
Then what now?
I don't know.
What do we do?
I can take you back.
I, uh…
Uh…
I wanna be with you.
CAN THIS LOVE BE TRANSLATED?
I'm sorry. Let's get going. It's starting.
Stop it.
No more.
I know.
I know who you're attracted to.
I've known for a long time now
that you like someone else.
Go.
Goodbye,
zombie.
What's up with Ho-jin
swapping his flight all of a sudden?
It could be his girlfriend made him stay.
I tried to ask him if he had a girlfriend,
but no response.
Really?
Did we interpret things wrong?
Hmm. Listen up. So you mentioned
there's a… a lady he pursued for a while.
Did that work out?
Jin-suk only said there was a girl,
so I don't know much about her either.
Well, why are you so interested
in other people's love lives?
He would be an amazing person
for noncelebrity casting.
He's just perfect.
I bet it'd be a good show.
Something bad just happened to us.
Bad like what?
This post claims that Cha Mu-hee
was hooking up with a married guy.
What?
Let me see.
PHOTO EVIDENCE OF CHA MU-HEE'S AFFAIR
THIS RAMEN CHEF WHO WAS ON TV
IS CHA MU-HEE'S EX
THEY EVEN MET IN JAPAN
WHILE HIS WIFE WAS PREGNANT
Apparently, Cha Mu-hee
used to date a top ramen chef
who became a store owner in Japan.
Rumor has it they were together
while the missus
was carrying the man's child.
- Oh my.
- Who is this guy?
Ah, this is a picture Mu-hee
took of him while in Enoshima.
Looks like it was taken
near his restaurant on April 8th.
And his missus was pregnant then.
8th April?
You sure it was posted on that day?
- Yeah.
- Wait a minute. Hold on.
What? What am I missing?
That's my birthday.
Oh, really?
Well, um, this picture here
looks a bit peculiar.
It could be of someone else since it's
a side profile shot they're looking at.
The post was deleted before she got big.
It's sus if you erase posts or unfollow.
It's like evidence.
She was there that day?
Exactly. Why'd she choose to be there?
It really makes her look bad.
Which means
this will impact the show.
It's probably nothing serious.
- I can look into it a little more.
- Hmm.
Ladies and gentlemen,
may I have your attention, please.
Welcome on this
Korean Airlines flight 001, Incheon.
On behalf of the crew, I ask
that you please direct your attention to…
Hiro.
You should get ready for the airport.
You slept here?
Hiro.
Hiro?
Hiro!
I went to get us food.
There's some water in the fridge.
What did you get? Any juice?
Mu-hee, you gotta leave now.
- Why?
- Nanami called and said Hiro collapsed.
What?
I'm needed to interpret right now.
But you can still make it
to your flight if you leave now.
What the heck is all this?
I was just sleeping,
and you stuck a needle in my arm?
You even called a doctor.
What did you think I'd done?
I apologize.
I know you're not as tough as you look,
but you wouldn't act so foolish
over heartbreak.
I jumped the gun.
I forgot I had taken my allergy meds
and had a few drinks. That's all.
And Joo Ho-jin?
Why'd you call that guy?
This is so embarrassing!
Now that I think about it,
this must be embarrassing for you.
Then why don't you stay passed out?
Don't be ridiculous.
But
he should have flown back by now.
Why is he still here?
I don't know.
I haven't had the chance to ask him.
Here he comes.
Would you like to ask him yourself?
The doctor says it was a side effect
of the antihistamines he took.
He also says there's no need to worry.
Once the IV is done
and he's rested, he should be fine
to catch his flight today.
Thank you.
Has he slept the whole time
without waking once?
Yes, he has.
- Excuse me.
- Sure.
Hello?
Why are you still here?
Good morning.
Are you feeling all right?
I'm all right.
Your flight was yesterday,
so why are you still here?
Did you meet Cha Mu-hee yesterday?
I did.
You're probably under the impression
that yesterday, you interpreted
my first confession to her.
But in reality,
I had already told her many times before…
…though she hadn't understood
because I'd told her in Japanese.
If…
she and I spoke the same language
and if she could understand
everything I had said
and my feelings toward her…
do you think I could have
won her over before you did?
To be honest,
I also had trouble
understanding her words.
I came close to giving up many times,
but, luckily enough,
a wonderful interpreter appeared
who helped me understand her.
An interpreter?
Yes.
Get well soon.
This is bad. Something's come up
on Ms. Cha Mu-hee's end.
Hmm?
It's a scandal.
Already?
Not with you!
- Then who? Me?
- Not you either, Hiro.
Huh?
People are saying she had an affair
with a married man.
An affair?
Oh man, answer your phone.
People believe I had an affair?
But I'm the one he cheated on.
That fucking son of a bitch!
Ruining my life even now! Asshole!
The complete guide to Do Ra-mi's affair.
She allegedly had an affair with the chef
of a ramen restaurant
who has a Japanese wife and a baby.
His wife was pregnant around the time
Cha Mu-hee is suspected
to have met him in Japan.
As the affair rumors grow,
Cha Mu-hee posted a story on Instagram
with the caption, "My blood is boiling."
Was it an affair,
or was the man two-timing her?
Opinions are still divided.
She visited a ramen shop
and posted a photo with the family
while keeping the store anonymous.
She didn't throw her ex under the bus,
which means they're still on good terms.
So it seems she wasn't having an affair.
Pretty cool, huh?
Things have been crazy
since we made it back from Italy.
Luckily enough, it might be dying down
since a K-pop scandal
replaced ours in the news.
Yeah. She posted a friendly photo
with her ex and his wife.
There's people who still believe
that she had an affair though.
There's not much we can do about trolls
who post and drop mean comments.
But, I mean,
isn't Mu-hee pretty easygoing?
She seems to be close
with her ex's wife, even.
They're not though.
Apparently, the ex cheated on Mu-hee
with that woman.
What?
She thought bringing it up
might fuel the fire.
So she said he was just an acquaintance
since that's the most simple way
to finally stop it all.
What an ass.
Mu-hee must've been mad.
She must have felt so… so angry.
Wait a minute.
You managed to learn this, how exactly?
Was it Yong-u?
Huh?
Yeah.
So the man in the picture
she took back then in Japan,
if that's not the chef, who is he?
Hello.
Oh.
When you met Eiko, right.
The man from Enoshima?
He looks just like me.
There's no resemblance at all.
We're similar enough
to where they couldn't tell.
But you saw Ho-jin.
You know they look different.
Don't we look alike?
Mm, I don't really remember,
but I think you both have thoughtful eyes
and a regal air about you.
You do?
But saying you two look alike
makes it seem as though
she's dating a man who resembles you
because she's still not over you.
Tell her you don't look alike,
so she won't be upset.
- It's a pass from her. Yep.
- You see?
Why are you here? What do you want?
I'm on a business trip
and wanted to… to personally thank you.
Mu-hee.
The way you promoted
the restaurant online went viral.
I appreciate it.
Thank you very much.
Also, I just finished
this ramen pack to push for sales online.
I brought some for my friends to try.
Could you try
and share it again on Instagram?
Seriously?
Sorry.
I'll go change his diaper, then.
Given the situation,
we had to tell the world we were buddies.
However, we're not.
I'm the dreadful ex who two-timed you,
vanished, and just found somebody else.
Yeah, that's right.
You better get lost. Your ramen packs too.
Sorry.
I came back because it's serious.
To tell you the truth, my boy's sick.
I need to make more money for his surgery.
He's had a heart problem since birth,
you know.
I'm being shameless here
'cause I was hoping you'd help.
She said it was her
ex-husband's.
Mm.
She got pregnant during her divorce.
I don't know.
Eiko wasn't doing too well,
and neither was the kid.
So I said you should still give birth.
I'll take care of him.
So after all that, I ended up a dad.
Mu-hee.
As your responsibilities grow,
your ego matters less too.
Seriously? You wanna guilt-trip me now?
But you're the one who lied to me.
You gotta be kidding.
That's true.
I'm a complete jerk.
- But I'm not a traitor.
- What?
The whole time we were together,
you thought I was gonna leave you.
I ended up abandoning you,
so you were right.
So I'm not a traitor.
Sure.
Yeah, I was panicking
because I predicted it.
Lao Tzu said that
if you feel troubled,
maybe better futures
are all you can focus on.
As your ex,
you had love,
but I lost you
'cause the future just spooked you.
Don't be so fearful with your guy
and be a little more present too.
Please stop with the advice.
I'm a bad person who can't help but worry.
I'm being quite serious
now that you're well-known.
Everybody's digging for information
about us, and even Eiko's ex too.
If the tabloids are this nosy,
it's about to get a lot worse
for your boyfriend.
I figured you'd feel anxious about that.
There's some big downsides
to becoming famous, aren't there?
Sorry.
Don't say a word if I write about it.
I hope you make enough.
Don't forget the hashtag
Momo-chan Ramen. Thanks.
Thank you very much!
She shows up, makes a scene,
and says she's a family member.
And then an affair?
She did respond and denied it all.
Like mother, like daughter, huh?
Blood explains everything.
Isn't her father's blood
running through her veins too?
Hey.
Mu-hee really does resemble
that woman a lot.
Undeniably so.
I do know Mr. Cha,
chairman of the Myeongjin Foundation.
I used to do a lecture at that university.
Are there family issues
I should be warned about?
His brother died a while back, didn't he?
Mm-hmm, yeah.
Chairman Cha told me he had two brothers.
The second eldest is now in charge
of a business in China, I think.
But I hear the youngest died quite young.
I believe he died in a terrible accident.
What kind of accident was it? Do you know?
I don't know any details, unfortunately.
Just ask Mr. Oh about it.
He'd be likely to help you
since they went to school together.
But why are you so curious
about that family?
Ah! Cha Mu-hee is a member
of that family. Am I right, Ho-jin?
I saw a post online.
So you gonna tie the knot?
Meet the future in-laws?
Please don't get ahead of yourself.
Oh.
So you started dating finally?
Yes.
Oh!
That's great. Congratulations.
But, uh, is Cha Mu-hee doing all right?
There's been bad press.
Don't tell me you saw that.
Rumors has it she dated a married guy.
That's not true, right?
Of course not. You believe that stuff?
No.
A lot of people say it's true, you know.
Look at me.
People can claim whatever they want.
It's not true though.
"The truth isn't for us to decide."
It's from your own book, Young-hwan.
How can you publish these words
and just believe
manipulative gossip like that?
Yeah, no. I didn't think it was true.
And yet you still bought
she'd pull something like that.
Don't worry about it if it's not true.
I'm pissed off!
It's irresponsible to gossip!
That's how these rumors spread!
Stop riding my back.
I didn't do anything wrong.
You know you represent
the brightest minds as a writer…
…and that even you could be
manipulated easily
by baseless speculations
is, I mean,
extremely disappointing.
I'm sorry about that.
I…
just…
I'm sorry.
I apologize.
It's time to go home now.
Hey, y… you wanted to talk
to Mr. Oh about something.
He's coming over for a drink in a bit.
Just stay.
- I'll make his acquaintance on my own.
- Why?
I'm a loose cannon?
So you won't finish a game of "Go"
with your old friend?
Be careful.
I was pretty close to winning the game.
He left. Did you have a fight?
Oh, come on, ma'am.
Do you believe
I would pick a fight with a man
who's young enough to be my son?
Really?
I was just scolded
for being a loudmouth.
Oh well.
He can't exactly pick fights
with every person
who starts gossiping about her.
He must be frustrated.
ASSOCIATE PARK JI-MIN
JUST SENT MATERIALS FOR THE UPCOMING
CONFERENCE INTERPRETATION. PLEASE REVIEW
MS. CHA MU-HEE
MR. JOO, DID YOU LAND OKAY?
I DID. DON'T WORRY. IT'LL ALL WORK OUT.
Ho-jin, I don't think
we can meet up for a while.
I'll reach out again
once things calm down.
PAPAGO♥
ALL RIGHT. SPEAK SOON
If the tabloids are this nosy,
it's about to get a lot worse
for your boyfriend.
You should rest.
As advised, we put a notice
of legal action on all the forums,
and most of the comments
have been taken down.
- Kim Yong-u.
- Yeah?
You sure Mu-hee and the guy
don't know each other?
The man in that Japan trip picture.
Um…
She said he's just a guy
she happened to meet there.
- Is he famous?
- No, he's some regular guy.
- Huh.
- Yong-u.
If this type of story goes viral
during a time like this,
it might make things difficult for her
and the nobody. You know that, right?
Mu-hee is very aware, too,
and has not spoken to him
at all because of it.
She's being extremely cautious.
Just be careful, man.
Oh yeah.
A sports agency reached out for you.
I know sports management was your goal,
so you'll move over soon.
Thank you so much.
No problem.
Don't bow when it's just the two of us.
Wait till my sister hears about it.
- So which champion will I work with?
- You're gonna love this.
Listen, you're going to Europe!
- A European athlete?
- Yeah!
Will I fly to Europe immediately?
Yeah, sure.
First, let's prepare your visa.
And then, you should hit the gym
and get in shape. Get it? Get it?
- Uh, Uncle, about that.
- Hmm?
Uh, could I get, like, three months?
No, wait, maybe six months?
Come on, Yong-u.
You got a girl?
Well, it's still quite new.
I'm worried Europe might ruin it.
You think going in six months won't?
How do you know that?
I mean, it's not like
she doesn't want us to work.
Yong-u. Nephew. Listen up.
You focus on one target.
Your dream, or love. Pick one.
You only get one dream per man, okay?
Why did he pick my birthday to go there?
Hey, Mu-hee?
It's the same passcode.
I remembered it.
I figured I'll wait inside.
It's been a while, honey.
Honey?
It's Do Ra-mi.
I'm here 'cause we need to talk.
You must be surprised
since I showed up all of a sudden.
But then, I have been here before,
so I'm not worried at all.
I don't really care, but you're…
you're wearing this gown again?
Oh, this.
Do Ra-mi wore this when she was here.
I'm trying to look more like her.
Hmm.
Tell me. The suspense is killing me.
I'm saying this on behalf of Mu-hee
because she'd never tell you.
What's that?
Well…
Hey, Ho-jin.
No, I, uh…
Honey, this might
very well upset you and complicate things.
Not much we can do.
The decision's made already.
Given everything going on.
But I wanna believe you can take it.
You're acting awkward. Long intro.
It's Mu-hee-esque.
It's Do Ra-mi-esque.
I'm sorry, Do Ra-mi.
I was mistaken. You're pretty ugly to me.
And Mu-hee's pretty, no matter what.
Whenever she smiles.
She looks pretty when she cries.
She's pretty even when she's angry.
But Do Ra-mi is sorta grim.
No matter what she does.
Do Ra-mi and Mu-hee
are practically the same.
That's enough.
Ugly Do Ra-mi, just spit it out.
I'm prepared to hear what you have to say.
I don't mind at all.
It's okay.
Break up with her now if you want to.
You even refused
to follow me on Instagram, Ho-jin.
Now people will start poking around
and obsess about you 'cause we're dating.
People think we had an affair this time.
In the future,
they might accuse you of worse things.
I think the best thing we can do now…
is to
end things between us.
No.
I don't get ashamed or afraid
because of gossip,
and I have nothing to hide.
They won't manipulate me like that.
They can't harm me like that.
You'll be fine for now,
but it could affect you later.
Why should I care?
We'll break up eventually anyway.
For the time being,
let's not worry
and end it over things like that.
Thanks for coming here
just to give me some useful advice.
But, Do Ra-mi, I think it's time to go.
I wanna see Mu-hee
if you don't mind, okay?
Can we agree that
Do Ra-mi came to see you tonight?
I feel ashamed 'cause admitting I'm Mu-hee
is embarrassing.
Now I can't say that I zoned out.
That would sound crazy.
I actually don't mind.
I've become pretty used to it.
Isn't this
a little awkward?
Like…
Uh, I'm not used to
transforming when I'm with you, Ho-jin.
- Huh?
- My transformation.
Ah, I see.
I don't know how.
I'm, uh…
Why don't you
transform by
taking off that silly robe you're wearing?
Ah… right.
Oh, right.
Uh…
Trans…
formation…
Hey, Ho-jin.
Oh, hey, Mu-hee!
Why are you cracking up? Excuse me?
I missed you, Mu-hee.
I was worried about you.
But I've been missing you more.
My transformation queen.
Hey, Ho-jin. Are you on the train?
- Yeah, it's leaving soon. And you?
- I'm on my way to the editing room.
I could've checked the footage later,
but Yeong-a wanted me to come today.
Otherwise, I'd go to Busan with you today.
I'd be too busy
to hang out with you anyway.
The conference is too long.
I mean, I wasn't gonna
actually follow you, Ho-jin.
I'd love to see Busan. That's all.
The meeting will likely run long,
so I'll get home late.
But if it's gonna be too late,
just stay there overnight.
No. Then I wouldn't be able to see you.
I'd really miss my Mu-hee.
I'll take the last train.
Well, all right.
Um, I wish you a safe trip.
I'll message you when I get there. Bye.
If he wasn't coming back,
I would've gone to Busan tonight.
Cha Mu-hee is here.
Mu-hee, are you all right?
I can't believe all of this.
Either way, I'm glad it's over.
Sorry for the chaos.
What happened was terrible.
- Sorry.
- Hmm.
You didn't deserve this mess.
Thanks for coming.
Um, well,
it'll be good to catch up with you
before we finish editing the part
we shot in the castle.
- Mm.
- Hiro is also gonna be here today.
Hiro's going to be here?
Did he get upset
'cause of the commotion I've caused?
He didn't.
Actually, Hiro helped
to make sure you'd be okay.
He covered up your scandal in Japan
by releasing marketing articles
way before it got any chance to spread.
He did that so it would seem like
made-up gossip too.
He helped me?
Oh.
I appreciate that.
You know, I was gonna talk about
Hiro's confession of love
that happened that day.
Is it appropriate to include that?
Oh, but it…
it's not like it meant anything important
beyond the project.
It did, Mu-hee.
He actually meant it.
You didn't know?
Hiro! Hello!
- Welcome.
- Hello.
The train will be departing soon.
Please have your ticket ready
as the conductor…
Ho-jin?
Ji-sun.
- You going to Busan?
- Yeah, I've got an event there.
I see. I'll help my parents
take care of a few things.
Ah.
Hiro.
I was wondering if you're… all right.
Are you okay?
- Mm.
I heard you helped me out.
Thank you.
Seems it's impossible.
"Okay, thank you"
isn't really a conversation.
I wonder when Nanami's coming in?
Did he really mean what he said back then?
I'm not sure how to bring it up.
Castle.
Love… Really?
That make sense?
This isn't the best method to ask him.
Ask me.
I understand most of what you said.
I've been trying to make progress.
Okay, but, uh…
Is it possible you picked up
what I just said?
Castle, love, really?
I meant it.
Strange how we bump into each other.
Back then, this is how we met
all those years ago.
Flying to Japan that time.
That's right.
This is a miracle given the odds.
I can't help but ask you…
What?
Enoshima.
The birthday present I told you about.
You know which one?
I'll answer your question.
The truth is, I really did
like you.
What were you doing
in Enoshima on my birthday?
Ho-jin, did you… have a crush on me?
CAN THIS LOVE BE TRANSLATED?
This love is bittersweet
I wanna be yours, I wanna be yours
Close to me, close to me, close to me
Bittersweet
This love is bittersweet
I wanna be yours, I wanna be yours
Close to me, close to me, close to me
Bittersweet
This love is bittersweet
Say it to me, say it to me
I'll light it up
The way you walk to me