[Disclaimer:
All depicted events are fictional
and for entertainment purposes only;
viewer discretion is advised]
Do you know that spirit?
It's none of your business.
You literally said,
"He's not the Khemmika you knew."
You talked about me, didn't you?
See that sign over there?
It used to be a viewpoint.
How about we pitch a tent
and do some stargazing tonight?
I've got a long-range rifle, baby!
Hey, are you done yet?
Jet,
help Uncle Chai
gather the entire village.
We'll form search groups
to look for Te, Korn, and Phu.
They must be found before noon.
Why before noon?
If they're not found by noon,
we're looking for bodies.
You may rise.
You came because of
those three boys, didn't you?
I fully understand
that the three of them
have offended you.
I will make them pay
for what they've done.
All I ask is that
you let them go
and let them live.
I never wanted those impure souls.
It was someone else who caused this,
not me.
What do you mean?
Lord of the Mountains, Phuchong,
we've done everything,
but she wouldn't regain her senses.
Hold her tight.
There's an intruder in my forest.
I assume this has something
to do with you.
Little boy, please wake up
and help Khem.
Please.
Little boy...
Khem!
Khem...
I'll have the nymphs release them,
but only if they enter monkhood,
cast off desire for at least six years,
and observe the Eight Precepts for life.
Should they fail,
they shall be summoned back here,
cursed to roam this forest,
never to reincarnate again.
I am deeply grateful.
Phuchong is my name.
One more soul
has strayed into this forest.
I can only help those three.
As for the other one,
you'll have to find a way on your own.
The other one?
Who are you referring to?
We're in trouble, Master.
It's Khem.
He's disappeared, Master.
You need to help him!
Please.
It's my fault, too.
I shouldn't have taken my eyes off him.
I'm begging you, too.
Please help him.
Please.
I never said I'd refuse.
You all will stay here.
Don't let the flame die.
If I'm not back in an hour,
light a stick of incense to summon me.
Khem!
A letter for you, Khem.
[Notification of Killed in Action
and Posthumous Commendation]
No...
It can't be.
Calm down, Khem.
He wasn't supposed to die like this.
He can't just leave me.
No...
He would never leave me.
Khem!
Are you okay, Khem?
Breathe slowly, okay?
Take it easy.
Khem...
Help! Khem needs help!
Khem!
Khem...
Please marry me.
I'm sorry,
but my love is for Wat.
Even if he never comes back,
I'll keep waiting for him.
If anything happens to her
while I'm gone,
you're in big trouble.
Khem and I...
We're engaged, Mom!
Thank you. You're...
Pawat.
I'm Pawat Wongpradit.
Pawat...
That's a beautiful name.
I'm Khem,
Khemmika.
You remember everything now, don't you?
You are...
Mr. Chayod,
aren't you?
Just call me Yod like you used to.
I haven't changed,
and you're still my Khemmika.
But...
Mr. Chayod,
your Khemmika
is gone.
But you remember me now.
Let me take care of you
just like I promised to.
Please, Khem.
Come stay here with me.
Let's stay here together.
I can't.
If I stay here,
that means I'm dead.
No, Khem.
Trust me.
Everything will just go back
to the way it was.
Step back.
Please just let me go.
How long will you keep rejecting me?
When will I matter to you?
Argh!
Run, sweetie!
Mom...
I've been watching over you all along.
Every day, I wished
I could show myself to you.
I'm sorry...
I wasn't able to do that until now.
It's totally okay.
I always knew
you'd come for me.
Are you doing okay, Mom?
Don't be scared.
I'll take you out of here.
Come on.
Let's go back to Master.
Think you're leaving this place?
Mom!
Khem!
You know I own this place.
- Khem!
- Did you actually think I wouldn't know
- where you were hiding?
Khem!
Mr. Chayod,
let him go.
Please don't hurt him.
Just take it out on me!
Mom...
Mom!
I have cherished and protected you
for over 80 years.
How could I let you be taken
by someone else so easily?
Leave me alone.
(Incanting)
Go away!
You have no idea how much I loved her.
(Incanting)
And how much it hurt
to watch her suffer because of you.
(Incanting)
You left her in your last life.
And you don't love him in this one.
(Incanting)
Why the hell are you standing in my way?
You didn't love him.
You've only loved yourself.
Look at that face.
Look at the face
of the one you claim to love.
I told you to look at that face!
Should this be
the face of someone you love,
someone you want to protect?
Is this how you want him to be?
If your love were real,
you wouldn't want this to happen.
Khem!
Khem, hang in there.
Master...
Master,
it's been an hour.
Come with me.
Get the pot.
Here you go.
Close it with a talisman.
A talisman!
Seal the pot!
Where's Khem, though?
Follow me.
Both of you.
Khem!
Khem...
Khem, where are you?
Khem!
- Khem...
- Khem!
You're Charn, right?
Yes.
- Khem!
Your instincts are strong.
Focus your mind on Khem,
and follow wherever your gut leads you.
Me?
Yeah.
Just give it a shot.
This way!
Khem!
Khem...
Hang in there, Khem.
We're coming.
Khem!
Khem.
Please show yourself.
Khem...
Khem!
- Khem...
- Show yourself, please.
- Where are you?
- Come to us, Khem.
- Khem!
- Khem.
- Khem...
- Khem!
- Stop.
(Incanting)
- Khem!
- Khem...
Khem...
- Khem!
- Khem...
Leave it.
I'll take him.
Take this.
Okay.
Yod!
It was you, wasn't it?
I'm sorry.
How could you do such a thing?
I'm your brother!
And Khem was your friend.
How could you kill her?
How could you?!
I didn't mean to.
I'm sorry.
I just wanted her to let go of you.
By doing something this evil?
You forged the paper.
You're going to jail for this!
I'm sorry, Wat.
I was a fool.
Couldn't think straight.
I just knew I loved her.
I really did, Wat.
Please forgive me.
Please...
Forgive me, Wat.
Our parents' inheritance...
and everything I have...
It's all yours.
From now on,
we're no longer family.
Now leave.
Get out of here!
I said, "Get out!"
I'm sorry, honey.
I'm sorry...
I wasn't strong enough.
I should've waited longer for you.
Wat,
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Hold me if you want.
Let your tears fall if they must.
But never forget that I'm not Pawat
and that you're not Khemmika.
The past is in the past.
Right now, we're just two people
who have met by chance.
Master,
can you please stay with me for now?
At least until I fall asleep.
How will you sleep
staring at me like that?
Can I...
hold your hand, please?
Just this once.
Next time, I won't go easy on you.
Te!
- Found them?
- Hey...
Mister!
We couldn't find any of them.
Right, we didn't see them.
- Did you search everywhere?
- Found them?
Yes, mister.
Let's keep going.
- Come on, follow him.
- Go.
Let's go.
Korn!
Te, Korn!
- Where are you?
- Phu!
- Te!
- Where are you?
Where are you?
Te, Korn, Phu!
- Where are you guys?
- Mister! Mister...
- What?
- We haven't found any of them.
Where are they?
Guys,
we need to find them.
Hey, you go that way.
All of you.
- Search everywhere.
- Let's go, guys.
- Let's go this way.
- Te!
Alright, mister.
- Korn!
- Where are you?
- Follow me.
- Korn, Phu!
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Let's go this way.
Phu!
Te, Korn, Phu!
Where are you?
It's already 4:45 A.M.
Do it.
Will it really work?
It did last time.
My master said you sense things well.
But...
they don't really get along with me.
Will it really work?
Just do it.
You'll never know if you don't.
Te, Korn,
Phu!
Show yourselves.
Come out already.
You're causing trouble for everyone.
That way, Jet!
- Let's go.
- Go.
Move, move.
Right here.
- Watch that.
- Careful.
Get him in there.
Hey,
lucky for them
that the forest guardian let them out.
Alright,
you should get some rest.
I'm taking these guys to the hospital.
Thanks, Uncle.
Yeah.
- Let's go.
- Go.
- Hold them tight.
- Okay.
Don't fall asleep.
Hang in there.
Ask me anything you want.
I know you've been dying to know
since last night.
You're right.
I've got a lot of questions.
But...
you should go rest.
You've had the hardest time.
I'm getting some sleep, too.
When we've got our energy back,
let's have a meal together.
Khem can join us, too.
So it's you who has been
stirring chaos in my forest.
I merely came to tend to my own affairs.
I meant you no offense, Lord.
Then...
what brings you here,
to provoke me in my own domain?
You may stay if you wish,
but I forbid you from laying a finger
on the souls bound to my forest.
Then, by the same token,
I ask that you
keep clear of the karma I must bear.
From this moment on,
do not lend aid to any vile souls
who dare stand in my way.
- Or else...
- What could a lesser spirit do to me?
Begone from my cave
at once!
Wat...
I'm sorry,
Master.
Have you...
been sitting here all night?
Yeah.
Didn't want to wake you up
by moving my finger.
No need to smile.
I'm annoyed.
I didn't do it willingly.
Being harsh again.
Go wash up and get dressed.
Then come with me.
Uh...
- Will you have breakfast now...
- No.
You and I have things to deal with.
Tell me
how you followed Khem into this life.
When I decided to leave this world,
I prayed with all my heart.
[I can no longer bear the sins]
Should there be a next life...
[I have hurt the ones I love...]
[I offer my life as penance.
Please forgive me... From Chayod]
Let me see Khem again.
Before my new life began,
I encountered her soul.
And I found that malevolent spirit,
who had long bound herself to her.
At last,
you've come to me.
You were torn apart
from your love in this life.
In the next one,
what fate shall you face?
Let me go.
Who are you?
Why are you messing with me?
Don't you remember me,
Krongkwan?
Who are you talking about?
Let me go.
What did I do to you?
You turned me into this!
Let her soul go.
I told you to let her go.
Khem...
Leave me alone!
How could you do that, Yod?
How?
How could you do that?
Do you understand me now?
How does it feel
to be torn away
from your beloved by another?
Still...
thanks to you,
I didn't have to lift a finger.
It's a pity, though,
that you chose to take your own life.
Don't you know that it's sinful?
You may not be born a human
in your next life.
Or...
would you rather become
my spirit servant?
What say you?
I'd rather be born a beast
than serve a wretched spirit like you.
Do as you will.
If you'll keep pursuing your grudge
against Khem,
I shall bind my soul to hers
to protect her in every life.
You?
What power do you have over me?
Yod!
Yod,
don't do that.
Yod...
Yod!
Don't do that.
Stop.
Yod...
Please.
Yod!
What's going on?
What's happening here?
See you soon.
That malevolent spirit is 'Ramphueng.'
She has great power
and has lingered
for more than four centuries.
That's all I know.
Ramphueng.
Khem,
I'm sorry for everything.
Everything I did
was out of my love for you,
even if it was a selfish kind of love.
From here on,
whether you choose to forgive me or not,
I will bear the consequences.
I forgive you, Mr. Chayod.
Also...
thank you
for always protecting me.
Wat,
I entrust Khem to you.
Take good care of him in this life,
for you have loved him deeply
for so long.
Farewell, Wat,
Khem.
Leaving but telling me
to do things, huh?
May you find peace in another life,
Yod.
With you staring this hard,
how am I supposed to eat?
Uh...
Sorry.
I was just thinking of...
- Ram...
- You're returning to Bangkok, right?
Is there nothing to do at the camp?
There you go
shutting me down again.
Now that we know who my karmic enemy is,
aren't you going
to do something, Master?
I helped you with Chayod
only because that karma was bound to me.
As for the rest,
it's beyond my reach.
But we've come this far, Master.
You want me to break my promise
to my grandfather?
I've done my part.
The rest is yours to face.
Wait here.
There's still someone
waiting for your farewell.
Let your mom know I said hi.
I'll sleep in the hall tonight.
Thanks, Jet.
Mom,
you're safe here.
Please come to me.
Mom...
How am I supposed to eat
when you hug me this tight?
I've been waiting for you
for years, Mom.
Mom,
why...
have you never once come for me?
I had only this much strength.
If I had come to see you more often,
I might have faded away
long before you grew up.
I'm sorry, sweetie.
I understand, Mom.
I've always felt...
your presence with me all along.
Come on, let's eat.
Don't you want some, too, sweetie?
Master told me...
- this...
- Meals prepared for spirits
are not meant for the living to eat.
Mom,
you should try some.
I made it with all my heart.
This is actually better than my food.
You raised me well, Mom.
I couldn't have done it without you.
Don't cry, Mom.
It's been years
since we had a meal together.
- Let's eat, sweetie.
- Okay.
Let's eat.
The food's getting cold.
With cooking skills like this,
you won't have any trouble
finding a lover.
I haven't had any.
Please send my thanks to Jet, Charn,
and Master Paran.
Everyone loves
and cares for you so much.
I believe that Jet and Charn do,
but...
Master?
He's so cold and harsh.
That's not true.
He's just pretending to be cold.
That one worries about you
more than anyone.
What?
Are we talking about the same Master?
He even saved you when you were little.
What?
But...
I just met him
for the first time a few days ago.
How would that be possible?
I took you to Grand Master Sek's place,
remember?
I do.
But...
have I met Master Paran before?
It was him
who carried you all the way
to me and your dad.
Hey!
So it was him
who saved me?
Yes, sweetie.
Now that you're with him,
I'm convinced
that fate has sent a guardian
to watch over you.
Just this much
is enough to ease my worries.
But...
about the curse,
I'm not even sure...
if he's gonna help me.
But...
don't worry, Mom.
I'll take good care of myself
and...
live a long life.
I know you will.
It's late now.
I think it's time for me to leave.
But...
before you do,
can you sing me a lullaby
like you used to?
Sure.
Come on.
♫Sleep now, honey, I'll lull you near♫
♫Swinging you gently,
I'll be right here♫
♫My little treasure, don't shed a tear♫
♫My beautiful angel, you are my dear♫
May you rest in peace, Auntie.
Pour the water and accept the blessing.
(Chanting)
May you be blessed.
May my parents be filled with happiness.
In our next lives,
I hope to be your child again, Mom.
Dotty!
You've changed a lot, huh?
Looks like he remembers her now.
That means he remembers you, too!
You remembered him
right away, didn't you?
Just help him already, Master.
No need to act so reluctant.
- Ouch...
Something's off. He didn't punish us.
Maybe he's giving in?
Sorry.
Did I wake you up?
Go sleep in the bedroom.
Why are you doing it
right over where I sleep?
Well,
I'm cleaning every corner of the place.
Today?
For what?
Yeah.
Maybe...
it could change Master's mind.
What's up with you?
So,
I've made up my mind.
The club's going back to Bangkok soon,
and...
I want to ask Master
if I can stay here longer.
What?
What happened?
Weren't you mad at him just now?
Are you possessed?
Are you under a spell?
Calm down!
I just feel like
he's not actually cruel.
And at the very least,
if I stay here and make myself useful,
he may change his mind.
There you go, man!
Don't worry.
I'll help you out.
I swear,
this place will be spotless
before he wakes up.
There won't be a speck of dust anywhere.
Better keep your word.
Let's do it now, shall we?
Which room should we clean first?
So...
- This room?
- How about Master's?
Let's clean this one first.
Stop it, Ramphueng.
You know my name?
I was minding my own path.
It is you who came to provoke me.
Go into the forest
and look for red pieces of paper
rolled like this.
Because it's not dark yet,
Phrai, the territory holder,
is still awake.
Phrai?
Who's that?
May I stay here
until the semester break ends?
Please.
Please, Master.
Master's dad and Prim's were close,
so they'd often visit each other.
♫Our love would never fade away♫
♫Eternal love lasts forever and always♫
♫Even in death, my love will stay♫
♫If this were our very last day,♫
♫Our love would never fade away♫
♫Eternal love lasts forever and always♫
♫Even in death, my love will stay♫