It's already dawn,
and we've heard all the stories.
Why aren't they out yet?
They're driving me crazy.
In fact,
there is one other way to help Mu Long.
Say it.
The solution lies inside you.
You mean the Dragon Deity's Power?
That scent…
Master Dragon Deity?
Searing flames, ignite!
You're not Lu Wuyi.
Come with me.
Master Dragon Deity?
It's you?
So you really are helping Lu Wuyi.
Wuyi,
what happened to you?
- Wu…
- It was him.
He used Word Magic on Mu Long.
He joined forces with Jiu Ying long ago.
I found out,
and when I tried to tell you, Wangyan,
he wounded me.
Ji Ling hurt you?
Ji, help me.
I'm afraid that if Wangyan
learns the truth,
she'll come to despise me.
I don't want to lose her.
You're not saying anything.
Are you admitting it?
Why did you give me this bracelet?
Bai Ze's Eastern Purple Lightning
can suppress evil.
Wear it, and it can temporarily suppress
Jiu Ying's spirit fragment.
Is it really meant to suppress
Jiu Ying's spirit fragment?
That bracelet is fake.
Ji Ling, didn't you say that bracelet
could suppress Jiu Ying's fragment?
Was it a lie?
If I hadn't lied to him,
how could I have lowered his guard?
You can go kill Chi Wen now.
You really did keep your promise.
Now you can sit
on the Dragon Deity's throne
forever.
I believe Wuyi.
Wangyan…
You've sat on the Dragon Deity's throne
too long.
You don't want to give it up, do you?
As long as the Word Magic
on Mu Long isn't lifted,
Han Ba won't hand over
the Dragon Deity's Power,
and Wu Shiguang
won't be able to become a dragon.
And that means the throne stays his.
You betrayed your oath to Master Chi Wen.
Didn't you reclaim your demon power too,
betraying your oath just the same?
You have no right to accuse me.
But why did he snatch Mu Long's pendant?
Because Su Jian's memories
are stored inside it.
He wanted to help Jiu Ying
hide something shameful.
It has Jian's memories inside.
Even if you take the pendant,
it won't help.
We already know everything.
Lu Wuyi was created by Jiu Ying,
wasn't she?
It's empty?
The memories are gone.
You lied to me.
So she took
the memories back.
The manuscript!
The first chapter of that manuscript
was Little Pomegranate's story.
The handwriting was all crooked.
It was really ugly.
But still, I recognized the words
"Little" and "Pomegranate".
THE GREAT DEMON AND LITTLE POMEGRANATE
That was Su Jian's handwriting.
She wrote the story
of Little Pomegranate.
Master Dragon Deity returned this to us.
He didn't want it.
I'll go bring the medicine over.
NIAN
So what she wrote was "Nian",
as in never forgetting.
So whenever the wind stirred the tree,
all it carried
were sighs.
And yet I never had the courage
to go up to her.
Don't go. It's dangerous.
His demon power is leaking out.
To keep another drought from breaking out,
I grant you the Dragon Deity's Power.
It can temporarily stop
your demonic energy from leaking.
But this borrowed power
will run out one day.
Wangyan, Han Ba's mind is in chaos.
He's about to lose control
of his demon power.
I won't be able
to see Mu Long finish
her story collection after all.
I hid the Dragon Deity's Power
in the place where I first met Su Jian.
I placed a seal on it.
Only when Mu Long regains consciousness
will it be unsealed.
Please, save Mu Long for me.
I'm sorry that even at the very end,
I'm still this selfish.
This is for you.
At just over 20, you're the perfect age
for carrying an old man's fan.
I'm coming…
to you.
Because of what you did,
none of this can be undone now.
The memories were long gone
from that pendant.
Whether I took it or not,
nothing could have prevented
Han Ba's collapse
after learning the truth.
The ending was written from the start.
Blaming me won't change a thing.
Such is fate.
No matter how many times we try,
some things can never be undone.
Some people are destined
to be like two great mountains
separated by an endless plain, a canyon,
or a distance they can never cross.
They watch over each other from afar,
yet can never take one step
or even half a step
toward one another.
Tell me.
What are they waiting for?
They're waiting for a snowfall.
With just one snowfall,
they can bow to each other from afar
and grow old together.
With just one snowfall,
they can bow to each other from afar
and grow old together.
What, you don't like it anymore?
It doesn't really go
with what I'm wearing today.
Come with me!
Wuyi!
I wonder whether Wu Shiguang and Wangyan
will be able to find Ji Ling and Wuyi.
Right now, only Ji Ling can wake you.
There's nothing I can do to help.
Su Jian treated me like her older sister,
yet I forgot her.
Ji Ling took Wuyi away
right in front of me,
yet there was nothing I could do.
Do you still think of her
as your little sister?
She is my little sister.
Maybe I can't tell
real memories from fake ones,
but when Jiu Ying held me captive,
it was Lu Wuyi
- who risked everything to save me.
- Wangyan…
When she looked at me,
the trust and dependence in her eyes
couldn't have been fake.
The one truly at fault in all this
is Ji Ling.
Wuyi was blinded by love.
That's why she covered for him.
You lied to me.
Whatever the truth is,
we have to find them first,
not only to save Lu Wuyi,
but also to put an end to this drought.
I already have three strands
of the Dragon Deity's Power in me.
Once I get the last one, I can transform
into a dragon and bring rain.
I'll take you to Ji Ling.
I know where he is.
Why?
Because I don't trust Lu Wuyi.
Wu.
Has the blowback
from the rewinds gotten worse?
That's none of your concern.
Wu, we are alone now.
Tell me. Why did you lie to me?
Since you've lived
through countless rewinds,
you must've known
Wu Shiguang and the others
learned the truth from the painting
and that the pendant
was no longer important.
And you must've known long ago
that there were no memories
left inside it.
Am I right?
Yes.
So,
from the very beginning,
this was a trap you carefully laid for me.
Then why did you trick me into stealing
that pendant for you?
Because you killed my sister.
I killed Wu Wangyan?
Do you know
who matters most to me
in this world?
Wu Wangyan.
That's right.
Even after she learned
that I was a monster created by Jiu Ying,
that all my memories with her
were fabricated,
she still saw me
as her irreplaceable little sister.
Wuyi,
don't call yourself a monster.
Don't call yourself trash
that nobody wants.
I don't know what others can give you.
But what I give you is my heart.
You will always be
my most beloved little sister.
Those words were meant for Su Jian,
not for me.
This isn't real.
Then what about this?
Is this fake too?
Listen to me carefully.
I will say this to you once again.
I will always be by your side.
You ruined her promise.
You killed her.
In all the previous rewinds,
you killed her right in front of me.
FIRST TIME
You joined forces with Jiu Ying.
You killed Wangyan
so Wu Shiguang would break down,
giving Jiu Ying the chance
to seize Wu Shiguang's body.
You said I lied to you.
You're right.
I did lie to you.
I was never trapped in the time rewinds.
I chose to start over again and again,
so I could stop you.
Too bad I failed every time.
Wangyan!
SECOND REWIND
THIRD REWIND
- Wangyan! What's wrong?
- Wuyi.
Wangyan, listen to me.
Ji Ling is going to kill you.
Come with me, now!
Wuyi, what are you talking about?
- I'm serious.
- Nobody…
Wang…
Every single time,
I had to watch my sister…
Wangyan.
…die by your hand.
FIFTH REWIND
Wangyan! Wangyan!
SIXTH REWIND
Wangyan.
SEVENTH REWIND
EIGHTH REWIND
NINTH REWIND
TENTH REWIND
ELEVENTH REWIND
TWELFTH REWIND
THIRTEENTH REWIND
Ji Ling…
You killed my sister.
FIFTEENTH REWIND
I'll never forgive you.
SIXTEENTH REWIND
I hate you.
SEVENTEENTH REWIND
I hate you!
NINETEENTH REWIND
Again and again, I had to endure
that piercing, bone-deep pain,
and still I couldn't change a thing.
But this time,
I did it.
Wu Shiguang didn't get
the Dragon Deity's Power kept by Han Ba,
and Wangyan learned what you were after.
Everyone has seen your true colors.
Wu,
do you know why I trusted you so much?
Do you know why I was willing
to do everything you said?
No.
- Because…
- I don't want to know.
So Wu Wangyan
is the only one you truly care about.
Because she
truly cares about me too.
Don't I care about you?
No matter.
I've grown used to it by now.
The people around me always end up
leaving me one by one.
No one ever stays.
Lift the Word Magic from Mu Long.
Even if I die,
I won't undo the Word Magic for you
to let you get the Dragon Deity's Power.
You knew I was here?
Have you forgotten
how I found you in the first place?
Why did you appear
outside the Shilin Sect?
I don't know.
I just felt a voice calling me,
telling me to come here.
All these years later,
that obsession is still in me,
telling me to go find you.
And somehow, I always do.
I wonder if I'll ever be able
to figure out
where that obsession comes from.
Li Jie,
do you blame me
for lying even to you?
Though I don't know your true intentions,
I have always known
what kind of person you are.
In all the years I've stayed by your side,
a lot of the time,
I didn't understand
your choices or intentions.
But I knew
you must've had reasons
you couldn't speak of.
I will always be
your shield and your blade.
What do we do now?
They're now all wary of me.
Bring Mu Long here for me.
I'll find a way to make Lu Wuyi
lift the Word Magic.
Understood.
Be careful.
Give me back my sister!
You're using the Dragon Deity's Power
against me?
I'll go rescue Wuyi.
You're trying to take my ring?
I'm going to use Xiaowei's power
inside that ring
to lift the Word Magic on Mu Long.
Like the Twelve Thoughts,
the Spirit-Binding Ring
obeys only its master.
Even if you take it, it won't obey you.
Its master?
The ring's true master
is Chi Wen, not you.
The Dragon Deity's Power in me
came from my brother.
I'd like to see if it'll obey you over me!
Ji Ling…
Wangyan.
Do you still
see me as your little sister?
No matter what happens,
you will always be
my most beloved little sister.
I will
always be by your side.
The Word Magic was cast by Lu Wuyi.
Even if you take the ring, it won't help.
Don't believe him!
Wangyan's Word Magic
is far stronger than mine.
If I had really cast it,
how could she possibly fail to undo it?
Wu Shiguang,
Lu Wuyi somehow gained
the power to rewind time.
Her power has already
surpassed all of ours.
You're sharp enough.
Haven't you noticed
anything strange about her?
I don't know
which of you is telling the truth.
But it doesn't matter.
Once I get the Spirit-Binding Ring,
I'll know.
Wangyan,
let's go.
Master Dragon Deity…
You Chi!
Hand over the ring,
or I'll kill him.
Only the ancient divine jade,
the Spirit-Storing Jade,
can hold the Dragon Deity's Power.
The Spirit-Storing Jade
was split in two by heavenly fire.
One became the six-eyed butterfly demon's
Spirit-Storing Butterfly.
The other became the Spirit-Binding Ring
worn by the Dragon Deity.
Wuyi!
So it really was Lu Wuyi.
Return.
The Spirit-Binding Ring
refused my summons.
How is that possible?
The ring has accepted Lu Wuyi
as its master.
Where could she have taken Long?
What Lu Wuyi wants has always been
the Dragon Deity's Power.
Han Ba said…
I hid the Dragon Deity's Power
in the place where I first met Su Jian.
The Wei mansion's weaving workshop.
I… I want to go home.
Don't be afraid.
You'll be home soon.
The Wei mansion?
Isn't that just an ordinary household?
How could it possibly hide
the Dragon Deity's Power?
The giant axle in the workshop
is the core of a Firefluff Tree.
I noticed it the first time
I went to the Wei mansion.
Back then, I wondered
why Xiaowei always fled
to the weaving workshop
to escape the Ice Curse.
The Firefluff Tree is of fire.
The Ice Curse can't get close to it.
Han Ba hid the Dragon Deity's Power
inside the tree core
and cultivated there to keep
his demonic energy from leaking.
What's a Firefluff Tree?
It sounds pretty incredible.
In remote antiquity,
heaven and earth split apart.
Nuwa sought five-colored stones
to mend the sky
and sent the Fox Queen to keep the earth
together with four pillars of ice.
Where the Four Ice Pillars stood
grew four divine trees
of metal, earth, water, and fire.
The Firefluff Tree was one of them.
Han Ba said that as soon
as Mu Long woke up,
the seal would undo itself.
Oh, no. Let's go!
Wake up.
Wuyi,
where… where am I?
Where's Mr. Yan?
Kneel.
Drink it.
I know him!
I've seen him at the Dragon Deity Temple!
He's Master Chi Wen!
The Dragon Deity has answered our prayers!
We're saved!
- Master Chi Wen!
- Master Chi Wen,
- please send us rain!
- Master Chi Wen, save us!
You can't just stand by and watch us die!
Master Chi Wen!
He's not the Dragon Deity.
- He can't help us!
- Master Chi Wen…
‪-Master Chi Wen…
‪-You did nothing!
- He's not the Dragon Deity!
- He's a fake!
He's a fraud!
You're a fraud!
Why did you lie to us?
Why?
Why can't I change the ending
after everything I've done?
Why?
Ji Ling. Ji Ling.
Ji Ling, wake up.
Ji Ling.