(Uilhan Brewery)
(1. Malting, 2. Malt milling, 3. Mash tun, 4. Hopping)
(Kim Se Jeong)
(Highly passionate, highly sensitive)
(Lee Jong Won)
(Shin Do Hyun)
(Baek Sung Chul)
(Uilhan Brewery)
(Naro Beer)
(Brewing Love)
(This is a work of fiction.)
(Scenes with child actors and animals were filmed...)
(under production guidelines along with experts.)
(Busan)
(Episode 1)
Mr. Lee, where are you?
Hurry up, will you?
Come on. A single truck won't be big enough...
to load all the beers there.
- It'll take a moment. - Don't forget the cash.
I'm in a rush and practically giving these away.
I'm well aware of that. Why else would I be risking my life?
Are you sure Jisang doesn't know about this?
If Mad Dog Yong Ju comes by, it'll be over for us.
I know that,
so get here before she does.
Sure thing. Hang tight.
I won't be long.
Mr. Lee, that was fast.
(Special Task Force)
That was fast, wasn't it?
Goodness.
Ms. Chae.
Ms. Chae,
what brings you by this early? And in a wing truck of all things.
You're asking as if you don't know.
Well, I don't.
Then allow me to explain in person.
According to the Liquor Tax Act, manufacturers...
cannot make direct sales to small business establishments...
and supermarkets.
That's why wholesalers...
lay a bridge between those two parties.
- Like yourself. - Right.
But that dear wholesaler...
received beer on credit...
and is selling it to small businesses at a discount...
while planning to take off without paying the manufacturer.
No wonder I had to come here at the crack of dawn.
Well,
I would've paid if I had the money.
Search me, why don't you?
I don't have a single penny.
As if I don't know you have it rough.
That's why I supplied beer for a year...
without taking payment first.
- Mr. Park. - Hold on a second.
You see, I...
Well, hold on.
Darn it.
What...
Oh, no.
Must you take it this far?
I'm doomed anyway, so what's there I won't do?
I have nothing to lose.
Get lost in your wing truck while I ask nicely.
- Mr. Park. - Get lost, darn it!
Get lost.
Why you... Get lost.
Are you all right?
That serves you right for coming at me.
Darn.
Yes, Mr. Lee. I'm heading out there right now.
Darn it. Mr. Lee!
Why are you just standing out here when...
- Whatever. Let's move the beer. - How?
I can't get my trucks in here.
Don't whine. We don't have much time.
Jisang Liquor is already here.
Darn it.
You! Move your cars.
I already have an agreement with Ms. Chae.
Ms. Chae...
(Jisang Liquor)
(A few hours ago)
Thanks for coming this early in the morning.
I bet Mr. Park is cooking something today.
I'm getting a bad feeling.
He still won't get the best of us when we have Ms. Chae in our corner.
- What's there to worry? - You're right.
Wholesalers always give you a headache.
Don't give all wholesalers a bad name, Mr. Kang.
During our worst times,
it's the wholesalers...
who buy our beer promising us they'll sell them.
Mr. Park and Mr. Lee are the rotten apples.
She's absolutely right, you punk.
Let's get this over with and grab some breakfast.
Sounds good. All right.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
(Back to a while ago)
Mr. Park.
The sun is out.
Let's wrap this up.
Pay us back until the end of the month,
or we'll press charges.
You can be punished by imprisonment for up to ten years...
or by a fine of under 20,000 dollars.
- You know the drill. - Yes.
Mr. Park and Mr. Lee who we call family.
Have another good day.
- Sure. - Thank you.
I'm Chae Yong Ju.
Gosh, don't.
- We'll have ours, ma'am. - Sure thing.
Here.
There you go.
Finally, we were able to take care of Mr. Park and his co-conspirator.
Good job, everyone.
Shall we fill our glasses?
Selling our product...
- That is a job half-done. - That is a job half-done.
How do we complete our business?
- By collecting the bill. - By collecting the bill.
(Pop)
I'm sorry, but I'm not one to drink soju.
Who pops open a beer bottle...
with a spoon?
He joined us from another division...
and doesn't know any better. I'm sorry.
- I should've educated him. - It's all right.
Hey, new recruit.
Many open bottles with spoons,
but people like us who brew and sell liquor...
only open them with bottle openers.
Why? When a spoon is used,
bottles can easily be chipped...
which turns them into scrap.
Hold on a second.
Unbelievable. This one's chipped. Sir?
It is our duty...
to make sure they can be recycled.
To us, 13 cents isn't chump change.
You punk.
Isn't that what Ms. Chae said when you joined the company?
Beom, you're all grown up.
That was years ago.
I'm no longer the youngest member of this team.
I'm an assistant manager now.
Has it been that long already?
Either way, welcome to the world of liquor!
(Brewing Love)
(Grilled tofu, Kongguksu)
You were this big when I first saw you.
Is that the infamous black special ops uniform...
that Ms. Chae wears...
when she goes out to collect payment?
- I can't believe it. - Fetching, right?
- It's killer. - It's pretty.
I heard it was Ms. Chae who had this beer...
rank second in sales in Busan.
She worked her butt off with all the guys here.
Up until six years ago,
all we wanted was for people to try our beer just once.
But that's tougher than you think.
You see, people stick to what they usually drink.
They rarely try a different brand.
We were calling it quits since there wasn't a solution.
However, there was one person who wouldn't give up.
Hello, I'm here to promote Likey.
It's delicious. Please try it.
Thank you.
Yong Ju, this is something we should do together.
She did everything in her power.
Don't just stand there.
Hello, I'm here to promote Likey.
She made it happen one way or another.
This is a hangover relief that pairs well with Likey.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Hello, I'm here to promote Likey.
- Please try it. - We present Likey.
- Goodness. - No way.
We're promoting Likey!
There are no duds.
- There. 2 bottles! - There. 2 bottles!
People only drank liquor sold by Baekmok Liquor,
but that's how Jisang was able to catch up.
Yes!
Sir, my goodness.
- What happened? - Sir.
Yong Ju, you're here.
- You must be busy, so thank you. - Ta-da.
Switch the products to Likey.
- That's right. - This is what the chairman likes.
- All of them. - You won't believe it.
Just do it.
All that's left...
is to rank first in sale.
Mr. Kang, aren't you coming?
Sorry?
- Let's go. - Sure.
- Come on. - Right.
I see you all left your drinks untouched again.
Here you go.
But there's more to the business than just sales.
Bottles must be constantly sold and in bulk...
for the liquor and money to circulate.
Since we couldn't make that happen,
wholesalers started to take the liquor on credit,
not pay us back,
and run.
That gave birth to the legendary Lady in Black.
(Lady in Black at High-speed)
(Special Task Force)
Mad Dog Yong Ju?
It's really her.
Darn.
Take it, okay?
- Okay. - That's when we learned...
how Ms. Chae always delivers...
when dressed in black.
She's hardcore.
Hardcore.
Did you hear about the HQ liquor team?
No.
The chairman is paying the team a visit...
to deliver an order.
The chairman will visit in person?
- Yes. - No way.
Isn't that the same as a four-star visiting a base?
- That gave me goosebumps. - Exactly.
It's the first in ten years.
Last night, the chairman's secretary ordered...
the Planning Team and Marketing Team to prepare a meeting...
which has them on high alert.
That's horrendous.
Both teams will be getting any sleep.
But why is he paying them a visit?
(Naro Beer)
Who is it?
Who is Yoon Min Ju, the brewer of this beer?
(Step 1: Pour milled malt into mash tun)
(Mash tun: A vessel designed...)
(to optimize glucose concentration of barley)
His name is Yoon Min Ju.
He became certified by graduating...
from the Brewmaster course at VLB in Germany.
For four years, he has been running his own brewery...
in Yangjin of South Chungcheong Province.
His hops are grown and his pub downtown is run...
by people in the village he hired.
That's 934g.
In 2021, he first released...
his craft beer "In My Name."
In short, it's called Naro Beer.
The beer is currently only known to people in that region.
Why can't we brew beer like this?
If you can't, have him join us.
Buy the rights to Naro Beer...
or develop a new beer together.
By any means necessary,
have him join us at Jisang.
Yoon Min Ju.
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
An emergency meeting has been called.
Gather in my office.
Wait. Where's Bang Ah Reum?
Well...
You know how she values her lunch hour.
- We'll discuss it first and... - Seriously?
As if we'll come up with anything without her.
Call her.
Have her back at the office.
Yes, sir.
(Bootlicker)
I'm sorry, but I'm still on my lunch break.
Please take a look.
(The one who will always take my side)
Let's begin.
Sure. Ms. Bang Ah Reum.
Section chief at Jisang Liquor's Planning Team.
(Section Chief Bang Ah Reum)
You reside in Hanan-dong...
and own a building, two cars,
and two convenience stores.
The cash you have is...
Is that enough to be Grade A?
We'll get back to you after verifying your identity.
Are there certain things you look for in a husband?
I...
only care about one thing.
That's all I'm looking for.
Which is...
Perfection.
Just that. That's all I want.
(Hwi's Toast)
(It's actually...)
(Chungcheong Province)
(Where there's a will, there is a way.)
Sebastian, shall we embark on our journey again?
All right!
(Hwi's Toast)
(Uilhan Brewery)
Hello?
Isn't anyone here?
Yes, this is it.
What the...
You startled me.
Hello.
You made this, didn't you?
It's nothing weird.
I sell toast sandwiches from my truck,
and I fell in love with your beer after having it at a pub yesterday.
I came across your brewery while on the road, so I dropped by.
I'm not some weirdo.
Okay, fine.
I lied about randomly passing by.
I sought out this place.
Can you give me a job?
You can pay me with your beer.
Are you one to draw lines?
Is that a no?
It's just that I love your beer.
"Maybe working here will get me all the beer I want."
I only came by with that innocent thought in mind.
I can't work here full-time,
but I'll come the second you need me.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Like I said, I'm not a weirdo.
- I know that. - Exactly.
What? You know that? Really?
But even I thought I was being weird.
Why is he so handsome?
Oh, my.
I'm Yoon Min Ju.
I'll call you when I need your help.
Sorry?
Oh, awesome! I never thought this would work out!
You're so cool.
That's my thing!
- Ignore what I said. - No way!
(Uilhan Brewery)
No taking back!
I'm Oh Chan Hwi.
Please, call me later.
Wait.
Can I get an advance for beer?
I just want to send a few bottles...
to my sister who lives in Busan.
Chae Yong Ju!
Why? Did you hurt yourself?
Just a little bit.
You're so careless.
You're a former special force. Don't be such a crybaby.
I didn't.
I'm totally fine. Gosh...
Surely, you got our company's product?
You're a true salesperson to the bone!
Does the company ever acknowledge your loyalty?
Tell them you want a raise!
That's my job. I do what I have to do.
I wouldn't be able to do that.
But at least you look good.
Yes, at least I make ends meet.
- What's that? - I brought you a present.
I was in Chungcheong Province today,
and I found an incredibly-tasting beer.
Did you even buy a glass?
I knew you were sometimes a little crazy.
No, the guy who brews this beer isn't normal.
At first, he drew a strict line between us.
- Here you are. - Oh, my.
By the way, how will you drink it?
- I'll drink it as is. - Wait a second, then.
Here.
(Uilhan Brewery)
Poor into this special glass and then, drink it.
If you drink it without a glass,
you can't fully savor the flavor because it's trapped inside.
I see.
Yes, if that's what you recommend.
By the way, we haven't met before,
but you gave me beer, a glass, and even a job.
Why? How could you possibly trust me?
No particular reasons. You seem to be a good guy.
Oh, I'm touched by your words.
I didn't even give off my charm,
but have you already noticed mine?
I have a keen sense of figuring out people.
Gosh.
He recognized my good personality at once.
Perhaps I was unintentionally giving off my charms.
Shut it before I hit you.
Okay.
Anyway,
he was surely a strange person.
I felt as if he was seeing through me.
Gosh, I can't explain this feeling.
"Man, I already know everything."
That was what his eyes were telling me.
Gosh!
This tastes unbelievably good!
This one should be our company's!
Tell me who made this again!
Brewmaster Yoon Min Ju!
"In My Name, Yoon Min Ju?"
Gosh...
(Naro Beer)
What the heck are you doing from the early morning?
But...
You really drive me crazy.
You'll burn to death under the scorching sun...
if you act the fool like that.
I mean, you may die!
Start working already! Hurry up!
But I'm the boss.
I envy you so much.
No one gives a darn about what you do or don't do.
But I have two jobs, you know?
Time is gold,
so stop fooling around now.
I'm not the one wasting time talking.
What?
He should speak louder if he wants to say something.
Leave him alone.
He wants to say something to you, hoping you won't hear it.
Then, why did he say it?
Anyway,
- it's not my thing. - Me neither.
(A bug)
Gosh.
Block!
That "block" again?
Why is he fussing over such a little bug?
- Right? - Goodness.
No one would share affection with him.
He's actually a poor guy.
What are you talking about?
- He's a boss in the end. - Oh, I see.
Ladies, you are also blocked for five minutes.
- What nonsense! - What rubbish!
Oh, she finally came.
The queen has finally arrived.
- Let me see. - Gosh.
Jjuan is such a blessed girl.
How could one get such a good husband?
You simply can't.
You couldn't find anyone even when you're over 50.
Hello.
I'm late.
Sorry.
Why didn't you get more sleep...
- and come tomorrow instead? - Stop!
Stop fooling around.
My love will literally come tomorrow!
No, forget what I said!
Why are your lips out so long again?
You could even hang clothes on them.
Jjuan!
- You look so bright today. - What?
In what sense?
How can one interpret this face like that?
CEO Yoon, you are...
such a good mind reader!
A mind reader and not a chicken sexer?
Are you kidding me?
Shall we start working now?
This way. Slowly.
Slowly. Relax.
Oh, your legs are so long.
You jumped over it at once.
Now it's time to wear this hat.
Where is my sweet husband who will help me wear my hat?
He left...
for a new life.
Let him be.
Didn't they say they were busy? When will they start working?
Let's have one together. In 1, 2, 3. That's it.
I'm the only one working.
Here it comes.
- Darn. - I will drop it there.
- Let's work together... - Be careful.
It's already 11am.
Let's go for lunch now...
and start again when the sun goes a bit down.
- Whenever the times... - Whenever the times...
- Gosh. - Guys,
we'll have lunch at home.
Enjoy your meals.
Enjoy and eat as much as you want.
Let's go back.
Darn.
(- Let's go and eat lunch. - Ok, let's go.)
(- Enjoy your meal. - See you.)
(Enjoy your meal and see you later.)
Let's go.
They suck all my energy.
Photo.
I love this quietness so much.
Who's it?
(Incoming call)
Hello. This is Bang Ah Reum from the Planning Team...
- of Jisang Liquor. - "Hello."
- Jisang Liquor... - As I couldn't reach you,
I'm leaving you a message.
- We would like to visit you... - Jisang Liquor?
in person to make you a great offer.
- Will you be available? - I'm sorry. My answer is no.
Blocked.
Photo.
Fine. Do whatever you want.
(17th Village Chief of Baegok-ri, Very Nice Man)
Hi, everyone.
Long time no see.
But I see myself every day.
Let's get to work! Come on, let's work.
What do you think you're doing?
Why are you sitting between a husband and a wife?
In our village, public displays of affection are not allowed.
What kind of law is that?
So you can do whatever you want because you're the village chief?
Yes, I can!
And you too, Jjuan.
You must follow our village's policy.
Understood?
What's wrong with you? Is there a funeral today?
Why do you say that? She looks happy today.
- Yes. - Right?
My gosh, I get it. Marrying Kim would be like...
going to a funeral for a beautiful girl like her.
It would be a funeral that never ends.
- What are you talking about? - My gosh.
That's not true! No.
My love, don't listen to him.
Think of him as a barking dog.
Get away from her. Separate!
- Right now! - What?
You're so loud.
How did you learn to say that?
I guess you're trying to be a native English speaker.
What?
I'm no native speaker. Mr. Yoon here is the native speaker.
Didn't you say you went to a beer school abroad?
Was that in Germany? Hello!
Is that so?
Then if you speak any German or whatever they speak over there,
say something in their language. Come on, show us.
What?
Why was he born with a mouth if he's never going to talk?
Let him be.
I bet his mouth didn't want to be born on his face either.
It was just stuck with that face.
His mouth did nothing wrong.
Mr. Yoon.
Be honest. You can hear everything, right?
Yes. I can hear you...
well.
We know that you can hear us.
Why would you wear a headset? You'll just get a heat rash.
My goodness.
It's already 6pm. You all should go home.
- You should all leave. - My gosh.
What's wrong with you? You're always so punctual.
It's like you're a machine.
A machine without a heart!
And it's taking longer for us...
to warm up to a machine. Okay?
What? We finished that in the blink of an eye.
- We finished that. - Yes.
Should we go?
- Shall we? - Let's go.
- Yes. - Yes.
Good work.
- You get that, right? So... - Hey.
- I was on my way to see you. - What?
- You can just tell me. - My gosh.
Goodness. You look good.
Well, I was just...
You know, earlier today, there were other people.
The village chief and the ladies were there.
I didn't get a chance to tell you.
Well, the thing is that we have to...
- You should go. - What?
Weren't you going to tell me...
you guys were traveling to her hometown?
Can you see the future?
No way.
I could tell that she was in a good mood all day today.
She's always happy when it's time to visit her family.
My gosh, I knew it.
You read my wife's mood the best in this village. Seriously.
My mother-in-law's birthday is coming up soon.
But without us,
you'll be short-staffed when there's so much to do here.
What will you do?
It's the busiest time of the year.
My gosh.
Don't worry. I'll take care of it.
My goodness. Thank you.
And here. Have a safe trip.
What? My goodness. Oh, my!
Thank you. We'll use it well.
Here, take it.
Thank you.
Right. Here you go.
Put them in the fridge and share them with the others.
Gosh, don't turn it down. It's fine!
- Gosh, you didn't have to. - Thank you.
We'll get going then.
- Go inside. - I'll see you guys go.
No, go inside.
My gosh.
I'm done with my day now.
Our day isn't over yet!
Our day is just beginning now!
- Let's go! - Yes!
- Cheers! - Let's drink it.
- Yes! - Go!
- Cheers. - Cheers.
One more bottle!
- One more bottle! - One more bottle!
I must go.
You two enjoy it.
- Just one more drink. - Come on, Yong Ju.
- Let's just have 1 more drink. - Just 1 more drink.
This is it for me. Bye.
See you.
Bye!
This is it for me.
She's so cool. She knows when to call it a night.
- Beom. - Yes?
I heard she was single.
Does she live with her parents?
I'm not sure.
I did hear her talk to her grandmother once.
But she never talked about her parents.
I'm sure they're fine.
Grandma.
She must have fallen asleep while waiting for me.
All right.
My gosh.
She didn't have dinner again.
She just had to scoop up some rice to have dinner.
She could've done that.
It's Min Ho's birthday today.
Darn it. I'm always bumping into things.
Hey, don't give me that judgmental stare.
I just have a lot on my mind.
When my mind is preoccupied,
I sometimes can't see these sharp edges.
Okay? Got it?
If you got it, say...
something.
Hey, Min Ho.
Today is my birthday. You're really not coming?
I'm not sure. I'm still thinking.
Come. You have to come.
If you don't come, I'll get upset.
I'm going to get mad at you.
Fine. Okay. I'll be there.
Did you eat?
(Hwi's Toast)
(Brewmaster Yoon Min Ju)
The brewmaster?
Hey, it's the brewmaster! Do you need a part-timer?
Yes. Well,
it's not a job for the brewery.
Do you like cats by any chance?
Cats?
(Hwi's Toast)
Are you sure he wouldn't mind if we just showed up at his brewery?
You said he wouldn't return your calls or texts.
We must do everything we can to contact him.
That way, the management won't blame us.
We need to confirm whether or not he's interested in working with us.
If he's not, it'd be better to end it fast for everyone's sake.
Let's come back before the sun goes down.
Okay.
(Uilhan Brewery)
Hello.
Oh, right.
Let's sit there.
Okay.
He's different from what I had in mind.
I thought he would be sensitive and picky. Right?
So what brings you here?
I've been trying to contact you. I'm Bang Ah Reum...
from the Planning Team of Jisang Liquor.
Bang Ah Reum...
Ah Reum as in "beautiful?"
Sure.
I came all the way here...
to make you a great offer.
Mergers and acquisitions.
This is a great opportunity.
Yes. It's a great opportunity.
I'm sure it will be great if you join us.
Sure. Okay.
I'll tell him to think about it once the owner comes back.
Pardon?
Aren't you Mr. Yoon Min Ju, the CEO?
From what I know, he runs the brewery alone.
Oh, me?
I'm Oh Chan Hwi. It's my first day as his part-timer.
Darn it.
Then where's Mr. Yoon?
(Busan)
(Cheonma)
Please don't do anything. Just wait for me.
(Jisang Liquor)
What's your problem?
Hey, Baekmok. This is our turf.
How dare you cover our poster with yours?
Dear me. I guess you're from Jisang.
You guys are forever ranked second.
What's the point of putting up the posters? It's a waste of paper.
Hurry up!
I'm sorry, sir!
(Hwadon)
One of your guys and a guy from Baekmok...
got into a huge fight over putting up the posters.
Come on. Let me run my restaurant.
I told you many times not to fight here.
Just give me a minute. Hold on.
Have you lost your mind? Who do you think you are?
Do you think you can handle us all by yourself?
I'm not alone.
Where's your team manager?
Gosh, I'm sorry about that.
My guys were so motivated to work. So they must've covered yours.
I'll make sure this never happens again.
Let's wrap this up here.
Hey, bring some drinks.
Please play by the rules in the future.
Sure.
By the way, I hope there is indeed a future.
I'm hearing some bad things about your company.
Excuse me.
Hello. What's this about?
Yong Ju! Our Busan branch is finished!
What?
You know what? I'll make sure...
I see him become the chief of staff no matter what.
You'll make my unfulfilled dream come true, right?
Anyway, a lot of people came.
Can't you be punctual at least?
You're here. It must've been a long drive.
He's your son. Don't be so formal.
I thought this was his birthday party.
But it seems you need these flowers more than him.
You retired a long time ago.
Do you still think you're a two-star general?
How dare you?
Come out.
How dare you glare at your father?
How rude!
Do you still go around and read people's minds?
I can't read people's minds.
I don't have supernatural powers. I'm just sensitive.
Besides, there are a lot of people who are just as sensitive as me.
If this is about the panthers again or whatever, just forget it.
It's empaths!
It means hypersensitive people.
Nonsense.
You're making a big fuss...
for being sensitive like a mental patient.
You're just weak.
Moreover, it's not an illness.
I told you not to treat me like I'm mentally ill.
I've never heard of these hypersensitive people...
called empaths.
Do you know why?
"You're not manly. You're not active."
"You're timid. You won't have any friends."
"You can't even work with other people."
Because of people like you who try...
to mold people's personalities to fit your needs,
many conceal their true selves like sinners.
- Yoon Min Ju! - Everyone is different!
And that's normal.
Why do you always make me...
compare myself to others for being different?
You never change.
You're still as authoritative as ever.
What?
(Ministry of National Defense)
Salute to the commander.
- Salute. - Salute.
Salute.
At ease.
It's okay.
What took you so long?
I'm sorry.
Do you want to get out of here?
Let's go.
There.
Mr. Nam. Say that again.
It's as I said on the phone.
The head office will shut down our Busan branch...
and merge it with another South Gyeongsang branch.
I think they'll let go all our boys too.
What should I do?
Why so suddenly?
The business is struggling, they say.
On top of that, there's this beer called Naro Beer,
and the chairman himself wants to sell that brand.
To carry out that order,
the only option is to shut down the Busan branch.
What the...
You know...
You know the madness we've been through.
Baekmok Liquor had full control of Busan.
Despite that, we worked together,
and got this far after six years of crazy hard work.
Shutting down...
They'll shut us down?
Give me a little more time.
We can overtake Baekmok Liquor.
I can do it, Mr. Nam.
I begged and pleaded already.
The people high up decided already.
They cut us off.
What the heck...
Do you remember this spot?
I liked...
what you said to me that day.
I got the money Mr. Choi owed us.
Why do you work so hard?
To get promoted?
Shouldn't I work hard at my own job?
Yong Ju.
You really...
did so well.
No. I can't give up like this.
I must do everything I can.
- Doesn't this look fun? Shall we? - Yes.
I'm sorry about earlier.
One corn dog, please.
- Here you go. - Thanks.
Doesn't it look good?
Yes.
- Nice. - Gosh.
- I want to play. - Okay.
Go ahead.
Let go.
- Hey. - Hooray.
Well done.
(Whac-A-Mole)
What are you? You're huge.
(Play to win!)
You like teddy bears?
No. A man doesn't like teddy bears.
I just noticed how big it was.
You can't fool me.
- You're wrong. - I'm right.
Min Ho. It's okay to like them.
What's wrong with liking teddy bears?
Don't worry about what Dad thinks.
You can like whatever you like.
Okay?
Shall I win that for you?
Isn't he the best big brother ever?
If you want to win one of the big ones,
you must score over 700 points in one go.
That's not too easy.
- Over 700 points? - Yes.
Min Ho.
That doesn't sound easy.
I really wanted it as a birthday present.
Can you refill the magazine?
Sure.
Hi, kiddo.
You want that bear?
Oh, sorry.
Don't you want that as a birthday present?
I want it.
You want it? Then you must have it.
I really need to shoot something right now.
Shall we?
On top of that, there's this beer called Naro,
The chairman himself wants to sell that brand.
To carry out that order,
the only option is to shut down the Busan branch.
Where did I hear that name?
In My Name.
Yoon Min Ju...
What are you doing?
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
You're not fine.
You're...
not fine.
(Brewing Love)
Win over Brewmaster Yoon Min Ju.
I swear to get Yoon Min Ju.
I'm Bang Ah Reum from Jisang Liquor's Planning Team.
I'll reject whoever comes.
I'll block you, Ms. Chae.
You'll block me?
Stop her. Do whatever it takes.
Chae Yong Ju.
CEO Yoon's tough to get, isn't he?
He's hard to get every single day.
I'm unblocking your block.
Unblock me!