[theme music playing]
LOVE NEXT DOOR
Hey.
Stop right there.
Hey!
[Seok-ryu breathing heavily]
[mellow music playing]
What you said earlier…
what did you mean?
[man] Seok-ryu.
Hyeon-jun?
What are you doing here?
I got on a plane to see you.
I've missed you.
What are you doing?
Can't you see I'm talking with her?
I know you.
You're Choi Seung-hyo, right?
Seok-ryu's childhood friend.
I think you know me too.
It's nice to meet you. I'm Song Hyeon-jun.
I can't say the same.
We're not on greeting terms either.
Oh, is that so?
Why did you even show up here?
And why now of all times?
Why, what was going on?
I don't think I need to
give you an answer.
Let's go, Seok-ryu.
-Hey.
-I have something to say.
A lot too.
[Geun-sik] What do you think you're doing?
-Sir. Ma'am.
-What the hell are you doing?
How dare you come here?
Let go.
Let go of me.
Mi-suk, don't try to stop me.
Even if it kills me,
I'm going to destroy this bastard tonight!
[Mi-suk] I won't stop you.
But you can't do it here.
One neighborhood commotion is enough.
[breath trembling]
You bastard… [sighs]
[exhales deeply]
[Mi-suk] Are you coming home
from work, Seung-hyo?
Yeah.
Well done.
I'm sure you're tired. Go on home.
And Seok-ryu, you come home.
You too, Hyeon-jun.
[Seok-ryu] Mom,
why would you invite him home?
This is between us.
I'll take care of it.
It's a family matter. There should be
etiquette in relationships too.
You two called things off
without our consent!
Is marriage a game?
Enough talking. You two come with me.
[exhales]
[smacks lips]
-[Mi-suk] Do you want more food?
-[Hyeon-jun] Yes, please.
-[Geun-sik exhales]
-Why is Mom so calm?
Why is she being so generous?
She's possessed by a ghost
who can't let people starve.
Jeez, do I need to call a shaman?
Then, what about my brother-in-law?
Was he always this shameless?
-Brother-in-law? Don't call him that.
-[grunts]
I thought he was just trying
to be friendly then.
Was it two years ago?
He came to our house for vacation
because Seok-ryu was busy.
Oh, right.
He gave me a bunch
of pocket money back then.
Shut your mouth.
[Mi-suk] Do you want more soup?
Yes, I'd appreciate it.
[Geun-sik scoffs] My goodness.
He doesn't know when to refuse, does he?
That little punk.
Goodness.
-Dad, where are you going?
-[Geun-sik] The rooftop.
I can't stand being
in the same room as that bastard!
Just give him everything!
Just eat until you explode!
[door closes]
-Yeah, eat up.
-Thank you.
[quirky music playing]
My head hurts.
[exhales]
[Seung-hyo scoffs]
Hey, why aren't you going in?
Aren't you here to see Seok-ryu?
Forget it.
There's an unwelcome guest inside.
Unwelcome guest? Who?
Seok-ryu's ex-fiancé.
What?
Is this bastard high?
How dare he appear in front of Seok-ryu?
I'll kill him.
Don't do anything.
Why? We have to kill that jerk.
I want to kill him more.
[Mi-suk sighs]
Did you get enough to eat?
Yes, it was delicious. Thank you.
That's good.
I feel like I've done my duty,
so I'll say what's on my mind now.
Mom, why are you talking like that?
Are you shooting a historical drama?
From what I hear,
Seok-ryu cheated on you. Is that true?
Excuse me?
No, of course not…
Unless you did?
[sighs]
Then…
did you cheat?
No, I didn't.
But it was my fault.
I take full responsibility
for breaking off our engagement.
-[sighs]
-You little punk!
[Seok-ryu] Dad, don't!
Hyeon-jun, that's enough.
It's not like that, Mom.
[exhales]
I had a feeling my daughter
wouldn't have done that.
Still, I wanted to ask to make sure.
If it were true, I wanted to apologize.
But since that's not the case…
You bastard.
Come get this beating.
-Wait, honey.
-[Seok-ryu] Mom!
-Mi-suk!
-Mom! I said it wasn't his fault.
You can't hit people with this!
You'll kill him!
Fine. I'll kill this bastard
and go to jail.
Hey, you bastard!
How dare you break my daughter's heart?
How dare you?
-I told you I can't go to jail with you!
-Mom, please!
Hyeon-jun, let's go.
I've seen this before.
It's totally déjà vu.
This is so immersive!
-[Seok-ryu] Come on.
-Hit me until you feel better!
That's why I came here.
-You're going to die.
-Good.
You think I won't?
Mom! Jeez!
-Mom, stop!
-[Geun-sik] Not too much!
Wow! This woman's so strong!
[Seok-ryu] Come on. I said let's go!
Come on.
Ma'am, I'm sorry.
You punk! I can't let that bastard
leave in one piece!
I'll come back again, sir.
Don't come ever come back, you bastard!
If I ever see you here again,
I'll knock your head off, you prick!
My son works out, punk!
[groans]
This burning sense of justice
is rising from my core.
Beer's not enough to cool it.
Want another one?
Let's go and cause a scene instead.
I'll cover the costs.
Whatever.
You won't even pay for the beer.
You said you wanted to
kill him even more.
I was just saying.
-Who am I to do that?
-What?
What do you mean?
You're the son of Seok-ryu's mom's friend.
You've been her best friend
since childhood.
Exactly.
-We're just friends.
-Hey!
Being friends is an incredible thing.
One definition of a friend says it's one
who carries my sorrows on their back.
How cool is that?
What if I get involved
and dig up more of her sorrows?
-I don't even know how she feels.
-[Mo-eum scoffs]
You're so frustrating.
How much longer will you keep this up?
When I think of all the time
you've wasted already,
you could've dug
until you reached the Earth's core.
[mellow music playing]
Mo-eum, did you…
That's right. I saw the time capsule.
Hey. You should've buried just the letter.
If you hide your feelings in there too,
how would anyone know?
-Look.
-[Seung-hyo clears throat]
You're the only one who's suffering.
You didn't tell her, did you?
Are you insane?
Seung-hyo, you have to
save yourself from unrequited love.
Even I can't rescue you.
-[sighs]
-[Mo-eum] But…
I will root for you.
[slurps]
I'm off.
[grunts]
Darn, I should've teased him
about it some more.
[chuckles softly]
[smacks lips]
[slurps]
[crushes can]
LOVE IS ALL ABOUT TIMING
[lounge music playing in the background]
Why did you come?
Did you come to be beaten to death
by my parents?
No, I came to live.
I came because I wanted to
breathe, eat, and sleep again.
-[sighs]
-[Hyeon-jun] Without you,
I can't do those basic things.
I can't live.
That's not because of me.
It wasn't because we were special either.
It would've been the same with anyone.
We dated for years.
-It's an obvious feeling.
-Don't say that.
No matter how much you hate me,
don't say it as if we were nothing.
-Seok-ryu…
-[Seok-ryu exhales]
I came to get you back.
I still love you.
Hyeon-jun, it's over between us.
It's not love you feel anymore.
It's just a habit.
A bad habit you've yet to fix.
Don't come back here. Please.
I'm sleeping over. Give me some clothes.
[Mo-eum] What?
My goodness.
-Did you run away from home?
-Probably.
I bet it was interesting to see
Hyeon-jun inside your house.
How did you know?
I ran into Seung-hyo.
-You did? Where?
-In front of your house.
He was pacing back and forth,
like a dog that needed to pee.
[Jae-suk] Mo-eum! Come here.
Jeez, why now? In a bit!
[Jae-suk] Hey, my carpal tunnel
or whatever is hurting my wrist,
-so I can't open this jar of jam!
-Jeez.
Hold on! Hey, give me a second.
I need to help my mom.
-I'll be right back.
-[Seok-ryu] Sure.
[Mo-eum] Mom, I told you
if you eat that at night,
your blood sugar will spike!
[footsteps descending]
[inhales, exhales]
Are you asleep?
No.
[Mo-eum] Okay.
Are you sleepy?
[chuckles]
No, say what you want to say.
How does it feel to see Hyeon-jun again?
[scoffs]
Took you long enough.
I mean,
I just remembered
what we talked about last time.
Don't eat until I get back. Wait for me.
Don't you dare lay a finger.
[mellow music playing]
[Mo-eum] Hey.
You still love him?
-Your ex?
-That's half-right and half-wrong.
What does that mean?
I loved the time we spent together.
Everything he gave me.
I still love that.
But for some relationships,
I know it's better to end them.
So I'm doing my best to forget him.
And he needs to do the same.
Has there been
any changes in your feelings since then?
Nope. I'm much more calmer
than I thought I'd be.
Even when I was getting on
the flight for Korea,
just the thought of seeing him again
made my heart feel like it would burst.
[exhales] Okay.
Well then, I guess there's no need
for me to get involved, right?
[Seok-ryu] What?
I mean,
if you wanted,
I was going to beat him up for you.
I would've waited right behind you.
As long as I don't kill him, it'd be fine.
[chuckles] Hey, isn't it illegal
to aid and abet in assault?
[chuckles]
Look, a true hero
can put aside their lifetime job
in the name of friendship.
Forget it. [chuckles]
Just worry about your civil service job.
Your wish is my command.
[inhales]
All right. To ensure the safety
of our citizens tomorrow,
I shall proceed to sleep.
Good night.
Don't fight for world peace
in your dreams and get some rest.
[chuckling] Okay, I'll try.
Goodness.
Still, I'm relieved.
It seems your feelings have dulled a bit.
The feelings for your ex.
[mellow music playing]
[Seung-hyo sighs]
BAE SEOK-RYU
CHOISSEUNG
[birds chirping]
[Geun-sik] Honey?
Honey, it's time for breakfast.
You want me to kill you this early?
You expect me to make breakfast?
No, come and eat.
Why did you make
tteokbokki for breakfast?
Spicy food is the perfect remedy
for stress.
Experience the privilege of being the wife
of a tteokbokki shop owner. [chuckles]
Yeah, it's better to have
my stomach hurt than my heart.
By the way, did Seok-ryu come home?
I think she's in her room.
Speaking of which,
do you think she was trying to protect him
by taking him out like that?
What are you saying?
He was about to get knocked out,
so she took him out of the ring
before you could land a haymaker.
In any case… [chuckles]
…it's as if you were Mike Tyson
or Manny Pacquiao.
You went wild on him. [chuckles]
You did great.
It made me feel better
to see you hit that punk like that.
God.
Maybe I shouldn't have hit him though.
-[Geun-sik] What?
-You know.
You think he came here to get hit?
-He must still have feelings for her.
-What are you trying to say?
I know it's late, but if they want to,
I'd be okay if they got back together.
Her life will return to normal
if she goes back to the US with him.
You think that makes any sense?
Come on, why not?
A person's feelings
aren't always logical or consistent.
No!
What are you… Absolutely not!
That punk hurt Seok-ryu. I hate him.
And I don't want her to go to the US!
I mean… I don't want it either…
I'll give you some fish cake broth.
-It'll be refreshing.
-[phone vibrating]
[clicks tongue]
KOREAN FOOD CRAFTSMAN
PRACTICAL SKILLS
JIJIM NUREUMJEOK
Choisseung didn't even get taste this.
[Mi-suk] Seok-ryu!
-Mom, please knock.
-Where are you going?
I have plans.
You're going out dressed like that?
Yeah. Why?
Get changed. Wear something else.
Why? I don't want to.
Don't embarrass me
in front of our neighbors!
You always walk around
in worn-out T-shirts and flip-flops.
They can tell you're unemployed
from a mile away.
-Because I am.
-[Mi-suk] You little brat!
You want me to wear a dress then?
This is nice. A dress.
Who'd wear this around the neighborhood?
You. Look at those bags under your eyes.
And why are your lips so pale?
-Did you even wash your face?
-Seriously?
[Mi-suk] Look at me.
You look so lifeless.
Are you aging now?
Put some makeup on.
-[Seok-ryu] What's with you?
-Add a little blush too.
Apply some red lipstick.
What's suddenly gotten into her?
Who goes to class dressed like this?
You look pretty today.
[quirky music playing]
[chuckles softly]
I'LL BE THERE SOON
I HAVE SOMETHING TO SAY
You need rocks to smack
into each other to see if sparks will fly.
I guess Mom had an ulterior motive.
[Hyeon-jun] What?
It's nothing.
What brings you here?
I clearly told you not to come back.
I told you I came back for you.
[door opens]
So we meet again.
[sighs softly]
Come on. Get on.
-What?
-Aren't you going to class?
You'll be late.
That's right.
Seok-ryu.
Grab on tight.
[pop song playing]
What's with the bike?
The Earth is sick.
It's an environmentally-friendly approach
for an architect who's concerned
about the climate crisis
and carbon neutrality.
Also, the extra weight
makes for a good workout.
You told me to get on.
What's with the dress?
It doesn't suit you.
-And what did you do to your cheeks?
-Hey.
If you're talking about my blush,
it's Peach Fuzz,
and it's this year's color of the year.
As if you knew!
Goodness, I guess
you were expecting to run into him
since you're dressed up like this.
That's not true!
This was my mom's doing.
I'm not going to eat
her side dishes anymore.
I can't hear you. What was that?
I said you look ugly.
I couldn't hear you again.
Can you repeat that?
You look ugly-- [exclaims]
Hey! That's dangerous. We could crash!
Then, stop messing around!
Jeez, what a lunatic.
[song continues playing]
-Last night--
-About last night--
-Go ahead.
-No, you first.
No, you go.
[gulps]
What did he say last night?
What?
He wouldn't have come here
from the US because he was bored.
He must have come for a reason.
Don't tell me…
-Does he want to get back together?
-What?
Well…
Well, so…
I must be right.
What? Did you start to waver
after hearing that?
[sighs softly]
I don't blame you.
It must've felt nice again
to see him after so long.
Hey, is that the only way you can talk?
It's true.
It's not like you two were just dating.
You were engaged.
Seung-hyo!
Still,
how could you be swayed by that?
Don't you have any self-respect?
Stop the bike.
-I said stop!
-Damn it.
[grunts]
-[quirky music playing]
-[sighs]
You said stop.
Jerk.
[Seung-hyo exclaims]
Hey.
[groans softly]
[sighs]
[slicing]
What is it? Did I do something wrong?
[chuckling] No.
You look full of energy today.
-You can do it.
-I can do it.
[door closes]
-Hey, Seung-hyo. Want some coffee?
-Should I make some for you?
[Seung-hyo] We have the
Misom project meeting this afternoon.
We'll review
the Jeseon-dong coffee shop plans too.
And we need to start preparing
for Greip's flagship store,
so get ready.
Na-yun, is that white mark on his back
a ghost or something?
-It's foundation.
-[Myeong-u] What?
-[door closes]
-Shade 21.
No. Shade 19?
Makeup? Seung-hyo must've had
a passionate morning!
It was intense enough
to leave a mark of a hug on his back!
-Those facial features look familiar.
-[Myeong-u] What?
Who is it? No way. Was it Tae-hui?
Were you two talking about me?
[Myeong-u] Yeah. I mean, no.
-What?
-It's not her.
It's not? Then, who is it?
It's obvious.
-Jeez.
-Who is it?
-What's wrong?
-What? Well…
It's not you.
-Me?
-[Myeong-u] No.
Hey, who is it?
What was that? [chuckles softly]
TEMPERATURE OF TIME - ONGGI KETTLE
What are you doing?
I gave you some Botox
so you'd stop scowling.
I must've been too focused.
You sure that's all?
And not scowling about something else?
Stop trying to find out.
You caught me.
But didn't we agree to make a coffee pot?
It says "kettle" here.
Yeah, I changed it.
I've spoken with the person in charge too.
You didn't even tell me.
But why change it?
There's no romance
if things heat up too quickly.
Turn on the heat
and carefully bring the water to a boil.
I believe in the importance
of taking time.
Like an onggi?
Like love.
[Tae-hui] In my twenties,
I hoped too much
for things to heat up quickly.
But now, I want to focus
on warm and subtle things.
Slowly and for a long time.
You've changed a lot.
It's because of you.
No, it's thanks to you.
Stop being scared.
I won't ask you to take responsibility.
Let's just wait and see.
I'll follow my heart.
You follow yours.
And Seok-ryu will follow hers.
Why would you suddenly bring her up?
It's so easy to get you worked up.
Where did my cool, calm ex-boyfriend go?
You turn into a teenage boy
at the sound of Seok-ryu's name.
It's not that.
-You keep going off-topic, so--
-You're trying way too hard.
This is cute too though.
[exhales]
[smacks lips]
[indistinct chatter]
[amusing music playing]
[Dan-ho] Yeon-du!
Dad.
Did you take the afternoon off again?
Yeah. You had a mild fever this morning.
Let's go home early and rest.
Unbelievable.
What will your company think of me
if you keep acting like this?
What?
They'll think of me as a weak child
who's prone to crying for her dad.
Yeon-du, having days off
is an employee's fundamental right.
Did you forget
I'm a social affairs reporter?
If they treat me unfairly over this,
I don't care who they are.
I'll confront them.
Dad.
Just keep your job until I go to college.
Okay.
Wait for me.
Goodbye. [exclaims]
[sighs]
Why am I the one
who always loses games and pays for lunch?
Hold on. Are they rigging them
behind my back?
That's mine.
-[engine accelerating]
-[horn honking]
[tires screeching]
[horns honking]
[man] Are they drunk?
What?
[dramatic music playing]
Just a moment!
Sir?
Cardiac arrest.
-Someone call 119!
-I'll do it!
[line ringing]
Hello? I'm at the intersection
near Hyereung Kindergarten.
A car just ran into a streetlight.
Do you have a hammer?
Yes, but I think the driver's unconscious.
Yes, I understand.
Please move!
[grunts]
Sir.
Sir?
[seatbelt unlocks]
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten,
eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen,
fifteen, sixteen, seventeen, eighteen.
[captivating music playing]
-[man grunting weakly]
-[Mo-eum exhales]
Are you okay? Don't get up.
Stay down.
I know it's uncomfortable,
but let's turn to your side.
Okay.
It'll be okay.
[Mo-eum breathing heavily]
[breathing heavily]
[exhales]
[amusing music playing]
Jae-suk! What are you looking for?
-My sunglasses.
-[In-suk] What?
I had them on just a second ago.
-Goodness. Hands on your head.
-[In-suk laughing]
-My goodness. I don't believe it.
-[laughing]
Hey, it wasn't right under my nose.
It was right on my head!
Jeez, is it my age?
Why am I so forgetful these days?
Don't get me started.
I needed to go to the post office
to send a package yesterday.
I put my shoes on and left
but forgot the box.
-Goodness. That's so sad.
-What's wrong with you?
I can't trust myself anymore.
I can't even remember words when talking.
I called the washer a vacuum
and the vacuum a fridge.
And I call Dong-jin Seok-ryu.
Hey, this gastrodia root extract
is supposed to be a gift from the heavens.
They say it contains neurotransmitters,
so it improves blood flow
and helps prevent dementia.
-Really?
-Try it.
-Give me one.
-Another extract?
Don't rely on these things.
Open it for me.
-Open it for you? Okay.
-Yeah.
Get in the habit of writing notes
if you're worried about dementia.
-[In-suk] Notes? Okay. Here.
-[Hye-suk] Read books and newspapers too.
You still haven't fixed that habit?
-[Hye-suk] What?
-What?
You can't go a day without showing off.
That bad habit.
-Hey.
-[In-suk] What's with you?
You two are the closest
but are so harsh when you argue.
Yeah, Mi-suk.
You're irritated
because Seok-ryu's fiancé's here.
Don't be sensitive
and take it out on us…
Where did you hear that?
-Dong-jin. I went to the gym this morning.
-[In-suk gasps]
I'm going to kill that punk!
Damn it.
-[Jae-suk] Hey!
-Can't keep a secret in this town.
I heard he was begging to get her back!
And why wouldn't he?
-She's so beautiful!
-That's right.
Seok-ryu looks just like you
when you were young!
She does take after me.
Yeah, Mi-suk was so popular
in high school.
-[Jae-suk] That's right.
-You remember too, right?
I don't know. I don't remember.
What?
Right. That's how you were back then.
-[Jae-suk] Yeah.
-Mi-suk was so pretty.
-Hey.
-So pretty.
[Jae-suk] She's popular like her mom.
The apple doesn't fall far from the tree.
Don't take him back
no matter how much he begs!
-He's a despicable bastard!
-[In-suk] Right.
He's not that bad.
Yes, he is! He disgraced her
with a canceled engagement!
That's right!
Crushing him into a pulp
wouldn't be enough punishment.
Hey, what do you mean,
"crush him into a pulp"?
My son-in-law's not some herb extract!
You're all so crude!
-Forget this!
-[Jae-suk] Hey!
-That's not what I meant, Mi-suk.
-[Hye-suk] My gosh.
-What on earth were we supposed to say?
-[Jae-suk] I swear.
She's in menopause.
-Mood swings.
-[Hye-suk] We all are.
-[Jae-suk] This is so hard.
-Pomegranate juice is good for that.
-Open that for me.
-Wait just a second. Mi-suk!
She's not going to get over it.
-Stop drinking that.
-Just leave her.
[Hyeon-jun] Seok-ryu.
Wait…
[exclaiming in pain]
Hyeon-jun, what's wrong?
Are you okay? Did you hurt yourself?
-[whinces]
-[Seok-ryu] Are you okay?
I got you.
-My acting's improved a lot, hasn't it?
-What on earth are you doing?
I'm sorry.
You wouldn't have turned around otherwise.
Seok-ryu,
I messed up back then.
I know I wasn't good enough.
I should've tried harder
to be more understanding.
No, you didn't do anything wrong.
I know you did your best.
I was too overwhelmed.
I only thought about myself.
You had no other choice--
I'll get going.
Let's get something to eat.
If it's for the last time,
I'm fine with that. Just once.
Let's grab a meal together.
Dan-ho?
Yeon-du!
She said she had something to give you.
-What?
-[Dan-ho] Go ahead.
Stoop down a little.
Like this?
[chuckles softly]
-[pleasant music playing]
-[exclaims]
Does it sting?
No, it doesn't sting at all.
It feels so warm.
It shouldn't feel warm.
That means bacteria got in it.
-Just a second.
-[Mo-eum] Okay.
[Yeon-du] There.
Wow, Yeon-du.
I'll get better in no time
because of your ointment.
Thank you.
-You know what?
-What?
You were so cool today!
Even though you didn't have webs
coming out of your hands,
you were way cooler than Spider-Man.
[Mo-eum] Really?
Hearing that gives me so much strength.
Thank you.
Come with us if you're getting off work.
We'll give you a ride.
What do you think? Should I come?
Let's go.
[chuckles]
Are you feeling hot?
Yeon-du has a cold,
so I can't turn on the AC right now.
Yeah, I'm fine.
But it looks like you're hot.
A little bit.
-Do you mind if I take off my jacket?
-Sure, you don't have to ask.
-[exhales]
-[engine accelerating]
I think Yeon-du has completely fallen
for you today.
At last! I finally did it.
I'm not taking this off tonight.
Do you get hurt often like that?
It's not often. Just sometimes.
Because all sorts of incidents happen.
Don't you get scared?
Like what happened earlier?
No way. None of that scares me.
Other things scare me.
"What if I can't save the patient?"
"What if I'm too late
and can't do anything?"
You're so brave. I admire you.
You're glorifying me
because of what I said.
It's true though.
When I saw you, I realized
we don't have to look far for heroes.
They're close to us.
I was just doing my job.
Oh.
But I did meet a real hero once.
-Really?
-Yes.
-Who was it?
-Well…
Once, we were rushing
a child to the hospital.
-Right.
-At that time, the roads were blocked.
We couldn't move forward at all.
That's when someone got out of his car,
and he directed traffic to clear the road.
There was like a superhero.
It felt like I had met
the man of my dreams.
I don't know who he is,
but I call him Mudflat Man.
Mudflat Man?
Yes, he had the funniest T-shirt on.
It said, "I love you, mudflats."
[tires screech]
-[Mo-eum grunts]
-[amusing music playing]
Are you okay?
-[Dan-ho] I'm sorry.
-Did the lights…
I LOVE YOU, MUDFLATS
[Dan-ho groans]
Dan-ho, where did you get this shirt?
Well, the thing is…
while I was covering a story,
I met an environmental group called
the Mudflat Guardians who gave one to me.
Mudflat Guardians?
[Dan-ho] Yes.
Holy cow.
So you might know him then.
Who else is in that group?
I don't know.
They're mostly older men and women.
[Mo-eum] Not them. I mean, young guys.
So I didn't see his face,
but he seemed to be about our age.
I think he was as tall…
as you…
[horn honking]
[exhales]
Good night!
[Dan-ho] Wait…
What? Why are you following me?
Well, I had something to give you.
Just a moment.
So…
[groans softly]
[Mo-eum] Seriously?
Why do you have
so many medical supplies in your bag?
They're all for you.
The pharmacy said
you need different medications
for each healing stage.
This one prevents infection.
This prevents scabs from forming.
This one's for scars.
Please don't get hurt again.
I have to go park my car.
[breath trembles]
[Mo-eum breathing heavily]
[panting]
Mudflat Man was the reporter.
-[exhales]
-[heart thumping]
What?
Why is my heart pounding?
What is it, a drum or something?
[exclaims]
[dramatic whoosh]
PERFECT MATCH
I knew it.
Those pale, squashed facial features.
I'm sure it's Seok-ryu.
I knew this would happen!
I was worried about her from the start.
Damn it!
[machine beeping]
-[machine beeping]
-[Na-yun exclaiming]
[amusing music playing]
-What are you doing?
-Miss.
You are not a cheetah.
Of course, you're not a puma
or a jaguar either.
What are you talking about?
You should run at a speed
that's appropriate for humans.
I didn't sign up for a personal trainer.
I'm in the middle of my own workout,
so can you go away?
You're making me uncomfortable.
[machine beeping]
You'll break the equipment
and yourself at this rate.
-Don't worry about it. Leave me alone.
-[machine beeping]
[machine beeping]
[Na-yun] Hey, come on.
What do I do?
I can't allow that.
What on earth are you doing?
-[machine beeping]
-[groans]
This is perfect for you.
You can run straight
to the Serengeti at this speed.
-What's wrong with you?
-Eyes on the road!
Okay, go.
[both breathing heavily]
[Dong-jin] Look, zebras!
[indistinct chatter on TV]
I'm watching my show.
Why do you have to stand
in front of the TV?
Today wasn't a coincidence, was it?
[groans softly]
Hyeon-jun came here,
and you suddenly had me dress up.
Gosh, I applied lotion,
but why are my heels so cracked?
Look at this. You're changing the subject.
I can clearly see
what you're trying to do.
Don't do this anymore.
It won't change anything.
This won't do.
Let's go to the sauna tomorrow.
-No, I'm not going.
-Why not? It's nice.
We can soak in hot water and exfoliate.
Right.
Hasn't it been years since you exfoliated?
-Gross. I can't associate with you.
-Body scrubs can handle that, okay?
What's so great
about scrubbing your flesh off?
Above all,
I hate getting in the water with others.
-Why?
-It's uncomfortable.
Why would you sit around naked
with other strangers?
Who cares? We're all women.
Also, you're my daughter.
Isn't it nice to go with your mother?
Maybe when I was younger,
but we're independent
and separate entities now.
You still have that kind
of outdated fantasy?
Yeah, I'm old-fashioned and from the '80s.
You're modern and sophisticated.
Good for you, you brat.
How sophisticated of you.
Must be nice.
-[door opens, closes]
-[scoffs] Jeez.
-[door closes]
-[dog barks distantly]
-Why are you walking around late at night?
-Is that a dog I hear barking?
Don't you watch the news?
The world's a scary place.
Did someone turn on the local station?
It's making
the whole neighborhood noisy. Jeez.
Forget it. Fine, do whatever you want.
[cats meowing in the distance]
[suspenseful music playing]
[footsteps approaching]
[suspenseful music building up]
[suspenseful music fades]
You crazy bastard! You scared me!
-Quiet! This is a residential area.
-That's not what's important!
Why the hell did you follow me
and scare me like that?
Why did you suddenly run like that?
Because I thought someone was chasing me.
You could've called my name.
Well, you could've looked back.
Why were you only looking straight?
You should've called out and reassured me.
You should've checked first
before blindly running.
[exhales]
Jeez.
I think this is our problem.
We pass things off on each other,
make excuses, and shift the blame.
We don't say what we need to say,
so we go around in circles
and end up fighting,
like last time.
[breathing heavily]
What I wanted to say…
wasn't that.
I wanted to answer you.
That day,
you asked me what I meant.
Stop driving me crazy!
Back then and now, you keep doing this…
so I feel like…
I'm going to lose my mind because of you!
-What I meant was…
-Don't.
Look,
right now… [exhales]
…I have a bunch of error messages
popped up in my head.
It's overloaded and has stopped working,
so I can't perform any new tasks.
So, later.
Tell me later.
-Later when?
-Just later.
Things are pretty complicated
for me right now.
Because of Hyeon-jun?
No, it's not because of that.
There's just a lot of other things.
[smacks lips]
[inhales]
Yeah, okay.
I'll hold off on answering you.
I'll postpone it
until your error messages are gone.
I'll wait until things
aren't complicated for you anymore.
-Seung-hyo, I--
-[Seung-hyo] Later.
You say it later too.
But let me ask you one thing.
Are you going to keep seeing that jerk?
No, I don't plan on it.
You mean it?
All right, then.
[mellow music playing]
I think we've done plenty
of walking and running now.
Let's go home.
Okay.
[clears throat]
[Seung-hyo] Go on ahead.
I'll definitely be behind you this time,
so you don't have to look back.
Don't be scared.
[music continues playing]
[Hye-suk inhales]
[groans softly]
Mmm.
[phone chimes]
MY BIRTHDAY
TODAY
[amusing music playing]
-Where are you going?
-It's an emergency.
There was a 17-car pileup this morning.
Is that so?
Then, when do you get home--
[door closes]
[knock on door]
Seung-hyo?
He must've left early.
I'll be there soon. I'm almost there.
What's wrong?
Why did you call me at dawn…
[Tae-hui] I wanted you
to be the first to see it.
It's our first sample.
You told me to come
for something big. This was it?
This is something big.
It came out beautifully.
It does look nice.
The body is round like an onggi.
The spout is like the eaves
of a traditional roof.
You wanted to preserve
the subtle curves of Korean design.
Isn't it nice?
Isn't it similar to your sketches?
I told you it was nice.
Are you longing for praise these days?
No.
I only long for praise from you.
I'm starved for it.
Let's keep things professional.
Do you usually get a lot
of broken jars like that?
[Tae-hui] Oh, those?
Of course.
-And it's not due to a lack of skill?
-[Tae-hui scoffs]
Look here, Mr. Architect.
Do things always go according to plan
on site just because you design them?
A wise answer to a dumb question.
No matter how carefully I shape the clay,
no one knows
how it'll come out from the fire.
Will it become a perfectly formed vessel?
Or will it crack and shatter to pieces?
You won't know
until it goes into the kiln.
[mellow music playing]
That sounded
like such a great quote. Right?
Not only am I beautiful
and make onggi well but I'm also eloquent.
You're so great at praising yourself
that you don't need my help.
I said I'm still starved for it.
Let's get something good to eat in Seoul.
I'll go and change.
-[Hye-suk] Hello.
-Hello, Ambassador.
Is the vice minister inside?
We're having lunch.
I'm sorry, but the minister
called for him today, so he's gone.
Goodness. He did tell me to let you know.
It's going to take a while,
so he asked for a rain check on lunch.
Is that so? Okay.
Have a nice day, ma'am.
-You too.
-Thank you.
[Hye-suk] What are you all doing tonight?
LAVENDER
[exclaims]
Please don't get hurt again.
[heart thumping]
What's going on?
Why is my heart thumping?
Are you kidding me?
Why is it beating faster?
Why did it skip a beat this time?
[Min-ho] Why are you
grumbling to yourself?
-I thought you were with someone.
-No, it's nothing.
[Jeong-u] Ms. Jung,
why is your face so red?
-It's red?
-[Jeong-u] Yeah.
-[Min-ho] Do you have a fever?
-No.
Are you sure your cut isn't infected?
No, it's not that.
I've applied an excessive amount
of ointment.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
[pop song playing in the background]
CONDITIONS IN THE FIELD FOR PARAMEDICS
ASSAULTS ON EMTS RISE
What are you looking at so seriously?
Yeong-in, did you know
almost 14% of firefighters suffer
from PTSD, depression,
and sleep disorders?
I'm sure they do.
Their job exposes them to a higher risk
of danger than the general public.
There are about 300 cases of assault
on paramedics each year.
Most offenders avoid punishment
because they were drunk.
Dan-ho, you've suddenly become
very interested in firefighters.
Oh.
There's a paramedic I know.
I've seen her be treated badly before.
I've also seen her risk her life
to rescue others too.
So you're going to write an article?
What?
Give it your best, okay?
Good luck!
We might cover a story,
but we can't truly understand it
without firsthand experience.
It really becomes your story
after you go through it yourself.
I didn't know being a working mom
would be this hard.
-I got a call from the school today.
-Yeong-in, I just thought of a new story!
Can you excuse me… I mean, I have to go.
[chuckles softly]
I don't know what it is,
but the spark in his eyes is back.
[Tae-hui] This place is really good.
The food's clean and the view's nice.
Oh?
[groans softly]
-Hello.
Seok-ryu, we came to eat too.
Fancy running into you here.
I know.
[Tae-hui] It's nice to see you.
But since we each have company,
I think it'll be uncomfortable
for us to sit here.
Would you like a new table?
-Yes.
-No, it's fine. We'll sit over there.
-Let's just sit.
-Yeah, sure.
[inhales]
[mellow music playing]
How is it? Is the food okay?
Yeah, it's fine.
I'm glad. I put some effort into this.
It's been a while since our last date.
I've been curious about something.
What is that?
It's the japchae I made.
I've been taking cooking classes.
When it comes to cooking,
you're good enough to start an academy.
I'm studying
for a Korean Food Craftsman certification.
I want to do it professionally.
Really? That's great.
But are cooking classes enough?
How about going to cooking school?
The CIA is nice.
They have a campus in California.
[Seok-ryu] I don't know.
Tuition wouldn't be cheap.
I haven't thought that far ahead yet.
[Hyeon-jun] You can take your time.
But can I try your japchae?
[Seok-ryu] What? I don't think you can eat
food from the outside here.
Excuse me?
I have a favor to ask.
Someone very special to me made this food.
I know it might be against the rules,
but can I open it and just try a little?
We normally don't allow that,
so please make it quick.
Thank you.
Your boyfriend is very romantic.
[exhales]
[slurps]
[exclaims]
This is so good.
This is the best japchae I've ever tasted.
[exclaims]
Want me to get you a new knife?
No. [clears throat]
The steak's a little tough.
Fresco wants to see us next week.
Do you have time?
-Even if I didn't, I'll make time.
-Right.
Remember Hye-won
from when we signed the contract?
She asked about our relationship.
So I said you were my ex-boyfriend,
but we still like each other.
Why would you make things up like that?
She looked interested in you,
so I made a preemptive move.
Correct that before the next meeting.
And don't lie like that ever again.
Liars are who I hate
the most in this world.
Not keeping a promise
is a type of lie too.
What?
Like secretly meeting someone
they said they wouldn't.
[coughing]
[amusing music playing]
Are you okay?
-[Seok-ryu coughing]
-[Hyeon-jun] Drink some water.
You should chew your food thoroughly.
I'm fine.
It just went down the wrong pipe.
People might think it's a big deal.
-[clears throat]
-[Hyeon-jun] It's a big deal to me.
Even the smallest things bother me.
And I want to take care of you.
It's just like before,
and it still hasn't changed.
I have to go to the restroom.
[Hyeon-jun] Okay.
Didn't you say you wouldn't see him?
What's it to you?
-And you're one to talk.
-Are you talking about Tae-hui?
-You know we're doing a project together.
-Right.
You came to eat at a hotel for work.
You're a great businessman.
And you? You're eating with someone
you have no business with.
[Tae-hui] There you are, Seok-ryu.
I wanted to say bye.
[Seok-ryu] To me?
[Tae-hui] I got some wine
to go while paying.
This is yours.
No, thank you. I don't drink wine.
It's fine.
Then, give it to your boyfriend.
He's not my boyfriend.
Oh. Sorry about that.
Anyone could've mistaken him
for your boyfriend.
Then, I'll take it.
-[elevator dings]
-[door opens]
Let's go.
I knew this would be fun,
but I didn't expect it to be so thrilling.
-What does that mean?
-A "love square" is a first for me.
That man seemed close to Seok-ryu.
I'm sorry about earlier.
You couldn't eat properly because of me.
It wasn't pleasant.
The man in front of me had his eyes
at the back of his head.
Every fiber of his being
was focused on someone else.
Still, I'll accept your apology.
Because that will make me look cooler.
Again, I'm sorry.
-[phone vibrating]
-[scoffs]
Just a second.
Choi Seung-hyo speaking.
I felt strange today.
The japchae you made tasted good.
We sat across from each other
and shared a meal.
So it felt like old times.
I'll treat you something
even better next time.
Hyeon-jun?
There is no next time.
It was just this once.
That's why I agreed to come.
[clicks tongue]
Then, let's say this was
the last time we eat steak.
Next time,
how about pasta for the last time?
Then, doenjang stew for the last time
and kimchi stew for the last time.
[Seok-ryu] Hyeon-jun.
Don't be like this.
Let's not do this.
Seok-ryu.
Can you drop me off
at the nearest station?
[phone chiming]
LAVENDER
JAE-SUK, IN-SUK
-[phone chiming]
-[scoffs]
Everyone's so quick to respond.
Did they finally figure out
what day it is today?
[phone chiming]
[Jae-suk] Emergency!
I ordered frozen crabs
and had them sent to my office.
But I forgot and left to see someone.
They're all going to spoil.
Can someone put them in their fridge?
[In-suk] Goodness, I can't help!
I'm so sorry.
I'm eating out with my family.
[Mi-suk] I have plans too, so I can't go.
If Hye-suk's off work, can't she go?
Seriously?
[amusing music playing]
These little brats.
Is melting ice more important
than your friend's birthday?
[sighs]
[exhales]
I'll go.
[music ends]
[keys jingling]
HYEREUNG REALTY
Why would they asked me to do this?
[grunts]
Why is this so heavy? Jeez.
Goodness.
Damn it!
-[party popper pops]
-[Hye-suk screams]
[all laughing]
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
[Hye-suk] Hey, what's going on?
You brats!
You scared me!
♪ Happy birthday, dear Hye-suk ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Hey! Blow out your candles!
Make a wish before you do!
I bad-mouthed all of you so much.
I'm sorry.
[all cheering]
Surprise!
You were so surprised, weren't you?
I really wanted to try this!
I'd only seen it on TV.
It's my first time!
It's childish. I tried to stop her.
You don't like…
I guess she does like it.
She loves this stuff.
Goodness, who knew we'd live
to see the day when Hye-suk cried?
I know.
Hey, Ice Princess.
It only took 60 years,
but your heart's finally warmed.
It's because there were too many candles.
Who would cluelessly put all of these in?
We didn't go with Korean age,
so we took one out.
Really?
[phone chimes]
[gasps]
-What?
-Who is it?
It's Seung-hyo.
[Seung-hyo] Happy birthday, Mom.
I left early,
so I didn't get a chance to say.
[Mi-suk] Must be nice.
-It is nice. I love it.
-[Jae-suk] What about your husband?
-Did he prepare anything?
-Hey, birthdays are no big deal.
He left early for an emergency
this morning.
Yeah, he's a busy man.
-Let's cut the cake!
-[Jae-suk] Yeah, let's taste it.
Is that green tea frosting?
No, it's mugwort.
Jeez, I'm so sick of it!
[In-suk] We're no longer the Suk Sisters!
Why bring that up again?
[Mi-suk] Hey,
mugwort is good for your health.
-Bring some plates, Jae-suk.
-[Jae-suk] Okay, are there forks?
-[Mi-suk] No, we need some.
-Bring everything.
[indistinct chatter]
[pleasant music playing]
Do you have any lily of the valley?
Hello.
Do you have lily of the valleys?
I need lily of the valleys.
[phone vibrating]
[Hye-suk] Thank you, my son.
[Seung-hyo] Oh? Ms. Yu!
How did you know I was here?
The other teachers told me.
They said an unrealistically
handsome young man was at the pool.
I thought it was a water spirit,
so I came.
[both chuckle]
Congratulations on winning
the design contest.
Thank you.
I was surprised to get the call.
What do you mean?
It went to the rightful winner.
This place is special to you.
It is.
Oh, did you tell Seok-ryu too?
-No, not yet.
-Hurry and tell her. She'll love it.
She won't remember.
Of course, she will.
She called to ask if the results
were out a few days ago.
[pleasant music playing]
Hi, Ms. Yu. It's Seok-ryu.
Are the results
for Choisseung's contest out yet?
Not yet?
Okay. I'm sorry to keep calling you.
[groans softly]
Are they out now?
MINISTRY OF EDUCATION
ANNOUNCEMENTS
What's taking so long?
Hello!
Are the results of Hyereung High's
gym remodeling and design contest out yet?
Yes, Hyereung High School.
Not yet?
Okay, thank you.
[Jin-ae] I think she thought
I'd find out sooner.
She's asked me several times.
[exhales audibly]
[exhilarating music playing]
I'll get going now.
Have some alone time with the pool.
You have to create a new future.
Make sure it's a nice goodbye
to the past.
Seung-hyo, good luck!
-[chuckles softly]
-[Jin-ae chuckles] Bye!
[Tae-hui] No matter
how carefully I shape the clay,
no one knows
how it'll come out from the fire.
Will it become a perfectly formed vessel?
Or will it crack and shatter to pieces?
You won't know
until it goes in the kiln.
Seung-hyo,
you have to save yourself
from unrequited love.
Even I can't rescue you.
[Dan-ho] There once was an athlete
in the 200-meter event
whose weakness was
being slow off the blocks.
But despite this, he overcame it
through his tireless efforts.
Even if it's a bit late,
I'd tell him to muster up the courage,
just like the swimmer did.
[phone vibrating]
CHOISSEUNG
[Seok-ryu] What?
-Where are you right now?
-[Seok-ryu] Why do you care?
Where are you?
I'm at my dad's shop. I'm practicing.
Wait right there. I'm on my way now.
[pleasant music playing]
[Hye-suk] What's this? [chuckles]
Why did you come here?
[dramatic whoosh]
[dramatic music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[mellow music playing]
[Seung-hyo] Looking back, I had plenty
of chances to tell her how I felt.
-[Geun-sik] Smile!
-Honey, me too!
-[Geun-sik] Get out of there!
-Okay
-Take it! Smile!
-Okay! One, two, three!
[camera shutter clicks]
-[Geun-sik] Okay, now!
-Get out for a second.
[Seok-ryu] Let's take one together.
Take one of us!
[Geun-sik] Okay! One, two, three.
Seung-hyo, take one with Seok-ryu.
-[Seok-ryu] Yeah.
-No, it's fine.
-Just take it. Come here.
-[Geun-sik] Hurry up.
Here we go!
One, two, three!
[camera shutter clicks]
[Seung-hyo] The day we graduated
high school and finally became adults.
God.
I can't stand to look.
-Where are you going dressed like that?
-A date.
It's a group date with PE majors.
I hear they're really handsome.
[Seung-hyo] The day
the ice cream was sweet
and cherry blossoms flew in spring
when we were immature 20-year-olds.
Where are you going?
The US. I found it.
I got into UC Berkkeley.
On a full ride too! Isn't it awesome?
Remember my friend, So-yun?
She applied,
so I just put in an application too.
But look!
I got in.
They say you follow friends to Gangnam,
but I'm following mine to the US.
Honestly, I thought
my mom would be against it.
But she told me to go.
[coughing]
[Seok-ryu] But I'm
actually a little excited.
This will be my first time overseas.
And it'll be my first time on a plane.
I've never even been to Jeju.
But my first trip is to the US!
Isn't this amazing?
That late night at the tent bar
when she said she was going to the US.
And…
-tonight.
-[doorbell chiming]
-Seok-ryu.
-Hey, right now…
Hear me out first. [panting]
I won't delay it any longer.
I said I'd wait until later,
but that was an excuse I made
to pretend to be considerate.
I lied to myself.
It was out of fear. I was scared.
So…
The thing is…
I'm going to say it this time.
When I said you were driving me crazy…
When I said I was losing my mind
because of you…
What I meant by that was…
I…
like you.
[mellow music playing]
LOVE IS ALL ABOUT TIMING
ALREADY LOVE
[pop song playing]
LOVE NEXT DOOR
How do I face her tomorrow?
She's not asleep. No.
If you've drawn the knife,
you should cut something.
-Why aren't you in a T-shirt today?
-I washed them.
[Mi-suk] You wore perfume too?
Does that mean your answer
has no expiration date?
Seung-hyo might not know,
but I think I liked him first.
[Dan-ho] I want to clear up
any misunderstandings about me.
Not just anyone can survive
the social affairs department.
I've changed my strategy.
The "lasts" didn't work,
so I'm going back to the beginning.
[Seung-hyo] The reason why I can't stay
as Seok-ryu's friend
isn't because she's a woman.
It's because she's Seok-ryu.
Subtitle translation by: Sue Mounce