You took a leave?
[Episode 2 The Familiar Stranger]
That's new.
Just admit you skipped class.
What's with all the excuses?
You've got a month of school service,
starting this week.
Instructor.
The dean is looking for you.
Okay.
Stop looking.
Wait till I'm back.
The instructor's gone.
Why are you still squatting?
I'm sorry.
I thought you were ditching too,
so I took you with me.
What's done is done.
One, four, two, eight, five, seven.
One, four, two...
What are you mumbling about?
None of your business.
Hello.
I'm Chen Haowei from Class 2.
I didn't ask who you are.
Also,
can you stop smiling?
Okay.
You don't have to wear it that low.
You can pull it up a bit,
to your shoulder.
Let me help you.
Isn't that better?
[Wishing Upon the Shooting Stars]
It's too heavy.
Come and help me!
Chen Haowei!
Coming.
Excuse me, I need to come through.
Move it in.
Chen Haowei.
Dad.
Is he the little assistant you hired?
Young man.
Who are you calling Dad?
Is this your friend?
I thought he was a tenant.
Why are you pretending not to know me?
I really don't know you.
Did you stay here last night?
Where else am I supposed to sleep?
Haowei,
go see if he has checked in.
Are you done?
Is it fun to mess with your son?
Are you kidding me?
How can I not recognize my own son?
Right.
You don't like me anyway.
I embarrass you. I make you look bad.
That's why you refuse to acknowledge me.
Fine.
There's no record
of any other guest checking in.
Did you hear that?
You're not registered.
You're not staying here.
You're not my guest.
Or did you come here to steal?
You guys are boring.
What's there even to steal?
You watch your mouth.
What do you mean "what's there to steal?"
You don't sleep here.
I don't know you.
Why don't you get out?
-You're trespassing.
-Where am I supposed to go?
-Where should I go?
-I don't know you.
Please leave.
-You're trespassing.
-What?
I haven't eaten yet.
-Get out, or I'll call the police.
-Stop pushing me!
-Get out.
-Stop pushing!
Fine, I won't.
Alright!
I'll go!
Haowei.
I'll check
if there's anything missing inside.
You take the things out of the car.
Li Wanzhe.
One bowl. Fill it up.
What's up?
Are you fighting with your dad again?
He's acting all crazy this morning!
He pretended not to know me,
and threatened
to call the cops on me for stealing!
How childish.
He asked me who I was.
Who am I?
If I'm not... then who am I?
What are you doing?
Li Wanzhe.
Say my name.
He Xiangyong.
I can't say my name!
Why?
He Xiangyong, He Xiangyong,
He Xiangyong, He Xiangyong.
Stop acting.
I'm serious!
I can't say my name!
How is that possible?
He Xiangyong, He Xiangyong, He Xiangyong.
I can't say it!
Mom.
Say his name.
How would I know his name?
Isn't he your new friend?
You don't know him?
Who?
You don't know him either?
No.
Even the Village Chief doesn't know him.
How are we supposed to?
He's He Xiangyong!
That's not what He Xiangyong looks like.
Stop joking.
He is He Xiangyong.
Is today April Fool's Day?
No, it's not April Fool's Day today.
Do I look different?
No, you are you.
You look exactly the same.
That's weird.
I know. Give me your phone.
They don't recognize me.
But I can still log in and send messages,
right?
Why is there no internet?
No way. I paid the bill yesterday.
[Li Wanzhe]
See?
No service.
Did you do something yesterday?
Or did you eat something weird?
Yesterday...
Wasn't there a banquet thing yesterday?
Yeah.
After that, we went to Haitai.
After Haitai, I went back.
Uncle Hua made me garlic shrimp vermicelli.
That's it!
Yes! It was Uncle Hua!
He drugged you
with the garlic shrimp vermicelli!
Li Wanzhe.
Don't be an idiot right now, okay?
I don't have time to mess with you.
It's true!
The beach at night is the most dangerous.
Hong.
You pop up like a ghost
and scare us every time.
Ghosts don't scare people.
Other things do.
What do you mean?
Did you go to the beach last night?
Yes.
It's dangerous!
And something weird will to happen.
Hong.
Do you know him?
Shooting stars are the prettiest!
I love shooting stars.
But
there are no shooting stars
in the daytime.
No, I'm...
Shooting stars?
The shooting star!
Didn't you make a wish yesterday?
You said you wanted to wake up in a world
where no one knows who you are.
You said
you don't want to be He Xiangyong anymore.
I wish
I don't have to be He Xiangyong anymore!
-I'm kidding.
-Let's jump.
No!
-I'll jump!
-Forget He Xiangyong!
-Then I can start over!
-He Xiangyong, I...
I'm just kidding!
No way.
I wasn't even serious about the wish!
Besides,
you said it yourself yesterday.
We've made so many wishes
since we were kids,
but none of them have ever come true.
Do you have a better explanation?
Fine.
Let's say it's true.
Then how come my wish came true,
but yours didn't?
You made a wish too, didn't you?
Look.
Out with the old, in with the new.
Same goes for bags,
same goes for jobs.
Why are you so hard on yourself?
Compared to me, you're pretty amazing,
you know?
Sometimes I'm kind of jealous of you.
Why jealous of me?
You can get up whenever you want,
and go to work whenever you want.
And you don't have to face toxic relationships.
Your family's ice shop
is literally five minutes away.
I feel like
my life's lacking some excitement.
I asked you to jump into the sea,
and you said no.
Not that kind of excitement.
What kind then?
Well...
I want to fall in love.
I want to fall in love!
Then go for it.
I want something passionate and intense.
I don't get it.
Are you an idiot?
I mean,
I want that kind of happiness.
The kind
that makes a moment feel like eternity.
Like fireworks.
Maybe
the shooting star really liked you.
That's why it didn't affect me.
That's ridiculous.
Listen.
In this world,
there are so many things
that don't make sense.
You just have to face them,
and accept them.
Just accept it.
No...
Besides,
you don't want to live as He Xiangyong,
do you?
So just take this opportunity
as a rebirth.
From now on, you are free!
You're no longer the He Xiangyong
who kept disappointing everyone.
Are you serious?
Then say it.
He Xiangyong, He Xiangyong, He Xiangyong.
See?
It's God's will.
Fine.
Then what?
Where do I sleep tonight?
Your home.
My...
Didn't I just tell you
my dad's going to call the cops on me?
Listen,
you leave it to me.
I'll see you at your place in two hours.
I'll take care of it.
Li Wanzhe.
Li Wan...
I'll be waiting.
Li Wanzhe!
This is ridiculous.
Haowei.
Come down here.
What's wrong?
Go find the young man from this morning.
Why all of a sudden?
I know he seems weird,
but I keep feeling bad for him.
Are you sure?
I also think he needs help.
Go find him.
But I haven't finished hanging up the wetsuits.
I'll do it. You go.
Even you are against me!
I finally found you.
Our guesthouse is not expensive.
I'll give it to you later.
Have we met before?
No,
we haven't.
You're just walking and walking.
Where are you going?
It's none of your business.
What are you even doing here?
Stop following me, okay?
Here.
There's water, medicine,
and slippers.
Just take care of your wound, okay?
Otherwise it'll get infected,
and you'll feel the pain.
Here.
Do you know why the sea is blue?
Because the fish in the sea
make sounds like "blue blue blue."
That's boring.
Why did you say
you're the boss's son this morning?
I made it up.
How do you even make up things like that?
What about me?
How do you know my name?
Thank you for the medicine, water,
and slippers.
I'll pay you back later,
with the money for the stay.
Did something happen to you?
Are you in trouble?
Are you always this curious about strangers?
Judging from your attitude this morning,
I don't think you're a stranger.
Fine.
Let me tell you.
It's just a misunderstanding.
No need to take it seriously.
It doesn't matter who I am.
A stranger is just a stranger.
Okay?
Thank you.
If you're really going through something,
we won't give you a hard time.
Look.
The boss looks scary,
but he's actually very easy to talk to.
What time is it now?
What?
10:20. What's wrong?
The helmet.
You changed your mind?
We really haven't met before?
Here we go.
Chen Haowei, are you sure you can do it?
It's your fault.
You took way too long talking to the teacher.
Come on.
It's called bonding.
Watch out for other people.
Look.
Just focus on riding.
Nailed it.
Don't you think
the weather is really nice today?
Yes, I do.
-I can't catch up with my boat.
-I'm going to speed up.
Pretty steady, right?
I almost fell.
Do you know that my hands are for drawing?
Okay.
Too fast.
Isn't it steady?
It's not like the boat is going to fly.
Why are you riding so fast?
It's about to leave.
Okay, I'll be faster.
I'll be faster.
Be careful.
We're almost there.
It's okay.
You can stop here.
I gotta go. My boat is coming.
Let me know when you're back.
I'll come get you.
No need.
You don't have to come all the way
to pick me up.
Who says I'm coming all the way
to pick you up?
I just wanted to get some shaved ice up ahead,
so I figured I'd pick you up on my way.
Up ahead?
That's a restaurant.
Doesn't matter. Go catch your boat.
Alright.
Be careful when you ride.
Okay.
Bye.
Mr. He, let me go over it one more time.
Anyway, they were college classmates.
And they were in the same dorm.
One on the top bunk,
one on the bottom bunk.
Whenever I went over,
we'd all hang out together.
That's how it is.
So you know him too.
I know him pretty well.
Mr. He, I brought him back.
Come, come.
Mr. He.
Let me introduce.
This
is me and Xiangyong's best friend from college.
He's Xiaoyou.
Yesterday was a misunderstanding.
He's not a thief.
He was in a bad mood yesterday,
so he went to the beach to clear his head.
But he lost track of time
and went back too late,
so no one noticed him.
Yes.
That's right.
You came back with He Xiangyong?
Yes.
Where is he then?
I want to know that too.
Where do you live? And what do you do?
How come
I've never heard He Xiangyong mention you?
Mr. He, didn't I just explain this?
Fine.
I'll tell you one last time.
Listen carefully.
Anyway,
when Xiaoyou was doing work exchange abroad,
all of his money were scammed.
After he came back,
his luggage was stolen,
and all his documents were gone,
which made him too scared to go home.
But don't let this fool you.
He's actually amazing.
He once worked at a cliffside guesthouse
a thousand meters above sea level.
And he was a helper at an ice hotel
where it is minus thirty degrees.
He Xiangyong brought him to work here
because he values his abilities.
Yes.
Everything Li Wanzhe said
is true.
Since you were his classmate,
why didn't you say so this morning?
Instead, you said you were my son.
Yeah.
Didn't you just...
I'm sorry.
Yes,
I know it's hard to believe.
But sometimes
I can get too immersed in things,
and end up in a really strange,
really weird state.
Besides, I had just woken up this morning.
I had a nightmare,
and he was gone.
So I just
panicked,
and said something out of line.
I hope you don't mind.
Besides,
He just came back from abroad.
It's,
it's not easy
to adjust to the environment here right away.
Besides,
with everything that's happened,
how could he even talk about it?
And Mr. He,
let me tell you.
He...
His dad is hard to deal with too.
He must have been so messed up this morning
that he mistook you for his dad.
Are you saying that I'm hard to deal with?
No.
He Xiangyong is so weird.
He brought his friend back,
and then disappeared himself.
But it's not bad to let Xiaoyou stay here.
Look.
If you have anything to say to Xiangyong,
just tell Xiaoyou.
If Xiaoyou hears anything from Xiangyong,
he'll let you know.
Two birds with one stone.
Why are you so chatty today?
Wanzhe says you want to do work exchange.
Yes.
Your son said the guesthouse needs help.
I...
I think I'm quite good at this kind of thing.
So I'd like to give it a try.
Haowei.
Take him to check in.
He can take the other bed in your room.
Then show him around the guesthouse
and let him know the work.
I don't know what you guys are up to,
but please tell He Xiangyong to come home fast.
Come with me.
You got this!
Genius.
Genius!
This is the front desk of our guesthouse.
The fishing gear is left out again.
-Come here.
-The newspapers are not put away either.
-I'll show you how to check in guests.
-The phone is left around. Seriously?
What are you doing?
Don't touch the boss's stuff.
Isn't the fishing gear
supposed to be in the storage room?
We sleep upstairs, right?
Give them to me.
Those are the boss's fishing tools.
He'll get mad if you put them around.
Well...
The bathroom is on the left.
-And...
-The kitchen is on the right.
I can see that.
Our guest rooms are in the back.
-We have four-person rooms and six-person rooms.
-Excuse me.
Let me show you.
This is our rooftop,
where we dry our clothes.
The light bulb's burnt out
and no one changes it.
This is also my favorite place
in the guesthouse.
[Zhong Xiaoyou]
Li Wanzhe!
What?
How's it going? Are you alright?
No!
Why not?
These are the old clothes
I don't wear anymore.
Just make do with them for now.
What about now?
I asked my mom
about my grandma's aunt's uncle.
He made a wish on a shooting star too.
And it came true! He made a lot of money!
Can you ask him?
Are you an idiot?
That was over a hundred years ago!
How am I supposed to ask him?
I'm not a psychic!
Then what should I do now?
Just stay here.
I'll figure something out.
How long will it take?
If you're bored,
go to the rooftop and wish on a shooting star!
Wait, is it really the shooting star?
The moon works too!
Li Wanzhe!
Call me if you need anything!
I don't have a phone...
Thank you.
Come again.
Be careful on the stairs.
Okay, thank you.
Bye.
-Hello, auntie.
-Hama-chan.
Well...
Have you eaten?
Yes, I have.
Do you want some shaved ice?
I'm good.
Thank you.
Okay.
I'm sorry,
but we're closing.
Auntie,
is Wanzhe back yet?
Wanzhe?
Li Wanzhe
is hanging out with his new friend today.
He keeps coming and going.
In and out.
I have no idea where he is.
And honestly,
I don't know when he'll be back.
So... sorry about that.
It's okay.
Auntie.
Let me help you.
No, no, it's okay.
I got it.
It's fine, really.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Hama-chan is smiling.
Just leave them there.
I'll wash them.
Okay.
That stupid Li Wanzhe.
He didn't even wash them
before giving them to me.
One day, the farmer said to his cow,
"You need to milk yourself today."
And the cow said...
Just get to the point.
You don't need to tell a joke.
Is this really your first time here?
You seem really familiar with this place.
Of course it is.
The reason I'm familiar with it
is that it's my friend's house.
He told me about it.
It's normal.
But,
you don't feel like his classmate to me.
When Mr. He was talking to you today,
you looked really nervous.
Are you suspecting me now?
I'm sorry.
But yes, I am.
Fine.
If that's the case,
can I suspect you too?
Suspect me of what?
Does the boss know
you were his son's high school classmate?
Don't be surprised.
He and I are very close.
I know everything about him
and everyone in his life.
How else do you think I know your name?
Did he ever mention me?
Of course.
What did he say?
You really want to know?
Go on, tell me.
He said
you're the last person he wants to remember.
It better be true.
Take it or leave it.
[Mr. Chen: When are you coming back to work?
You're just gonna leave everything behind? Just lose all Mr. Lin's money and disappear?]
How's business today?
Not bad.
Are there many guests?
Same as always.
A bunch of tourists.
Your mom said
you were out with a friend all day.
Who is he?
He Xiangyong.
He Xiangyong?
But your mom said it's a new friend.
I haven't finished yet.
I mean
He Xiangyong's college classmate,
Xiaoyou.
Are you close to him?
Yes.
How long have you known each other?
For a long time.
You've never mentioned him.
Well,
I just don't talk about him much.
You're weird.
Why are you asking so many questions today?
Because...
Because I don't want you to go out
with someone I don't know.
What?
You're crowding me!
It's hot!
I'll turn it down.
Hot?
You can take your clothes off.
I don't mind.
I just remembered,
last time,
Village Chief Wang said there was some...
some...
there was some seafood stew left.
I'm worried Dudu might steal it.
I'll go... Dudu!
Come here!
Dudu.
This smell...
It's my habit.
A quick spray helps me relax.
That's your habit.
Not mine.
If you want to relax,
just enjoy the wind and sea breeze.
Why do you need to spray that stuff?
So weird.
I'm reading!
I'm going to bed!
Did He Xiangyong say anything else to you?
What do you want him to say about you?
I'm just asking.
So he really tells you everything?
Yes.
Because I'm his most important friend.
And I know him best.
I don't think so.
If you really are that close to him,
why didn't he ever mention you to Mr. He?
You were his high school classmate.
Why are you hiding it?
You're the one being weird.
Since we don't trust each other,
let's keep our distance from now on.
We stay away from each other's business.
Great.
That's exactly what I wanted.
Okay!
Just look on the bright side.
How often does a wish come true?
If I were you, I would borrow some money
and renovate the guesthouse.
-Expand it, redo the decor.
-Li Wanzhe.
Stop saying things like that, okay?
It's not that simple.
My head is about to explode.
And now there's Chen Haowei to deal with.
How come nothing happened to you?
I told you.
You're the one the shooting star chose.
So wishes have no effect on me.
How is that possible?
Li Wanzhe!
Can you come down here for a second?
Why are you here so early today?
Come on up. Let's chat.
Just come down for a second.
No.
It's too far and I'm lazy.
Hurry up.
I like you.
My name is Hamaguchi Soumi.
My birthday is January 10, 1998.
I'm a Capricorn.
My blood type is AB.
I love plums.
And I hate mushrooms.
Why is he introducing himself?
My dream is to travel around the world.
The place I really want to go is Antarctica.
To the whole world,
you're just someone.
But,
to someone,
you are the whole world!
Li Wanzhe,
you are my whole world!
I've liked you for a long time!
Please go out with me!
I think I ate too much watermelon.
My stomach hurts.
I need to go to the bathroom.
Wow, your joke is so funny.
Your Chinese has improved a lot,
Hamaguchi Soumi.
Keep it up.
Keep going.
You got this.
I'm not joking!
It's funny.
I'm serious!
I'm serious too. It's very funny.
[Epilogue]
Thank you.
I told you,
you didn't have to come to pick me up.
Who said I came to pick you up?
I came for the shaved ice.
It's a twenty-minute ride from the pier.
Twenty minutes?
Didn't I just make it here in fifteen?
I'm a driving god.
From now on, just call me Driving God.
What's wrong?
Are you wearing perfume?
Yes.
Why all of a sudden?
Nothing. I just think
this smell makes me feel relaxed.
Do you want to smell it?
I'm good.
Are you sure?
But,
I'm interested in your shaved ice.
-Shaved Ice?
-Let me share it with you.
You have it.
Take mine.
-I didn't say I wanted it. I didn't.
-I want to trade with you.
Don't mix them together.
I'm not.
-You're taking the mung beans again.
-Just one bite.
I want to try it.
I want to see
if this shop is better
than the one my friend's family runs.
Your friend's family has a shaved ice shop?
Yes.
It has the best shaved ice on the island.
I'll go next time.
And I'll judge myself.
Okay.
Their fenguo
is the best in the world.
No, I think
this mung bean milk one
is way better than yours.
Way better than yours.
The mung bean milk one is super delicious.
Fenguo is the most delicious in the world.
Didn't you want to trade with me?
I was just curious.
So you're the manga artist
[Next episode]
that Xiangyong is in charge of?
Didn't you say you wanted to fall in love?
Now love is here.
Why are you freaking out?
I really like you.
That's impossible.
I tell myself
one, four, two, eight, five, seven.
Why these numbers?
Have you dated He Xiangyong before?