QUEEN OF TEARS
Stop.
I recognize that truck.
I did find it odd
when my grandfather suddenly wanted
to change the ventilators
and told us to leave.
That's the day I saw that truck.
So you think that truck
carried his secret fund?
If I'm right,
wouldn't the money be at home?
EPISODE 12
You shouldn't get wet.
Wait here while I bring the car over.
You have arrived at your destination.
Hae-in.
Hyun-woo.
That was quick.
Why are you out here?
Get up.
I was a bit dizzy.
I'm hungry too.
Let's have something tasty
before we go home.
Sure.
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
Should we call the police?
-Wait.
-We should.
You were attacked
by three men last time too.
You're…
Eun-sung.
What? Do you recognize me now?
What a shame.
How could I…
Exactly. How could you mistake me
for Hyun-woo?
Hae-in!
Open the door.
And if I do?
What will you tell him?
-What?
-Are you going to tell him?
That you got in my car
after mistaking me for him?
He'll be shocked.
Wouldn't it be better if you said
we were going somewhere?
Hae-in.
Open the door.
Open it.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Then I'm relieved.
I thought something happened to you.
Let's go.
I ran into Eun-sung earlier.
And he invited me back home.
You know I've wanted to see Grandfather.
I'll be back.
I understand.
Let me go with you.
I'm sorry,
but I only invited her.
Don't worry.
Just pick me up later.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Surprise.
How did you find me?
What's wrong?
-Aren't you glad to see me?
-I mean, I was going to call.
I see.
Jeez, I had no idea.
So I thought of killing you
once I tracked you down.
Geon-u.
Is this him?
Jeez, he looks better in photos.
Hey, Dong-u.
Say, "Daddy."
-His name is Geon-u.
-Hey.
I named my son Dong-u, so that's his name.
Anyway, it must've been tough
to live with a dense idiot.
Soo-cheol will be arrested soon.
-Why?
-I did some illegal deeds
as a finance director.
I planned it out
so that he'd take the blame.
I tipped off a prosecutor
before leaving Korea.
-You didn't have to do that--
-Hey.
I did it all for you.
What if he wants revenge
and comes looking for you?
God, he's noisy. Hey!
Do that in the bathroom.
The person you dialed is unavailable.
MY SON, HYUN-WOO
Hyun-woo and Hae-in aren't picking up.
Are they spending the night in Seoul?
That's better than driving back
at this hour.
Honey, don't you think
-we're being too liberal?
-What do you mean?
Forget about Hae-in.
Hyun-woo didn't even go abroad to study.
Don't you think he's too open-minded?
What's the issue?
They're not strangers.
Divorced couples
are more distant than strangers.
-Is this right?
-This isn't your first rodeo.
What did you say when you heard
Hyun-woo was marrying into that family?
"Is this right?"
And when he decided to divorce?
And when he first brought
his in-laws to stay here,
didn't you say the same thing?
I did.
"Is this right? Is this wrong?"
There's no point in worrying.
Life will take its course.
-Let them be.
-You're right.
Honey, have you seen his eyes lately?
There's no turning back for him now.
No one can stop him.
Then stop it already.
-What?
-Stop calling him.
Okay.
MISSED CALLS
FATHER
What? What's going on?
Hey.
-You're up.
-What have you done to me?
What is this?
God, you're noisy. Go back to sleep, okay?
I'll light up a briquette
to keep you warm while you sleep.
Why are we here?
-I want to see my Grandfather.
-You're wet and cold. Get changed first.
And let's eat.
That's not why I'm here.
That's why I brought you here.
Get changed and eat with me.
Then you can see him.
-Is the steak almost ready?
-Yes, sir. I made yuzu salad.
It's her favorite.
Good. I'll pick the wine.
As for the plate…
This one.
-Okay.
-And for the wine…
Use this.
MR. PYEON
-What is it?
-I got rid of Mr. Baek.
-Are you sure?
-Yes. What should I do now?
Don't call me and lie low for now.
-The money and the plane ticket?
-You'll get it.
But they'll suspect us
if we meet or I pay you now.
Wait until I call you.
POWER OFF
Put some more flowers.
Yes, sir.
How does it feel to be back home?
It doesn't feel like home.
This is your favorite wine.
-Right?
-No thanks.
Are you sure?
The steak is good. Try it.
I don't have an appetite.
You said you were hungry.
I was,
but not anymore.
Let's go now.
Go where?
Give me some time.
-For what?
-So I can clear up the misunderstanding.
What misunderstanding?
You said
that I pushed you
into a ditch only to save you.
But that's not true.
Do you recognize this?
What's that?
It belonged to you a long time ago.
Why do you have it?
Don't tell me…
-That was you?
-It was.
Was that when we first met?
No, it was before that.
Before?
When?
You were the one who saved me?
Yes, I was the one who saved you
from drowning that day.
What are you doing?
I couldn't sleep,
so I was looking at some old albums.
Can I join you?
Of course. Please sit.
Goodness, is this Hyun-woo?
Yes.
Gosh, he was always handsome.
He was. Not everyone knew his name,
but they all knew the cute son
of the pear tree house.
You're blessed
with a handsome and smart son.
Yes. He's good at boxing and swimming too.
Right. Look here.
He even went to
a children's Marine Corps Camp.
He once even saved a kid from drowning.
What is it?
I think
I recognize this beach.
Why were you there?
To see my mother.
That's when I saw you drowning.
-Really?
-Yes.
It was me who met you
and developed feelings for you first.
I didn't know.
You should've told me.
My mother abandoned me
at an orphanage to keep her secret.
So I couldn't say anything.
-It must've been hard.
-It was. So…
eat with me.
I've always wanted to eat with you
at this table.
Hyun-woo reluctantly
ate with you every day.
But this has always been my wish.
So don't look at me that way.
Let's eat.
-Is that really her?
-Gosh.
Let me have some time with him.
Grandfather.
Do you…
recognize me?
Have you gone insane?
How dare you let her in?
Is she in there alone?
-Let her be.
-Are you a saint?
She humiliated you in front of everyone.
Move!
She's with a geezer
who's not in his right mind.
-What could happen?
-Let go.
-Long time no see.
-I guess.
-Has it been a month?
-I heard.
I'm sorry you're sick at such a young age.
That's why I'm visiting my grandfather.
-Because I might die at any time.
-Hae-in.
What are you trying to find out
when you're dying anyway?
What are you afraid I'd find out?
This is exactly why
he entrusted me with everything.
He was afraid his family
would scheme something at times like this
-and only trusted me!
-Talk all you want.
We both know
-that you're lying.
-What?
You only have the power of attorney
as long as he's alive.
So I trust
that you'll take good care of him.
Since when did you even care?
All your family did was fight over money.
I know. But our family suffered
thanks to you,
and now we've become quite close.
But I'm not grateful.
I'll be back soon.
-Don't go.
-Let me go.
What'll you do?
Where's the main gate?
The main gate…
Hae-in.
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
Hyun-woo?
Is that you?
Yes, it's me.
What's the matter?
What happened?
Did you get beaten up again?
How many times must I tell you?
I don't get beaten up.
I can even handle three guys at once.
Seeing how arrogant you are,
you must be Hyun-woo.
Can you excuse me?
What happened?
I thought you got rid of him.
Exactly. You shouldn't have done that.
Done what?
-Come on.
-Check first.
-What?
-You can kill me
after five minutes,
and it won't make a difference.
So call the person
who hired you to kill me
and see if they keep their promise.
I got rid of Mr. Baek.
-Are you sure?
-Yes. What should I do now?
Don't call me and lie low for now.
-The money and the plane ticket?
-You'll get it.
But they'll suspect us
if we meet or I pay you now.
Wait until I call you.
Hello? Wait, listen--
Damn it.
MR. YOON EUN-SUNG 2
The number you have dialed is unavailable…
This asshole.
You're just a real estate scammer for now.
But you'll become a killer
once you kill me.
Don't pull one on me.
The police are still investigating
your assault case on me.
But if I die, that case
will turn into attempted murder.
You'll become a suspect
and get additional punishment
for planning it.
Then Interpol will put you
on their Red Notice,
their highest wanted list.
I told you to shut up.
You'll get at least 20 years for planning
a revenge killing and fleeing.
But if you don't kill me,
you'll only get three years for the fraud.
You could even get probation if I convince
the landowners to settle the case.
So? I'll put everything aside
if you stop here.
So you just let him go?
-Are you stupid?
-Yes, I was.
Pay me right now.
Or I'll tell the police
that it was you who hired me.
This is where I've been staying.
Gosh, you startled me!
It's okay. Don't clean up.
I've just been too busy.
I wondered where you were staying
after the divorce.
You were here.
Well…
Has it been uncomfortable?
No, it's a good place.
It was newly built and fully furnished.
Why did you sleep on the sofa?
Well…
You know I sleep well.
I can sleep
wherever I put my head down.
I guess you could sleep well
after our divorce, unlike me.
-What?
-It was your dream to get a divorce.
Now that it's come true,
you must've found peace
in this newly built
and fully furnished place.
That's not what I meant.
It's okay. At least one of us
was happy after the divorce.
I'm glad.
I wasn't comfortable at all.
This place gave me sick building syndrome,
so I suffered from headaches.
And look. The living room
is right next to the kitchen,
so it's not easy to air this place out.
And most of all,
you're not here.
Isn't that better for you?
Not at all.
At times, I wondered how it would feel
if we had lived here as newlyweds.
It would've been nice to live
in a small place like this
even after arguing with each other.
My mind would wander like that,
and I'd miss you.
I did.
I'm hungry.
Really? I'll cook you something.
Get some rest.
This looks good.
Let's eat.
You're really good.
Why didn't you ever cook?
I never had the chance.
By the way…
Will you see other women after I die?
What?
Will you live with someone
in this small place even after arguing?
Will you make her stew and live happily…
ever after?
What are you saying?
Just eat.
Answer me.
Don't change the subject again.
Do you want to die before me?
You worry too much.
Who would want to date me?
Everyone thinks you saved me,
because you're helplessly in love.
They're also criticizing me
for not knowing that
and leaving you.
So what kind of woman--
What kind of woman
wouldn't want to date you?
You're handsome, kind,
smart, but not arrogant.
Plus, you're a good cook.
There's no man like you.
Even if I was reborn a hundred times,
I'd still marry you
every single time.
How could you say such a thing
without even blinking…
your eyes?
It's true.
So why would I hesitate?
You know how to make my heart race.
Do you finally get it?
Hae-in doesn't care about you.
She's always using you.
I've always known that.
-Yet you still let her?
-Yes.
It's a habit.
I was always used
by you too.
You resent me
for abandoning you abroad, don't you?
Do you think I didn't know
that your adoptive parents abused you
despite getting paid handsomely?
Was it a coincidence
that those nondrinkers died
while driving drunk?
What are you saying?
What about the orphanage director
who mistreated you?
They closed down due to
a sudden fire, and the director died.
Was that a coincidence?
I never neglected you.
I didn't just sit on my hands
when those people caused you pain
or got in your way.
And that hasn't changed.
Being the chairman isn't enough.
It's my goal to make everything yours.
And I won't sit still
if anyone gets in my way
whether it's Hae-in or someone else.
Do you understand?
This is my way of loving you.
If you truly love her
and don't want her to get hurt,
then don't let her use you.
I won't stand for it.
Come on.
How could you get hurt again?
What happened?
I already told you.
It was a minor car accident.
My mind wasn't all there
when I was driving.
Right, did you get to see
your grandfather?
Grandfather, do you recognize me?
Lady, I'm hungry.
Grandfather…
Have you gone insane?
-How dare you let her in?
-Grandfather.
-I have no time.
-Is she in there alone?
Let her be.
Are you a saint?
She humiliated you…
Do you remember this pen?
You gifted it to me.
You even engraved my initials on it.
It can record sounds.
I'll place it over there,
so if you have anything to say, record it.
I'll be back soon.
He'll recognize the pen once he comes
to his senses.
He got it custom-made and gifted it to me
when I became the CEO.
It's something only we know.
What did Hae-in say?
I bet she asked about the secret fund.
Why did you have to hide it
and make us all suffer?
You should've wired it to me
if that was your plan all along.
What'll you do?
Take it with you when you die?
You fool.
You can't die. You're only barely alive
because of that damn money!
Are you sure you're out of it?
Did Hae-in tell you?
She's dying soon.
She has a rare case of a brain tumor
and won't live long.
Look at what happened
to the great Hong Man-dae.
You can't even process the fact
that your favorite granddaughter is dying.
Serves you right.
I'm strong.
I'm the best.
I'm a lunatic.
I'm a total lunatic. I'm--
I'm a strong male--
When did you get here?
I came after my morning jog.
You remind me of myself
when I first started boxing.
I like this attitude of yours.
Where are you coming from?
I dropped Ho-yeol off at school.
I see.
By the way,
does your wife work somewhere far away?
-Do you only meet on the weekends?
-No, we live together.
I see. I just never met her.
You see…
When we first got married,
my mom told her this.
"You're my daughter-in-law."
You're not my daughter.
A daughter-in-law can't be a daughter.
I hit Mi-seon.
Come on.
But you have your own parents,
and I can't do that to you.
We should watch what we say
and never get physical
if we're in-laws.
Yes, you're right.
So now that you're married,
-let's avoid seeing each other.
-What?
Seriously?
You can visit your parents or go on a trip
during national holidays if you want.
Thank you.
And don't bother
getting me birthday gifts.
It's uncomfortable.
If you want, just text me an emoji.
Don't you think that's too little?
Shut up. However, I have one condition.
My son has many flaws,
and there's nothing I can do.
You can try to fix him,
but don't return him to me.
Come on, Mom.
I'll do my best.
Your mother is so laid-back.
Thanks to her,
my wife's colleagues all say
that she has the best mother-in-law.
I can see that.
Since my mom treats her well,
my wife tends
to turn a blind eye to most things
that I do.
That's how we live.
Hey…
-I didn't mean to brag.
-But you did.
I didn't mean to.
Are you sulking? Soo-cheol.
Damn it.
This is it?
I know you stole all their pricey artwork
-before leaving.
-No, I didn't.
I just grabbed a few.
Then I bought an apartment.
I know you stole
a golden Buddha statue this big.
No, I didn't.
You're not fooling me.
Geon-u, are you okay?
Hey, what are you doing?
I see. So he's your weakness.
Are you crazy?
Touch him, and you're dead.
Where is the statue?
I know you haven't sold it.
I already looked into it,
so don't lie to me.
It's in a private safe.
We'll go there tomorrow morning.
Okay. Good.
Good girl.
Hey, pour me some wine. Okay?
Did you sleep well?
Yes.
I like this place.
I fell asleep right away just like you.
I told you.
Do you want to sleep more?
No.
Give me ten minutes.
No, just five.
We haven't had
a nice breakfast in a while.
I should have some salad and coffee.
Hyun-woo sneaked in here last night.
What?
Goodness. How?
He knew the back gate's camera was broken
and came in through there.
I see.
-He's so smart and thorough.
-Not at all.
He didn't erase the dashcam footage
in the other car.
So I found out how he got in.
Why are you putting me in a pickle?
Have you forgotten who I am?
You're the defected heroine
who joined our side.
No. Keep this up, and I'm going back.
Ms. Moh will kill me if she finds out.
I'm close to locating the secret fund.
That's why Hae-in came here.
God, this is driving me insane.
Give me 3% of the money then.
Make that 5%.
Do you mean that?
I betrayed them,
and they're still livid about it.
Of course. You can trust me.
Don't smile at me.
Handsome men are dangerous.
Seul-hee is going to kill me.
Thank you.
I forgave you once,
so how dare you
side with them again like a rat?
Dogs can be pets, but not rats.
They need to be killed at all costs.
Return your car pass, ID card,
and company card before you leave.
Your greed could cost you
all the money you have, Grace.
It would be best
to lie low for your safety.
-Ms. Moh.
-Get lost.
No, I can't do that.
How can I
when there's a huge misunderstanding?
I make a living out of information,
and people often mistake me for a rat.
But what can I do?
That's just who I am.
A misunderstanding?
Then explain why
you brought Hyun-woo of all people
to my house.
Hyun-woo offered me a deal.
He offered to give me
10% of the secret fund.
So he knows where the money is?
That's what I was curious about.
So I agreed to help.
And where is it?
Hyun-woo offered 10%,
but I'm fine with 7% from you.
Don't mess with me.
Then a small building and just 5%.
I deserve that much.
Tell me.
He thinks
it's in this house.
-Could I be wrong?
-What?
I see some men
taking photos of me behind that wall.
Jeez.
I can't believe this.
I still got it, don't I?
-Let them be.
-Why?
They'll leave in a bit.
Did they leave?
Bang-sil.
They left.
You don't have to suck it in anymore.
There you go.
I think I saw them
-yesterday as well.
-What?
They kept coming by in a black van.
They keep taking photos of things.
Where did I put my pricey heels?
Hey.
We need to talk.
What do you want?
You took a photo of our house?
Give me your camera.
-We didn't take anything. Let's go.
-I saw you.
So give it to me!
Goodness.
Hey, are you crazy?
Hey.
-You hit me first.
-Yes. So what?
Do you know what kind of heels I have on?
They had poop on them,
and I'll trample you with them!
You scumbags!
Gosh, that hurts.
Hey, what are you guys doing there?
-Dad…
-What are you doing?
Help us…
Ready, set, go.
Cross. That's it. Cross.
Cross.
One leg.
Cross. That's it. Cross.
Yes. Cross.
One leg.
-Jump.
-Did you hear?
Jump! What?
-They're forming a Yongdu-ri Quintet.
-Right.
You mean the village patrol team?
I heard about the mysterious van.
Exactly.
Keep going. Repeat.
I'm going to sign up.
I've quickly grown some muscles too.
I bulked up. Touch it.
No thanks.
Quintet means they'll pick five people.
Being a part of it means I'll be
one of the five strongest men here.
Do you think I can make it?
I want to punch something and break it.
Do you suggest a wooden bar or roof tiles?
Soo-cheol--
I know it won't be easy.
But I had a good dream last night.
I'm feeling hopeful.
There'll be less than five participants.
All right.
We're done then.
It'll be us five.
Leave me out of this.
I just stepped down from office.
People might interpret it politically
if they find out I formed a private group.
It'll only spark a conflict
between the two parties.
I can't leave my mom's side either.
You always leave her unattended
when you drink.
-Why are you pretending to be a good son?
-Come on, guys.
We need at least five members
if we want this group to be funded.
Does this mean
I'm in?
Yes, it does.
I can punch this.
That's okay.
Becoming one of us means
it'll be permanent.
You can't back out later.
See?
I told you you didn't have to try much.
Are we almost there?
Yes.
Almost.
Shall we get out?
This is nice.
Everyone confesses their feelings here,
and no one has failed so far.
Your love comes true
if you confess it here.
And it's worked every time.
That's absurd.
Not only do you get
a beautiful sunset,
but the light also gives your face
a warm tone,
which makes you look more gorgeous.
You look beautiful
right now.
Is that so?
So will you confess your love?
It's actually more
of a request.
What kind?
A divorce withdrawal.
Asking you to marry me again
would be too much.
So could you at least
take back the divorce?
You remembered my size.
Of course.
But I should put that on you.
Get a refund.
Why?
You said you wanted to
marry me every single time.
That's if I was reborn, but not now.
Why not exactly?
Why?
Yesterday, I thought…
it was you.
-What?
-I…
followed Eun-sung
because I thought it was you.
It has come this far.
My memory is unstable.
I forgot where I was.
And in the end,
I couldn't even recognize you.
Hyun-woo?
I told you
that we shouldn't be together
if my illness worsens.
But…
that time came sooner than expected.
The sunset is beautiful.
You're right.
The sunlight
makes you look more handsome.
But…
are you even really Baek Hyun-woo?
Is this real? Am I not dreaming?
I can't be sure of anything anymore.
That's why I can't make any promises.
I'm sorry.
What's that in his hand?
The curtain is in the way.
It has low resolution.
Should I get a higher one?
Have you seen my mother?
No, I haven't.
You're not lying, are you? I'm serious.
What is he saying?
I'm serious too.
Hey! Yeong-song!
-Have you found her?
-No.
She wasn't in town either.
We should call the police.
I already did.
Good job.
You don't think
she's in the mountains again, do you?
-Goodness.
-The sun will set soon.
I'll check.
Wait.
I think I can help.
There it goes.
A bit more to the right.
A bit more,
and you'll see the mineral springs.
A bit more. Yes, there.
Go up from there.
More.
Keep going.
There's a peak called the Fairy Peak.
That's it!
There she is!
Mom!
-Is she asleep?
-Yes.
Thank you so much.
I'm jealous.
Of what?
My father is sick too,
but I can't even take care of him.
Right.
I heard.
He was one strong man.
He wouldn't budge
no matter how much I challenged him.
So I kept at it.
But I wouldn't have done it
had I known this would happen.
Do you know
what the last thing I said to him was?
"I'll see you at your funeral."
This darn mouth of mine.
I should've been more careful.
I've never challenged my mother before.
Are you bragging right now?
My mother left home
when I was very little.
My father was abusive and cheated on her.
So I grew up without her.
Then she got dementia,
so I took her out of the nursing home
and have been living with her.
It's my wish
to argue with her when she's sane.
I…
I had no idea.
All of us
have burdens that we must carry in life.
Even those who look the most carefree
carry heavy stones in their pockets.
So…
don't be jealous
or blame yourself.
I'm sure your father knows
how much you care.
I tracked the truck.
It left for your house in Hanil-dong
from the warehouse in Gyeonggi Province.
What is this?
So all that money is at home?
That's impossible.
Even if an apple crate
holds 600 million won,
he'd need a total of 1,500 crates.
He'd need more than just a storage room.
It'd require about 100 pyeongs of space.
Could there be
a secret space in our house?
Or a warehouse perhaps?
We stopped by the district office
to check the floor plans,
but we found nothing.
Then what is this?
Last night,
Grandfather told me something when we met.
What is it?
Do you have something to say?
Lady, come to my house
if a war breaks out.
We have an air-raid shelter.
You can hide there.
He mentioned an air-raid shelter.
An air-raid shelter?
In our house?
That can't be.
He was probably rambling.
We have something similar.
He told me about how he had built
a panic room.
You're right. I heard too.
But where is it?
We only heard about it.
None of us knows where it is.
Even the floor plan didn't show anything.
That's true,
but there could be a secret floor plan.
If the money was here like Grace said,
then I would've known.
All that money won't fit
in a couple safes.
Yes, and we also have that room.
You know the movie
with a secret room, Shock Room?
It's Panic Room, you idiot.
I heard this place had a panic room.
Do you know about it?
This isn't the Yongdu-ri Quintet.
It's a trio.
They'll join us for drinks later
after we finish patrolling.
Who's that at this hour?
Maybe they're those men
from earlier today.
We should've brought a Taser or something.
-It's a taxi.
-A taxi?
They drove a black van.
Who could they be?
Why would they bring
a suitcase here at this hour?
Isn't this what they say about killers
-on the news?
-Should I call them?
Should I?
How have you been?
I definitely…
had…
a good dream last night.
I'm sorry.
This is everything except for the money
spent on the flight and hotel.
I bought an apartment in the U.S.
but I'll get the money back.
I'll give it to you once I get it.
I'm truly sorry.
Do you even know
what you've done?
Giving back that money won't cut it.
-Mom.
-I'm aware of that.
I know it's unforgivable.
I'm truly…
sorry.
It's late, and we all need to sleep.
Go to bed for now.
Okay. You can sleep
-over there--
-Don't be absurd.
I don't want to see you
or that thing, so leave.
His name is Geon-u.
And you have no right
to tell them to leave.
This isn't even our house.
He's right, Seon-hwa.
So you're going to live
with someone else's baby?
He's my son!
I cut his umbilical cord,
sang lullabies to him every night,
and bathed him myself.
Geon-u
said "Dad" before he could even say "Mom"!
Get up.
But…
We need to clear up some stuff.
What should we call each other?
You know my age,
so we can't be like how we used to be.
I don't care.
I care. I'm older than you.
Do you want me to treat you like one?
Ma'am?
I didn't return
so we could live together again.
-Then?
-I came to return everything.
And Jun-ho--
That bastard is planning
to use you as his scapegoat.
Stop him, or you'll end up in prison.
So you came here just to tell me that?
I was worried.
I only got married to mooch off
of a stupid, wealthy guy.
So I didn't expect you…
to care
so much about me.
No one has ever
treated me the way you did.
I couldn't forget how well…
you treated me.
I couldn't even eat well.
That's why I'm here.
So you came here to tell me that?
Really? And once you're done,
will you leave again?
I feel shame too.
I can't live with you.
No.
I must live with you.
I don't care why you're here.
I'm going to live with you.
I'll never let you or my son leave again.
Go if you want.
I'll find you no matter where you are.
You really
don't listen, do you?
-I'm older than you.
-Be quiet.
-So--
-Excuse me.
Have some of this.
Thank you.
She's my master's…
-She doesn't look like a mom.
-Stop staring.
I heard she made quite an entrance.
It was insane.
My husband told me about it.
She appeared in the middle of the night
while holding Buddha's head.
My husband was so shocked.
He keeps getting sleep paralysis
and waking up.
I told you.
Chun-sik needs some black goat extract.
Then feed him.
Really?
Is that golden Buddha really made of gold?
Pure gold?
Beats me.
What does your hunch say? We should decide
between "like" or "dislike."
-What do you mean?
-I mean…
We'll run into her often,
so we need to know
what kind of stance to take.
Will we welcome or ignore her?
Exactly.
Is it like or dislike?
We'll do as you say.
I'm not sure yet.
You're not?
I feel bad for her,
but something feels off too.
I need to watch her a bit longer.
He still remembered
my size.
A round brilliant cut?
Didn't you go to work?
Yes.
But I forgot something.
I'm going to return it.
-I see.
-I thought about what you said.
I think I pushed ahead too much.
I'll return it on my way to work today.
I see.
Today?
This isn't what's important right now.
Don't feel bad.
I'm really okay.
I see.
Okay then.
What?
What is it?
I just
tried it on.
It was a new design.
I wanted to study the trends.
I can't slack off
just because I'm taking a break.
That's true.
I liked the ring.
You know that rings suit me awfully well.
You have a good eye.
I'll give you that.
But…
it's just that.
So don't misinterpret my actions.
Wait.
Are you sure
you've finished analyzing the trends?
Maybe study it more.
I'm done analyzing it.
I'll get going then.
Hae-in.
I won't return it.
I'll leave it where it was before.
You need to analyze the trends,
so wear it whenever you want.
A panic room? Like the one in the movies?
For when there's a nuclear bomb?
Where there are guns
and years' worth of food?
I'm not sure about that part,
but the chairman did mention a panic room.
But no one knows where it's located.
I see.
-What about on the register?
-It wasn't in there.
Ask the designer.
He passed away.
The son took over the firm.
Then ask him.
I did,
and he doesn't know.
I asked for the floor plan,
but he had none.
I kept calling him
and now he won't pick up anymore.
Really?
What'll you do then?
There's not much I can do.
Someone else needs to convince him.
Who?
-You.
-Me?
Goodness, we meet again.
You never know the future.
I totally agree.
I've met my lifesaver again.
Gosh, I don't deserve that title.
How's the building in Pangyo?
Good, and it's all thanks to you.
I almost lost it.
By the way,
I heard my friend here pestered you.
I apologize.
I didn't want to get involved
in something complicated.
No, I'm sorry about asking such a favor.
If this panic room
was made for evacuation,
air pipes and electrical installations
for ventilation and communication
should have been installed.
But I couldn't find any on the floor plan.
How will we find it?
We'd have to turn the house upside down.
What's interesting
is that his elevator
that connects to the basement
was specially built unlike the others.
His elevator?
It never felt different to me.
It has two doors.
The back side is a door as well.
The front door leads to the family room,
but the back door leads
to a whole different space. Is that it?
And that's the panic room?
That's my guess, but I'd have to check.
-Can't we just raid the place?
-There's tight security.
We'll be sued for trespassing.
But what if Seul-hee
finds it before we do?
I spoke with his doctor today.
His doctor told me
that he hasn't been receiving
any mandatory treatments
like rehabilitation or memory training
ever since he woke up and returned home.
He's likely out of medication,
but he hasn't made another appointment.
What? I knew this would happen.
What should we do?
We can report them for confinement
and enter the house
with the police.
And check out the elevator?
Let's all go first thing in the morning.
You're back.
I knew it.
You seemed a bit off
ever since Hae-in came by.
Do you come to your senses
every now and then?
But the duration is too short
for you to do anything.
You can't request help.
You can't move freely.
You have no phone either.
This place must be hell, mustn't it?
You're right.
This is
a living hell.
And…
I'm being punished.
That's why I gave you that pill.
So that you could sleep in peace
with no worries.
So why aren't you taking them?
Moh Seul-hee.
Was this always your motive
for coming here?
Then did you think I truly loved you
or something?
Aren't I just terrible?
Don't you miss your kids?
You can go.
Just tell me
where your secret fund is.
There's nothing you can do
when you're only sane
for a short moment at a time.
Just tell me,
and everything will be fine.
Tell me!
What's going on?
Hyun-woo.
Did you call an ambulance as well?
No, the officer I contacted
hasn't arrived yet.
Then what's going on?
Did something happen?
What is it?
What's going on?
Tell me.
-Move.
-You can't enter.
Jeez.
Hong Man-dae, age 80, has dementia.
We believe a cervical spine fracture
was the cause of death.
He'll be taken to Daemang Hospital soon.
Dad!
Dad?
Father.
We're here.
We're here now.
Dad…
Do something…
Beom-jun.
Do something.
His hands are still warm.
No.
What's going on?
Honey.
Sir.
Please give him CPR or something.
-Dad…
-I'm sorry.
Do something, please.
I'm sorry. We need to move him.
We need to move him. I'm sorry.
-Dad!
-Excuse us.
Dad!
Wait!
-Dad!
-I'm sorry.
-Wait.
-We need to move him. I'm sorry.
-We have to move. I'm sorry.
-Dad!
-I'm sorry.
Grandfather.
Dad…
A prominent business mogul
passed away early this morning.
After beginning
as a shoeshine boy in the streets
and building Queens Group
into an industry leader,
Hong Man-dae,
the former Queens Group chairman,
has died at the age of 80.
He suffered a sudden heart attack
a month ago and had been in a coma.
Despite recently waking up,
he had showed signs of vascular dementia.
The industry is closely monitoring
Queens Group's leadership situation.
Hong signed the power of attorney
to his domestic partner, Moh Seul-hee,
which grants her rights,
such as control of his shares and house.
However, due to his passing,
her rights will become null and void.
Due to Chairman Hong's death,
his entire fortune will be handed out
according to his notarized will.
This takes effect immediately
without needing the court's approval.
Did you get that?
Pack up and get going.
Shouldn't we focus
on wishing him peace for now?
We can discuss such matters later.
He loved this house.
Please give him
one final tour.
You little…
You're blessed
with a handsome and smart son.
Yes.
He's good at boxing
and swimming too.
Right.
Look here.
He even went to
a children's Marine Corps Camp.
He once
even saved a kid from drowning.
-What's going on?
-Don't go there.
-Hurry up!
-What's going on?
-What's happening?
Hae-in!
-Two.
-Three.
Why did you go in there?
Are you okay? Come along.
Su-wan…
No, Su-wan…
Su-wan, please!
My poor son!
Su-wan!
QUEEN OF TEARS
Hae-in. Thank you.
It was you, wasn't it?
I told you. I want her to live.
I'm going to leave once I'm done here.
Balsam?
It signifies my excitement
and hope for the first snow
that I thought I'd never see.
This is…
what you call true fate.
You're going to ruin this all
just for Hong Hae-in?
He took the bait.
Keep Eun-sung in the loop
so that he'll feel anxious…
Hae-in!
There's something
I didn't tell you as well.
Subtitle translation by Soo-ji Kim