"Pure and innocent"!
Sister, what does that mean?
Nothing.
[Why did he put up]
[the paperweight I gave him as a prize?]
[Not good.]
[He thinks the prize I offered]
[was far too valuable.]
[He's hinting at me.]
[True.]
[There are too many people here today.]
[So many eyes are watching.]
[No.]
[No matter what,]
[I must win that paperweight back.]
[Then no one will think]
[I was deliberately giving the Chen family a gift.]
[If I clear my name,]
[his name will be cleared too.]
This is a fine piece.
This jade paperweight
looks very valuable.
The Chen family truly is wealthy.
Wealthy?
Squeezed from the people.
Two realms split by one beam.
The greater bows to the small.
Five warriors above,
can't beat a pair below.
Guess the object.
What large and small kingdoms?
This object of yours
must be a spirit-writing stick
and a Daoist sand tray.
Wrong.
How is that wrong?
Didn't you ask me
to find a Daoist for you?
Anyway, your answer is wrong.
Stop being so cryptic.
Only green willows may tether a horse.
Only
green... horse...
Sunlight over a gushing spring.
Brother Ye,
the place in your riddle
isn't somewhere you've been, is it?
Of course it is.
But Brother Ye,
you've traveled far and wide.
The places you've been
are places others have never seen.
Isn't it unfair
to set such a riddle?
Then I'll withdraw the riddle
and stop playing.
No, don't.
What if someone guesses it?
I know the answer.
Sunlight over a gushing spring.
Is it Yangquan?
Correct.
Here.
I'll have someone
send you gunpowder.
Thank you, Lord Ye.
How did you guess it?
My ancestral home is in Shanxi.
This guessing game isn't fun at all.
Such a dawdler.
Green willow means the wood radical.
Tethering a horse
must be the other half.
Is it qiang, meaning mast?
Wrong.
Aunt, try again.
It's chu, meaning pestle.
Green willow means the wood radical.
Can tether a horse—
Among the earthly branches,
Horse corresponds to wu.
So the character is chu.
Miss Gu is correct.
How impressive.
Miss Gu is amazing.
Large kingdom, small kingdom...
I know the answer.
Wrong guess.
Still haven't guessed it.
Isn't that Young Master Wang?
Let's go take a look.
Cousin.
What are you doing here?
I just came out of the privy
and lost my way.
I wandered into a room
and happened to see this painting on the desk.
It suits my taste perfectly.
May I ask who painted it?
Could I have it?
This painting has lofty spirit.
It looks like Xuruo's work.
I don't think so.
Why?
Look at the inscription.
"How small the other peaks appear!"
It's Taige style, a formal court script.
Precise, powerful, and dignified.
Without more than ten years of practice,
one couldn't write characters like this.
But Young Master Chen
is so young.
How could he have written it?
Miss Gu is right.
It was indeed not painted by me.
Then what do you think of it?
I think
this painting is not only grand,
but also carries
the force of reaching the summit
and seeing all other peaks below.
It's just...
Only what?
It feels somewhat hollow,
not like true feeling.
Well said.
Brother.
Greetings, Mr. Chen.
Uncle.
Lord Ye.
Young Master Wang.
Then tell me,
who painted
this Ascending the Heights?
It should be an older
and highly respected teacher.
Older?
Highly respected?
Uncle.
Miss Gu did not mean it.
This painting
was done by you?
My apologies.
I spoke out of turn.
I dared to
judge your fine work so rashly.
Please forgive me.
I say,
since you are here as a guest,
why be so afraid?
It's all right.
Once a painting is completed,
it is meant to be judged.
Miss Gu need not apologize.
Exactly.
They say a minister's heart can hold a boat.
Lord Chen is not yet a prime minister,
but he's nearly in the Secretariat.
So, half a boat at least.
But for a dignified prime minister
to hide behind a door and eavesdrop—
that lacks grace.
Someone wanted to critique my painting.
It is only natural
that I wished to hear it.
So it was Lord Chen's painting.
Then may I have it?
Since Young Master Wang likes it,
take it.
Thank you, Lord Chen.
Actually, I came to find Lord Ye.
Lord Ye is of noble character,
and serves as the Crown Prince's reader.
It is getting late.
I fear
he should return.
I still have a riddle unsolved.
I'm not going back.
What kind of riddle
could stump Lord Ye?
Uncle.
It is a riddle from Miss Gu.
It has stumped everyone.
Let's hear it, then.
Two realms split by one beam.
The greater bows to the small.
Five warriors above,
can't beat a pair below.
Guess the object.
Isn't that an abacus?
You actually guessed it.
I'll have the prize sent
to you at once.
You call that hard?
What?
With so many of you here,
no one guessed it?
You all...
Uncle.
Earlier I went to visit Fourth Uncle.
He refused to see me.
Later, Grandmother came as well.
Fourth Uncle still would not see her.
Only after Grandmother said
she would summon a physician
did he open the gate.
Let's not speak of him.
For next spring's imperial exam,
do you plan to sit for it?
That is my intention.
I plan to return to the academy tomorrow
and shut myself in to study.
Good.
Tomorrow, take your essays
to Minister Chang Tinglan's residence
and ask him for guidance.
I have already spoken with him.
From now on,
every ten days,
he will review an essay for you.
Lord Chang?
But he is not a great scholar.
Yes, Third Uncle.
Go.
I think
this painting is not only grand,
but also carries
the force of reaching the summit
and seeing all other peaks below.
It's just...
It feels somewhat hollow,
not like true feeling.
True feeling.
Miss,
incense burns so strongly at Baoxiang Temple.
Yes. Today is the Double Ninth Festival.
Not everyone is here to pray.
Some may be here to climb heights.
Let's hurry forward.
After praying for Grandmother,
we can come back and look around.
Yes, miss.
Look.
Autumn shadows fill the river; wild geese take wing.
With wine and friends, I climb the emerald height.
What a pity.
I didn't bring good wine.
A rare day off
should be spent resting properly.
Why insist on climbing a mountain?
Uncle, you can't run.
I secretly brought you here to climb.
If anything happens to you,
my mother will skin me alive.
Uncle.
My lord.
Uncle, don't scare me.
Uncle.
My lord.
Bodhisattva above,
please protect Grandmother.
May she be safe
and free from disaster.
Miss.
Isn't that Lord Ye?
Go see.
Cousin Jinzhao.
What happened to Lord Ye?
His heart may be acting up.
If you know it is his heart ailment,
do you have medicine with you?
He usually keeps medicine on him.
But he happened to be off duty today,
so he didn't bring any.
Guard Li went down
to call a physician.
I understand.
A heart ailment cannot wait.
No.
We can't wait for Guard Li.
Qingpu.
Press his Tanzhong pressure point.
Yes.
Please move aside.
Will this work?
What are you doing?
If you harm him,
our whole family could die.
But we can't just watch him die.
Let go. But...
No buts.
He moved.
Miss, it's working.
It really is.
It's you.
You're awake.
Thank heaven.
Don't move.
Bodhisattva bless us.
Do you still
feel unwell anywhere?
Yes.
Where?
My hand.
My hand is trapped.
On the road, go slower if you must,
but don't jostle him.
Yes.
And you too.
Don't move around.
Even after taking medicine,
you should rest for several days.
Why such a nag at your age?
What did you say?
I said,
you're so young, yet such a nag,
like an old nanny.
Lift the sedan.
Let's go too.
The Marquis of Changxing leads the military lords.
Ye Xian is his heir.
With a heart ailment, he cannot take up arms.
And he is the marquisate's only son.
If the military heir cannot fight,
he has no future.
Yes.
A heart ailment is hard to cure.
Miss,
you are amazing.
It is getting late.
We've been out for half a day.
We should go back.
Let's go.
When can we pass?
I still have things to do.
I need to go home.
Miss, I'll ask.
When will they let us through?
Can't someone give us an answer?
Say something.
When can we pass?
Miss, I heard
a noble has come to Baoxiang Temple to offer incense.
The whole mountain is sealed off.
Offer incense?
That's clearly a lie.
People offer incense early, not late.
It is already afternoon.
Who comes to offer incense now?
What rotten luck.
Had I known,
I would have gone down with Ye Xian.
When I climbed the tree earlier,
I saw on that hill
another path.
Why don't I go scout it first?
If it can be used,
I'll come back for you.
All right.
Then wait for me.
Let us through.
We need to go down.
Exactly.
Why isn't Qingpu back yet?
Could something have happened?
Is this the path Qingpu mentioned?
Why is there no one here?
Why isn't there a soul here?
Help!
Mr. Chen!
Protect the Crown Prince.
Yes.
So the man that day
really was him.
Damned Crown Prince.
Die!
Can you still stand?
Were you frightened?
What?
You mean
Jinzhao is still on the mountain?
Yes.
I found a path in the back hills
and planned to return for Miss.
But who would have thought the way back
was also sealed off?
So I came back first
and inform you all.
It will soon be dark.
Please give me more people, Madam,
to go back up the mountain and find Miss.
Good child.
You may have as many as you need.
Take my tally at once
and summon people.
Come, Nanny Zhao.
Thank you, Madam.
Go.
In my view,
Jinzhao
is just too playful.
Jinzhao is not that kind of person.
What are we to do?
Will you confess or not?
Still refusing?
I've already seen him
kill people twice.
Will he kill me to silence me?
Greetings, Mr. Chen.
Mr. Chen.
I truly heard nothing.
I saw nothing.
I promise.
I won't say a single word.
Please.
Please spare my life.
Today's matter is gravely serious.
If word gets out,
who knows how many people
it could bring death upon them.
This is...
Take it.
I cannot protect you otherwise.
It's poison.
Mr. Chen.
I won't breathe
a single word of it.
Otherwise,
may lightning strike me.
No need for oaths.
Take the medicine.
Then I will believe you.
Mr. Chen.
When I came today,
many people saw me.
My maid and I
were together at first,
but then we got separated.
I imagine by now
she has already gone back.
If she finds
she cannot find me,
she will surely send word when she returns.
She may even report it to officials.
Right.
On the way,
Lord Ye saw me too.
If he suddenly learns I died,
he will certainly ask about it.
So what?
If too many people ask,
then everyone will know.
So killing me
would do more harm than good.
And this is sacred Buddhist ground.
Killing here is unlucky.
Please, Mr. Chen.
Why not spare my life?
Saving a life earns great merit.
The dead are the only truly reliable ones.
When today's matter is done,
I will naturally protect your grandmother
and the Ji family
and keep them safe.
Lord Chen.
Why must you do this?
Since you say the girl is one of us,
she can naturally be trusted.
Trustworthy or not,
I trust only what I test myself.
How did it go on your side?
He confessed.
Let's talk inside.
After all that questioning,
he only said the leader's surname is Xiao.
Every time they met,
he wore a veiled hat,
his face was hidden.
From his bearing,
he seemed like a scholar.
He spent freely.
When one of their men died before,
the compensation money
was a full five hundred taels.
That is why each of them
was willing to die for him.
Surname Xiao?
Could it be Xiao Qishan?
Wasn't he once an adviser
to the late Prince Chengqing?
Back then, Prince Chengqing
obeyed that man in everything.
After Prince Chengqing's rebellion failed,
The Marquis killed the prince,
and that adviser vanished.
This time, the news of the Crown Prince leaving the palace
was leaked by us
to Prince Glorian.
But Prince Glorian actually used
one of Prince Chengqing's former strategists.
That means...
It means Prince Glorian
has always brooded
over Prince Chengqing's death.
It seems Prince Glorian
is plotting something big.
Lord Chen,
you must be extra careful.
Same to you.
Lord Chen.
We are in the same boat now.
Back then, the late Prince Chengqing's rebellion
left the Criminal Justice Office in ruins.
If the Chief Councilor
had not valued us,
how could we have
to handle such an important case?
In the future,
I hope you will support me, Lord Chen.
You and I both serve our teacher.
We should
work as one.
Stop pretending.
Get up.
Greetings, Mr. Chen.
Rise and speak.
It's over now.
When today's matter is done,
I will naturally protect your grandmother
and the Ji family
and keep them safe.
Thank you for saving me just now, Mr. Chen.
What is it?
What are you looking at?
I'm looking at you.
You seem
different from before.
I mean that time I set fire to the storeroom
and snatched your lantern.
Why didn't you say so the last two times?
Because I didn't dare.
This time, I dare.
You just saved my life.
You were too afraid to say it
because you saw me kill?
You only killed when you had no choice.
How am I different?
I can't quite say.
It reminds me
of when I lived in Tongzhou.
There was
a young servant named Gou
who played with me often.
We often played together.
But one year he returned to his hometown.
After he came back,
his whole nature changed.
He became quiet
and stopped playing with me.
He only begged Grandmother
to send him to Suzhou
as an apprentice in a shop.
I only learned later
that during that month,
his father had died.
I shall watch from heaven
whether Great Yan
under your protection, Chen Yanyun,
can prosper without end.
I'm not saying you are like him.
What I mean is—
I understand.
Sit.
My ancestral home is also in Tongzhou.
Even now,
your grandmother still manages it.
I wonder when
I can return to Tongzhou.
What is it?
Do you dislike the capital?
I don't like the capital.
The capital isn't fun at all.
Unlike Tongzhou,
there are docks,
temple fairs,
and book markets.
The capital has those too.
The capital is different.
The capital has too many rules.
Many entertainments are forbidden.
For example,
in Tongzhou,
during New Year, we held temple fairs.
Tongzhou's wealthy merchants
take turns hiring opera troupes
to perform at the fairs.
And I loved iron-flower shows.
So every year, Grandmother
hired performers
hired iron-flower performers to perform.
It was so beautiful.
But the capital forbids it.
Forget iron-flower shows.
I heard that since the year before last,
even Aoshan lantern displays are banned.
Molten-iron fireworks?
But
Fire and fireworks can easily start a blaze.
Miss.
Miss, miss.
You finally came down.
I was worried to death.
Are you all right?
Look, I'm fine.
Thank you.
Let's go home. Come.
Did you bump or hurt yourself?
I heard you encountered a noble.
Did they trouble you?
I'm fine.
I just returned a bit late.
Only after the noble left
was I allowed down the mountain.
Which palace was that noble from
to put on such airs?
I wouldn't know.
As long as they didn't trouble you.
Hurry back and rest.
You've had a long day.
What kind of attitude was that?
What are you thinking about, Miss?
The night before my coming-of-age,
I remember it all.
The person I saw that night
was Mr. Chen.
What should we do?
Will Mr. Chen turn against you?
Speaking of that,
there is something
I need you to do.
Please tell me.
I have an old acquaintance,
surnamed Nie.
His wife and daughter are in the capital.
Help me settle them properly.
I cannot show myself.
When you find her,
don't mention me.
He probably won't.
He ordered me to do something for him.
Right.
Tomorrow morning,
go find Shopkeeper Luo.
Ask him to choose several
marionettes.
I need them.
In this capital review,
we found
officials such as Zheng Tuo,
of the Shanxi Bureau,
were found unfit—
376 in all.
Among them,
37 were dismissed,
42 were demoted,
16 were transferred out,
and 28 were formally reprimanded.
The capital officials
number 1,364 in all.
Yet 376 were found unfit.
Many military nobles did not even attend.
The scene
was truly brutal.
So harsh,
yet Master was rated competent.
This shows how strong
his reputation is.
One can only say
it was luck.
I must also thank Lord Lin
for saying in public he was not close to me.
I called him Teacher for so many years,
and he repaid me with "not close."
Yet in the blink of an eye,
he himself got into trouble.
Indeed.
Heaven sees all.
Master.
I have a favor to ask of you.
If you mean managing the household,
then no.
What happened before
was only a few days ago.
Right now,
returning household authority to you
cannot be justified.
It isn't about household authority.
Lan comes of age next year.
She was raised before your eyes.
Her coming-of-age ceremony
should also be decent, shouldn't it?
This is not the time for that.
In any case, that is next year.
We'll discuss it next year.
I just remembered
there are matters in the front courtyard.
That's all for now.
Miss.
These are
the three marionettes you wanted.
They are quite exquisite.
Yes.
We found
the best craftsmen to make them.
Thank you, Uncle Ping.
Then let's go now.
What happened?
Don't panic.
Miss.
to notify Madam Nie.
I had just reached Fentiao Alley
I ran into people snatching things.
I ran into a group looting.
the clansmen of Madam Nie's late husband.
They kept saying
the property belongs to the clan
The property belongs to the clan
and must be taken back.
They also said their second brother
was heir to a hereditary title,
called...
the hereditary rank Yunqiwei.
For speaking wildly before His Majesty,
he was beaten to death.
so they blamed Madam Nie for bringing misfortune.
Nie Fengming.
Miss.
Could Mr. Chen's friend be...
Go on.
Yes.
Though I didn't understand
what they meant,
I knew
Madam Nie
was the person you wanted found.
So
I placed them
at the silk shop.
If I overstepped,
please punish me.
Punish you for what?
For doing the job too well?
Thank you, Miss.
Let's go.
To the silk shop.
May I ask, are you Miss Gu?
Yes.
Thank you, Miss Gu's servant
for helping me out of trouble.
Please, no need.
Please rise.
Miss Gu and I are strangers.
May I ask
why you sent someone to find me?
Here is the matter.
I have a cousin.
Some years ago in the capital,
while doing business,
he received Lord Nie's help.
This cousin of mine
heard I was coming to the capital,
so he asked me to visit you.
Who would have thought
we'd happen upon a disturbance?
Help?
Yes.
This man
was always eager to do public good
and help others.
But he forgot
those who needed his help most
were his own family.
You must be Xiangyun.
This cousin of mine said
this month is Xiangyun's birthday.
So
he specially asked me to bring gifts.
String puppets.
Are all these for me?
Yes, all for you.
Do you like them?
I do.
Mother, may I take them?
Since they are for you,
take them and play.
Xiangyun, come.
Come with sister.
All right.
Thank you, sister.
Miss,
I'll bring more tea and snacks.
Please sit.
This is wound medicine.
Take it home and apply it to your wounds.
Thank you, Miss Gu.
This time, disaster befell him.
The court
pitied us, orphan and widow,
and spared us punishment.
But those clansmen
have instead set their eyes
on my late husband's possessions.
After all is said and done,
it is my fault.
I was blind.
I married
such a heartless, short-lived wretch.
Mother.
Father was a good man.
He is not a ghost.
Your father left us both behind
and went off to die alone.
Yet you still speak for him.
Father did it for righteousness.
For his righteousness,
he sacrificed both our lives
and made us suffer like this.
What kind of righteousness is that?
I don't feel it's suffering.
That day Father said
after he died,
I must still live well.
I promised Father,
so I must do it.
After he died?
What?
Did he tell you before he died?
How is that possible?
It was that day,
the night before Father went to the palace.
Enough. Stop talking.
It is late today.
We should be leaving.
Miss Gu, thank you again
for helping me today.
Wait.
Why did you suddenly think
of asking Miss Gu to visit Madam Nie?
It was just a passing impulse.
We spoke a few words at Baoxiang Temple.
I suddenly felt
she was a good choice.
Miss Gu is indeed clever and bold.
She can hold her own in trouble.
Mr. Chen.
Miss Gu sent word.
She asks when you are free
and wants to meet.
Greetings, Mr. Chen.
Rise.
Why have you come to me?
Speak.
Mr. Jiang is not an outsider.
Say what you need to say.
I came to report back.
The matter you entrusted to me
has been completed.
No wonder you would not appear yourself
and sent me instead.
You met Madam Nie and Xiangyun.
I not only met them,
I also
dealt with a pack of Nie clansmen.
They forced Madam Nie
to hand over
what Lord Nie left behind.
and swallow up the Nie estate.
You have no idea.
You didn't see
how far
they had pushed her.
I don't know
what relationship
you had with Lord Nie.
Nor do I wish to know.
I only hope
that for Xiangyun
and Madam Nie's sake,
you can help them.
so their lives
can be a little easier.
No.
Why?
Can't you
help that orphan and widow?
There is no why.
No means no.
Do not mention this again.
Go back.
Fine.
Since you won't help,
then I'll do it. All right?
What you refuse to do yourself,
I'll stand in.
I promise it won't implicate you.
Will that satisfy you?