Delaney with the puck!
He's trying to fend them off!
Delaney shoots!
He scores!
Ransom wins!
Hannah. Hannah.
We won.
♪When the morning comes...♪
Uh, excuse me, gentlemen.
The UN has declared
an international band emergency,
and they say that my dad
is the only man for the job.
An international band emergency?
Have they called Prince?
They tried, but he is famously dead.
Good God, this is worse than I thought.
Sorry, guys.
You're so weird.
Also, can we hit Dairy Queen
on the way home?
What? Are you saying the international
band emergency was a ruse?
Is Prince even dead?
Han! Honey, you were phenomenal.
Uh, how was I?
Mm, you were okay, too.
Ah, yes!
Okay, can I help you?
I just want to know
how your new song is coming along.
It must be going well,
because you missed three cues tonight.
The muse waits for no one.
Oh, does the muse play clarinet?
Because we're looking
for a new alternate first chair.
Just write, Hannah.
Han?
I'm gonna skip the game today.
Got an extra monster cookie
if you want one.
Hannah?
Babe, you okay?
Yeah, yeah, sorry, I'm...
I'm not super hungry.
Uh, don't worry about me, I'm-- I'm good.
Okay, love you.
Look at those smug motherfuckers.
Their ten-game streak ends now.
Not if their new center
has anything to say about it.
Please, he's been skating
in fucking cornfields.
- Iowa, or whatever.
-  Indiana.
Kid's fast as fuck. Physical, too.
Doesn't matter. Nothing's getting past us.
Yeah, see? Simms gets it.
Yeah, come on, boys.
Let's get it.
Fuck, yeah. Let's go.
He also doesn't back down from anything.
Same as Garrett.
Oh, shit. Papa Graham's mad early.
No pressure, man.
Garrett, good to see you.
Looks like you got
a tough one out there today.
Feeling good?
Yeah, you know what?
Don't worry about me. I'm ready.
Sorry, I left my phone in the car.
It's okay.
Hi, Garrett.
Cindy.
Good luck out there today.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Sean, I am so sorry
that you had to find out like that.
I never meant to hurt your feelings.
But also, literally, how dare you suggest
that I am incapable of being alone?
Like, that's so fucked of you,
Sean. So fucked.
Again, could not be more sorry.
Please just call me back or text me or--
Please hang up or press one to re-record.
- Oh.
- Allie, what are you doing here?
Uh, this is the drama building.
I'm in the correct place.
What are you doing here?
This is perfect. You're not busy, right?
I need a huge favor.
No, Beau, sorry, I can't
take on anyone else's stress today.
I am emotionally raw.
I'm the shell of a woman.
Okay. Okay. Thank you, Ira.
You, too, Ira.
Bye, Ira.
Sorry about that.
Ira is not great at ending conversations.
Jo, this is Allie. Allie--
You're Joanna Maxwell.
Yeah, Allie's a fan.
Nice to meet you.
Wait, are you Allie Hayes?
Don't we have the same agent?
You know who I am.
Joanna Maxwell knows who I am.
Well, you can just call me Jo.
Yo, respectfully, there is literally
no way I can make that happen.
Joanna's back here doing a master class
with the seniors,
because she's so famous.
Definitely not famous.
And because she's so famous,
she has this big self-tape.
- It's a same-day audition.
- Last time I read with Jo,
I got in trouble
for my voice
- being "stiff and distracting."
- Well...
So, I thought that maybe
you could read with her, Allie,
so I could go do literally anything else.
What?
- Beau...
- Uh-huh?
You don't just ask someone
to be your reader.
- There's an etiquette, fool.
- Mm-hmm.
Sorry about him.
I couldn't ask you to do that.
It would derail your entire day.
No, no, no, derail it, please.
Seriously, it is not a problem.
I would be honored
to read with the Joanna Maxwell.
This is it, folks.
The start of our
long-awaited game with St. A's
and their new center, Aaron Delaney.
And we're underway here in the first.
Hawks take possession.
Oh, shit.
Brutal hit from Aaron Delaney.
Seems the new guy's fitting right in with
St. A's legendary trash-talking bullies.
Whoa! How is that not a penalty?
Hawks regain possession.
Graham starts out
from behind his own net and...
Oh! Delaney says, nope.
He shoots... and beats
Simms's blocker side
for the goal.
Come on, Graham.
It's not fun if you don't fight back.
Fuck you.
Take it easy, princess.
Whoo!
Hey, come on, bro.
Shake it off. You got this.
Wellsy, where are you?
Just write, Hannah.
Nasty cross-check by Delaney.
Vipers are absolutely dominating
the Hawks right now.
Hawks can't play the zone.
Vipers collect the puck
in the Hawks' zone.
Are you kidding?
The Vipers are relentless.
There's is a slashing penalty
on St. A's 29.
-  Just write, Hannah.
- There's Delaney again.
What the actual fuck?
Delaney shoots.
Well, that wasn't
the first period I was looking for.
Graham, Delaney's shadowing you.
Move the puck. Look at Birdie and Dean.
We got two periods left.
Your turnovers are killing us.
Don't worry about us. We're good.
Fuck that. I'm not good.
Let's just work as a team
and try not to do it all ourselves.
- No more one-on-one sloppiness.
- I got it, okay? Fine.
Hey, cut the attitude, Graham.
I mean it.
Hey, Delaney's trying
to take you out of the game,
so take their defenders out, too.
As soon as the puck comes in,
- you just get rid of it.
- Who died and made you coach?
I'm out there, too, man.
Okay, then worry about yourself,
all right?
Okay, fine.
I don't know what your problem is,
but I suggest you do
whatever it takes to work it out.
Fucking quick.
Sorry. Sorry. Uh...
I-I couldn't be in my room, so I came.
And I-I heard.
Who was that you were playing?
It's actually an original.
Part of a series I wrote
when my son first went off to day care.
Kind of exploring the emptiness of time.
Wow. Y--
- You're incredible.
- Ah.
I would hope so.
That's why I'm here, right?
You okay?
Yeah, I finally get it.
When you said,
"Write music that lets people in."
Like, just now, I-I didn't know
it was about your son, but I felt it.
That's a sweet compliment.
Just having a hard time taking it,
because of the general melancholy.
Uh, it's...
It's just that I don't think
I could ever write anything
that comes close to doing that.
- Come on, that's not true.
- No, it is.
I-I can't do what you do.
Letting people in.
- Hannah--
- No, it's okay.
Um, I made a mistake trying to do this.
Anyway, uh, it's been an honor
to be a part of your class.
I really hope we can keep in touch.
Not on my student email,
because if I don't do the showcase,
then I-- I won't be here
next semester, but, um...
I'll send you my old one.
It's a Yahoo, for some reason.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold up.
Hannah, Hannah, Hannah,
Hannah, Hannah.
Just, if you don't come back here
right now, okay?
I'm still your advisor for as long
as you're here, so, talk to me.
Get your money's worth.
I have been doing this a while.
I mean...
Like, doesn't it hurt?
Doesn't what hurt?
Ripping yourself open over and over again.
Letting people see all the weird,
jagged pieces of you.
Is that what it feels like?
Yeah, well, it doesn't feel good.
I don't subscribe to the notion
that art has to be painful.
In fact, if done right,
allowing people into our truth,
that can even be healing.
Yeah, I don't-- I don't know about that.
In-- In my experience,
whenever I tell someone my truth, it...
it ends badly.
Well, that doesn't mean we have
to close ourselves off for good.
It doesn't?
No, that just means we have to cling
to the people who see us and smile.
There has to be someone like that
in your life, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, there is.
Then, with love, what the hell
are you doing here talking to me?
Taking up my rehearsal time.
Yeah, you're--
You're right.
Sorry. Um, I'm gonna...
Thank you. Thank you, Daveed.
Anytime.
Hey, hey, it's me.
Um, are-- are you okay?
Or did I-- did I do something wrong?
Just, you said you were coming,
and you're not here.
And I-I really wish you were here.
You always help me
get out of my head, and...
I could just really use a Coach Wellsy
pep talk right now, so...
Yeah, just...
Uh, if you could just
let me know you're okay.
I'm here.
Okay.
Heavy into the second.
Briar's trailing 3-1.
You can tell Graham is frustrated
with this incessant coverage.
- Move it!
- Fuck you!
Up, G.
- You got Logan!
- Come on, man! Get rid of it!
- You got Logan! Move it!
- Heads up, G!
- Can't keep up, Daddy's boy?
- Fuck!
-  Come on, then!
-  Woof.
Someone hold Garrett's hair back,
because he is getting sloppy.
Go! Go! Go!
Delaney banks the puck to himself
past Graham and breaks up the ice.
No! Fuck!
Delaney sends the puck
behind the Hawks' net.
The Hawks are on their heels again.
The pass comes out front
to Delaney, and...
Hey, we need the trainer!
What an absolutely brutal hit from Delaney
and a brutal end
to the second period for the Hawks.
Birdie sure got his bell rung.
Let's hope he's okay.
How you doing, Birdie?
Everything's so fucking bright.
Okay. You're not going back in.
Rogers, you're up.
I'm gonna put you on D for the third.
- Me?
- Yeah.
Just keep your feet moving. Di Laurentis.
Yeah, I'll look out for him, Coach.
- Fuck Aaron Delaney, man.
- There's no way that was an accident.
He knew exactly what he was doing.
Okay, guys, anything can happen
in 20 minutes.
Maybe we switch to a one-two-two
trap to really cut off their outlets,
amp up the pressure?
That won't work.
It doesn't matter what we do.
We were getting our asses kicked
before Birdie got domed.
- We know what the problem is.
- You got something to say?
You know you're locked off.
I told you to get rid of it.
- Logan, come on.
- No, everyone is thinking it.
Garrett Graham's got to do it all himself,
and now, we're down by two.
Stay in your lane, Josh.
Guys, come on. It's not that deep.
No, it fucking is for some of us, Dean.
It is that deep.
I'm not gonna let us lose this game,
because Phil Graham's son
gets to do whatever he fucking wants.
You don't know
what you're talking about.
- Come on.
- You gonna fight me now?
Hey! Calm down.
We're on the same team, G.
Don't you get that?
You're not the only one
who can play hockey.
who's been busting their ass,
and you're not the only one who wants
to beat these motherfuckers!
We are on the same team!
Logan, just give him a second
to calm down.
I don't need your fucking help, Tucker.
Fuck.
Hey.
Need a pep talk?
What's going on?
Are you okay? Where were you?
I'm fine.
- I called, but you didn't--
- No, I know. I'm...
I'm sorry. I should have texted.
I w-- I was dealing with something
that kind of took over for a minute there,
um, but I'm-- I'm here now.
You're dealing with what?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. Okay?
Just, you know, it didn't matter
as much as being here for you.
Please just text me next time.
I was worried about you.
I know. I know.
Okay, focus up.
Graham, what's going on out there?
Everything.
I'm playing like shit,
getting pressured like crazy,
making stupid mistakes.
Everybody's counting on me
to be in control,
but I just got in a stupid fight
with Logan, because...
Your dad's here.
With Cindy.
We can't let him win.
It gives him power.
This is how we win. We just--
We show up, and we live our lives.
Okay? We can do that.
Right?
Yeah.
And as for everything else,
we can just start with the small stuff
and work your way up.
Small stuff?
Yeah, whatever that means for hockey.
I guess the small stuff
could be stop playing like shit.
Okay, yeah. I can do that.
Delaney's kicking my ass, though.
Guy's a fucking monster.
Wellsy.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm...
I'm good.
I promise.
Okay.
Hey, Graham.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Graham and Delaney meet center ice,
ready to start the final period.
What? Nothing to say this time?
Delaney, you suck!
Hey, that hit was bullshit, man.
You all right?
- Yeah, yeah. Let's go.
- I got you.
Hawks in their own zone.
Vipers forecheck, recover the puck,
and get it back to the point.
Clutch deflection by Tucker
gets the puck back to Graham.
But can he get past Delaney?
Graham puts on the brakes,
spins and drops to Tucker.
- Tucker shoots.
-  Yes!
Scores! Hawks score!
Whoo!
Let's go! Yes!
Good pass, G!
Let's go!
Whoo!
I like that! I like that, Tuck!
Okay, Briar, looks like we've decided
to get off our knees and stop sucking.
And... cut.
Wow. Okay.
Holding back tears?
I mean, such a smart choice.
Beau wasn't kidding.
You really are
a much better reader than he is.
And you have cuter clothes.
Thank you for this, by the way.
You got it. Of course.
God, it is just so fun to be hanging out
with someone who's, like,
actually doing the thing, you know?
You're auditioning for a TV show
on your day off from Broadway.
It's so chic.
Oh, I think you'd feel differently
if you saw me hiding my pin curls
under an old baseball hat
with my falsies barely hanging on.
Ah, you've got to know
how cool that sounds.
Broadway's hard, dude.
It's... Like, I know I'm super lucky.
But, oh, my God, I'm also so exhausted.
I don't have time for anyone.
My dating life is in shambles.
That, I can relate to.
Ooh.
I smell token straight boy drama
in the theater department.
No, it's, like...
Okay, well, can we still
be peers in the industry
even if I tell you all my messy bullshit?
Oh, that's literally the only way
we'll be peers in the industry.
My ex, like, found out
I hooked up with someone
and just got, like,
all scrunch-faced and, like,
just basically accused me
of not being able to be alone.
Ugh.
Boys are so silly.
So, you fucked a little.
It's not like
you're in a new relationship.
Thank you. I've hooked up
with this new guy a couple of times.
But this isn't about him. It's about me.
- I am capable of being single.
- Yeah.
I mean, you're sleeping
with other people, too, right?
Totally.
- Except...
- Except, you're not.
It's okay.
It'd be different if you and this new guy
were texting all the time or had, like,
cute, gross nicknames
or something like that.
Oh, no, you do.
So, how long have you been
hooking up with new guy?
Like, a month... ish.
Bitch, I hate to break it to you.
You're in another relationship.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
Hey, I can see
I've caused some turmoil here.
We need to get off campus.
Somewhere with alcohol.
-  ID?
- Hey, can I do an old fashioned?
Thank you.
Nice fake.
Excuse me?
Just saying,
it's not the worst one I've seen.
Oh, no. No, this... This is real.
Please. I work at a bar.
I can spot one, like, five booths away.
Maybe you need any glasses,
because it's definitely not fake.
Your name is Carter St. James.
The Fifth.
Mm. Yeah.
Nobody's named that.
That's a name from Glee.
Well, I guess I'm lucky they don't ask
too many questions here.
There you go.
I guess I am, too.
What are you doing?
That guy was hitting on you.
So?
Look, you want to prove
you're not in a relationship?
The best way to do that is
to sleep with someone new
who you'll never see again.
I don't think hopping to yet another man
is the answer.
You're a relationship girlie, right?
The best way to get over that
is to have no-strings-attached fun.
But there legit has to be no strings.
And that guy has "no fucking strings"
written all over him.
I don't know, having sex with someone
and not getting to know them at all, like,
doesn't it feel a little...
Slutty?
- Yeah, that's part of it.
- I was gonna say "meaningless."
Allie, you're in college.
You have the rest of your life
to have meaningful sex.
Don't you want to know what being single
and slutty has to offer you?
Hey, you with the cheekbones.
Hey! Hey, hey, what are you doing?
♪Tonight, tonight,
tonight, tonight...♪
What's up?
If my friend wanted to have really hot,
meaningless sex with you,
but the only caveat was that you couldn't
learn anything about each other,
and you had to promise
not to call her after,
would you be cool with that?
Oh, yeah, most definitely.
Great. Buy her a drink.
This one's mine now.
♪And maybe I'll be your number one girl ♪
What do you say?
♪Tonight, tonight,
tonight tonight ♪
Coming out of the last time-out
with two minutes left,
it's looking real good for the Hawks.
Graham and Logan
have been having a blast out there.
We love that for them.
And more importantly, we love it for me.
- That's what I'm talking about.
- Let's fucking go, baby.
- Any final words of wisdom, Cap?
- Let's win this fucking thing.
- Let's go!
- Whoo!
-  This is it, folks.
It's looking like the last face-off
of the game.
Hey, man.
Everything they say is true.
Playing against you has been really fun.
Yeah, all right.
Graham, you know what's gonna
be even better than me beating you?
What's that?
Beating you in front of that lying slut.
Garrett! Garrett!
What are they going to do?
The NCAA?
Guess we'll find out.
Aren't you gonna
yell at me or something?
Why would I yell at you
if I need you to actually hear me?
- Coach...
- Garrett,
you're on the brink of greatness.
But I can't help you get there
if you're not in it for the right reasons.
And after that hot-headed bullshit?
I'm not sure that you are.
Either way, I won't condone
that kind of behavior on my ice.
As of now,
you're suspended for four games.
Garrett.
No, we have an agreement.
I don't win, you don't talk to me.
Clearly, this is an exception.
- Move.
- No, hang on. Just listen.
I'm proud of you.
- What?
- That was some tough old-school hockey.
I just got suspended.
Four games.
Yeah, that is not ideal.
But hey, it happens, right?
You get worked up. You lose your cool.
Part of the game.
But shit will rain down, though.
NCAA will be on your ass, but don't worry.
I'll call the Bruins.
I'll take care of this.
No one will keep
Phil Graham's son off the ice.
So, that's it, huh?
Excuse me?
As long as I have "Graham" on my back,
I can just beat people up
with no consequences
for the rest of my life?
Like you.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Yes, you do.
You know, I don't remember you
complaining about being a Graham
when you landed the best coaches,
when you got on the best teams
with the best equipment.
With the best bruises.
Right? Easy to write it off when your kid
plays such a violent sport.
I did what I had to.
That's fucking bullshit. And you know it.
I don't want to hear what a terrible dad
I was for making you tough.
For wanting you to have the best.
Oh, fuck you!
You don't want the best for me.
- It was never about me.
- Of course it was!
You're about to play for the Bruins.
I made that happen.
You can hate the name
on the back of your jersey all you want,
but it doesn't make you better than me.
It just makes you ungrateful.
I will never be like you.
You already are.
Stay the fuck away from me.
Stop calling. Stop coming to my games.
We're fucking done.
What the hell, Garrett?
I really can't do this right now.
Can you just please get in the car?
- No. What was that?
- Are you serious?
You're mad at me?
You lied to me, Hannah.
I didn't lie to you.
You did. You looked me in the eye
and told me you were okay.
You promised me you were okay.
You just had to make it through one game.
- Oh, my God.
- One hour. That's it.
I had to go back out there
and play against that piece of shit.
- Do you not trust me, or what?
- Garrett, you lost your shit on him!
- You didn't hear what he said.
- I know what he fucking said.
What? Did he call me a whore?
A liar? That I wanted it?
Who cares?
I heard it every day in high school.
I wasn't just gonna stand
there and listen...
- I was fucking defending you!
- Well, I didn't ask you to do that.
I didn't want you to.
I didn't want anyone to.
People in Ransom
didn't just turn on me, Garrett.
They turned on my family.
My parents lost friends.
My dad got fired.
You want to know why I didn't tell you?
It's because every time I tell someone
the truth, it fucks everything up.
It ruins people's lives.
And it happened again.
No, my life isn't--
No, tell me you didn't
just put your season at risk.
Your future with the Bruins.
How do you think that makes me feel?
You blow this all up for me.
What do you want me to say?
You want me to apologize?
Say I'm sorry? I'm not.
I could face that asshole a hundred times,
and one hundred fucking times,
I'd beat the shit out of him again.
Yeah, well that scares me, Garrett.
It scares me that you would risk
everything for me
when I'm telling you it's not what I want.
I worked so fucking hard
to put it all behind me.
I scare you?
What? No, what? Of course not.
- That's what you said.
- Garrett, you're not listening to me.
Fuck.
My dad was right.
Your what?
This is who I am, Hannah.
This is just how I'm programmed.
No, you're not. You're not Phil.
I am. I fucking am.
Do you think I like being like this?
You know, maybe
not right now, but someday...
you're gonna look at me the same way
Cindy looked at me.
And that would kill me, Hannah.
Garrett.
- Garrett!
- No, no.
I'm not good for you.
You shouldn't be...
This is over.
This needs to be over.
Just write, Hannah.
I just want you to write down
what happened...
in your own words.
Okay?
Han, honey, I'll tell you what.
I am missing my euchre partner
right about now.
Hanny, save me. I bet the house.
Dad says hi.
What's up?
Mom.
Han?
Is something wrong?
Yeah, my-my-my bike.
My-My bike is wrong.
Okay. We can fix the bike.
No, I don't think we can, Mom.
Is she okay?
Okay. Tell me.
Why can't we fix your bike?
Because...
Because, um...
Because I lost my scholarship.
I'm gonna need you
to connect some dots, honey.
No, I wasn't gonna tell you, because
I wanted to figure it out on my own.
Um, so I was--
I was gonna win the pop showcase
and get another scholarship.
But Garrett and I broke up,
because he played St. A's,
and he got into a fight,
and it's all my fault.
And now I have to walk home.
Okay. Okay. Breathe.
Breathe.
So...
a lot to unpack there.
Let's start with the small stuff
and work our way up.
Okay?
First off, let us figure out the money.
We always do.
Don't worry about the grant.
We will find a way for you
to be at Briar next semester.
How can I not worry about it
when it's my fault?
I'm the reason that you can't afford it
in the first place.
Like, I'm the reason
for the therapy bills and the lawyer.
I ruined your lives, and I-I'm sorry.
I'm-I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
What did you do wrong?
What?
Well, if you're feeling guilty,
then it must mean
that you did something wrong.
So, what is it, exactly?
Uh...
I should have...
You went to a party, sweet pea.
You were a high school kid
who had a drink, that's all.
You didn't do anything wrong, Hannah.
That night and everything that happened
after that is not on you.
There's nothing that you could've
or should've done.
And as far as ruining our lives...
I am fine, and so is your dad...
despite being terrible at euchre.
Yeah, he really-- He really is so bad.
He's the worst.
But I love him.
And we love you.
So, will you let us do our jobs
and take care of you?
Are you nodding?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm nodding.
Good.
So, how's your ice?
Oh, uh...
Yeah, it's good.
- Right.
- Good ice.
Okay, did you change your mind?
It feels like you changed your mind.
- No, no, no. I'm super into this.
- It's... that's...
- Okay.
- Promise.
Right.
You're kind of a shit liar.
Look, the benefit of being strangers
is you don't owe me anything, right?
You know...
It's really not you.
I-- You are very charming
and have the kind of body that suggests
you work out on federal holidays.
Well, I take Memorial Day off.
Only human.
Okay.
It's just...
It has recently come to my attention
that I'm a serial monogamist,
um, which I don't want to be.
You know, I love love,
but I also love sex.
And-And I don't want to not have one
just because I'm waiting for the other.
Sure.
Which is why
I became involved with someone.
- You have a boyfriend?
- Oh! Oh, my God, no, no. Can you imagine?
But we are at the very least something.
Like, some weird baffling thing.
More weird or baffling
than this conversation?
Okay, well, I am trying to explain
myself to you, Carter St. James.
Right. Sorry, sorry. Continue.
I want to have hot, meaningless sex.
- I do.
- Mm.
But the last time I tried,
I just ended up hurting someone
that I really care about.
So...
I just, like, I want to do it
the right way this time.
Yeah, I get that.
You do?
God, now I'm gonna have to go back
and tell the living theater legend
that I'm not fun,
and I can't be slutty.
Okay.
Here's what's gonna happen.
I'm gonna kiss you.
You're gonna kiss me back.
- Pull my hair. Just really sell it.
- Mm.
And then you can go back
to your clearly very invested friend.
And you can brag
about how hot and meaningless it was.
Okay?
One kiss, and I'm bragging?
Oh, it's gonna be
a really good fucking kiss.
Bullshit.
Only one way to find out.
♪How come we never even dated ♪
♪But I still find myself
thinking of you daily?♪
♪Why do you always leave me aching ♪
♪When you were never mine
for the taking?♪
♪How come we never even dated ♪
♪But I still find myself
thinking of you daily?♪
♪Why do you always leave me aching ♪
♪When you were never mine
for the taking?♪
♪I can't make you love me ♪
♪No, I can't make you love me, babe ♪
♪No, I can't make you love me ♪
Go the fuck off.
Making out with a hot stranger at the bar?
Who is she?
I am she. She is me.
I'm actually so proud I could cry.
You have to admit you had fun.
So?
I'm out four games.
Yo, what's going on with you, bro?
Where'd that come from?
I don't want to talk about it.
You never do.
Yeah, I just thought that,
you know, maybe...
You know, for a second there, I...
thought we were
on the same team again.
♪When someone tells me
they're from Massachusetts ♪
♪Now I always ask, "What part?"♪
♪I wonder if you kept
the pilgrim ashtray ♪
♪If it's still propped up
on your bar cart ♪
♪Could make a grand
off of the chain you bought me ♪
♪But goddamn, it's not for sale ♪
♪When someone asks me
who's my favorite Batman ♪
♪I'll think of you and say
"Christian Bale"♪
♪As long as I live ♪
♪I'll remember the names ♪
♪Of your favorite beers
and your video games ♪
♪The look on your face ♪
♪When you turned 26♪
♪And your dad got too stoned ♪
♪Yeah, that one's gonna stick ♪
♪You broke me to pieces
but I root for you ♪
♪Even though everything
went up in flames ♪
♪I'll never forget
how I bloomed for your gaze ♪
♪Or your wall of guitars
or your video games ♪
♪Or your video games ♪
♪Pick up your phrases ♪
♪Now I say, "It's aces"♪
♪But it always sounds so fake ♪
♪I wonder if your tongue is turning over ♪
♪Anything I used to say ♪
♪It's getting darker, so I turn you down ♪
♪But I can't turn you off ♪
♪Oh, oh ♪
♪As long as I live
I'll remember the names ♪
♪Of your favorite beers
and your video games ♪
♪The look on your face
when you turned 26♪
♪And your dad got too stoned ♪
♪Yeah, that one's gonna stick ♪
♪You broke me to pieces
but I root for you ♪
♪Even though everything went up in flames ♪
♪I'll never forget
how I bloomed for your gaze ♪
♪Or your wall of guitars
or your video games ♪
♪Or your video games ♪
♪At least I'm treading water
and not about to drown ♪
♪I'm not trying to find you, babe ♪
♪You're just around ♪
♪Everything reminds me of you ♪
♪Even now, even now, even now ♪
♪As long as I live ♪
♪I'll remember the names ♪
♪Of your favorite beers
and your video games ♪
♪The fire in my gut
that I've chased ever since ♪
♪You set the bar ♪
♪You're gonna stick ♪