GLORY
The toll has been collected.
SUMMER OF 2022
JAEPYONG BUILDING
CAUTION! SCHOOL
RTNNJ
SEMYEONG STREET, NO. 71
PARADISE APARTMENTS
Just moved in?
How are you?
You have finally arrived.
It took you a long time.
Welcome.
This flower is called the devil's trumpet.
The one they call the angel's trumpet
because he plays facing the ground.
And this one is called the devil's trumpet
because he plays facing the sky.
God thought it was rude.
Maybe that's why it only smells at night.
I have to break earthen pots
before I throw them away.
Yeon-jin, I miss you.
Do you remember
that I used to hate summer?
Fortunately, I moved away
before it got warmer.
I've been putting photos together since yesterday,
but I'm slow
because their faces are charming.
I started imagining
that you will one day
open the door and come in here.
What is all this?
This is Jae-jun and Sa-ra.
Photos of all of us.
Sorry.
Who are you?
It's me, Yeon-jin. It's me.
You haven't changed at all.
You're still rude.
You should take off your shoes
when you enter someone's home.
You gave me a new reason to kill you.
You should have at least recognized me.
To kill me?
You to kill me?!
Yes, I will kill you.
I will do my best to kill you.
So come quickly, Yeon-jin.
I'm already here.
Do you want to hear
how I became like this
while we wait for you?
An official report has been submitted.
Guardians must come. It's a procedure.
I'll just scold her, no worries.
Okay, I'll call you.
Park Yeon-jin.
-That?
- Why are you beating your friend?
Don't come for that again.
Your mother is coming.
We are not friends.
Let me ask you something.
What are you and my mom doing?
We are friends from school.
So you're her errand boy?
That's why you helped her with the divorce.
And gathered evidence of my father's adultery.
I thought you slept with my mom.
Let's go!
Deliveries are waiting! Get up and walk!
You embarrass me. I said you are not coming.
Everything will be fine if they make up and hug each other.
Sa-ra, come.
How can I help?
I am Dong-eun's guardian. Her class teacher.
Hey.
Did you come in your school uniform?
You called the police because of a simple dogfight?
The deputy director knows.
I'll deal with you later. Come.
Take me too.
I have been an orphan for seven days.
My parents traveled.
- They play golf.
- Don't?
You should have called me.
I'll take him too.
Good.
I was wondering why you were still here.
How do you eat?
- I have a housekeeper.
- Is it?
Today was an important day.
You have disappointed me greatly.
I didn't expect the police.
That's why I'm disappointed.
You couldn't solve the poor thing.
I told you
to only hang out with Jae-jun.
And Sa-rom.
The shaman told you
to avoid people with O in their name
because they bring misfortune.
I mean Son Myeong-o and Choi Hye-jeong.
Come in. We're running late.
MOON DONG-EUN
SUNGHAN SECONDARY SCHOOL
Here we have Dong-eun!
The same Dong-eun you see every day!
Welcome.
Sorry for harassing you.
I wanted to apologize.
You don't get angry anymore?
You shouldn't have called the police.
You scared us.
Speaking of which, Dong-eun,
will you be checking from now on?
is the curler hot?
Let me go!
This is a crime! Let me go!
You are doing us a small favor.
How is that a crime?
She already apologized to you.
I'm just wondering if he's hot.
Is it hot?
I think he's ready.
Let's see.
Help! Help me!
Don't bother.
Scream all you want. No one will hear you.
No one will come.
The professor gave us the keys.
Why are you doing this to me?
Why on earth are you doing this to me?
I'm sick of hearing that.
Why do they always ask that?
I do it because I'm untouchable.
Nothing changes for you.
Just look at yourself.
You made a fuss at the station,
and now you're here again.
Is there any change?
No one will protect you, Dong-eun.
Not the police, not the school, not even the parents.
What do we call such people?
Disenfranchised.
Do you live in a boarding house?
Because of you, I know what it means to live in a motel.
He must pay when the Moon is full.
Like in a fairy tale!
Dong-eun must be my good fairy.
He's checking to see if my curler is hot.
Let me go!
- Let me go!
- Shut up!
- Let go!
- Myeong-o, shut her up.
Let me go!
You are too loud in public.
IT'S BORING ME
Hydrogen peroxide?
Just give it to me.
I have a stain on my blouse.
What stain?
Maybe from the blood?
Give me hydrogen peroxide.
What happened? Who did it?
Did you tell your classmate?
I've seen a scar like that before.
If you can't do it alone,
I will go with you to report it.
Who did it?
Yes, mom?
I'll call you.
That's what I did.
And the one before that.
You know what, Yeon-jin?
Your daughter likes to look at the world upside down.
Does she think people will understand her
when the world turns upside down,
even mixed the colors?
You have the same shoes as my mom.
So it's you.
Park Yeon-jin's daughter, Ha Ye-sol.
You know my mom?
I think about her every day.
Hate sometimes resembles longing.
You can't get rid of her.
Hatred?
I don't know that word. What does it mean?
What does "hate" mean?
How funny!
What is it?
Are you going to run away?
Her eyes that darken when she is excited.
Where have you been for so long?
I missed you a lot.
A smile that stretches her lips.
Every hair of her wonderful hair.
When you add it all up,
you get a picture of hatred.
She took off her clothes before going in!
We're shit. Shame on us.
Move over.
Your piggy bank?
It was in a box with rice.
- I couldn't believe it.
- Give it back to me.
Oh, no.
Is Dong-eun angry?
Nicely caught.
It's full.
Seriously? How sad.
Dong-eun.
You are very thrifty.
Crazy scumbag. What did you take this time?
Syrup or glue?
Stop it! Don't do that!
Dong-eun is terribly rich!
- There are 200,000 won.
- You pay for all this?
You are rich! You don't need that money!
Please. Give it back to me, Yeon-jin.
I see you are being polite now.
Good.
I'll give you your money back.
But I want you to dance while we drink.
Then I won't even touch the money. Can you?
-What?
- Dance, I said!
Song and dance go well with alcohol.
What is it? You don't want to?
If you really don't want to, there is another way.
I found this here.
You're all in a coma.
But if you pretend to be proud,
you'll be in an even bigger coma.
So dance.
Humiliated.
If you don't want to, it doesn't matter.
When I saw you today, Dong-eun…
You have beautiful legs.
I'll pick a song.
I have many in my cell phone.
AMBULANCE
TEMPORARILY CLOSED
DUE TO THE DEPARTURE OF THE NURSE
Seriously? When?
I'll call you.
Dong-eun dropped out of school.
She put our names on the form.
She gave it to the deputy director,
who is bothering our professor.
From the body?
She listed us by that
who beat her more?
Which one am I?
This is serious, you understand?
Hey!
Jae-jun! Yeon-jin!
Come.
Crazy bastard!
If you want to leave, do it quietly.
And you haven't sinned anything? Nothing at all?!
If it happened,
something is wrong with you!
Please correct the form!
PRINT FORM
If the principal sees this,
it will affect your judgement, Mr. Kim.
I know that. Please.
What is this?
What is that reason?
Violence at school.
It's Yeon-jin's fault, Sa-ra's,
Jae-jun, Hye-jeong and Myeong-o.
You did nothing.
Tongue for teeth!
Did they break your arm or leg?
You don't have any broken limbs.
What kind of violence is that?
What do you mean, I didn't do anything?
You're crazy, you understand?
It's not terrible if friends slap each other.
And why is it okay?
slap a friend?
What?
You said
that your son is in teacher training college.
It's okay to be slapped by friends...
I was good to you.
And now you're looking for a beating.
What now?
you have to say
about my son?
Do it again! What did you say?
-Get up!
- Don't!
- Move. What did you say?
-MR. Kim!
-Get up! What did you say?
-Kim!
Stop it!
Move!
-Kim!
- Get out of my way!
Stop it!
-Kim!
-Get up!
NEW WORLD BARBERSHOP
Ms. Jeong, your cell phone is ringing.
Here I am.
- Don't!
- What happened?
Just a moment.
For God's sake!
Please?
That.
I am her mother.
Who's calling?
Here you go. Open it. It's okay.
Dear mother!
A MILLION WON
I also need my father's signature.
I'm not actually Dong-eun's father.
I'm like a father to her.
In that case,
you sign.
Sometimes legal issues are important.
I don't have a fancy signature.
- May I sign in block letters?
-Of course.
Sign up,
and then write the reason for printing again.
-Reason?
- Keep it short.
"Unconformity."
ROOM FOR RENT
What did you forget?
Didn't you know?
Your mom emptied the room this morning.
Dear God. This is your school uniform.
They will call you for sure.
She's your mom after all.
For God's sake.
SPACE GROUP
ARCHITECTURE AND SOCIETY
REASON FOR PRINTING: NON-ADAPTATION
GUARDIAN: JEONG MI-HEE
HEAVENLY GIMBAP
My scars itched.
I had in my stomach
strong menstrual cramps.
Then I thought of something.
The pharmacy only opens at nine,
and the Han River is 20 minutes away.
The water will be cold.
But then everything will be easier.
Scars will not itch.
What more could you want?
That will be the best.
Is there Dong-eun
pretty face?
From a man's point of view.
I don't know.
Don't be silly.
Not only her face is beautiful.
Why didn't you cover her mouth?
Move away. You are difficult.
Where are you going? For more drinks?
Hye-jeong will bring.
I would, if I were to go get a drink.
Morning mass.
My old man is going to get rid of the studio
if I don't come right away. Fuck it.
They have mass for the elderly.
I barely answered him not to invite you.
Do you want him to stop calling you?
How many white blouses do you have?
-Amen!
Jesus Christ said:
"If someone slaps you on the right cheek,
turn him the other."
-Amen!
"To the one who would like your petticoat,
leave the upper one to him as well."
-Amen!
"If someone forces you a mile,
go with him two."
-Amen!
- We believe in you, Lord.
-Amen.
How Sara's dad's voice broke!
You should have seen it!
Maybe he was shocked that he didn't see anything.
Come on.
I want chocolate milk.
Good.
- And you?
- Hye-jeong!
You know I'm fasting this week.
Hell.
Gyeong-ran.
When will you stop crying? Tomorrow?
Stop crying, you fucking bitch.
Damn, you're so loud.
Gyeong-ran, if you scream again,
I'll shove it in your mouth.
Where is she from?
She must be crazy. Did she come willingly?
You're going, Dong-eun.
I missed you terribly.
You left without a word.
Your dream that you described on Cyworld.
"A wise mother and a good wife." Did you mean that?
Did you seriously write that?
Where the hell did you get that?
Sarah wants to paint.
Jae-jun will get a golf course.
Hye-jeong will be a flight attendant.
You want to be a wise mother and a good wife?
What the fuck?
Why did you leave me out?
I have a dream too. I will be a millionaire.
I have no dream, Dong-eun.
Dreams are for people like you.
You, him and her.
When you make your dreams come true, you'll work for me.
I don't need sleep. I need a job.
Not a bad job.
I will probably marry young and beautiful.
I will choose a good man.
I will have one or two children.
And I will live happily ever after.
There is no word
which covers it all, doesn't it?
It exists.
Shit.
Shut up, Sarah.
You're so scary.
And you?
What are you dreaming about?
About you.
From today you will be my dream.
I really hope so
that we will meet again.
SUMMER OF 2006
Enough banter! Save it!
Don't be so strict!
Her hands and feet are full of cigarette marks.
Do your job.
GRADUATION RESULTS 2006
MOON DONG-EUN, YOU PASSED GRADUATION.
FALL OF 2006
2005 - MATHEMATICS
2006 - FINAL EXAM
FALL OF 2007
FALL OF 2008
Excuse me.
I didn't mean to bother you.
I am 20 years old. My name is Koo Seong-hee.
I heard that at the end of the month
you leave the factory.
I wanted to talk to you
before you leave.
Also. Thanks.
-On what?
- Why were you tiptoeing?
Did you see that?
Anyway, congratulations!
I heard you got into college.
You must be happy.
You can go on group dates and find a boyfriend!
That's not what I'm looking for.
I'm going to college because I have to go somewhere.
Where are you going?
To Samsung?
Hyundai?
I wasn't kidding, Yeon-jin.
From that day you were my dream.
SUNGWU TEXTILE FACTORY
The strongest coffee you have. Cold.
I feel sleepy.
Want a double iced Americano?
Okay, I'll take that.
Download counter.
Next, please.
Iced Americano and hot coffee with milk.
With lots of whipped cream
and chocolate crumbs.
We pay separately,
but stamp the coupons for me.
I expected that. I don't have a wallet.
- Damn it.
Pickup counter.
Next, please.
Grain to grain of bread.
Mr. Yeo-jeong.
-Coupon to scones coupon.
- How is that?
Help my brother.
You always say that, so I have to pay.
Let him grow up.
Good.
You can get rich with coupons.
I can't get rich with coupons.
How is that going anyway?
WELCOME, FRESHMEN OF THE CLASS OF 2009.
Welcome!
I kept thinking about it.
Where will I meet you again?
You have everything.
You are not afraid of anyone.
In which place I could scare you,
even for a second?
I couldn't think of another place.
My sports hall
has 60 square meters.
HA YE-SOL
That sounds like a fairy tale!
Now I'll take the curler
which is very soft and bright.
The one to whom
you care the most, Yeon-jin.
Is my story a fairy tale?
That. But I don't like it
because my mom is not the main character.
Why do you think that?
My mom is rich.
The main characters are always poor.
No, you're wrong.
In this story, your mom is the main character.
Our story is not a fairy tale.
It's a fable.
We consider fog to be thick
when the visibility is less than a kilometer.
A fog warning was issued yesterday
and it is still valid.
Did you know
that the greatest danger to a safe flight
nisu tajfuni ni munje, nego magla?
"Whoever injures his neighbor
let it be done to him as he has done."
Although the number of accidents is higher on clear days,
mortality is highest on foggy days.
Please beware of the fog.
I'm Park Yeon-jin.
"An eye for an eye",
tooth for tooth,
break for break.
The wound he inflicted on another
let it be given to him too."
I don't know.
That sounds too fair to me.
Do you agree?
Subtitle translation: Davor Fröbe