Sorry, I just went
inside your room
‘cause you weren’t answering.
Are you okay?
You look good.
You’re wearing our
engagement ring today?
I always do.
Can I call you, Maui?
Only my family
gets to call me that.
Why? Am I not family?
I’m your future husband,
to be exact.
Hey! Did you just
take a photo of us?
I was fixing my bra.
No, I’m not.
Girls, just let it go.
Naomi, can we talk? Please?
You know her, Sam?
Kind of, she's...
She’s my friend.
You really have to check, huh?
Of course, you believe
your friends.
You can’t even tell them
I’m your sister.
Do you need a hug?
Our friend here is really happy.
This is fun.
Shit!
He seems mad.
Bro, let’s order some milk.
- Go now.
- Go.
Take a shot first
to give you courage.
Go after him.
Why am I so worried
about his reaction?
I didn’t do anything wrong.
We’re not even a thing, right?
Unless...
He’s jealous?
But why would he be?
Come on, just take the shot!
Go.
Good luck!
Hey, there’s a chick.
Hey.
Hello! Ridge.
Clyden’s best friend.
Sam.
Sam?
Bro, I’ll just go
to the bathroom.
I really need to poo.
Okay, I’ll go with you.
Together?
What?
What “what”?
You came here to ignore me?
Huh?
Ignore you?
What makes you think
I’m ignoring you?
Just earlier.
The club’s too big.
It’s normal for us
not to see each other.
Fine, you’re not ignoring me.
You just don’t want
to talk to me.
I’m talking to you right now.
Okay.
Let’s get to the point, okay?
Before you jump
to any conclusions,
the guy I was dancing
with earlier is Sevi.
He’s just my friend.
Who’s asking?
I didn’t ask about him, right?
I just thought
you might be jealous.
Huh?
Me, jealous?
No way.
Okay, you’re not jealous.
Why didn’t you tell me
you’re coming?
If you stopped ignoring
my messages and calls,
then maybe you would know.
Oh my gosh!
I’m sorry.
I was just busy all night,
going around.
I didn’t mean to ignore
your text and calls.
I’m sorry.
What are you doing?
I’m right behind you.
Just answer it, please.
Hey...
I’m sorry I didn't answer
your calls earlier.
I didn’t mean it.
It’s okay.
Jeez. You just want
to be babied, huh.
What did you say?
I said,
thanks for coming!
Do you want to have a drink?
I don’t really drink.
I just came here to support you.
That’s all.
Just three bottles.
Please?
I don’t drink.
Two?
Maui.
Final offer, one bottle?
Fine, just one bottle.
So, how exactly
did you end up here?
I thought you were
going to study all night?
I thought so too.
But I finished all
my readings earlier.
You finished everything?
In one sitting?
Fast reader.
How arrogant!
Hi! I’m Jo...
Sorry.
I’m happily married.
Oops.
Okay.
You’re such a snob.
The poor girl.
I mean, it’s better than
just outright rejecting her.
So, I said I’m married.
And she’s not my type.
Oh yeah,
because I’m your type.
Are you drunk?
Why don’t you say “no”
if I’m not your type?
Because...
- Because what?
- Because you’re drunk.
Wait!
What’s that?
I wonder who that’s for?
I don’t know, maybe somebody
just left it there,
or they just forgot about it.
What a waste.
It’s so pretty!
The one who gave it
must be really sweet.
They brought
a bouquet to a club.
I mean, who does that?
Does what?
Those
cute and sweet things.
If that were given to me,
I wouldn’t let go of it.
So nice!
Cheers!
Okay...
I think it’s really time
to go now.
No.
I don’t want to. Just...
- No.
- One more.
- Maui.
- So cute!
One more!
Let’s go now.
Sam.
Here’s the playboy!
- Move, bro.
- Hold on.
I just want to
ask her a question.
Ask her tomorrow.
She’s drunk.
I think she can answer
my question better
when she’s drunk.
Sam...
Do you really not know
where Yanna is?
- Are you sure?
- Bro, that’s enough.
Don’t take advantage
of her state.
I hope you won’t either.
You know this guy?
The fuck!
What’s your problem?
Tell you what?
Why don’t you bring Sam
back to her friends?
Where are you
bringing her anyway?
- I’m bringing her home.
- Home?
Sam, do you know this guy?
I’m bringing my fiancée home.
- Do you have any problem with that?
- Fiancée?
Really?
Are you fucking with me?
Hey!
Shan, calm down.
He’s really my fiancé.
It’s okay. Look.
Don’t tell anyone, okay?
It’s a secret.
Are you sure?
I’m just making sure
you know this guy.
And you...
Now that you’re the last person
seen with Sam,
if anything bad
happens to her...
you're the first one
I'm coming after.
Let's go.
Okay. Bye!
Bye!
Be careful!
Why did we have
to go home so soon?
Look at yourself,
you’re already drunk.
One more bottle!
It’s still early!
Maui! No more drinking!
What? Do you want to get sick?
Sick?
Come on, doc,
I’m fine! See?
You’ve had enough,
believe me.
And you’ll get dehydrated,
that's bad for your kidneys.
Did you know your kidneys filter
the toxins in your body?
Including alcohol, by the way.
So if you overdo it,
they’ll really get damaged.
You’re so cute!
You’re so cute when you go
all medical on me.
I know I’m cute.
But, seriously,
prevention is better than cure.
Okay, doc.
Hydrate.
Okay.
More.
When you become a doctor,
and let’s say I get sick,
will you take care of me?
Of course.
But I’d rather
you don’t get sick at all.
So maybe ease up on the alcohol.
Okay, doc.
Do I smell like vomit?
‘Cause I just finished
throwing up.
No,
you smell good.
Can you feel my heartbeat?
It’s so loud and fast, right?
Are you sure it’s not mine?
You know...
It’s actually nice to have
someone beside me.
I used to have my best friend,
Yanna, you know?
And she was always there for me.
But now
that she’s living
in the province,
I just...
I just feel so alone.
I’m sorry.
I’m so sorry for
crying in front of you.
Hey, it’s okay.
It’s okay.
Don’t be sorry.
You can open up to me
about anything.
I may not be your best friend,
but I’m willing to listen.
Thank you, Cy.
You’re never alone, Maui.
Why are you being so nice to me?
When I first met you,
you were so rude.
I was rude because
I hate your family.
But…
But?
But you’re not your family.
Thank you, Cy.
And thank you for all the nice
things you did for me tonight.
You’re welcome.
Okay.
It’s already late.
Get some rest and
don’t forget to hydrate, please?
Okay, goodnight.
Shit!
I want something... demure.
Oh my god.
What the hell did I do?
So there’s a house party
this weekend.
It's the birthday of
a friend of a friend.
Wait.
Hey, Sam. Are you okay?
Right, what’s going on
with you today?
Huh? Nothing.
What were you saying Nicole?
She said that there's
going to be a house party.
Basically, everyone in the
social circle is invited.
You’re not listening.
Are you thinking of something?
Or thinking of someone.
Right, are you thinking about
that guy from last night?
Is he the one
who’s hard to read?
Is he your new boyfriend?
Is he already your boyfriend?
I don’t even know
what he is to me.
We’re engaged but it’s fake.
We’re not lovers, but
we’re not really friends either.
Wait, you guys are asking
too many questions.
All right, let’s go with this...
Is he your new boyfriend?
What? No!
He’s just
someone I know.
Really? Just someone you know?
Or someone you want to know
more and more and more?
Right? That’s different.
Wait! Oh my gosh!
What?
I think I know him.
Is he Clyden Ramirez?
Huh? You know him?
Yeah. Of course, I know him.
I have this friend,
she’s a med student too,
and she’s always raving
about how good-looking,
hot, handsome, all that,
and smart he is!
And she’s totally
obsessed with him.
Apparently, he’s pretty well
known around med schools
in Manila.
Really?
Tell me more. What else
do you know about him?
Well, he’s not exactly known
for being super friendly.
He mostly keeps to himself,
but he’s always with two people.
Two people?
His best friend, Ridge,
and some girl I don’t know.
She’s really pretty. Tall,
smart and in med school.
They do study sessions,
classes, everything!
I know Ridge. But the girl?
Who could it be?
I wonder who that girl is.
Who is she?
What does she look like?
Is there something going
on between them?
He has an account now.
Of course, it’s private.
Is this from last night?
Review time!
Okay, Eva. It’s your turn.
Okay, you ready?
- Ready.
- Go, Cly!
- Okay.
- Let’s go!
What is the primary function
of the loop of Henle
in the nephron?
The loop of Henle
is for water reabsorption,
and helps establish
the concentration gradient
in the kidney,
which allows for production
of concentrated urine.
- So smart.
- You’re good!
- So she’s smart.
- Ridge, expound.
He has never called me smart.
What's important
is that God loves me.
Lord, thank you! Amen!
Happy Birthday to the most
brilliant, kind-hearted,
and amazing person I know.
Grateful to have you and for
everything you’ve done for me.
Cheers to many more years
of memories together!
Wait, is there something
going on between them?
Why am I feeling like this?
First, I kissed him
on the cheeks.
Now, I’m feeling jealous?
No, I’m just confused.
This is nothing.
Oh my gosh he’s here.
I’m not ready to face him yet.
Maui!
Didn't see you there.
Hi! Hey!
I was just outside
getting some fresh air.
Are you still hungover?
Yes, I actually have
a headache now.
Last night just got a little
out of hand, I guess.
Probably the alcohol talking.
Whatever happened, just
forget about it, seriously.
Forget about what exactly?
What do you want me to forget?
Nevermind.
So...
So?
So, have you eaten yet?
Yes. Actually, I’m full.
I ate with Eva
before I went home.
Eva, huh?
Okay. Actually, I'm full too.
Okay.
Why does it bother me so much?
I’m not supposed
to feel this way.
Damn! Do you guys
know how wild
the party was?
Sam here was so hyper!
She was sexy dancing with Sevi,
and Sevi was just
standing like a statue.
He was disgusted with Sam.
It’s too bad we didn’t
get to witness that.
Right, it’s been a while since
we all went out together.
What do you expect?
Yanna hasn’t been around.
- Where is she?
- Right.
Do you know
what happened to her?
Yes, where is she anyway?
Is she avoiding us?
Should I tell them?
It’s better if it will
come from Yanna.
Girls, she’s just
going through something.
And I think she
needs some space.
Going through something or
is she ghosting us?
Luna, it’s not like that.
You know something
about ghosting?
It’s when they’ve seen
your messages,
then pretend
there's a problem...
and then you find out
they're a cheater!
They already have another girl.
That's it!
I think this is about
something else.
Right?
But really, that's
actually a big red flag.
Whether it's in a
relationship or friendship,
ghosting is never okay, right?
True! If you're done,
just say it properly, right?
Not just ghosting
out of nowhere.
I have a question.
Speaking of red flags...
Do you think a guy
is a red flag if
he is hanging out
with two girls at a time?
Looks like this is
about something else, too.
It depends.
What do you mean by hanging out?
Well, I know a guy
who is normally
grumpy
but he’s being nice
and sweet to two girls.
Is he leading them on?
Backburner!
- Backburner?
- Backburner!
For example.
A guy has two girls.
He’s keeping the second one
as an option.
So, if the first one
doesn't work out,
he goes to the second one.
Backburner.
And where did you read that?
Dude, it's true. Legit.
I mean, I'm just telling you
guys so at least you don't...
What do you call it?
So you don’t become
colorblind to red flags.
Wow, you managed to
squeeze that back in, huh?
Why? Who’s...
Who’s the guy? Why’d you ask?
It’s nothing.
A guy from school and...
he’s doing that
to one of my friends!
No big deal.
What time are you coming home?
Hey, I’m just curious.
Who’s Eva? Why are you
always hanging out with her?
I don’t need to know.
It’s not my business.
We’re not a couple.
Naomi’s Birthday -
seven days left!
It’s like, we’re a thing. But also...
They’re talking...
- I’ll talk to you.
- Something like that.
I’m playing safe with you.
- Where are you?
- I know Naomi likes photography,
so I hope she loves
her birthday gift.
Maybe shoes, but
you don’t have to.
Is that Naomi with Jaron?
Really?
I know him.
He’s a schoolmate,
a year younger than me.
Naomi’s turning eighteen.
She can date whoever she wants.
But...
last time I checked,
Jaron is dating Raylee’s sister.
So what the hell
is he doing with Naomi?
- Promise.
- Okay, sure.
So,
how are you and Cy?
We're fine.
Nothing’s changed.
By the way, look.
Pretty bag, right?
Do you like it?
Mom, that’s way too
expensive for a bag.
Jeez, Maui.
Limited edition or luxury bags
are just like love...
- Here we go…
- or relationships,
it's hard to find.
Impossible to forget,
and totally worth the search.
So, you really have to value it,
and you have
to take good care of it.
Okay, Mom.
By the way,
I think Naomi is going
through something.
I don’t really care.
How could you not care, Mom?
She lives in the same
house as you,
and she needs attention,
especially motherly love.
Oh my gosh.
Maui, I’m not her mother.
And besides,
her mom died because of her.
Mom, do you even hear
yourself right now?
Of course, I hear myself.
It's true. Her mom died
because of her.
Because that kid wanted to
go swimming at the beach.
I have to make this call.
Hello?
Patrick?
Can I speak with Hannah?
I want the bag.
What do you mean, waiting list?
Where’s Hannah?
May I speak to Hannah?
Hannah! Yes.
Yes, I want the bag.
The White Ostrich. Yes!
Now.
Naomi.
Naomi!
Naomi, can we talk?
Oh my god.
I’m sorry.
Hey, it’s fine.
It's fine, don’t worry.
Why are you here?
I wanted to talk to you.
About what?
I saw you with Jaron.
Is there something going on
between the two of you?
No, we’re just friends.
I’m just concerned about you.
I know Jaron is
dating someone else.
Please, don’t meddle
with my relationships
with other people.
I'm not a kid anymore.
I can make decisions for myself.
Even though it will hurt you?
Everything hurts me, Sam.
I’m already numb.
So, please stop acting
like you care about me.
Stop protecting me.
I really care about you, Naomi.
Maui.
How’s your wound?
It’s better now.
Let me see.
Does it feel cold?
Actually, you should
see a doctor,
to make sure you
didn’t damage any nerve.
I will.
Okay.
Cy...
random question.
Why did you want to be a doctor?
Was it because of your family?
It was at first.
Charles used to
physically hit me
when we were kids.
Oh no.
I’m sorry you went through that.
Thanks.
I didn’t tell
my parents about it.
That’s why
I learned how to treat myself.
And it also occurred to me that
I’d rather help other
people than myself.
Kids, especially.
That’s why you chose pediatrics?
I wanted to help
people in all aspects..
Fighting against injustice,
standing by those
who can’t defend themselves,
donating,
providing medical care.
Whatever I can do to help.
I have the privilege to do so.
I don’t want to just
close my eyes and act
like nothing’s happening.
Anyway, you should
get some rest.
I’ll prepare dinner tonight.
You’re cooking?
Yes.
I’ll just call you
when it’s ready.
Okay. Thanks, Cy.
Let’s eat!
Thanks for cooking.
You’re welcome.
I do enjoy cooking.
It's a mental break from all the
memorizing and studying.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Let me.
I’m sorry.
It’s okay.
Go.
Okay, let’s eat.
Yes.
Sam.
Let’s mate.
Huh?
I think we should mate.
Let’s date.
What?
Are you serious?
What do you mean date?
As in...
date romantically?
Yes. Let’s make this work.
What do you mean?
What are we going to work on?
Our non-existent relationship.
I mean, if you want to continue
living with each other,
then
we should make this work.
So,
you want us to date?
Let’s hang out.
Hang out?
Yes, hang out.
I mean, for example,
I cooked so
we could eat together
and hang out like this.
He’s so confusing.
For example.
A guy has two girls.
He’s keeping the
second one as an option.
So, if the first one
doesn't work out,
he goes to the second one.
Backburner.
Maybe Luna’s right.
Maybe I am the backburner.
First of all,
don’t say “date me” so casually.
Hanging out and
dating are different, okay?
Especially mating.
Check your dictionary.
Second,
don’t worry about us
continuing to live together.
I’m moving back to
my condo next week anyway.
And lastly,
aren't we breaking
the engagement?
Isn’t that the deal?
Wait.
So, you’re moving out next week?
Yes.
I see.
I understand.
I’m just going to stay here.
The dogs can’t live with me
in a condo, so...
We’ll just stay here.
Do what you want.
And as for the deal,
yes,
it’s still on.
Good.
Better to keep things clear.
Ridge is calling.
Excuse me.
Hello?
All right, bye now.
Fine then.
Cheers!
Are you sure it’s okay
for us to be here?
Of course!
It’s an open birthday party.
I’ll introduce you
to the birthday girl.
Elle!
- Hi!
- Cheers!
Hi, girls!
- Hi!
- This is Elle,
she goes to our neighbor school.
Elle, these are my friends,
Sam, Raylee and Ayessa.
- Hi! Happy Birthday, Elle!
Thank you so much girls!
Nice to meet you.
Elle!
Birthday girl!
OMG, it’s Eva!
She’s really pretty. Tall,
smart and in med school.
They do study
sessions, everything!
So, have you eaten yet?
We ate with Eva
before I went home.
Thank you!
I decided to get a drink.
Yes, sure. Go ahead!
Hi, girls!
- Hi, Eva!
- Hi!
They’re my friends.
It’s so nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, too.
- Enjoy the party!
- Bye!
Well, enjoy the night. Bye!
So, she’s Eva.
She’s pretty.
She doesn’t even look stressed
even though she’s
always up late studying.
If she’s here,
maybe he’s…
- There we go.
- Got it. Cheers!
…here.
What a joke?
He said he never
takes his ring off.
You’re wearing our
engagement ring today?
I always do.
I don’t know why this is
bothering me so much.
I’m not even wearing my ring.
But he said
he never takes his off.
But when he’s with Eva,
he doesn’t wear it.
What a lie.
Hey, cheers!
Are you okay?
I’m good.
It’s good.
Right?
Girls, I’ll just go
to the restroom.
- Okay.
Hi, girls!
Cy.
Relax, Sam. It’s okay.
It’s nothing.
There’s nothing.
I hate him!
I’m okay!
I’m okay.
Hi!
Bye!
Why are you here?
My friend is a friend
of the birthday girl,
so she invited us.
Okay, so let’s just
go home together.
No thanks.
I’m with Raylee.
You can drive your
friends home instead.
I think they’re drunk.
What’s your problem?
Nothing!
Go, drive Eva home.
Eva’s not going anywhere
‘cause this is her house.
And the birthday girl
is her sister.
Well, good for you then.
What’s your problem?
Are you jealous?
Where’s your ring?
Why did you have to lie
and say you never take it off?
What?
Why are you asking me
about my ring?
You’re engaged to me!
I know.
So, where is it?
Hey!
What’s up with you?
- Nothing.
- You’re all smiles today.
You know, I've noticed you've
been quite distracted.
Are you thinking of Sam?
Jeez! No use in denying it, bro.
I can see it on your face.
You like her.
So what are you waiting for?
Ask her out already!
You better hurry, or someone
else might beat you to it.
Bro, how can you say I like her?
That’s just your opinion.
Opinion?
This is Ridgen Alcazar
you’re talking to, bro.
I have hard fucks.
Hard what?
Fact. Fucks.
Same thing.
They’re both hard, bro.
Cy,
your studies are
your top priority. Right?
But ever since you
started living with Sam,
a lot has changed.
Including you.
You became more…
Considerate.
- Huh?
- Huh, my ass.
I said so much and
all you can say is, huh?
Here,
do you check if she’s eaten?
If she got home safe?
Do you ask how her day went?
You’re like a machine
when you're studying, Cy.
But now?
You get distracted so easily.
And you know why?
Because you like her.
Yeah, boy!
Bro, think all you want.
I’m just being nice.
Nice?
After all the time
we’ve spent together,
do you really think being nice
is even in your vocabulary?
Of course.
As if.
And hello, man of few words?
Just confess already,
before it’s too late.
Okay…
Sam, date me.
Let’s make this official.
So bad. That’s way
too straightforward.
Let’s date.
Let’s take things
more seriously now.
Let’s make it official.
Wait, how do I even say this?
Sam, I think we should...
take things seriously now.
So awful! What are you
even saying, Clyden?
Sam.
Let’s mate...
- I think we should mate—
- Huh?
Let’s date.
What?
Ridge is calling. Excuse me.
Hello?
Cy, how was it?
Did you do it?
Did you confess?
I tried, but I got cut off.
And she didn’t respond
the way I hoped.
Ridge, I think I messed up.
That’s ‘cause you
didn’t ask for my help!
But seriously, maybe it’s
just not the right time yet.
The moment will come
when you won’t be able
to hold it in anymore.
Yes. Maybe you’re right.
Bro, it’s your chick.
What chick?
Sam!
Follow her.
Where’s your ring?
Why did you have to lie
and say you never take it off?
What?
Why are you asking me
about my ring?
You’re engaged to me!
I know.
So, where is it?
You have no reason
to be jealous, Sam.
I’m not hiding anything.
Why would I?
All I ever think about
is you. Always.
Damn, I want to
kiss you right now.
I already moved out
from our house.
Really?
What if Clyden comes
to pick you up?
Are you going to say no?
Hey, Adi!
Remember the time when
you said you have a friend
who’s interested in meeting me?
Yes. Lewis.
Can you set us up for a date?
Why are you here?
I missed you.
Sam!
Your boyfriend?
You're not even
wearing your ring.
What?
I always wear it.
It’s always around your neck.
Fine.
I’m going to wear it.
See?