[The construction site of Rongcheng Group]
Gai,
what did you do to offend the boss?
Who said I offended the boss?
Then why did you get sent to
the front line?
Yeah.
"Front line" is a good way to put it.
They even matched you
with a job that suits your profession.
Come on.
Even if I explain it to you,
it's pointless.
Let me tell you,
not everyone
can understand
the boss's good intentions.
You know?
Is it this truck?
Yes, yes, this one.
Do I have to open the door myself?
Coming.
Gai, please.
Watch out, Gai.
You're rusty.
Indeed.
Gai, take care.
Put it here.
Here.
Okay.
Listen,
don't say I didn't warn you.
You guys,
if you take care of me properly
during this period,
this is a crucial chance
that could change your future.
Got it?
We must serve Gai well.
Yes.
We'll definitely take good care of you.
Everyone, pay attention.
Recently, someone has been
scattering nails on the road again.
Be careful when driving.
Come, let me take a look.
The tires are punctured.
It's too dangerous.
My god,
how wicked.
Pay attention.
Go.
Rest assured, Gai.
All right, get to work.
Get to work.
[Born with Luck]
[Episode 10]
If Zheng Yongbing is
really the man we're looking for,
he is upstairs right now
doing who knows what.
And we can only sit in the car,
staring out the window feeling helpless.
How about I go up
and take a look right now?
You can't go alone.
If you're going, we go together.
You keep an eye out here.
I can handle it alone.
I'm a veteran cop.
I know what I'm doing.
Besides, for something like this,
I can't let
a girl take the risk.
Song Xing.
Li Qian,
know your place.
Miss, come out quickly!
-What kind of crappy elevator is this?
-You scared me.
It's broken again.
Call the property management.
Have them come fix it immediately.
There are so many photos—
I don't believe
we can't find a clear one.
In his home
it's like a constant feast,
with the earth's milk,
the lush green of forests,
and the tears of the ocean.
But,
my friend,
don't envy that kind of evil man.
One day,
the earth's milk…
The earth's milk…
The earth's…
At his age,
a decline in memory
is normal.
Milk.
Beer.
Hello, Chief.
Didn't you say Zheng Yongbing
is on a diet?
His breakfast and lunch are so plain.
Why did he buy
so much meat
and beer for dinner?
There's someone else in his room.
You and Song Xing stay put.
We'll be right there.
But Song Xing...
Stay put.
Understood?
Understood.
Sorry.
The subscriber you dialed
is temporarily unavailable.
Liu!
Sit down.
Come.
You must be hungry.
There aren't any good dishes.
Just have something simple.
Help yourself.
Come.
Liu,
what exactly did you
come back for this time?
To be honest,
someone specifically
invited me back
to close a big deal this time.
A big deal?
What is it?
Bianzhong.
A full set of nine.
My goodness.
If you get caught,
that's a death sentence.
And if I don't get caught?
If I don't get caught,
I can make 800,000 yuan.
Wait, Liu.
I mean,
coming back this time
is too risky.
I heard the police
have a 50,000  yuan reward out for you.
I really need the money.
Otherwise I wouldn't risk my life
for 800,000 yuan.
This time coming back to Sanjiangkou,
I didn't even dare to
take public transport.
I was afraid someone would recognize me.
You see,
I came back on a coal train.
I didn't dare to go to a hotel either.
So I had to come to you.
My life
is in your hands, brother.
Don't worry.
It's absolutely safe here.
I believe it.
I'm relieved.
When this is over,
I'll reward you handsomely.
Don't mention it.
Sorry,
the subscriber you dialed
is temporarily unavailable.
Please redial later.
What's going on?
Liu,
there's another advantage here.
No one ever comes looking for me.
It's fine.
I'll go take a look.
Who is it?
Excuse me, Mr. Zheng.
The downstairs tenant reported
that there's a leak in their apartment.
They suspect it's a problem
with your bathroom,
so I came to check.
Okay.
I'll go to the bathroom now
and check it out!
Come in.
It's the property management.
I don't really know them.
How about I go down and take a look?
What if it's really leaking?
Okay.
You go.
The bathroom is indeed leaking.
Is the leaking water
blue?
It seems a bit blue.
Sorry.
We will report it for repair right away.
And you are?
I... I am his friend.
Why don't you
call Mr. Zheng out,
and we can go downstairs together
to take a look?
He's inside turning off the water valve.
It's dripping inside.
Otherwise,
you can come in and take a look first.
Please come in.
After you.
Come on.
Let's check the bathroom first.
It's right over there.
Can I ask you a question?
Let's fix the leak first
and check the bathroom.
Don't be in a hurry.
After you answer my question,
I'll go wherever you want.
Speak.
Mr. Zheng,
he wasn't in the bathroom, was he?
He was lying in that room.
If I hadn't been taking a shower,
I would have been killed by you guys.
You were so eager for me
to go to the bathroom,
you must have had bad intentions.
[First Inpatient Department]
[Incoming Call: Mentor]
The department plans
to make an exception and promote her.
She needs a year of training.
Keep an eye on her.
Don't let anything happen to her.
Your phone is ringing.
[Incoming Call: Mentor]
Wait, your phone is ringing.
I know.
G- Go quickly.
Chief Qi,
how is the situation?
The suspect Zheng Yongbing
took a hit to the head.
It shouldn't be a serious issue.
I didn't ask about him.
How is Li Qian?
Come with me.
[Incoming Call: Mentor]
Chief Zhang, your phone is ringing again.
I know.
Who is it?
Answer it.
It's just a superficial cut—
four stitches.
Then why is she still in a coma?
Her blood pressure, heart rate, breathing—
everything
came back normal on the tests.
[Incoming Call: Mentor]
What exactly is going on?
When we first came,
she was fine.
With such a big incident,
I guess she's afraid of being criticized,
so she's faking it.
It's like this.
If it's a real coma,
the eyeballs won't move.
If it's fake,
when exposed to light,
the eyeballs will definitely avoid it.
Please pry her eyelids open.
No need,
you can just shine the light directly.
Hello, Mentor.
Zhang Yi'ang,
what's going on?
Before you left,
what did I tell you?
Mentor, you're so well-informed.
Say hello to Director Gao.
Mentor, don't worry.
Nothing happened;
Li Qian is perfectly fine.
How can I not worry?
Hearing that from you
makes me even less reassured.
Cut the crap.
Start a video call.
I need to see it myself.
That's enough.
Mentor,
look.
[Switch to voice chat]
Why isn't she moving?
You call this "fine"?
I won't pursue
your unauthorized action this time.
Director Gao!
[Switch to voice chat]
Li Qian.
How is it? Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Has the suspect's identity been found out?
The surveillance footage is too blurry
to make out his face.
We were just about to
conduct an intensive interrogation
when Zheng Yongbing
started pretending to be unconscious.
I can tolerate Li Qian faking a coma.
Can I tolerate Zheng Yongbing faking one?
Chief Qi,
anyway, Li Qian is fine.
You should go back early.
Well...
How do you
plan to interrogate Zheng Yongbing?
I have to make him talk.
Calm down.
Make sure you don't break the rules.
As long as the facts exist,
the masks will be torn off.
Don't worry.
Thanks for your hard work.
Okay.
Which room? Let's go.
[Inpatient Department]
♪ Snow blankets the Volga River ♪
Did he move?
Yes.
His eyes didn't move on my side.
It did on mine.
Peel his eyelids open.
Wait, did I go to the wrong room?
What's his condition?
Blunt-force injury with a laceration.
He's had four stitches.
Then why is he in a coma too?
His blood pressure, heart rate, breathing—
all test results
are normal.
So we've moved directly
to this stage.
For a situation like his,
how can I wake him up immediately?
There are many ways.
But...
Let's talk outside.
Put it away.
Sit.
Get out of the way.
You got nerve.
Who hit you over the head?
I don't know.
No.
I don't know him.
You don't recognize him,
but he goes to your place to eat?
He's... He's just a customer
at the store.
He occasionally asked me out for a drink.
That's how we met.
I call him Liu.
That's...
That's all I know.
Liu's his full name?
Liu Bei.
Is his courtesy name Xuande?
You better behave!
"Bei" as in "houbei"?
It's "Bei" as in "houbei".
"Bei" as in "beihou".
This
Bei.
Is that Liu Bei—
the tomb raider
who scams scammers?
You even know this, Chief Zhang?
He's a fugitive wanted
under a Ministry of Public Security order.
The department has been
tracking him all these years.
A few years ago, this Liu Bei
set up a Ponzi scheme.
Impressive.
He claimed
he had already tunneled into
the burial chamber
of First Emperor of Qin's mausoleum.
Many people lost their life savings
to his scams.
Families were ruined.
A few people were upset,
went looking for him,
and he stabbed two of them to death.
You've got a whole archive in your head.
Does... Does this count as
harboring a wanted criminal?
It definitely counts.
No.
I... I didn't want to!
He suddenly came to me.
He's a reckless guy.
How could I refuse?
Harboring a wanted criminal is now...
It is punishable by up to
three years in prison,
or criminal detention
or public surveillance;
in serious cases, it's three to ten years.
No.
Officers!
I don't want to go to jail!
I know the policy.
Ask whatever you want.
As long as I know,
I'll tell you everything.
I was really threatened by him.
Where is he now?
I don't know.
But I know
he arrived by hopping on a coal train.
He took a shower at my place,
leaving black water everywhere.
Why did he come to Sanjiangkou?
He said
someone wanted to
buy a set of bianzhong from him.
He had the bianzhong.
He was acting as a middleman this time.
He said after it's done,
he'd get a commission.
Do you know the transaction amount?
I don't know about that.
Is that all?
That's all.
But according to our intel,
you're involved in more than just this.
What else is there?
I'll be honest with you.
That matter has been traced to you.
Otherwise,
did you think we invited you
for dinner today?
We didn't come here today
for Liu Bei.
He's just a side note.
We are here for you.
Go on.
You speak, or I speak?
I'll say it then.
I… I did suspect
there was something wrong with those two.
Are you done?
Tell us the whole process, okay?
Not long ago,
two men in their thirties
suddenly showed up at my door
and asked if I wanted to buy some stuff.
They gave me some gold jewelry
and a fake God of Wealth statue.
I suspected at the time
that the stuff was stolen.
But they threatened me with a knife.
Officers.
I'm a victim too.
Why are you always getting threatened?
Exactly.
I'm just
out of luck.
And then?
Then,
to cut my losses,
I sold the stuff.
To whom?
Zhou Qi,
the PR manager of
Fenglinwan Nightclub.
And that fake God of Wealth statue—
I sold it to Hu Jianren
from Rongcheng Group.
I got 60,000 yuan for it.
What about the people who sold it to you?
Find someone immediately.
Based on Zheng Yongbing's description,
get the sketches of these two suspects
done first.
Okay.
Where is Song Xing?
Chief.
Song Xing.
Li Qian was afraid you'd be in danger,
so she went in.
Right?
No.
I didn't want her to take risks,
so I didn't let her go up.
But later,
I have no idea
why she went up by herself.
Talk less.
Did you find anything at the scene?
Yes.
Chief,
this is the suspect's backpack.
[Jinshui Pavilion]
There are only a few clothes inside.
It's cursive script.
Hegegao.
Jinshui Pavilion.
It should be pronounced Jinshui Pavilion.
Song Xing, come here for a second.
[Inpatient Department]
Look what you've done!
What are you laughing at?
[Protect the environment,
safeguard our home.]
Do I have to teach you how to open a door?
No need.
I'll open it for you.
[Protect the environment,
safeguard our home.]
This is exhausting.
Sit.
Tea?
Coffee?
Come, have some snacks.
Spit it out.
Kai,
I wasn't joking about
what I told you last time.
No, no.
Let me finish.
What's the rush?
Have a seat.
This matter is extremely important to me.
You know
I am someone
who has always been upright.
You are just stupid.
You've got such a good position
and you don't even know how to
line your own pockets.
No wonder my sister divorced you.
I guess it's just my personality.
Right now, a bunch of corrupt officials
want to oust me
and transfer me to the provincial capital.
Then,
they'd use
the position of
Director of the Administrative Committee
to line their own pockets.
Tell me,
how could I let them succeed?
As for making money,
you can work together.
No.
I absolutely will not do such a thing.
The only way I can think of
to stop them right now
is to have you...
No.
Please
injure me.
If you think
I didn't pay you enough last time,
you can take any
of the old furniture
and antiques in my house,
whatever you want.
I don't collect junk.
My ancestors had some money.
These are all genuine
antiques.
Slow down.
If this was really made of
yellow rosewood,
then it would indeed be valuable.
But with your cheap firewood...
But what if it really is
yellow rosewood?
If it really was yellow rosewood,
my sister wouldn't have
divorced you.
Okay.
Alright, so these pieces of furniture
aren't worth much—
you probably don't care for them.
I am a man of culture.
These paintings
and calligraphy on the wall
must be worth something, right?
Kai,
pick any painting
you like at home
and take it.
What about this one?
Good eye.
It's by Guo Bin.
Look at this handwriting.
And who is that one by?
By Ding Guanpeng.
I also have one by Wen Zhengming.
I'll go get it for you.
Wait a minute.
Who is this one by?
That one is a fake.
It's a fake, not worth anything.
Let me see.
Yu Yueran?
I've heard of this person.
His calligraphy is very valuable.
Yes, the real ones are valuable.
This one is a fake.
It's not worth anything.
I want this one.
It's fake.
I like fakes.
Okay?
Okay.
Well, tonight,
I'll break your arm
at the entrance of the committee office.
It takes a hundred days
to recover from a broken bone.
At that point, who's going to force you
to transfer to the provincial capital?
Even with your arm in a sling,
you can still go to work.
What do you think?
If you think it's suitable,
I definitely have no problem with it.
Bro,
the big truck is trying to overtake us.
If I let him overtake us,
I'll change my name to Fang Beichao.
♪ Stars are twinkling over Crescent Bay ♪
♪ A gentle breeze
sways the willow branches ♪
Bro, you're impressive.
♪ A gentle breeze
sways the willow branches ♪
Bro,
the big truck has overtaken us.
♪ Sneaking around, peeking through ♪
Overtaken Fang, chase him!
Chase him.
Okay.
What's wrong, bro?
Bro,
right now I just want to go up and ram it.
That's a truck.
If we ram it,
that would be a fatal mistake.
Bro, you're right.
Our "tool" really
does need upgrading.
I did say
that sharpening the axe
won't delay chopping wood.
But now it won't start.
Are we going to carry it to get upgraded?
Snow covers the Volga River.
Troikas run on the frozen river.
Troikas.
Weren't you driving pretty fast?
Why did you stop here?
Come on, chase me!
Come on!
Come on, get out.
Get out.
You...
Bro,
you need a tire repair.
It's cheap here.
Mao.
Mao!
[No swimming.]
Back then,
when I first came from the village,
I had no education and no skills,
and couldn't find any work.
I was about to starve.
It was you, Mao,
and Gang who took me in.
Coming here means stability.
[Xia Tinggang, Thief]
I'll give you 3,500 yuan a month.
[Mao Hongwei, Thief]
Right.
And food and lodging are included.
Gang, Mao,
whatever works. You decide.
This Gai...
Little Gai is good.
Not only did you take me in,
but you also taught me
the rules of survival in this city.
What?
-Where should we go to
grab a bite and have a drink?
-Bro, let's get some barbecue.
-Bro.
-“Have a drink.
Wait, why...
Why is it only 400 yuan?
Wasn't it 3,500 yuan?
Wait, you eat my food
and sleep in my place.
It all costs money.
Wait, bro.
I did all the work myself.
Do you even have a conscience, Gai?
Do you know
what gratitude is?
If it weren't for you guys,
I wouldn't have gone down
the path I'm on now.
Gai,
spare me, please.
Mao,
what are you talking about?
I'm showing my gratitude.
But let's
put our personal feelings aside.
You punctured our company's car;
you still have to pay for it.
Of course,
I will pay.
100,000 yuan.
How much?
Too much?
Just right.
100,000 yuan?
100,000 yuan, you...
Gai.
Lord Gai!
I'm really begging you.
Forget 100,000 yuan.
I don't even have 500 yuan
on me.
It's not that I don't want to
pay my respects to you.
This...
Even if I go out to borrow,
no one will lend me any money.
Lord Gai.
Mao,
don't be afraid,
I'm here.
[IOU] [Borrower: Mao Hongwei]
[Yang Wei—private money lender]
Mao.
[IOU] [Borrower: Mao Hongwei]
The money is yours.
You paid me back.
Yours.
What are you doing?
Take it.
We agreed on this.
I thought you were joking.
What are you doing?
Take it back.
Wait,
why are you pushing it?
Looking down on me?
Stop pushing.
What are you doing? You...
Gai, if you're going to do this...
What?
If you have any other friends
who need money,
introduce them to me anytime.
I'll lend them whatever they need.
Let's go. I'll give you a ride
to get some help.
That's great.
Mao,
we haven't seen each other for years.
I don't really have
anything good to give you.
Just a stack...
Take this.
I've had this with me for a few days.
I've grown attached to it.
You take it.
Take it.
Take care of yourself.
Th-Thank you.