FINANCIAL CHIEF MANAGER OF CONGLOMERATE MR. CHA FOUND HANGING IN PUBLIC BATHROOM
Jeong Gu-won?
You have something precious to me.
I want you to be more responsible.
Acid?
Are you…
So I wasn't seeing things the other day.
What…
are you?
I'm…
a demon.
You humans call me…
the devil.
EPISODE 3 JOINING HANDS WITH A DEMON
We analyzed the liquid on the ground,
and it turned out to be sulfuric acid.
Had it splashed directly onto your face in that concentration and amount,
it would've melted it and could've been fatal.
It's highly likely that they're targeting you.
Is there anyone you suspect?
I'm Cha Tae-jun, the head of Mirae Group's financial team.
I'm reaching out to share an important piece of information.
Does anything come to mind?
No.
I can't think of anyone who would resent me enough to do this.
Humans are so insignificant.
Come in.
Move along.
Line up here.
Hurry up!
Do gambling houses let homeless people in these days?
Business is slow for them.
Where do you think you're going?
Let go! You can't do this to a lady!
I'll question you first since you're in such a hurry.
Go sit down, all of you.
Sit down.
What's your resident ID number?
Drink this while you wait, sir.
I don't drink rubbish like this.
You and your attitude.
Did you live abroad or something?
Don't get me wrong. I'm older than I look.
I see. Okay, sure.
BACKGROUND CHECK
Her name actually means "lady."
NAME: NOH SUK-NYEO ADDRESS: UNCLEAR
What's taking Do Do-hee so long?
What the hell?
The wonderful aroma of Arabica.
You're hanging by a thread now.
You might actually die.
And in a very…
insignificant way at that.
Why are there so many crazy humans these days?
Are you finished?
You've been waiting for her?
It must be reassuring to have him.
Please keep me updated on the investigation.
I will. Have a safe trip home.
Don't you think
the two of them will get married?
I highly doubt it.
The roulette wheel's finally spinning.
-The roulette? -Yes.
I'm betting everything on an odd number.
Is it that hard to keep yourself safe?
What if I had been even a second late?
My precious tattoo would have burned away.
So you're saying that you're a demon?
So you're the devil. Why call yourself a demon?
What are you, a Pokémon?
A Poké…
Listen carefully.
A demon is an extremely noble being whose goal is to make deals with humans.
What kind of deals?
Simply put, I grant humans' wishes.
-Like a genie in a bottle? -Don't you compare me to that beefy Smurf.
You've seen what I can do. If I wasn't a demon, what would else I be?
We normally call the likes of you superhumans.
Forget it. Think whatever you want.
-Then you are a genie-- -Except for that.
To be honest,
I don't care whether you're a devil or an angel.
-You don't believe me. -That's not the point.
The point is that you possess amazing powers
and that I have your tattoo, the source of them all.
So you don't believe me.
No, I don't.
I knew it.
You humans are always so doubtful.
I was wondering why you were so obsessed with the tattoo.
Things must've been pretty rough for you.
You need to stay close to me to use your powers,
but you have no excuse to do that.
You're not my ex, much less my boyfriend.
What you need right now
seems to be a title that would let you stay close to me.
-Am I wrong? -What are you trying to say?
We share the same fate.
That's what I'm trying to say.
The same fate?
We're in the same boat now.
And there's a way for both of us to get what we want.
Which is?
You're going to be my bodyguard.
Bodyguard? What do you mean?
Let me break it down for you.
A bodyguard is someone who protects their client from--
I know what a bodyguard does.
I'm a demon.
Are you telling me to protect some insignificant human?
You could tell yourself
that you're protecting your precious tattoo instead.
-No. -If protecting's not your thing,
think of it as fighting the bad guys.
You want me to fight on your behalf?
Do you actually think I'm a Pokémon?
You'd be in trouble if I died, no?
What would happen to your tattoo if I died?
As you know,
I'm in danger right now.
I don't know who's after me or why,
but someone's out to kill me.
You need your tattoo,
and I need your powers.
This is the only way for both of us to get what we want.
Don't you agree?
-So will you be my bodyguard? -My answer is a firm no.
Then what do you suggest? Do you have a better idea?
I don't know, but I won't be your bodyguard.
-Where are you going? -The creep might try his luck again.
I'll walk you to your door.
That's exactly what a bodyguard does. There's not much to it.
I said I'll never be your bodyguard.
Get in front of me. I'll watch your back.
How's the security here?
Do you not hear yourself?
SUNWOL FOUNDATION
I'm incredible as…
Oops, my bad.
Maybe not.
To think my amazing powers
depend on the wrist of such an insignificant and weak human being.
What if he breaks into her place?
If she dies and I lose my powers for good,
how am I to make deals?
Just be her bodyguard if you're so worried.
Don't be ridiculous.
How can a demon become a bodyguard?
Demons used to be bodyguards.
What nonsense is that?
"Demons originally existed among humans
and protected them as their guardians."
Guardians are basically bodyguards.
I don't want to be either.
I'm cut out to be a demon.
How did you get this out anyway?
I was tidying up your desk.
By the way,
what if Do Do-hee runs her mouth about your identity?
She doesn't even believe I'm a demon.
And you know how humans are.
I saw the devil.
-Oh, my. -Dear Lord.
What did the devil look like?
The devil showed up in front of me
as the man of my dreams in order to tempt my soul.
A chiseled and well-proportioned nose.
Skin as smooth as porcelain.
Sexy yet innocent lips.
Most importantly,
he had this melancholy look in his eyes.
Even his voice was like music to my ears.
I ended up
falling in love with the devil.
No one will believe I exist,
and they will soon forget
ever hearing about me.
You're right.
I got flogged big time in my past life for saying I'd seen an evil spirit.
My butt still aches when it rains.
You're exaggerating. That wasn't even in this life.
Anyway, would your powers really disappear if Do Do-hee died?
I have no idea. That's why I'm so anxious.
Something bad might happen.
This damn manual is full of threats and has no useful information.
I should just throw it away and…
No, I shouldn't.
So you admit it's a manual?
All I want is to have my peaceful and comfortable life back.
I just want to live eternally
as an apex predator who never ages or dies.
Is that too much to ask?
-You're not hiding it? -You'll find it anyway.
I quite liked the challenge.
Seriously…
Be my bodyguard.
How persistent.
Or should I go laser off this tattoo?
Is she threatening a demon right now?
Appointment booked.
Treatment begins in five, four,
three, two, one.
-Tattoo covered with Pororo. -That nutjob!
DO-HEE THE NUTJOB
PHOTO SENT
He's not taking the bait.
He saved me again.
Just like last time.
Mr. Cha, the Mirae Group head of finance, who was accused of embezzlement,
was found dead this afternoon.
A passerby found his body in a public restroom near his house
around 2 p.m. and made a report.
MY DELICATE BLOSSOM
Why are you being so clingy? You saw me just the other day.
I know you're happy because I called.
Did you call to nag me again?
That's not why I called.
Is everything okay at your company these days?
My company?
Why?
I saw on the news that your head of finance killed himself.
The thing is, he called me yesterday
and said he had important intel.
I disregarded it, assuming he was after some money.
But now that he killed himself,
something doesn't feel right.
Shouldn't you be worrying about your own company?
This is nothing,
so stop being nosy and focus on your company.
Ms. Yoon.
Bring me every news article about the deceased head of finance
and the financial statements for the last decade,
be it for headquarters or the affiliates.
I've been blind all this time.
Good morning, Director Jeong.
Come on in.
You seem to be in a good mood today.
I just realized the situation might not be too bad.
It's not like my tattoo is gone. It's safe on that woman's wrist.
You're one positive man.
I also realized I couldn't get my tattoo back
-just by jumping into the water. -Then?
The conditions would have to be the same as when I lost it.
What conditions?
Location, temperature, weather, and so on.
If the same conditions are met, I'm sure I'll get my tattoo back.
That makes sense.
Do you smell something burning?
I roasted the coffee beans to perfection today.
That's not it.
This is the smell of burning meat, not of plants.
You're right.
It smells like when you grill steak.
I'm also feeling some heat.
-Mr. Park. -Yes?
What the…
-Is this the spontaneous combustion? -Just like that?
Have you recovered your tattoo…
What's going on here?
You told her everything? Why would you…
My life was at risk.
I had to confess.
Help us out over here!
It's getting worse!
Is the oxygen fueling the flames?
Cut out that scientific gibberish!
It's so damn hot!
It's hot!
What just happened?
The spontaneous combustion has begun.
No, this is not okay.
I just fell asleep.
Who's calling this early?
GU-WON THE SAVIOR
You'll be my bodyguard?
-She picked up. -Be quiet. I can't hear.
Where are you? Are you home?
I am.
I need to see you. I'll come right over.
What's your plan?
I need to make a deal.
Put it all in! I need to go now!
Right now?
My goodness.
You can't just show up like this.
I haven't even washed up.
I'll be your bodyguard.
Really?
Good, you made the right…
Hold on. What changed your mind?
You were so against it yesterday.
I thought about it all night,
and it suddenly hit me.
Even insignificant things deserve protection.
Humans even protect insignificant and worthless insects
like longhorn beetles.
Are you comparing me to a longhorn beetle?
Both deserve to be protected.
Something's fishy.
There must be a reason why you changed your mind.
You hated the idea yesterday.
What made you…
-What are you doing? -What?
Very suspicious.
You must be hiding…
Focus, Do Do-hee.
We share the same fate, remember?
Always keep in mind that we're in the same boat.
You're right.
Sure, be my bodyguard.
Can you start today?
Before that,
I need you to come with me first.
This place…
It's too high!
Why did you bring me here?
This is the best place to spot humans for a deal.
I don't do well with heights!
Oh, come on!
Found one! Let's go!
This way.
Let me take some.
Can you hold this?
Additional chemotherapy would be meaningless.
Still…
Is there anything we can try?
I'm sorry.
Over there.
I won't even ask you to let her live.
I just want Yeon-seo to stop suffering.
Even if it's just for one day.
That's all I wish for.
I'll grant your wish.
Who are you?
I'm a demon.
In other words, you just hit the jackpot.
What?
If you sign a deal with me, your kid will be healthy for ten years.
I don't know who you are, but you can't just barge in here…
Yeon-seo!
Oh no!
-We're both short on time, so here it is. -Yeon-seo…
How did you…
The terms are simple.
You're going to hell after ten years.
If I do,
can Yeon-seo really live?
Make up your mind before I go find another person.
Wait, you're pushing her too--
Stay out of this.
Give her time to think. It's a difficult decision.
There's no time!
Time?
So you're doing this because…
I'll sign it.
I would go to worse places than hell
if it would stop Yeon-seo's suffering.
That was close.
Does the spontaneous combustion speed up the more I use my powers?
Do you know any nice cake places?
It's your industry, after all.
Cake?
I always celebrate a new deal with dessert.
What happens after you burst into flames?
I'd burn away.
You mean you'll die?
Kind of.
I'll cease to exist for good, which is more cruel than death.
So that's why you make deals.
To stop yourself from burning away.
And you even celebrate by eating cake.
You really are the devil, aren't you?
Nothing's free in this world.
I get to live eternally in return for granting human wishes.
I'd say that calls for a celebration.
You're exploiting people's misfortune.
Is that wrong? You want to do that to me too.
Each and every moment of your life
is built on the desperation and misfortune of others.
Doesn't that bother you?
I don't know why you're so upset,
but I save people.
Didn't you see the child dying in pain?
Will she ever be happy again after finding out that she survived
at the expense of her loved one?
You wouldn't be able to understand,
but humans can feel this thing called guilt.
Humans tend to romanticize unnecessary and inefficient emotions
as part of being human.
Let's head to the office.
No.
I'm not going to use you
lest I end up exploiting others' misfortunes.
You can afford to say that now.
But once your life is at risk,
you'll end up relying on my powers.
By nature, humans surpass demons
when it comes to selfishness.
You killed someone on top of all your dirty tricks?
You'll have to pay
for what you've done.
That's what I'm talking about.
Director Jeong! How are your fingers?
I made a deal,
and my fingers are fine.
Don't talk to me.
I was worried sick, thinking I'd never see you again.
What do you take me for?
I got restless after you stormed out,
so I looked into the day you lost your tattoo.
-And? -Listen to this.
Assuming that you fell into the sea around 30 minutes after midnight,
the temperature of the seawater in that area was 15.8°C.
And here comes the most important part.
That night,
there was a full moon.
How often does that occur?
Every 29.5 days.
Since it's been 1.5 days…
Just 28 days to go.
Another 28 days?
That's too long.
But aren't you Do Do-hee's bodyguard now?
Oh, that.
-I got fired. -Already?
She doesn't want my help anymore.
Did you two fight or something?
-Humans are just too greedy! -What?
Why would they pray if they don't want to pay the price?
I can't hear a word you're saying.
It's like they pester me to do wonders for free.
Now that I've literally put out that fire,
the tables have turned.
What exactly did she say?
Whatever.
I don't care what she says anymore.
In response to the recent sugar juice scandal,
the PR team suggests focusing on health-oriented new products.
Ma'am?
Ms. Do.
Please go on.
The healthy image of our new products
will replace all the negativity from the sugar juice scandal.
"Be on the defense…"
I mean, "Be on the offense."
Your words inspired us.
I brought what you asked for.
Also, I'll get your bodyguards in order as soon as possible.
Will she ever be happy again after finding out that she survived
at the expense of her loved one?
You wouldn't be able to understand,
but humans can feel this thing called guilt.
Is something bothering you?
Not at all. Why would I be bothered?
SEOUL HANSE MEDICAL CENTER
Oh no.
I'm sorry, sir.
Tell him you're sorry, Yeon-seo.
I'm sorry.
So your name's Yeon-seo?
Do you have a wish?
Her wish is about to come true.
She wanted to spend her tenth birthday out of the hospital.
Is that your wish?
Spending your birthday out of the hospital?
No? Then what is it?
I hope my parents won't have to suffer because of me.
That's my wish.
Yeon-seo.
Honey.
Mommy!
-Don't run, you'll trip. -Don't run, Yeon-seo.
My goodness.
I told you not to run.
Humans.
They're ever so difficult.
The cake's here.
-Thank you. -Enjoy.
-How many candles are there? -Ten.
-Ten. -Ten.
You're turning ten, Yeon-seo.
You love flowers, don't you?
-Let's sing. -Okay.
Here we go.
-Happy birthday to you -Happy birthday to you
-Happy birthday, dear Yeon-seo -Happy birthday, dear Yeon-seo
I would go to worse places than hell…
if it would stop Yeon-seo's suffering.
We're here, ma'am.
Hey.
I mean, ma'am.
Do you have any weapons? Maybe a handgun?
MARTIAL ARTS FOR BODYGUARDS
I guess…
I don't exactly need one, being a weapon myself.
UNDERSTANDING SECURITY EQUIPMENT
Mr. Han.
What's with the sudden bodyguard?
Ms. Do will be taking center stage in our new product promotion.
She must be preparing for her eventual fame.
She's really a step ahead of everyone, isn't she?
By the way, don't you think
the bodyguard is unnecessarily good-looking?
What do you mean, "unnecessarily"?
Talk about workplace benefits.
Since he's a bodyguard,
he must be a really good fighter.
Is he perfect or what?
But I bet he has a weakness.
-He has to. -That's right.
-For example… -For example?
He could be bad in bed.
Why is that a weakness?
How does that qualify as a fault?
That's perfectly fine!
It could happen to anyone.
Why would that ever be a problem?
I didn't want to know.
Being a bodyguard is pretty easy.
Were you expecting some kind of drama?
As if.
Why did you come back?
You didn't want to be my bodyguard.
Just because.
My life was so peaceful and perfect that it was almost boring.
I thought I could use some trouble.
What changed your mind though?
You didn't want my powers.
Just because.
It takes one scumbag to deal with another.
How did you end up a demon?
Were you born one?
Is it a family business
like a generations-old restaurant?
Comparing demons to restaurants? I truly…
have no words.
How old are you? When were you born?
I've lived for 200 years as a demon.
You really don't look your age.
Anyway, does that mean that there was a time
you weren't a demon?
-I used to be human. -Really?
Of course, I was on a different level from all those other insignificant humans.
Although I don't remember it.
To me, it seems like self-hatred.
You consider humans insignificant because you were too.
It's written in a book.
"God needed someone to work in hell,
so he hand-picked a human to become a demon."
And I'm the human he chose.
Not because you were anything special
but because you fit the job description.
You're a jerk.
WORDS OF THE ALMIGHTY JU: THIS IS IT FOR ME. I LOVE YOU, DO-HEE
What is it now?
ALMIGHTY JU
The number you have dialed cannot be reached.
-Turn the car around. -Please leave a message…
Madam Ju?
Why are you sitting on the ground?
It'll take a toll on your knee.
I can't believe you.
Madam Ju?
MISSED CALLS MY DELICATE BLOSSOM
Madam Ju, are you okay?
Madam Ju?
This isn't funny.
What's going on?
Madam Ju, wake up.
Madam Ju.
You can't do this.
This is a prank, right?
You totally got me, so please wake up.
I'm here.
I'm right here. Please wake up.
That's enough.
Save her.
I can't bring the dead back to life.
Why not? I know you can!
Save her right now.
Please save her.
I'll sign a contract or whatever you want me to, so please.
Just this once.
Madam Ju!
You can't do this.
Wake up!
Madam Ju!
Please save her.
It seems as if all the life has been drained from Ms. Do overnight.
She must be in shock.
She was very close with the chairwoman.
Should we go comfort her?
Futile consolation attempts will only hurt her further.
Try not to let your emotions show.
That's the best thing you can do for her.
She's been like that the whole time.
So it's you.
You're not even crying.
I don't deserve to cry.
They died because of me.
So what if it was my birthday?
I should never have rushed them.
Do you think you're God?
How can anyone die because of you?
You feel sorry for yourself if you think like that, don't you?
You're no better than a speck of dust floating around.
A speck of dust
can't tip the scales.
There you go.
Good girl.
Mom. Dad.
I miss you.
Do-hee.
I called your name many times, but you didn't answer.
Madam Ju didn't like taking pictures.
She said they never did her justice.
I think this one looks good.
But it's nothing like her.
That smile makes her look like she's only a shell of herself.
Funeral portraits reflect how the bereaved want to remember the deceased.
It still feels like the whole thing is just a joke.
I feel like she'll show up any minute
and shout, "Surprise, you little brat!"
Then burst into laughter.
That would be much more like her.
She was such an eccentric person.
I thought her last moments would also be special.
But a heart attack?
You just got here?
Yes, Aunt Cheon-suk had apparently ordered
an audit team to be formed before she passed.
It was put on hold, but I had to take care of some paperwork.
An audit team?
Who put it on hold?
The board passed an emergency motion.
You didn't hear about it?
This is hardly the time for an audit.
Look at that.
Everyone's busy buttering Suk-min up.
Is this the Joseon Dynasty or what?
Being the eldest son means nothing.
Mom never liked Suk-min.
She even sent him to prison for driving drunk.
I have a feeling
Mom would've made an unusual choice. Don't you agree?
Right. She was unique indeed.
Seok-hoon, come over here for a second.
You two always seemed to have
a special bond.
Camaraderie between outsiders, is that it?
It's just that we studied abroad together as students.
But don't fool yourself, Do-hee.
Seok-hoon has a different background from you.
He comes from the Ju family,
while you come from a vulgar family
who worked with machines and other people's hair.
What's vulgar
is the way you think.
Is this the Joseon Dynasty or what?
You're still talking back to me?
My mom is no longer here to take your side.
Stop drinking unless you want everyone to see your true colors.
I can never get through funerals without alcohol.
Everyone's wearing black.
It's horrible.
I put up with even more horrible things
while being sober.
Mom was always mean.
I guess that's why…
you two got along.
Hello, Isabelle.
Hi, it's been a while.
I'm so glad to see you.
I heard a lot about you from Chairman Noh.
I see.
It's too early to call me that.
Congratulations, ma'am.
Please don't say that.
I'm afraid that's a bit inappropriate.
I think so too.
There are more and more female CEOs as well.
You're right.
Austin!
Justin!
-Austin! -Boys will be boys.
So this was a party, not a funeral?
CCTV CONTROL ROOM AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
The seasons differ above and below ground.
Underground, spring starts around October.
Even during the chilly winter above ground,
buds are sprouting below the ground.
So tell yourself this when things get tough.
"Spring is about to begin within me."
What's with this Mother Nature vibe? It's not like you.
I was having a moment there.
Just play along, you brat.
Pick a character and stick to it.
Are you Mother Nature or Sailor Mouth?
I'm Sailor Mouth, so what?
Just put that in here.
Gosh, the water's leaking!
-Hey, you just go away. -What's wrong with this?
Go away!
-You can't sprinkle it like that! -Okay, I get it!
I thought no one was here.
Want one?
Madam Ju hates the smell of cigarettes.
Grandma? But she's gone.
Everything belongs to my dad now,
and it'll all be mine soon.
I'd prefer the smell of cigarettes over that of an old granny.
I said Madam Ju hates the smell of cigarettes.
I'll let it slide today.
Because today
is a happy day.
I can't let it slide.
So I wasn't the only one who wanted to get out of there.
Can I join?
Who are you?
I'm someone inseparable from Ms. Do Do-hee here.
But don't get me wrong. I'm not her ex,
much less her boyfriend.
-Are you her bodyguard? -No.
I just got off work.
Want a sip?
You can't hide your upbringing.
You two are a perfect match.
What the hell?
Want a sip?
Madam Ju
used to hole up here
whenever she was feeling down.
I never got that about her…
until now.
The greenhouse didn't just protect her plants
but Madam Ju herself.
She was aware…
that her children would rejoice
at her death.
Her prediction came true.
That must've been why she was always so mean.
She was lonely all her life
to the very end.
It breaks my heart that I never got to say goodbye to her.
Do you know why people wear black to funerals?
It's to prevent the soul of the deceased from recognizing and following them.
That's why
they hide themselves in black clothing.
Then I'm wearing the wrong color today.
Madam Ju must be so lonely today too.
She can't recognize anyone at her own funeral.
She can recognize you now.
What's the point?
I wouldn't know even if she came to see me.
Just give it a chance.
Thank you, Madam Ju,
for finding me.
Both 17 years ago and now.
Thanks to you,
I got to act like the devil's spawn as much as I wanted.
If we ever get a second chance…
let's…
fight even harder
and love each other more dearly.
My goodness. What are you, in a fashion show?
You just have to stand out, don't you?
Aren't we all here as the bereaved family?
Who gave her the right to be here?
The detective has some information for all of us.
What on earth could it be?
Good to see you all.
Sorry, that came out wrong.
Whatever this is, make it quick.
It's rude of us to leave our guests on their own.
Of course, sir.
Detective Lee.
There are just too many documents to go through.
Did the deceased often take painkillers?
Yes, she had a knee problem.
The medicine she took on the day of her death…
was diclofenac.
Hold on. That's not possible.
She never took that because she was allergic.
But it's been confirmed that it was diclofenac
that she took on the day of her death.
I'm telling you this because the label didn't match the contents.
Are you saying that Mother passed
due to medical negligence?
We thought it was a simple heart attack.
Didn't Director Choi prescribe her meds?
How could this happen?
We'll investigate all possibilities, so let's not jump to any conclusions.
Mr. Cha and the audit team.
All I can tell you right now
is that it has the power to make you chairwoman of Mirae Group.
Perhaps Mr. Cha
had proof of someone's wrongdoing.
And that person killed Madam Ju
to stop her from digging it out.
Medical negligence doesn't sound good.
Especially since everyone's saying Mirae Group is in crisis.
We'll only be giving them something to gossip about.
Just thinking about what people will say
gives me a headache.
Everyone will be busy making up stories.
They think we chaebols sold our souls to the devil or something.
By how much did our stock prices drop?
We can't risk them dropping further.
First, who knew about the deceased's allergy
to diclofenac?
Her doctor…
as well as everyone here.
Let's announce that it was a heart attack.
That's a good idea.
We can't afford any rumors right before succession.
Then again,
it's not like Mom can come back to life if we reveal the truth.
I'll put in a word with the commissioner general.
Be sure to keep this a secret.
Where's Attorney Jeong?
He's waiting outside.
Is the will going to be read outside?
We want to make it official.
Sure, there's no point in waiting.
Detective Park.
Madam Ju was murdered.
It wasn't a heart attack or medical negligence.
It was murder.
I know why Madam Ju was killed
and why I might get killed.
Are you drunk?
Why are you making a scene?
Which of you did it?
You? Or you?
Or…
were you all in on it?
Take her away.
Step back if you don't want to get hurt.
Do-hee, what's wrong?
What's going on?
Let's get started.
Ms. Do Do-hee's presence is required.
Ms. Ju Cheon-suk left a will detailing her assets,
including shares and convertible bonds, with a suspensive condition.
Condition?
Her will is as follows.
"I bequeath all real estate, including the mansion in Hannam-dong,
and cash to be donated to Hansarang Welfare Foundation."
"I also bequeath Mirae Group's management rights,
as well as all shares of its affiliates,
to the designated legatee."
So who's the designated legatee?
"The designated legatee is Mirae F&amp;B's CEO,
Do Do-hee."
What just happened?
As expected of her.
So this was a surprise party?
"The inheritance
is contingent upon Do Do-hee registering her marriage within one year
following the passing of the testator, Ju Cheon-suk."
"If this condition is not met,
her share shall be bequeathed to Hansarang Welfare Foundation."
Do Do-hee…
will be our chairwoman?
The deceased also wrote letters to her family members,
as this news would give you quite a shock.
Let me see.
I'm sure there's more.
Mom wouldn't have done this to me.
"Money ruined you all."
"Every man in your life is…"
Seriously?
What does it say?
You don't want to know.
Madam Ju.
What on earth is this?
She made this decision
after much contemplation.
TO DO-HEE
You!
What did you do?
What the hell did you do?
Calm down. Pull yourself together!
You're not going to accept it, are you?
The only way to stop me
is to kill me.
Do-hee.
Wait and see, Madam Ju.
I promise to reveal the truth
even if I have to join hands with a demon.
Mr. Jeong Gu-won.
Marry me.
I think you should stay out of it.
I need to find out who's behind it.
To do that, I'll need to form an audit team.
Ms. Do and Mr. Jeong.
The way they interact hints at physical intimacy.
I don't want you to go out alone and get in trouble.
So let me keep holding your wrist.
People already suspect we're dating as it is.
It's a beautiful day, Young Master Yi-sun.
Young Master!
My memories are starting to come back.
There's nothing like secretly holding hands
under the table at team dinners.
There's something so enjoyable about secret physical touch.
I like Do Do-hee.
Subtitle translation by: Min-jin Kim