To Thorfun.
Phoon has arrived in Chiang Mai.
Today, Phoon happened
to run into P'Fah as well.
And Phoon lied,
saying that Fun is doing fine.
Do you want to stay in
P'Fah's room tonight?
You'll stay with me
until I fall asleep, right?
Yes.
Uh, Phoon.
Can I have Fun's LINE ID?
Are you dating anyone right now?
I'm not dating anyone.
I can't be the sky for anyone.
Can you be the sky for me?
Is that not allowed?
Phoon.
Phoon. Phoon.
Yes?
Are you okay? You suddenly went quiet.
Oh.
I'm fine.
I thought you were bored with
what Fah was talking about.
Looks like it's about to
rain. Should we head back?
Let's go.
Hey, Jo. Where have you been?
Just running some errands. What about you?
Out.
You didn't even wear a
raincoat. You'll catch a cold.
I'll be fine.
Where are you heading next?
Back to my condo.
And damn it, it's raining again.
What about you?
I'm heading back too.
- Drive safe.
- You too.
- See you.
- Bye.
Was that your friend?
Yes.
What's his name?
His name is Johan.
Oh, P'Johan.
Why?
Interested?
No.
If I were to recommend someone,
Jo would be the last person I'd recommend.
No—second to last.
The last one would be Arthit.
Hmm. Why is that?
He's not a very good person.
If I were to recommend
someone from the group,
I'd want you to meet Hill the most.
Why do you think you need
to introduce someone to me?
I just think it'd be good if
you had someone to look after.
And if there's going to be someone, I
want them to be a good, trustworthy person.
So if you date anyone, they
have to pass Thorfun first, right?
Yes.
Then they'll have to pass me too.
I am your brother, after all.
Looks like the power's
about to go out again.
Will you be okay?
Uh…
Honestly…
Do you want to stay in
P'Fah's room tonight?
Yes.
Sorry for bothering you again.
It's okay.
I just ordered this.
May I sit here?
Sure.
Here's some water.
I think it'd be better if you moved dorms.
I'll find a new place for you.
My dad might scold me.
He'd already paid the deposit.
Then I'll talk to your dad myself.
May I have your dad's number?
I've sent you my dad's number.
Wait a moment. I'll
talk to your dad for you.
Aren't you going to bed yet?
Then I'll go to bed first.
Mm.
Who is it?
Hello?
Hello, Uncle. This is Tonfah.
Oh, Tonfah?
You startled me. I was
wondering who it was.
Why are you calling? Is something wrong?
It's about Phoon.
About Phoon?
What is it?
About the dorm you chose for Phoon.
It's not very good.
So I thought it'd be
better for him to move.
But I wanted to ask
for your permission first.
I had no idea the dorm wasn't good.
I've recently changed jobs
and have been very busy.
So I asked my secretary
to handle the booking.
I see.
Alright then.
Tonfah studies here too?
I had no idea.
Yes, I study here, and I
happened to run into Typhoon.
What? You ran into Typhoon too?
How was he?
Did he say anything or tell you something?
He didn't say anything.
Did he mention Thorfun at all?
I heard she's studying
medicine near home, right?
Then I'll take care of Typhoon myself.
Including finding a new dorm.
Then I'll leave Typhoon in your care.
Yes, uncle. Don't worry.
How are you?
We'll go look for a new dorm together.
Did Dad allow it?
Yes.
P'Fah.
Is something wrong?
No.
You should go take a shower.
You've been tired all day. Get some rest.
Did Typhoon mention Thorfun at all?
Where are you, Fun?
Tomorrow morning, I'll pick
you up. Rith wants to talk to you.
Are you sure you don't
want P'Fah to take you?
I'm sure.
Uncle said he'd come pick me up.
They suddenly flew to Chiang Mai like this.
Is something wrong?
Is it about what P'Fah
called about last night?
I don't know.
I'll get going now.
Okay.
Why did you suddenly come to Chiang Mai?
Rith already had
business with a client here.
It suddenly got moved to today last night.
It's about P'Fah, right?
Probably.
Is Dad angry?
I warned you not to
get involved with Tonfah.
If Tonfah's family finds
out about his divorce,
because Thorfun's mother
caught him with another woman,
and knew about you who is his child...
An illegitimate child.
That's right.
That's why he doesn't dare face them.
He hasn't contacted that family for years.
But...
P'Fah's parents aren't like that.
I know.
But Typhoon should know his father well.
Rith really respects Tonfah's parents.
He's afraid of being seen badly.
And that it might affect his career.
You have to understand him.
I understand.
You really are a good kid.
Even after everything he's done to you,
you still love him and
respect him as your father.
He's the only family I have left.
Typhoon.
You already knew Tonfah
studies here, didn't you?
Yes.
But I didn't think I'd
run into him this soon.
What did you tell him?
I didn't tell him anything.
What exactly do you want?
Wasn't killing my daughter enough for you?
You even made Wit and Pha see me badly.
I already told you, didn't I?
You can study wherever you want,
but stay away from Tonfah.
Do you understand?
Or are you planning to
tell Tonfah about Thorfun?
That you killed your own sister?
He must be so proud of you.
I didn't kill Fun.
I didn't mean to.
So you're saying you're not at fault?
Look at what's happened to me.
Everything has fallen apart.
My family was torn apart.
And you're saying you did nothing wrong?
Remember this—no one wants you.
I never even wanted you to be born.
Do you know your mother
abandoned you when you were little?
And now no one even knows where she is.
If it weren't for Thorfun's mother,
you wouldn't even be standing here.
Look at how you repaid us.
You killed our child.
And remember this well
no one sees you as family
except Thorfun and Tonfah.
Once Thorfun died,
you crawled back to Tonfah,
thinking he wouldn't abandon you, right?
Dad, can I stay with P'Fah?
I won't say anything. I promise.
Yes, you have to promise.
Because if you tell him,
he'll abandon you anyway.
Because you're afraid
he'll hate you, right?
Right?
You have to withdraw from
university within this week.
Dad.
You already sold the house in Phuket.
If I withdraw too, where
am I supposed to go?
Where you go is your problem. I don't care.
But you must stay as far away
from Tonfah's family as possible.
The farther, the better.
As for money, I'll have Kong handle it.
Remember this.
Don't ever let me see your face again.
Do you understand?
Dad, please don't.
Please don't abandon me.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
No matter what it is, it's my fault.
I'm the only one at fault.
I never wanted to be
born just to ruin your life.
I'll stay quiet, but please…
don't abandon me.
If you still see me as your dad,
then you must stop
getting involved with Tonfah.
P'Fah.
Yes, P'Fah?
You didn't reply, so I called.
Are you still with your dad?
No.
I just got back to my room.
P'Fah.
Yes?
Are you free these days?
Yeah, I am.
Why?
Could you take me out somewhere?
Please?
I really want to go out with you.
Sure. Where do you want to go?
Anywhere.
As long as you're with me.
I want to go everywhere with you.
Are you okay?
What does your dad say?
Dad just came up for work.
So he stopped by to see me.
I see.
Uh
I'll hang up now, P'Fah.
If Fun were still here,
everything would be better.
Why did it have to be you who left?
Why was I the one left behind?
Why couldn't it have been me instead?
Typhoon.
Are you okay?
It's okay.
I think Dad might be stressed about work.
So he may have lost his temper.
Failing this exam
it's okay.
You can retake it next time.
Can you stop saying that?
How can you say it's okay?
You'd never understand me.
Everyone loves you.
I'm just bad luck.
No matter what I do,
it's never good enough.
This house doesn't even need me.
Don't say that.
What do you want me to do for you?
There's nothing you can do for me.
Typhoon.
You're leaving again?
Can't you stay?
Don't call to chase after me.
Go.
I'll be back.
Typhoon.
Where are you?
Why is it so loud?
I told you not to call.
Let's go home, okay?
I'm not going back.
Can't we talk properly?
There's nothing to talk about, damn it.
Stop calling me already. You're annoying.
Typhoon.
Hey!
You just bumped into me.
What the hell?
Stop calling already!
Typhoon, what happened?
Are you okay?
Hello, Typhoon.
Stay right there. I'm coming to you.
Still so young.
Such a shame.
A good kid, top of the class.
So much potential. What a waste.
I heard she snuck out at night.
And then a drunk driver came the wrong way.
- Wow.
- She died on the spot.
That's so pitiful.
Why did she take the car
out so late at night anyway?
They said her younger
brother got into a fight at a bar.
She was worried, so she rushed to find him.
Such bad karma, having
a younger brother like that.
So young, yet already going into bars.
And he doesn't even study. The only
sister he could rely on passed away first.
Mm.
I heard both the father and
mother were arguing about it.
No one wanted to take
the younger brother in.
- Really?
- Yeah, that's what I heard.
You little bastard! You damn kid!
You got my child killed!
You killed my child!
I'm sorry.
You damn kid, remember this — you
should never have been born as my child.
Where are you going? Wait!
After that, our family fell apart.
So broken that it could never
be put back together again.
That's enough. I won't
put up with you anymore.
Why? What did I do?
You're just a womanizer,
sleeping with anyone you please.
Even after marrying me, you
got another woman pregnant.
Shut up. Stop talking.
Do you know how much I've endured
raising that child for over ten years?
That's already more than enough.
Every time I see his face, I see how badly our family
failed, how utterly broken it became. Do you even know that?
I told you, I didn't mean to
get that woman pregnant.
He's an illegitimate child, and
he caused my child's death.
Why wasn't it that kid who died?
Why did it have to be Fun?
Why did it have to be my child?
Still crying like always.
Faun.
I've missed you all this time.
I know.
You wrote to me every single day.
I missed you too.
You've been through so many
terrible things, haven't you?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I wasn't there with you.
I'm sorry too. I'm sorry… I'm sorry, Fun.
None of this is your fault.
Don't cling to me anymore.
You have to move forward.
Do you understand?
Please love yourself.
Just like I loved you, okay?
Would it be okay…
If I don't want to endure anymore?
If I just let everything end…
And stop trying altogether?
Then I could finally go be with you.
Phoon.
Don't hurt the person I love.
You have to take care of yourself.
Eat good food.
Take yourself to good places.
Tell yourself you love yourself often.
Can you promise me?
Live for me.
Thank you for coming to see me.
Thank you so much.
Feel free to take a look.
Do you like it?
I do.
Can we move in today?
Well, you've already paid the deposit.
You can move in right away if you want.
P'Fah.
Yes?
I'll hurry and earn money to pay it back.
No need. Your father
entrusted that money to me.
My dad?
Yes.
Then shall we start moving your things?
I'll go with you.
Fun'd been busy lately? I
texted her but she didn't reply.
Well
I guess so.
Oh.
At first, I thought…
You'd study photography.
P'Fah.
Yes?
I'm going to take the medical school exam.
Really?
Yes.
Then…
You'll study here first and
take the exam later, right?
Uh…
Yes.
P'Fah, could you…
Help tutor me?
Well…
Of course I can.
But if we're going to tutor,
you have to promise not to quit halfway.
You have to keep studying until the exam.
Can you promise me that?
Until the exam...
Yes.
Many students who start tutoring
tend to change their minds halfway.
The tutor ends up feeling a bit hurt too.
But still...
The exam is still months away.
Can you promise me you'll stay until then?
Hmm?
Yes.
I promise.
Why did you make that face?
You finally call yourself
“Phoon” again like before.
Is that strange?
Not at all. It's much better.
You're the same, P'Fah.
You always refer to yourself as P'Fah.
That's true.
Do you usually refer to yourself like that?
I only do that with you, Phoon.
Do you remember why?
When we were kids...
There were a lot of
kids in our neighborhood.
If I just called myself “P',”.
You'd get confused about which one.
So I used my name instead.
So you'd know.
Oh.
Thank you for helping me move dorms.
Honestly, thank you for everything.
It's no big deal.
I have to go now. I'm tutoring a junior.
Okay.
See you. Call me if you need anything.
Do the homework on page 15.
And, um...
That should be enough for today.
See you.
P'Fah.
Hello, P'Fah?
Phoon.
Is the new dorm all set?
All set.
It suddenly started raining.
I was worried about
a blackout, so I called.
Mm.
It's just raining.
P'Fah.
Yes?
What if...
It's a place where it rains all the time,
Then...
How do people
live there?
There is a place like that.
Meghalaya State, India.
It gets over 10,800
millimeters of rain a year.
That's nine times more than Thailand.
They adapt by building steep roofs,
So water doesn't pool.
They raise their houses,
Grow rain-resistant crops,
And always carry flashlights and umbrellas.
You could say.
Rain is just normal there.
Clear skies would be the strange thing.
But some people...
Learn to be happy in the rain.
Learning to be happy in the rain.
That's true.
Phoon.
You're serious about
becoming a doctor, right?
Of course.
Good. I'll prepare the materials.
Shall we start tutoring tomorrow?
Sure.
Isn't that too soon?
You still have plenty of time.
I don't have much time.
P'Fah.
Have you been waiting long?
(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
Not at all.
Do you want anything? I'll order for you.
Hmm.
I'll have an iced latte.
Got it.
One iced latte, please.
Thank you.
Here you go.
P'Fah, look.
The sky is so beautiful today.
Even though it rained hard last night.
That's really nice.
That the sky can make you smile like this.
Phoon.
Yes?
You're smiling, you know?
Yes.
And do you realize it?
That you suit a smile more than anything.
Smile a lot, okay?
Oh.
About today's tutoring...
Let me see.
How do I do this?
Okay, come on.
Ah, this one. Read the
question first, Phoon.
They're asking for a unit vector in the
same direction as U, which equals U.
And the absolute value
of U, first we think about...
What is a vector?
A vector is...
Vector comes from...
What are you looking at?
If you don't finish this problem,
I won't let you go home.
Phoon.
Let's sit for a bit.
Up ahead is the clock tower. When you
come to class, you'll see this clock tower.
And this is the dormitory.
The cafeteria is on the left.
On the left.
That's the right, Phoon.
I thought you didn't like
taking photos of people.
Why have you been
taking so many of me lately?
I want to keep these
moments as much as possible.
And photographs.
Are the clearest proof.
Like how you like taking
pictures of Fun, right?
Your time is up.
I know.
Let me stay with P'Fah a little longer.
Until the semester starts.
After that, I won't interfere
with P'Fah ever again.
And if you guys run into
each other at the university?
I'll pretend I didn't see him.
Like we're strangers.
And if Tonfah doesn't agree?
I'll make him hate me.
So much he won't even want to look at me.
Just make sure you do what you said.
P'Fah.
I'm not free today. Let's
cancel the tutoring session.
It's okay. Are you free tomorrow?
I'm not.
Then when are you free?
I'm not free anymore.
Aren't you eating?
I told you, I'm not hungry.
Please eat a little.
I said I'm not eating.
I'm sorry.
Did I do something wrong?
I'll head back first.
How will you get home?
I'll call a taxi.
Happy birthday, Johan!
Bottoms up! Hey, Fah!
Everyone!
Today's my friend Johan's birthday.
One big sip!
Alright, together!
Hey!
Whoever finishes their glass gets cash!
You're ridiculous.
Come on, enjoy it. Have some fun!
It'd be way more fun without you.
Hey!
Alright, bottoms up! Cheers!
- Come on, Fah!
- Where'd you come from, so hungry?
Fah!
Hey, Fah!
What?
What's wrong with you?
Nothing. I'm fine.
I'm gonna step outside for some air.
What's with him?
- What's his problem?
- How would I know?
Hey, go talk to him.
This killed the mood.
What's wrong?
Got something you wanna talk about?
Do you think I'm okay?
What do you mean?
Everything.
Who I am.
My personality.
The things I do.
The things I say.
Is there anything wrong with me?
What made you lose
your confidence like this?
My brother.
Your brother?
Yeah.
The kid next door when I lived in Phuket.
He happened to study here.
So we ran into each other again.
Back then,
We were really close.
He is someone I can't help but worry about.
So much that it makes me
want to take good care of him.
But ever since I moved out of the house,
and stopped contacting him,
I've felt guilty ever since.
And now,
that we finally get to
see each other again,
I just want to make
up for the time we lost.
But…
He is not okay with you anymore?
At first, it seemed fine.
But then suddenly,
he started pulling away.
He doesn't answer my calls.
And barely reply to my messages.
It's like he doesn't
want to see me anymore.
So I started thinking that
maybe it's better if no
need to have me around.
While you were gone, did
anything happen to him?
It seems like
his parents got divorced.
But his dad and older sister
are still living with him like before.
Do you think he's hiding
something from you?
Hiding something?
Maybe.
I don't really know.
All I know is that this already
makes he feel really bad about me.
I don't dare do anything at all, Hill.
It feels like
if I make even the slightest wrong move,
I'll lose him forever.
Are you sure
he's just your younger brother?
Why are you asking that?
He seem really important to you.
He's just my younger brother.
I've taken care of him
since we were little.
So you think it's your responsibility?
Yeah.
Fah.
About what you asked me,
whether there's something wrong with you,
for me,
no.
I believe you've done your best.
You're always taking care of others.
Try caring about yourself too.
Thanks, Hill.
Right now, even I
am starting to feel exhausted too.
Dad.
I don't want to do this anymore.
I don't want to hurt P'Fah.
If you don't want to do it, then
don't show your face to me again.
But P'Fah must hate me already.
That's even better then.
So who are you going to
choose—Tonfah or your father?
Dad.
Can Phoon ask for a chance?
Just to see him one more time.
Are you sure that will be the last time?
Yes, I'm sure.
And after that,
I will never get involved
with P' Fah again.
Phoon.
Have you been waiting long?
Not long at all.
Are you feeling unwell?
I'm fine.
You feel warm.
Why didn't you tell P'Fah
if you weren't feeling well?
It's okay.
I don't know when I might
have hurt you unintentionally.
If there's anything you
don't like, can you tell me?
I'll try to improve myself.
It's really okay.
You're fine just the way you are.
Then eat well, okay? After
that, you can take your medicine.
Stay over in P'Fah's room tonight.
With you being sick like
this, I can't leave you alone.
Or should P'Fah stay in your room instead?
Your room is fine.
Okay.
Here's your medicine.
Phoon.
You seem to really like this chair.
It can see the sky outside the window.
It feels really relaxing.
You're still warm.
Want to lie down and rest?
I'll sit here and read beside you.
If you're not okay, call me.
Okay.
This might be the last time
that I get to be with P'Fah like this.
The last time.
The last time I wish would never come.
Goodbye.
P'Fah.
Phoon.
You're inside, right?
Come out and see me for a bit.
Phoon.
Are you okay?
Come out and talk to me, please.
Phoon.
I know you're inside.
Aren't you going to answer me?
Do you hate me now?
I really don't know what I did wrong.
But can you tell me,
what I did wrong?
You're my important little brother.
Can we go back to how things were?
Get out.
What nonsense are you rambling on about?
It's annoying.
Do you realize,
how damn annoying you are?
And get away from my door.
Go wherever you want.
I'm sorry.
I'll go now.
I'm really sorry.
I never wanted this to happen.
It's been sent ever since you were little.
Since you were one year old, every March.
Your birthday month.
Mom?
There's something?
If you want to know,
transfer the money first.
Go get it at home.
I've got an idea—how to
get Maew to talk to P'Fah.
- Why chocolate milk?
- Because I like it.
We could just buy everything, you know.
Wow, someone's generous.
I don't think P'Fah likes that.
Look at Fah—so possessive.