Subtitle by Kisskh.Asia Translator [ Admin Qari ]
May I be like the stars
and you like the moon.
As long as the world remains,
so shall we.
I only wish to stay with the one I love,
watching every sunrise and sunset.
I want to be with you forever.
Eternals and demons walk different paths.
You and she are ultimately different.
Have you ever
truly cared for me?
No.
Never.
In this life and the next, through all lifetimes…
May we live and die together,
and share life and death as one.
[Moonlight Mystique]
[Episode 7]
Hurry up!
Hurry!
Can you be faster?
-Hurry up!
-So annoying.
Full of nonsense.
Hurry!
Wait.
What does running
have to do with cultivating?
Of course it does.
Have you forgotten what I told you yesterday?
What's the most important thing
in a duel?
You're not trying to teach me how to escape, are you?
You're very smart.
What you're learning today
is the
Turtle
Running
Technique.
Yesterday you taught me to play dead,
and today you're teaching me to escape.
Turtle, don't forget
you promised Fan Yue to teach me Eternal skills.
If you keep messing with me,
I'll call that devil here right now.
My good disciple.
Don't rush.
After all, I'm a 1000-year-old spirit turtle.
When teaching, I've got to put on some airs, right?
I officially inform you
that you have passed all of my tests.
From today on,
I will teach you
the real
skills.
Really?
Are these the real skills you mentioned?
My signature skills
are divination and alchemy.
[Golden Elixir Scripture] [Zifu Pill Formula]
[Golden Elixir Scripture]
Today, I'll teach you,
without holding anything back.
Don't just pull out that little seashell every time.
I'm telling you,
I'm really not messing with you this time.
They really are
my signature skills.
He knows what I want.
I want to be stronger.
What does he want me to learn from you?
Divination?
Or alchemy?
These can't make me stronger.
He doesn't really want to help me,
and neither do you.
Stop right there!
No one is born the strongest.
If you can't even protect yourself,
how can you live long enough to grow stronger?
You can't get fat
by eating one bite.
You can't reach the sky in one step.
If you aim unreasonably high
and rush things,
the more you practice, the worse you'll get,
and the further you'll stray from the path.
To grow stronger,
it's not just about strength.
It's also about mindset.
If you want to learn properly,
stay
and start from the basics.
If you don't want to learn,
you can grab that little seashell
and call Fan Yue over
to take you back right now.
At worst, I'll just get beaten by him again.
But you...
will never
amount to anything.
Weren't you giving me the turtle shell and the medicine book?
Why did you take them away?
So,
where do we start,
Master?
What
did you just call me?
Master.
Since
you've called me Master,
today,
we should
set a rule.
What rule?
Just tell me.
To become my disciple,
you need to pay first.
It's not what I want either.
I'm just staying here temporarily in Lanling,
and I have to pay for accommodation every month.
Otherwise, they would've kicked me out long ago.
They are so stingy.
Why are you still staying here?
Do you think I want
to be exploited by those old fossils?
I've been making elixirs every day,
and it...
and it has made my turtle shell almost crack.
But I'm the only 1000-year-old spirit turtle
in the whole Eastern Continent.
Everyone knows I'm skilled in divination,
and everyone wants to capture me to predict the future for them.
In this vast world,
only Lanling
can protect
my turtle body!
It's it.
There are four steps:
look, smell, touch, and taste.
These are the ways to identify medicinal herbs.
My disciple, as the saying goes,
make the most of what's around you.
Since you've come to this mountain,
you should learn to make use of what others consider useless.
What's the effect of the old tree bark?
It clears heat and disperses blood stasis.
Smart!
Let's go.
How do you make it?
Turn up the heat.
Don't underestimate this alchemy furnace.
It's older than me.
It was forged from meteoric iron that fell from the sky.
Have you understood?
Good.
Wait.
Can you understand it?
I can.
What does the letter say?
They also refused to come.
Among the 72 Sects,
except for Kunlun Sect and the Wuliang Sect,
none are willing to start a war.
Then how can we conquer the Cold Spring Palace?
Be gentle.
This table was just repaired.
I know.
I held back my strength.
The 72 Sects
each have their own philosophy.
Some seek worldly engagement,
some are reclusive;
[When the Lanling Sect and others discuss the matter of the conquest, our sect will definitely spare no effort]
[Our sect fully agrees and is willing to work together to discuss the strategy for the conquest]
some value culture, some value martial arts;
some are radical, some are conservative.
The different philosophies lead to disagreements.
Since the truce between the Eternals Race and the Demon Race 100 years ago,
the Human Race has been living in peace.
It's understandable that the Eternals
don't want to break this peace.
Sect Leader, since you know this,
why did you send letters to them?
I thought that
even if some sects don't like war,
among the 72 sects,
there would still be at least
30% supporting it.
But I didn't expect that
I couldn't find even three sects.
As you all know,
these sects are spread across the Eastern Continent.
It was...
It was exhausting.
But that's not the main problem.
The real problem is that
we spent a lot of money
from the treasury to send the letters this time.
It's becoming increasingly empty.
You should stop using the term "treasury."
Otherwise,
people will think we're rich.
Well, why don't you start some new business?
Back then,
when Chong Zhao was running that steamed bun stall,
he made quite a lot of money.
Yes.
Speaking of Chong Zhao,
he's already been punished
and has completed his self-reflection.
I think it's time to let him back.
Although he can no longer serve as an Eternal Envoy,
he is, after all,
the head disciple of Lanling Sect.
We can't just let him stay on that mountain forever.
Master Turtle!
Master Turtle, are you there?
I'll be out in a minute! Wait for me in the yard!
Hurry up and find a place to hide.
Coming!
Master Turtle!
I'm here.
-Thank you, Master Turtle.
There's no need.
What's going on lately?
Why do you suddenly need such a large amount of elixirs?
Well,
it's because of Chong Zhao.
They all say that Chong Zhao
is a once-in-a-century genius in Lanling
with limitless potential.
But now he has been given 300 lashes
and sent to Heart-guarding Cliff.
However, with him gone,
the position of the Eternal Envoy in Ning'an City is now vacant.
The Sect Leader said there will be a martial arts competition,
and the winner
will become the new Eternal Envoy.
We expend spiritual power during training,
so we came to ask you
for some elixirs to replenish it.
Chong Zhao
is the Sect Leader's direct disciple.
How did he end up like this?
Well,
he brought it upon himself.
If he had had no other choices,
it would have been acceptable.
But to save someone, he delayed reporting
the news of the Demon Race harming the Human Race
by a day.
Otherwise,
the Demon Race wouldn't have had the chance
to wreak havoc in Ning'an City.
I heard that the person
is the daughter of the governor of Ning'an City.
Do you think Chong Zhao
has fallen in love?
He actually made such a huge mistake for a woman.
Alright.
The high-up Eternals are waiting.
Let's take the elixirs back first.
Master Turtle.
-We're leaving.
-See you.
Go ahead.
What did they mean by 300 lashes?
And what is the Heart-guarding Cliff?
Master.
Have you learned anything these days?
Of all the hardships in the world, guarding the heart is the hardest.
Master,
my resolve
seems to be wavering.
The Eternals are also made of flesh and blood.
On this long journey,
confusion and doubt
are natural things.
The true self-cultivation
is not in the mountains,
but in the bustling world.
Go down the mountain.
Experience what you must experience,
and bear what you must bear.
Right and wrong,
good and evil, cause and effect—
in the end,
you will find the answer.
Master.
Do you still think there is
nothing suspicious about my parents' death?
After your parents' incident,
the entire Lanling Sect was mobilized
and investigated for a whole year,
but in the end, the result was the same.
Chong Zhao,
some things should be let go
when it's time.
Otherwise,
you'll suffer.
Recently, Cold Spring Palace has been very active.
Within three months, they've wiped out three clans.
Zhen Yu has taken the internal elixirs of the three chiefs
to heal the wound from his severed tail.
Being so impatient,
he must be planning to stir up trouble again.
With me here,
Zhen Yu won't stir up any big trouble.
What's the situation at Jingyou Mountain?
The Jingyou Fox Clan has always stayed out of external conflicts.
They didn't make any moves.
The top priority now
is still to help Bai Shuo gather the Five Contemplations.
As for everything else, we can just watch from the sidelines.
Master, I've been wanting to ask you a question.
You compromised with Bai Shuo so many times.
Is it really just because of the Desireless Stone?
Master, I'm boldly reminding you.
Don't let Bai Shuo become your weakness.
Since the day I became the Demon King,
I've had no weaknesses.
Aren't you afraid of the Master punishing you?
Whether you're an Eternal or a Demon,
no matter how strong your sorcery is,
once you fall in love,
you'll have a weakness that can be exploited.
Don't worry.
Our Master
will never fall in love.
No matter what,
if Bai Shuo causes any trouble in the future,
even if it means risking the Master's punishment,
I'll clear the obstacle.
Are you still
thinking about Chong Zhao?
Don't drink too much.
The peach blossom wine is rare.
I've only kept a few bottles.
Alright, alright.
Keep going.
You're my disciple after all.
You can drink as much as my wine you want.
Where is
Heart-guarding Cliff?
The Desireless Stone is still inside you.
You can't run around.
And Chong Zhao delayed reporting the demon situation because of you.
If something happens to you in the Eternal Race,
and he ends up clashing with the sect for you,
what should we do?
Because of me?
For me,
he almost got an entire city killed.
If it hadn't been for the Five Eternals of Lanling arriving in time,
and if my father hadn't sacrificed his life to exchange for Kindness,
the whole city would have been destroyed.
I honestly wish he had never done it for me.
If the Five Eternals had arrived earlier,
maybe the city wouldn't have fallen into chaos,
and maybe my father wouldn't have...
But what right do I have to blame him?
After all,
everything that happened in Ning'an City
was because of me.
Girl,
there are many things in this world
that can't be judged right or wrong.
No one can foresee everything in the world.
Most of the time,
we just
follow our hearts.
The past cannot be changed.
We must look forward.
Yeah.
I can't go back to the past.
To the bright moon,
to the night sky,
to this miserable life,
♫Don't linger, don't regret♫
and to the past that I can't go back to.
Cheers!
♫The last moonlight♫
You're still young!
Why did you say that your life is miserable?
Do you even know what life is?
♫The water from my hometown flows gently♫
Then tell me,
♫Sending me to the distant place♫
what is life?
♫In this life, at this time♫
I can't tell you
what life is.
♫I dare not look back♫
But...
if I must say,
♫Is there the same moonlight♫
life
is the process of going from having nothing
♫on your path?♫
to having nothing again.
The beginning and the end are already set.
♫I'm walking on a never-ending long road♫
But the experiences in between
♫In the vast world, how can I go there?♫
are up to you to decide.
With my thousand years of age,
♫The night wind is chaotic, and the sound of the Qin is broken♫
I can tell you four things not to do:
♫The moonlight is gentle♫
♫All the attachments left are just a dream♫
don't be obsessed,
don't torment yourself,
don't force things,
♫I listen to the past, never enough♫
and don't be pretentious.
Live
♫I sing until I have no voice, only wandering remains♫
your life well.
Understood?
♫I forget the past, don't care anymore♫
Girl,
♫After many cycles♫
I don't know
♫I ended up with desolation♫
how much you've really taken in.
Fine.
Everyone
has to walk their own path.
Whether it's good or bad,
only by experiencing it yourself
will you truly understand.
[On the 22nd of June, in the 9th year of Chenghuai, my husband Chong Tai and I went to the Western Mountain]
[On the 18th of June, in the 9th year of Chenghuai, my husband Chong Tai and I patrolled a remote area in the southern part of the city at night]
[On the 11th of April, in the 9th year of Chenghuai, my husband Chong Tai and I patrolled the city]
On the 7th of May, in the 9th year of Chenghuai,
my husband Chong Tai and I were patrolling the southeast.
We saw a village in the distance,
with paths crisscrossing
and people coming and going.
[Chong Tai, Eternal, Lanling Sect]
[Meng Ning, Eternal, Lanling Sect]
-Look.
-We wanted to enter the village to investigate,
but when we stepped forward, the scene and the people suddenly vanished.
Could this be the mirage in the legend?
That's weird.
Yes.
On the 14th of June, in the 9th year of Chenghuai,
my husband Chong Tai and I were passing through Qingyao Mountain
when we saw a snake demon kill more than ten people.
So we tried to kill the demon,
but she was pregnant.
In the end, we let the baby snakes return to the forests.
I don't know whether what we did was right or wrong.
All the Eternals know that your parents were killed
by a scorpion demon ten years ago.
But do you know
that two days before your parents were killed,
Qian Yin had already died?
You've been investigating for years but have found nothing.
Do you know why?
Because
you've never set foot in the Demon Race.
What you see now
may not be the truth.
And in places you can't see,
the truth
might be right there.
On the 15th of July, in the 9th year of Chenghuai,
the Eternals and demons fought a great battle,
and we lost more than half of our forces.
While we were cleaning up the bodies of the Eternals,
two of them showed no signs of demon injuries.
Since they weren't killed by demons,
how did they die?
Did my parents uncover something
that led to their deaths?
It seems
I really need to visit the Demon Race.
You came after all.
Why do you always want to get physical every time you see me?
I do miss the you
who saved me in Ning'an City.
Don't even mention Ning'an City!
Just the fact that you used the Nether Poison to harm the Human Race
is enough for me to execute you right now!
Is that so?
So today, are you here in the Cold Spring Palace's territory
to kill me
or to beg me?
Take me to see Qian Yin's grave.
How dare you show disrespect to my guest?
Sorry for startling you.
Just like humans,
demons who die
would be buried by their family members,
and monuments would be erected
in their memory.
That
is Qian Yin's grave.
He died on the 15th of July, ten years ago,
and your parents
died on the 17th of July.
You expect me to believe you with just a tombstone inscription?
You've come here with me.
You still won't admit that you believe me?
Ten years of Fortunei
and seven years of wintergreen
can be used to make a fourth-grade elixir,
which can gather spiritual energy.
Twenty years of withered Poria
and thirty years of perilla leaves
can be used to make a third-grade elixir,
which can expand spiritual veins.
A hundred years of refined ice and a thousand years of Snow Lotus
can be used to make a second-grade elixir,
which can refine spiritual foundations.
Master,
why is there no record of first-grade elixirs?
First-grade elixirs?
That's a legend from ancient times.
No one has ever seen one.
Tell me more about it.
Maybe I can make it.
I'm not underestimating you.
A first-grade elixir can even
withstand the thunder tribulation of a high-up Eternal ascending.
It's not an ordinary thing.
I've never made one myself.
You?
Forget it.
If I really manage to make it,
what will my reward be?
You can't make it.
Tell me what the reward will be first.
How about you tell me what reward you want first?
If I make it,
lend me your turtle shell.
The shell of a 1000-year-old Mystery Turtle
can make divination more accurate.
You want my shell?
Don't even think about it.
You're not after my shell,
you're after my life.
If a turtle loses its shell,
it can be easily killed by anyone.
Then where did this shell
come from?
It's the shell of a dead turtle.
You gave me someone's remains?
What's so strange about it?
After I die,
my remains
will be yours too.
How long will that take?
You're really wishing for my death, aren't you?
Of course not.
I just think that a turtle like you
might live longer than I will.
I can't count on
your remains.
Good that you know.
Where are you going?
Going back to sleep.
So you little troublemaker
won't try to get my shell
while I'm asleep.
Now that Old Turtle has left,
the long night
does seem a bit boring.
It's so late now.
I wonder if that Demon King is asleep yet.
Fan Yue?
He really is asleep.
What?
Nothing.
I'm staying up late
making elixirs.
So?
Don't ask me like it's none of your business.
It was supposed to be you teaching me.
But you sent me to Old Turtle
and now you're just sitting back,
enjoying your free time.
Enjoying my free time?
What else would you be doing?
What are you doing?
Are you busy
fighting over territory with the Cold Spring Palace?
Fan Yue.
I'm listening.
Let me tell you,
my alchemy skills are pretty good now.
If I make a first-grade elixir,
even Old Turtle will have to call me Master.
It's said that first-grade elixirs are very powerful.
Once I make one and take it,
both Eternals and demons will be afraid of me.
So will you.
Really?
Just you wait.
♫We're destined to be together forever from the first sight♫
I also learned some divination techniques from Old Turtle.
But I'm not used to
♫Goodbye, loneliness♫
this turtle shell,
♫The one who was slightly late♫
so I haven't been able to get any predictions.
Do you think he's deceiving me?
Deceiving you?
♫You came towards me, closer and closer♫
He's a 1000-year-old turtle.
He's really cunning.
There's a moon here,
a crescent moon.
♫You enriched my life♫
Is there one over there?
So, both the Eternals and demons
are looking at the same moon.
♫The stars light up your eyes♫
All the races live on the same land.
Naturally, they see the same moon.
♫You are the light I yearn for♫
You talked a lot today.
What exactly are you trying to say?
♫You are my determined way home♫
Didn't I tell you?
Staying up late making elixirs is very boring.
Boring?
♫Let this moment stay forever♫
Am I just your entertainment?
Not really.
It's just that when I'm bored,
♫I'm hugging you in the crowd♫
I naturally think of a boring person.
Bai Shuo.
I have things to do. I have to go.
♫Let's never let go♫
Master.
Why are there still so many?
Previously, when you went to Ning'an City,
matters piled up in the Polar Region.
Everyone is waiting for you to make decisions.
Then why
were even trivial matters like disputes
presented to me?
There's no choice.
Among the ten thousand demons in the Polar Region,
no one respects anyone else.
The only one they respect is you, the Master.
If you don't decide the outcome or make a ruling,
they'll keep fighting forever.
So, Master,
please bear with it
and finish reading these files.
Wait.
What can I do for you?
I have a question.
What do you think of when you're bored?
When I'm bored?
Drinking, fighting and sleeping.
I mean, what person do you think of?
I do think of someone.
Who is it?
Can I not tell you?
Why?
I'm embarrassed to tell you the person I like.
Master, I'll leave you to your work.
I'll put these over there for you.
The person she likes?
You killed him?
Yes.
Zhong Zhao trespassed into the Cold Spring Palace's territory.
Lady Fu Ling, not only didn't you capture him,
but you also killed one of your own.
What exactly are you planning to do?
I'm getting more and more confused.
I don't need you to understand.
What?
Is the life of the bear demon not worth anything?
Or is it that
in your heart,
you only care about Chong Zhao's life?
When you used little demons to practice,
did you ever care about their lives?
Besides,
this bear demon almost ruined my plan.
He deserved to die.
For such a trivial matter,
you actually came to report to the Grand Master.
I really underestimated how petty you are.
Enough.
Are you done?
Fu Ling,
tell me about your plan.
Grand Master, you once taught us
that when someone wants something,
we should give it to them.
Even if it's fake,
it must be convincing.
Chong Zhao is investigating the truth behind his parents' deaths,
but he has no leads.
At this point, if I give him a clue—
whether it's real or not—
he will cling to it.
As long as he wants to investigate,
he will have no choice
but to fall into my trap.
Lady Fu Ling,
you truly are a master of strategy.
But don't say I didn't remind you.
You'd better settle this quickly
to avoid future complications.
And don't let any other thoughts take root,
or you might disgrace your identity as the Young Lord of Cold Spring Palace.
Alright.
Since
he has an obsession he can't let go of,
we'll help him strengthen it.
Once he has an inner demon,
he will
be of use to the Cold Spring Palace.
Fu Ling,
I want you
to use every means possible
to force him to abandon being an Eternal, become a demon,
and join
our Cold Spring Palace.
Yes.
Master!
What happened?
Did
the alchemy furnace explode again?
I made it!
Not bad, my disciple.
You can make a second-grade elixir already!
I didn't misjudge you after all.
This time,
I can give Fan Yue a report.
Why should you report to him?
If she fails to learn anything,
I'll strip you of your 1000-year-old turtle shell.
Luckily, your comprehension is exceptional.
It looks like my 1000-year-old turtle shell is safe now.
Today is a good day.
I'll go and get a couple of bottles...
of nectar.
Let's celebrate.
Again?
Yes!
Didn't you go to get the nectar?
How did you come back so quickly?
Bai Shuo?
It's you?
You escaped from the Demon Race?
Are you here to seek help from our Eternal Race?
No, wait.
You are a human.
How did you enter the Eternal Sect?
And why are you hiding here with Old Turtle?
Tell me!
What happened?
Sir, you sure have a big temper.
You just saw me, and now you want to get physical already.
That day, you were kidnapped by Master Bright Moon.
The Eternal Sect sent countless disciples to search for you in the Polar Region.
Now that you've appeared in the Eternal Sect,
come with me to meet the Sect Leade!
You're not looking for me.
You're looking for the Desireless Stone.
The Desireless Stone belongs to the Eternals!
It should stay in Lanling!
But I don't belong to the Eternals.
It makes no difference!
You're carrying a demonic object.
Who are you trying to send a message to?
Is it Master Bright Moon?
I've always said that humans are hard to predict,
and they're easily controlled by demons.
You're a human carrying the Desireless Stone.
Don't even think about leaving!
Chong Zhao!
Get out of my way!
Bai Shuo is innocent.
Uncle Master, you can't kill her!
Shut up!
Don't forget who you are.
She carries the Desireless Stone
and is colluding with the Demon Race.
She is an enemy to our entire Eternal Race!
Don't be so blind!
I'm not the one who's blind.
You are!
Are you saying I'm blind to right and wrong?
I dare not disobey you.
But if you insist on this,
I will have no choice but to go against you!
You are beyond help!
Enough!
Chong Zhao,
this has nothing to do with you.
Entering the Demon Palace that day
was my own choice.
Just like now, I choose not to stay with the Eternals.
As an Eternal, you want to kill a human.
As long as you're at peace with it,
go ahead.
Stop.
Sect Leader, you came at just the right time.
Bai Shuo is colluding with the Demon Race
and sneaked into Lanling. Her intentions must be malicious.
She must be eliminated!
Sect Leader, are you going to kill me too?
Lanling Sect will not kill an innocent person.
I know you didn't do anything wrong.
So, are you willing to let me go?
Of course,
that's impossible.
The Desireless Stone concerns the peace of the world.
As the Sect Leader of Lanling,
I can never allow it to fall into the hands of the demons.
Master!
What do you want?
Rather than letting you return to the Demon Race,
it's better to...
make you forget it.
West sun mountain.
East moon river.
A snake slithers across the grass.
A fish leaps above the sandy sea.
The earth knows, but the sky does not.
Only by stepping in can you find the way.
The head of the Eternal Sect
actually laid hands on a human.
I think
Lanling Sect
should just change its name to Lanling Evil Sect.
Fan Yue!
How dare you break into our Eternal Sect?
Give us Bai Shuo!
I'm here to take you back.
Shuo!
You can't go back to the Demon Race with him!
Fan Yue,
are you really going to go against the entire Eternal Sect?
Bai Shuo is mine.
I allowed her to stay temporarily in the Eternal Sect,
but that doesn't mean Lanling Sect has the right to keep her here.
Sect Leader,
that turtle shell...
It looks familiar.
So familiar.
Sect Leader, I'm innocent!
I was forced by Fan Yue to become Bai Shuo's teacher
for a few days as a way of repaying his favor.
The fact that the Desireless Stone was stolen
has nothing to do with me!
Stop making excuses.
If you hadn't given him the turtle shell,
how could he have broken into our Lanling Sect?
When I gave him the shell to repay his kindness,
I didn't know he was the Demon King.
Your words alone aren't enough to prove it!
Sect Leader,
I'm utterly loyal to Lanling.
Heaven and Earth are my witness.
I didn't betray you!
Please, spare me!
Master,
Old Turtle has been making elixirs for the Eternals for many years.
This time, he was forced by Fan Yue.
Master, please forgive him.
You have no right to plead for Old Turtle!
You dared to attack your teacher,
and you even said I can't tell right from wrong.
It seems the 300 lashes weren't enough for you!
You need a few more!
I didn't mean to offend you.
But if you try to kill Bai Shuo,
I can't just stand by and watch.
I believe
killing innocent people is not something the Eternals should do.
Sect Leader, did you hear that?
He said I kill innocent people!
Alright, Jing Lei.
Stop making things difficult for Chong Zhao.
We've watched him grow up.
We know him very well.
As for Old Turtle…
Lanling
has been using
the black turtle as our totem.
If we really punish him,
we'll become
the laughingstock of the 72 Sects.
So, I'm the bad guy now?
Are you saying we won't punish either of them?
Then tell me, what should we do?
Calm down.
Keep your voice down.
You're about to burst my eardrums.
Old Turtle,
let me ask you.
Since Fan Yue
was able to use your turtle shell to enter our Lanling,
can we use the same shell
to find the Bright Moon Palace?
I've sensed it.
Fan Yue has already
destroyed the teleportation turtle shell he gave me.
Now, no one can pass through.
You contacted our enemies
and leaked our techniques.
What's the use of keeping you?
He's not entirely useless.
Old Turtle's alchemy skills
are considered one of the unique arts of us Eternals.
The elixirs he makes,
if sold to the villages down the mountain,
could bring us some more money.
You want to spare him for just a little money?
A little money?
Senior Jing Lei,
why don't you make some money and show me?
Okay!
Sell it!
Give it to her!
-Give it to her!
-Stop it!
Listen to me! Give it to her!
Stop it!
-Shut up!
Old Turtle,
how about this?
You've been in the sect for years.
You haven't made any significant contributions,
nor have you put in much effort.
You'll be punished
by making 100 more Great Restoration Elixirs every month.
The money from selling them will be used to support the sect.
That's all for now.
100 elixirs?
Doesn't that mean I'll be worked to death?
You're reluctant, aren't you?
In that case,
we'll have to strip off your turtle shell,
break your spiritual bone,
and then...
Say no more.
I'm willing.
Go!
Sect Leader,
Bai Shuo can activate the Desireless Stone,
and she doesn't align with the Eternals.
Please give the order,
and I'll immediately lead the troops to the Demon Race
and bring Bai Shuo back.
I also request to go.
Last time, we sent disciples
to investigate the location of the Bright Moon Palace,
but we still haven't made any progress.
This Fan Yue,
relying on the fact that the Eternal Race can't find him,
is too arrogant.
Is Fan Yue only relying on the fact that the Eternal Race can't find him?
There are only a few of us here.
Let's face the truth.
Even if we find the Bright Moon Palace,
we still won't be able to get Bai Shuo back.
-Feng Yu.
-You…
Can you stop always discouraging everyone?
You should encourage us more.
I'm just telling the truth.
It's better than you guys
deceiving yourselves.
Come on, you...
Alright.
Feng Yu was right.
The key to this matter is not Fan Yue,
but Bai Shuo herself.
Alright, dismiss.
Well, Sect Leader...
Dismiss.
Fine.
What else do you want to say?
I feel like
you're deliberately avoiding
bringing back Bai Shuo and the Desireless Stone.
I, Jin Yao, the 68th Sect Leader of Lanling,
am here to respectfully hear the ancestral teachings of the sect.
Lanling Sect Leader, listen to the order.
The Desireless Stone will be awakened by a human girl.
She is the only one in this world who can activate the divine stone.
If she appears,
Lanling must assist her in activating the Desireless Stone.
This divine decree
is known only
to the Sect Leaders of Lanling.
I will obey the divine decree.
The ancestral teachings of Lanling
have been passed down for tens of thousands of years.
We have been waiting for the human girl
who can activate the Desireless Stone.
Now that
Bai Shuo can awaken the Desireless Stone,
she must be the fated one
in the divine decree.
Isn't this Wutong Heart Flame?
Could the next Contemplation appear in Yi City?
Wutong Heart Flame?
Yi City?
Wutong Heart Flame only appears in Yi City.
And Yi City
is where the Yi Clan lives.
Yi Clan?
I've never heard of it.
Yi Clan is naturally strong,
with incredible strength.
However, due to their limited bloodline,
their cultivation is mediocre.
No matter how hard they try,
they can only cultivate the lowest-level magic.
They have always been discriminated against by the Eternals and demons,
so they live far away in Yi City.
Then what are we waiting for?
Let's depart immediately.
Yi City
is a moving city in the desert,
with its location constantly shifting.
It is usually invisible and impossible to find.
It only opens during the annual
Wutong Martial Arts Contest,
and only on that day
can everyone know its exact location.
So mysterious?
What is Wutong Martial Arts Contest?
A thousand years ago, the Eternal Race and Demon Race
fought endlessly, battling over territories with heavy casualties.
So, the Eternal Lord and Demon King at the time
proposed that the two races
hold an annual martial arts contest to settle their territorial disputes.
The King of Yi,
wanting to reconcile with the Eternals and demons,
agreed to host the contest in Yi City,
with three spirit pills made from Wutong Heart Flame
as the prize for the winner.
Wutong Spirit Pill
is an extremely pure and sacred treasure.
Those who use it
can greatly increase their spiritual power
and improve their cultivation.
In the Desireless Stone, I foresaw
many disciples from both the Eternal Race and Demon Race gathering in Yi City.
It seems they are preparing for the second Contemplation.
We not only need to enter Yi City,
but we also have to hold the Wutong Martial Arts Contest,
allowing disciples from both races
to enter the city as well.
It has been seven years since Yi City last held the Wutong Martial Arts Contest.
Why has it suddenly stopped?
Could something have happened in Yi City?
Why do you have so many questions?
I'm not only doing this for myself;
it's also to help your Master.
Are you still going to keep things from me?
No one is keeping anything.
No one knows why Yi City is closed,
nor does anyone know
where Yi City is now.
You just said
Yi City is a moving city in the desert?
That's right.
What if I tell you
I might know where it is?
How could you possibly know?
The Desireless Stone showed me
a desert
and a children's rhyme.
Not everything in this world can be explained
or answered clearly.
I'm doing this
for my reasons.
Chong Zhao,
do you trust me?
Of course I do.
But Shuo is with the Demon Race.
I'm worried about her.
Don't worry.
Master Bright Moon
needs her to activate the Desireless Stone.
He won't harm her for now.
All we need to do now
is wait for the right opportunity.
Do you understand?
You seem troubled.
Is there something else?
Master,
I found Qian Yin's tombstone.