BOYD:
Previously on
From.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
You feel it. You do.
When I walked inside the ruins,
I think I went somewhere.
You're a Storywalker.
But you can't change a story
once it's been told.
Me and Jade, we try to save
those children, set them free.
We've come back
over and over again
because we failed
the first time.
Knowledge comes with a cost.
[GRUNTS]
[GASPS, CHOKES]
TABITHA:
Where's your father?
He's not back yet.
Wasn't he with you?
TABITHA: Yeah.
We just got separated.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[BOTH GRUNT]
BOYD: Sir, can you hear me?
Dad!
Okay, come on, kiddo.
BOYD: He's okay.
JADE: We need to tell people.
TABITHA: We have no idea
what happened out there.
We don't even know if it's true.
You, me, Jim.
Jim's not home.
Put that down.
She's here to help.
Sara took his eye out
with a screwdriver.
Can you stitch him up?
Once the baby was born,
we were supposed to go home.
It's okay.
We got you. I got you.
ACOSTA: You think you're some
kind of hero? What you did
to that kid up there?
You're a fucking monster.
[SIGHS]
You played a very special role
in a very important story.
I couldn't come
to them as I was.
[GRUNTS]
[BONES CRACKING]
SOPHIA:
Not with
everything they learned.
Are you all right?
I'm lost.
[TIRES SCREECH]
I'm sorry you won't be here
to see what comes next.
It's always my favorite part.
This is when
they tear themselves apart.
[MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[MUSIC CONCLUDES]
Hey, Sophia.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Sophia?
[WOMAN SOBBING]
No. No, no, no.Sophia!
[SOBBING CONTINUES]
Hey, hey. Hey, okay.
Come back inside.
No, I can't.
You need to get back inside.
I can't go back in there,please.
Kenny.
Okay, get inside!
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
Hey!
What'd I tell you?
I told you, you don't
go outside, I told you!
He's dead.
What?
[SOBS]
My father died.
Oh.
SOPHIA: [SOBS]
Okay, okay, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, bud, okay.
Okay, I didn't...
You don't go outside, okay?
I didn't mean to, I just...
I'm sorry.
Hey, what's going on?
He's gone. [SOBS]
It's okay, it's okay.
I don't know
what now. He's gone.
[SOBS]
KENNY: [SHUSHES]
I'm sorry.
You don't go outside, okay?
We're gonna
take care of you now, okay?
[EERIE MUSIC CONCLUDES]
[DOOR OPENS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Boyd.
Uh--
Would you step back
inside for a minute?
What I'm about to say
is not for me.
It's for everyone here.
If people find out
what happened...
what you did...
What we did...
That's the kind of thing
that could tear
this place apart.
And I can't let that happen.
So, if anybody asks,
and they will ask...
you're going to tell them
that you lost your eye
trying to help Fatima.
And if I don't?
Then I will tell everyone
that you killed Tillie.
And then I'm going
to put you in the Box.
You understand
what that means, right?
Right?
Good.
They're going to find out.
One way or another,
the truth always comes out.
Well, if I was you...
I would make sure it doesn't.
[RADIO STATIC]
["GOOD MORNING
GOOD MORNING" PLAYING]
♪ Good morning
Good morning, good morning ♪
Good morning ♪
♪ Nothing to do to save
his life, call his wife and ♪
♪ Nothing to say
but what a day
How's your boy been? ♪
♪ Nothing to do
It's up to you ♪
♪ I've got nothing to say
but it's okay ♪
♪ Good morning
Good morning, good morning ♪
♪ Going to work, don't wanna go
Feeling low down ♪
♪ Heading for home
You start to roam
Then you're in town ♪
♪ Everybody knows
there's nothing doing ♪
♪ Everything is closed
It's like a ruin ♪
♪ Everyone you see
is half asleep ♪
♪ And you're on your own
You're in the street ♪
♪ After a while
you start to smile
Now you feel cool ♪
♪ Then you decide to take
a walk by the old school ♪
♪ Nothing has changed
It's still the same ♪
♪ I've got nothing to say
but it's okay ♪
♪ Good morning
Good morning... ♪
[SONG FADES]
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC CONCLUDES]
["QUE SERA SERA" PLAYING]
♪ When I was just a little boy
♪ I asked my father
what will I be ♪
♪ Will I be handsome?
Will I be rich? ♪
♪ Here's what he said to me ♪
♪ Que sera, sera
♪ Whatever will be, will be
♪ The future's not ours to see
♪ Que sera, sera
♪ What will be, will be
♪ Now I have children
of my own ♪
♪ They ask their father
what will I be ♪
♪ Will I be pretty?
Will I be rich? ♪
♪ I tell them tenderly
♪ Que sera, sera
♪ Whatever will be, will be
♪ The future's not ours to see
♪ Que sera, sera
♪ What will be, will be
[SONG CONCLUDES]
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
No, God, no.
Oh, God.
No, no, no.
What's that?
Go back inside.
Mom, what is that?
Hey.
No, Mom, what is that?
What's in the bag?
I don't know.
What happened?
I don't-- Nothing.
It's okay.
Mom!
Ethan, come on!
Ethan, no, no, no.
No, no, no. Hey!
ETHAN: Is that my dad?
BOYD: No, no, no.
Is that my dad?
Is my dad in there?
BOYD: Hey, everything's okay.
Hey.
Mom.
BOYD: Okay? Everything is okay.
Honey, you shouldn't
be here, honey.
ETHAN: It's not him, right?
It's not him.
Hey, hey, hey.
Listen to me, okay?
You're gonna go...
You're gonna go
with your sister.
You're gonna go down
to the barn, okay?
You're going to
check on the animals.
No, no.
Yes, please, please, Julie.
ETHAN: It's not him, right?
Listen.
ETHAN: It's not him.
BOYD: Listen to me.
Julie, please.
I need you to go
to the barn with Ethan.
I need you to be brave.
Can you do that?
Okay. Take him. Okay.
BOYD: Just try to breathe.
Look at me.
Ethan, we're going
to go for a walk.
It's not him.
We'll go find him, right?
Come on, please.
We'll find him, right?
BOYD: Go with her.
Come on.
Tabitha. Tabitha.
Oh, my God, Boyd.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Get it down.
BOYD: Okay.
Just...
Hey, Jade.
[CROWS CAWING]
[MUSIC CONCLUDES]
It's not him, right?
We need to go find him.
Julie...
we're going to find him, right?
We're going to find him.
You promise?
JADE: Okay.
[GRUNTS]
JADE: I got it.
BOYD: Okay.
JADE: Good.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
BOYD: Nice and easy.
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
Okay.
Stop.
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
[SCREAMS]
[RESIDENTS MURMURING]
TABITHA: Oh, my God.
[SOBS]
Oh, shit.
No, no, no. No, no, no.
Come here. Come here.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. No.
Oh, no.
Oh, Jesus.
[SOBBING]
It's going to be okay.
Hey, hey.
Hey.
[SOBS] Oh, my God!
TABITHA: [CONTINUES SOBBING]
Why?
Why did they do that to him?
[SCREAMS] Why?
[MUSIC FADES]
[SNIFFS, CRIES]
Thank you.
Yeah.
Of course.
What happens now?
Um...
Well, I'll talk to Boyd
about a burial.
Who's Boyd?
KENNY: He's the sheriff.
He's the one that helped
get you out of the car.
He seemed kind.
[LIQUID POURING]
He is.
He is. He's kind of the thing
that holds this whole
place together.
Hey, if you want,
we could take a walk
down into town,
you know? I could show you
around a little bit and...
maybe get you a spare set of
glasses from the storage room.
I'd like that very much,
thank you.
Okay.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
ETHAN: I hate it here!
I hate this place!
Hey! Stop Ethan!
I don't want to be here anymore.
You need to stop, okay?
What did you do?
Why didn't he come home?
I did nothing!
You're lying! You're a liar!
You guys always fight.
I want Dad!
I hate it here!
I hate you!
Please.
[FOOTSTEPS FADING]
We didn't fight.
It doesn't matter.
[SOBS]
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING]
[BOTH BREATHE HEAVILY]
BOYD: I got it. I got it.
JADE: That's it.
I'm gonna go check on Tabitha
and the kids.
I'm good.
JADE: Okay.
ELLIS: Dad.
I'm gonna need some help.
Hey.
Yeah, okay.
Okay.
[MUSIC CONCLUDES]
JADE: Watch your step.
BOYD: All right.
[GRUNTS]
It's okay.
[GRUNTS, BREATHES HEAVILY]
All right.
Let me get the door open.
You good?
All the way to the end.
Yep.
[GRUNTS]
We need to clean him up before
Tabitha and the kids see him.
BOYD: Yeah.
"Knowledge comes at a cost."
The fuck does that even mean?
We need to talk.
Sara.
Sara, what's...
What's going on?
They found Jim
in the barn this morning.
Is he, um...
Uh...
Um...
I'm gonna need you
to head back up to the clinic.
But you said
we'd get new glasses.
Are you going
to the storage room?
Yeah.
I can take her.
No.
You're Sophia, right?
I'm Sara.
I used to work at the diner.
I know where
all the good stuff is.
Okay, okay. Yeah.
I know you two were close.
I'm sorry.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
SARA: Come on.
[MUSIC CONCLUDES]
JADE: The children...
The seven kids,
they kept saying this word
over and over again.
Anghkooey.
BOYD: Okay.
When we played
the song at the tree,
it was like something unlocked.
And we finally understood.
Anghkooey.
It means "remember."
And we did.
"Knowledge comes at a cost"?
That's why they wrote it.
It killed Jim because of us.
"If we push too hard,
something would push back."
What's that?
Something Sara said
once we were out in the woods.
Her brother, he had a theory
about this place.
He didn't think looking
for answers was a good idea.
[EXHALES]
So what do we do now?
Assuming you're right, that you
and Tabitha have been
coming back here
over and over and over,
that these kids keep calling you
back to help them,
how do we do it?
I mean, how do you even
begin to save something
that's... already dead?
I don't know.
I'm working on it.
Yeah.
Work harder.
Come on.
[DOOR SHUTTING]
SARA: Give me a second.
Mm-hmm.
Hey.
Are you all right?
We're not friends.
Don't talk to me
like we're friends.
Okay.
It's right through here.
Come on.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Ethan?
Julie?
Where's my mom?
Uh...
She'll be back. She just had
to step out for a minute.
Can I get you something?
I'm going for a walk.
I want someone to go with you.
It's the middle of the day,
Donna. I'll be fine.
I just need to...
Okay.
Uh, Ethan's asleep.
DONNA: Julie?
If you need anything,
you just ask me, okay?
[GRUNTS]
Randall?
Randall.
What the hell do you want?
Hey, what happened?
My dad is... [CRIES]
Jesus Christ.
JULIE: [CRIES]
Hey, look, I'm sorry.
No, don't, don't.
I need your help.
Yeah, okay.
I need you to come back
to the ruins with me.
Why?
Because I'm gonna save him.
RANDALL: Julie.
[SCUBS VIGOROUSLY]
TABITHA:
[BREATHES HEAVILY, CRIES]
[DOOR OPENING]
TABITHA: [BREATHING HEAVILY]
Tabitha.
Get out.
No, listen, please. I just--
I said get out!
This means it's real.
The memories.
Everything they showed us.
It's real.
It is real.
I don't give a shit.
Do you understand?
I don't fucking care.
Look, I can't even imagine
what you're going through.
I know you don't
want to hear this right now,
but what they did...
this message...
[SCRUBBING CONTINUES]
I think they're doing it
to stop us from digging further.
They're trying
to make us afraid.
Well, then it worked.
Because I'm fucking terrified.
My husband's dead.
Do you understand?
You have to think
about your children now.
[SCOFFS]
You know what?
Fuck you.
What do you know, huh?
What do you know?
Do you want to go back
to The Bottle Tree
and play your stupid violin?
Because you got nothing to lose.
Because you don't give a shit
about anybody but yourself.
That is not true.
It should have been you...
hanging from the fucking rafter.
It should have been you.
Fuck it.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[ENGINE STARTS]
Hey!
Fuck.
Hey, hey, hey!
Turn it off.
Fuck!
Turn off the engine
and get out of the ambulance.
No.
No.Hey.
Are you insane?
Get the fuck out
of the ambulance.
You want to go for a ride?
I'm coming with you.
Jesus Christ.
KRISTI:
It's okay. It's okay.
Come out, Kristi.
KRISTI: It's okay.
Fine.
Hey! Stop!
[MUSIC CONCLUDES]
Kenny.
I heard about Jim.
Yeah.
They left us a message
this time. That's new.
Yeah, but Jade
has a theory about that.
Sure, everybody's got a theory.
No, there might be
something to this one.
Boyd! [BREATHES HEAVILY]
Kristi's in trouble.
What?
Acosta took the ambulance.
She's got Kristi inside.
A tad big.
Okay. Um..
Nope, those do not work.
[CHUCKLES]
How about these?
Those look good.
SOPHIA: So, um...
It's so sad.
All these things... they...
they belong to people
that were trapped here?
Yeah.
I wonder who these belonged to.
Um... It's kind of nice,
though. I mean,
there's a part of them
that's still here,
a part that's... not forgotten.
I've never really thought
of it that way.
What happened
this morning to that man?
Does that sort of thing
happen a lot?
It never used to.
For a long time after Boyd
found the talismans,
things were...
It happens a lot more often now.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said that.
It's okay. It's important
to be honest about things. Um...
My dad used to always say that.
Do you have family here?
No.
Not anymore.
[SIGHS]
Uh...
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
You must be hungry.
We should get some food.
Yeah, I am. I'm starving.
Come on.
[MUSIC CONCLUDES]
[SIGHS]
[CAR APPROACHING]
What the fuck?
Here they come.
What?
Hey!
No, wait. Don't go!
What's going on?
Acosta's got Kristi
in the ambulance.
Where the fuck are they going?
BOYD: God damn, Acosta.
DONNA: What the hell?
BOYD: All right.
So everyone says
there's no way out, right?
You just go round and round?
Well, I didn't.
The night I got here,
we drove in,
we stopped in the road,
and then everything just...
It all fucking exploded,
and then I took
all of you at your word.
Why should I believe
a single thing you people say?
Look, is this about Elgin?
Look, you need to understand--
No, I don't need
to understand shit, all right?
Fuck. You're a doctor.
You're supposed to help people.
You really okay with that?
Oh, I'm not okay
with any of this.
And you're a cop.
And what you're doing
is gonna get people hurt.
No.
What I'm doing is getting out.
Right fucking now.
[CAR ACCELERATES]
RANDALL: Julie.
Look, Julie, slow down.
Slow down.
So what? We step inside
the ruins and then what?
We walk through time?
Ethan called it Storywalking.
Okay, great.
That doesn't make it
any fucking better. Julie, stop.
You can't--
What?
Like, what happened?
With your dad?
What you're going
through right now.
Hey, you gotta take a breath.
And what?
What do I do then, huh?
I am telling you,
when I walked into those ruins,
I went somewhere.
Okay?
If I did it once,
I can do it again.
Even if there is
the slightest fucking chance,
I have to try.
Please.
Just tell me
what you need me to do.
[SOBS]
Why didn't you come home, Jim?
[SNIFFS]
I was waiting for you.
Why didn't you come home?
[SOBS] I'm so angry at you.
All night I thought about
what I wish I said to you
in the woods.
I thought about the fact that...
I've loved you since
the first moment I saw you.
There's been so much fighting,
so much pain.
You were still my person.
You're my everything.
I'm so afraid
you didn't know that.
How am I supposed to do this
without you here?
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING]
We're gonna be okay.
Julie and Ethan.
I don't know how...
but I'm going to find a way
to take care of them,
to keep them safe.
You don't have to be afraid.
I love you, Jim.
Goodbye.
BOYD: Here we go.
Hey, get out of the way.
Hey, stop!
Okay, slow down.
BOYD: Stop!
Slow down. Slow down.
Stop! Stop!
[OVERLAPPING SHOUTING]
Fuck. You're going way
too fucking fast right now.
We've been through town
twice already.
What more do you need to see?
There's got to be a way.
I'm not just going to sit around
and wait for those things
to pick us off one by one.
You guys just hang
your rocks at night.
You pretend you're safe,
thinking that Sheriff Boyd
is going to what,
somehow save you?
Let me tell you something,
Boyd... Boyd doesn't know
what he's doing.
None of you people know
what the fuck you're doing.
But you do.
Yeah, well, at least I'm trying.
That was a lot faster.
Yeah, that's the pattern.
She's looking for a way out.
She's just going to get
more and more...
What do we do?
Get the strip.
Yeah.
Victor?
You in here?
VICTOR:
You shouldn't have come here.
Hey.
I...
I heard about Jim. I'm sorry.
You shouldn't have come here.
You should never
have come to this place.
Have you gone to see Ethan yet?
No.
No? Okay.
I can't.
You can't?
Well, Victor,
he's your friend, and...
he needs you,
so when you're ready...
Those words on the wall...
The words, sure, yeah.
Yeah.
You see, this place
takes everything good.
It takes everything...
everything good away.
And then what
if it takes you next?
Me? Well,
I'm not going anywhere.
No, no.
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
You don't know that.
No.
Okay.
VICTOR: So you just
shouldn't have come.
You shouldn't...
You shouldn't have
come to this place.
You should never have c...
Hey, hey, hey, listen.
No one should have
come to this place.
Hey, none of us.
But, you know, we're here.
You and me, and we're together.
I'll take that
any day of the week,
no matter what
gets written on the walls.
We...
We face this together.
Okay? Okay?
So you just... walk inside?
Yeah.
And then what?
Then I find my dad.
You go first.
What?
Just... walk inside.
Why?
Will you just do it, please?
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
What's supposed to happen?
Nothing.
I... I just had to make sure
that the same thing
wasn't gonna happen to you
when you come in to get me.
Come back.
Look, look.
I need you to give me some time
before you pull me out.
Okay?
Even if it looks bad.
What do you mean
if it looks bad?
Julie, what's gonna happen?
Promise me. Please.
Okay, fine.
You have to promise.
Promise!
All right, yes. I promise.
JULIE: Okay.
[CREATURE 1 SCREAMING]
[CREATURE 2 SCREAMING]
Dad!
BOYD: All right, you guys.
Get out of here. Go!
Go! Go!
[GUNSHOTS]
Dad!
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS]
Get off me!
But I want to play.
[GRUNTS]
Come on, come on.
Randall!
Randall, pull me out!
There's no one here to help you.
No!
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS]
[SCREAMS] No, no, no!
Look at me. Look at me.
It's okay.
I saw him. Oh, Randall.
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
Oh, my god. I saw him.
You saw him.
I saw him, but I couldn't--
I have to go back!
No, no, no, stop.
No, no, no.
Hey, stop, stop, stop.
Oh, God! [SOBS]
I got you.
I have to go back.
Ethan?
[KNOCKS]
Ethan, can I come in?
Ethan?
Donna?
Ethan's not up there.
What?
I was here the whole time.
Ethan?
Tabitha, he was upstairs!
Ethan!
[GRUNTS]
All right. Got it?
KENNY: Yeah.
Hey, she's gonna be okay.
[ENGINE RUMBLING]
My mom, she...
She always believed in hell.
But you know what I think?
I think hell
is for people who think
that they deserve to suffer,
and I don't.
I am a good person,
and I don't deserve to be here.
None of us deserve to be here.
I don't know that. I don't.
I don't know a single thing
about you people.
And you know,
maybe the real reason
that you don't try harder
is that deep down you think
that you deserve to be here.
The real reason
we don't try harder
is because every time we do,
somebody fucking dies.
Do you know
how many people I've known
who thought they knew
exactly what this place is?
How many theories
I've listened to
on why we're all here?
Or brilliant ideas
on how to get out?
You want to know
what they all have in common?
They're all fucking dead.
There is no way out.
Do you understand that?
No! Okay?!
There's a way!
There is a way!
There is always a way.
Ethan.
Okay, pull over.
He's fine.
He's a fucking kid
in the woods whose father
just died. Pull over!
No, no, no.
Hey, come on.
Marielle. Let's go.
Okay.
Let's go, let's go.
Fuck.
KRISTI: Stop!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Kristi!
Are you okay?
BOYD: Hey, get the fuck
out of the car.
Get the fuck out!
KENNY: Hey, you good?
Yeah.
What the fuck
is wrong with you, huh?
You could've killed somebody,
you know that?
Turn around.
ACOSTA: [GRUNTS]
[HANDCUFFS CLATTER]
Fucking driving like
a crazy fucking person out here.
[HANDCUFFS FASTEN]
Huh? Answer me!
Boyd!
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
BOYD: Let's go. Let's go.
Ethan.
What?
Ethan, he was walking
on the road.
BOYD: What?
Yeah.
Dad?
Ethan.
JIM: [SIGHS]
ETHAN: [GRUNTS]
God. Oh.
What are you doing out here?
I came to get the radio.
[SIGHS]
It's broken.
I thought maybe
I could send Thomas a message.
The real Thomas.
That he should look for you
so you wouldn't be alone.
What's wrong?
Everything's okay.
Do you remember
what I told you last time
we were here at the RV?
That when bad things happen,
we have to look after each other
and always do our best?
That's right.
And your mom and your sister...
they need that from you now
more than ever.
You're not staying, are you?
I wish that I could.
Dad... what's happening?
I need you to do something
very important.
The night we arrived
here and we crashed the RV
and we were trapped inside...
you had a dream.
Do you remember
what you dreamt about?
The Lake of Tears?
That's right.
Do you know why?
It's here.
And I need you to find it.
Why can't we find it together?
TABITHA: Ethan![GASPS]
TABITHA: Ethan!
Dad?
Dad, where are you?
Ethan!
Dad, come back!
Dad, please come back!
Ethan, Ethan!
Baby, why are you here?
I was so worried.
I saw Dad.
He was right here.
Oh, my baby.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC CONCLUDES]