And Music of the Week…
MARS!
Po!
Let me… go home now.
You came home?
Wait. Are you saying you didn’t…
I ruined last night’s date, didn’t I?
Next time, I’ll watch a
movie at your place again.
Can we say I'm your boyfriend now?
That's up to you.
I don't know if you're
going to call me that,
but I will.
My boyfriend.
Why are you watching me sleeping?
Well…
you look cute.
Was… last night okay?
Mm.
Do I really have to go
back to the group’s house
and check the music chart?
Are you staying here for good?
I want to, honestly.
It’s time for me to leave.
I’ll get going.
One, two, three.
Yay!
Did we win that chart already?
Not yet.
- What are you guys celebrating for then?
- Come on.
We’re celebrating because
you’ve finally grown up.
Congrats, bro.
That's how it should be.
The student I’ve nurtured.
You? Come on.
Give me the credit, okay?
Eh?
You're number one when it
comes to taking credit, dude.
How is the chart going, by the way?
This one is pretty hard to climb.
If we rank number one,
we stand a high chance
to win the remaining three.
I already opened the page.
All you have to do is to
press the refresh button, man.
1. WOULD YOU MIND? - ICE
I’ll refresh now, okay?
Yeah.
I’ll do it now.
Uh-huh!
- I’ll do it for real now. - Yeah!
Damn it!
- Our song is number one! - For real?!
Woo-hoo!
Number one!
Great job.
- We did it, guys. - Great job.
We did it.
Great job, guys.
I need to tell my mommies now.
Let me check it one more time.
Eh? Where are you going?
ONLY THREE MORE CHARTS TO
GO AND WE’RE GOING TO PAK
I WISH YOU WERE HERE WITH ME NOW
Whoa.
Look at those crazy in love.
Those in love are annoying, aren’t they?
You’re right, Dylan.
Did I mishear that?
You two actually agreed?
Oops, I don’t think so.
I bet it’s destiny.
You want a smack?
I’m kidding.
What’s up?
Did you see the leaked news about MARS?
Huh?
Check it now
because I think you can
explain the whole thing to me.
LEAKED IT! FAMOUS IDOL SPOTTED
BRINGING HIS SPECIAL SOMEONE TO HIS CONDO!
Do you have anything to say?
I saw the photos on my timeline already.
How long have you been hiding this?
Well,
I can explain it.
What’s the point of explaining it
now?! It’s too late, don’t you know?!
Hey.
I’m sorry.
- I just… - Why, Po?!
Why does it have to be my bias?
Why does it have to be Pepper?
LEAKED IT FAMOUS IDOL SPOTTED BRINGING
HIS SPECIAL SOMEONE TO HIS CONDO!
LET ME DIG UP MORE INFO #PEPPERMARS
REAL OR JUST FOR HYPE? #PEPPERMARS
CYBER DETECTIVES ON
THE CASE NOW! #PEPPERMARS
"WHO SAYS" IS BLOWING UP. MEMBER
SCANDAL LEAKS. IT'S OVER #PEPPERMARS
If the person you like likes someone else,
how do you feel?
SAYS HE LOVES US BUT SLEEPS
WITH ANOTHER WOMAN #PEPPERMARS
ARE THEY JUST USING FANS
FOR MONEY? #PEPPERMARS
If you don’t get it, then shut up.
SO LET DOWN. I DON'T WANT TO
SUPPORT HIM ANYMORE #PEPPERMARS
WHAT'S WRONG WITH THAT? HE
JUST HAS A GIRLFRIEND, RIGHT?
Being in an idol group means there are a
lot of rules and expectations to follow.
Telling the fans you love them
doesn't hit the same anymore
because your heart's
already with someone else.
I’LL STOP SUPPORTING THEM I
DON’T LIKE A LIAR #PEPPERMARS
See?
This is because a golden
rule for idols is that
they can’t be in a relationship.
PEPPER KNEW IT FULL WELL, BUT WHY DID
HE END UP DOING IT ANYWAY? #PEPPERMARS
I HAVE NO MORE PASSION TO SUPPORT HIM #PEPPERMARS
WHEN IS THE COMPANY RELEASING A STATEMENT? #PEPPERMARS
WE NEED YOUR ANSWER @ONERENTERTAINMENT
@ONERENTERTAINMENT WILL PROBABLY JUST PLAY DUMB
AGAIN @ONERENTERTAINMENT DON’T KEEP QUIET, OKAY?
Hello, yes?
Oh, if we’re having a press conference,
we’ll inform you later.
Yes. As for now,
- we couldn’t reach him yet.
- Yes. Goodbye.
Yes. Okay.
- Hello? Yes? - Hello?
Oh, I see.
Please give me a second.
Please hold the line for a
moment. I’ll transfer you.
HOW IS PEPPER NOW?
What did Gam say?
She told me to clear things
up with you guys first.
I’m sorry.
I… made everything worse.
Relax, bro.
Nothing is ruined, okay?
Let’s focus on both of you first.
How are you feeling now?
I think you should go be with her now.
How could I go?
- We’re now focusing on the
charts and... - We’ll take care of it.
Go to see her.
Be careful.
Don’t let anyone see you with Gam,
or else she will get dragged into this.
Avoid going to the condo.
Tell Gam
not to worry about it.
I don’t think anyone has the photo
that can identify it’s her.
But…
Go, bro.
I’m thanking you all on her behalf.
- Have you seen the news? - Yep.
This one, right?
Who do you think Pepper’s girlfriend is?
I have no idea. Her face isn’t seen.
Exactly.
I'm sorry you had to go through
something like this because of me.
Sit down.
Why are you saying sorry?
We’ve prepared for this since
our first day, haven’t we?
It’s true,
but I’m still worried about
what’s going to happen to you.
I’m fine.
Fine?
Your situation is even worse.
With all this negative buzz,
it’s now even harder
for you to win the charts.
Your group reunion won’t be successful.
What should we do?
Has anyone taken any action?
Did they hold a press conference or
release the statement for the fans?
What should we do? Why is it that I can't
think of anything for stuff like this,
but I can come up with ideas
for other things so easily?
Why are you smiling?
Don’t you see that I’m stressed out?
I’m just impressed.
Instead of worrying about yourself,
you’re now trying to figure out
how to solve a problem for my group.
Why are you this adorable, huh?
I’m not adorable. I’m pretty.
Roger that. Got it.
Well…
If anyone finds out it’s
me, I’m totally fine.
I’ve prepared for that since
the first day I started dating you.
So, now you should stop worrying about me
and prioritize your group and yourself.
Okay?
But I certainly won’t let this affect you.
I don’t want anything to happen to you.
Per, honestly,
I’m wondering why the
photos got leaked now.
Those photos were taken a
long time ago, weren't they?
Even before you returned
to the group’s house, right?
Yeah. Dylan said the same thing.
Someone intentionally leaked the photos.
That’s why I’m here at Oner to talk it out.
Let me know what she says.
Yeah. Talk to you later.
Ah. Here you are.
Miss Pemika asked for you.
And… Why is Po…
You will understand everything soon.
As for you, come with me. Now.
Are you asking for me too?
It’s about Pepper’s scandal.
I thought we were on the same page.
I thought you’d allow MARS
to really prove ourselves,
but you’re doing this to get in our way.
You thought I leaked Pepper’s photos?
And you didn’t?
Yes, I did,
but it wasn’t for stopping
your song from winning the chart.
For what then?
To conceal this scandal.
Leak It sent me these photos,
saying they’d release this scandal.
I was left with not many choices.
I had to exchange the other
member’s news to save you,
or I had to pay Leak It to save you
because I won’t let this
ruin your fame, no matter what.
So, you chose to ruin Pepper’s instead?
Your value is higher than his, Thame.
You’re in my business
plan, but Pepper isn't.
To say it correctly,
both of you broke the rule.
Among these four,
saving you is already enough.
What did you do to Po?
So, the traitor I’ve been searching
for isn’t Jun, but Po, right?
What did you do to him?
And what do you think I should do
to the person who got in and
caused damage to the company?
Leave all of MARS’s footage with Tae.
You have no right to take any of it.
I’m sorry, but what’s going on?
But this whole thing isn’t his fault.
If you’re to punish someone for this,
it should be me.
Thame,
this industry doesn't revolve around
what’s right or wrong or fairness.
It’s about who can sell more
and who the market demands.
And that person will always
appear spotless in everyone's eyes.
Right now, no matter
what mistakes you make,
the company will protect you at all costs.
If we have to choose between Ice and you,
the company will still choose you.
Listen up.
What you’re choosing is your work plan,
not me.
That’s true,
but if you want me to
follow your work plan,
you must handle it just as you told me.
Try figuring out the solution, Thame.
If you want the company to handle it,
this is the only way possible.
Damn it.
What’s up, troublemaker?
Mick,
where did you take Po?
- Did you fire him? - Yeah.
Hey,
he works a lot better than you.
What are you talking about?
Nobody works better than I do.
If there wasn’t someone like me,
would there even be an example
of "easy work with good pay"?
But don’t worry.
Why would I ask Miss Pemika to fire him?
Having him here makes my
life even more comfortable.
Huh?
But you said "yeah"?
I mean, I moved him from working with MARS
to working with Ice now.
Bro, can you go grab my bag for me, please?
- It’s downstairs. - Oh, sure.
You’re all right?
Are you okay?
Thame, relax.
I’m totally fine.
Thank you for coming to see me
while it’s really such a mess out there.
I just want to make sure
you’re really okay.
I’m good.
I’ll do everything to show you
that no matter what happens,
we’re going to be fine, too.
Yeah.
Go already. I’m sure it’s
really chaotic out there.
Give me one moment.
I really have to go.
Please thank Ice for me.
Come back already.
We’ve got big trouble here.
What?
Our fanbase account decided to rest.
DUE TO THE RUMORS THAT
ARE CURRENTLY A HOT TOPIC
WE WILL BE PAUSING
UPDATES ON THE GROUP'S NEWS
All right. I’ll head back now.
I have to go.
Our fanbase account decided to rest.
What?
BAIFERN
PO
WHAT’S WRONG?
WHY DID YOU CLOSE YOUR ACCOUNT?
- Hello? - Fern,
why did you close your account?
Do you think I wanted to do that?
I didn’t want to do it either.
But I'm mentally breaking down right now.
Do you understand?
Don’t let your emotions take over, okay?
You're running a fanbase account.
Shutting it down all of
a sudden has a big impact.
It'll seem like Sphere
will stop supporting them.
Po, when I became his
fan, I followed my heart.
Now that I'm mentally breaking down,
can't I follow my heart too?
Did you do what I asked you to?
Are you really going to use this method?
Yeah.
I already told Per about
this when he came back.
We have to protect both
our dreams and our love.
No matter what, we have
to make it work, right?
But what Thame said is right.
Because of Pepper’s scandal,
more people searched for our group’s name.
True.
I already scrolled through it.
People are really searching
for our group's name more.
It seems they want to know
who we are and what we do.
And it seems to have an
impact on our song, too.
A scandal doesn’t only
have negative effects,
but it creates buzz too.
The point is,
how do we turn it to our advantage?
Are you saying
we should push the buzz
about why idols aren't allowed to love?
This is actually the question
people have always been asking.
They’re already wondering if it’s fair
for idols to not have their private lives.
What if they throw a question back at us?
Like, if you knew the rule from the start,
you shouldn’t have decided to be an artist?
Shit. What if someone
really wants to be an idol?
Aren’t there any other
choices for them about the rules?
The point is,
Per and I dating someone doesn’t mean
we love our fans less than before.
What we’re doing now,
trying to keep the group going,
isn’t just for ourselves.
We’re doing it for our fans, too.
I’m totally fine with
everything you guys said,
but I’m just wondering
if this buzz can really help
our song climb up the chart.
I’ll consult with Gam.
Fern,
I understand how awful
you must be feeling now,
but let me ask you something.
Does the fact that he’s dating
make you like him less?
Frankly speaking,
yes, a bit.
I just feel like
they won’t love us the way they did before.
Previously,
we were their everything.
But now, I’m no longer sure
what we actually are to them.
Hey.
Let me tell you something.
From filming their documentary
for some time already,
I can tell there’s no way
they will love you guys less.
Do you know why?
That’s because you’re part of their dreams,
their future, and their lives.
No matter if they’re dating someone or not,
without you,
they won’t be able to
protect their dreams at all.
Damn it, Po.
That sounds like
being a fan means providing
scholarships to kids with dreams.
I was being so damn emotional,
but you went all about merits.
Activate your account, okay?
Only you can help him.
You know well
it’s not that everyone will
understand this whole thing.
And I bet you know better than I do
that during this time,
it’s really easy for
anti-fans to ruin them.
Fine. I get it now.
I’ll reopen the account now.
But can you tell them something for me?
Let them take action. Anything will do.
He can either admit or deny it.
Fans just want to know the truth.
Uh-huh. I now understand
what Thame is about to do.
You’re appearing on a show
to promote your song, right?
I think they will ask you about this.
Actually, you can start from that.
But if you want to start that topic,
you mustn’t make them feel like
you’re avoiding their questions.
But if you want to answer, go ahead.
We’ve been well prepared for this anyway.
We’ll hold hands and
get through this together.
I’ll help check the buzz for you guys.
Things will turn out well. Trust me.
By the way,
your fanbase account is
activated already, right?
Yes.
It’s settled now, then.
Okay.
MUSIC OF THE WEEK CAN WE REVEAL IT ALREADY?
WHO ARE YOU, HUH? HOW DARE
YOU GET INVOLVED WITH MY BIAS!
- YOU'RE NOT WORTHY OF PEPPER!
- WILL HIS FAME FADE BECAUSE OF THIS WOMAN?
- THEY DON'T EVEN SUIT EACH OTHER -
IT'S YOUR FAULT "WHO SAYS" IS DROPPING
I’M SURE SHE’S THE WOMAN IN THAT SCANDAL
- HOW DARE YOU THROW YOURSELF AT PEPPER?
- YOU’RE SUCH A CAREER KILLER
Play deaf da dub dub da dub
Da dub dub da dub
Don't care what they say, I play deaf
Who says what? I’m not
listening, my heart’s too loud
Sorry, I can’t hear you now
Welcome MARS!
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. Hello. - Hello.
Oh, come on.
Since you’re this popular,
why wouldn’t we invite
you to our show again?
Am I right?
I’M GOING TO SUE MAKING
MY HEART RACE LIKE THIS
We’re so overwhelmed now.
Today’s viewership is a real
phenomenon for our live stream.
We’ve never had this
many people tune in before.
Wow, the live stream
viewership is at 350 K now.
PEPPER, YOU SHAMELESS PERSON!
BETRAYING THE FANS, HIDING A GIRLFRIEND!
That’s totally amazing.
Is there anything you want
to say to the viewers, MARS?
First, we want to apologize to everyone
for not taking any action
sooner about the whole thing.
Everything that happened in the past
has made us realize a lot of things.
What I want to tell everyone is…
- WHAT’S GOING ON?
- THIS IS PEPPER’S GF’S ACCOUNT
- THAT’S THE ONE!
- LOOK AT HER HAIRSTYLE IT’S DEFINITELY HER
WHY DID YOU CHOOSE THIS BITCH?
SHE’S BEAUTIFUL BUT OBVIOUSLY OLDER
I’M DISAPPOINTED
Got it.
I’m sorry,
but we’ve just been informed by the company
that they will be
holding a press conference.
Anyway, all the fans,
please wait for the company’s statement.
Now, let’s continue
checking out music videos.
The company is holding a press conference?
About what?
Hey.
Pepper’s girlfriend’s
photo is on X already.
- Have you seen it? - Not yet. Show me.
There you go.
Whoa.
Clear enough, huh?
That’s Miss Gam.
Whoa. I can’t believe it.
There’s a huge age gap.
Netizens these days are scary.
They’re digging up her
info as if she killed someone.
You’re right.
It’s Miss Gam?
She didn’t pick up my call.
She must be running an errand or something.
- Hello? - Hello, Thame?
It’s Gam.
Why didn’t you pick up Per’s call?
Well, I just finished the meeting.
I want to discuss it with you first
because I came up with a new plan,
and I already talked to your company.
The show already mentioned
that Oner will be holding
a press conference, right?
But before that,
give me some time to talk to Per.
Hello, members of the press.
We’d like to thank
everyone for being here today
to attend this press conference
and hear our side of the current issue
about the leaked photos of
Pepper, one of MARS' members.
This has led to rumors
that he is in a relationship
with the woman in the photo.
Pepper will personally
clarify the situation.
I’m Pepper, from MARS.
I would like to apologize
for everything that happened,
and I would like everyone to rest assured
that she and I are no longer together.
Let’s break up.
Are you talking about us
pretending to break up for now?
This is your new plan, right?
No.
I’m talking about a real breakup, Per.
Gam!
Regarding the person in the photo,
I admit that
we were in the talking stage for a while,
but there's nothing between us now.
Why?
Is it because of the leaked photos?
But you told me that though it’s
leaked, it’d be fine, didn’t you?
Before this, it was fine,
but actually, it isn’t.
Hold on.
But you told me we’d never
let go of each other’s hands.
My members and I have been
trying every possible way.
I…
It wasn’t easy for me to build
myself up to where I’m today.
So, is it fair for random
people to tear me down like this,
as if I murdered someone?
Gam.
Don’t listen to those comments, okay?
We don’t know their identities.
We don’t even know if they’re real.
But if affects my job
and the people in my company.
That’s why I need to care.
Now, our relationship is
simply that of good colleagues.
Lately, it's been other teams
from that company handling
work with MARS instead.
As for the leaked photos
circulating on social media,
they were taken late last year.
As for the photos at the event,
it’s true they were taken
three months ago, but by that time,
there was nothing between us anymore.
You have things you need to protect,
and so do I, Per.
I’d like to ask everyone
not to bring her up anymore,
as she is not a public figure like I am.
I’ve been trying so hard
to become who I am today.
I can’t stand losing it.
I…
I’m sorry.
And most importantly…
But I just can’t handle
this kind of pressure anymore.
Right now, she and I…
are no longer involved with each other.
In my heart now,
apart from my members,
there is only our Sphere.
It's unfortunate that this scandal
came out during your comeback.
I’m fine,
but our fans must be so shocked.
Let’s consider the
latest song we just released
as both a declaration of love and
a comforting message from all of us.
Please accept it.
All right, everyone.
I hope that today, we've
cleared up all the issues.
Thank you so much for today.
I thought you wouldn’t come.
You want to talk to me, don’t you?
Yes.
What do you want to talk about? Go ahead.
I just don’t get it,
why things turned out this way.
Thame has figured out a way, hasn’t he?
And…
I heard that you also agreed.
Actually, I think Thame’s
solution might work out.
- But why… - But it takes time.
And this huge amount
of time would stop them
from hitting number one on every chart.
Having to carry me along like this
will prevent them from succeeding.
1. WOULD YOU MIND?
- ICE 2. TEDDY BEAR - AMECHAN
1. WOULD YOU MIND? - ICE 2. WHO SAYS - MARS
1. WOULD YOU MIND?
- ICE 2. TEDDY BEAR - AMECHAN
I'm in so much pain
because I had to lie to Per,
that what I have is more valuable than him,
while he’s the most valuable to me.
But I want him to be an
idol again with his members.
I want him to realize how
important he is to the group
and to stop blaming himself
for putting MARS in trouble.
If that’s the case,
you two didn’t have to really break up.
But that means he’d
have to lie to his fans.
It would be even worse.
This world isn’t that kind to us.
Time can’t help us with everything.
But I know what I can do for MARS.
Do you mean…
Do you know what’s going
to happen from now on?
My issue will be a game-changer.
POST UPLOADED
THEY'RE FRAMING HIM FOR SURE
LET'S HELP MARS GET AN ALL-KILL!
WHY DIG UP THE PAST WHEN IT'S ALREADY OVER?
MARS MEMBERS ARE SO CUTE! SENDING
THEM LOTS OF LOVE. FROM NANO’S MOMMY
MOMMY IS SENDING YOU SUPPORT
MARS MUST GET AN ALL-KILL
THIS GROUP’S SONG IS GOOD CHECK IT OUT NOW
EVERYONE, GO VOTE AND MAKE
THE ANTIS EXPLODE WITH RAGE!
LET'S SAVE OUR BOYS
WHAT’S WRONG WITH IDOLS BEING IN LOVE?
INTRODUCE THIS GROUP TO
ME I WANT TO SUPPORT THEM
AN IDOL IS A HUMAN TOO. HE
SHOULDN’T BE TREATED LIKE THIS
And that’s the love I can give Per,
which is bringing back his dream.
PEPPER MARS
OMG!
Guys, they did it!
MARS has now got an all-kill!
Really?
Yeah!
They won!
See?!
- Whoa! - Wow!
Guys, they did it!
Amazing!
Wow! Dylan!
You might be different from me, Po.
You might have more time than I did,
and I hope Thame and
you can do better than me.
I love you.
This concert is not only a
confirmation of the MARS’ future,
but also a step towards success
that could catch Korea's attention
and lead to a contract with us.
It’s amazing.
You guys really swept the
#1 spot on every music chart.
You should be spending
time with your members.
Pepper cares about you a lot.
He doesn’t want you to think
we succeeded just because
he broke up with Gam.
If I really get to go there,
I’ll call you as often as possible.
We’ll keep moving forward
together like that, Po.