[Disclaimer:
All depicted events are fictional
and for entertainment purposes only;
viewer discretion is advised]
Hello,
Master...
I told you to stay out of it.
Khem's a good guy.
You'd better go keep him safe.
The night's far from over.
They're here.
Are you looking for me?
[Ubon Ratchathani, 2010]
(Incanting)
Grand Master,
is he gonna die?
Everyone dies eventually.
It's all part of karma.
But...
that boy's karmic enemy...
Not even I can stop it.
Even you can't do anything.
But you don't need to worry.
That boy's got...
at least ten more years.
I have less than that.
By the time his day comes,
I'll already be gone.
When the time comes,
I'll be the one to help him.
I've warned you many times.
You are meant to stick with white magic,
and your duty is to protect our village.
My power is black magic,
and I meddled with things
I shouldn't have.
That's what took your mom's life.
Promise me
you'll never interfere
with someone else's karma,
can you, Paran?
I promise.
[Ubon Ratchathani, 2025]
Everyone, are you ready?
- Yes.
- We are.
Let's do it.
They're here.
(Incanting)
Are you looking for me?
Give me the boy,
and I shall spare the rest of you.
What has he done to you?
Can't you just let him go?
It's not your place to know.
If you hold on to hatred
and keep causing harm,
no good shall come of it...
Shut your mouth.
Whatever I choose to do
is no concern of yours.
You'll either give him to me
or foolishly try to stand in my way.
Your grandfather failed to stop me.
But you, so naive and powerless...
Do not presume to defy me.
Come what may,
I shall never let him go.
I'll make him suffer
for as long as I want.
His fate is not yours to alter.
You're back, Master?
How is everything?
Prepare yourselves.
Once An Invitation to the Devas
is complete,
I shall pronounce the invocation.
(Incanting)
I, Paran Ruengdet,
humbly invoke the power
of all my revered masters,
all Enlightened Buddhas,
the Buddha,
the Dhamma,
the Sangha;
my parents in this life
and in the spirit realm;
the divine beings who have cared for me
in every life;
the guardian deities who protect me;
the great gods; the Great Bodhisattvas;
all mighty divine beings
in the 19 planes of heaven,
the 16 planes of Brahma realm,
the 15 planes
below the summit of Mount Meru,
the 14 planes of the lower realms,
and the 21 goddesses of Earth and Water.
I seek your divine protection
over my life,
the lives of those I love,
my disciples and followers,
and everyone in this village
that no harm
may come near.
Escort my disciples.
Then check every corner of the village.
- Yes, Master.
Why?
Why the hell are these fools
sticking their noses in?
I'm sorry for causing you
so much trouble last night.
You're Khem, right?
Yes.
Come closer.
Just go.
That thing you're wearing...
I need to see it.
No need to take it off.
Just pull it out from your shirt.
I was right.
That's Grand Master's amulet.
Only two like this exist.
'Grand Master'?
Grand Master Sek,
his grandfather.
He was also a shaman.
When I was a kid,
I came here.
I'm sure I did.
And Grand Master Sek saved me.
Where is he now?
Thank you
for keeping me safe until now.
Where are your parents, though?
They passed long ago,
even before my grandfather.
You must've been through
some tough times, too, right?
Take that necklace off.
Isn't it broken?
Take it off.
I'll replace the cord for you.
I think...
I'm done with mine.
Seriously?
- Yeah.
- I still have so much left to paint.
- I've been working on it since morning.
- Jet...
Thanks.
- You're just too fast.
- You woke up late, didn't you?
You're just too fast, Khem.
Show me yours.
Look.
Isn't the color of the lotus
kinda weird?
What do you think?
Well...
I think it looks great,
but maybe it could use
a bit more blending here.
Whoa.
You did this in just half a day?
It looks awesome.
I kinda pushed myself to finish it.
Whoa.
So this is the hand
of a legendary artist.
So soft!
You're overdoing it, Prae.
Stop it.
You didn't need to hold his hand.
- Okay.
- It's okay.
Here,
look at Praemai's artwork.
It's really pretty.
The color balance is on point,
and so are the details on the clothes.
That was such an in-depth comment.
Should I be expecting
a grade, Professor?
What about eighth grade?
Aren't we talking about an A, B, or C?
Oh, Charn! You're here.
Come here.
Have you seen Khem's painting?
Right there.
It's amazing.
The detail in it is impressive,
especially in the woman.
She looks really kind.
I used my mom's photo as a reference.
If she sees this,
she'll be really proud.
You're...
no longer with your mom, right?
Please forgive me for being rude.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Charn, look up!
You're overdoing it, too.
Forgive us, Khem.
This camp is full of weirdos.
It's okay.
Actually,
it's been a long time since she passed.
I'm Charnvit,
a third-year psychology student.
This is my first volunteer camp.
Nice to meet you, Khem.
Whoa...
Why so formal?
Well,
nice to meet you, too!
Prae, are you done?
Wow.
This looks gorgeous, babe.
I didn't do this alone.
This is all from the hands
of a legend, Khemjira.
Khemjira?
Right!
That's him,
the guy with a girl's name.
- I see.
- Yeah.
Honestly, I'd totally believe
he's a tomboy.
- He's gorgeous.
- You're right, dude.
In this day and age,
isn't it inappropriate
to judge people by how they look
and joke about their gender identity?
Why so serious, dude?
We just meant to say he's cute.
Just take it as a compliment, man.
Let us know if you need anything.
Hey, what are you doing?
Get your hands off Khem now.
Stay right there.
I'll take care of every one of you.
What the fuck?
Is Khem a monk or something?
Why can't we touch him?
Well...
If you're done with your work,
how about giving them a hand?
They want you there.
Come on.
Just go.
Now, alright?
- What the hell?
- Go!
Let's go.
Did they hurt you?
Jeez, acting like total thugs...
They're just a bunch of jerks.
Look who's talking.
They were just being friendly.
New friends are fine, right?
Who's this guy?
A new friend, too?
I'm right here.
Why don't you just ask me?
Actually,
when you want to get to know someone,
shouldn't you introduce yourself first?
What? You're getting on my nerves.
- Hey...
- Who said I wanna know you?
Come on.
What's wrong with you guys?
This is Charn,
also a junior.
He's a psychology student.
This is Jet,
my best friend.
Since we're all here together,
it wouldn't hurt to be friends,
right?
It's indeed full of weirdos.
- Here we go.
- Alright.
- Sod Chaeng!
Coconut rum,
Ubon Ratchathani's local gem!
You can't get it in Bangkok, you know!
Exactly, Worn.
Smells so nice.
- Thanks.
- Don't mention it.
It's not often I get to drink
with the young ones.
I'm enjoying this.
- Yeah.
- Right.
- Here you go.
- Oh, thank you.
Some snacks.
- Here.
- Thanks.
Rae!
- Yes?
- Rae!
- Bring us more snacks.
- Okay.
- These are almost gone.
Here you go.
This is also a local gem.
- Wow.
- My wife made it.
We're probably gonna drink
this Sod Chaeng till dawn.
Rae, you can head to bed first.
We don't mind.
Come on,
she always stays up late.
Let her be here
in case we want something.
Yeah, I usually stay up late.
If you need anything, just tell me.
I'll get it for you.
But...
don't drink too much, okay?
I heard you have
an early start tomorrow, right?
Hey, Worn,
cheers.
- Oh, cheers!
- Come on.
- Sod Chaeng!
Guys.
Hey.
Why don't you go upstairs?
Argh!
Please stop.
What the hell do you do for me each day?
I'm working hard to make money for you,
and you have the nerve
to boss me around?
That's not what I did.
I was just telling you
- 'cause you might have to work early.
- Shut your mouth.
- Should I just kill you now?
- Argh!
Worn...
- Should I?
- Please...
Kill? Seriously?
You sure it wasn't a dream?
A dream, my ass.
He was totally losing it,
like he was possessed.
He kept beating his wife badly.
Beating his wife?
Which Worn are you talking about?
The one who brought us the tools?
No way. It's not him.
He's a good guy.
He's also nice, actually.
Yeah.
He was breaking up a dogfight
at the temple the other day,
and he wouldn't even dare to hit them.
He was completely normal
to his wife this morning.
You're making things up, bro.
Right.
No one believes me at all.
Who would actually fight
in front of their guests?
If you're sure about it,
you should tell the locals here.
You're staying at their place.
If something goes wrong,
you'll be in trouble.
And domestic violence...
isn't something to be ignored.
Exactly.
And it's none of your business.
- Hey!
Stop it!
Stay here.
Sit down.
Eat your food.
Just eat it.
Sorry.
What were you tryna do?
Why would you get involved?
Don't forget the reason you're here.
I know,
but I don't know what to do.
I haven't even had a chance
to talk to Master yet.
Come on,
nothing about it is hard.
Your food, Master.
Well... Uh...
I just wanted to thank you...
for replacing my necklace cord
the other day.
Please give it a try.
If you don't like it,
I'll adjust the seasoning for you.
How is it, Master?
Fantastic, right?
It's alright.
Don't bother adding more stuff to it.
And if you keep staring at me like that,
I don't think I have any appetite.
Go change your shirt.
Okay.
He ate it all.
Thought he said
it was just alright, huh?
Master!
Leave that to me.
I'll clear the table.
Alright.
Please get it done.
Uh...
Master,
may I have a moment with you?
You have that much free time?
Is there nothing to do at the camp?
I mean...
Since Grand Master Sek saved me before,
he might have left some way
to break my curse.
Do you...
happen to know anything about it?
It was him who warned me
to stay away from people's karma.
I've said enough. Hope you understand.
Please help me.
Please.
I'm begging you.
Don't do this.
I can't help you.
Do you want me to break my promise
to my grandfather for you?
I know it might sound selfish,
but I don't think...
you can stand
seeing people suffer, right?
[Phra Nakhon, 1939]
Mister...
Sir!
Mister,
I'm up here!
Can you please get me a ladder?
I mean...
I can't get back down.
Uh...
Say thanks to him.
Aw.
You're sleeping, huh?
Is this your cat?
No, it's not.
I don't know where it came from,
but it was stuck up there.
So you went up to help the cat
and ended up stuck there yourself?
The way it cried just broke my heart.
All I thought about was saving it.
I didn't even think about myself.
You also wanted to help me.
You looked totally shocked
when you saw me up there.
Thank you.
You're...
Pawat.
I'm Pawat Wongpradit.
Pawat Wongpradit...
That's a beautiful name.
Oh,
I'm Khem,
Khemmika.
I've fixed all the windows now, Master.
Thanks a lot.
So...
I'll see you later.
Goodbye.
He was totally losing it,
like he was possessed.
He kept beating his wife badly.
Look.
- About what you asked...
- Master...
Is it possible...
that...
Worn might be possessed?
You saw the energy, didn't you?
My guess is he went into the forest
to fetch something
and passed through those spirits.
Living with nature and spirits
is just the way things are here.
It's nothing unusual.
Still got some booze?
I'll have some tonight.
You drank it all, though...
Worn!
Worn.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- You forgot this.
- Oh, thanks.
So many of you came.
Did Te invite you over for drinks?
Oh...
We don't drink.
But Te and the others
always talk about Rae's fermented pork.
We were wondering
if we could try a little.
Right?
- That's right.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
- Right.
Rae, still got some fermented pork?
Yes.
Come on, join me.
Let's eat.
Okay.
Why would you be here, too?
Khem asked me to come.
You didn't need to know.
This one is ready. It's already sour.
Just put it in the fridge,
and it's good to go.
- Thank you.
- The other two still need time.
Leave them out for now,
and put them in the fridge tomorrow.
Whoa, this is way too much, Rae.
- I feel bad taking so much.
- Don't worry about it.
I always make extra. Worn loves it.
Go ahead and share it with everyone.
Rae,
what happened to you?
Uh...
I fell.
That's all. I'm alright.
Stay out of this, Khem.
Rae might've actually fallen over.
It was so obvious
a toddler could see right through it.
I know!
I'm not that stupid.
Even if Worn actually hurt his wife,
it's none of our business, right?
What if he's actually possessed?
Possessed?
By what?
A party spirit, perhaps?
You, too, Khem.
Don't say such things.
Uh...
We've arrived at the Master's house.
By the way,
why are you following us, Chan?
Aren't you supposed to be
on your way back to Auntie Kaew's?
It's way over there, on the same route.
Both of us have to go now.
See you, okay?
Let's go, Jet.
We need to go now.
Quickly.
Hey, Worn.
Take it easy.
Are you starving or something?
Come on,
it's once in a while, man.
Once in a while?
You literally drink every day.
What is it?
Look,
be honest with me.
You worried about something?
Got some problems?
Someone like me?
There's no way I'd have any problems.
How's it going
with your wife, Rae?
We're fine.
What problems could there be?
No problems at all?
No.
Married couples
do fight, you know.
Kaew and I argue all the time,
but we never get physical.
Hey...
I'm not the kind of guy
who'd lay a hand on Rae.
Jeez.
Who's that?
Hey!
That boy,
come here.
Well... I...
Auntie Kaew asked me to come.
You know, she's Uncle Chai's wife.
She's really kind and...
I get it.
I'll be there.
Thanks a lot.
Okay.
Want some drinks?
Did my wife tell you
to tell Chai about this?
What do you mean?
I don't...
I have no idea.
Did my wife tell you I beat her?
Hey, Worn!
Take it easy.
Why take it out on him?
He has no idea.
Just finish your drink.
You called me here
'cause you chose to take her side?
Hey, wait.
Wait, Worn!
Jeez, you son of a bitch.
What?
Seriously?
So...
how is Worn now?
Okay.
It's damn late. Where are you going?
Charn called.
He told Uncle Chai about Worn,
so Uncle Chai warned him.
And now he's mad,
thinking Rae told Uncle Chai about him.
Right now,
he's heading home, totally drunk.
I'm afraid...
that Rae might get hurt.
Shit!
When did you...
give Charn your number?
Gosh.
That's the only thing you picked up?
It's not the point at all.
Fine, my bad.
I told you
to stay out of their business.
But if you're going,
I'm coming with you.
Rae!
Rae, where are you?
Worn?
You're drinking again?
Leave me alone.
You should stop.
Let go.
- Please, Worn.
- Go away.
Kill them...
Do it.
You bitch.
You talk too much.
I'll make sure you can't tell anyone
a damn thing anymore.
- Worn...
- You bitch.
Please don't do it.
Stop it, Worn.
Let go of me!
- Leave me alone.
- Are you alright, Rae?
- Don't mess with me.
- You're safe now.
Let go of me.
- What are you doing?
- Go away.
Have you gone nuts?
Stay out of our fucking business.
Kill them...
Kill them all.
Kill everyone.
I will kill you all.
Kill them.
Kill them now.
(Incanting)
What are you doing?
Exorcising.
He's freaking possessed.
(Incanting)
Stop it, Chai.
That's enough.
He's not the one possessed.
The one who's really possessed
is this bitch.
You...
Rae!
Come.
I will kill you all.
Rae...
- Please.
- Rae's surely tough.
She's endured your shit all this time.
Worn! Rae!
We're back!
Did you make us dinner?
We're so hungry.
Got any leftovers?
Are you home, Worn?
What's wrong, Jet?
Take a look around.
Actually,
we've gone through this bamboo grove
over and over.
We're being messed with.
Khem!
What the fuck is going on?
Rae...
Make your choice. Who will you save?
Stop that.
Rae!
Rae...
Rae,
please don't do this.
I'm sorry.
It's too late.
Your Rae
is gone.
Don't do that!
Rae...
Please don't.
Stop.
You chose to come here.
I suppose that means
my lady's gotten hold of that boy.
Get out of this body.
You don't belong here.
She's been dying
to kill that bastard for ages.
I just gave her what she wanted.
It's her choice.
Stay out of this.
Don't involve yourself
in karma that isn't yours to carry.
What about those who wronged my lady?
Have they paid for their sins?
This is what Rae wants.
Even you can't stop it.
Rae!
Rae...
You'd better not
underestimate me and my disciple.
What the fuck is going on?
Khem!
Jet,
can you hear me?
Master!
Please help Khem.
Listen.
You need to help him.
What?
Why's that?
There's no time to explain.
I'm gonna let you see spirits
for a while.
After that, it's your call.
You can do it, Jet!
Ake?
Khem!
Khem...
Are you alright?
Shit!
Who were they?
Jet!
This way! Come on.
Thong?
Come on, Khem.
Hurry.
Rae,
if you can hear me,
follow my voice.
This body is waiting for you.
She's not coming back.
Who'd want to live
with a husband drowning in debt,
drinking all day, and beating his wife?
That's just another kind of death.
Come back, Rae.
Handle your own problems.
Don't use a spirit
to do your dirty work.
(Incanting)
My lady won't spare you.
Rae!
Rae...
- Rae...
- Rae.
I'm sorry. It's my fault.
You've done nothing wrong.
I was a piece of shit.
Please forgive me.
From now on, I'll quit drinking
and focus on paying off my debts.
Forgive me, Rae.
I'm sorry, too.
Thank you.
Rae and Worn managed to
rekindle their love
because of your help.
It's too soon to say that.
Things are not that easy.
- What do you mean?
- Jet,
wake Uncle Chai up
and take care of the rest.
Yes, Master.
Follow me.
Master,
what did you mean it was too soon
to say they'd rekindled their love?
Even if Rae forgives Worn,
he won't really change.
But he did make a promise.
He did,
but that doesn't mean it'll happen.
But I think they're trying.
After all, they still love each other.
Listen, Khem.
Love isn't always enough
to make things work.
If being together
only leads to problems,
why bother?
Master,
you were willing to help Worn and Rae,
yet refused to help me.
Is it just because
I don't belong to this village?
My duty
is to take care
of the people in this village.
I'm an outsider.
I get it now.
Still,
I'll do whatever it takes
to stop being an outsider in your eyes.
No touching.
I'm sorry.
Step up.
Oh, gosh...
- Slowly.
- Take it easy.
Careful. You'll bump into the door.
How did you end up like this?
Take it easy.
What have you been up to?
Save that for later.
For now, let Charn get some rest.
Right, Jet.
I'll have those three guys
stay somewhere else for the time being.
Thanks a lot, Uncle.
Don't worry about him.
He'll be fine.
What? Why would I worry about him?
He literally asked for trouble himself.
I'm leaving.
Good night.
Good luck.
Thank you so much.
He came to say goodbye.
He's going to work in the city
for a while
to pay off his debts.
He'll be apart from Rae for a bit.
See?
It's not that easy.
So,
was the spirit that possessed Rae
someone from Khem's past karma?
She sent her servant spirits
to harm the villagers.
I'm sorry.
The spirit only stirred up
the resentment that was already there.
Sooner or later, Worn and Rae
would've fallen apart anyway.
He's saying...
don't blame yourself.
It's not your fault.
- Right, Master...
- When your friend is with us,
you can drop the dialect.
Okay.
Well...
Is there any way I can see spirits again
like I did last night?
I still want another round with them.
Jet!
If I do that,
your parents will beat me up.
Right,
a spirit showed up
to save Khem last night.
I caught a glimpse...
It looked like a man...
dressed in khaki.
Khem,
have you seen him before?
Yeah.
It's him
who keeps showing up.
Long time no see,
Wat.
Do you know that spirit?
It's none of your business.
You literally said,
"He's not the Khemmika you knew."
You talked about me, didn't you?
See that sign over there?
It used to be a viewpoint.
How about we pitch a tent
and do some stargazing tonight?
I've got a long-range rifle, baby!
Hey, are you done yet?
Jet,
help Uncle Chai
gather the entire village.
We'll form search groups
to look for Te, Korn, and Phu.
They must be found before noon.
Why before noon?
If they're not found by noon,
we're looking for bodies.
♫No matter how long time's passed,
you still have me♫
♫Through storms and stars,
together we shall be♫
♫Even if nightmares come,
we shall make them flee♫
♫With our hearts aligned,
we'll win gracefully♫
♫You still have me,
we're destined for eternity♫
♫Through storms and stars,
together we shall be♫
♫Even if nightmares come,
we shall make them flee♫
♫With our hearts aligned,
we'll win triumphantly♫