(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
ALL FIGURES,
INCIDENTS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS,
AND OTHERS ARE FICTITIOUS.
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
WERE FILMED SAFELY
IN ACCORDANCE WITH GUIDELINES.
SHIN I-RANG, HAN NA-HYUN
LAW OFFICE
How may I help you?
Ma'am!
So that's why I didn't see you lately.
Did you pass away?
You struggled so much,
only to pass away like this.
-Ouch!
-What are you saying?
I'm not dead yet.
Oh.
-Geez.
-You really aren't dead!
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
You silly young man.
Unbelievable.
You came early.
I bought some coffee for you.
Hello.
Oh, dear.
I can see her too.
Attorney Han, this is…
I can even touch her.
Of course, you can. She's not a ghost.
She's not?
Why are you both so eager to call me dead?
-I'm sorry.
-Sorry about that.
Ma'am, why don't we sit down and talk?
Sure.
Who is she?
She's a close acquaintance of mine.
What brings you here?
I'm here to meet you, young attorney.
Why?
Did you get caught up in any trouble?
No, nothing like that.
It's because of my late husband.
Does he perhaps have
silver hair, bushy eyebrows…
and a handsome face?
Oh, my.
Words say the attorney here is
nearly psychic.
It must be true.
An attorney doesn't need psychic powers.
Oh, my head!
Did your husband have
some kind of disease?
Well,
he had Alzheimer's.
He came back to his senses
from time to time,
but most of the time,
he only had memories of his earlier years.
It must've been hard.
Did he perhaps have something
to do with shoes?
How did you know?
He was a shoemaker.
Even when we met the first time,
he was making shoes.
YEAR 1979
He was awfully rude to me.
-At the time…
-So I…
…Seoul was a magical city
where everything changed overnight.
I was a young girl with splendid dreams.
Still, he's a premed student
at Hanguk University.
Isn't he great husband material?
So what if he's great husband material?
I'm the one who's going to be the best.
That sounds so like you.
Even so, it's a shame.
There isn't anyone suited to be
your husband as much as he is.
What are you doing?
I'm leaving without you.
He's so cool.
Are you here for new shoes?
Excuse me?
The showroom is over there.
This is the workshop.
I know that.
And what I need isn't new shoes…
but you.
Back then, I was preparing
to open my own shop
with the marriage fund
I got from my parents
after graduating
from a famous fashion academy.
Shoes that make you happy
as soon as you wear them.
Shoes that feel like
they will take you somewhere nice.
To make the finest shoes
made with sincerity.
That was my dream.
MERRY SHOES
The best kind of shoes aren't made
simply with money and skills.
Without fine leather,
the best kind of shoes cannot exist.
I also know
that quality leather is a must.
Which company's leather do you want?
Is it imported leather?
From Italy? France?
There's someone I want you to meet.
Seon Hwa was from Hamgyong, North Korea.
-Seon Hwa.
-She burnished the leather alone
without anyone's help.
Her leather was soft like a feather,
yet strong like metal.
I fell in love with it straightaway.
IDEAL SHOES
Don't be nervous.
Everyone, relax.
One, two, three.
-One more time.
-That was how
-we opened Ideal Shoes.
-One, two, three.
Ideal Shoes? Do you mean that Ideal Shoes?
Yes, that's the one.
Seriously?
My heels right now are Ideal Shoes.
Oh, that.
It's from our steady-selling line
that's been produced since 1981.
You have an eye for shoes.
Wow.
I see you in a whole new light.
But why did you quit working?
You're still healthy and well.
I had to focus on something
more important than work.
Anyway,
the three of us opened this shop alone
with a small budget,
but we were confident
in the products we made.
-They're so pretty.
-That's how our shoes
started to fill the display cabinets.
More and more people loved our products.
One, two, three.
-Smile a little more.
-We'd make shoes all night,
but we couldn't stop smiling.
IDEAL SHOES
Get in closer.
One, two, three.
It was when I learned
that Seon Hwa left behind
her newborn baby in North Korea.
What are you doing?
I was making a wish.
To meet my son in North Korea again.
Oh.
I'll also make a prayer
for your wish to come true.
Me too.
We felt like we had the world.
We had nothing to fear.
Not until
Seon Hwa got arrested.
She was accused of being a spy.
It turned out
Seon Hwa was sending money to North Korea.
Let me go!
She explained that the money was
for her family in the North.
-Wait. Let go!
-She's innocent.
-She isn't a spy.
-Seon Hwa!
However,
what we got in return
was a frightening threat.
They questioned if we were also involved.
If so, Ideal Shoes was
to close down right away.
My husband and I couldn't say a thing.
If the company closed down,
dozens of employees were to go jobless.
And their families added up to hundreds.
In the end,
we could do nothing
but hope that she'd be released safely.
The years went by.
When we went to visit her,
she was
already dead.
We made her grave on a hill
where North Korea was visible
and buried her cremation urn there.
It was devastating.
Only if we had visited her sooner…
Only if we hadn't cared about the company
and saved her…
Then, she may still be alive.
Struggling with regret,
we made up our minds
to find her son in North Korea
and give her share to him.
Please make sure to find him.
I'm sorry.
I see. Thank you
for your hard work, though.
I'm sorry.
I see. Thank you.
We appreciate it.
But it wasn't easy to find her son.
WILL
My husband ended up
writing a will about leaving him
an inheritance out of anxiety.
And after a year since he passed away,
her son,
Cha Eun Seong, was found at last.
It says the heir must provide
one-third of the inheritance
to Ms. Ryeo Seon Hwa's son,
Cha Eun Seong, if he is found at any time.
Most of the inheritance is
the shares of Ideal Shoes.
The company will be at stake
if one-third of it is given to him.
Ms. Ryeo Seon Hwa's contributions
to Ideal Shoes are mentioned as a reason.
The case will be in our favor
if your mother is against this will.
What's her opinion?
My mother thinks it's only right
to do as my father's will says.
She told Cha Eun Seong
about my father's will herself.
She's always been like this.
She can't stand to enjoy any luxuries
when Ms. Ryeo wrongfully
passed away in prison.
-Thank you. Have a great day.
-Thank you. Enjoy.
She lives alone in an old, small house.
She sells vegetables on the street
no matter how hard I try to stop her.
Welcome.
Normally, she lets me
have my way with everything.
But she thundered at me
when I refused to give the money.
She said she'd even take it to court
if she needed to.
I see.
All right for now.
We'll have to check more in detail,
but the deceased's will exists
along with your mother's strong intention
to execute it.
Thus, a trial seems inevitable.
Then, we must win this case.
Why don't you try persuading your son?
You'll have to go to trial
against your son at this rate.
It'll be tough.
I've already tried.
He's adamant.
That's understandable.
I honestly doubt your son could accept it.
Not unless you compromised
with a much lower amount.
I won't compromise.
I'll never settle for a lower amount.
Even if it's taken to court,
I want to follow my husband's will.
But…
Okay.
We understand, ma'am.
Please go home for today.
We'll get back to you
after a thorough check.
Oh…
Here.
You can find materials and pictures
about Seon Hwa in this envelope.
My number is in it too.
Please help me keep my husband's promise.
We'll see what can be done.
Oh, right.
We need to know about your husband
if we're to prepare for the trial.
May I know his name and date of birth?
His name is
Kang Dong-sik.
He was born on March 1, 1953.
I'll be counting on you.
WILL
Hello, sir.
How do you do?
I'm Kang Dong-sik, the shoemaker.
I'm Attorney Shin I-rang.
This is Attorney Han Na-hyun.
Hello, I'm Attorney Han Na-hyun.
I'm right here.
-Oh, right. You can't see me.
-He's over there.
It's nice to meet you.
He says it's nice to meet you.
Anyway, I see
you're easygoing
and practical, yet polished.
And you mostly sit
with your left leg crossed.
How did you know?
One's shoes tell everything about them.
You've worn those uncomfortable shoes
until the heels are frayed.
It means you have
an easygoing personality.
Those are machine-stitched shoes
made with synthetic leather,
but you chose a classic design.
It means your taste isn't half bad.
Gosh.
The right heel is frayed
more than the left heel
because your pelvis is misaligned
from crossing your legs.
But it's not too serious, so don't worry.
Wow, amazing.
What is it? What did he say?
He got it all right about me
just by looking at my shoes.
What about the old lady from earlier?
I could sense
a diligent and humble nature
from her shoes.
He doesn't recognize Ms. Chae.
Can you hand me one of the pictures
we got from her?
What if he possesses you?
We need to do anything
to help him regain his memory.
And he doesn't seem dangerous.
It might be okay even if he possesses me.
IDEAL SHOES
Oh, boy.
I'm running late.
Where's the young man that was just here?
Excuse me for asking, miss stranger,
but where is the nearest bus stop?
Why do you ask?
I need to go to Malli-dong to make shoes.
Customers will be disappointed
if I don't have the shoes ready on time.
This is bad.
Sir.
Malli-dong isn't the same anymore.
What? What do you mean by that?
What I mean is--
Miss.
I'm really sorry,
but I don't have time to hear you out.
To my customers,
my products mean more than just shoes.
They're partners for success
and life companions for their new lives.
Oh, I'm running out of time.
I have business there anyway.
Let me accompany you.
Sure, please lead the way.
OKCHEON BUILDING
Sir, please wait inside for a second.
Okay.
My goodness.
-Excuse me, ma'am.
-Yes?
-May I ask you something?
-Okay?
What bus should I take
to get to Malli-dong?
Bus number 0411
will take you straight there.
Here it comes.
Why, thank you.
Sure.
Wait!
BUS 0411
MALLI-DONG HANDMADE SHOE STREET
Sir, please take me
to the handmade shoe street in Malli-dong.
Okay.
This must be the place.
Welcome.
How strange.
This has to be the place.
Excuse me.
What are you looking for?
Do you need anything?
This is supposed to be my workshop.
What's all this flashy stuff?
Who are you, mister?
I'm a shoemaker.
-Where are my shoes?
-Get out.
This place is my workshop.
-There's no workshop here. Get out.
-What's the matter with you?
This has to be it.
Attorney Shin!
Here, try it on.
I'm sorry.
I thought he'd remember something
if I took him out
and let him see things for himself.
I shouldn't have.
Excuse me,
but do you know me?
You must've been so lonely alone.
I'll help you from now on.
SHIN I-RANG LAW OFFICE
What are you going to do with this case?
I think we should settle at a fair level.
You think so?
I believe my duty as her attorney is
to help her execute her husband's will.
It's not likely, is it?
Nevertheless, you'll fight to the end.
I get it now.
I'll have to work my butt off.
Are you going to help me?
We share this office,
and you're up against Taebaek.
It would be heartless
to let you fight alone.
Instead, we'll split
the contingency fee fifty-fifty.
Deal.
Father, did you give the Ideal Shoes case
to someone else?
I did.
Why? I even consulted
with CEO Kang Ji-hoon myself.
Shin I-rang and Han Na-hyun
are defending the other side.
So what?
Personal feelings may hinder
an attorney's judgment.
So, I had someone else take charge of it.
No, I have no personal feelings.
Let me do it.
I'll prove myself, Father.
You're saying
this is where I used to live?
I don't remember,
but it feels very familiar.
WORKROOM
This is…
What was it…
What is it? Do you remember anything?
What was this again?
So, these…
used to belong to my husband.
I couldn't throw them out.
It's a relief we have a lot to refer to.
Thank goodness.
Look at this old thing.
Oh, my goodness.
I-rang, what are you doing?
Don't wear this kind of thing!
Sir.
His shoes are for easy wear.
So what if they're easy to wear?
They're classless!
Bah!
-Hmph.
-I-rang!
Seriously? This is the fifth floor!
Geez!
Let me start the briefing
about Kang Ji-hoon's will contest.
"Will. I, Kang Dong-sik,
leave this as my last will."
We must focus on this date.
That needs to be checked.
I'm putting Attorney Oh on it.
Excuse me. Let me ask you something.
-Yes?
-Well…
Do you know these people?
IDEAL SHOES
No, I don't.
I see. Thank you.
Hello.
Do you perhaps know these people?
Let's go.
2010 COMMERCIAL
2015 COMMERCIAL
WHY OLD KOREANS LEAVE A WILL
TESTIMONY
KANG JI-HOON, IDEAL SHOES CEO
Now that we've visited the field
and collected enough materials,
why don't we go meet Mr. Cha Eun Seong,
Ms. Ryeo Seon Hwa's son?
Give it to me!
I said no to these shoes!
-Take the other one off immediately!
-Attorney Han, stop him!
Bah!
Thanks, Attorney Han!
Wow.
It's leather.
-Excuse me. May I ask you something?
-Yes?
I'm looking for Mr. Cha Eun Seong.
Our chief? He's over there.
Chief.
You're having a late lunch today.
It's not good to skip meals.
Come by anytime.
Okay?
And eat up.
I will, ma'am.
-Enjoy.
-Thank you.
I eat here every day.
Are you okay with noodles?
I can handle anything.
This is delicious.
It's good.
I'm all right.
Feel free to ask me questions.
When did you come to Korea?
I hear your hometown is in North Korea.
That's right.
I was born in Hamgyong and separated
from my mother when I was one.
After my aunt died,
I came to Korea more than ten years ago.
How did you come
to dye leather for a living?
My hometown is known for leather-dyeing.
All my family and relatives
were in the field.
When I heard my mother was
in the same line of work,
it broke my heart.
How much do you know about your mother?
I heard she kept sending money
to my family in the North
and tried to get us out of the country.
And that she lost contact with us
as soon as we arrived in China.
Moving on to the next story.
"Today is the first death anniversary
of my beloved wife."
"I've been trying
to keep a level head for my children,
but it's not so easy."
"Whenever I listen to the songs she liked,
pass by the road we often walked together,
or look at the food we enjoyed together,
I'm reminded of my wife."
"I miss her so much"--
He doesn't even know
that his mother passed away.
I feel so bad for him.
I guess Ms. Chae
couldn't possibly inform him
of his mother's death.
We'd better tell him eventually
when we get a chance.
PITTER-PATTER BUTCHER-STYLE BBQ
Go in without me.
I'll park the truck and follow you.
Wait.
What is this?
SHIN I-RANG
Isn't this your phone number?
In case you go missing again.
-Attorney Han.
-To make it easier to look for you.
Park and come up.
OKCHEON BUILDING
Oh, it must be love.
It's nothing like that.
Ghosts can see everything.
That's right.
This is love
What should I do?
If you suddenly leave me behind
WORKROOM
Even so, it's a shame.
There isn't anyone suited to be
your husband as much as he is.
He's so cool.
DEAR DONG-SIK
…I CAN'T HIDE MY FEELINGS ANYMORE…
DAEUN CHOCOLATE
CONGRATS ON
HAN NA-HYUN'S GRAND OPENING
What am I doing here?
Snap out of it.
SEOUL
VACANT
Hi, Na-hyun. Are you still at the office?
Your mom sent me to deliver a lunch box
for you and Attorney Shin.
But I don't see any space to park.
Okay, take your time coming downstairs.
See you soon.
Oops.
Oh, my.
What was that?
Oh, no. I-I'm sorry.
Were you even looking at the road?
I'm so sorry, sir.
Unbelievable.
Repairing the bumper alone
would cost as much as your cab.
I'm so sorry.
Are you drunk?
No, not at all.
Dad?
Oh, hey.
My goodness.
That's crumpled up bad.
On second look, it's a minor scratch.
-What?
-It's a scratch.
No, I just crashed--
It was already like this.
It's all right. Are you not injured?
I'm okay, but you--
I'm okay because I'm young and strong.
-Dad.
-Na-hyun.
-Mr. Yang?
-Oh, hi.
Do you know this man?
You must be Attorney Han's father.
Hello, I'm Managing Partner Yang Do-kyung
of her former workplace.
Good lord, this is horrible.
-Dear me.
-What's going on?
Well, I was trying to stop
the lunch box from falling and…
Oh.
Sorry. We'll handle it through insurance.
-Are you hurt?
-No, no. I'm not hurt.
-I rammed into his car.
-Excuse me?
No, I rammed into his car.
What are you talking about?
I specialize in car accidents.
I caused this accident, end of discussion.
No, Na-hyun.
I really did ram into his car.
What a complicated situation.
I'll get going. I'll see you another time.
Oh, okay.
Mr. Yang.
Yeah?
-What is that?
-It's nothing.
-Is it for me?
-No, it's for someone else.
It says, "Congrats on
Han Na-hyun's grand opening."
Oh, boy.
Why is it written there?
It's not for you.
What the?
What was I doing here?
What did I do to make my hand like this?
Where did my phone go?
Sir, did something happen in your house?
Yeah. I made shoes.
-Shoes?
-Yes.
Shoes for who?
I can't remember.
Why are you taking your shoes off?
Oh, nothing. You're late.
-Something came up.
-I see.
Where did you get that plant?
Guess what.
Managing Partner Yang of Taebaek was here.
-You mean, Yang Do-kyung?
-Yes.
Where's Attorney Han?
She stepped outside to see Mr. Yang off.
Maybe they're having dinner together.
Try calling her if you're curious.
No, I don't think that's necessary.
OKCHEON BUILDING
SHIN I-RANG
Takes a lot of work, doesn't it?
I'm sorry. What did you just say?
You've got to connect
two different individuals,
smooth them out,
and polish them from time to time,
which is why it's so difficult.
Both shoes
and love.
Love? What are you talking about?
A ghost knows everything, brat.
The two are also the same in a sense
that they shine more
the more heart and soul you put into them.
Oh, please.
It's your brother-in-law.
What?
-I-rang.
-Bong-su?
PITTER-PATTER BUTCHER-STYLE BBQ
Attorney Han, what brings you here
at this hour--
Where were you?
You said you'd park and come up.
-Oh, I--
-Why didn't you answer your phone?
I lost my phone--
Also, why did you leave work
by yourself without waiting for me?
You made me worry.
I heard you left with Mr. Yang.
-I didn't want to disturb.
-Disturb?
There was a car accident. I handled it
through insurance and left him hours ago.
I had no idea that you were home.
I took this and looked everywhere
in Malli-dong for you!
Really?
Are you angry?
I'm not angry…
I'm just tired. My feet hurt too.
Thanks.
Thanks for what? I said I'm tired.
How can you be this bad
at reading emotions?
I'm sorry. I'll never do it again.
Why are you laughing?
I'm sorry.
You say sorry at everything.
What's wrong with you, really?
Beats me. Why do I keep apologizing?
Did you have dinner?
You think I did?
Me neither. Care to have dinner with me?
What are we having?
I know a delicious place nearby.
-Welcome!
You must be hungry.
Eat all you want, Attorney Han.
This is unusual of you.
Is today a special day?
No,
but you had a tough day because of me.
You'll regret it.
I'm a sushi killer.
Me too.
Where's the tuna?
We can make an order.
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
Could you make us
two plates of tuna sushi?
-Coming right away.
-Thank you.
Wow, it looks good.
-Here's your tuna.
-Thank you.
Here you go.
This is really good.
I see you're loving it.
It's delicious.
Where did my shoes go?
Mom, my Heartsping shoes are missing too.
-That's odd.
-I was going to wear them.
Sir.
Take a slow look at these as you wait.
You brought your whole family's shoes.
Oh, dear.
-See you later.
-Okay.
PITTER-PATTER BUTCHER-STYLE BBQ
Goodness, gracious.
How are your feet?
Let's please focus on the trial.
Long time no see, sir.
I'm so glad to see you well.
It's been such a long time.
I was sad that you left Taebaek.
But I'm relieved
to see you work with Attorney Shin.
All right. Let's play fair.
Yes, sir.
Aren't you being too sweet to Shin I-rang?
Am I?
Then again,
you don't know what kind of freak he is.
Oh, my.
Why is this out here?
This can't be.
TO MY DEAR BELOVED H,
FROM DONG-SIK
Hold on.
Let the trial begin
for Case 2025-Gahab-1901458.
Ms. Chae is running late.
I know.
Where's Mr. Kang?
He's in the truck.
He's not going to come. Don't worry.
This trial has been convened
following the lawsuit
filed by Plaintiff Kang Ji-hoon,
claiming that the will of his late father,
Kang Dong-sik, is invalid
while Defendant Chae Jeong-hui,
his mother, maintains
the mandatory execution of the will.
Defense counsel,
you may begin your opening statement.
In 1979, Kang Dong-sik, Chae Jeong-hui,
and Ryeo Seon Hwa opened Ideal Shoes
in the alley for handmade shoes
in Malli-dong and became co-owners.
I've submitted corporate documents
and pictures to prove this.
EXHIBITS 2-1, 2-2, 4-1, 4-3
Ms. Ryeo Seon Hwa's leatherworking skills
served as a foundation
for the growth of their business.
In recognition of her contributions,
the late Chairman Kang Dong-sik
left a will to bequeath one-third
of the inheritance to Ms. Ryeo's son.
Therefore, as the representative
of the defendant,
I demand that Plaintiff Kang Ji-hoon
promptly execute the will
of the late Chairman Kang Dong-sik
and transfer one-third of the inheritance
to Ms. Ryeo's son, Cha Eun Seong.
That is all.
We'd love to carry out the will…
if the chairman's will is genuine.
Ms. Chae Jeong-hui, the wife
of the late Chairman Kang Dong-sik,
has proved it to be
her husband's handwriting.
That's right.
With the help of the Korea Institute
of Document Examination,
a thorough analysis of the will
shows that the will was indeed
written by the chairman.
But the problem lies elsewhere.
Attorney Shin I-rang.
Will you tell me
when the will was written?
What for?
It obviously says so on the will.
Please tell me when it was written.
June 12, 2019.
Correct, and that is the problem.
Why is that a problem?
Chairman Kang Dong-sik's symptoms
of Alzheimer's worsened in 2021.
And the will was written in 2019,
which is 2 years before that.
Was it really written in 2019?
WILL
I, KANG DONG-SIK…
The analysis result
of the ink used in the will shows
that it was written
with a Napoleon fountain pen.
The company of this fountain pen
raised the pH level of its black ink
from 6.7 to 7.2 to improve its smoothness
in November of 2022.
Surprisingly enough,
the pH level of the ink used in the will,
which was supposedly written in June 2019,
turned out to be 7.2.
Thus, it cannot be established as fact
that the will was written in June 2019.
Besides, in November of 2022,
the chairman could not recognize his wife
as well as his own son
due to severe dementia.
Attached is a expert testimony
from a medical specialist.
Objection!
Let us hear more.
Thank you.
Now,
if the will wasn't written by the chairman
whose disease was worsening at the time,
who could it be that wrote the will?
Through document anti-forgery software,
we examined the similarities
between the will
and the writings
of another particular person.
The result shows
that the usage frequency
of conjunctive words and pronouns
and the placement of verbs
match by more than 94%.
This particular person is…
DAEUN CHOCOLATE
Are you done?
Yes, I'm almost done.
They're beautiful.
Aren't they?
If you were sound of mind,
you would've agreed with me.
Honey.
Please tell me you do.
Now, hold this.
Write.
-Write?
-Yes.
Write what?
"Will."
"I, Kang Dong-sik…"
I, Kang Dong-sik…
"…leave this…"
…leave this as my last will.
What…
Honey.
This particular person is…
Ms. Chae Jeong-hui.
His claim doesn't make sense.
She has no reason to fabricate the will.
Yes, she does.
The one who reported Ms. Ryeo Seon Hwa
for being a spy…
-Let go!
-She's not a spy.
Seon Hwa!
…was Ms. Chae Jeong-hui.
It can't be.
This is ridiculous!
Honey.
I submit the document
of the Military Intelligence Agency.
INFORMANT: CHAE JEONG-HUI
Honey! Why would you?
The document clearly states that
Ms. Chae reported Ms. Ryeo Seon Hwa.
We were not informed
of this evidence in advance.
Ms. Chae reported Ms. Ryeo,
but when Ms. Ryeo passed away in jail,
she attempted to leave an inheritance
to her son, Cha Eun Seong,
so that she could offset her guilt
even by fabricating her husband's will.
Honey!
Now that the will is proven to be fake,
the plaintiff has no duties
to share the inheritance
with Ryeo Seon Hwa's son.
No, Mr. Kang.
-Not now, please.
-There's no reason to continue the trial.
-What…
-Thus, I request…
-Say what must be said!
-…a prompt conclusion
of this trial.
I wrote it!
What?
I wrote the will!
Me!
Defense counsel, what are you doing?
Do you want to be ejected
for perjury and contempt of court?
Hey, Mr. Judge.
Listen to what I have to say!
I--
Your Honor!
Attorney Shin I-rang has
a serious chronic disease.
I request a recess
due to his current condition.
A recess, not a conclusion!
TO MY DEAR BELOVED H,
FROM DONG-SIK
Why did you report Ms. Ryeo?
-I'm sorry.
-Honey.
But he likes someone else.
I saw you with him at the workshop.
Seon Hwa!
Let's give up on this case.
What happens if Seon Hwa is alive?
It'll be a complete game-changer.
Find where Ryeo Seon Hwa
is buried immediately.
Some people are looking for you.
-Run away.
-It's Seon Hwa.
It's her.
Subtitle translation by: Eunjin Erica Kim