Greetings, Princess Fu.
Our Princess Consort
invites you for a chat.
Her Highness is waiting for you inside.
Zhao Chun'er.
Why did you ask me to come here?
Her Majesty asked me to show you
the people you want to see—
your friends.
Lin Mu?
Lin Mu!
Your Highness!
-Your Highness?
Your Highness.
How are your injuries?
We're fine.
Don't be sad, Your Highness.
I'm strong.
I won't die easily.
Zhao Chun'er!
What exactly do you want?
What can a weak woman like me do?
I just know you.
I know you value friendship
and that you must be very worried about
your friends,
so I brought you here to see them.
Shouldn't you thank me?
After all,
they were captured because of you.
And they might even die because of you.
This meeting today
might be your last.
Come at me!
They've done nothing to you!
Yes.
I am coming at you.
If it weren't for you,
they wouldn't have ended up like this.
For the sake of our old acquaintance,
I'll show you a clear path.
If you agree to marry Yan Xun,
Her Majesty will agree to let them go.
Otherwise, they will be branded
as traitors just like you
and Li Ce,
and executed.
Your Highness!
Don't agree!
So?
Haven't you always prided yourself
on being great?
What are you hesitating for?
Do you want to stay here
and keep watching them suffer!
Zhao Chun'er!
Living a life worse than death?
I don't understand.
Why must you make me marry Yan Xun?
Don't you like him?
Why are you doing this?
Do you think I still care about Yan Xun?
Have you forgotten what I told you?
I just want you to be miserable.
I want you to watch the people around you
get implicated because of you
and suffer.
Open the door!
Because you're a jinx,
everyone around you
will be dragged down by you.
Are you going to agree or not?
Are you going to open the door or not?
Zhao Chun'er,
you are truly insane.
I am the future Queen of Great Yan!
Who dares to be insolent?
Stop!
Chun'er.
Are you alright?
Your Highness,
you're here.
Princess Fu,
let's leave it here for today.
Don't blow things out of proportion.
Brothers,
I will definitely rescue you.
[REBIRTH]
[Episode 18]
Lady Chu,
can we talk upstairs?
What do you want with me, General Cheng?
Trying to kill me again?
I have no personal grudge against you.
We were on opposite sides before
just because of different positions.
That's not the case anymore.
We now share the same interests,
so we can put aside our differences
and talk about cooperation.
I can help you escape from Yan Xun.
What are you up to?
I don't care about you.
I just don't want to see Yan Xun
become more and more crazy because of you.
What I want
is a wise King of Great Yan.
Why are you telling me this?
Because you are the only one
who can influence him.
If you leave him,
it might make him less arrogant and cruel.
That would be a good thing
for me and the entire Great Yan.
How do you want to cooperate?
You are not fully recovered.
Stay a few more days
and recover before you leave.
You should give me what you promised.
King Ximeng wants me to take your life.
I can't die yet.
If you don't die,
my tribe and I will!
Your poison is acting up.
Rather than suffer,
I might as well end it for you.
Your injuries are not fully recovered yet.
If we fight now,
I won't let you go back alive.
He has no antidote.
He won't last more than a few days.
Stay with him while you can.
Zhuge Yue?
Zhuge Yue! Zhuge Yue!
Zhuge Yue, wake up!
Zhuge Yue...
wake up.
Chun'er!
What exactly do you want?
You've already achieved your goal.
Why did you provoke Chu Qiao?
Chun'er,
you weren't like this before.
Ever since you met Chu Qiao,
you've become...
Go on.
What have I become?
You've become twisted and terrifying,
nothing like the Chun'er I knew.
Li Yan,
you're right.
You are absolutely right.
Every time I see Chu Qiao,
I feel like I'm trapped in a nightmare.
In that nightmare,
I'm a hideous monster!
I'm sorry, Chun'er.
I shouldn't have said that.
You are not a hideous monster.
You're the person I treasure most.
Li Yan,
you don't understand.
You're loving the wrong person.
You never truly knew me.
I've always been ugly
and broken.
The Chun'er you loved
was killed by Yan Xun long ago.
On the day of my wedding,
the moment he rebelled,
he killed me once mercilessly.
In the reed marshes of Great Yan,
those soldiers humiliated me
and trampled on me.
That was when I died all over again.
Chun'er, say no more.
Chu Qiao saw it with her own eyes!
She saw my most humiliating moment.
I hate her so much.
Why?
Why could she, just a slave,
act so high and mighty
while she watched me get pinned down
and humiliated
by those people?
Why was it so easy for a slave like her
to ruin my life?
Li Yan,
you didn't expect this, did you?
The Chun'er you like
is a naked,
filthy monster.
If you regret it now...
Chun'er!
No matter what you've been through,
I will not leave you.
I am willing to love
every one of your wounds
and endure the suffering with you.
Will you really not despise me?
Chun'er,
no matter what kind of person you are,
I will always stay with you
for the rest of my life.
For all those who wronged you,
I will make them pay double for you.
[Qifeng Palace]
Your Majesty.
I'll marry Yan Xun.
I knew you would come.
I like making deals with smart people.
Then I still can't
compare to you.
I can marry Yan Xun for Li Ce's sake.
But you
can kill your own child
for the sake of power.
You have so many scars on your hands.
Does it hurt?
Thank you for your concern, Your Majesty.
They are old wounds.
They don't hurt anymore.
A woman's hands
must be beautiful.
What are you afraid of, General Chu?
This White Jade Suet Cream
is made from the fat extracted
from the tenderest part
of newborn lambs in the Snowy Region.
It melts when applied to the hands.
It's the best thing
for moisturizing a woman's skin.
I'm going to tell you a story.
When you finish listening,
your hands will be moisturized.
There once was a woman.
Her husband fought with his brother
over the family inheritance
and was killed.
The woman was pregnant.
To save her and her unborn child,
-she begged her brother-in-law for mercy.
-Your Highness!
I am willing to give up any status
to serve by your side.
She even gave herself to him,
hoping to use her sincerity
in exchange for her and her child's lives.
The man agreed.
He took her body
and claimed that
he had fallen in love with her.
But secretly,
he still had her child killed.
From now on, you are my beloved concubine.
I will certainly keep
my promise to you.
I will let his child grow up safely.
The Prince Consort of Chang is about
as far along in her pregnancy as you,
and she is due soon too.
Your Majesty, do you mean
you want to send the child in my womb
to the Prince of Chang's Mansion
to be raised?
If the child is born and lives there
as the son of the Prince of Chang,
when he grows up,
I will grant him official rank
and noble titles,
and let him enjoy a life
of wealth and honor.
Your Majesty,
His Majesty has ordered me
to take
the little Heir Apparent to the palace
for a routine pulse check
by the imperial physicians.
Just one little Heir Apparent?
Yes.
Just one.
Your Majesty!
Yan Qing, what's wrong?
The little Heir Apparent
contracted the plague...
and has passed away.
The man lied to the woman,
telling her the child died of illness.
The woman knew he was lying,
but to survive,
she couldn't expose him.
She could only smile
and play along with him.
Later,
this woman got pregnant again
and gave birth to the man's child.
Looking at the child,
she was in immense pain,
feeling that she had failed her child
who had died.
Day and night,
she heard the cries
of the dead child.
If you were this woman,
what would you do?
What about Li Ce?
Isn't he innocent?
No matter how much suffering
you've endured,
you shouldn't
make him pay for your grievances.
Then tell me,
aren't the slaves of Qingshan Manor
in Great Yong
innocent?
Aren't the soldiers
on the battlefield of Great Yan
innocent?
Slaves
have the fate of slaves.
Soldiers have the fate of soldiers.
As the crown prince of the royal family,
he also has his fate.
This is his fate,
and it is mine as well.
You simply don't understand
what men are,
or what power is.
Attachments
are meant to hold back fools
who trap themselves.
I became the Empress
not because His Majesty loved me so much,
but because I could do many things
for him,
allowing him to rest easy.
Do you think His Majesty doesn't know
there are many doubts about
the Crown Prince's assassination?
But his fear
is more important than anything else.
He would rather kill his own son
by mistake.
In the face of imperial power,
attachments
are not worth mentioning.
You don't have to hold a grudge
against His Majesty,
because you
are just like him.
You are the same kind of people.
You're wrong.
I have put a great deal of effort
into becoming like them.
The Crown Prince is my son,
but more than that, he is a man.
I may not understand my son,
but in my life,
I have seen too many men,
enough to understand them.
I imitate them,
trying to become them,
so that I can survive
in this palace.
You may like Li Ce now.
But that's only because
he hasn't seized power yet.
He still needs you.
Once he seizes power,
he will become
a completely different person.
Think of Yan Xun, whom you once helped.
I know Li Ce.
He is not Yan Xun.
Miss Chu,
you are indeed interesting.
Unlike most people
in this palace.
I will give you a chance.
If you don't want to marry Yan Xun,
you can choose to stand on my side
and work for me.
What do you say?
I'll marry him.
But I have one request.
Before I get married,
I want to see Li Ce one last time.
I've told you so many times.
Don't bother me.
Fu?
You're here to see me?
Li Ce,
you've suffered.
What are you doing here?
I don't want to see you.
You don't want to see me?
Then who was smiling so happily just now?
Who was happy?
Don't flatter yourself.
I brought you back to Biantang
hoping you could help me.
Now look what has happened.
Because of you,
not only have I been accused
of colluding with Ximeng,
but I've also lost my position
as Crown Prince.
What are you doing here?
Get as far away from me as possible.
Don't come to bother me anymore.
Li Ce,
I'm marrying Yan Xun tomorrow.
What did you say?
I am going to Great Yan soon.
Is that far enough?
Qiao.
What's going on?
If I marry Yan Xun,
the Empress will let you leave here,
and you will be able to save your life.
You may no longer be the Crown Prince,
but I didn't touch the money
you left in that shop.
It should be enough
for the rest of your life.
Qiao, are you crazy?
You nearly died
escaping from Great Yan,
and now you want to go back?
I told you I was just using you.
You don't need to get involved
in my affairs at all.
I left that money for you.
Take the money and leave right away.
Go!
Li Ce,
I am the all-powerful,
invincible General Chu.
Trust me.
I will get you out of here.
Isn't this Zhuge Yue's shadow puppet?
Your Majesty,
we are ordered by the King of Great Yan
to prepare your wedding makeup.
It's not my first time.
I am very familiar
with the wedding customs of Great Yan.
I know what to do.
[Boque Palace]
Your Highness!
Lin Mu?
Open it!
Your Highness!
Yan Xun.
The Empress promised me
that as long as I agreed
to the marriage alliance,
my companions would be released.
You are going back on your word!
Chu,
this is the dowry
I requested
from the Empress for Princess Fu.
It's a long journey
from Biantang to Great Yan.
In order to prevent unexpected events,
I have to prepare something in advance,
don't I?
Don't worry.
Provisions in Great Yan are precious.
We don't feed idlers.
As long as Princess Fu arrives safely
in Great Yan,
I will release them immediately.
According to Her Majesty's decree,
Crown Prince Li Ce has been disrespectful.
He is stripped of his title
as Crown Prince
and demoted to a commoner.
He is exiled to his fief in Youzhou
and confined there.
He shall depart today.
I...
receive the decree.
Li Ce,
trust me.
I will definitely get you out of here.
Your Highness,
you've been staring at this shadow puppet
all the way.
Does it have some special meaning?
Shut up.
This shadow puppet is a secret signal
from Qiao.
It can help us escape.
It's very important.
Gentlemen, your tea is ready.
S-Sir.
Your cup is full.
Thank you.
Enjoy your tea.
Your Highness.
Coming.
Here you go.
Enjoy.
Sir.
It's him! It's him!
This shadow puppet is beautifully made.
Enjoy your tea.
Your Highness,
it seems this shadow puppet
doesn't have any special use.
Don't worry.
Qiao will definitely find a way
to save us.
Your Highness.
Qiao is here to save us?
No.
This doesn't seem to be the official road.
Why did we stop?
Don't panic. I'll go down and take a look.
Where are they?
Where is everyone?
Great!
You're finally here!
What did I say?
I told you Qiao would definitely
come to save us.
I'm afraid I will disappoint you,
Your Highness.
Her Majesty specifically ordered me
to send you to hell.
No.
You have been demoted to a commoner.
You don't deserve
to be called Your Highness anymore.
Zhan Ziyu!
Don't think you can do whatever you want
just because Her Majesty
is backing you up.
The people coming to save me
will be here soon.
I knew someone would come to save you,
so I specifically chose this road for you.
By the time your people arrive,
they can only collect your corpse.
I am no longer the Crown Prince.
I will no longer pose any threat to her.
I didn't expect
she still wouldn't let me go.
What a pity.
Although you are her son,
you don't know her at all.
You're wrong!
I know her too well!
I just thought that
no matter what conflict I had
with my mother,
we were still blood,
and things would never come to this.
You think that to Her Majesty,
you're only a threat to her power?
Your very existence
is a humiliation to her.
Only when you completely disappear
can she truly feel at ease.
Let's see how far you can run.
Song Cheng!
Run, Your Highness!
Run!
Take him.
Minglu.
Minglu?
You actually...
Cut the crap!
Minglu,
take them and go first.
I still have something to do.
Assemble the troops
and prepare to depart!
Consort Helian is missing.
What is it?
Your Majesty,
Consort Helian is missing.
Missing?
Your Majesty,
Consort Helian
said she was going for a walk nearby
and went to that hillside.
But when the maids went to look for her,
she was not there.
We've already sent people
to search the entire hillside,
but they found nothing.
Then keep looking.
Where could she possibly go alone?
Yes.
You guys, follow me!
Split up and search!
Go now.
Yan Xun should only be delayed
for a short while.
I can't go alone.
I have to take everyone
in the prison cart with me.
Impossible.
I only agreed to let you go.
Those people aren't part of our deal.
Well now,
the deal has changed.
Though I'm from Great Yan,
I've heard that in Biantang,
the god here governs
the love between men and women.
I pray that you bless His Majesty
so he may achieve his heart's desire
and be happily united
with Queen Chu forever.
I am willing to spend my life
in vegetarian devotion and accumulate merit,
only in exchange for His Majesty
and his beloved being together in happiness.
How could you believe in such a thing?
Your Majesty?
Utterly foolish.
I am ignorant.
I saw Your Majesty
worrying because of Queen Chu
but didn't know how to ease your burden.
I just heard from the mountain people
on the road
that this temple is very efficacious,
so I wanted to come up
and pay my respects.
Everyone is waiting for you.
Don't waste time.
Run! Run!
Hurry! Hurry!
Let's go!
Your Majesty,
while we were looking for Consort Helian,
Chu Qiao escaped in the chaos.
It is my fault.
Please punish me, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
it's all my fault.
If Your Majesty
hadn't been looking for me,
Her Majesty wouldn't have...
Get in the wedding carriage.
Your Majesty?
I told you to get into
the wedding carriage.
Your Majesty.
Now that Chu Qiao has run away,
she will definitely return to Tangjing.
Should we inform Biantang Empress?
Let's go.
Return to the Capital of Great Yan.
Didn't we agree to meet at the residence?
Why are you here?
I was afraid you'd change your mind
and go back to Great Yan with Yan Xun.
I didn't know
that Lord Zhuge could get angry too.
Couldn't you tell
I've been angry all these days?
I really couldn't.
Whether you're angry or not,
you always have a frozen face.
Chu,
I prepared this for you.
Do you like it?
Chu,
let me draw your eyebrows for you.
Do you remember
when we were in Yingge Courtyard,
I also drew your eyebrows for you?
You promised to go back to Great Yan
with me.
But why?
Why would you rather stay in Biantang
with that incompetent Crown Prince
than go back with me?
Your Majesty.
Look at me.
I am not Queen Chu.
Didn't you want to be Queen Chu?
Haven't you always wanted to replace her?
I'm giving you the chance.
Why aren't you taking it?
I thought you were a smart person.
I didn't expect you to be so stupid too.
Princess Fu!
Do you know that
holding the Empress hostage is treason?
You, a deposed Princess,
and me, a useless prince,
are a match made in heaven.
You bold traitor!
To frame me,
you dare to hold His Majesty hostage?