(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
Are we sure
the patient is doing okay?
His BP is dropping again.
Hang on. Let me check.
You should eat these.
You need to eat well today.
- Thank you. I will.
- You're welcome.
Uh, excuse me, but the girl that was here.
Did you see where she went?
Uh, she left a while ago.
Do you know when?
About ten minutes ago.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
You are Hong Woo-jin's guardian, right?
Uh, yes.
The operation went well.
We'll have to monitor his progress,
but the surgery was successful.
God, thank you.
Thank you so much.
Hang in there.
Yeah.
BLOODHOUNDS
MARINE SPIRIT!
KIM MYEONG-GIL
Hey.
Gets me every time.
Let's go.
Whoa!
Let's run.
Woo!
Ah!
- Eighty-six!
Eighty-eight!
- Eighty-nine!
- Ninety!
- Ten more!
One!
- Two!
- Three!
Twelve.
Thirteen.
Fourteen.
Good morning, sir.
Continue.
Fifteen.
Sixteen.
One, two, three, four!
One, two, three, four, five!
You did it! Yes!
- Whoa!
- Good job. Get up.
What we want to do is topple them
and knock them off balance, right?
- So I think--
- Hey, guys.
I think we should have a talk.
I already told you both no.
If you go back there, you're gonna die.
We understand
why you would be worried about us, Mr. Oh.
Then why don't you listen to me?
To be rebellious?
Uh, Mr. Oh, if I may,
let me tell you what I think about this.
After all the experience we've gathered,
I believe we can fight
Kim Myeong-gil and win.
Yang-jung and Du-yeong are dead.
How can you win?
By following all the instructions
that Mr. Choi gave us.
Uh.
Too many people have had their family
and things they love taken away
by Kim Myeong-gil.
Mr. Choi said
that if we gather those people
and combined our resources
that we'd be sure to win.
Everyone's in hiding
because they know
that they don't stand a chance alone,
but if others like me and Woo-jin
decide to show up,
I'm sure they're gonna want to help us.
What if… Kim Myeong-gil gets to you first?
Oh, you don't have to worry
about the two of us.
Woo-jin has fully healed,
and I've gone up two weight classes,
so my punches are stronger.
We're fully prepared to take him
and his minions down this time.
Between what we've learned
from Mr. Choi, Mr. Lee, and Mr. Hwang,
I'm sure we can beat Kim Myeong-gil.
No.
I won't allow you to.
And that's the end of it.
Mm.
Mr. Oh, I'll be in Rome
by the time you read this letter.
I rented out a small room
with the money Grandpa left me.
I had promised him
that we'd all go to Rome together
- after taking down Kim Myeong-gil.
-
But I ruined everything.
I won't ask you to understand my actions.
But if I stay here,
I'll keep thinking about Grandpa.
and I can't handle that.
Wherever I go, I'm reminded of him,
and I can't stop crying.
It's driving me crazy.
Things will get better
if I'm somewhere far away.
I love you,
and I'm sorry.
- Jesus, it hurts so much.
- What you're feeling isn't pain.
It's the feeling
of weakness leaving your body.
What does that mean?
It means you're gonna emerge
stronger than yesterday.
Guys.
Follow me.
Yes, sir.
This is the last
of Mr. Choi's emergency money.
Take it and go.
I tried to hold you back
because of my fears, and I'm sorry.
I'll book a room and car for you in Seoul.
Don't get hurt.
Thank you
We appreciate it.
We'll win, no matter what.
809.
Oh, here.
Yes?
Yeah, uh, hello.
The two of us were sent here
by Mr. Oh In-muk.
Come in.
Let's go.
Now, if I come back
and find the tape's been torn
or moved at all,
I'll report you to the police.
Uh, why?
My underwear is in there.
- Oh, no, that's not gonna to happen.
- Nuh-uh. Nuh-uh.
There's one bed here and another above.
Who wants the one on top?
- Doesn't matter.
- Yeah.
Then you take the top bunk.
Okay.
Uh, excuse me, sorry, but may I ask
how you came to that decision? Hm?
Just because I can.
Oh.
Uh, here's the key card
and the keys for the car
Grandpa told me to rent.
And here's my number,
but don't call me, please.
I'm busy.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
Cool.
Thank you.
See you.
Hey, wait a sec.
Didn't she just say
that Mr. Oh is her grandpa?
Mm-hm. She did say that.
Ah, they do look alike
now that I think about.
They're both small
and wear glasses.
It seemed like she was forced
to let us stay here.
Yeah, it did.
I feel bad.
Enough of that.
- Let's wash up and strategize.
- Okay.
- My stomach really hurts. Out of the way.
- Whoa, ouch.
YANG JAE-MYEONG
Why him?
Because I think we need to capture
Yang Jae-myeong first to gather intel.
You?
YANG JAE-MYEONG
MR. MOON, PRESIDENT IM
I think we need
to gather our allies first.
We'll be more powerful
if we work together.
That's a good idea.
But how are we going to find this person?
IIL GROUP HEIR
Mr. Choi said he'd be our greatest asset.
I was thinking about it
on the way here.
It won't be easy to get him to meet us.
But I'm gonna try to come up with a plan.
Mm.
- Hey, look!
- Hm?
Whoa!
I think this is a convertible.
- The roof retracts?
- Yes.
It's fabric.
Sir.
There are so many people
who have been screwed over
by Smile Capital just like you.
We're suggesting that we all join forces.
Honestly, the loan sharks in this area
basically all know one another.
If you were to take the lead,
all the others would follow you.
And then what?
You take back your money
and make sure Smile never pulls this shit
with private moneylenders again.
We can obliterate them. Hm?
You've lost a couple hundred million
to them, right?
No, can't do it.
Ah.
If your little plan doesn't work,
I can end up dead.
What about all your money?
Fuck that. It's not worth it, man.
I mean, I can make more.
I'm not getting involved.
You see, I value my life more than money.
- Sir, please--
- Hey.
Hey, what the fuck?
What happened?
Sir? Sir?
Yo, you aren't allowed in here.
Oh, my junior marines!
What are you guys doing here, huh?
Sir, what happened to you?
Huh?
Oh, I uh…
A few days ago,
a bunch of gangsters came in
and took everything I've got.
Why?
I have ten billion won in bonds
that expire within a month.
If you get all of this money back for me,
I'll give you a cut.
Five percent.
This is way too good to pass up.
Then we should sign it now.
An elegant lady like yourself
probably doesn't know
how these things work.
Uh, these matters
require mutual trust, you know,
to come to an agreement.
I'll find someone else then.
- Hm.
- Uh, wait. Wait, wait. Hold on, hold on.
Sometimes we can…
…make exceptions.
Now…
MOON GWANG-MU
I found out later
that in the middle of that contract,
written in the fine print,
it said that if I didn't get these bonds
within the month,
I had to pay for half the entire amount.
Yeah, that was in there.
Definitely sounds like
Smile Capital's way of working.
What the fuck it that?
Its CEO is Kim Myeong-gil.
Kim Myeong-gil who worked for Mr. Choi?
Yes.
Where is that son of a bitch now, huh?
Did you hear about
what happened to Mr. Choi, sir?
What?
I'm sorry, but…
Mr. Choi was killed by Kim Myeong-gil.
Uh, what are you guys talking about?
Kim Myeong-gil killed Mr. Choi, Mr. Hwang,
and Mr. Lee. He killed them all.
We've been lying low in the countryside
with Mr. Oh until till now.
Fuck, stop it guys.
This isn't funny, okay?
I said… I said stop it.
I said stop it. This isn't funny at all!
What?
How could Mr. Choi be dead?
Why?
What do you mean?
Are you saying he's dead?
Come on, fucking answer me, you assholes.
Damn it!
God!
How could Mr. Choi be dead?
Tell me how, huh?
Man, I'm tired.
Oh, I'm exhausted.
Let's get some rest.
- Yes, sir.
Who's there?
It's been a while.
- These motherfuckers.
- Ah, shit.
Uh…
Hey, I'll tell you everything.
Just don't hit me, huh?
Word got around amongst the homeless,
so we've been going around
facilities for the disabled to steal IDs.
We weren't asking about you.
What's going on at Smile Capital?
Oh, well, then you should've been
a little more specific.
Has the casino opened, sir?
Wait a sec.
Hey, look down.
Can you maybe try a tough guy act?
How do I do that?
First off, don't be so polite.
Dude, that guy is clearly over 40.
I don't want to talk down to him.
All right, okay.
If he speaks down to you,
punch him in the face.
Mm-hm.
Hey, hard to believe, but I'm actually 31.
And I won't speak down to you guys,
so there's no need for any violence.
My body is a wreck right now.
Not too long ago,
a piece of shit
slashed both of my Achilles heels,
and I spent four months
in physical therapy.
That piece of shit is our friend.
Watch your mouth.
What happened was on me.
I totally deserved all of it.
So, back to the casino?
Yes.
I happened to overhear
the director talking on the phone.
Director? What's his name?
Kim Jun-min, sir.
He's alive?
Some piece of shit slashed his neck
with a knife, and he--
Ah, you're on the same team.
Okay, I understand everything now, 100%.
I'm gonna watch my mouth now,
so there's no need to hit me.
I fucking hate Kim Jun-min.
That guy's a fucking asshole.
Smile Capital's also a bunch
of motherfuckers.
I'm only in it for the money. That's it.
I'll tell you everything. I've been dying
to tell someone about their bullshit.
All right, we get it.
Please get to the point now.
Based on what I heard on the phone,
they're fighting with Iil Group
over the contract,
so Kim Myeong-gil
is really pissed off lately.
And?
Kim Jun-min is tight with this guy,
Im Jang-do.
He's an asshole too.
He was in charge of dealing with the cops,
but he just disappeared one day.
And recently, Kim Myeong-gil was drinking
at a hostess bar,
got into a fight with some dude,
and ended up breaking his wrist.
So the cops were called in,
and it was a whole scene,
but they swept it all under the rug.
That doesn't usually happen
when the police are called to a scene.
So from what Kim Jun-min said,
Kim Myeong-gil has found a guy
to replace Im Jang-do.
Apparently, he hasn't told anyone
about it yet.
Why?
Because he doesn't trust his own men.
And?
And he also plans on taking over
a golf course in Gyeonggi-do.
That's the reason
why we're busting our balls out here.
We get paid shit,
but they practically work us like mules.
Right, guys?
And that concludes my updates for the day.
Hold on.
You know you're fucked
if we send this to Kim Jun-min.
Keep your mouth shut.
No need to worry, sir.
If you need anything else,
feel free to get in touch.
Just like you, I'd like to see
Smile Capital crash and burn.
So do you think you'll be able to get us
the phone number Iil Group's eldest son?
Oh, no, I don't think I can do that.
People like them are pretty serious
about their privacy.
Oh.
IIL GROUP CHAIRMAN'S ELDEST SON
IIL GROUP HEIR
CONFIDENT TO DEVELOP A GLOBAL HOTEL
Oh, his name is Hong Min-beom.
He has the same last name as me.
Bro, this proves that Seoul has
the best jajangmyeon, right?
Yeah.
Why are you using my computer
without permission?
It's logged into all of my messenger apps.
We're so sorry.
We didn't open any messenger apps.
Go to that café next door.
Okay. We're sorry.
- Turn it off.
- Got it.
But how about just this once?
Hurry.
Yeah, that's all.
- Sorry again.
- Ugh.
How did she find out?
Uh, the messenger app must've alerted her
when we turned on the computer.
Mm. Mm.
Whoa!
- Damn. Look.
- What?
Hong Min-beom has 500,000 followers.
Let's see now.
Whoa! Stop, stop, stop, stop!
Didn't I say…
to have the contract ready by today,
so I could spend the money?
I tried my best,
but my father--
Hey, Beom.
Please don't kill me.
Please don't. Please.
Do what I asked you to,
and deliver the contract to me
by this Friday.
If you don't, I'll release the video.
And I will make it look as if
you threw yourself off a building
because of the footage.
Yes. Yes.
Do you want to get rid of Kim Myeong-gil?
We can help you.
What the fuck? Who are these guys?
WE KNOW WHERE THE HARD DRIVE
CONTAINING YOUR FOOTAGE IS LOCATED
Let's just meet them.
We better do it quickly.
The contract is due on Friday.
Then ask if they can meet us now.
What do I do if they say yes?
Have them meet you at the bar you like.
They'll show their true colors
once they drink.
Oh, shit.
Don't worry.
I can get two of my guys to follow you.
Hey, In-seong.
- Yes, sir.
- Tastes good, right?
Oh, yes!
I told you not to drink.
Uh, right.
Come on. They're here.
- Hello, sir. Hello, sir.
- Hello, sir.
Hey, guys. I'm Min-beom's cousin.
Oh, I'm Kim Gun-woo.
And I'm Hong Woo-jin.
I'm the one who sent you the DM.
Have a seat.
Yes, sir.
Let's talk over a few drinks
if you guys don't mind.
Uh…
Uh, I'm really sorry,
but I was attacked and stabbed
by Kim Myeong-gil's men
and they tore my liver, so I can't drink.
If you don't want to drink,
you can just say so, you know?
I’m not lying.
Here, here,
here.
We get it, yeah.
Okay, pull it down.
It’s a disturbing sight.
Why don't you sit this one out?
Were you stabbed too?
Well, actually,
I just don't drink alcohol, sir.
We’re about to talk about serious stuff.
Let's drink.
Well, what is the point
of us meeting here then
if we're not gonna be open
with each other?
How can we trust you
if you back out of something so trivial?
And to be blunt,
you asked to meet up
because you also need us.
- I’m sure I can have just one drink.
- No!
I'll be the one to…
to have a couple drinks with you.
All right.
Min-beom.
Now, let's drink.
Cheers.
Damn, you're a natural.
Let’s drink from the tall glasses.
These ones are too short.
This is the right way.
- Okay.
- Here.
There we go.
Mm.
Hey, dude. Whoa!
- Slow down.
- Mm-hm.
Much more relaxed now.
Shit.
This is fun.
No, hey, listen to me. Hey, man.
I'm so stressed by that son of a bitch.
I knew you were cool
when you raised your shirt.
- I'm your bro.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, you're my bro. Pour me another.
- Yes, sir!
Because of that stupid asshole…
…I lost so much hair from the stress.
I have hemorrhoids.
Earlier he punched me
before I could even speak.
The police commissioner fucking loves me!
When we're together,
he calls me commissioner.
I'm like, "Hey, bro!
Stop calling me that."
"People are gonna get the wrong idea."
Bro, we have to take care of this kid.
He's family. He's good. He's a good kid.
Woo-jin and Gun-woo,
do whatever the hell you want.
Fuck it, all right.
We've got your back till the end of time.
Should I pour you another, sir?
- I can't drink anymore.
- Okay.
I can't because I have hemorrhoids.
I work too much.
We should keep drinking.
Oh, shit.
Bro.
What the hell?
Oh, good morning, Min-beom.
Did you sleep well?
What's going on?
Uh, you brought us over last night
saying we should have a few more drinks
at your place.
Oh.
We were about to wake you up
for instant noodles.
- To cure the hangover.
- Uh-huh.
Have a seat.
- Gun-woo, take this.
- All right.
- And I can go wake up Gang-yong.
- Okay.
Uh, how much did I drink?
Gun-ho?
Gun-woo.
Oh.
What are we doing?
Oh, Gang-yong is going to communicate
with a computer expert
from the police agency.
That person will hack
Kim Myeong-gil's phone,
and then we'll burn all of the hard drives
in the safe.
The noodles are done.
You should eat, bro.
Gang-yong, get up.
When Kim Myeong-gil goes to Iil Group
to meet you this Friday
to sign a contract,
that's when you're gonna do it.
Who is?
You.
Right. Of course it's me.
Yeah, let's just eat.
How much did I drink?
Whoa! Be careful.
- Oh!
- Ah, nice.
Enjoy.
Mm.
- Thank you for the food.
- Thank you for this meal.
It's been so long
since I had this.
- Whoa.
It's huge.
It's so tall.
How many stories is this?
Thank you.
- Hello. Hello, sir.
- You're here.
- Hi, everyone
- Hello.
Hi.
- Let me introduce you to my team.
Go ahead.
Detective Yoon Han-gu.
Nice to meet you.
- Hi.
- Hello.
I'm Team Leader Kang Tae-yeong
from Cyber Crimes.
I'm not supposed to be here,
but nice to meet you.
- Oh.
Let's also keep my presence a secret.
We're all here in secret.
Okay.
Anyway, Tae-yeong is the leading
cybersecurity expert in the country.
She'll explain
how to hack Myeong-gil's phone,
and then she'll lead you through the steps
to activate the safe.
Right. There are two ways to do it,
and the first way is to use Wi-Fi, yeah?
So I'll install a jammer
in the meeting room,
and that will temporarily block
Internet access.
That will naturally lead the subject
to reconnect to the Wi-Fi again,
but the moment he connects
to the transmitter I made,
I'll be able to access his phone device.
And once I do, it's game over.
I've also researched
the different safe apps
that he's likely to be using.
As for the second method,
it depends if we can get him
to open up a more direct route for us.
You know how these days
we scan personal QR codes
when entering buildings.
I'll make one to post at the entrance.
ELECTRONIC ACCESS LIST
Then have him scan it.
Once that QR code has been scanned,
it'll open a door
for me to again hack into his phone.
We will be using both methods
at the same time, yeah?
Wait.
What do I have to do?
Uh… you just need to make sure
he stays connected to the Wi-Fi
for as long as possible.
I'll have access to his cloud,
but depending on the size,
it could take some time
to rake all of the data, you know?
If we're lucky,
we may be able to get evidence
for all of his crimes
and catch his accomplices.
Whoa.
But what if…
that bastard catches on?
What's our backup plan?
We're using both methods at once
to avoid needing a backup plan.
Oh, come on, dude.
What is this? Seriously!
No matter what it takes,
we have to destroy
that fucking hard drive tomorrow.
If it was up to me,
I would just take his phone.
Should be easy. Not so complicated.
What's with all the technical details?
Maybe I can take his phone.
Han-gu.
Uh, may I ask what's on the hard drive?
Oh, shit.
You don't need to know.
Got it?
Yeah.
Min-beom, let's get some air.
Min-beom.
You must be nervous.
I know it's a difficult operation.
And, of course,
there are also a lot of limitations.
Bro.
If we don't erase that hard drive,
I'll never be free of Kim Myeong-gil.
I'll be fucked.
That's why I am going to try my hardest.
Please trust me a little more.
I'll try.
Whoa. It's gone.
It's gonna work?
Of course.
Please take your temperature here.
Scan the QR code with your phone.
Shouldn't it be the other way around?
This is how our building does it, Miss.
That's unusual but okay.
So far so good.
- Okay.
- Yes!
Oh.
What's wrong? What?
There's seems to be nothing
in the file folders.
Give me a second.
The, uh, the safe app you had mentioned,
it's not here.
Are you sure the information was right?
Yeah.
Jang-do was not in a position to lie.
Is this asshole onto us?
Oh well.
Director Hong.
How are you?
Oh shit.
- What?
- There's no safe app on his phone.
This fucker has two phones.
What do you mean?
The phone he used
to scan the QR code was black,
but this one's silver.
- Ah.
So what do we do now?
We just need
to get him to connect to the Wi-Fi.
Sir, he's leaving the room.
I'm fine. Don't worry.
- Do you need something? Okay.
- I said I'm fine.
What happened?
Kim Myeong-gil has two phones.
The one we managed to get into
didn't have the safe app.
The phone with the app is in that pouch.
And?
We're still trying to figure out
what to do.
There's not enough time left.
The meeting is wrapping up.
Why don't we talk in private for a second?
Oh, shit.
Tae-yeong, Han-gu.
Could you guys give us
just a minute, please?
Uh, yeah.
Min-beom, what did Im Jang-do use
to take the video?
A cell phone.
Isn't there a chance he would've sent
that video to Kim Myeong-gil's phone?
You mean to get confirmation?
Right.
Before you sign the contract,
instruct him to delete the video first.
Simple as that.
Then Kim Myeong-gil will have no choice
but to take out his phone.
What if he doesn't?
What if he says he didn't receive it?
You should ask him to show you
his entire chat history with Im Jang-do.
And tell him that Im Jang-do said
he was going to send it to him.
You serious?
Criminals like Kim Myeong-gil
trust no one.
In order to check
that Im Jang-do finished the job properly,
he would have asked him
to send the video for proof.
I don't think I can.
You can trust me.
That's not it.
I don't think I have what it takes
to stand up to him.
I'm scared!
Fuck, just looking at him
makes my hands shake!
Min-beom.
Look, you will be able to do this.
I will kick down those doors
at the first sign of trouble.
And if things get out of hand
at any point,
I will use all of our family's resources
to protect you.
So please muster up your courage, okay?
Min-beom, we will barge in there with him.
You can do it.
You sure kept us waiting, didn't you?
What were you doing?
Could the lawyers please step out?
I need a moment in private with Mr. Kim.
Okay.
I'm sure you don't want to be arrested.
What's with… this bravado?
Erase the video
before we sign the contract.
It's not here.
I'll delete it as soon as I get home.
You have my word.
Don't bother lying.
I know that your guy sent it
to your phone.
I want to see you delete it.
- I'll do it now.
- No.
I'm going to delete it myself.
I don't trust you.
And if I refuse?
Then I'm not signing.
You must be crazy.
Well…
You think my family will sit still
if you lay a finger on me?
I've been so embarrassed,
so I've been trying to take care of this
on my own.
But… my aunt runs the tax department.
One phone call from me,
and within 24 hours,
your company will be audited.
So,
you want to pay tens of billions in taxes?
You want to go there? Huh?
You've become more eloquent.
At least with your threats.
I learned from you.
I like it.
Well, I don't.
WI-FI OFF
WI-FI ON
We're in.
Okay, give me a second.
Ah!
The safe app.
It is here.
- Yes!
- Hell yeah!
- Okay
- Shh!
All right, I will break in now, okay?
Will that be all, Mr. Hong?
Now we can sign.
Okay. Should I go ahead with it now?
Do it.
Okay.
TOTAL INCINERATION IN PROCESS
It's done.
Yes.
- Hey, are you 100% sure that it worked?
- Yes, definitely.
- Oh, thank you.
- I'll extract all of the data right now.
Okay, yeah, extract it. Extract it all.
This is all thanks to you two.
- Oh, not at all.
- Not at all.
We'll gather all the evidence
on that phone,
and that bastard Kim Myeong-gil
will end up behind bars, so don't worry.
- Great.
Thanks for your hard work.
Gang-yong will be in touch.
- Okay, thank you.
- Thank you.
There's something
I've been thinking about.
Your wound, your scars.
I'd like to help you get treatment for it.
Oh, I really appreciate it,
but I'm okay.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Thanks to this scar,
I was able to meet some amazing people,
and it gave me the strength to carry on
instead of giving up.
So I…
I'm okay with my scars.
I understand.
I'll see you guys soon.
- Okay.
Please walk them out.
- Yes, sir.
- I'll say bye here.
- Okay, thank you.
- Bye. Thank you.
- Thank god it ended well.
- I know, right?
- I knew things would go well.
- Uh-huh.
- Oh, and Gun-woo.
- Hm?
Do you remember when Mr. Choi asked
Im Jang-do about the gold bars?
Yeah, uh, about how
only In-beom knows where they are.
Yeah. How much do you think it's worth?
I don't know.
My guess is
somewhere around tens of billions.
Wow.
That includes the money
he stole from Mr. Choi, right?
Right.
If the cops let Kim Myeong-gil
slip away again,
he's gonna take the money and gold
and leave the country.
We can't let that happen.
That money belongs to Mr. Choi.
Let's get ready.
Let's chase him down to the end
and maul him to death.
I'm in.
- Yes, sir!
- Woo!
- Beom, Jun-min, good work, you guys!
- Sir!
Man, let's go for round two at my place.
Woo! We're here.
Don't you smell something?
Hm, it does kind of smell like smoke.
Quiet.
Don't.
Fucker!
Go.
CHOI TAE-HO
- Where are you?
- Working overtime, sir.
I'll send a driver
with a phone over right now.
I need you to find someone.
- How many people?
- For now, just an old man.
How urgent is this?
If you find him by tomorrow at noon,
I'll pay you triple.
All right, sir.
SERIOUS CRIME INVESTIGATION
DIVISION UNIT 1