[music playing and singing]
♪ ♪
[cheers]
[muffled music and singing]
Wait, what'd you say?
We said, stay out
of our way or we'll kill you.
Why are you--
ah!
Oh!
It's no use.
These guys have been
completely brainwashed.
[music playing]
Out of the way!
Ah!
[fighting sounds]
[music playing]
♪ ♪
Oh!
Ah!
[groans]
♪ ♪
Please, listen to me!
[smashes]
Let it go.
What do you think you can do?
Oh!
♪ ♪
Ah!
[kicking]
♪ ♪
Somebody help!
[whoosh]
Who are you?
[music playing]
♪ ♪
Electrowave tackle!
Ah!
Spider-Man!
Mitsuba!
This looks pretty bad.
Nothing we can't handle.
[theme music]
♪ ♪
[singing]
[music playing]
♪ ♪
Yee! Yee!
[singing]
♪ ♪
It's my turn!
Let's go.
[fighting sounds in background]
Hey, come back.
Don't go yet.
I mean, we've finally
been reunited.
[spits]
You boys are leaving already?
You really should
have stayed down.
Uh--
Quick!
Get away!
This is your chance!
We'll keep them distracted.
But hurry!
[crying]
[music playing]
You're all alive.
I still can't believe it.
♪ ♪
You three risked everything
for a scumbag like me.
I owe you my life.
♪ ♪
You guys are my brothers.
I need you!
.44 Magnum!
[whack]
[whoosh]
Ah!
[whack]
♪ ♪
[gasping]
Are you OK?
Yeah, I'm good.
All done over here.
Oh, man.
They kicked your ass.
Can you walk?
Sure.
No sweat.
Now let's go beat that monster.
Ah!
It-- it's you!
Huh?
Good to see you.
That punch,
the moment it landed,
it woke me up!
[crying]
I'm so-- so sorry!
I know.
[ALL] We're sorry
we hurt you, Boss.
Please forgive us!
[crying]
♪ ♪
[NAKAO] I'm the one
who should apologize.
Huh?
It's my fault
you wound up here.
Sorry I left you behind.
Won't happen again.
[ALL]
Ah!
We're OK!
Hmm.
What's going on?
His love for his friends
broke Shocker's control.
I'm sorry, but this
will have to wait.
We need to move now.
Right.
Hmm!
Let us show you the way.
[music playing]
Hey.
Huh?
I've been thinking about it.
We're supposed to wait
for the show's climax.
That's super boring.
Yeah, you're right.
I mean, it's a good plan,
but I'd rather be
fighting Shocker now.
Mitsuba, how dare you
make me wait another second
to avenge our grandparents!
We should have gone
straight for the Batman
instead of sneaking around
like rats on the damn roof.
[MAN] How about you
two fight me then?
[BOTH]
Huh?
[music playing]
♪ ♪
No way.
It's you, the Spider-Man!
Yeah, sure.
Let's do it.
Get ready to fight.
Ah!
Rider!
Machine V3-yah!
- I was kidding.
- Huh?
Oh.
[laughs]
You guys really
are entertaining.
I'll give you that much to you.
[growls]
Can't wait to see
how this turns out.
[shimmering]
Huh?
He vanished?
Yee!
Ah!
[music playing]
Nice work.
It's not easy to transform
without the brainwashing.
Well, we learned
from the best.
Almost there!
[thud]
Oh!
I've been expecting you.
Mm!
Ah!
Uh, Raiko.
Oh!
Wait. Hold on a sec.
What are you?
[thud]
Mm.
So, Raiko, tell me,
is there a chance you
aren't brainwashed anymore?
I mean, all that time
we spent together.
It had to mean
something, right?
Come on.
[music playing]
♪ ♪
My feelings haven't changed.
I love you.
Ah!
[ALL]
The hell was that?
Ah!
[crash]
[ALL]
Boss, just hold on!
[RAIKO] It seems that man
has made traitors of you too.
[ALL]
Ah!
I have no choice
but to kill you all.
Mm!
Leave her to me.
Take the others
and keep moving.
I'll catch up.
Oh!
Don't take too long.
Now die!
[ALL]
Ah!
♪ ♪
Right behind you.
Huh?
[music playing]
You know, you're the one
I was most interested
in going up against.
You're a pro wrestler.
How about a revenge match?
[laughs]
This time, I'm going to hit
you till you stop fighting.
I hope that's OK with you.
You're welcome to try.
♪ ♪
Ah!
It looks like we've both
improved since our last fight.
That works for me.
♪ ♪
[knocking]
[HENCHMAN]
Master Bat-Man,
it's almost time.
[laughs]
[shimmering]
[cheers, applause]
[music playing]
♪ ♪
[singing]
[crowd chanting, "hey"]
♪ ♪
[NAKAO] Love is
an amazing thing, huh?
[BOTH]
Huh?
There's a few things
out there that I love,
a handful of great people, too.
Just thinking
about that stuff's
enough to make me feel
like I'm on cloud nine.
And you, you just love
the hell out of pro wrestling,
don't you?
Mm!
Ah.
What's going on here?
Do you two know each other?
We don't.
But this old man
taught me something.
Oh!
Even a combatant can
get stronger as long
as they train hard enough.
Ah!
That's my Raiko!
I may still just
be a lowly combatant.
No way!
What is this pressure?
[RAIKO] But I can become
stronger than a monster.
Ah!
[music playing]
My body, it won't listen!
I can't move!
Raiko!
[guffaws]
Ah!
You really did enjoy all
that training we did together.
You actually care about me!
Ha, Raiko, I love
you so damn much!
[slam]
[laughs]
[thud]
Did that finally shut you up?
Uh, just checking in.
I can't tell now.
Are you sure you're
still our enemy?
Definitely.
OK, but this whole
"I love you" thing?
Ah!
I'll kill you!
Mm!
Ah!
[music playing]
[crash]
♪ ♪
[fighting sounds]
Ah!
♪ ♪
Time for a Rainmaker!
The move I've worked so hard
to perfect is faster!
[intense music]
♪ ♪
Ultimate Electrowave Throw!
Ah!
♪ ♪
[gasping]
[singing]
♪ ♪
[whimpering]
Uh, unbelievable.
You countered
Kazuchika Okada's Rainmaker
with a version
of Naoya Ogawa's STO.
[shimmering]
That move was my own.
[cheers]
[music playing]
♪ ♪
[RAIKO]
I lost again to a human.
Not even Shocker.
[music playing]
♪ ♪
No, it wasn't just her.
It was the power that came
from her unshakable commitment
to her beliefs.
Her strength lies
in her resolve.
She was more
determined than I was.
Amazing.
I see now,
I want to be stronger.
♪ ♪
Radio check.
Are you in position?
I'm ready.
So am I.
All set.
Just say the word.
[YURIKO]
Looks like
I'm just in time.
I'm glad you made it!
Nice work.
You beat her?
Yep.
Let's do it.
[music playing]
[fireworks]
[cheers, applause]
[light flash]
Everyone, thank you
so much for coming today.
And now for the grand finale.
We have a gift to share
with our beloved fans.
[cheers, applause]
[beeping]
[music and vocalizations]
♪ ♪
Cut the lights!
[light thuds]
[sirens and screaming]
A fire?
[WOMAN]
Emergency announcement.
A fire has broken out.
The concert will not continue.
For your own safety,
follow all staff instructions.
Evacuate.
Proceed to the nearest
exit in an orderly fashion.
I will repeat,
emergency announcement.
Everyone, please stay calm!
Walking is safer
than running!
Make sure to not
lock the doors.
Leave space for others
when you exit.
This way, please.
What is this?
Do not let them escape.
[ALL]
Sir!
Yee!
[NAKAO]
I don't think so!
[fireworks]
Ah!
[screaming]
My Raiko!
I'm going to get
you out of this.
Even if I have to take
the boss's head.
Tojima and Ichiyo,
you're up!
[music playing]
Huh?
Let's do this, Shocker!
♪ ♪
What the hell?
[BOTH]
Now Rider Double Kick!
Ah!
[crashes]
[ALL]
Did they hurt you, Master?
Who the hell are you?
I'm V3.
I'm Kamen Rider!
And we've come to stop you.
Your evil scheme
ends here, Shocker!
[shimmering]
♪ ♪
You idiots ruined everything.
[growling]
♪ ♪
I'm going to kill you all.
[singing]
♪ ♪
Well, well.
Impressive.
However, with these odds,
do you think you can survive?
[theme music]
[singing]
♪ ♪