(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
[Fate Chooses You]
[Episode 9]
Master, be careful.
Master, let me help you.
You call this place...
Nine Absolutes Cave?
Master.
Don't you have the incredibly powerful,
always battle-ready,
divine weapon Nine Absolutes Sword?
I just borrowed the name
and called this place
the Nine Absolutes Cave.
Isn't it majestic?
You're living a good life here.
Where is the Immortality Pill?
It's over there.
It's still brewing though.
It's cold
and chilly in this cave.
I rely on this furnace to warm my quilt
to help me fall asleep.
Come over and have a drink.
This is a sixty-year-old Luosang wine.
We buried it together back then.
I just took it out a few days ago.
Such good Luosang wine!
I must have a few sips.
Come.
Lu, come sit.
Master.
Here.
Uncle Chu Ying.
Such great wine!
Come, Master.
Master, Master.
Come, Uncle Chu Ying.
Xin Xiong,
as a Great Completion Realm cultivator,
rarely meets his match.
Even when he left Tianyuan Sect
to build Xin Xie Manor,
he was able to single-handedly elevate
Xin Xie Manor to the ranks of
the Twelve Immortal Sects.
It's a pity that
there is a decline in talent
and there are no successors.
After guarding this coveted spot
for many years,
only two disciples remain.
They don't even know etiquette.
When they see their elders,
they don't even know to greet them.
No manners at all.
I pay my respects to Senior Uncle
from the Qingshan Sect.
I worry for Xin Xiong.
I wonder if this Xin Xie Manor
will still be able to hold out
after he's gone.
Xin Xie Manor is a quiet,
sparsely populated place.
It's not as lively as the Qingshan Sect.
But my master is healthy
and has the Immortality Pill
to sustain him.
He's not worried about
what happens after he passes away,
so there's no need for you to worry too.
If you have free time in the future,
the Qingshan Sect is always welcome
to come and give advice.
I heard that the Qingshan Sect
is tucked away in a corner
and relies on renting
other sects' land.
It is also the only one among many sects
that doesn't test for immortal perception.
You can join as long as you pay.
Then why didn't you join them?
I have no money.
You...
Bai Zongying from Tianyuan Sect
pays respect to all seniors
and fellow Taoists.
Asking for a scolding.
What's wrong?
You like him?
No, no.
Then who is he?
He's a senior from Tianyuan Sect.
I've seen him a few times,
but he doesn't know me.
You are just into him.
Dr. Zhu.
Taoist Bai.
Is your master not coming this time?
My master is in seclusion.
He ordered me to go ahead.
Once Divine Doctor Su
sets the time for opening the furnace,
our sect's Elder Cang Fengzi
will come in my master's stead.
Okay.
Everyone.
I believe my junior
has already told you the reason
for gathering everyone here.
I will not repeat it.
Now, please
report your respective
Gongshan Jade Tablets.
The Wang family of Jinqiu
has 1 jade tablet.
But my father is old,
and I am also seriously ill.
So,
I would like to request
2 Immortality Pills.
If anyone is willing to
sell their jade tablet,
the Wang family
will not only offer a handsome reward,
but if you have any requests
in the future,
our entire family will also assist you.
The Lingxu Sect originally
only had 1 jade tablet.
But I had a close friend
whose time was running out
and he unfortunately passed away.
But before he died,
he gave me his Gongshan Jade Tablet.
Thus,
I now have 2.
I am a Captain with the Dongyou Army.
I have 1 Gongshan Jade Tablet
and want to exchange it for
an Immortality Pill
for my Lady.
Xin Xie Manor also has one.
Continue.
Sun Moon Cavern
has 5 jade tablets.
Our dynasty has 6 tablets.
Wait.
I remember at first
the imperial family only had 3 tablets.
How did it become 6?
Master Fu is an immortal,
so you might not understand.
There are still many people in this world
who are loyal and love their country.
Qingshan Sect,
1 tablet.
Lingji Mountain,
10 tablets.
That's not right.
Lingji Mountain should have one less than
Sun Moon Cavern.
Why instead of having fewer,
there are actually 6 more?
It could have dropped from the sky,
or we picked up on the road,
or we bought it with money.
It's none of your business.
If you're not convinced,
go buy them with your own money.
Zigai Mountain
has 3 tablets.
Senior.
There...
There are 30 tablets by now.
Are there really that many?
Tianyuan Sect...
20 tablets.
How many?
20 tablets?
Tianyuan Sect,
20 tablets.
You really have the nerve to claim that.
If that's what you're saying,
should I be thanking you
for leaving 10 for me?
Why don't you say
you have 30 tablets instead?
You might as well take them all.
Why did we even come?
Chongling Valley only said
Gongshan Jade Tablets can be
exchanged for the Immortality Pills.
They never said we had to
state their origin.
Tianyuan Sect
will definitely present
these 20 tablets.
If Master Fu has any doubts,
you can come find me later.
Or I can find you,
if you prefer.
T-That won't be necessary.
I was just curious
and asked casually.
Record it.
Tianyuan Sect
has 20 Gongshan Jade Tablets.
Everyone,
that's all for today.
My master still needs time to
refine the pills,
so we cannot yet determine
the exact time for
the Pill-Tasting Conference.
But please rest assured,
it won't take too long.
Today, our valley
has prepared guest rooms for all of you.
You may leave,
or you can stay in the valley for a while.
That's what he said?
No way!
Y-You actually believed him?
I mean...
Let me tell you.
When he was a prince,
I knew
he was no good.
I know him too well.
What nonsense!
You were busy performing back then.
How did you have time to know him?
The palace is
only so big.
What secrets could it hide?
Besides,
at that time,
I was already an eighth-grade musician.
What a high-ranking official!
Don't be so sarcastic,
will you?
Can't you talk properly?
When I was 8 years old,
my parents sold me to the palace.
If it weren't for
my good voice,
I would have been castrated
and sold as a eunuch.
Later, I followed my master
to learn medicine
and built this Chongling Valley.
To be honest,
I've seen a lot
in my life, haven't I?
But I've never seen
anyone so
shameless.
Have you heard the term,
"Master of the Four Realms"?
His honorific title?
He gave it to himself.
He brags about his magnificent
and graceful brushwork.
Guess what?
It's as ugly as it gets.
Let me tell you,
his handwriting is so bad
that I write even better with my foot.
Right.
A-And he also brags about
his painting skills,
saying it can stir up storms
and subdue the spirits.
It's all gibberish!
Right.
Maybe it should be pasted on the door
to guard the house,
or hang it by the bed to ward off evil.
It's disgusting to even look at it.
The living and the dead would shun it.
You don't have to always
compare yourself with him.
I'm not trying to compare.
I just don't understand.
Seriously,
what did you see in him back then?
Why did you insist on taking him
as your disciple?
I mean,
back then, I had begged you for so long,
but you completely ignored me.
You said you'd only take him
as your disciple.
In the end,
I only became an honorary disciple.
This...
It's been so many years.
Why mention him again?
I don't really care.
I just feel it’s a real shame for you.
All right.
You are doing well too, aren't you?
Chongling Valley has been thriving
for all these years.
Even the Twelve Immortal Sects
have to show you some respect too.
Don't mention them to me.
What I despise the most
are those bastards.
It took the human race only
a few thousand years to evolve
from a primitive state
to building their own cities
and developing their own civilization.
In just a few thousand years,
we learned to make paper
and keep written records.
We invented the compass
to navigate the seas.
We know how to manage and think.
We created
a splendid civilization.
But do you know
when
this development stagnated?
It was when cultivation appeared.
The power of a cultivator is limitless,
capable of doing anything.
It was precisely their arrival
that completely destroyed
the progress of human civilization.
You might find it hard to imagine
that it took our species
only a few thousand years to reach
this level of development.
But now, tens of thousands of years
have passed,
and the lives of the commoners
remain the same.
With their faces to the soil
and their backs to the sky,
they practice slash-and-burn farming
and remains at the mercy of the weather.
Be it flood or drought,
as long as a disaster strikes,
the commoners
have no escape.
In today's world,
everyone is committed to
personal cultivation.
Everyone feels that
entering an immortal sect to cultivate
is the best way out.
They constantly delve into alchemy,
breakthroughs, ascension, and immortality.
Under such a trend,
people only focus on
personal cultivation,
and no one cares about
the well-being of the ordinary people.
This way,
the path for the human race
is growing ever narrower.
Then why are you making
the Immortality Pill?
Narrower and narrower...
There are too many people in the valley,
and they refuse to leave.
We don't have enough guest rooms.
Will you stay here?
Yes.
Then you shall stay here.
Where are my two friends?
They are patients.
Patients all stay at Mingzhu House.
If you want to find them,
you can go over and ask.
Okay, got it.
Are you clear about
the rules in the valley?
What rules?
The use of magic is
prohibited in Chongling Valley
Got it.
I'm not done.
Who allowed you to leave?
Then keep talking.
Well,
the room you assigned me
won't do.
There are dense forests
and many birds in this area.
I'm afraid the noise in the morning
will keep me awake.
Change it for me.
I can't.
What kind of attitude is that?
It can't be changed.
You little brat.
I bet you're doing this on purpose!
[Mingzhu House]
This place is so much better
than the room I am in.
We've arranged
with Dr. Zhu.
Tomorrow afternoon,
he will personally examine Miss Lyu.
At the Wei hour,
I'll come to pick you up.
Cunsu Hall is over there.
Meals are free.
If it's inconvenient for you,
you can have someone
deliver the meals to you.
Do you two
have any other questions?
No.
Thank you.
I'll go back now.
Thank you for your trouble.
Take care.
You're welcome.
Take good care of the patient.
Miss Xin.
Where are you staying?
I live near Li Ying Garden.
I know.
I heard all the cultivators
are staying there.
Did you know each other before?
W-We just met.
His name is Huai Qing.
He's Dr. Zhu's disciple.
He's very nice.
He's nice to everyone.
Nice to everyone?
Yes.
Come on in,
have a seat.
Lu.
No.
You go back first.
I need a break.
Xieyun Cottage.
Don't get lost.
Okay.
Why am I here again?
Wasn't I just here a moment ago?
Senior.
Senior!
How do we get to the pantry
at Li Ying Garden?
♪ Honor and disgrace;
rumors and prejudice ♪
♪ Everyone has their own take ♪
♪ Fingers coated in blood
and disasters brought about ♪
♪ Were never what I wanted ♪
♪ The great way is fading away,
besieged by mysterious traps ♪
♪ Who dares to treat life and death
as nothing? ♪
♪ In the blink of an eye, the body
collapses, and the soul is destroyed ♪
♪ The fire starts raging across the land ♪
Senior, are you also here for
the Pill-Tasting Conference?
I'm a friend of Su Taiyi.
You are Divine Doctor Su's friend.
Then I should call you Senior.
I'm Xin Mei from Xin Xie Manor.
May I know your name, Senior?
Lu Qianqiao.
"Qian" as in one in a thousand,
"qiao" as in tree.
So you are Mr. Lu.
I recognize this place now.
You don't need to see me off.
Thank you, Mr. Lu.
I'll take my leave now.
What a small world.
Sobered up so quickly?
Guess who I just saw.
Was it Xiaotao, Xiaohong,
or Chunxing, Qiuju?
None of them.
It's Miss Xiahua from Wei County.
The one who beat the drum in Wei County
to seek justice for her father.
It was you, Lord Lu Huai,
who presided over the case.
I was the one who picked her up.
From the office's entrance to the hall,
it's only a few dozen steps.
You actually managed to hook her up?
What do you mean by "hook up"?
Our relationship is pure
and innocent.
She's recuperating
in Chongling Valley now,
staying in Mingzhu House.
I'll go accompany her for a few days.
Coincidentally,
you also met Immortal Xin.
You should try harder,
and maybe you can rekindle your romance.
Have a good time.
Wait for me!
Hurry up!
Coming!
Is it like this?
Add a sword!
Right, right.
Make the face thinner.
Make it thinner.
Draw it well for me.
Okay.
And here.
Have you seen the woman in this painting?
You know this crazy woman too?
I was at home,
teaching my wife a lesson,
when she rushed in and
beat me up.
Look, she loosened my teeth.
Then she just turned and left,
without even giving me half a coin.
Which way did she go?
That way.
What, did she beat you up too?
Miss.
Do you think it's her?
I don't know.
We'll just do whatever
our benefactor says.
Where else can we find a job
this easy and profitable?
Is there a customer?
Have a seat.
It's hot today,
and it's right at noon.
I see you've had a long journey.
You must be exhausted.
How about a bowl of barley tea?
It's the best way to quench your thirst
and cool off.
Have you seen this woman?
No.
Just kidding.
You've seen her?
When? Where is she?
This is a teahouse
where people can come to rest.
You came in and started questioning,
like an official
interrogating a prisoner.
You didn't even order a pot of tea.
How am I supposed to host you?
Bring me a pot of tea.
Although herbal tea quenches thirst,
asking for information
is tiring.
You must order a pot of Biluochun.
Is this Biluochun?
Yes.
Our exclusive recipe.
Naturally, it's different from elsewhere.
Please enjoy.
I ordered the tea,
and paid the silver.
You can tell me the truth now, can't you?
Well, I’ll have to give that some thought.
Our teahouse is a hub for travelers.
There are many people who come and go.
Many just have a sip of tea,
rest their feet, and then leave.
There are so many faces,
so I have to recall carefully.
Then bring another pot of tea.
Thank you, Miss.
That woman is slender
and is about the same height as me.
She has delicate features,
a gentle voice,
yet possesses a certain tenacity.
She loves to use a sword.
That sword is special.
It looks like a crescent moon
and is very pretty.
I think...
if that sword were to take your life,
it should be quite easy.
What did you say?
Grandmaster.
I, as the Master,
have everything prepared.
When the time is right,
I will renew your bones for you,
Grandmaster.
I've already prepared
a set of animal bones.
It's being nourished in the cold spring
in the back mountain.
Animal bones?
Animal bones...
might be
the closest thing to human bones,
they afterall are not of the same origin.
They simply cannot merge
with human flesh and blood.
I'm afraid it will cause other illnesses.
For example, weak constitution,
a body that easily feels cold,
and severe heartache.
It's okay.
I know.
Then why would you still, Grandmaster...
If I don't use animal bones,
should I go find a set of
actual human bones?
Rest assured.
I know what I'm doing.
Dr. Zhu.
Dr. Zhu!
Acute cough and wheezing!
Coming!
Master!
Master, you dropped your shoe!
Feeling better?
Much better.
Thank you, Dr. Zhu.
No problem.
Just rest well.
Okay.
[Shunxin Residence]
These are fruit sent by Chongling Valley?
Yes.
This is all they have.
I really can't live like this anymore.
Young Sect Master,
[Xu Feng from Lingji Mountain]
the Immortality Pill
is about to be unsealed.
We will soon return to the sect.
1 Gongshan Jade Tablet
exchanges for 1 Immortality Pill.
The Tianyuan Sect reported 20 tokens.
With the 10 tablets I reported,
that makes 30 tablets.
Exactly enough to distribute.
Young Sect Master,
Sun Moon Cavern's capabilities
shouldn't be underestimated.
They have 5 tablets.
On this train of thought,
the imperial family has 6 tablets,
while Bai Zongying has 9 tablets left.
Do you think they have 、
enough to distribute?
Young Sect Master,
don't worry about others.
The Sect Master has made it clear.
This time,
he asked you to exchange
those 4 jade tablets,
but you reported 10 all at once.
Tianyuan Sect only has 5 tablets,
but Bai Zongying dared to report 20.
If I reported anything less,
wouldn't it be an embarrassment
for our Lingji Mountain?
Then...
What are we going to do about the rest?
Look.
What is this?
Bank notes?
This land in Zigai Mountain,
owned by Cai En, is leased.
The lease is about to expire.
They haven't renewed the lease,
nor have they moved out.
Why do you think that is?
Think about it.
Those two mortals
were dressed in rags.
I have no idea where
they got that jade token.
Xu Feng.
Let me ask you,
why do people want to live forever?
Why?
For a carefree and happy life, of course.
Even if they live forever,
can they be carefree?
You're brilliant, Young Sect Master.
But this is still not enough.
I have my ways.
Go.
Give this letter
to that female disciple
from Xin Xie Manor.
Tell her
that I'll be waiting for her
right here.
May I ask,
are you Immortal Xin Mei
from Xin Xie Manor?
Who are you?
Our Young Sect Master would like to
have a word with you.
Immortal Xin,
would it be convenient for you to go to
Shunxin Residence for a chat?
It's not convenient.
I'm not feeling well today.
Then when will you have time?
Our Young Sect Master
is from Lingji Mountain—
He's even waiting for you!
Auntie,
do you want a queue number?
It's a dozen numbers earlier than this.
Two taels of silver
for one.
I'll take it.
Alright.
Here you go.
Go inside.
Miss Xin?
Miss Xin!
It's you, Zhang Dahu.
Yes.
Are you here to see a doctor, Miss Xin?
Not feeling well?
Tell me about it.
I have been
walking through this valley for years.
I'm practically half a doctor.
I just can't drink water recently.
I throw up as soon as I drink water.
Then you can't line up here.
This is Dr. Zhu's clinic.
He specializes in colds, emphysema,
and heart and chest diseases.
You seem to be having
some digestive issues.
You should see Dr. Liu.
He's good at treating your sort of issues.
I'll take you there.
Dr. Liu?
Yes, Dr. Liu.
Just right ahead.
Let's go that way.
Let's go.
Senior Liu.
You're here again.
Delivering a letter to Senior Zhang.
Come here.
Right here.
Dr. Liu
specializes in regulating
the spleen and stomach.
But he as he gets older,
he only does rounds on the 7th and 9th
of each month.
Isn't today
the 7th?
His queue numbers
were snapped up two months ago.
Don't worry.
I have a way to get you in.
Get in?
How?
Your illness came suddenly.
We have to make an exception.
Here's the plan.
In a bit,
step on my shoulders
and we'll climb over from here.
Don't worry.
In our Chongling Valley,
the use of magic is forbidden.
I don't need magic for this height.
She flew that high?
Let's go!
Miss Xin.
Stop walking.
This is the place.
In a moment, Dr. Liu
will come out of there.
As soon as he comes out,
you rush over
and lie on the ground.
Don't worry. Trust me.
No doctor will just ignore you.
What's with the "ah"?
Are you afraid of looking foolish
just to get treated?
Do you want your life or your pride?
But...
It's just that getting an appointment
with Dr. Liu
is so hard.
By the time it's your turn,
you might already be dead.
Listen to me. Follow me.
Oh no.
My stomach hurts.
Maybe I ate something bad
last night.
I need to go to the toilet.
I'll be right back.
Don't go.
What am I supposed to do without you?
My lady.
Didn't I tell you already?
As soon as he comes out,
just lie on the ground and scream in pain.
The physicians in our valley
all have a heart of gold.
They won't ignore you.
Be sure not to hesitate.
Why am I sweating so much?
Mr. Lu.
Master, slow down.
Wait for me, Master!
Master, your shoes.
Master, your shoes!
Master!
Master, your shoes.
I heard you brought a patient back.
Where is she? Let me take a look.
I taught you all your medical skills.
What are you hoping to look at?
All the more I must take a look.
I want to see what kind of patient
could receive
personal treatment from
of the Grandmaster of Chongling Valley.
Master, your shoes.
By the way,
you're sure she's a young woman,
right?
Grandmaster, please.
There's just something about
this girl that I really like.
How old is she?
About your age.
A cultivator?
She looks like
such a sweet, delicate girl.
I thought...
you liked the bright and charming type.
Will you still see her?
Yes.
Spell of Utterance.
Master.
What is the Spell of Utterance?
The Spell of Utterance is a kind of magic
where whatever you say becomes law.
No matter how unreasonable the request is,
the one under the spell
will follow all instructions
to complete the request.
It reminds me of the cold case
that shocked the Yong region back then.
It was a young, wealthy man who was
under influence of the spell.
In broad daylight,
he slit his own throat.
It's said that this kind of magic
has been lost for many years.
I didn't expect
to see it again today.
But this sort of magic
is extremely powerful
and has many restrictions.
First,
the spellcaster's cultivation level
must be much higher than the victim's.
Second,
it's easier to take effect when the victim
is completely off guard.
The only way to break it is to
kill the person who casted the spell.
But she is still in the
Foundation Establishment Stage.
Looking at the whole Chongling Valley,
there are many whose cultivation
is higher than hers.
If this spell
was not cast in the valley
but on the way here,
it will be hard to find who was behind it.
So what exactly are
her symptoms now?
A large amount of water is
seeping out of her body.
I tried to feed her water,
but it worsened the symptoms.
So it seems,
before we find the spellcaster,
we still have to feed her water.
Fish Drinking Technique.
You taught me that.
Is anyone here?
I didn't expect
to meet you here, Mr. Lu.
I was actually going
to see Dr. Zhu Yu.
But the line was too long.
Then a guy
who knows Chongling Valley well
brought me to
the backyard of Suwen Hall.
He said I could wait there
for Dr. Liu, who specializes in
the spleen and stomach.
And then...
And then you had to lay on the ground
to get the doctor to examine you.
Many people do this.
You are not the first.
Give me your hand.
Let me check your pulse.
Mr. Lu, you also know medicine?
A little.
Your condition is stable now.
But until we find
a permanent solution,
you can't drink any more water.
Can't drink any more water?
Mr. Lu,
what exactly is wrong with me?
It's not an illness.
It's a spell,
called the Spell of Utterance.
Spell of Utterance?
You can understand it as
absolute obedience to the spoken word.
Once this spell is cast,
the victim will follow every order
of the spellcaster.
Think carefully.
When did your body
first start
having problems?
If you put it that way,
it must have been in Pingxiang Town.
I was just passing through,
and then a
crazy man
ran toward me.
Judging by his appearance,
he didn't look like he was
from the Central Plains.
He looked like he was from Beixiang.
He told me
the water was poisoned
and told me not to drink it.
At the time, I thought
I had just met a madman.
Thinking back on it,
I haven't been able to drink water
since then.
But I’ve done nothing
against this madman.
Why would he want to harm me?
He might not be the spellcaster.
When casting the Spell of Utterance,
sometimes
the spellcaster doesn't need
to be present.
People, animals,
even a green leaf
can serve as a medium for the spell.
I didn't notice it
at all back then.
The Spell of Utterance
can only be cast by
a higher-level cultivator
on a lower-level one.
Your powers are weak.
It's normal you didn't feel it.
How can I break the spell?
Please advise me, Mr. Lu.
Kill the spellcaster.
Is that the only way?
That's the only way.
Then I'm doomed.
I... I can't even imagine
who would want to harm me.
And
if I can't find the spellcaster,
does it mean I can never
drink water again?
Since you consider me your senior,
I won't let you die.
Do you have a way, Mr. Lu?
Yes.
Mr. Lu,
where are we going?
Qiyue Lake.
The Qiyue Lake in Chongling Valley
has crystal clear water
and extremely dense spiritual energy.
It's extraordinary.
The spiritual plants here
grow very well
because they are watered by the pool.