ADAPTED FROM BAI LU CHENG SHUANG'S
LOVE IN THE CLOUDS
My younger cousin
might be absent-minded sometimes
but she has many people proposing to her.
However, I am very picky
as her older cousin.
I think no one is good enough for her
besides the First General
of the Six Realms.
A while ago, at the same place,
you mentioned
using my body to
help you raise netherbeasts.
Are you using
your younger cousin as a bargaining chip?
You can refuse, General.
Just assume I've never mentioned this.
I see.
EPISODE 11
If you had been sincere
in buying back Xinliu's freedom,
why did you even marry her?
You should've let her go.
Instead, you kept
her in the Dengxian Cave.
Is this what you call freedom, huh?
No.
That's not it.
It's you.
It's all of you!
Why must you doubt Xinliu's love for you?
Ji Bozai.
Little fairy,
listen well.
I planned all of this
just to take Ji Bozai's life.
You and Zhang Tai have no value to me.
I can release both of you.
But you will be the one
to decide.
TOMB OF BELOVED WIFE XINLIU
What are you doing?
Kill him
and I'll release you and Zhang Tai.
- What do you think?
- Dream on!
I will never hurt Ji Bozai.
Dream on!
No. I'll never…
I'll never…
No.
What?
Don't tell me you've
truly fallen for Ji Bozai.
There's no true love
without sacrifice.
You are wrong.
If he can die for you,
I'm sure he will feel happy.
No!
You are wrong.
I will live on with Ji Bozai.
Why didn't she kill you?
Why?
- Ji Bozai. Come back.
- Why?
Come back.
Get out.
How are you?
Ming Yi.
As long as you kill Ji Bozai,
I will spare you and Zhang Tai.
Why didn't you choose the easy way?
Why should I do as you wish
and become trash like you?
How dare you scold me?
So what? Do I need to pick a day for that?
Mu Xinliu is dead.
So you captured
every fairy that resembled her
to be your puppet
and control them like
how you controlled Xinliu.
This is not true love!
It seems like you are
no longer trying to save her.
- Zhang Tai.
- Ming Yi.
Xun Ming.
When you possessed me just now,
I could feel a seal in your memory.
Perhaps there's
another story to Xinliu's death.
What did you say?
Have you thought about this?
Perhaps your memory with Xinliu
was altered.
Xun Ming, think carefully.
Dengxian Cave has never
seen any sunlight in the valley.
Why is the cave always bright
in your memory?
Also,
there were many "Zheng" characters carved
at Luosheng Forest and Dengxian Cave.
Do you really not know what they mean?
Or are you purposely avoiding the truth?
Why?
Did Xinliu not want to stay here?
Where are my true memories?
Why can't I see them?
The seal on your memories
can only be opened by an external force.
Why don't we make a deal?
I'll help you undo the seal
and you release Zhang Tai.
Why should I trust you?
Don't you want to know the truth?
Divine souls of all realms,
I'm willing to give away all my memories
without any regrets.
You should practice the qin
in Luosheng Forest more often.
Yes, Qibai.
Xinliu,
Officail Website : kissasian.be
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
I want you to tell me
whether you have
true feelings for me or not,
you're the only one I love.
Xinliu,
say it to me.
Quickly.
I'm back.
General, you leave early
and come back late recently.
You're being secretive
and you have blood on your clothes.
What are you doing, General?
Xinliu,
Lord Hanfeng has agreed to our marriage.
The condition
is that I raise netherbeasts for him.
When the netherbeasts mature,
he will be the ruler of Jixing Abyss.
So all your injuries
came from the netherbeasts?
I'm willing
to do anything for you.
If someone finds out,
you should escape first.
After I hide my primordial spirit,
I will escape from this place to meet you.
Why must you do this?
You put yourself
and me in a cage.
Don't even think about leaving me!
Xinliu,
tell me. Whether
you have true feelings for me or not,
you're the only one
I love.
General,
I found the medicine to treat your body
at Jixing Palace.
Thank you.
I'm very fortunate
to have you as my wife.
I heard the Heartbond Array
can suppress the netherbeasts' power.
The side effect on
you is getting more serious.
My spiritual power is too weak
to cultivate the Heartbond Array with you.
Why don't you
undo the heart imprint with me
and find a stronger
fairy to cultivate with you?
Even without the Heartbond Array,
I can still find a way to
suppress the netherbeasts.
Don't even think about it.
No matter what,
I will not
let go of you forever.
What happened to your wrist?
I was distraught
and got hurt myself.
You used your blood
to concoct the medicine for me?
Xinliu,
don't hurt yourself for my sake anymore.
General, you are really good
at lying to yourself.
General.
Don't worry.
I can suppress it.
General, drink this medicine.
The netherbeasts' influence
can only be resisted with
a strong enough spiritual power.
What I just fed you
only made you weaker.
Why?
Why can't the netherbeast kill you?
- Why?
- You know why.
You know very well why!
Xun Ming, I hate you.
I hate you so much!
I hate all of you.
I hate all of you!
Why must you marry me? Why?
Why must you trap me here?
It's just one life.
If you want it,
I'll give you everything.
Xinliu.
It turns out
I won't taste any freedom in my life.
This isn't true. This isn't true!
Xun Ming, these are all true.
All the beautiful memories you have
were fantasies created by your obsession.
Did you really love her?
- You only love yourself.
- That's enough.
Quit that act of a loyal husband.
It's time to keep your promise
and release Zhang Tai.
Don't you know
that foxes
are the most cunning
and the most untrustworthy?
You want to save her?
Dream on!
Xun Ming, do you still not get it?
Mu Qibai altered your memories
so you will let him use you
to raise netherbeasts.
Do you think you can stop Mu Qibai?
Even if you can stop Mu Qibai,
you still can't stop
the person behind him.
What do you mean?
Why bother asking?
Today,
our souls
will be laid to rest here.
He is trying to destroy the Illusory Realm
and trap us here forever.
Let's go.
Zhang Tai's primordial spirit
is still in Xun Ming's hands.
- I…
- If you can't let go of her,
you can die with her.
Ming Yi!
- Ming Yi.
- The exit is closing.
We can't die here. Go!
How troublesome.
The passage is going to disappear. Go.
Go!
Die here with me!
Ji Bozai!
Biting off more than you can chew.
What a fool.
We still don't know who the fool is yet.
Disperse all evil and return
everything to its primordial state.
Break!
Zhang Tai.
Ming Yi!
Grief Blossom?
Were you poisoned by the Heavenly Grief?
She can't find out about my identity.
Ji Bozai.
Ji Bozai forced
you to show your true form,
and here you are venting your anger at me.
He is not as disgusting as you, liar!
It seems like you've
remembered everything.
Xun Ming.
I saw how useless you were
and couldn't accept
the truth of Xinliu's death
so I helped you
by sealing your true memories.
Instead
of thanking me, you wish to go against me?
Have you forgotten?
Everything you can do means nothing
before the netherbeasts.
The Illusory Realm was broken.
You are just a spent tool.
You are no longer useful to me.
Even if I die here,
you will still meet
your nasty ending one day.
Nasty ending?
Since the day we raised netherbeasts,
His Lordship has discarded all humanity.
Only by raising netherbeasts
can Jixing Abyss
obtain the strongest power
and be a part of the Upper Realms forever.
What His Lordship is doing
is a small sacrifice for the greater good.
Wretches like you know nothing.
Sacrifice is inevitable
on the path to greatness.
When it is necessary,
I can even sacrifice
the person closest to me.
If killing at this level
results in divine punishments or karma,
all the more reason for me
to rewrite the divine law.
Your Highness,
our next plan is…
First, it was Hou Zhao.
Then, it was Xun Ming.
Ji Bozai is avenging Bo Yulan.
His next target
will be me.
Ji Bozai is fighting for Jixing Abyss.
We can't do anything to him.
If we want to ruin Ji Bozai,
we must first remove
his identity as a warrior.
My Lord, you're awake.
Come.
Granny Xun and I
made this medicine for you.
How did we escape?
Thankfully, you created the exit.
We spent a lot of effort escaping.
Jixing Abyss's general
died during our wedding.
Someone from
Judgment Hall was here, right?
Yes. Zhang Tai was saved thanks to you.
After she recovered,
she went to
Judgment Hall with Immortal Situ
to accuse Xun Ming
of abducting fairies everywhere
to harvest their primordial spirit.
Later, Lord Hanfeng arrived
and said Xun Ming
committed suicide out of guilt before him.
Judgment Hall
stripped Xun Ming's title as a general
and pronounced him a criminal.
He still died in
Mu Qibai's hands after all.
You knew
who I've been trying to avenge,
didn't you?
Yes.
When you asked Ruo Shui
to accuse her father, Hou Zhao,
you weren't planning to hide it anyway.
I've been by your side
for so long and I'm not a fool.
In this current situation,
I'm afraid Mu Qibai already knows
that you are trying to
punish those who harmed Fairy Bo.
I'm not from Judgment Hall.
How can I punish them?
You could've killed all of them
but you spent all your efforts
searching for evidence
to turn them into criminals.
Aren't you doing that
because you don't want
them to die as innocent people?
So, you were the one telling Zhang Tai
how to accuse Xun Ming
at Judgment Hall.
Yes.
They hurt the innocent
and abducted immortals to the Sunken Abyss
to make them suffer.
They should be punished.
They are the real criminals after all.
Speaking of which,
when the Illusory Realm collapsed,
you could've abandoned me.
Why did you return to save me?
Who knows?
Why are you smiling?
Do I need a reason to save you?
I've always been kind. You know that.
I'm even keeping Ming Xian's stupid fan
so I can return it to him.
He is my rival after all.
You fought Ming Xian
because you had
a wager with Princess Tianji
and had to win.
Since you mentioned
how honest and kind you are,
had it not crossed your mind
to use any dirty tricks back then?
Officail Website : kissasian.be
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
For example,
poisoning Ming Xian?
Is that what you think of me?
Why should I poison him?
If I want to win,
I can just win
against him fair and square.
If I lose,
dying to him isn't
something embarrassing either.
I see.
You are an honest person.
I'm guessing that Ming Xian
is also happy to
have an opponent like you.
Those who were
fortunate enough to fight against you
must have had
their most exhilarating battle ever
because you are not an opponent…
but a despicable person?
…but a close friend.
You don't believe in anyone, right?
You won't eat anything
that has been touched by others.
Right now,
there's someone
who is willing to trust you.
I wonder
if you are willing to trust us more.
I trust you.
Immortal Situ.
Please come again another day.
Immortal Ji and Fairy Ming Yi are asleep.
Someone's here.
It's our wedding night.
Should we let a night visitor of Wugui Sea
see us planning some important business?
You are a philanderer, My Lord.
Instead of consummating
on your wedding night,
are you plotting to kill someone else?
You've left Moonlit Blossoms for so long.
Have you forgotten how to act?
You saw it through?
Saw what through?
That you are not a philanderer?
Or
that you are just…
Ming Yi.
We should let our visitor
have a clearer view, at least.
You tricked me.
How can you act when your will is so weak?
You're biting me for real?
If I get hurt, it's on you.
There's no one here.
He's still around.
- There's no one at all.
- Who told you so?
Weren't you immersed in your act?
Continue.
You tricked me like this too,
when you first
brought me back to Wugui Sea.
The first night.
It was you
who caused the fire on our first night.
Also,
if I hadn't rejected you the next morning,
- does it mean…
- Yes.
I was thinking of an excuse.
Perhaps your heavy makeup
or bad taste in outfit.
Perhaps I'd say you smelled too good.
Ming Yi.
If I tell you
that I…
SHE TIANLIN, MING XIAN'S MASTER