[Fated Hearts]
[Episode 7]
Awake, huh?
This is
very rude of you.
Wouldn't it be even ruder
if someone else saw this?
I might as well kill you first.
If I silence you, no one will ever know.
Then you should have
done it while I was sleeping.
I don't like taking advantage of people.
Besides,
it would be such a pity
if I didn't get to see you
begging for mercy
before you die.
What a pity indeed—
I've never learned
how to beg anyone for mercy
in my whole life.
Everything can be learned.
You could give it a try today.
Your Highness!
Make him leave.
Hurry up.
Yes, Your Highness!
As long as you don't tell anyone about
what happened last night,
we can still be partners.
What are you thinking?
Nothing happened last night.
I saw you were drunk senseless,
so I just brought you back to rest.
Your looks aren't nearly enough
to catch my eye.
That's for the best.
But whether I kill you or not
depends solely on my mood.
It has nothing to do with what did
or did not happen last night.
Fine.
But could you please
change your position first?
You're making my legs go numb.
How's that?
Holding a knife to someone
feels rather rude, doesn't it?
What's with these lousy clothes?
Messing with my moves.
What are you looking at?
Didn't you leave?
W-Which young lady
is talking to me right now?
When I woke up today,
my vision was all blurry.
I...
I couldn't see a thing.
Then let me fix that for you.
Oh...
What...
What was that just now?
I can't hear anything, either.
You'd better be deaf and mute.
My lips are sealed.
Your Highness.
I...
Get to the point.
Xia Jingshi has come to Yujing,
saying it's regarding
the marriage alliance.
He'll arrive today.
Your Highness,
are you letting her go just like that?
How about I keep an eye on her for you?
She'll be back.
Is it true that
Prince of Zhennan will arrive
in Yujing today?
This news
came from the morning court session,
so it must be true.
His Majesty has arranged for
the Minister of Rites, Shen Wu,
to receive him.
But I heard that
Prince of Zhennan
isn't bringing many attendants with him.
Does my brother know about this?
What did he say?
I haven't heard
any news from the First Prince.
Your Highness. His Highness
the Second Prince is here.
Sister.
Guess what gift
I've prepared for you?
Well, well.
You're not focusing on your studies
and instead spending time
preparing gifts for me.
Be careful, Father might punish you
if he finds out.
If Father finds out,
he might even praise me
for being thoughtful.
Come on, bring it up.
Be careful. Slowly.
Sister, come check this out.
This is what I specially prepared for you:
a hundred-year-old walnut tree.
It symbolizes a harmonious marriage
lasting 100 years,
specially chosen to wish you
a joyful wedding.
I'll take it then.
Thank you, Chengyang.
What wonderful gift
did Brother prepare for you?
Brother has always adored you the most.
He must have given you
all sorts of
strange little trinkets, right?
Sister,
where did you put his gifts?
Brother...
He didn't forget to you a gift, did he?
He doesn't approve of your marriage?
Nothing gets past you, does it?
Oh no.
Brother didn't give you any wedding gift,
and here I am,
as your little brother
making such a grand gesture.
Sister,
as for this walnut tree...
I'll just pretend I never saw
or heard of it.
I appreciate the thought, though.
You can take the gift back.
Don't worry.
I won't mind.
But what if Brother
just won't agree?
What then?
I will marry Xia Jingshi.
Sister,
I just remembered
I still have homework to do today.
I'll take my leave now.
Come on. Move it away.
Yes.
Hurry up.
I take my leave.
Let me out!
Let me out of here!
Xueying!
Sister!
Don't come closer! Go away!
What's happening?
Yesterday,
right after I brought the kids here,
these
unreasonable bastards
sealed off the residence
and wouldn't let anyone leave.
I know who's behind this.
Don't be afraid.
Wait for me to come back.
Sister!
What's your intention?
If you want to eat, have a seat.
If not, keep quiet.
I hate being disturbed
while I'm eating the most.
So you knew about this all along.
Knew what?
Don't play dumb.
Xueying's residence
is being closely watched,
allowing people in but not out.
I was wondering which bastard
did it.
Turns out it really was you.
Miss Yixiao, you're in quite a temper.
It seems none of the dishes on this table
are to your taste.
But whether they suit your taste or not
doesn't matter.
As long as they suit mine,
that's what counts.
Yesterday, you said it yourself
that you'd let me go,
but now you've gone back on your word
and broken your promise.
What exactly are you playing at?
I'm protecting you guys.
Why can't you appreciate
my good intentions?
Protecting?
This is clearly imprisonment!
Imprisonment?
The entire Yujing City
is my territory,
all under my control.
And you're someone I brought back myself.
Would I even need to imprison you?
Can you possibly escape from my grasp?
As my defeated opponent,
you sure have quite the attitude.
Looks like
you don't want to cooperate after all.
Of course I do.
But it has to be me
who sets the ground rules.
You have your rules,
and I have mine.
It's not solely up to you.
Your Highness.
All our men in the Feng Battalion know
that Susha is to form a marriage alliance
with Jinxiu.
Somehow a rumor has spread,
saying that Your Highness
opposes the marriage alliance,
and that His Majesty is going to
strip you of your military command.
Our men are furious
and threaten to confront the court.
I fear a mutiny may break out
in the ranks.
Utter nonsense!
Order all Military Commanders
and Deputy Generals
to come see me immediately.
Yes, Your Highness.
Go find out
exactly who's trying to
undermine army morale.
Those deliberately spreading rumors
must not be spared.
Yes, Your Highness.
The Feng Battalion
has always had iron discipline
and stands as the model
for all the armies.
Every soldier faithfully
fulfills their duties
and obeys orders.
Now it's said the army
is restless with signs of mutiny,
but I don't believe it.
If you ask me,
it must be you
leading officers
whose hearts are wavering.
Everyone here
has been through
life and death alongside me.
There are no outsiders here today.
If you have any complaints,
please speak up freely
and hold nothing back.
Your Highness,
there's one thing I don't understand.
Susha and Jinxiu
have such deep-seated hatred,
and now, all of a sudden, we are to form
a marriage alliance to seek peace.
Could it be...
Could it be because
we lost the battle at Pingling City
that we must humble ourselves for peace?
I believe this is the very question
on all of your minds.
That battle at Pingling City was fought
by us.
If this marriage alliance
is because we lost,
then how can I
face all my brothers in arms?
Utter nonsense!
A marriage alliance between two kingdoms
is such a momentous matter,
affecting the major affairs
of both kingdoms.
How could it be determined
by a single battle?
Besides, let's be clear—
it was Jinxiu that proposed
this marriage alliance.
Why?
Because they chickened out.
They don't dare fight us anymore.
They want to use the Battle of Pingling
as a graceful exit,
and that's why they came to us
with this marriage alliance proposal.
It was Emperor of Jinxiu
who proposed the marriage alliance,
yet you're all
sulking and feeling resentful here.
What are you trying to do?
Are you trying to force His Highness
to rebel?
Enough!
You only need to remember two things.
First,
the defeat of Battle of Pingling
was my fault.
None of our soldiers in the Feng Battalion
are to blame.
Your Highness, how could it be your fault?
Second,
regarding the marriage alliance,
I have agreed to it.
I understand
any grievances our soldiers may have,
and I'll take responsibility.
Any resentment our soldiers feel,
let it be counted against me.
But you must tell everyone
that His Majesty has not stripped me
of my military power,
and no one at court
is plotting against me.
The weapons of our Feng Battalion
will only ever be pointed at our enemies,
never at our own people,
and mutiny will never be tolerated!
Yes, Your Highness!
Your Highness,
I have urgent news to report.
Speak.
Yun Qing's dagger?
This is the dagger
you previously awarded to Yun Qing.
He values it more than his life
and never parts with it.
How did it end up with you?
Your Highness,
Yun Qing quietly left
the camp early this morning.
He left this dagger
with a message for Your Highness,
that he intends to kill someone
on Your Highness's behalf,
and that he's failed you in this life
and wasted your cultivation.
Is he leaving the Feng Battalion?
You may leave.
Yes.
What does he mean?
Who does he want to kill?
You said this morning
that Xia Jingshi is arriving in Yujing?
Yes, he's arriving today.
[Yujing Border]
He intends to kill Xia Jingshi?
Xia Jingshi is coming for
the marriage alliance.
If he dies in Yujing,
Susha will be accused
of betrayal and dishonor,
and Yun Qing's crime will be unforgivable.
Please, Your Highness, save Yun Qing.
Yun Qing is completely loyal
to Your Highness.
He knows that Your Highness
cannot kill Xia Jingshi yourself,
so he wants to kill him for you.
How can he be so foolish?
If he does this,
isn't he just giving up
all his hard-earned military achievements
and his promising future?
Yun Qing is your sworn brother,
but he's also like a little brother to me.
Don't worry.
I'll definitely find a way to stop him.
But...
Your Highness,
Yun Qing is the best archer
in our battalion,
and he knows the terrain well.
If he wants to kill Xia Jingshi,
I'm afraid...
Besides,
where would we even find him?
Why should I help you?
As long as you help me find him,
you can name your price.
I have no price to name,
and I don't have that ability.
Although you've lost
the strength to draw a bow,
you still have an archer's keen eyes
and experience.
Well, I'm flattered.
Yun Qing doesn't know
Xia Jingshi's exact time of arrival
in Yujing,
so he can only lie in wait
for Xia Jingshi to appear.
The most secure position to strike
would be near the city gate.
The terrain outside the city gate
is too open,
leaving Yun Qing nowhere to hide,
so he can only stay inside the gate.
What you need to do is simple:
just tell me
if you were to assassinate Xia Jingshi,
what position would you choose?
If it's really as simple as you say,
then why bother coming to me?
I'm sure there are
plenty of skilled archers
in your army as well.
You probably don't know that
Yun Qing is considered Susha's
most formidable archer.
Ordinary archers can't even imagine
how formidable he truly is.
Miss Yixiao,
you are
the greatest archer in the world.
Right now, only you can guess
what Yun Qing might be thinking.
I'm not nearly as skilled as you say.
It's not worth mentioning.
See how good he is with words?
When asking for help,
one should act like it.
Tell me, what are your conditions?
I can agree to three of them.
That's not what you said just now.
Fine.
Five it is.
"The entire Yujing City
is my territory.
Everything's under my control."
First Prince,
you're truly impressive, huh?
If you're really that impressive,
how come you can't even find someone
when you want to?
Leave some leeway in your dealings.
Don't push things too far,
and always leave yourself a way out.
Don't you agree?
What's wrong?
You look
quite reluctant, First Prince.
I've agreed to help you,
yet you didn't even say thank you.
Thank you.
That's more like it.
As for the first condition...
The guards at Miss Ling's residence
will be withdrawn.
Alright.
I haven't thought of the other four yet.
Let's leave those pending for now.
Give me the map of Yujing City.
What?
Afraid I'll sneak a look at
your secret maps?
Forget it if you won't share.
The maps are in my study.
Come with me.
Miss Yixiao.
Xia Jingshi and his party
set off from the post station
at the border early this morning.
They should arrive in Yujing
in no more than four hours.
This is the gate
where Xia Jingshi will enter the city.
[West Gate] [Post Station]
Then he'll follow this road
all the way to the post station.
What kind of bow does Yun Qing use?
He took a two-picul bow with him.
His archery skills are such that
within 100 paces, he never misses;
at 150 paces, he hits 6 or 7 out of 10;
and at 180 paces, 3 or 4 out of 10.
We've already sent people
to search along the route
from the city gate to the post station,
within a range of 100 to 150 paces
on either side,
but we still couldn't find Yun Qing.
Should we expand the search area?
There's no time left.
[West Gate] [Tea House]
How far is this position
from the city gate?
Just over 50 paces.
That's enough.
Are you suggesting
Yun Qing would choose a closer position?
He knew you would
try to stop him,
so he deliberately took
a two-picul bow.
But have you considered that
a two-picul bow is so large,
and bringing it to a crowded area
would make him too conspicuous?
With so many of you searching
and still not finding him,
it shows that he has
concealed his whereabouts
extremely well.
Yun Qing only took a two-picul bow
to deceive us,
to make us misjudge
his position.
There's an archery shop here.
[Archery Shop]
He must have bought
a new bow here.
When Yun Qing left,
he left his personal token.
This shows that after the assassination,
he doesn't want to implicate
the Feng Battalion,
so he surely wouldn't use
a Feng Battalion bow for the killing.
The bows from the archery shop
[Archery Shop]
may be crudely made
with a range of no more than 50 paces,
but for
a master archer,
50 paces is more than enough
for him to be confident
he can make a lethal shot.
Besides,
Yun Qing is ready
to die anyway.
He only wants to kill,
with no intention of escaping,
so he doesn't have to leave himself
a way out.
Officail Website : 📺 dramacool.club
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Therefore,
if it were me,
I would choose this tavern.
[Tavern]
Who are these people?
How dare they act on the street?
How bold of them!
Looks like they're from
the First Prince's Residence.
Indeed.
Did something happen?
Yun Qing!
[Susha Kingdom's Feng Battalion, Yun Qing]
Get down here now!
Yun Qing,
this is His Highness's military order!
Are you even refusing
to obey His Highness now?
Yun Qing.
Your name was given by His Highness,
your skills were taught by His Highness,
your position in the Feng Battalion
was arranged by His Highness,
and your life
was saved by His Highness
from among the refugees.
Have you forgotten all this?
I, Yun Qing, would never dare
forget Your Highness's great kindness.
Is what you did today
meant to force me
to collect your corpse myself?
Your Highness.
I only know
that in your heart, you would never agree
to the marriage alliance with Jinxiu.
I only wanted to kill Xia Jingshi
to ease Your Highness's burden.
Have you thought about the consequences?
You wanted to trade your life
for Xia Jingshi's life—
would I ever agree to that?
What is Xia Jingshi anyway?
Is his miserable life
worth trading yours for?
On the first day I brought you
into the Feng Battalion,
what was the military discipline
I ordered you to uphold?
Honor heaven above,
respect the earth below.
Be loyal to the ruler and the kingdom,
and never fail the people.
This isn't about being loyal to me,
Feng Suige,
nor is it about not failing me,
Feng Suige.
I taught you skills
so that one day
you could serve our kingdom—
not to repay me personally.
Do you understand?
I, Yun Qing,
will remember that.
Get back and report
before the camp is dismissed today.
Yes, Your Highness.
If you dare to be late,
you'll face military punishment.
Thank you
for your help today.
When will Xia Jingshi arrive in Yujing?
The officials of the Ministry of Rites
have gone to the city gate to welcome him.
He should arrive soon.
I just saw Lu Ke
preparing your military robe.
It seems
you're also going to the city tower.
Xia Jingshi
is not that important.
I'm only going
to support my sister.
I'll go with you.
What if there are others
who want to assassinate Xia Jingshi?
Take me with you,
so I can help you spot
if there are other assassins.
You just want to go see Xia Jingshi,
right?
Actually,
I'm quite curious too.
If Xia Jingshi sees you
and discovers that you're now
a concubine in my household,
how would he react?
So you agree?
[Yujing City]
Here they come. Stay alert!
It was you who rescued me
from the death camp.
From now on,
my life belongs to you.
[Uphold Virtue to Honor the Ancients]
I, Xiao Weiran—
I, Fu Yixiao—
I, Ning Fei—
[Nan]
From this day on, join the Zhennan Army
and swear loyalty unto death
to His Highness!
Those who kill the people of Jinxiu,
I shall devour their flesh
and drink their blood!
Those who slay even one soldier
of the Zhennan Army,
I shall execute without mercy!
Kill!
With this as my betrothal gift,
Heaven and earth as witness,
mountains and rivers as matchmakers,
I vow to stay by your side till death.
Would you be willing
to marry me in your bridal finery?
What's wrong?
I will share life and death
with Your Highness!
This is a military order!
Protect His Highness!
[Yujing City]
I am Shen Wu, Minister of Rites.
Prince of Zhennan, you've come from afar.
The journey must have been tiring.
Minister Shen, no need for
such formalities.
Prince of Zhennan,
please follow me to the carriage.
His Majesty is waiting for you.
The rest of you,
please follow the ceremonial officer
to the post station to rest.
I will accompany you, Prince of Zhennan,
into the palace to have an audience
with His Majesty first.
[Yujing City]
Prince of Zhennan, please.
Let's go.
Fu Yixiao.
Did something come back to you?
[Peace]
Stop thinking about it.
Loosen your grip,
will you?
Alright?
No one here will hurt you.
Loosen your grip first.
Do you remember who I am?
Half a smile,
half a sneer—
just like you.
Feng Suige.
Yes, it's me.
Bastard!
Don't push!
Such simple folk customs.
Simple folk customs indeed.
My husband and son
were both killed
by you Jinxiu people!
How dare you come to Yujing?
May you die a terrible death!
A terrible death!
You executioners!
[Palace of Susha Kingdom]
By order of our Emperor,
I have come to Susha
to marry Princess Xiyang.
Our Emperor
sincerely wishes
for lasting friendship
between our two kingdoms
and for the people to enjoy
a life of peace and stability.
In times of war,
it's always the common people who suffer.
I,
like the Emperor of Jinxiu,
wish for peace throughout the land.
Your Majesty, please rest assured.
Princess Xiyang and I
will do everything to maintain peace
between our two kingdoms.
I was worried
about Xiyang marrying into a foreign land,
but today,
seeing your fine character,
Prince of Zhennan,
I feel much more at ease.
In the future,
I hope you will treat each other
with respect
and live in harmony.
Your Majesty,
I've obtained permission from our Emperor
to return all Susha warriors
we captured
in the Battle of Pingling,
hoping our kingdoms will maintain
friendly relations for centuries
and lasting peace throughout the world.
It's thoughtful of you, Prince of Zhennan.
When the time comes,
all Jinxiu prisoners
will be handed over to you
and return with you to Jinxiu.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Now that the two kingdoms
have ceased hostilities and made peace,
Prince of Zhennan and Xiyang
deserve much credit.
This way please, Prince of Zhennan.
Your Majesty.
Please sit.
Bring some wine.
Your Majesty,
it's not yet noon,
not suitable for drinking.
I'm meeting my future son-in-law.
Doesn't that deserve a drink?
As you command.
Neither sitting nor bowing.
If you marry my daughter,
you'll be my junior.
You're a prince, and I'm an emperor.
There's a distinction
between ruler and subject.
Shouldn't you
bow to me?
Your Majesty,
let tea serve as my drink.
Are you trying to treat me as your equal?
When I marry the princess,
I'll observe the proper etiquette
between father and son-in-law.
Why not wait until the wine's served?
To express my sincerity,
whether it's tea or wine,
what difference does it make?
Try this.
How is it?
Princess Xiyang has a sweet tooth.
How do you know
these are Xiyang's favorite pastries?
Your Majesty is a man of great talent
and broad vision,
with the world in your heart.
Recommending such sweet pastries to me
certainly isn't because
you like them yourself.
I suppose
Your Majesty wants to test
if Princess Xiyang and I
have compatible tastes,
right?
Prince of Zhennan,
you're quite perceptive.
The pastries you just had
were created by Xiyang herself
when she was only seven years old.
Her mother said that as a princess,
she shouldn't be cooking herself
and should let the royal chefs handle it.
But Xiyang insisted
that these pastries
were meant for her family,
and she couldn't entrust them to others.
Therefore,
in this entire world,
only she and her two brothers,
myself, and the Empress have tasted them.
And now, you're the sixth.
It's truly enviable
to hear Your Majesty speak
so fondly of family matters.
I know that
although you and the Emperor of Jinxiu
are brothers, you're not close.
My children are different.
Though they were not born
of the same mother,
their bond as siblings
is deep and strong,
second to none.
That's wonderful.
And?
The marriage between you and Xiyang
was Xiyang's own choice.
I know that
others say Susha was defeated
and could only buy a few years of peace
by marrying off a princess.
They are wrong.
If it weren't for
Xiyang's affection for you,
I would never
trade my beloved daughter's
lifelong happiness
for a few years of peace in Susha.
What I mean is
I
will absolutely not allow Jinxiu
to fail Xiyang.
In this marriage,
what I want is my daughter's
happiness and well-being.
I
will not give you
any chance to disappoint Xiyang.
Your Majesty speaks wisely.
Kingdom affairs are kingdom affairs,
and family matters are family matters.
I won't confuse the two.
[Wutong Mansion]
Stop!
This is the First Prince's Residence.
No trespassing allowed!
Step aside.
I'm looking for Feng Suige.
Who do you think you are,
daring to call the First Prince
by his name?
Ning Fei from Jinxiu.
Get lost!
Is Fu Yixiao
here with you?
Get lost, get lost.
You...
Feng Suige!
Feng Suige, come out here!
[Wutong Mansion]
Feng Suige!
I know you're in there.
Why are you making so much noise?
Yixiao needs to rest.
Miss Ling,
it's me,
Ning Fei from Jinxiu.
I don't care who you are.
Stop making such a racket here.
Yixiao is ill and needs rest.
What's wrong with her?
If you're smart, you won't persist.
Her affairs are none of your business.
Just leave.
Yixiao isn't seeing anyone.
Take me to see her.
I'll just take a look at her
from a distance,
without disturbing her any further.
[Wutong Mansion]
-Take your hands off me.
-Who's being so noisy here?
Please step aside, Miss.
I don't want to hurt you.
Hand Yixiao over to me.
Do you want to die?
I'm talking to you!
[Wutong Mansion]
So this is Jinxiu's greatest warrior?
I haven't even said it was on.
[Wutong Mansion]
Greetings, Your Highness.
Mr. Ma,
I'd like a word with Prince of Zhennan.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Do you still remember me?
We've never met before,
so how could I remember you?
So you really don't remember.
Three years ago,
at the border between Jinxiu and Susha,
on the desert.
Prince of Zhennan, you should know that
my father is a warrior emperor
who founded our kingdom
through military might,
and my brother is the commander of
Susha's three armies,
so I can be considered
coming from a military family.
Given my background,
I also thought about achieving glory
on the battlefield
like my father and brother did.
It's not that I enjoy war.
I just believe
that as a princess,
I should do something
to serve our kingdom.
You don't have to go to war
to serve your kingdom.
You have your own duties as a princess.
What you just said
is exactly the same as
what my brother said back then.
Three years ago,
I wanted to follow my brother to battle,
but he wouldn't allow it.
But I was young and impetuous then,
and somehow found the courage
to secretly acquire a suit of armor.
I pulled some strings,
snuck into the army,
and followed the troops into battle.
My brother
started from the bottom level
and made military achievements
step by step
until he became commander.
I wanted to be like him.
But on the second day of the campaign,
I ran into trouble.
I had heard from my brother
that there was a shortcut
in the desert.
To catch up with my brother,
I slipped away from my attendants,
intending to take that shortcut.
Little did I know
I would be completely lost.
What was even more desperate
than my dire situation was
that I was discovered by the enemy.
It's a woman.
I don't kill women.
Let's go.
♪ Flying alone ♪
♪ With no need for direction ♪
♪ Flying up to the clouds ♪
♪ Yet the sun is hiding ♪
That water pouch saved my life.
♪ Roaming freely ♪
I survived for two more days,
♪ Unafraid of wind or frost ♪
until my brother
came to my rescue.
There was a name
carved on that water pouch:
♪ The wet wings ♪
Xia Jingshi.
♪ Will carry me far away ♪
Prince of Zhennan.
It was you who saved me that day,
and it was also you who spared my life.