[Would you like to join Spirit Fingers?]
♫ A heart that remains unchanged through time ♫
♫ Our eternal story that will last forever ♫
[This drama is fictional, and any similarity
with reality is purely coincidental.]
[Production guidelines were followed
when filming children and animals.]
I won't draw that giant creep.
[Episode 10]
He said Gi Jeong is a giant creep.
Kiddo, watch closely.
This is the kind of guy I am.
There he goes overacting again.
Just get started already.
Alright, alright. Let's draw quickly.
Start.
What?
Can we do couple poses?
U Dol...
Brother-in-law.
Of course, absolutely.
U Dol, what are you doing?
Just leave him be.
Focus on drawing faster!
This kid's impressive.
Isn't Red even more impressive
for picking a fight with a kid?
After giving birth to him,
my mom ate seaweed soup for weeks.
Oh, Mother!
Kiddo.
Things won't go your way.
Idiot.
Five minutes is a long time.
Just give up already.
No way, I'll definitely make you mine.
No, I'll make you my brother-in-law.
Time's up. Five minutes are over.
U Dol, get up quick.
Hey, Gi Jeong.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
You're not fine.
Are you okay?
This is nothing for me.
Right, kiddo?
Yeah.
I figured I could finally get a proper look here.
They cropped out all the faces in the mall photos.
If even a bit of his face shows, he goes crazy.
It actually works better for me that way.
Because his face isn't overexposed.
Oh, I told you to drop that idea.
He has absolutely zero interest in that world.
You know CEO Kye from Star &amp; Studio, right?
I do.
The legendary photographer
who makes anyone famous.
I begged him to take just one look
and finally got him here.
But...
You know J One? J One?
Hey, stay still.
The senior coming now
worked with J One before fame
and made him a top star.
You gotta impress him, okay?
Ugh, I don't care about that.
You said triple pay for today, right?
Keep your word.
Got it, man.
Darn, you are ridiculously handsome.
Senior, it's an honor to have you visit our place.
Man, I'm busy.
Is this the guy?
Where's the camera?
Ah, yes. Here it is.
What's with your face?
Why do you look so sour?
How about a smile?
Don't wanna.
What did you say?
If you want me to smile,
try making me laugh first.
Charming.
Now I want more.
Stop. Won't do it.
I begged for three years.
Thanks to this cute kid, today was fun.
Shall we take a group photo?
- Sure.
- Okay.
Let's go over there.
U Dol, wanna take one with me?
- Yeah.
- Pose like this...
Ah, done.
Sorry.
Four, three, two.
How was today? Did you have fun?
Well... it was okay, I guess.
It was fun, right?
Will you keep seeing that giant creep?
Huh?
I said we broke up.
U Dol, eat this.
Think I'm stupid?
I saw you holding hands earlier.
Five, four, three, two.
I'll say it again.
I hate that guy.
U Dol.
Even though the kid's still in grade school,
he's got this air that keeps you in check.
No wonder Baeblu gets flustered around him.
Gi Jeong handled him pretty well though.
'Handled well'? My foot.
He's just as mentally immature.
U Dol might actually be more mature.
Jeez.
Still, that kid was way too bold.
Even though he's a pathetic younger brother,
he nearly broke the precious spine
responsible for continuing the Nam family lineage.
That's not it.
I won't tell Mom.
I don't get it at all,
but maybe that guy has
some charm only you can see.
Huh?
He relaxed his body.
Then suddenly, he lifted his hips a little.
And he held himself up with his own strength.
He's really thoughtful.
Must take after U Yeon.
As expected, he's still
one step ahead of my brother.
Really?
He actually gave permission?
Yeah, I guess he learned something from it.
Good call bringing him along.
You did great holding out earlier too.
No.
U Dol was so light,
so it was like lifting a feather.
Or maybe your waist is just super strong?
Of course my core strength is amazing.
As expected, the man's back power is...
Hello?
Did we get disconnected?
Gi Jeong!
Huh?
Yeah.
What? I thought we got disconnected.
Why'd you stop talking?
Well.
It sounded too suggestive.
Suggestive?
Your... your comment about...
What did I say that was inappropriate?
I only mentioned your waist being really strong.
Well, that...
you know.
How's that...
I'm hanging up.
See you tomorrow.
Gi Jeong? Gi Jeong.
Wait.
What? Why...
But at our age,
should we really be discussing
PG-15 teenage romance?
Let's talk about adult relationships,
adult relationships.
Nothing? How about you guys?
You're at the perfect age for it.
Ugh, why are you asking us that?
What about you, Black?
Black's relationships aren't interesting.
They're boring yet she never stops dating.
What about her latest fling?
She already broke up.
How do you know?
Wait, are you two giving
each other dating advice now?
Jonathan.
Jonathan told me.
How does Jonathan know?
Wait, are you two that close?
No, it's not like that.
The more you talk, the deeper
the hole you dig, time to stop.
Long story short, he and Jonathan
found out. The end.
Ugh, enough! What's important here?
What matters is Black's relationship ended.
Why aren't you dating anyone?
Huh?
Why aren't you two dating?
I wonder that sometimes too.
Do you really
not have feelings for each other?
What about Seon Ho?
Have you ever felt anything for Geu Rin?
I have.
Sure have.
Pretty often, actually.
Oh my, what are you gonna do about that?
What about you, Geu Rin?
Ever felt a spark with Seon Ho?
He's annoying.
Why are you following me?
You seemed upset earlier.
You were awfully cheeky today.
I've got something to ask.
I don't wanna hear it.
Ms. Taeng Ja!
So Jonathan didn't tell you
why I broke up with that guy, huh?
Because he called you Ms. Taeng Ja.
You called me that even though you knew?
Taeng Ja.
What did you just call me...
How can I make you see me as a man?
Taeng Ja, what do I need to do
for you to see me as a man?
I!
I told you not to call me Taeng Ja!
What about you, Geu Rin?
Ever felt a spark with Seon Ho?
I'm home.
Why are you drinking alone?
Did you eat something wrong?
I got the rod of love.
Is that soju?
It's here! It's here! It's here!
Why do you like me?
Should I only say one reason?
No, list them all out.
It's your homework.
I'll check your answers in person.
Yes!
Oh my god!
Hey, that's really naughty.
So what's so naughty about it?
Are you saying that talking about
strong waist strength is a naughty thing?
No.
Jo Mi Rae, did you get heatstroke or something?
You just said it was naughty.
The one who felt the naughtiness
in that word is the naughty one.
Ah, Nam Gi Jeong, Nam Gi Jeong.
He's got that devil of lust deep in his heart!
Speak in a way I can understand.
In Earthling terms.
Did you guys kiss?
Not that peck from before, but a real kiss.
What are you talking about? That never happened.
Really?
Okay, let me put it in Earthling terms for you.
Nam Gi Jeong will soon
pounce on you.
You didn't stop reading smut, did you?
Why would I stop?
You should go pray or something.
The lust demon's all over you.
Hey, catch U Yeon.
He will pounce on U Yeon! Catch U Yeon.
The kissing technique to win her heart.
Do I really have to teach this with my mouth?
This is all the expertise I gained
through spending money and time.
Hey, Nam Gi Jeong.
You can really act dense when you want to, huh?
Please.
Please teach me.
Don't just mindlessly charge in.
Oh.
The most important thing
is her preference.
Her preference?
[Version 1]
U Yeon.
[Ask Permission]
Can I?
A girl who wants you to ask her
in a romantic way before kissing her.
Can I kiss you?
No.
Ugh, why would you ask something like that?
[Version 2: Pull Closer]
A girl who wants you to pull her in and kiss her.
Don't do that.
Like a real man, smack the wall!
[Version 3: Wall Slam]
No, don't do this.
[Version 4: Soulful Gaze]
A girl who wants you to gaze into her eyes
and naturally lean in for a kiss.
But U Yeon
wouldn't do any of these.
Ugh, hopeless kid.
He's getting lessons just because he can't kiss?
I didn't expect Nam Gi Jeong's
love life to be like this.
Hey, what book did he ask us to buy for him?
Can't remember even after hearing it 100 times.
'A book about how to read books properly'!
Wait,
didn't he buy and read that last time?
That was about reading books properly,
but this one's about how to read books
about reading books.
What kind of nonsense is that?
It's not about being possessed by lust demons.
I'm just chasing my dream.
Dreams?
I've chosen my path.
I'll become a romance novelist.
What?
You said not long ago that
you were going to become A&amp;R.
You said you wanted to create idols
like Legend with your own hands.
No, I think I'm more talented in this field.
And there's someone inspiring me these days too.
Other than Legend?
Yep.
- New face?
- Yeah.
Se Ra.
Hey, Oh Dae O.
What are you doing at a bookstore?
It's so unlike you.
Right back at you.
Oh Dae O, I can't find it. Let's just go.
- What's wrong?
- I didn't put on makeup today.
Did you come to buy a workbook?
Yeah.
Oh, dear.
Why today of all days?
Wait, how did he know I was talking about him?
We're looking for a book about how to read well.
Do you have any recommendations?
Bigfoot.
Hello.
- Yes.
- Hi, Bigfoot.
You said you left a pencil case
and croquis book here?
I left them in the Baeblu room.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
I've been distracted
because of my younger brother.
Oh, it's nothing.
Guests leave all sorts of things behind.
Bigfoot.
By the way, Jonathan, I'm curious about something.
You're a rocker, right?
Correct.
Wow.
Were you originally aiming to be a rocker?
That's right.
What's your dream, Baeblu?
I don't
have any particular dream yet.
There's nothing I'm exceptionally good at.
I don't know what to pursue.
Then consider what you enjoy doing.
Maybe that'll give you some direction.
I did think about that.
But I don't even know what I like.
A blank slate, huh?
Well, with a blank slate,
you can draw anything, right?
Blank slate?
Now that I think about it,
there's something I do like.
Does that mean Nam Gi Jeong becomes my dream?
Me too.
I didn't know
you thought of me like that.
No, that's not it...
What do you mean 'no'?
I heard everything.
That's not what I meant.
What are you going to do?
Take responsibility.
For what?
For you.
Yesterday, you shook me up
with suggestive comments.
And now you're messing with my heart,
so what are you going to do about it?
What 'suggestive comments' are you talking about?
Nam Gi Jeong will soon pounce on you.
First, figure out her preferences.
[Permission, Pull Closer, Wall Slam, Soulful Gaze]
Let's start with Option 3.
What?
Gi Jeong.
Oh, come on.
Stop that now.
There's also Option 4.
Stop saying such stupid things, please.
You can't do No. 1, No. 2, and No. 4 either!
What?
No, absolutely not.
I knew you'd say that.
But someday, we will kiss.
Of course, I want to do it right now, though.
I can't hear you.
If you really like someone,
kissing comes naturally.
I really like you too, but...
Okay, you don't need to explain.
I already knew this is how you are.
But I wanted to see
if you have other sides to you.
Other sides?
U Yeon.
How much do you think you know about me?
Huh?
The you I know isn't your entire self.
The me you know isn't all of me, right?
So, I guess that means liking someone
is about wanting to get to know
each other more and more.
Oh, my head.
You really make me think a lot.
Oh my gosh.
Is it too late to go to the study room?
No, it's not.
Looks like Se Ra and Mi Rae
are staying late at the bookstore too.
Oh, it's time to go.
Maybe I should start going to the study room too.
No.
Am I that embarrassing?
Oh, right!
It was jealousy, right?
It's not jealousy.
U Yeon.
I really can't handle studying.
But I'll never become someone who embarrasses you.
I'll start seriously thinking about my future too.
You said you'll become amazing?
Yeah, need to make it more specific.
Okay, let me know
when you figure it out. I'm leaving.
- Study hard.
- Yeah.
Gi Jeong.
Huh?
Can I...
Can I go see you work?
Huh?
I want to know more about you, is that okay?
Sure! Sure! Totally fine!
I'll make sure to pick a day when I look my best.
Alright, see you later.
Hey, be careful on your way.
Well, look who it is.
Aren't you neglecting your work?
Sorry, I had lots to do yesterday.
It's fine. I only had one beer yesterday.
Managed to walk home
on two feet instead of crawling.
Impressive.
People keep saying I'm acting weird.
Did I change too suddenly?
Do I look like I'm pretending?
- Absolutely not.
- Right?
Love changes people.
At the very least, I should avoid
worrying the person I like.
You know that's how I approach
relationships, right?
Even before...
Last time too, I went home early
because I didn't want you to worry.
So responsible.
Of course. See you later.
Geu Rin.
About Pink's question...
- Huh?
- What about you, Geu Rin?
Ever felt a spark with Seon Ho?
Go on, hurry.
Did you hear? Senior Heo Zero
is returning to school.
I heard. School life might
actually become interesting now.
He looks really cool when smoking.
Wow, I thought I was watching a photoshoot.
Didn't he date that freshman
from the stage design department?
Ah, Nam Geu Rin? Probably broke up.
- What?
- Really?
So that's why Eun Gi was crying his eyes out?
He cried?
Bawled his eyes out.
Hey, that's harsh.
You've ignored his words for three years,
but said yes to some girl you just met?
Hey, you're here.
Nam Gi Jeong, nice to meet you.
Ah, this is Manager Noh Ji Won
from SN Entertainment.
My junior from school.
I'm sure you're tired of hearing
compliments about your looks.
[Manager Noh Ji Won, SN Entertainment]
How should I persuade you...
Why did you change your mind?
You said you hated the attention and being busy.
Exactly.
Well...
I'm happy with how things are,
but if I can become better,
I should try.
He said he wants to get to know you better?
Huh?
Yeah, why?
That's a totally suggestive thing to say.
Why is that a suggestive thing to say?
The male lead in the novel I read yesterday
said that exact line before doing 'that' with her.
But you said that?
Oh man, why did you do that?
Doing 'that'?
Mi Rae, get a grip.
And please read clean fic instead of smut.
You shouldn't have access
to adult content. How'd you get it?
It's a secret.
Anyway, true love is R-rated apparently.
So, you're going to visit
where your boyfriend works?
Yeah, I've never seen Gi Jeong working before,
so I thought he might be upset.
Also, I thought there might be
sides of Gi Jeong I don't know.
Oh, already checking for cheating?
No, that's not it...
Gi Jeong's here.
He said he's late for work,
just came to see me quickly.
Fix Jo Mi Rae.
See you at the study room.
Not sure if she can be fixed.
Let's go.
Oh, right.
I had somewhere to go.
I need to get my act together.
Suddenly?
Yeah, I'll stop by there with you, I guess.
No, it's fine.
I'll go alone.
You're the top student. You should study.
See you later.
So handsome.
Even candid shots of my boyfriend
look like magazine spreads.
He's so handsome.
Gi Jeong.
U Yeon. Hey, don't run, you'll fall.
Huh?
Why are you here so fast?
Just wanted to see you sooner.
We're such a pair of fools, right?
No.
I'll be the only fool here. Just me.
You can't be a fool, it'll ruin your studies.
Your dream is to get into college, right?
Oh, wait.
Did you say I'm your dream?
No, I didn't.
Let's go together, Miss Piggy.
I'm home.
Song U Yeon, stop!
Hey, take this trash out first.
Why? Hurry up.
Mom, why do I always get these chores?
Anyone could do this, it's not just you.
- Hurry up.
- Fine.
Anyone can take out trash, why always me?
What's up with you again?
You apologized last time,
and now pulled this again.
It wasn't a one-sided apology.
I apologized for disrespecting you.
I thought you would apologize too if I went first.
Why would I apologize to you?
You always argue back at the end of everything.
Why are you acting like this?
You weren't like this before!
Because I used to be a coward!
I did what you said, even if I didn't like it,
because I was afraid you'd hate me.
Now I'm not scared anymore!
I don't care if you hate me.
I hate it when you play favorites!
What?
Ugh, fine. I'll do it myself.
It's either you or me. Who else would do it?
I wouldn't ask if I weren't busy.
I'll take it out.
U Seok.
No, U Seok. Don't get your hands dirty.
Let go. I'll take care of it.
I was going to get some fresh air.
Feeling relieved now?
Does it feel good making your brother
do it after two months?
I can't take this anymore.
[Gi Jeong: Did you get home safe?]
[Sorry I couldn't walk you home because of work.]
[Almost died worrying.]
[Almost died.]
Officail Website : kissasian.be  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
How many times will you type that?
[Don't worry, got home perfectly fine.]
[Glad to hear. Thanks.]
[What's there to thank?]
[Just grateful you are here.]
[Here we go again. Stop saying that.]
[Talk later. Eun Gi's calling me.]
[Okay, work hard.]
Gi Jeong, you know what?
Sometimes,
I used to find comfort in dark rooms.
I don't have to see the blurry floor
because of tears.
But these days, it's different.
Whenever the floor starts to get blurry,
someone mysteriously appears to wipe my tears.
You see,
I'll become an amazing man.
No need to stress about it now.
I just feel destined for greatness, you know?
Such reckless confidence
strangely calmed me down.
Is it some kind of spell?
Whatever it is,
I'll always believe you.
And I
keep liking you more.
But
sometimes
you feel too good to be true.
I just like you.
I'm behind you.
You're special to me.
You are super duper extra special to me.
You
should like me back.
To someone like me,
you're something that could never happen.
So sometimes,
I can't help but feel afraid,
that one day,
I'll wake up and you'll be gone.
Ugh, kill me now.
Here I go again.
But Koo Seon Ho,
I'm not ready to answer you yet.
I'm truly sorry.
Why?
It's because it's not easy for me.
Seon Ho.
You've started
avoiding me again, huh?
Avoiding you? What are you talking about?
Hey, did I do something wrong to you?
Why are you like this?
Is it the first time I've avoided you?
This is the second time.
The first time was when I confessed,
and the second time is
after what happened last time.
Have you really never felt
your heart flutter for me?
Is your 'Acaprio'
still blonde?
No.
Got it!
What's the big deal?
Never felt a flutter?
Hey... Who is this?
I missed you.
Rin Rin.
I'm back.
Koo Seon Ho,
how have you been?
You two are still close, huh?
Take your hands off her, senior.
Huh?
Your hands.
Hands?
Rin Rin!
Does it have to be like this?
Nam Gi Jeong would call U Yeon
beautiful even if she looked homeless.
That's Nam Gi Jeong. The real problem
is the people around him.
- Group model shoot today, right?
- Yeah.
They might even compare you to them.
You need at least a little protection.
I'm not sure if that's right.
Ah, the lens.
You prepared the mystic teal color I requested?
No.
Can't be helped.
This is my favorite dress. Be careful wearing it.
Thanks.
Okay, don't forget the live chat update.
Yeah, see you at the study room later.
Okay.
Should we catch a movie after so long?
You came with Song this morning, huh?
Ah, she slept over at my place.
I think she had something
going on with her mom again.
Song always runs to you
when that happens, doesn't she?
- Huh?
- Well...
I'm not exactly the most helpful friend.
That's not true.
Song felt bad that I've been
sleeping alone these days.
Let's watch movies another time.
I have loads of homework.
Let's go.
Wait.
This wasn't the original plan, right?
It's my decision.
You did whatever you wanted too, right?
No, seriously.
This isn't okay.
Can you iron and hang that properly?
I didn't even tell you to wear it,
but why are you freaking out?
Fine, then I'll wear it too.
No need. You have your own outfit.
No, I don't want that.
Then I'll wear the same thing.
I don't want that too. This is my studio.
Are you the boss here?
I'll do as I please, okay? Stop it.
Come on. Just hear me out once.
Why is Gi Jeong acting like that?
Group shoot today.
He called Miss Piggy accordingly.
And?
The outfits changed.
- Gi Jeong's clothes?
- No, the models'.
How?
I think it's here?
She's a model?
Mi Rae was right.
It makes me feel intimidated.
No.
I'm me and she's her.
If Gi Jeong saw this, he would lecture me again.
Yo.
Hello.
U Yeon! Why are you here already?
Go, go. Come back later.
You told me to come straight after school.
Anyway, you can't be here now.
- Should we call in the model?
- Do it.
- Let's go.
- Gi Jeong. Shoot's starting.
Models, please come out.
Hey, darn it!
U Yeon, stop watching.
Just look at me.
Are you okay?
Even your hiccups are cute.
Ah, nice.
Keep the wild energy till the end.
Push through to the finish.
Tension, tension!
Three, two.
- Great.
- U Yeon.
Sit here.
Don't look there.
Don't turn around
until I come out.
This place is full of wolves,
and pretty girls like you are in danger.
Stay like that, okay.
It came out great.
Can you hold their pants for a second?
- Dae O.
- Yeah?
Tell that traitor to get ready.
Say he's up next.
Hey, you heard him, right?
Okay, please go.
Ah, this is making me anxious, seriously.
Come quickly.
Why'd you dress up so nicely again today?
- Don't look back, got it?
- Okay, okay.
Please wait a moment.
My friend's embarrassing. I'll apologize for him.
Me too.
This situation is...
Like 'comrades in misery'?
'Shared suffering.'
Okay!
Ah, nice.
Cut.
Now prepare for the next outfit.
Tell Gi Jeong to come.
Gi Jeong!
Why am I so nervous?
You got this.
Keep your eyes on me.
Okay, strike a pose.
Cue.
Set the mood.
Good.
I've never seen him so serious before.
Different from how he is at SF.
Right, turn slightly.
Half-step back, okay.
Perfect.
Even just dressing him up
brings out something in him.
Let's keep going.
Great, good.
Excellent.
Like you're looking at something comfortably.
♫ You make me understand ♫
♫ You make me find myself ♫
♫ 'Cause you're a star ♫
Crazy...
I actually fell for that act back then.
Rin Rin.
It's hot. Let's talk inside.
Want me to break your arm?
You are
really mad at me.
I've been reflecting hard.
Leaving like that.
Cut me some slack.
To be precise,
you didn't leave, but I dumped you.
Did you?
Right. We're nothing now.
Stop acting like this.
I came back because of you.
I thought about you a lot.
You're the only one I could think of.
Your acting's improved. I admit it.
But your act doesn't work on me anymore.
So get lost.
Since when
did you and Seon Ho become so close?
Were you lonely without me?
See you around, Rin Rin.
Why wait outside? You should've stayed in.
Huh?
Ah, it's too crowded inside.
It was a bit crowded today.
How was it?
I was the only one you had eyes for, right?
Yeah.
Let's go. I'll buy you something tasty.
Wait.
I think
I need to head home early today.
What?
You never mentioned that.
I forgot about tomorrow's pop quiz. Sorry.
Oh, really?
Can't be helped, I guess.
I'll walk you home.
No.
I have to meet my mom.
Huh?
She wants to visit the department store.
Your mom?
I should get going.
Thanks for inviting me today.
I'll text you.
What's this? Weren't you
all excited to go out on your date?
She says she forgot she has a pop quiz tomorrow.
What? A pop quiz?
Do they still do those nowadays?
Guess her school still does.
But why did you let her leave alone?
She had plans with her mom.
'Is she a kid?'
'What's with the pop quiz?'
[Is she a kid? What's with the pop quiz?]
Jo Mi Ryo said this.
Welcome.
You could've taken your time with the homework.
I finished it all.
Really?
Sit down.
Tell me.
The reason I like you...
I was just drawn to you.
I thought there'd be some grand reason.
Because you're bold and honest.
With anyone, anywhere.
I like how you don't worry about others
and stay focused on yourself.
Yeah?
What if I'm different outside SF?
- Huh?
- Would you still feel the same?
What if I were a timid mess
who can't even make eye contact?
What if I'm someone who always
blames myself for everything?
That's impossible.
Right, it couldn't be.
But I'm also not the woman you imagine.
Meaning, I'm a fantasy you built.
A version of me that only exists inside SF.
- That's not true.
- Yes, it is.
Hyuk.
If the me you like is your fantasy,
then don't try to get it through
someone else, make it yours.
If I pretend to fall
for your flirting here just for fun,
I become a witch seducing an innocent boy.
I'm not that irresponsible with my life.
What's with that look?
If that look means you understood
nothing and like me even more,
I'll kill you.
Where are you?
You have class.
- I'll skip it. Let's hang out.
- Are you a kid?
Why?
Let's get something tasty, okay?
Ah, tasty food!
Let's go!
Not eating?
Then I will.
Ah, that's petty.
I'm stressed.
Heo Zero.
Oh, jeez.
I was finally forgetting everything,
and then he shows up and messes me up again.
Messes you up?
Huh?
Did he stir your feelings?
No, that's not what I meant.
Why the sigh?
It doesn't bother you, right?
It does.
Seon Ho.
Is it normal to not care
when my girlfriend's ex keeps hovering?
Koo Seon Ho.
This is driving me crazy.
Wait a second.
Koo Seon Ho.
Why care about Heo Zero?
You think I'd waver because of him?
That's insulting.
Nam Geu Rin.
Which one did you just tell that you're stressed
because your ex keeps bothering you?
Male friend Koo Seon Ho? Or...
Boyfriend Koo Seon Ho?
Are you dating me, or are you playing pretend?
Think seriously again.
Gi Jeong was shining.
Brighter than anyone else there.
He didn't even have to try,
but it came naturally to him.
People who effortlessly have it all.
Born with everything from the start.
And me, who believed every word
those people said.
All the things Gi Jeong told me.
Words sweeter
than 'I like you.'
Words that reassured me
are now
turning into lies that come back
to hurt me.
When you fall for someone,
you end up discovering yourself,
not them.
Hidden parts of my heart.
The raw truth
about me.
What should I do, Gi Jeong?
I'm...
I'm starting to hate you.
Delulu
has returned.
Am I that embarrassing to you?
I wish you'd stop acting so confidently.
If you hate it, I'll quit. It's not a big deal.
If you betray our Song, I'll skin you alive...
I've got my own problems right now.
Those two walked in like Moses
parting the Red Sea.
All of this is because of Acaprio.
Then we should crush that punk.
You acted all high and mighty in front of me,
and this is all you're capable of, lying?
Don't you hate my mom?
All parents are like that.
They're just worried about you.
I don't hate your mom, but she scares me.
I'm thinking of breaking up with Gi Jeong.
So tell me.
Tae Seon, you're the one among us
who thinks the most.
Hey, does thinking always hurt this much?
Darn it!
These darn thoughts!
How do I get them out of my head?
Then stop thinking!
Darn it.
I can't. They keep coming!
You little punk!
Since when did you become such a deep thinker?
You're barely Homo erectus,
trying to act like Homo sapiens.
That's why your head's exploding!