ADAPTED FROM THE NOVEL
HIDDEN LOVE BY ZHU YI
Your girlfriend made this breakfast.
You must finish it all!
IMPROVING IMAGE QUALITY,
PLEASE HOLD YOUR DEVICE STEADY
Zhizhi's travel plan.
TRAVEL PLAN
CAMPING CHECKLIST
BEAUTIFUL COUNTRYSIDE
YOUNG GIRLS' FAVORITE TRAVEL PLANS
HIGHLY-RATED FIVE-STAR HOTELS
Go back to sleep.
Hello, your takeout is here.
I…
I didn't order any takeout. Sorry.
Mr. Duan Jiaxu ordered it for you.
Please give it to me. Thank you.
Remember to give a good review.
A good review?
I ordered supper for you.
DUAN JIAXU
TAP TO TAKE A PHOTO,
LONG PRESS TO RECORD A VIDEO
I have the same.
I'll eat with you.
DUAN JIAXU
I'll give you
a good review.
SANG ZHI
Listen, enjoy your meal.
I want you to focus when you work.
-All right.
-Okay.
-No problem.
-Definitely.
Xiaowan and Sang Zhi
are the smartest and most capable interns
that I've had in the past few years.
So who is smart and who is capable?
-Tell us.
-Xiaowan is smart. Sang Zhi is capable.
Of all my mentors,
you've doted on me the most.
I like the way you talk.
Well,
I prepared some small gifts for everyone.
Thank you for your help
over the past month.
-Pick out what you like.
-You're so thoughtful.
Mr. Zhang.
What are you guys doing here?
Do I get one too?
Mr. Zhang, today is the interns' last day.
How about a few words?
I do have to say something then.
Lately, your performances
have been really impressive.
If you want to work in Yihe,
come to me.
I'll recommend you for a suitable post.
Or I can write a recommendation letter.
Also, one last thing.
Gold shines wherever it is.
Bling bling.
-Go back to eating.
-Thank Mr. Zhang.
-Say it.
-Thank you, Mr. Zhang.
All right. Get back to eating.
If it's not enough, buy more on me.
-Okay!
-Hail, Mr. Zhang!
Very good.
SERVERS
NUMBER OF USERS ONLINE
We did it!
Yes!
Jiaxu!
Our hard work paid off.
Listen up, guys.
As of now,
the recent performance data
has exceeded our projected targets
by a large margin.
As you can see,
the current number is still increasing.
This is the best version we have had
in more than two years.
Let's give ourselves a round of applause!
Thank you,
colleagues of A Dream of Jianghu,
for your hard work throughout this year.
For this great masterpiece,
I can't even count how many late nights
and extra hours you've worked.
Today, our game is officially launched!
It's worth celebrating!
Let's raise our cups.
Cheers!
-Cheers!
Bonus!
I didn't catch that.
We've prepared food. Help yourselves.
Okay, Li Xun.
You have to get the last word in.
Xiaoyu,
today is my last day of interning.
This is a gift for you.
Thank you for your help.
When I first started working here,
I was clumsy and careless.
Over the past month,
I've really learned a lot.
There's one more thing.
I never stole anyone's boyfriend.
You know Jiang Ying, right?
If you are good friends with her,
you can accompany her
to see a psychologist.
I think it will be helpful
for her.
You'll also learn
about the actual situation.
Thank you.
It's white.
You've worked hard, Li Xun.
You too, Siyun.
Xiaoduan, I have to thank you
for your persistence
on the Celestial Progression System.
It's not just my accomplishment.
It's mainly the result
of everyone's concerted efforts
and hard work.
Previously,
all I needed to do
was follow your arrangements
and work accordingly.
I didn't have to consider anything else.
But this experience made me realize
that coordinating the work
of so many people
is quite challenging.
You did very well though.
Anyway,
I still want to thank you and Li Xun
for giving me this chance.
He has grown up.
Do you know what his greatest virtue is?
His modesty.
Now you trust my judgment, don't you?
I brought such talent back to Yihe.
Xiaoduan.
We have something to tell you too.
As you know,
our former chief programmer left
and his position has remained vacant.
Li Xun and I
have been discussing this lately.
We want to recommend you
for this position in our company.
We still need to apply with headquarters.
Do you think you're up for it?
But my qualifications…
Qualifications don't represent
one's capabilities.
We both believe in you.
However, it's not finalized yet.
We have to wait for approval
from headquarters.
Anyway,
I don't think it will be an issue.
Wait for our good news.
Okay.
In that case, thank you in advance.
No need to thank us.
You've been busy for so long.
Do you have any plans after this?
I plan
to make it up to my girlfriend.
I want to take her on a trip.
That's a great idea.
Do you want me to give you some ideas?
Don't give him any lousy ideas.
They're young people in love.
Your old-fashioned ideas
won't be helpful.
Wait, does age matter in love?
What?
Yes, it does.
I'll leave you two lovebirds to it.
To pamper your girl,
just buy the best for her.
It's the Dream Castle.
But I played this when I was a kid.
That's fine.
They also have
the biggest carousel in Yihe.
It will make me dizzy.
If you find these rides too boring,
they also have…
There are more thrilling rides.
I'll get scared.
Then have a look at this hotel.
I found it online.
It has a very high rating.
All guests gave positive feedback.
Many of them return.
Most importantly,
it's very close to the amusement park.
Whenever you feel tired,
we can go back to the hotel to rest.
I won't get tired.
In this case, staying in this hotel
would be a waste.
So do you dislike
this amusement park
or this hotel?
I don't like either one.
Actually,
it's not that I find camping a bad idea.
My main concern is that
a campsite usually has many insects
and maybe even venomous snakes.
I'm more worried
about how you will wash up there.
Moreover,
if it suddenly starts raining there,
there won't be any shelter.
I don't want you to have a hard time.
Then have you considered this?
If we go to the places you've planned,
we have to pay for the fuel to get there.
When we get there,
we have to buy amusement park tickets.
Food and drinks in the park
will cost money too.
And just now, you showed me
some package for two.
It…
It doesn't have much to offer.
Why is it so expensive?
Then there's this hotel.
I don't think it's even necessary.
We just moved into this new flat.
If we spend money on these things,
then…
So it's not that you dislike those places.
You don't want me to waste money.
That's not true.
I…
I never wanted to go.
I just want to go camping.
Why can't we just go?
I've already planned it.
Look at all these things I've prepared.
Mosquito repellent,
ambiance lights, napkins,
wet wipes, trash bags,
cards, board games, flowers,
baskets, and a bubble blower.
I have everything we might need ready.
So why can't we go?
You're so thoroughly prepared.
It's my first time camping.
Of course I need to cover all my bases.
It's best to be prepared.
Imagine this.
We'll bring all these items with us.
We can set up the tent together
and put up camp chairs and a table.
Then we'll sit there.
It will feel great, won't it?
We'll listen to the sound of the waves
and enjoy the sea breeze.
We'll wait for the sunset
and watch the sunrise.
At night,
there will be many stars filling the sky.
The most important thing is that
it will be just the two of us.
If we go to the amusement park,
it will be noisy.
But if we go camping,
it will be just the two of us.
I think
it will be very romantic.
What you just said
does sound tempting.
Then beach camping it is!
-We'll do that.
-Really?
Tomorrow morning at seven,
we will set out together.
I'll get up at six to pack.
-No, five.
-What?
I'll wake you up at four.
Seven? That early?
Is it early?
I don't even plan to sleep tonight!
I'll check if I missed anything.
This…
CHAPTER 22, RESPLENDENT
SEE THE STARS WITH YOU
Our first travel plan
is ruined just like this.
We need to speed up
because the light
indicates that it's getting late.
It will be dangerous at night.
Let's hurry.
-Then let's get started.
-Okay.
Here.
That's it.
Why is it stuck?
We'll screw from beneath. Right?
The screw.
Pull me.
I'm going to answer my phone.
Who is calling?
My mom.
Get out. I'm going inside.
Hurry. Get out.
I'll be inside.
Get out.
Zhizhi.
Mom.
Where are you?
I'm at…
Well, see for yourself.
Why does it look like
you're in a tent?
Bingo!
I'm camping.
It's so comfortable.
Are you camping?
Dear!
-Have some fruit.
-Hurry.
-Your dad is here.
-Where is she?
Look. She's in a tent.
Zhizhi, where are you camping?
I am…
at my friend's flat.
Did you set up a tent inside?
We were supposed to go camping
by the beach today.
But it's raining,
so we're camping at home.
It's also fun.
Show me around.
Your dad and I want
to take time to go camping.
That's right.
Show you around? Do you want me to?
I'll flip the camera, okay?
I'm doing it now.
Can you see?
Look.
Look. Out there, it's…
It's raining.
Can you see it?
Look.
It's raining.
This is the tent.
This is
the tent we set up.
Over here is the dining room.
Can you see it?
That is
the kitchen.
This is the kitchen.
Right over here.
The bedrooms are over there.
That's all.
And then…
-What happened?
I'm fine.
I…
I accidentally tripped
over some equipment.
Be careful.
Are you sure it was the equipment
instead of a dog?
Sang Yan, I wasn't talking to you,
so don't speak.
Don't be mean.
Zhizhi.
You camping inside
reminds me of when I was a child
and set up tents in the living room.
It felt so safe.
Isn't it fun?
Yes, it's fun.
If you also want to have fun,
you can
set one up in the garden.
Zhizhi.
If you want
to do another internship next summer,
come back to Nanwu.
Your mom
misses you
and talks about you all the time.
She can't even sleep well.
Come back home.
Zhizhi.
Come home after you graduate, okay?
So you can be closer to me.
I'll think about it
when I graduate.
It's still too early.
You should get back
to what you were doing.
We're going to finish setting up the tent.
Okay, go have fun.
Enjoy yourselves.
Bye.
Did you hit yourself?
I'm fine.
Let's continue.
Okay.
Come on.
It's still standing.
You've improved.
It's your turn now.
It's a little too easy.
I'm pulling it.
That was fast.
This one.
How about this one?
Just listen to me, okay?
Yes.
Pick a punishment.
Let me shuffle these.
This one.
I'm doing pretty well.
SEPTEMBER 1ST, SATURDAY
WE LISTENED TO THE SOUND OF WAVES,
FELT THE SEA BREEZE,
WATCHED THE SUNSET,
AND WAITED FOR THE SUNRISE.
BUT MOST IMPORTANTLY,
IT WAS ROMANTIC
WITH JUST THE TWO OF US.
Look.
This one.
Ladies,
did you see the campus announcement?
-What?
-Yihe University Design Competition.
I didn't see it. Did you?
What do you think?
I think it's legit.
It's highly worthwhile this year.
Many companies are involved.
That's right.
Are you interested?
I want
to gain some competition experience.
I don't care if I can get shortlisted
or win a prize.
-It doesn't matter.
-That's right.
But after we graduate,
it will beef up our resumes.
That's what I think too.
Sangsang, I'm so impressed with you.
How do you balance life so easily?
You have love and a career.
Sangsang isn't like you,
a simple love creature.
Me? I'm not like that.
Then…
Are you…
Of course I'm taking part.
I came to tell you guys about it.
Ning Wei,
you…
Forget it.
Wangwang, will you be participating?
I…
I won't.
I'll wait until next year.
That's fine too.
It's just the two of us.
-Sign up.
-Hurry.
-Is it on the official site?
Yes, we sign up on the school's website.
Wangwang.
Why did you want to see me?
I have something to give you.
-Here.
-What's this?
It's an edited version of your interview.
Thank you. I'll watch it.
It's nothing.
By the way,
did you submit your assignment?
Thank you for accepting my interview.
Well, if you don't mind,
I'm going back to training.
Can you wait a minute?
I have something else to tell you.
Actually,
I like you.
Ever since our first meeting
when you helped me out,
I've had feelings for you.
As we spent more time together,
I began to like you more and more.
I…
You don't have to rush to answer me.
I just want to tell you how I feel.
I admire you a lot
and really like you.
So don't feel pressured.
We will still be good friends.
Right?
That's all.
I'll go now.
Okay.
I confessed my feelings.
It's not so hard after all.
What's wrong, Sangsang?
There are too many themes
that I want to do.
I still haven't picked one yet.
It's okay. Take your time to think.
You can look through other materials,
books, and whatnot for inspiration.
What about you?
Me?
I'm working on The Century's Star Wars.
That's so cool.
Not bad, right?
I've been planning it for a long time.
It's a prequel story for the game
that I want to design in the future.
I'm quite confident about it.
That sounds great.
I'll get back to brainstorming.
If you don't have any ideas,
don't try to force it.
We still have time.
Go home and relax
for the National Day holiday.
Maybe inspiration will come then.
Get back to your idea.
I'm already in the car.
I remember someone said
that he would not pick me up.
He also said
that he didn't want to see me.
Ask Duan Jiaxu
what is wrong with him.
Why?
This morning, he called me
three consecutive times.
I silenced my phone,
but he ordered takeout for me.
Do you know what was written on it?
He added a note that said,
"My boyfriend is in poor health.
Please make sure he gets up to eat
or the consequences will be dire.
Thank you."
I was speechless.
Maybe he just wanted you to get up
and have breakfast.
It's healthy for you.
That had better be the case.
But I can understand his concern.
He was just worried
that no one would pick his girlfriend up.
If he's so worried about you,
why did he trouble me
instead of coming with you?
He's very busy.
Otherwise, he would've come with me.
Listen, I want you to text him and say,
"Just you wait."
Why?
What are you going to do?
I'll beat him up.
I'm driving here.
Stay still, will you?
Nuisance.
Shoot. I'm dead meat.
What's wrong?
I can't believe I forgot about this.
-What is it?
-Get me directions.
Your crispy taro-crusted duck!
I forgot to buy it.
I thought it was important.
Pull up directions for me now.
I don't have to eat it today.
No way! Mom will scold me again!
Get directions for me. We'll buy it now.
Take me home first.
Then you can go and buy it.
You've been fussing
with your camera for two days.
Do you know how to use it?
I need to get the hang of it.
When Zhizhi is back, I'll take you two out
and take beautiful pictures.
Come on, dear. Look at me.
One, two, three.
Beautiful.
Try another pose.
Another pose?
Okay. One, two, three.
Gorgeous.
-How about this?
-Okay.
You showed up out of nowhere!
You startled me!
I just wanted to give you a surprise.
Dad, did you get a new camera?
-Yes. How about a triple shot?
-He just bought it.
-Okay.
-All right.
-One.
-Okay. One.
Okay, two.
Give me a different pose.
Okay.
And another one.
I'm so blessed.
My beautiful ladies.
Where's your brother?
He said he was going
to buy the crispy taro-crusted duck.
I said to buy it before fetching you.
He just never listens.
You need to talk to him.
-He's so careless.
-I will.
-I'll go change my shoes.
-Okay.
Come down for dinner afterward, okay?
Hello?
What are you doing?
I'm missing you.
I miss you too.
Have you eaten?
Not yet.
What about you?
Neither have I.
When are you going to eat?
Not until I finish up some work.
Zhizhi.
I'll call you back later.
Okay.
-I brought you some fruit.
-Okay.
-Thank you, Mom.
-It's nothing.
I'll call you when it's time for dinner.
Sorry, my mom suddenly came in.
SANG ZHI
It's okay.
Spend more time with your parents.
After I finish my work,
I'll fly over to see you.
Wait for me.
DUAN JIAXU
SANG ZHI
Sorry, little fox.
I've locked you up for so long.
I HAVE A SECRET
I SEEM TO HAVE FALLEN FOR HIM
DUAN JIAXU
JIAXU, HAPPY NEW YEAR
MAKE A LOT OF MONEY
AND HELP HIM PAY OFF HIS DEBTS
MY DREAM
Duan Jiaxu.
I am really
in a relationship with you.
Is Zhizhi dating someone?
Who is the guy?
How old is he?
Is he a classmate?
Calm down.
I'm not sure either.
What if it's not her boyfriend?
He sounds like a suspicious guy.
We need to find out about it.
Let's go and ask her.
Let's go.
Do you think it's okay, dear?
Yes, it's okay. Just come.
I'm coming.
Zhizhi.
Your mom and I
have something to ask you.
Okay.
Take a seat then.
What's up?
Zhizhi, be honest with me.
Are you dating someone?
Come on.
If you're dating someone,
why didn't you tell me?
I called you every day.
I wanted to tell you.
But I wanted
to tell you in person.
So she's dating.
Well, Zhizhi.
Your…
Your boyfriend, right?
How old is he? Where did you meet?
Is he a student?
Or did you meet him outside of campus?
How is his character?
Where does he study?
What is his major?
Zhizhi, you see,
I think you're still too young.
How about you wait until you've graduated?
If you're in a relationship now,
when you graduate,
you'll have to settle down there.
Have you ever considered this?
Will your boyfriend come back
to Nanwu with you?
-Am I right?
-Yes.
The main issue is that you're too young.
You haven't graduated.
Why don't you wait until--
I'll go check if Sang Yan is back.
Sang Yan.
So who is she dating?
Calm down.
She's very tight-lipped.
I don't know who she is dating either.
You rushed into talking to her.
You've scared her.
How could she be open with us?
You have a point.
But anyway, we must keep an eye on her
when it comes to dating.
How?
She's out of town.
Everyone says that bugs
are also a part of the gaming experience.
But we've tested it many times.
Why are there still so many strange bugs?
Seriously.
I'm leaving now.
During the holiday,
I'll be counting on you guys.
If you encounter
any unresolved or unfamiliar bugs,
ask Zhang Sen for help.
Okay.
-Xiaobai.
-Yes.
While I'm away, I'll have to trouble you.
Email me everyone's daily tasks
and issues that you encounter.
If there are any issues you can't solve,
just contact me at any time.
You can count on me.
Thank you, guys.
Don't worry, Jiaxu.
For the next few days,
focus on being with your girlfriend.
We promise not to contact you.
-Right?
-Yes.
-That would be best.
Of course.
-Bye.
Wait, Jiaxu!
There's another error.
Bye.
Come in.
Sang Yan.
What do you want?
Are you playing a game?
Yes, and I'm losing.
But you're so smart. How could you lose?
All right. What is it?
You must be tired.
That's usually how gaming is.
It's exhausting.
Your shoulders must be aching.
Your hands as well, right?
What are you up to?
You look like you're ready.
Are you going out?
It's none of your business.
Are you going out for dinner?
What will you have?
Is it delicious?
Who are you going with?
Duan Jiaxu will be there. He will.
So do you want to come along
because Duan Jiaxu is going?
I'm quite understanding, right?
Mom!
You…
What's your problem?
I'll tell Mom not to make you dinner.
What the heck?
I'll go get ready then.
Okay, you have two minutes.
Three minutes.
Three minutes at most.
You're so slow.
Fine, five minutes!
I'll wait for you downstairs.
Sunshine, rainbow, and white horse
Can you tone it down a little?
You're smiling like a fool.
Sang Yan, please focus on driving.
Don't mind me, okay?
I don't understand
what is going on in Duan Jiaxu's head.
We're eating with a bunch of guys,
but he insists on taking you along.
You won't take me out to dinner.
He won't either.
What's wrong with taking me to dinner?
Well, won't you feel awkward eating
with people you don't know?
No.
People always say
others will feel awkward
if I don't.
You're right. I'm the one feeling awkward.
That's great.
In my senior year of university,
I remember you pretentiously said,
"I want to help you move into the new dorm
or I will feel really bad."
You insisted on going.
Now I finally understand.
Keep pretending!
I don't remember that.
There was one time
when our parents weren't home.
You insisted on joining us for a hot pot.
Duan Jiaxu and I even went
to buy menstrual pads for you.
I didn't insist on going at that time.
-You--
-That time--
It was you who insisted.
No, you insisted on taking me
to eat hot pot.
No, you wanted to go that time!
-I didn't!
-You did!
Do you think it's appropriate for you
to discuss pads with me?
Focus on driving and stop talking, okay?
When you were little,
you called him your brother.
You sounded closer to him than to me.
You just don't love me at all.
I was being polite.
I was being respectful. Understand?
Why weren't you polite
and respectful to me?
I love you.
Are you sleepy?
I'll get the sleeping bag ready.
Come on.
Let's go to sleep.
Which one do you want to sleep in?
This one.
I'll turn off the light.
Good night.
During the National Day holiday,
I'll go back to Nanwu with you.
Will you?
I know you miss home.