You...
Are you leaving?
Do you want me to stay?
You can leave, but pay me back first.
And don't forget every
cent of the interest.
Hey, Wooju.
Yeah?
When we're talking money, call me Boss.
Teach me how to sing.
You play the piano?
I can play anything after hearing it once.
How is that possible?
Like I said, I just
hear it and I've got it.
♪ Fly me to the moon ♪
♪ Let me play among the stars ♪
♪ Let me see what spring is like ♪
♪ On Jupiter and Mars ♪
♪ In other words ♪
♪ Hold my hand ♪
♪ Baby, kiss me ♪
♪ Fill my heart with song ♪
♪ And let me sing forevermore ♪
♪ You are all I long for ♪
♪ All I worship and adore ♪
♪ In other words ♪
♪ Please be true ♪
♪ I love you ♪
Whoa!
You scared me.
Didn't I tell you I was a prince?
I did it again.
Stop talking nonsense.
♪ Fly me to the moon ♪
♪ Let me play among the stars ♪
♪ Let me see what spring is like ♪
♪ On Jupiter and Mars ♪
♪ In other words ♪
♪ Hold my hand ♪
♪ Baby, kiss me ♪
(Wooju / Barcode Tinnasit)
(Raon / Jeff Satur)
(Woo-hyuk / DION)
(Q / Q)
(Hachi / Jason) (Air / Alpha)
"Wooju Bakery"
(Episode 7)
(Fly Me to the Moon)
Hachi, congratulations.
Is it finally fixed?
I think this device will be restored soon.
Communication on Earth
will be possible tonight.
Oh.
Will you be back soon?
Yes, I can finally say goodbye
to this dump planet Earth.
I like Earth quite a bit.
Don't you?
Well...
Hachi.
I have something I wanna give you.
A token of our friendship.
C'mon, let's try it on.
How should... how should I...?
Look there.
I'll put it on you.
Wow.
It looks good on you.
Thanks.
Don't forget me when you go back home, OK?
By any chance... do you wanna go with me?
No, I have to stay with the princess.
She needs me.
Hey, I'll see you soon, okay?
Okay.
Did you learn to bake from my dad?
Yeah.
I came here to see your dad.
Why did you want to see him?
He was my only friend.
My family, and my mentor.
He always took such good care of me.
But how could you not know he passed away?
We lost touch a long time ago.
He just left a letter and vanished.
Went somewhere far away.
I only heard later that he got married.
How did you know I was his son?
It was obvious the moment I saw you.
You look exactly like him.
Why didn't you say so earlier?
Would you have believed me?
Even if I told you now,
you still wouldn't believe me, right?
That's because you're
always saying weird things.
Your dad's soul must have brought me here.
I missed him so much,
that's how I found you.
What are you doing?
A kiss.
A kiss?
Yeah.
Who kisses like that?
Well...
That's how we do it back home.
Hey, since you're on Earth now,
do it the Earth way.
Officer Shin.
Yes?
The report on last night's case,
is it finished?
Just a second.
Here it is.
Officer Shin.
Yes, sir?
That... UFO... alien-related club,
did you quit it?
Yes. I decided to drop any hobbies that
interfere with work.
Okay, good. That's better.
That's the way.
A little lower here.
Ugh...
Hurry up!
Ouch.
Seriously.
Hey...
Turn around.
Wait.
Oh, for heaven's sake.
He's coming.
Mina, trust me on this.
I bought this for my
partner, but you take it.
Why? We haven't even left yet.
I'll explain later. Just put it on.
What's with the sunglasses?
I was in the dark for too
long. My eyes are sensitive.
Has anything been inconvenient lately?
Of course it has...
Not at all! You've taken
such good care of us.
Everything's been fine.
Hmm... I've been thinking.
And I'm curious how much you actually know.
You're aliens, aren't you?
What about it?
Are you here to arrest me? I
haven't done anything wrong.
What law did I break?
I'm a legal citizen here.
And I run a legitimate business.
What is your real purpose on Earth?
Secretary Lee.
Yes, Chairman.
Oh my god! Run!
Hurry... damn it.
(Operation: Alien Extermination)
Is this where Woo-hyuk grew up?
Yes, I grew up here.
I had lots of friends, and the
director took care of me like a mother.
Woo-hyuk.
- Hello, Director.
- Oh, come on in.
- How have you been?
- Oh, thanks for coming all this way.
(Operation: Alien Extermination)
Here is the list of confirmed aliens.
Wow, there are so many.
Yes, and...
The aliens' first target
is to activate the device inside
the Wooju Bakery building.
What do you mean, activate the building?
It looks like an ordinary building,
but it's actually a
special device for aliens.
Wait, hold on.
What's wrong?
Officer Sin.
We shouldn't be handling this alone.
Should we get the other
officers to look at this?
Ah...
Your mother seems like a wonderful person.
I've never called her 'mother', though.
Woo-hyuk.
Do you think love is only about giving?
Accepting love is also a form of love.
Hmm?
Officer Shin.
I'm off today, though.
Hey, senior.
Please, listen to my troubles.
What?
Today...
is the most important day of my life.
- It's so hot.
- No, that's not it.
I was supposed to go to the movies today.
Can't we do this tomorrow?
Or you can just tell me over the phone.
No, I need to see you in
person and tell you myself.
Please, as a favor to your junior.
Please, just listen.
Fine, I'm on my way.
Chairman, Officer Lee is furious.
He wants to wipe them all out.
Secretary Lee, what do you think?
I agree.
I don't think there's any
reason to keep them around.
The old owner of that bakery...
What about him?
How did he end up on Earth?
Do you, perhaps, know?
What do you mean by that...
He was the closest person to the King.
Why would he flee to Earth?
How should I know that information?
I'll be taking my leave.
There's still... the accomplices and
the next steps for the investigation.
I'll report back to you.
So you're saying aliens came to
Earth to harvest vital resources?
And they're still plotting a conspiracy?
And the leader of these
aliens is Lee Seong-yong?
Yes, that's right...
Are you really expecting
us to believe this?
It's all true!
Officer Shin and I risked
our lives to uncover this.
I'm not making this up.
Do you think I can I apply
for witness protection?
You just said you were
an alien, didn't you?
Uh...
The laws of the Republic of Korea
mandate full witness protection.
Ah...
I'll handle it.
Senior.
You don't actually believe him, do you?
Woo-hyuk, don't worry. I'll just
shoot him and be done with it.
Senior.
What's wrong with you?
I believe everything Officer Shin found.
And I believe this alien witness, too.
Because I'm an alien as well.
Do we really have to use a cart
to move something this high-tech?
The Chairman is rushing us,
so we have to get it there fast.
That's strange. Why is this
cart so hard to push today?
Hey! Get out of here, you jerk!
Get lost!
Move it.
Get out of the way.
Move.
Get out now!
Wow, this smells just like home.
Hey, try some.
Ah...
This is the first time I've
smelled a scent like home, boss.
Sir, the bread must be
paid for before eating.
Here.
Sir, this is too much.
Keep it all. No need for change.
Boss, why did you give him so much?
We won't be needing Earth
money for much longer anyway.
That makes sense.
Yeah, Earth was never really
a place for us to stay anyway...
Good grief.
Where's the owner of this place?
Our boss?
I'm the owner. What's going on here?
The owner?
You're the owner here?
It's true, I'm the owner.
Are you crazy...
You're the owner?
I mean... I work hard
like I'm the owner here.
Are you the owner here?
Yes... is there a problem?
We're taking over this building.
I happen to have a much
bigger and nicer place nearby.
I can help you move there. And
there're issues about moving, right?
We'll even cover the moving costs.
We'll take care of everything.
How about it? That's a
pretty good deal, right?
So, Prince.
We done being slaves here, too.
Wooju, let's sell this place.
Let's open a shop in a bigger place.
No.
Why not?
The landlord is here, too.
Grandpa, do we really have to move?
Sigh...
It seems it would be better to move.
How can that be?
The reason I opened this bakery
here is because of my father...
I just wanted to keep
my father's bakery going.
You're the son of the
owner of the old bakery?
Then get out of here right now, you brat.
There's no reason for a father and son to stay
in the same place and die together, right?
Are you threatening me?
What threat?
Who threatens someone by
offering them a huge pile of cash?
And begging you to move?
You call that a threat?
See that?
My brother is a police officer.
I'm calling him right now.
But Chairman, why are
we keeping them alive?
In my opinion...
Just like before, we should just make it look
like an accident and finish them off cleanly.
This is your brother calling.
If you run your mouth, everyone
here will die. Understand?
Hyung?
I'm a bit busy right now.
I'll come over as soon
as I'm done. Don't worry.
Hyung?
What did he say?
I've been a police officer on Earth
and lived a quiet life for a long time.
I even received an award from the
Commissioner of the Police Agency.
Secretary Lee.
Are we just going to
leave these people alone?
Just do as the Chairman says.
Sigh...
If they run away, it's going
to be a headache for me.
Forget it. The machine will
be activated soon anyway.
We'll be leaving soon, too.
That's true.
Try calling again.
Hmm...
This machine... I heard
it's very dangerous.
Is this machine really that dangerous?
It won't cause any trouble yet.
It will take a few more
days to fully activate.
If this building really activates...
Old man... can you stop
this machine now, please?
It's beyond my control now.
The building has
already started to activate.
Is there really no way to stop it?
It's not entirely impossible.
This harvester will extract the energy.
Then it will concentrate that energy
and send it somewhere in the universe.
So is someone else controlling
this building from somewhere else?
I don't know where, either.
Hachi, can you find out?
This is where the landing
jammer was fired at our spaceship.
Yes, and ship crashed because of it.
It would be possible to track
down the location by tomorrow.
I have one more thing to ask, Grandpa.
About Wooju's father...
How did he actually die?
Did you kill him?
That man...
He wanted to destroy the energy
harvester the Chairman built.
It was supposed to be a secret.
I don't know how he found out.
He even damaged the
building, causing it to go dormant.
I had no choice but to
tell the Chairman about it.
I really wanted to go back home as well.
You're a really bad person.
That's right. It's the same as killing him.
That's why I've always
felt so sorry about it.
Then why are you restarting this building?
Because...
Because of you, Your Highness.
As long as you're in danger, the Royal Family
will definitely send someone to save you.
Then the Chairman's
conspiracy will be exposed.
You're crazy!
Are you putting the
prince in danger for that?
No one has ever come to save us.
We've been living here
for over a hundred years.
I really... I really want to see my family.
I really miss them.
Air, Air!
Uh... Emperor?
Air, come here! Quickly!
What? What's happening?
Air, salute!