Mr. Yuan,
you've been dumping
Minghui shares lately.
Guess you've got cash
to burn on charity now.
What are you looking at?
Can't I chat with Mr. Yuan?
Even if Xu Wanxin
puts up something worth a fortune...
puts up something worth a fortune tonight,
it won't make a difference.
In the end, it all depends on my dad
whether he's willing to do her this favor.
A no-sale at an auction
will indeed make headlines.
Just wait.
Once my plan works tonight,
everything will fall back into place.
Hao, don't do anything reckless.
I won't be able to cover for you
if you go too far.
Just sit back and watch.
=Echoes of Gang City=
=Episode 7=
(Heartbeats and Breaths Fall into Sync)
(Utmost Brightness &amp; Radiance Charity Gala)
Welcome to Minghui Group's charity gala.
This gala dates back
to the Republican era
and has been carried on
for over a century by Mr. Xu Qianmo.
Now, let's welcome tonight's host.
Ms. Xu Wanxin,
interim chairwoman of Minghui Group,
and her husband, Mr. Shen Gu,
will open the auction.
A round of applause, please.
Good evening, everyone.
I'm Xu Wanxin.
Thank you for being here.
This is my first time
hosting this charity gala
on behalf of my grandfather, Xu Qianmo.
Whether it's children in remote areas,
elderly people in hardship,
or those fighting illness,
they gain a little more strength
because we are gathered here.
They gain a little more light
because of our kindness.
I now declare
"Utmost Brightness and Radiance"
Charity Gala
officially open.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you.
Thank you for your wonderful speech,
Miss Xu Wanxin.
Let's give her a round of applause.
Thank you. Please have a seat.
Over the years,
we've witnessed countless miracles.
Tonight, our first auction item
is provided by Ms. Xu Wanxin
of Minghui Group.
It is a painting collected
by the late Mr. Xu Zhaoming.
Created by the renowned
Ming dynasty artist,
Qin Xiyuan.
"Viewing Phoenix Tower".
Dated 1550.
Measuring 113.5 by 41.5 centimeters.
It bears inscriptions
of "Viewing Phoenix Tower"
and the seals
from both Mr. Xu Zhaoming
and Mr. Xu Qianmo,
reflecting its history and legacy.
The starting bid is 15 million
with each increment of 1 million.
Let's start. Here we go.
If this were at Christie's,
it'd be snapped up in seconds.
It's a top-tier collectible.
What a pity.
We can't spend money
to support our enemy, can we?
Tempting as it is. Better hold back.
16 million once.
16 million twice.
Anyone else?
17 million once.
17 million twice.
One last time.
Congratulations.
The painting "Viewing Phoenix Tower"
by Chinese artist Qin Xiyuan
goes to Ms. Song Qionghua.
Our second item tonight
is a Han Dynasty Jade Bixie Amulet.
Made of Hetian jade
with a smooth and lustrous texture.
Some areas show calcification
with a yellow-brown patina.
The starting bid is 16 million.
The starting bid is 16 million
with each increment of 1 million.
Why bring out such a worthless rock
to embarrass yourselves?
This item isn't appealing.
That's nonsense.
A Ming dynasty artist's painting.
A Han dynasty jade amulet.
They're highly sought after at auctions.
Mr. Haoran, surely you can tell?
I don't like how you're putting it.
Whether an item is good or not
should be decided by bidders.
Miss Xu can't bring out a decent item,
and now you're blaming us?
You have such high standards.
Tell us.
What counts as a good item?
I think Miss Xu's necklace
is quite nice.
European royal jewelry.
It's collected by Mr. Xu Qiaomo
from the Republican era.
If Miss Xu
is willing to put it up for auction,
I'll offer a round number.
Since this is her first charity gala,
it'd make it even more meaningful.
What do you all think?
Right.
Sounds good.
You think it's good?
Why don't you put up
your own family heirloom?
So, Miss Xu won't put it up?
Seems this so-called charity
is just for show.
Silence, please.
This necklace was a coming-of-age gift
from my grandfather
when I turned 18.
It means a lot to me.
But
if
it can contribute
to Minghui's charity effort,
I believe that's what my grandfather
would've wanted.
Your cufflink matches
Miss Wanxin's necklace well.
It's a gift from her.
An 18-carat Tear of Ocean sapphire,
A stone representing love.
It's of rare quality.
According to Mr. Xu Qianmo,
this necklace was an engagement gift
from a patriotic businessman
in the Republic era to his fiancée.
The starting bid is 100 million.
Each increment is 10 million.
The starting bid is 100 million
with each subsequent increace
starting at 10 million.
Here we go.
Mr. Haoran.
110 million.
Anyone else?
Mr. Shen Gu.
120 million.
Thank you, Mr. Shen Gu.
Mr. Shen Hao.
130 million.
140 million from Mr. Shen Gu.
Mr. Shen Gu.
200 million.
That's the highest premium
for this diamond necklace.
Mr. Shen Hao.
Shen Gu is willing to waste money
on charity,
but know your limits.
Thank you, Mr. Shen Hao.
210 million.
Mr. Shen Gu.
300 million.
300 million once.
300 million twice.
300 million thrice.
Congratulations, Mr. Shen Gu.
Tear of Ocean is yours.
Where is he going?
No idea.
What are you doing?
Don't move.
Bravo!
What's going on?
Shut up.
Bravo!
Shen Gu,
thank you so much.
I should return it to...
No need.
It matches my cufflink perfectly.
It's a gift in return.
Thank you.
I thought
I was going to lose it.
You won't.
♪Tonight the rain falls soft and slow♪
♪Blending with letters left unread
drifting through the air♪
♪You turn and look back at me♪
♪In those same eyes familiar tears
quietly appear♪
♪It feels like we have carried so much♪
♪So many questions time itself
could not make clear♪
♪The moment you walked into my life♪
♪Every dream I had became something
I want with you near♪
♪How many letters have I written
just for you?♪
♪If only you could truly hear
what my heart is trying to say♪
♪From this life on no distance
could keep us apart♪
♪The promise we made♪
♪Will find its way
to be fulfilled one day♪
♪But I want more
than just that fleeting gaze♪
♪Still I have not heard your answer♪
♪Can we still rewrite the ending
we face?♪
♪When regrets begin to turn around you
will hear it all♪
♪Everything that leads me back to you♪