Well...
Hello, students and parents.
I'm Teacher Pobmek.
Honestly...
I don't know what to say today.
So I'm just going to tell you a story.
This story is about a man.
He's a teacher.
A teacher is supposed to love kids,
care about them,
and be ready to motivate them
to grow and learn.
- Two times two equals?
- Four!
- Two times two?
But the problem is,
he's not into any of that.
And he was sure he wouldn't make it
all the way through as a teacher.
But he made it through,
thanks to another teacher
who was always there to support him.
Snap your fingers!
The teacher who taught him
that teachers are no different
from their students.
If students are growing and learning,
then teachers are growing and learning too.
And it's a beautiful journey
when you have someone by your side
through it all.
[6 Months Earlier]
Teachers, please keep an eye on the kids.
Thank you. Bye.
Go ahead and cross. Watch out for cars.
Hello.
- 10 minutes!
- 15 minutes!
10 minutes!
I think it's 15 minutes!
No, 15 minutes!
10 minutes!
Trust me. 15 minutes.
I think it's only 10 minutes!
No, I think
it might even be more than 15 minutes.
Hey, Nobel, show your teacher some respect!
Even though Teacher Pobmek's classes
aren't fun,
he's not late every day.
Please. Bitcoin, which team are you on?
What do I get if I guess right?
You get all these snacks.
[Just a pool for fun. Betting is bad]
Well then, I'm team...
You're late! You're late!
Hey, you up yet?
- Yeah.
- See?
I knew you'd go back to sleep.
I already let you sleep in really late.
Wake up right now!
Shit!
I checked the weather forecast.
It's probably going to be really hot today,
so wear lighter colors.
You're teaching geometry today.
Don't forget the models.
One last thing. The lollipop.
You look the cutest when you smile.
So smile at the kids a lot.
Make sure you leave by 7:30.
Otherwise, you'll be late.
It's 8 now.
Time to close the gate.
Wow, right on the dot, new teacher.
It's my first day.
I've got to bring the energy.
- Please take it from here.
- Of course.
Bye.
Yay! It's 15 minutes!
Hey, don't cheat!
Teacher Pobmek's 16 minutes late.
Why are you taking it all
for yourself, Nobel?
Hold on.
[Teacher will be late by how many minutes?]
Are you guys gambling?
- Do you know it's bad?
- No, he's 15 minutes late.
Look at the clock.
No! I can't read it!
Hey!
It's time for class.
Go back to your seats.
Kids!
Listen to your teacher!
Fine.
You're not going to study, huh?
Then take this!
Hi, Principal Sodchuen.
So today, Sodchuen,
I asked the kids to bring candy
to count numbers,
because I thought it was tangible
and would help them understand better.
I'm tired of arguing with you, Pobmek.
- You're just so...
- Adorable.
Annoying!
Forget it.
I didn't call you in here to scold you.
I just wanted to introduce you
to our new P.E. teacher.
He said he knows you.
Me?
Who is he?
Hey, Pobmek!
So you two really know each other.
Then I guess
there's no need for an introduction.
But how do you know each other?
We were neighbors.
My mom is close friends with his mom,
so we grew up close too.
Jee, can you come teach Pobmek for a bit?
Sure, Aunt.
Come on. Let me teach you.
What's this?
Why can't you dress neatly like Jee?
- Aunt! Hi!
- Hi.
- How are you?
- Look at him. So neat and clean.
And look at you!
Our kid got a 4.0, honey!
Yay!
Nice!
You've been best friends since childhood.
You can help each other out with work, okay?
Oh, Pobmek is the one who'll have to help me.
I just moved here.
I'll be relying on my friend here a lot.
Well...
I think it might be better
to learn on your own.
Excellent academic performance.
Outstanding record.
Wow. You were born to be a teacher.
You're too kind, Principal.
I'm just lucky.
I pick things up really easily.
I was an early bloomer.
"I was an early bloomer".
It's time.
I'm going to go introduce myself
to all the classes now.
Please excuse me.
See you, dude.
He's got that new-teacher energy.
Let's see how long that lasts.
Hey!
Don't tease him.
What about you, huh?
Do you still want to be a teacher?
I already told you.
I don't want to be a teacher.
And you think I want to be Acting Principal?
Just thinking
about Principal Maximov traveling the world...
makes me want to scream.
What's wrong?
I just felt like screaming, so I did.
Pobmek.
Yes?
You and I are both in a tough spot.
But don't forget
that we all have our responsibilities.
You chose to become a teacher,
no matter what your reason was.
So I want you to do your best.
Do you understand?
Yes, I do.
So, can I go back to my classroom now?
Oh, you're rushing back
to teach the kids, aren't you?
I'm going to sneak a peek at my boyfriend.
When I say "Good", you say "morning".
- Good!
- Morning!
Come on. Good!
Morning!
Yay!
For homeroom today,
I have an amazing mission for you.
And that is...
Is?
- Is...
- Is?
Writing a card to someone you love!
Yay!
Please pass them to the back.
You can write it
to your dad, your mom, or your siblings.
Anyone you love.
Write a card to tell them you love them.
I worked hard on this!
Give it to me!
Write your own, King!
I just want to look for a second!
I can't think of anything, Four!
King, let's each write our own card, alright?
Let's not copy your friend.
And Four, please speak nicely to your friend,
so he can understand.
Is that okay?
Okay, Teacher Solar.
Good job.
I know you're all working really hard
on your cards,
so I'm sure they're full of love!
Yay!
I saw you went
to Teacher Sodchuen's office today.
What did she get on your case
about this time?
Nothing.
She just told me a new teacher moved here.
He used to be my neighbor.
His name is Jee.
Oh, Teacher Jee.
I saw him this morning.
Yeah, that's him.
He's so damn enthusiastic.
He makes me look bad in comparison.
Then, try to improve yourself a bit.
No!
It's too much. I'm tired.
Complaining again.
You complain every day.
It's too much.
You're such a complainer.
You complain every day. Jeez.
Wow!
I didn't know my friend had this side to him.
He basically wants the whole world
to know they're dating.
Wait, Principal.
You don't want teachers dating each other?
I actually think it's a good thing.
They can help each other out.
I think
Pobmek is the only one relying on Solar.
If one day Solar isn't around, we're doomed.
Every day. Jeez.
I'm not complaining.
You are.
But that day will probably never come.
What's up, beautiful?
Oh, what a sweet talker.
What are you making, son?
Chicken breast salad, low calories,
with the salad dressing by Mommy Pranee
that was just delivered to me.
Have you run out?
I can send you some more.
Not yet, Aunt.
It's so good we never seem to finish it.
Are you talking about the salad dressing?
By the way, how was teaching the kids
to write cards?
The kids loved it.
I guess
they don't write letters anymore these days,
so they were super excited.
Nice.
If I come up with any new ideas,
I'll share them with you.
Okay?
Just what I'd expect from a retired teacher
who refuses to retire.
Beautiful.
Of course.
Once Teacher Pranee, always Teacher Pranee.
Being a teacher is for life.
[Teacher Solar is my hero]
[Teacher Solar & Teacher Pobmek]
You're just too cute.
After teaching the kids to write letters,
you still have time to write your own.
If your mom reads it, she'll be so happy.
Why don't you write one for your mom?
No way.
My mom's not sweet like yours.
- Let me see.
- Hey, no!
Why not? Let me see.
No! I'm shy.
What do you mean you're shy?
- Let me see.
- I'm shy.
No!
Ouch!
Shit. What's wrong?
Well...
I jumped over...
the school gate again this morning.
How is it? Feeling better?
Come on.
Hey, you don't have to.
It's okay. Let me do it for you.
Come on.
Solar.
Why are you so good to me?
What's gotten into you?
Why are you being emotional?
I'm not.
I'm just curious.
I feel like I'm just a burden.
I've never been able
to do anything nice for you.
Not just for you.
Not for others. Not for Sodchuen.
Not for the kids either.
I'm useless to everyone.
You might not see it yet, but I do.
You're slowly improving in your own way.
Don't cover my eyes.
I'd rather see you.
Sometimes when you can't see with your eyes,
you can see more clearly.
Alright, feet out.
All relaxed now, Teacher?
Okay.
Next, get ready to be punished.
I heard you're a bad teacher.
I'm a really bad teacher.
Can I retake the test with you?
No. Keep it on.
Not again.
What do you have to do first?
Thank you, Teacher.
Wake up, baby.
Wake up...
Flashcards for teaching the kids vocabulary.
It's not very hot today,
but wear light colors.
You look cute in them.
You look the cutest when you smile as well.
[Thank you :)
But next time, sleep with a blanket!]
So, you like how I've improved, don't you?
Sorry.
Is this Mr. Tewtawan Mancharoensin's
emergency contact?
Yes.
I'm his partner.
Please stay calm.
The thing is...
This morning,
when Mr. Tewtawan was crossing the road
in front of the school,
he was in an accident.
I'm Tewtawan's partner. How is he?
Please calm down. Well...
I even woke up before him this morning.
But I was so sleepy
and accidentally fell asleep.
If I'd pushed myself more,
I could've taken Solar to school.
Then none of this would've happened.
I didn't take good care of my partner.
You did take good care of him.
No! Not well enough!
Alright, if you say so.
But we've been taking good care of him.
Mr. Tewtawan has been awake for a while.
You can go in and see him now.
Solar!
Mr. Tewtawan, you're feeling better, right?
You're so lucky.
You got grazed by a car,
hit your head, and passed out,
but you look fine.
Really?
Have you checked thoroughly?
Well, according to the X-ray results,
there are no broken bones.
The CT scan shows no bleeding in the brain.
He just has a few bruises on his body.
Solar, are you okay?
Are you sure he's okay?
Why does my partner seem a bit off?
Everything looks normal.
He's probably just still in shock.
Do you want to admit him overnight
so we can observe him and put him on an IV?
Ouch!
I want to go home now.
Alright then.
You scared the life out of me this morning.
Next time, just wait for me
and be late to school together, okay?
Crossing the road in Bangkok
is dangerous as hell.
Hey! What the hell?
Solar! What are you doing?
What are you going to do to me, Uncle?
Huh? Uncle?
Yeah!
What did you put in the water?
I just put water into the cup.
Liar.
You put a sleeping pill in it, didn't you?
A sleeping pill? Why would I do that?
Because you kidnapped me, Uncle!
Uncle Kidnapper!
What Uncle Kidnapper
are you talking about?
And what's that?
Well... handcuffs.
See? You're Uncle Kidnapper!
You're Uncle Kidnapper!
What Uncle Kidnapper
are you talking about, Solar?
My name is not Solar!
Turn me back into my original body right now!
Your original body?
What are you talking about, Solar?
I said my name's not Solar!
If it's not Solar, then what's your name?
I... am... Sun!
Sun?
What the hell are you talking about?
Your name is Solar.
- My name is Sun.
- Solar.
- Sun.
- Solar!
I said it's Sun!
Ouch!
Solar!
Solar, where are you going? Solar!
To use the lift, you need a keycard.
Help! Help!
What's going on?
A kidnapper is trying to kidnap me, Auntie.
Excuse me? Did you just call me Auntie?
Please help me, Auntie.
I'm only a few years older than you,
and you're calling me Auntie?
- Let me hide in here, Auntie.
- No.
- Please, Auntie.
Please, Auntie.
Ow, my eyes hurt.
Next time you two want to role-play,
learn to respect your neighbors.
You're saying...
we're really friends, Uncle?
Of course, we are.
You still don't believe me?
No.
Why am I in this body?
When did I grow up?
You said your name is Sun, right?
Yeah.
Then let me ask you something.
How old are you, really?
I'm 7.
Why are you taking care of me,
Uncle Kidnapper?
You're going to take good care of me first,
and then ask my mom for ransom, right?
I told you, I'm not a kidnapper.
We're friends.
And I'm not asking for any ransom.
Even friends can kidnap each other.
Fine.
Whatever!
But don't act up.
Otherwise, I won't take care of you,
and I'll kick you out.
Stay here. Don't act up. Stay still.
Oh, you got back from the hospital so early.
How's Solar?
Well, Solar...
Wow!
Nice condo, dude.
Teacher Solar is okay now, right?
Yeah, he's fine now.
Thank you so much, Sodchuen, for checking in.
Solar's already asleep.
He's pretty loud when he sleeps, huh?
He tosses and turns in his sleep.
Tossing and turning this much is worrying.
You might want to have him do a sleep study.
Thank you so much
for worrying about my boyfriend.
It's late. Please go home.
- Oh?
- Hey!
Pobmek!
Come on! We came all the way here!
Hey! What are you doing?
You've made a mess!
Go to sleep.
Hey!
You're going to break the bed!
If you want to play,
go play in the other room.
Hey!
Why are you doing this?
What else do you want?
I get tired too, you know!
Didn't you say it yourself, Uncle?
That if I didn't behave,
you'd kick me out.
I want to go home already.
I want to see my mom.
Here.
This is your favorite, right?
I'll call your mom.
But let's do something while we wait.
What do you want to do?
Do you want to read a story?
You can pick.
You picked an English book.
Alright, let Uncle translate it for you.
Once upon a time,
there was a little hedgehog
and a little squirrel.
They lived in the same tree hollow,
but separately.
Then one day, a big storm blew through
and filled the hollow with fallen leaves.
At first, they tried cleaning by themselves,
but it was so tiring.
No matter how much they cleaned,
they just couldn't finish it.
So the two of them teamed up
and happily cleaned the tree hollow together.
What? A car grazed him? Oh no!
Where is he now? How is he?
He's okay now, Aunt.
He's safe.
He's back at the condo.
I'm out of town right now,
but I'll go back to Bangkok as soon as I can.
Solar is safe now. Please don't worry.
Really?
If you say so, then I'm relieved.
I'm glad he's fine.
Yes, Aunt.
How's it going over there?
Solar seems comfortable.
He's resting now.
No, I mean you, Pobmek.
How are you?
I...
I'm okay.
Are you really okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
You must be really shocked and tired.
A little.
Pobmek.
Yes?
You know, whenever I'm dealing with
something bad,
I have a trick to feel better.
What's the trick?
Whenever something's bothering me,
I clean the toilet.
Then I sweep and mop the floor.
No matter what I'm worried about,
it all feels lighter.
Hi.
I'm Solar.
Looking forward to living together, roomie.
I'm Pobmek.
Pobmek?
I'm Solar.
Our names are both related to the sky.
Is something stressing you out?
My mom said when something
is stressing you out or worrying you,
there's one thing that can help.
Cleaning the room.
Hey!
What are you doing?
I'm mopping the floor.
Huh?
You need to sweep before you mop.
You mop before you sweep.
Huh?
You sweep before you mop.
You mop before you sweep.
No, you sweep before you mop.
My mom taught me to mop first.
We're not getting anywhere
arguing like this.
How about this?
Let's have a staring contest.
Whoever blinks first loses.
The loser has to do
what the winner says, okay?
Fine.
Don't cheat.
Only use your eyes.
What are we even doing?
At this rate,
we'll never get to sweep or mop.
At least...
you're not stressed anymore, right?
[Pobmek, you know what?]
[The first day I moved into the dorm,]
[I was so worried
about whether I'd get along with my roommate]
Pobmek, you know what?
The first day I moved into the dorm,
I was so worried
about whether I'd get along with my roommate.
[Student Dormitory, Tanapak Building]
But when I met you, I knew...
I wasn't the only one who was worried.
So whatever you're worried about,
you'll always have me by your side.
I love you.
I love you too, Solar.
Hey!
Have you seen my boyfriend?
Hey, I just clocked in.
How could I have seen him?
Can you call and ask your friend
who worked the shift before you?
Can you hurry up?
Relax, I'm checking.
Pobmek, what's going on?
What are you doing here?
Oh.
Why aren't you wearing shoes?
You could hurt your feet.
But even when we have someone we love
by our side,
getting to the point of learning
isn't easy at all.
There are still many obstacles
that can test us at any time,
both from within ourselves...
and even from the ones we love.
This story isn't over yet.
It's only just the beginning.
Wake up, Teacher.
- Uncle Kidnapper.
- Sun?
- No, I'm going home to see my mom!
- Sun, come back here!
A teacher at the main campus
is acting strangely.
There you are.
No, I'm leaving!
It's some kind of mental health issue.
Don't worry.
I'm going to help you recover,
no matter what.