Characters, actions, places, occupations,
and events in this series
are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
I know I was too harsh on you.
If you slept with Shasha to spite me,
you are so mean.
I hope I will have a chance
to have a meal with your family one day.
I want you to take care of me.
Do you want to be my personal assistant?
I never thought I would meet you here.
Is that woman your girlfriend?
Don’t become another disappointment
in our family.
Are you blackmailing me?
Let’s call it a business negotiation.
Ton is influential in this industry.
If he tells you to do something, do it.
Understand?
Whether you become famous or not
depends on today.
Shasha, are you listening?
Sha!
Yes?
Listen.
Your mom entrusted you to me.
I have to make you famous.
If you do well today, we’ll all be set.
Then why didn’t my mom come?
She’s abroad with your stepfather.
Just focus on working
and saving a lot of money.
You can go to her anytime.
Turn around.
Slip it off.
Do I have to?
You want to be a model, don’t you?
Don’t waste my time.
Take it off.
(Just focus on saving a lot of money.)
(You can go to her anytime.)
Being this shy,
you probably don’t know that
backstage at runway shows,
models change in front of the crew.
Everything has to be fast.
If you’re like this, it’ll be difficult.
Lift your skirt.
If you want to be a model,
you have to be bold to go far.
Higher.
Lift it more.
Shasha.
Shasha!
Why do you look like such a mess?
Mm…
You have work today, you know that.
Get up, Shasha. You have a shoot today.
Can you cancel it for me?
Any excuse will do.
Stop being selfish.
The whole crew would have to stop
because of you alone?
Get up.
One.
Two.
Three!
Ugh…
Why do you look so worn out?
I’ll prepare a mask for you.
You reek of wine.
Did you drink or bathe in it?
Go take a shower.
Can I sleep a bit more?
Go shower.
And clean yourself properly.
Don’t smell like wine.
It’s embarrassing.
Go shower.
Everyone,
this is Baipor, my younger sister.
She’s interning as a creative.
Please teach her.
If she messes up, feel free to scold her.
Don’t hold back just because of me.
Nice to meet you. Please guide me.
You can scold me, but gently, please.
My heart is this tiny.
Min, are you listening?
Yeah.
You can talk to me anytime.
Prim’s sister is like my own sister.
But don’t be clingy with your partner
like she is.
I said scold her, not me.
Don’t worry. I’m not in a relationship.
Having one distracts you.
I’ll focus on work for now.
You’re just as bad.
Alright, everyone, it’s lunch break.
We’ll continue the meeting after.
Do you want to eat together, Prim?
Uh, I need to discuss work with Min first.
Do you want to come with us?
Sure.
Don’t be stubborn.
What’s wrong with you?
Fighting with your young girlfriend?
Yeah. She hasn’t replied for a week.
You’re not clear with her.
I’d feel hurt too.
Back then, I saw you bring Park home
and post it all over social media,
showing off to all the single people.
It’s not that simple.
I have another social circle.
If I come out as a lesbian,
people will gossip.
So you care more about gossip
than Praew’s feelings?
Min, I totally understand you.
But you’re not the only one
who needs to adjust.
She does too.
Ask yourself what you want.
And be clear with Praew.
Got it?
Let’s go
Hurry up.
Is this okay, Prim?
Anything you want me to fix?
I tried my best for you.
Thank you so much.
The previous AE spoiled clients too much.
Work wasn’t fun at all.
I couldn’t put anything into the work.
It was all about selling.
I understand your creative style, Prim.
I’ll balance bringing in
a lot of profits for the company
and keeping you happy.
But can you fix this part for me?
I’m afraid the client might misunderstand.
We don’t have that much budget.
Well, is it this part?
Oops, sorry.
Anything else?
No, that’s it.
Okay, I’ll revise it
and let you check again.
I still have a lot to learn.
Thank you for teaching me, Prim.
Good afternoon.
Oh, Bambi?
You didn’t tell me you were coming.
I wanted to surprise you,
but got surprised instead.
She brought work for me for proof.
She even got us a new client.
She’s great at pitching.
That’s good for your company.
Just keep it about work, nothing else.
I’m focused on work.
I barely have time for my partner.
Oh? You have a partner?
Yes, but it feels like I don’t.
We argue a lot lately.
Then try focusing on your relationship.
Pay attention to your own matters.
Maybe you’ll love each other more.
You can manage your time.
Prim won’t mind.
Thank you.
I hope my relationship becomes
as happy as yours.
I knew it. She’s suspicious.
She totally wants you.
Maybe she planned it
since that badminton court day.
Come on, you’re overthinking it.
No one tries that hard.
You don’t know anything.
Back when I wanted you to hit on me,
I used to hang around your faculty often
to get you to talk to me.
When you like someone,
you try to be near them.
Wow, I just found out.
So you liked me first?
No.
Technically, you chased me first.
But you just confessed.
So?
Fine. I liked you first.
So you’re mine now.
No one else can touch you.
If they try, they’ll meet my vicious side.
Like this.
Then eat me first?
I’m always ready.
Let me check the photos.
Yeah, this works. Thanks.
No problem.
Let me know if you need anything.
I thought you’d forget me
now that you’re dating a senior.
What are you talking about?
I’m not like that.
How'd it go?
Dating someone
who's never dated a girl before?
It’s good.
But she doesn’t want to go public.
She’s still not ready?
She’s grown. What’s she afraid of?
Then when will she be ready?
Months? Years?
Forget it. It’s probably not that long.
How do you know?
She might just be testing you,
then go back to a guy
or find someone better.
Praew, we’re still young.
Why waste time on uncertainty?
Hi, Min.
Why is your phone off?
I couldn’t reach you at all.
My battery died.
Do you have a power bank?
I can buy you one.
It’s okay. I’ll get it myself.
What’s up?
I came to take you to eat out
at that place you wanted the other day.
I’m broke.
Let’s go after payday.
It’s on me.
No, I’ll eat with my friend.
Hey, do you want Som Tam?
Our usual place?
Familiar taste? Do you want to go?
Of course.
Come eat with me.
You’re my girlfriend.
I can take care of you myself.
Try something new.
You opened my world,
so I’ll open yours.
Didn’t you say you don’t want to be around
that friend who makes you uncomfortable?
She just helped with work, nothing more.
And if she likes me, I can’t stop that.
I know you sulked
because I scolded you at the office,
but what you’re doing isn’t right, is it?
I want peace of mind.
Don’t sulk over something like this.
Don’t make me feel guilty
when you can’t give me clarity.
What do you want me to do?
Ignore everyone and date you?
I’m not alone like you,
who don’t have to care about others.
I’m sorry. I didn’t mean it like that.
It’s okay. I understand.
But I just want you to know that
I’m not asking for too much.
It’s just what partners normally give.
You want to meet my family, right?
Fine. I’ll take you.
Maybe then you’ll understand me.
Up to you.
Think it over.
Maybe you’ll find someone
who understands you better.
Maybe I’m too young for you.
Do you want pineapple? It’ll wake you up.
No, I don’t like sour things.
Okay.
What’s wrong? Why are you so drunk?
Nothing. I drink like this normally.
Do I need a reason?
Fine. You hired me as your manager.
I’m here to take care of you.
I’m not stopping you
from drinking or partying,
but don’t act like this.
It’ll ruin your work.
I showed up anyway, didn’t I?
Stop nagging like a mom.
I hired you as my manager.
Mm.
Then rest for now.
I’ll wake you up when they’re ready.
Here, an eye mask. I made it for you.
Thanks, but no need next time.
Brands already sent me.
Sure. A simple thanks is enough.
There is no need to brag.
I know you’re famous.
Gorya.
Yeah?
Don’t come to work tomorrow.
You’re not suited to be a manager.
What?
Are you firing me?
What did I do wrong?
Nothing.
We just don’t click.
And I don’t like people
controlling my life.
I’ll go back to clear things up
with Woonsen.
Back to someone who scams you?
Are you crazy? What are you thinking?
It’s my money, my business.
Yeah, you were the one
who kept begging me to join you,
and now you’re firing me?
Are you insane?
I’ve always been like this.
No one ever told you to fix your attitude?
Fine, I’ll leave.
I didn’t even want this job anyway.
It’s this kind of attitude
that makes you have no friends.
Sha, you haven’t been here in a while.
There are way more
good-looking people now.
Really? It feels the same.
No one’s interesting.
Are you sure?
What about that girl?
Did you break up?
Break up? We were never together.
But you like her, don't you?
I’m your ex.
I can tell just by looking into your eyes.
Don’t lie.
It was just a fleeting feeling.
I’m over it now.
You get bored so easily as always.
Win them over, then throw them away.
So if you don’t like her,
can I go after her?
Why did you ask me? Go ask her yourself.
I’m just being respectful.
But if you’re not into her,
I’m going for it.
Dating a puppy girl is like this.
You have to adjust a lot.
These days it’s not about age.
It’s about attitude.
Have some sympathy for her.
If I were her, I’d feel insecure too.
Dating you is like dating a ghost.
No presence at all.
Not everyone shows off their relationship
like you do.
So where is she today?
Not clinging to you
on the dance floor anymore?
She said she wants a break from partying.
She wants to focus on work.
Prim, Min.
Oh, Oil?
-Hello.
-Hi.
I didn’t expect to see you here.
We usually only meet in meeting rooms.
Let me take a break from work for once.
I just want to let loose.
But I never thought I’d run into
a Ladybird duo here.
With Prim, I’m not that surprised.
But Min too?
You’re into this scene too?
My friend just turned pro.
Prim!
Sorry?
She’s just joking. Don’t listen to her.
I don’t really want to talk
about work here, but I have a new client.
It might suit…
Sorry.
It might suit Ladybird.
It’s a spa product.
So I thought
you might want to try it together.
Try what?
Try the spa.
Oh.
Sure, I’ll contact you later.
Thank you for always bringing us work.
No problem.
I like people
who are beautiful and talented.
I’ll get going then.
I think she likes you.
Huh?
Seriously.
I’m going to the restroom. I need to pee.
What did I do wrong?
Tell me.
If I did something wrong, just say it.
Do you have someone new already?
Tell me.
Don’t hang up. Let’s talk first!
Oh, Airy?
Prim.
Is something wrong?
I had a fight with my partner.
Out of nowhere, she broke up with me.
She didn’t even give me a reason.
I was going to meet her here to talk,
but she didn’t come.
It’s my birthday today too.
Oh, that’s awful.
Did you come alone?
Yes.
I don’t dare go outside.
I feel embarrassed.
Hey, it’s okay.
Come hang out with me and Min.
Are you sure?
You guys came to have fun.
I don’t want to make things awkward.
Hey, we work together.
We’re like sisters,
so we should take care of each other.
If you need help,
with work or personal stuff, just tell me.
I’ll help if I can.
Can I hug you?
I really need someone right now.
It’s okay.
♪ It’s rare to feel this way,
can’t catch my breath ♪
♪ Got this feeling,
my heart’s such a mess, a mess ♪
TEXT ME WITH YOU GET HOME
♪ Just a look in your eyes
stirs up a storm inside, why? ♪
♪ Cause of you ♪
♪ What you do ♪
♪ You’ve got me melting, can’t lie ♪
Can we hear some cheers
for my MV heroine?
♪ Letting you walk away?
That’s something I won’t do ♪
♪ Would you mind if I fell for you? ♪
♪ There’s no one next to you? ♪
♪ You’re making me breathless, baby ♪
♪ Would you mind if I start right now? ♪
♪ Hope you will allow ♪
♪ Want to win your heart
before someone else steals you away ♪
Oh wow, look at you.
Sha, get up.
We’re closed. Come on.
Are you okay?
Get up.
Hurry up. Go home.
I’ll call a car for you.
No, I’m not drunk yet.
Hey, can I get more wine?
You’re way past drunk.
Come on, let’s go home.
Where’s Gorya?
Why isn’t she taking care of you?
Isn’t she your manager?
She’s not anymore. Just let her go.
Eh? What are you talking about?
So what now?
Should I take you back to your condo?
Whatever. I live alone anyway.
Oh, Airy. How are you?
I’m still hungover, but I’m okay.
Honestly, you could take the day off.
There’s nothing urgent today.
We can work from home.
It’s okay.
It’s better to come out and work.
Staying home makes me sad.
If you’re sad, just let it out.
Give yourself time,
and then pull yourself together.
If you bottle it up, it’ll explode.
Bambi is so lucky
to date someone like you.
Oh please,
sometimes I’m a pain in the ass too.
No one’s perfect.
But I think you’re the kind of partner
many people would want.
Ugh, I’m still hungover,
and I have to submit the draft tomorrow.
Should I go make you some coffee?
It might help you wake up.
Yeah, that sounds good.
Sure.
If you’re making coffee for Prim,
she doesn’t take sugar.
She’s hungover,
so she asked me to make it for her.
I didn’t know an AE
had to make coffee for the company owner.
It wasn’t in the job description.
You’re very eager.
I like taking care of people.
I want to take care of Prim.
Why don’t you leave that to me,
her girlfriend?
You have your own partner too.
Do you like seeing others take your place?
We broke up.
Oh, you broke up.
So you’re rushing to find someone new?
Maybe you should find someone
who isn’t taken.
I admire your effort,
but you need to tell the difference
between someone liking you
and simple kindness.
Last night was fun though.
Aren’t you overthinking it?
Being this jealous,
Prim might feel uncomfortable.
Jealousy makes our relationship stronger.
Then that’s good.
No need to be afraid of me.
I’m just friendly.
I’m not afraid.
I’m just annoyed.
Save your friendliness for dogs and cats,
not someone else’s partner.
Sis!
Ant, wake up already!
How did I end up sleeping here with you?
You were really drunk,
and last night we…
Nothing happened.
I’m just messing with you.
Oh my gosh, you scared me!
You were wasted,
so I dragged you here to my hostel.
You kept talking about your manager
all night,
crying while telling the story,
and then you fell asleep.
That really scared me.
I have a partner, you know.
Even if you’re Miss Universe-level pretty,
my partner’s still prettier.
Anyway, thank you.
I’m a total mess right now.
This is such a big deal.
How did you keep it to yourself?
Who could I even turn to?
My mom’s abroad,
and I barely have any friends.
Did you forget about me?
Here, drink this.
It’ll help your hangover.
Thank you.
If Ant hadn’t told me
about that bitch Woonsen,
you wouldn’t have told me, right?
I didn’t want to drag you into it.
So you fired me
and let her blackmail you instead?
Are you crazy?
Don’t give in.
If that video gets leaked,
I’m the one who’ll be ruined.
People will say I got famous
by selling myself.
Shasha, you know
you earned everything yourself.
Don’t let yourself become a victim.
I’ll help you.
Cry it all out.
Be weak just for today.
I’m sorry for firing you.
It’s okay. I understand.
Don’t overthink it.
We can’t change the past,
but we can fight it.
Don’t let bad people
have a place in this world.
Everyone’s ready to help you.
You just have to speak up.
You’re not alone.
Thank you.
Are you sure you left it in my room?
I’ve searched my room and faculty,
but I still can’t find it.
Did you check your old place?
Did you ask Boom?
I haven’t been back since I moved out.
It’s here.
Thank you, Min.
I’ll get going.
So this is how you want to play it?
Play what? I just came to get my stuff.
I’m talking about you doing it out of spite.
Going back to hang out with the friend
who likes you?
I’m not doing it out of spite.
I just think
being with people in the same circle
might be more enjoyable.
Also, I don’t want to feel invisible,
like I have no status.
You already know the condition.
I do, but I still feel hurt.
It’s okay to feel that way,
but don’t hurt my feelings.
I don’t like that.
Everyone has their own timing, right?
Well, it’s not that
I don’t want to go public with you.
I really want to tell everyone
we’re together.
Why wouldn’t I want to hold your hand,
show you off,
post pictures,
and show the world we’re a couple?
How about this?
I’ll take you to meet my family.
But we have to take it step by step.
My family isn’t open-minded enough yet.
I still can’t tell them
I’m dating a woman.
This is as much as I can do for now.
Are you okay with that?
Why wouldn’t I want to show people
how adorable my girlfriend is?
Okay.
We can take it slow and learn together.
Then…
stay over tonight?
Of course I’m staying.
I’ve missed you like crazy.
You’ve been staying at my place this long.
Doesn’t your mom mind?
I’m thinking of…
moving in with you.
What? I didn’t even invite you.
You invited yourself.
Why? You don’t want me around anymore?
Planning to bring someone else over?
Do you want me to schedule it for you?
What? No.
Besides Gorya, who I almost hooked up with
before you interrupted,
I haven’t brought anyone else here.
What about Airy?
Bambi, she just started recently.
Are you jealous already?
I don’t know. I just don’t like her face.
Something feels off about her.
She seems intense.
She’s trying to dress like me,
like she wants to be your type.
My type? What’s that?
Petite, long hair.
That’s your type, like me and Gorya.
Come on, I told you Gorya’s just a junior.
And my type isn’t just about looks.
I like you for being you.
You’re different.
No one in Thailand compares to you,
I’m telling you.
Not just Thailand but the whole world.
Come on, stop.
Just be nice to her.
I have to work with her
and you have to meet her again.
Fine.
Just work, and nothing else.
Nothing else? Like what?
I don’t know.
If she comes to your room,
she’ll meet the real Bambi!
Sure, I’m scared.
There’s nothing going on.
Just so you know.
No one gets close to me like you do.
We’ll see about that.
Here, a little extra love.
Grandma, it's delicious.
Delicious.
This one’s good.
Are you Min’s colleague?
Yes.
She’s a regular freelance photographer
at the office.
She takes really beautiful photos.
What about your parents?
Where are they from?
What do they do?
My parents passed away when I was young.
It’s just me and my older sister now,
but she’s married, so I live alone.
Are you a tomboy?
I like women,
but you can call it whatever you want.
Your mom told me already.
Did you break up with Park?
Why did you break up?
I like him.
You dated for years. What a waste.
What did you do to him?
Why do you assume I did something?
Why don’t you think he might be a jerk?
If people love each other,
they should be able to endure things.
Endure him hurting me,
both physically and mentally?
Come on.
Why are we talking about
something so stressful?
Our daughter rarely comes home.
Eat, eat.
Praew, eat.
Here, have some duck.
Here you are.
A big piece.
It looks like this family won’t have anyone
to carry on the family line.
You should hurry and find a boyfriend
and get married soon.
Don’t end up like Auntie Ju.
See? She has no family, no one,
growing old alone.
Why? She seems happy.
She has plenty of money.
Come on.
Money isn’t as important as family.
I think it is.
You both even borrowed money from her.
Let’s just eat.
Eat, eat.
Grandma, it’s delicious.
Eat a lot.
Okay, I’ll check everything.
Then go get Shasha.
Got it, Gorya.
Are you okay?
There’s no problem between you two, right?
Prim told me
you used to have issues with Shasha.
It’s nothing now.
I was just a junior who admired her.
That sounds familiar.
Alright, go ahead. Take care of it for me.
Sure.
Need any help?
No, I’ve got everything handled.
Shasha’s my friend too.
Let me help.
I bought lots of snacks.
Let me set them up for the press.
Ready, Shasha?
Min has arranged the press already.
Even if I’m not ready, I have to be.
I don’t know if I can control my emotions.
I’m afraid I’ll cry
and won’t be able to speak.
But thank you all so much for helping me.
It’s okay.
I know it’s hard to talk about something
you want to forget.
But just deciding to do this
is already so brave,
and it’ll help other women
going through this too.
Remember,
you didn’t get into this industry
because of that jerk or Woonsen.
You got here because
you’re beautiful, talented,
and you do it well.
Hey, don’t cry yet.
You won’t look good on camera
for the interview.
Okay, I won’t cry.
Just talk as much as you can.
If it’s too much, signal us right away.
Thank you so much.
Remember,
you’re not going through this alone.
You have us, Min, everyone at Ladybird,
and Gorya too.
We’re all ready to support you.
It’s time, Prim.
The reporters are here.
When did you start working
with your sister?
Not long ago. I just started.
I’m rooting for you today.
I’m sorry if I ever made you feel bad.
Looking back, it was all in my head.
No need to apologize.
I had my faults too.
If you have a partner,
don’t go around being nice to other girls.
Actually, don’t even smile.
Your smile alone could make
hundreds of girls fall for you.
Anyway, I hope everything
goes smoothly today.
I’m always cheering for you.
Thank you.
Hello, I’m Shasha.
Thank you everyone for coming today.
As you know,
I’ve had issues with my former manager.
She is attempting to blackmail me,
using things from my past.
What you may hear are things
I can’t go back and change.
But I will move forward.
I won’t let anyone discredit my efforts.
And I want anyone who has been harrassed
to speak up about it.
I’m ready to support you
and be there for you.
Let’s not let this happen to anyone else.
Are you Ms. Woonsen?
The court has issued a warrant
for your arrest
on charges of fraud and intimidation.
Please come with us
to the station for questioning.
Thank you so much
for leading the press conference today.
No problem. I’m into this stuff.
We’re women. Why the hell
hurt each other instead of helping?
Alright, I can tell you’re really into it.
Girl power.
Just talking about it gets me worked up.
Careful, you’ll get drunk.
What’s there to be afraid of?
It’s my place. If I’m drunk, I’ll just sleep.
Here you are.
The tee you wanted is finished.
Thank you. How much? I’ll help pay.
No need to act rich.
Just wear it. Others will want it too.
Oh, I see. So I’m your presenter?
Watch, it’ll be sold out in 10 minutes.
I’ll get ready to pin the product.
You’ve been drinking.
How will you drive home?
I’ll call someone to drive for me.
You can sleep here.
You’ve got clothes to change into.
Now you’re the one
inviting me to stay over?
No need to pretend.
Honestly, I do want to sleep over
but maybe another time.
I want today to end like this.
It feels just right.
Sometimes drinking beer
and having a good conversation
is better than sex.
I’ll head home now.
Thanks for the tee.
Are you saying I’m not allowed to have
any lesbian friends other than Prim?
But that’s just how this community is.
When someone new comes along,
people want them.
I’m sorry.
I didn’t think
it would make you two fight.
She’s so two-faced!
You still believe her?!
What do I have to do
to make you my stylist exclusively?
Being in a position
where you get to choose, it’s kind of fun.
You can’t handle everything on your own.
You’ve still got me,
and we’ll get through this together.