The Asian artist chart has been released.
Just like last year, Korean artists
have once again made it onto the chart.
And this one too.
Just 3,000 won more, please.
The Asia Artist Chart compiles…
- Thank you.
- Have a good day.
This makes the news even more promising.
Next up,
Gold Boys' Ra-ik caught up
in a dating rumor
with a trainee from the same label.
The agency remains silent.
Some reports say
the two first met years ago…
GOLD BOYS' RA-IK,
RUMORED TO BE DATING A TRAINEE?
WHO IS HIS RUMORED LOVE?
Attorney Maeng, did you eat?
I got you some porridge.
Try to have some later.
Okay?
Ra-ik denied the rumor!
Hurry, turn on Entertainment Special!
Gold Boys Ra-ik denied dating rumors.
Through his agency, he stated
that they're just close friends.
Saying work matters
more than dating for him right now,
he reassured fans.
- As baseless speculations continued…
- He said no.
Ra-ik's agency, Goldie Entertainment
- took a firm stance…
- She's just a friend.
…declaring they will take serious measures
against the spread of false information.
Let's go, come on.
It's recording, right?
- What?
- The dashcam, I wish you'd turned it off.
I said not to call me on promotion day!
You ruined everything…
What's going on there?
Who's she? You know her?
Yeah, she's the one
Ra-ik had a dating rumor with.
What?
The one that had you crying
for three days straight
without eating or sleeping?
That's her?
That jerk.
Saying he'd never date
and that he only loves his fans,
and now look at him.
So that's why you've got that long face?
What long face?
Stop talking nonsense and keep a lookout.
If anyone sees us, we're screwed.
See? I told you.
Never trust anyone
who lives with makeup on.
He's a grown man,
no way he's never dated at his age.
So why'd you give him your whole heart?
I mean, I didn't want you to get hurt.
Why would I be hurt? He's just a client.
My feelings… don't matter.
Why did you even come there?
- Because I was worried about you.
- No.
You were worried about yourself, not me.
Why? Were you nervous
because I met a prosecutor?
Afraid I might say something?
What?
The closer you try to get to me,
the more I can't help but doubt you.
You don't want
to be tangled up in this, right?
So don't come looking for me again.
Stay away from me, completely.
I saw Jae-hee that night.
What?
On my way home after meeting you,
I saw him going to the dorm.
But the news says he was at the hospital.
But I know what I saw.
He was there that night.
Definitely.
Could you give us a moment?
I think you need to explain this.
Later.
That night, after you left the store
and went up the trail…
you went to meet Hong Hye-joo, right?
How do you know her name?
Answer my question first.
I asked how you know that?
What matters isn't how I found out,
it's how I didn't know until now.
I told you,
you can't hide anything from me.
But I faced the prosecutor
without knowing this?
She has nothing to do with this case,
so there was no reason to mention her.
Do you realize how cornered you are
because of that reckless choice?
The prosecutors already suspect
your whereabouts that night.
- They'll soon find out that you two met--
- Hye-joo has nothing to do with this case.
I don't want her getting dragged
into this because of me.
I need to go somewhere.
I'll explain everything when I get back.
But before that,
please take her home.
Could you please?
Fine. I'll do that.
Hey, wait! Hold on!
Come on, I just bought that last month!
This is the footage we got from the taxi.
From just a quick look,
something feels really off and sticky.
Looks like that woman has some
serious grudge against Do Ra-ik, right?
Have you confirmed her identity?
We already checked the car.
But it turned out to be a company car.
Then we can just ask the company
to confirm the real owner.
We did.
But the thing is…
The car belongs to the Imhwa Group.
The Imhwa Group?
But is it okay not to tell her
that Ra-ik is staying here?
That's…
the client's private matter.
Get out, I need to get back to the office.
All right, then.
What?
Are you okay?
Why wouldn't I be okay?
No, that look on your face--
Chung-jae.
Don't ever talk to me
about my feelings again.
I'm not some incompetent person
who lets emotions ruin my work, am I?
No dashcam, no CCTV, no messages, nothing.
So what are you going to do?
What did she say earlier?
That night, when the two were talking…
A taxi suddenly pulled up, so we split.
Which means…
So there might be a witness?
Correct.
Go get that taxi dashcam, now.
Right now?
- Come on, you're joking.
- I'm not.
No excuses, make sure to find it today.
How am I supposed to find that?
I said I'm not talking to you!
I'll deal with CEO Geum myself!
He's still deciding.
Just wait a bit more, okay?
Please. I know exactly what he's planning.
He's just gonna leave us hanging
until the contract ends
and then toss us aside without a renewal.
I'll leave on my own before that.
Jae-hee.
Are you leaving the group?
- I have to look out for myself.
- Jae-hee!
People forget fast.
In a few years,
even the tiny offers we get will be gone.
You should hurry
and find your own path too.
I don't even have one.
You know I've got nowhere to go. I…
- Ra-ik!
- What? Didn't you change the door code?
Manager.
How long was Jae-hee hospitalized
after the concert?
What?
Were you two really together
for two full days?
Why are you asking?
Hey, Choi Jae-hee,
look me in the eyes and tell me.
The day Woo-seong ended up like that,
- are you sure you were at the hospital?
- What do you mean?
Answer me!
Where were you that day?
Jae-hee was at the hospital.
You know that he was hospitalized with me.
Are you trying
to pin everything on me now?
Stop it.
Let's go out first.
I know!
I saw it.
I know why you killed him!
Yeah?
Then say it! Why would I kill him?
Why would I kill him?
Hey, get out. Let's just get out!
Should I say it?
- Let go! I said let go!
- Stop it!
How did you even get here?
You came all the way here like this?
What if someone sees you--
Manager, are you sure that
Jae-hee was at the hospital that day?
I was at the office then, so I don't know.
Why do you keep asking that?
Where are you staying now?
I heard about your place.
- If you have nowhere to go--
- Then what?
Can you live with a murder suspect?
Right.
It was around that time.
When the controversy
over his poor attitude on stage began…
the company covered it up,
saying it was food poisoning, but…
The group we love hearing every day
and can't stop thinking about!
Welcome, Gold Boys!
We are gold! Gold Boys!
Great to have you here!
Ra-ik, we heard
you put a lot of effort into this album.
Is there a track you made
or is there a song that you like most?
It wasn't the body that was hurt.
It was his heart.
Because he lost the one
he loved.
See?
What's with her today?
I don't know.
She's been like that since she came back
from the prosecutor's office.
Looks like Kwak Byung-gyun
really grilled her.
Guess even the great Attorney Maeng
is powerless against him.
But doesn't she look a little sad?
Exactly, like someone who just got dumped.
Isn't it obvious?
It's because if she loses the case,
she'll lose all her success fees.
Get it together, Maeng Se-na!
He's just a client.
Don't you know
feelings are like a wild horse?
A horse running wild… you cut its throat
before it throws you off.
And fine, he can fall in love.
At an age when testosterone
is at its peak… Dating?
Of course, he should.
Idols are human too.
But he said he wasn't dating.
On Entertainment Exclusive,
July 16th, 2022, he clearly said…
No one deceived me,
but somehow I feel deceived.
And still…
When he had to deny his love…
what did it feel like?
Was he sad, hurt?
Or lonely?
In the end, all I do
is worry about you first.
Where can I possibly put
a heart that feels like this?
Attorney Maeng, did you see this?
It just came out as breaking news.
DO RA-IK SECRET LATE-NIGHT RENDEZVOUS
AFTER MURDER SUSPECT QUESTIONING
Isn't this in front of
the prosecutor's office?
Looks like it was taken from really close.
Yes.
Are you with Hye-joo now?
I took her home earlier.
Where are you now?
An article just came out, Hye-joo and I…
- I saw it. And actually--
- We need that article removed right now.
Isn't there any legal way to block it?
We can request a correction,
but that requires some procedures.
I'll look into what we can do first--
I don't have time for procedures now.
So you're saying,
there's no way to block it. Got it.
What? Got what?
Ye-sol, find out where the outlet
that posted this article is and call me.
- As soon as possible.
- Yes.
That's Hong Hye-joo, right?
What is this?
What is my sister-in-law doing here?
I knew it.
Knew what?
Gi-wook, did you know everything?
What do you mean?
Knowing Chairman Hong,
he wouldn't set up a meeting himself.
The truth is, your sister-in-law
asked you to, didn't she?
Well… Huh?
Do you realize what you did?
You set up a private meeting
between a key person in the case
and the lead prosecutor.
Very intentionally.
- What do you mean?
- Your sister-in-law, Hong Hye-joo!
She's deeply tied
to Do Ra-ik's murder case.
- What?
- I won't let this slide.
You are going to pay for treating
a prosecutor of Korea like nothing.
Keep that in mind.
Hey!
What are you talking about? Hey!
What?
Long time no see, Mr. Do Ra-ik.
What brings
a top star like you to this dump?
Take that article down, now.
No, I don't want to.
Articles are just like words.
Once said, you can't take them back.
I said take it down.
Wow, still soft about her.
Does she know?
That you're still this hung up on her?
Shut your mouth.
Why not kneel and beg me?
Who knows, I might let it slide,
just like last time.
Go ahead, release whatever you want.
I've done nothing to be ashamed of.
Sit down.
Sure. You didn't do anything shameful.
She did.
That Hong Hye-joo, or whatever,
she's the one who got cut
from the debut lineup recently, right?
Does she relieve stress by dating around?
How many guys does she go through?
Hey, that won't change anything.
Figure out how to shut me up.
She has no idea, right?
What you lost because of her.
You signed an unfair contract for her
and even turn against your mother over it.
It's all in the past.
Why are you bringing it up again?
You really don't know why? It was you.
You tattled to the company
that I took money.
Thanks a lot.
For making me write
trashy tabloids in this dump.
It wasn't me.
It doesn't matter.
I'm about to drop a real bomb anyway.
I can't believe I didn't know back then.
That Hong Hye-joo
was Imhwa Group's hidden daughter.
Well, now that I finally know the truth,
it's time to really dig in.
The follow-up article will be incredible.
"An ex-lover tied to a murder case."
I warned you before. If you touch
anyone around me, I won't let it slide.
If this happens one more time,
even I don't know what I'll do.
What are you going to do?
Did you forget? I'm a murder suspect.
Keep messing with me, and…
Stop! Enough!
How dare you threaten an active reporter?
- I swear, I'll--
- That's enough.
Enough? That bastard murderer is…
These were taken
long before Kang Woo-seong's incident.
From outside his house
to the makeup shop, the car…
You tracked every part
of his private movements.
Even him going to the bathroom?
This is legitimate reporting.
Don't you know?
Celebrities are public figures.
Their privacy can be restricted by law.
- Reporters have the right to cover that!
- Right?
- You tear apart my life with what right?
- You're right.
Public figures
may have diminished privacy,
but Hong Hye-joo is a private individual.
Publishing her personal information
without consent may amount to defamation.
And I'll hold you responsible
if your so-called reporting
can't be justified.
This is where you rushed off to?
To stand in front of a tabloid reporter
and proudly say you're a murder suspect?
- No, I just--
- I am your lawyer.
A lawyer has to know everything you do,
or even what you might do,
so we can prepare for it,
but you tell me nothing.
You acted on your own.
You even lied to me.
How am I supposed to trust
and defend you now?
I wasn't trying to lie--
Hiding something is lying.
Then…
I guess my whole life has been a lie.
It's me, Hye-joo.
I'm back in Korea.
Why aren't you answering?
I want to see you.
HONG HYE-JOO
I've had
to live my whole life
hiding everything about myself.
It's all in the past now, Hye-joo.
I got it, so please just stop.
Ra-ik has already ended it,
and you should…
HONG HYE-JOO
Woo-seong!
Since when?
Since when have you been
talking to Hye-joo?
Don't get it wrong.
I only did what you should've done.
And what exactly is that?
What is it you did for me?
You know, this is a crucial time for you.
You just started your solo activities.
If you get tangled up
- with her again--
- So that's it?
So you just cut off on your own?
Without even telling me?
- You know why better than anyone.
- It's none of your concern.
Ra-ik…
Woo-seong, I'm…
I'm not angry
because you didn't tell me about Hye-joo
or because you tried
to decide everything on your own.
What really makes me angry…
is that there are secrets between us now.
IT'LL ONLY TAKE A MINUTE
I NEED TO TELL YOU SOMETHING
To me, Hye-joo was something like…
a long-overdue assignment.
Where are you going?
We're out of beer.
I'll be right back.
I couldn't put it off forever.
I really thought…
It was time to end it for good.
HONG HYE-JOO
I'm at our usual spot.
I'll wait until you come out.
That is why I went to meet her.
You have five minutes.
Let's finish this in that time.
Five minutes?
It's been years since we last met.
And five minutes?
I came here because this was the only way
you'd really understand.
I don't want to keep in touch with you.
All your calls and messages bother me.
Don't reach out to me like this again.
I missed you.
That's why I'm here.
I…
I mean…
Back then…
I was too young.
Even so,
I shouldn't have said something
that would hurt you.
I'm sick of this.
What?
I've put everything into this solo album.
I'm not letting you mess up my life again.
So please, just get lost.
I'm sorry.
What?
I didn't mean to hide it.
I just…
You were trying to protect her, right?
That's why you acted so cold.
You were afraid she might get hurt.
You wanted her far from the case.
To me, Hye-joo is…
Someone I wanted to protect, but couldn't.
And we're completely over now.
That's why I couldn't tell you.
I was afraid that saying anything
would drag her into this.
I don't want her involved
in this case anymore.
Can you help me?
No dashcam, no messages.
You'll keep denying everything?
Because it's the truth.
We met in private as friends, that's all.
So a friend you hadn't seen in years,
you tried to hit with a car?
Ms. Hong Hye-joo? I won't ask again.
I already know you met Do Ra-ik
at the estimated time of the incident.
Why did the two of you meet that night?
I told you.
We just met as friends.
Ms. Hong Hye-joo,
if you keep refusing
to back up your alibi,
your status may change
from witness to suspect.
And if you end up in court,
these statements can work against you.
By the way, Prosecutor…
do they know?
About our blind date?
Just answer my question.
You should answer mine.
Why did you do it that day?
Telling me confidential details
of the investigation so easily
and pushing Ra-ik
as the culprit with no proof.
Isn't that some kind of illegal disclosure
of case details?
Who are you trying to lecture
about the law?
Ra-ik is not the killer.
Before you rush
to label him as the culprit,
check the alibis
of people around him first.
I saw on the news that his group members
were at the hospital that night.
That's not true.
What?
That night I saw him
near Ra-ik's house.
I saw Choi Jae-hee.
Why should I keep it secret?
You have to tell me a reason.
I mean, now the director is…
What's with you?
No, what's with you?
What?
You know you've been acting weird lately?
You lied that Ra-ik and Woo-seong
never got along.
- Why did you do that?
- Hey!
Who are you calling a liar?
I'm not the one lying, that jerk is!
- What?
- You don't know a damn thing.
That bastard…
Forget it.
If you know nothing, stay out of it.
And stop eavesdropping like a rat.
If you're hungry, you can eat…
What are you doing?
What do you mean?
I'm getting changed.
I told you to knock before coming out.
When did you say that?
And I'm in my house, in my room.
You could change in the bathroom.
That's such a hassle every time.
But where are you going?
You asked me to help Hong Hye-joo.
I need to figure out how.
Really? You're really helping?
- Then I'll help too.
- No thanks.
This isn't something you can do.
This is my job as your lawyer.
But don't expect too much.
I'm just going to look into it.
Wait…
It's not that I'm suspicious or anything,
but you told me not to hide anything, so…
I'm just saying this because I should…
Hye-joo told me earlier
that she saw Jae-hee
that night after I left.
- She saw Choi Jae-hee?
- Yes.
But Jae-hee
was at the hospital that night.
Seems like there's been a mistake.
And I'm not telling you to suspect him.
I just wanted to tell you.
I don't want to hide
anything from you anymore.
Okay, I'll look into it.
Why is this house so empty?
So she used to smile when she was little.
Do Ra-ik is not the culprit.
No way!
Why isn't she answering?
Hey, why don't you pick up my calls?
What's with that face?
Did you read the text I sent?
- I got the taxi's dashcam, and Hye-joo--
- I know.
She tried to run Do Ra-ik over with a car.
How did you find out?
Since when do you drink?
You didn't drink
so you wouldn't slip up with him.
The day of the incident
Hong Hye-joo saw Choi Jae-hee.
He testified that he was at the hospital.
But I don't think so.
Check his alibi properly.
Okay.
But shouldn't we deal with Hong Hye-joo
and Do Ra-ik first?
Yeah, we need to.
Right, we do.
But how? There's no way.
Yes, there is.
What way?
Chung-jae.
Why does it hurt this much?
You're hurting?
I knew you were pushing yourself too hard.
Hold on, I've got some medicine somewhere.
Let me see, do you have a fever?
My heart.
My heart hurts.
What happened?
Chung-jae, I thought
I knew everything about Ra-ik.
When he's happy, he scrunches his nose.
When he's focused,
his mouth hangs open a little.
When he's nervous,
his ears twitch just a bit.
I knew all that, and yet…
I never realized
how much he was hurting.
He must have been
in so much pain.
What about your pain?
Is it nothing?
Do you remember?
Back when your firm became
Goldie Entertainment's legal advisor,
I asked why you didn't take it,
and you said
you didn't want to get
too close to Do Ra-ik.
That you just wanted to watch him
from a distance… on stage.
I didn't understand
what you meant back then,
but after all this, I kind of get it now.
The more you get to know,
the closer you get,
the more layers you peel back,
the more disappointing
people usually turn out to be.
I'm not disappointed.
It's just unfamiliar.
And that scares me.
Back then,
whether I was sad or happy,
it always felt like
Ra-ik was right beside me.
But now…
even when he's right next to me,
he feels so far away.
Earlier…
when I saw the two of them…
they felt like people
from a different world.
A world…
I could never reach.
I wish I were disappointed.
I wish I were jealous.
But…
I can't even feel that.
If only I could…
I would go back.
with everything in me.
I'd go back to being distant again.
Somewhere far enough
that I'd never touch him.
I want to see him smile again.
I want to like him freely.
The way I used to.
Attorney Maeng…
Attorney Maeng?
Where did she go this morning?
Don't leave anything, eat it all.
I'll check when I get back.
You are up.
- Where's Attorney Maeng?
- She already left for work.
Here, take this.
What's this?
This is a mild, low-pH cleanser
with six plant-based,
gentle cleansing ingredients.
Ra-ik has really sensitive skin,
so he can only use this brand.
Can't you see? It's for washing your face.
And this. Ra-ik has some gum issues.
So it has to be an extra-soft brush
and gum-care toothpaste.
- They're a set.
- Here.
And this, a handmade German classic razor,
the exact kind he normally uses.
And this is European Oeko-Tex certified
100% cotton towel.
Take this too.
And these are supplements.
He looked way too thin yesterday.
- Make sure he takes them.
- These are the vitamins.
And this is omega-3,
probiotics.
Lutein with zeaxanthin and astaxanthin,
all in one.
And this one's
the Optimized Fucoidan capsules.
- Did you get all that?
- I don't care!
Just wash up and eat.
Attorney Maeng will contact you.
These are all the things I use.
What a coincidence.
This is what I do. Background checks.
It's all on Y**Tube anyway.
"What's In My Bag?", "Sweet My Home,"
all that stuff.
Her rule is to satisfy
every single need of her clients.
She really is a pro.
She didn't come home until dawn yesterday.
Were you two together?
Yeah, why?
Just asking.
But what are you two exactly?
Different last names, are you related?
Let's just say connected
in a way more tangled than blood.
Why are you asking?
No reason, just being polite.
Ever heard of small talk?
Why is that guy always so prickly
whenever he sees me?
Is he a hater?
Even after all that pain,
she's not mad at him?
Still taking care of everything.
DON'T LEAVE ANYTHING
EAT IT ALL, I'LL CHECK.
Yes, Director.
I just checked the email you sent.
Thank you so much for your help.
Yes.
Is the interrogation today?
I had no idea. I didn't prepare anything.
You don't have to.
Today, ambush is the strategy.
Let's go give them a proper blow.
I didn't summon you, yet you just show up.
It's not just about the questioning.
I think we can assist your investigation.
Quite the excuse.
You think I don't see through
this obvious tactic
trying to present an image of innocence
by voluntarily appearing?
Dragging out the case without indicting,
stalling while tossing around hypotheses,
that's a pretty obvious tactic too.
This is the footage from that day,
showing Do Ra-ik and Hong Hye-joo.
As you'll see,
there is no sign whatsoever
of the two colluding to commit a crime.
We already have this.
Context changes entirely depending on
how you look at it.
Since you saw it, you should know better.
That our meeting
was completely personal and private.
That's something
we'll need to look into further.
You could have met
to conceal evidence, couldn't you?
But you already know, Prosecutor.
That scenario was impossible
given the circumstances.
These are the call records
of CEO Geum Bo-sang.
As you can see,
after Do Ra-ik returned home,
there's a call
between him and Kang Woo-seong.
We've already secured
Mr. Geum's full statement as well.
If, as you claim,
Do Ra-ik and Hong Hye-joo met
to conceal evidence,
they would have had the murder weapon
and Kang Woo-seong's phone with them.
But after their meeting,
Kang Woo-seong called Mr. Geum,
so that proves
he was still alive at the time.
Therefore, your current claim
doesn't align with the timeline.
An investigation must always
remain open to multiple possibilities.
Just because the timeline
doesn't match the crime
doesn't automatically rule out collusion.
The two of them could have met
beforehand to plan
Kang Woo-seong's murder.
Then can you provide
any objective evidence
that these two were planning the crime?
We're conducting this investigation
to obtain such evidence.
Hong Hye-joo may be involved in the case--
"May be involved?"
Based solely on that speculation,
with no evidence or supporting facts,
you summoned her
and interrogated her intensively
for over six hours?
Well, if it's necessary
during the course of an investigation--
A legitimate investigation
should be based
on concrete evidence of the alleged crime.
You cannot proceed
without objective evidence.
It's clearly a targeted investigation.
What?
What you're admitting is that
after labeling him as your prime suspect,
you pressured Ms. Hong Hye-joo
without a single piece of evidence,
simply to force the circumstances
to fit your narrative.
As his legal representative,
I'm issuing a formal demand.
Cease your excessive investigation
into Ms. Hong immediately.
Otherwise, we'll file a complaint
stating that the prosecution
is conducting an unjust investigation
against our client.
Is that what you want?
Is it all over now?
Hye-joo…
They won't call her back again, right?
Since everything is properly settled,
they can't treat her as an accomplice.
Not unless some new evidence appears.
Really?
Yes. They might conduct
a simple witness questioning, but…
Thank you… All thanks to Maeng Se-na.
Thank you so much.
No… I…
Stinky!
Would you step aside for a moment?
Why should I?
Just wait in the car. I'll be right there.
Long time no see.
Class 1-4, Jeil Foreign Language High.
Stinky Se-na.
No, Maeng Se-na.
Sorry, should have recognized you sooner.
You've changed a lot since high school.
Of course I have.
I'm old enough now not to keep company
with people who barely qualify as human.
We have a lot to talk about.
Like how you've been,
why you took this case,
whether you knew I was the prosecutor
and took it on purpose,
or if you planned it
to screw me over from the start.
No wonder this investigation
is going nowhere.
You're too busy obsessing over
irrelevant crap like this.
What?
How long are you going to live
with that victim complex?
Use that time to work on your skills.
Then you'll catch the real culprit
and be the star prosecutor you want to be.
Good luck.
You seem pretty close
with that prosecutor.
How do you two know each other?
I don't.
- Why are you looking at me like that?
- No, you tell me.
What are you talking about?
It's too obvious.
You act like you've never dated anyone.
You've got one guy at home
and one at work.
What are you even talking about?
I've thought about this for a while.
The way that guy looks at you is weird.
So what is he? An ex?
Are you out of your mind?
Me? With that bastard?
He's just an unlucky classmate
I got stuck with.
I'd scrub him out if I could!
For a classmate,
you sound extremely hostile.
Whenever I think about that jerk,
I jolt awake
in the middle of the night, fuming.
Okay, I get it, so just drive carefully!
You're a lawyer and yet…
No, it's not me.
- The car isn't listening to me.
- What?
Se-na!
- Se-na!
- No, Ra-ik!
I've never been loved.
What are you doing?
I don't know how to give love
or receive it.
Are you saying someone did it?
Doesn't feel right.
If someone really held
a grudge against me…
Why did you lie?
It's…
I don't really know.
If needed, you should consider
shaping the flow yourself.
So you're telling me to drop my client?
Subtitle translation by:
Milena Martirosyan