Ongsa, do you think one year
is a long time?
I think it is.
It's long enough
for many things to change.
Why do you ask?
I'm thinking about taking a test
for the US exchange program scholarship.
What did you say?
Ongsa, are you keeping a secret?
So, you're never going to tell
your parents about me?
I knew
that you'd be here.
Sun.
I'm sorry.
Sorry for what?
I'm sorry for telling my parents…
that you're just a friend.
That's all?
Isn't that what you're mad about?
All this time…
I've been trying to understand you, Ongsa.
When I found out that you were Earth,
I should've been furious.
I should've even hated you
for lying to me.
But I forgave you…
because I already loved that person.
Whether it was Earth
or Ongsa,
a guy
or a girl,
it didn't matter.
I was already in love with that person.
Do you get me?
You asked for more time…
because you didn't want other people
to know we were together.
No matter how much I wanted it
to be in the open…
I agreed.
I did, even though I didn't care…
what other people thought of me
in the first place.
To me, us being together…
isn't something to be ashamed of.
As for the scholarship in the US…
I actually wanted you to come with me.
But I understood that you couldn't.
So, I chose not to go.
I decided to stay
so that I could spend time with you.
I know that following my dreams
is one kind of happiness.
But spending time with you…
also makes me happy.
I got up the guts
to tell my parents that I love you.
Do you know why?
Because I wanted them to know…
that there was someone good by my side.
I did my best at everything for you.
But why, Ongsa?
You act like…
what I've done is silly.
You act like our love is embarrassing.
It's not like that.
I didn't tell my parents
because I was afraid…
that they wouldn't accept us.
If that was the case,
it would be hard for you.
As for the exchange program abroad,
I really can't go with you.
But I don't want to hold you back
from following your dream.
I want you to do…
what you initially wanted.
Also, I hid our relationship…
because I was afraid
that people would criticize you…
for being with someone like me.
All the things you just said,
all the decisions you made,
you never asked me
if I was okay with them.
You always think for me.
You've never once asked for my input.
But somehow…
I'm always the first…
to get hurt by you.
Sun.
What are you doing?
Let's just call it off.
Ongsa?
Are you okay?
Can we talk later?
Of course, dear.
We can talk later.
Thank you.
I'll go talk to her.
What should I do?
Sun. Sun…
It's okay, Ongsa. It's okay.
She doesn't want to be with me anymore.
I didn't mean for things
to turn out this way, Alpha.
It's okay, Ongsa.
It's all right.
Just let it out.
Why are you giving me your pork, Mawin?
Because I know you like it.
Eat up.
Charoen, you should eat up too.
It's my meatless day today.
Humans.
Can I sit with you guys?
-Of course.
-Sit down. Take a seat.
-Come here, Aylin.
-Thank you.
"Thank you."
Hello, human senior Ton,
human senior Mawin.
Hi.
Hello, Luna's girlfriend.
Oh, look. These single-ass people
are teasing us.
-Wow.
-That hurts.
Human senior, stop being clingy.
-Stop that cutesy voice too.
-Why?
-Don't bump your head against mine.
-But I want to.
People in love are making me jealous.
Right? When will we have what they have?
I would love to volunteer, sweetie.
Eat properly.
-Eat up. Just stuff yourself.
-No.
You cling to her like a monkey.
Hey, Sun.
-Hey.
Eat with us.
Sit down. Take a seat.
I'm eating with Dear and the girls today.
Ah. Okay.
Why isn't she sitting with us today?
She always does.
Right.
Ongsa.
You all right?
Ongsa and Sun broke up.
-What?
How is that possible?
How come?
Tinh, what are you thinking about?
About something I can't quite figure out.
What are you talking about?
Do you think love is sustainable?
I think it is.
People say that love is the engine
that keeps lives going.
Whoa.
Do we need to be so reliant on love?
It's just what I heard.
Honestly, I don't understand it either.
But my mom said that love
has an expiration date.
Like the love Dad gave Mom.
Once it expired,
they got divorced.
So the answer to your question is
love isn't sustainable, right?
I guess so.
But I don't think that applies
to Ongsa and Sun.
What do you mean?
Maybe even though your love
hasn't expired yet,
if you don't understand each other,
you still break up anyway.
Tinh, you're so cool.
Why the compliment all of a sudden?
Your thoughts about love are so cool.
No wonder I like you.
What kind of "like" is that?
The kind that…
has no expiration date.
Though you like me as a brother,
I will like you this way forever.
Hey!
You again, Ton?
I picked a frangipani for you
because it's white and pure
just like your heart, Charoen.
But this flower is known
to be inauspicious.
Isn't that plumeria?
They're the same flower, Ton.
Hey, Ton. What are you doing here?
I'm here to hit on Charoen.
-What?
Ton! You like Charoenporn?
That's right.
Truly. Deeply.
Madly.
Then can I truly ask you a question?
Of course, Charoen.
What makes you like me?
Everything about you.
Can you be more specific?
I like that you're a demure person.
Then you can also like Kongkwan.
She's more demure than I am.
But I like you
for your Dhamma-loving heart as well.
Then you can like a nun.
Why do you have to reject me so hard?
Because I don't understand
why you like me.
Love isn't easy like in romantic movies.
To me, love is like an art film.
How?
It's incomprehensible,
but you can tell it's good.
Wow. That's sharp.
Dear, Vi, Kongkwan,
am I heartbroken?
Why?
Why am I heartbroken?
Because you belong to everyone.
You shouldn't belong to just one person.
So that's what it is.
It's so hard to be me.
I love you all.
Don't look at her, human.
That's right.
Whatever you want, you can tell us.
I want Sun back.
Can you guys give me that?
Tough one.
Do you want
Luangpu Sek's holy water instead?
No.
Let me console you.
I know a special spell
that can heal the downhearted.
What spell?
Hands.
Susu sasa patangka patangki.
Susu sisi patangki patangka.
Why does your spell sound familiar?
Do you feel better?
I guess I do.
And your spell smells quite nice.
What kind of spell has a smell?
The kind that comes from this
seven-souled centipede lozenge.
It's my family's product.
It consists of Siamese cassia,
sickle senna,
sacred lotus, star fruit, papaya…
A forced proximity scene.
The main character is walking towards us.
Sun.
Damn. That hurt.
She's in a terrible state of shock.
Look after her.
I have class.
Hey. Aylin.
Aylin. Stay.
It's okay, Ongsa.
Let's just go.
The teacher might get mad.
Let's go retrieve the ball.
Why are you doing this, Ongsa?
Doing what?
Do you really think I don't see you?
You go up the rooftop.
The Earth without the Sun is not livable!
Hey, Ongsa.
What's the matter?
Sun doesn't love me, Alpha.
You were acting unhinged,
trying to catch the sun out in the field.
There's only one sun left now.
At least I'm visible to this sun.
-The sun!
-Ongsa.
-Don't run.
-The sun!
-Stop.
And you've sent me 768 messages.
Have you been counting?
Seriously?
I feel bad.
I want to say I'm sorry
but I don't know what to do.
I've never been heartbroken before.
So you do what characters in movies
or music videos do?
Right?
Do you not care
how your actions will make me feel at all?
How do you feel?
Look up.
I said look up.
Ongsa.
Do you have any idea…
how much I love you?
If you do,
then why did you choose to leave me?
Because you've never understood me.
Not even once.
You don't understand what I want.
What can I do to earn your forgiveness?
Can you please tell me?
I just want you to love me…
like I love you.
I love you too, so much.
How is that different?
You don't understand me.
You've never understood me at all.
Ongsa.
Your mom and I would like to have a word.
I'm tired today.
Can we talk some other time?
It'll take just a minute.
Have a seat.
What is it?
Alpha and Aylin told us about you and Sun.
-Dad, Mom, I…
-Ongsa, my dear.
Don't worry.
We're not blaming you for that.
Aren't you guys upset that
I was seeing Sun?
Why would we be?
We are okay with whoever you like or love.
We want to say, though,
that we don't want this to happen again.
I don't want you to lie
or hide things from me.
I am sorry.
I did it because…
I was afraid…
that you would be alarmed.
that you would be disappointed in me
because I like girls.
Why would we be disappointed?
Ongsa.
You can always talk to us directly
about anything.
Don't come up with things on your own.
I know you care a lot about other people,
but I want you to stop thinking for them.
Stop being afraid
of what other people think
and be more considerate of yourself
and the ones close to you.
Maybe you will see something
you overlooked before.
Human, stop thinking for others.
And stop acting weird
and go get Sun back.
I understand now.
Sun.
Sun, it's me, Ongsa.
Please come out and talk to me.
Sun.
Sun, please come out and talk to me.
Sun, come downstairs, please.
You don't have to say anything.
You can just listen.
Sun. Talk to me.
Please.
Sun. I'm at your gate.
I'll be waiting here.
Please pick up the phone.
Sun!
I'll be waiting right here
until you come out.
Sun.
Ongsa.
Alpha. Why are you here?
I came to see how you were.
How's it going?
You haven't talked to her yet?
Is she ever gonna talk to me?
It's okay.
Though you don't succeed today,
you can always come back tomorrow.
What if I don't succeed tomorrow?
Ongsa, constant dripping…
Wears away a stone?
…makes a stone wet.
What kind of joke was that?
I don't want you to feel so down.
Sun is still mad.
She might not be ready to talk to you yet.
It's late. Let's go home.
You can come back again tomorrow.
Don't forget to bring mosquito repellent.
There are lots of them here.
Let's go.
There's no point in standing here.
Come back again tomorrow, okay?
Come on.
Go home.
Ongsa.
You talk to her.
I'll wait at home.
I came
because I wanted to apologize to you.
I'm sorry for acting like a crazy person
these past few days.
I was silly.
But I know now…
that what I did didn't fix what I am.
Do you realize now…
what the issue is?
We broke up…
because I cared too much
about other people's opinions.
I was so afraid
of what others would think or feel
that I overlooked the feelings
of someone close to me.
The most important person to me.
I was so afraid people would think less
of you for being with someone like me.
So afraid that I decided
not to tell my own parents.
You must've felt so hurt.
I am sorry.
But I know what you want now.
I…
want to love you.
I want to believe in our love.
I'm sorry…
for not understanding you at all.
I'm truly sorry.
Ongsa, I…
Sun.
Please forgive me.
Please allow me back into your orbit.
Aunt Aor, Uncle Nop,
this human senior
would like to spend the night.
She is studying with human cousin.
Good evening.
I hope you don't mind me sleeping over.
Not at all.
Where is Alpha?
She's out helping human Ongsa
reconcile with human Sun.
Aren't you helping them?
Human cousin told me to wait for you here.
Alpha was right.
You wouldn't be of much use
even if you went.
Are you saying…
I'm useless?
Aunt Aor, Uncle Nop, human senior
isn't spending the night anymore.
Hey. I was just kidding.
Don't touch me.
You guys are so sweet
an army of ants is heading our way.
Seeing them like this reminds me
of back when I was hitting on you.
Back when you gave me flowers every day?
Cheesy.
Hey, she came around because I did that.
Uncle Nop, you are the best.
You're my idol.
Aylin, wait for me.
Wait.
I've been studying for hours.
It's exhausting.
I feel sore.
I'm wondering if anyone here
wants to give me a massage.
Aylin, aren't you going to respond--
What?
She's out.
Are you really sleeping?
Aylin?
Are you asleep?
THAI GENERAL APTITUDE TEST 5
Human senior, what are you doing?
So, you've been awake?
I was really asleep.
But then your loud noise woke me.
When did you wake up?
When you called my name.
You poked my cheek.
Then why did you pretend to be asleep
when you were already awake?
I wanted to know
what you were going to do.
Do you know it now?
Just keep reading
and stop getting distracted.
How was that me getting distracted?
You're a bad girl, human senior.
You took advantage of me.
It's not taking advantage if you're awake.
Yeah?
Yes.
You took advantage of me.
It's not taking advantage if you're awake.
So, this is how you wanna play it?
I'm sleepy. I'm going to sleep.
I don't believe you.
-You did that.
-I'm sleepy.
You're not sleepy.
Aylin, get up.
-Human senior, stop annoying me.
-You sneaky little girl.
I want to sleep.
Sun, are everything all right?
Well, last night, Ongsa came to see me.
She apologized.
Isn't that good?
It is good, but…
-But?
I'm so devoted to love.
I'm willing to do anything
or even change myself for someone I love.
But if one day I feel like my love
is stronger than hers,
or like I try harder than her,
like when I decided not to join
the exchange program for her,
I will be the one who ends up feeling bad.
Ongsa and I will fight.
Then, we will break up again.
I don't want to feel that way
about Ongsa again.
Sun, I understand your commitment to love.
But a healthy love should allow you
to walk together at the same pace.
You don't have to entirely change yourself
for the other person.
You don't have to change to the point
where you become someone else.
When you love someone,
you should love who they truly are.
That's right.
You can be yourself
but also find a well-balanced approach.
If you completely change yourself
to be loved,
one day, you'll feel so uncomfortable
that you'll no longer want
the other person in your life.
You should learn to love.
Learn to love without losing who you are.
So, what should I do?
Every relationship comes with conflicts.
Your mom and I
have been married for 20 years,
yet, as you see,
we're still very much in love.
If two people truly love each other,
they'll eventually find a way
to work through their problems together.
So, what do you two think I should do?
I'd like you to think it through.
You don't have to choose just one path.
You can love Ongsa
and follow your dream at the same time.
Come on. Let's eat.
The porridge is getting cold.
Sun.
Have you been waiting long?
Not really. I don't mind waiting anyway.
I miss the first time we met here.
Do you recall?
I do.
You gave me the bracelet.
Which is back on your wrist again.
Without it,
I feel like something is missing.
It's become important to me.
I'm glad to hear that it's important.
Everything you've given me is important.
Ongsa.
I'd like to say sorry.
Sorry for what?
For being silly too.
All I wanted was for you to understand me.
I expected you to be who I wanted,
but I didn't understand you at all.
I tried to change myself for you
because I thought that if I worked hard,
our love would carry on.
But I was wrong.
I was so attached to you
that you felt uncomfortable.
But I know now what is right.
Ongsa.
I want to join the US exchange program.
I want to follow my dream.
That's great.
I'm glad you've decided to do that.
I believe you can do it.
And you will be happy doing it.
Thank you, Ongsa.
Sun.
Is something wrong?
There's one thing…
that I'm not so sure about.
What is it?
If I get the scholarship…
I'll have to live there for a year.
It's far away.
It's too far for you to come and visit.
How will we be?
The exams are finally over!
We'll see each other less next year.
Will you promise to be this lovely Aylin
for me forever?
I got the scholarship. I will be an
exchange student in the US, Ongsa!
So you won't get to see her for a year.
Even if Sun were to live in outer space,
I'd find a way to contact her.
You promise, Sun?
I promise.
Let's shoot a video
to capture memories for Sun.
Every moment?
Every moment,
especially the romantic moments.