(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 28=
(Yuzao Pleasure House)
Simu,
if you had exposed it later,
I would have believed
it was my own story.
I haven't seen you for days.
I just wanted to see
how you would surprise me.
What makes you
collect stories here?
I've always been fond
of listening to stories.
Didn't you know?
There are plenty of stories in the Void.
Why do you waste time and energy
listening to the mortals' trivialities?
Those are even stories of resentment.
I love those stories
that are vivid
with a life of their own.
Simu, you...
You want to be human?
Do you want me to be that?
There's too much work in the Void.
Why did you suddenly come to see me?
Three layers
of unknown zones popped up
in the Void Valley.
I accidentally broke
the outermost layer.
So I came here to confirm
whether you trapped Bai Sanxing
in the Valley.
In that case,
I need to work with Jiang Ai
to repair the outermost layer.
We must never let him get away again.
He isn't in there.
That's where I keep
the belongings of the former sovereign
just in memory of him.
If you want to get in there,
I'll let you in.
So it's for the memory
of you and your father.
Sorry for the offense.
It doesn't matter.
I put you in charge
of all the affairs.
It's good to be cautious.
My Lady,
Young Master Xu deeply admires you.
He's here to see you.
Miss He,
sorry to bother you.
She is
all mine tonight.
Don't mess around.
Your father will know.
You stay out of this.
Where's she?
Is she still here?
She doesn't want to see you.
Does she not want to see me?
Or do you not dare to let her see me?
You're a general,
but you act like a lovelorn husband.
How funny.
Try something else.
Provocation won't work on me.
Or...
We can make a bet.
Haven't you wanted me dead?
Then let's fight.
If I win,
you tell me where she is.
If I lose,
you'll be satisfied.
You're not worthy.
You don't dare?
You have a death wish.
Without spirit power,
you may not be a match for me.
Then I'll give you what you want.
Oh, I forgot.
You can't feel pain.
You saw the 22 graves,
didn't you?
Are you so eager to be the 23rd?
Maybe there will be a 24th
and a 25th.
No one can truly have her.
Now, she could be
sitting in some corner,
mocking your foolish infatuation!
You've been crazy about her
for over 300 years.
So what have you really got?
Young Master Xu?
- Yeah.
- Don't just stand there.
Get him up!
Is that all you've got?
She wouldn't care
whether you live or die.
Like I said,
you aren't worthy.
My bet paid off.
You keep seeking pleasure.
You're an official.
But you fought for a top beauty!
Who in this city
doesn't know
you have feelings for Miss Wang?
Will Duke Pei just let you
marry her?
And Fang Xianye!
He fights you on everything!
And you ruined your own reputation!
You've disgraced
our whole family!
From this day on,
behave yourself and prepare
for the wedding.
I'll handle
all the other things!
I requested His Majesty to approve
your marriage to the 5th prince.
I don't think your father
will disobey His Majesty.
We'll be family soon.
Just rest easy and wait
to be my daughter-in-law.
Your Grace,
the edict hasn't been issued.
Nothing is certain.
I know Duan Xu also wants to marry you.
But his family can't give any support
to your family.
Besides, Duan Xu is very arrogant.
He'll get into trouble sooner or later.
If you marry him,
a sword will be hanging over your head.
If he's caught in trouble,
your family can't stay out of it.
I believe you're clever enough.
You will weigh the pros and cons.
So it's you who have a treaty
with Song Xingyu.
Song Xingyu,
trying to run away?
Your...
Your Lordship.
I can no longer stay in this city.
He... He Simu
is going to find me.
Don't forget our treaty.
Even if you have the Glazed Pagoda,
I can still find you.
I... I'll give you
all the puppet spirits
I've made.
Please let me go.
Let me leave this city.
Otherwise, He Simu
will kill me.
Our great plan is nearly complete.
Once it's complete,
you no longer need to hide.
And I'll double the treasures
I've promised you.
Keep collecting Spirit Aura for me.
I'll handle
Her Grace.
During our last meeting,
I left without telling you.
So I came to apologize.
No need to apologize, Mr. Duan.
Mother told me
that you went after some bandits.
State affairs come first.
That's not true.
I just saw my beloved lady.
Do you know the plan
of our fathers?
In this city,
only a few people
are of marriageable age.
We don't have many choices.
So Miss Wang...
How about you marry me?
Your Lordship,
a letter from Consort Yu.
(To Duke Pei)
(Wang and Duan will get married.
Do something.)
Get Fang Ji to me.
Yes.
Great Ancestor,
what did I tell you that day?
They're finally in love, aren't they?
Oh, Great Ancestor.
I often think
you're more human than I am.
Ziji, look.
The plantain's color doesn't look
like something a spirit
who can't see colors
would paint.
It's beautiful.
That's because you're lazy, ignorant,
inattentive,
and unsuccessful.
But in my opinion,
it doesn't matter
whether poor General Duan loves her.
He must marry someone
his clan and Chancellor Du
have designated.
What?
You don't think so?
You don't know Duan Xu.
If I did,
what should I think?
He's best at pretending to obey.
No one can make him do anything
he doesn't want to do.
And he won't marry anyone
he doesn't like.
Something about that girl
must have attracted him.
Or she can help him
fulfill his wish.
He won't let himself be mistreated.
I've never seen you
so patient and familiar
with a mortal.
I care about him.
But this care
is only temporary.
It's even shorter
than his fleeting life.
That's too bad.
Duan Xu will have bad luck.
The court is in turmoil.
His marriage
may be a bumpy ride.
He'll have to miss
the lucky day I picked.
Great Ancestor,
will you really not
steal the bridegroom?
Get lost.
Assassin!
Protect Mr. Fang!
Something's not right.
Don't come out here.
Leave now!
Leave!
Who wants me dead?
Obviously my father, who sees you
as a major threat.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Duan Xu,
D-U-A-N, X-U.
My father, Duan Chengzhang,
wants you dead.
I read your essays.
They're excellent.
They shouldn't disappear from the world.
You should uphold justice
and give people a good life
as the sages said.
I've heard weapons
are the tool of evil
or virtue.
I'll be the tool of evil.
You'll be the tool of virtue.
What do you say?
So he hates me that much.
You've begun to shine.
You'll just be in more danger.
Shall I get Luoxian
out of Yuzao Pleasure House
to protect you for now?
No way.
The court is in turmoil.
We need her intel
from Yuzao Pleasure House.
Oh, I have something to tell you.
The corruption case took a turn.
Sun Changde of the Imperial Stud
backtracked.
Did he say
the 3,000 warhorses weren't phantoms,
but died of plague?
Something worse.
He even said
someone threatened and ordered him
to report this case to frame
the Minister of the Imperial Stud
and the Minister of War.
I guess Duke Pei
ordered him
to backtrack.
You and I both know
the corruption case is absolutely true.
But you forged
some of the evidence.
If they dig further,
they'll trace it back to you.
Let's take things
as they come.
Soon,
things will turn around.
Oh,
let me introduce someone.
Now?
Right here?
Someone
who matters most.
Someone I can't let go of
after trying really hard.
He Simu.
Simu,
can you show my friend
your true form too?
Simu,
this is my close friend,
Fang Xianye.
Xianye,
this is He Simu,
Sovereign of Spirits.
Sovereign?
Why did you call me out?
I didn't give you the right
to summon me
for fun.
I want to make a deal.
What conditions?
You come to my wedding.
Simu,
I want you to come to my wedding
as part of our deal.
♪I go alone in the night without end♪
♪I can't remember the seasons
or the passing years♪
♪Wishful thoughts creep onto my brows♪
Are you sure
you won't use this deal
on something more valuable?
Valuable?
I want you to see me in my wedding gown.
It's once in a lifetime.
Isn't it valuable?
♪Countless wayfarers roam the world♪
♪Luckily, I share a fate with you♪
Here, the invitation.
I humbly invite you.
On the 18th day of the sixth month,
the banquet will be served at my place.
I look forward to your presence.
May it bring joy
and lead to a blessed union.
♪But I fear♪
♪The world can't hold them♪
♪You always stay with me♪
Please don't decline.
♪See the world I've never seen♪
♪However the years may wind♪
All right.
I'll go.
Foxy.
Congratulations.
♪I open my eyes♪
Who is she?
My beloved woman.
Woman?
She isn't even human.
Could she be a spirit?
You told me she was...
Fang Ji,
how about you have a child
and I'm his honorary father?
Or...
If you don't mind,
let me adopt him.
A madman like you
should end up alone.
(Yueran Fragrance)
Master Xuan,
get me some superb amber.
Master Xuan?
It's you, Miss Duan.
Want ingredients?
Get me the best amber
for my fragrant powder.
I will make
the finest and sweetest powder
and wear the newest style of clothes
for my brother's wedding.
Make an identical sachet for me.
The ingredients are agarwood, amber,
storax, mint leaves,
bletilla, and benzoin.
All right.
Miss Duan,
please wait a minute.
Why do you stare at me?
I think your sachet
smells very good.
Did you blend the fragrance yourself?
What's its name?
Duan Shunxi.
It's done, Miss.
Hey, wait.
It doesn't smell right.
The bletilla is missing.
Miss Duan.
Sorry, Miss. I'll add it now.
Thank you.
(Maybe she's someone)
(who adores my brother.)
Master Xuan.
You don't look very well today.
Take care of yourself.
Young Master Xu's wedding
is a grand event in town.
You must be working hard on it.
Take care of yourself too.
Thank you.
Biqing.
That lady
somehow got to know
your aromatic ingredients.
Then she had the identical fragrance.
It will make her think of you.
Come on, Xu.
Your marriage
will break the heart
of young ladies in town.
Handsome disaster.
Are you saying
an ingredient was missing
and she didn't realize?
Strange, isn't it?
How lovely.
Hey, Xu.
You're getting married.
You must not
find other girls lovely.
Xu,
didn't you say
you loved someone?
Are you giving up on her?
Look, Xu.
This is my new sachet.
Smell it.
What do you think?
Mimosa flower.
Eupatorium.
Fleeceflower vine.
Magnolia flower bud.
Agastache.
That's all?
Yes.
Two more.
Fennel and lily.
Well, mistakes happen.
(I can't smell it all.)
(So this is the price
of exchanging senses.)
I'm getting old, anyway.
Jingyuan,
I'm afraid
I'll often make mistakes in this game.
You're still young.
Don't say that.
Age always
weakens the senses.
That's a natural rule.
(Lotusborn Pavilion)
Great Ancestor?
Great Ancestor,
where have you been?
I bought a sachet.
You can't smell anything.
Why do you need a sachet?
I can't smell.
But I like it
when this scent is on me.
Any problem?
No, no.
What kind of gifts
do mortals give for a wedding?
It depends on whose wedding it is.
You won't give Duan Xu a gift, will you?
He invited me to his wedding.
I can't go without a gift.
Come on, Great Ancestor.
You always hate
going to weddings or funerals.
You didn't even attend
the wedding or funeral
of my parents.
You really
favor him
and prioritize love.
He's different.
It's his condition for sense exchange.
I've realized
you're tolerant of him for no reason.
This is just a deal.
I happened to prepare
a big gift for him.
The horse administration case
is being investigated.
The key witness backtracked,
accusing Duan Xu
of forging some evidence
to attack the two cities.
Duke Pei's men
are keeping an eye
on this case.
I guess they'll probably
give him more trouble.
And I...
What I'm working on
can do Duan Xu a big favor.
This is your gift.
What should I give him?
You've been getting along with him.
Don't you know what he likes?
Come on, Great Ancestor.
When you gave gifts,
you used to be decisive.
Why are you so cautious now?
You still have some days.
It's hard to prepare a gift
that brings real joy.
That's right.
Farewell.
The Fire Star is off track.
A lucky day is coming.
Young Master Xu,
want to see the top beauty?
Unfortunately,
she was bored with stories
and then left this place.
I'm here for Luoxian.
But Young Master,
Luoxian is receiving an important guest.
She can't see you now.
Mr. Duan.
Luoxian,
Mr. Duan...
I must see Luoxian today.
Mr. Fang, do you mind?
Don't be angry, gentlemen.
Sharing music is also a pleasure.
I'd like to play music and sing for you.
(Wang Jin, Vice Minister
of the Judicial Review)
What a nice day today.
The top three scholars
of the same imperial exam
are all here.
Shall we close the net?
I've prepared the net
and had it in place.
I've heated the stove
with the ingredients.
We're waiting for you.
The fish is in the net.
We'll close the net
and eat the fish.
To Great Liang.
To people in the 17 Prefectures.
(Lotusborn Pavilion)
- Prophet.
Hey, destined one.
Won't you return the umbrella?
Give this umbrella to the Prophet.
Tell him Duan Shunxi came by.
The destined one must return
the Red Lotus Umbrella himself.
This way, please.
This place is impressive.
It takes a lot of trouble
to see you.
One must let go of his worries
before he finds peace in himself.
Every step here
will erase a lie.
There are white lotuses
in the front pond
and red lotuses
in the hidden inner pond.
This pavilion divides this place
just like dividing one's heart.
One side is full of peace
while the other is full of heat.
But you've never believed in gods.
Sorry to have you come
to my Lotusborn Pavilion.
Since you're here,
ask me what has confused you.
For example,
what's the relationship
between He Simu and me?
Since you know what I want
and you're prepared,
tell me about it.
You should know
He Simu had four family members.
Her parents, her aunt, and her uncle.
I am
the twentieth generation
of her aunt and uncle.
In private, I call her Great Ancestor.
My parents died young.
When I was little,
she took care of me for a while.
She watched me grow up.
Actually, I invited you here
because I prepared a gift
for your wedding.
Ziji.
(In the fifth month, spring ends)
(and peonies fall.)
Everyone knows
Consort Yu loves peonies most.
Are you saying
the 5th prince...?
I heard you have a photographic memory.
So you don't need it again.
Thank you for your help.
Is this your gift?
- Or...
- Great Ancestor never cares
about politics.
I'm the one
who prepared this.
But we're strangers.
Why do you help me?
I don't mean to help you.
When I was little,
I secretly found a journal
of Great Ancestor.
The one in that journal
was totally different
from what she is now.
The young girl named He Simu
was arrogant
and spoiled.
Her mother said
red suited her best.
So she made
over a dozen red robes.
She actually couldn't see colors.
But she said she loved them.
The journal was thick.
It recorded
small daily routines.
About friends,
about families,
and about partners.
♪Lingering for a fleeting moment♪
♪Was once touched by laughing tears♪
One page said,
"Father died.
I'd return to the Spirit World."
♪I'd be a guest in a sweet dream♪
Then nothing more was recorded.
I used to think
Great Ancestor was weird.
But I couldn't tell
what was weird about her.
After reading that,
I suddenly realized
that time had long stopped
for her.
It stopped 300 years ago
when her father passed away.
♪Wander to the other shore
with the lantern♪
She still wears
her favorite clothes
and does things
her family members taught her
and expected her to do.
She's becoming unfamiliar
with this changing world.
She's angry
and frustrated.
Just like the journal
that stopped abruptly.
When the last two lines were written...
♪Dawn and dusk rise and set♪
She no longer needed to be understood.
She only needed to be feared.
She buried those she valued
in the journal
and froze everything in time.
Over the past 300 years,
no one has entered her world.
♪Accompanied by eternity♪
♪As all things turn and flow♪
♪Whether I stay or go, I'm all alone♪
(Sovereign's Hall)
Mr. Duan,
either you're her spell bearer
or whatever,
I want you
to get her frozen time
to move again.
This is
why I'm helping you.
♪As stars shift and change places♪
♪A century is like a dream♪
♪Let me journey across them all♪
Thank you, Prophet.
In that case,
I have another favor to ask.
What is it?
Her Grace has a pearl.
She and I exchange senses
via the Pearl.
Do you know about that?
I know it very well.
I want you
to give me a blessed flower.
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪