Subtitle by Kisskh.Asia Translator [ Admin Qari ]
May I be like the stars
and you like the moon.
As long as the world remains,
so shall we.
I only wish to stay with the one I love,
watching every sunrise and sunset.
I want to be with you forever.
Eternals and demons walk different paths.
You and she are ultimately different.
Have you ever
truly cared for me?
No.
Never.
In this life and the next, through all lifetimes…
May we live and die together,
and share life and death as one.
[Moonlight Mystique]
[Episode 9]
Why is there an evil aura in Yi City?
What is the evil aura?
Heaven and earth produce spiritual energy.
Eternals and demons all cultivate with this spiritual energy.
Yet evil aura
specifically comes from evil cultivators.
Evil cultivators?
They cultivate by devouring essence.
Since there's an evil aura,
there must be
evil cultivators in Yi City.
Devouring essence...
The Desireless Stone led us to this Yi City.
So is the appearance of the evil cultivator
related to the next Contemplation?
Bai Shuo?
Bai Shuo!
Fan Yue? Fan Yue!
Mana is banned in Yi City.
But it's not working on her?
Fan Yue!
I once saw this monster in the Desireless Stone.
Let's go.
Shuo.
Stay out of the Bright Moon Palace's business.
Who are you?
How dare you break into Yi Palace?
Yi Palace?
Don't be rude.
Back off.
Yes, sir.
I didn't expect you, the Master of Bright Moon Palace,
would join the competition in person.
Earlier today, with the Eternals and demons around,
I couldn't expose our collaboration with you.
Please forgive me
for my disrespect.
Let's cut to the chase.
Just now,
I saw some evil aura entering Yi Palace.
Did you see it wrong, Master Fan?
There has never been any evil cultivator in Yi City.
How could there be an evil aura?
It can't be wrong.
We've been chasing him all the way here.
We saw him entering Yi Palace.
Go with me to find him if you don't believe us.
Since you saw it with your own eyes, Master Fan,
I will report this to His Majesty right away
and search the palace.
However, this is Yi Palace after all.
It's in the dead of night.
I'm afraid it's improper for you to enter the palace now.
I've told you about the evil aura and the evil cultivator.
Whether you investigate it or not
is up to you.
Evil cultivators are banished by the Three Races
If there's really an evil cultivator in the city,
our Yi Clan will not let him go for sure.
Let's go.
You could clearly tell that
the lieutenant of the King of Yi tried to stop us on purpose
from entering the palace to investigate the monster.
Why did you give in so easily?
If that monster is really related to the King of Yi,
what do you think
you can find out in that way?
You'd even die in there.
You don't need to make up these excuses.
As the prestigious Master of Bright Moon Palace,
how could you let them shut you out of the palace gate
just for your worry
about my life?
Master.
Master,
did you hunt that monster down?
That monster
entered Yi Palace.
You came just in time.
Tell me,
who on earth are you?
I found you kinda weird
before we entered Yi City.
You seem to be very sensitive to things in here.
Spiritual power is banned in Yi City.
Even Fan Yue is restricted by the rules.
But you can use your spiritual power.
Are you a Yi citizen?
Yi citizens are born with limited spiritual power.
But your power is so strong that you can kill a thousand with a single strike.
It's enough to make you the guardian of Bright Moon Palace.
Are you a human or a demon?
It's none of your business.
None of my business?
I made a deal with your Bright Moon Palace.
Since it's a deal, we should trust each other.
There's a lot going on in Yi City right now.
Your identity is fishy.
I can stop the deal.
It's not up to you.
You should have known
the real identity of Tian Huo, right?
Tian Huo's identity
has nothing to do with claiming the Heart Flames
and gathering the Five Contemplations.
Fan Yue,
I know you are quite mighty,
and I can't beat you.
But it doesn't mean
I have to accept your schemes and deception.
I can ignore her identity,
but I need trust and respect for our cooperation.
Tian Huo,
you may leave now.
Yes, Master.
Tian Huo
is indeed a Yi citizen.
As for why she has the extraordinary spiritual power out of limits,
this is her own business.
It has nothing to do with us.
Fine.
Everyone has secrets.
I can stop asking about it.
But since she is a Yi citizen,
she must know this city well.
When looking for the entrance to Yi City,
I almost died in the sand formation.
Did Tian Huo provide any clues?
Tian Huo's been by my side for seven years.
She's never had any contact with Yi City over the past seven years.
The entrance to Yi City changes every year.
None of us—
neither you, me,
nor Tian Huo—
know the specific location.
But now that we're in Yi City,
is she still clueless
about the three Heart Flames?
Yes.
So,
you've never doubted her?
Never.
You can totally trust her,
but why should I?
Because you have to trust me completely.
I can't trust anyone
except myself.
Here's my promise to protect you.
I can assure you that,
as long as I'm alive,
I will let no one hurt you.
Sounds quite touching.
Fan Yue,
you're giving it your all
to protect the Desireless Stone,
not me.
♫A lifetime of guarding everything with you♫
♫Crossing the abyss to fulfill our vow♫
♫I'll leap without a thought for tomorrow♫
What?
Isn't that the truth?
♫This moment feels like forever♫
Of course, you can think that way.
♫I've missed too much time in my life♫
So,
♫I'll throw myself into this flame for you♫
don't make any reckless moves,
and don't be delusional.
Zero in on looking for the Heart Flame and Five Contemplations.
♫Even if I'll perish♫
That's all
♫At least I can still kiss your face♫
I need you to do.
♫Burn out my waning moon♫
OK! That's all!
Once we're done with it,
♫In exchange for a lifetime of passion♫
there's gonna be
no more ties between us!
It's been seven years since I was last in Yi City.
Feels like it's changed a lot.
Even a person
can change a lot
in seven years, not to mention a city.
I know Hua Lin well.
Everything happening in Yi City
is under his surveillance.
There's no way he doesn't know about the monster.
The Three Races forbid evil cultivation.
If that evil being is really related to the King of Yi,
then both the Eternal and Demon Races
will surely go after the entire Yi Clan.
Don't worry, Master.
I've cut ties with the Yi Clan
ever since my departure seven years ago.
Now I'm back here just to get the Contemplation for you.
I will get to the bottom of the monster as soon as possible.
General, what's wrong?
You go first.
I'll be right there.
Yes, General.
General, you're really vigilant.
I watched you grow up.
How could I not know it was you?
Princess.
I've already cut ties with Yi City.
I'm not your Princess.
Hua Hong...
Don't call me that.
I am the guardian of Bright Moon Palace, Tian Huo.
Lady Tian Huo,
how have you been these years?
I'm not here to catch up with you.
Why is there a monster in the palace?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Stop playing dumb here.
I'm patrolling with the guards.
Nothing suspicious was found.
Don't worry.
If there is really an evil being in the palace,
His Majesty and I will show no mercy.
You're still as hypocritical
as before.
You clearly know
whether there's a demon in the palace.
If Eternals and demons find out about it,
I'm afraid the Yi City you've been swearing to protect
will fall apart.
The palace is a sacred place.
No evil beings are allowed here.
So you don't need to worry about that, Lady Tian Huo.
The fate of Yi City doesn't concern me.
Where is the second Heart Flame?
Since you're joining the Wutong Martial Arts Contest as Lady Tian Huo,
you should abide by the rules and keep it fair.
Who are you to talk about fairness with me?
No matter what,
I'm your uncle.
Uncle?
Yes.
You are my mother's sworn brother.
My grandfather raised you up.
The Mei Family helped you and the King of Yi get to where you are today
with all the glory.
But how did you treat her?
Now you wanna talk about fairness with me?
Where were you when my mother was forced to death?
The Mei Family has been loyal to Yi King for generations.
Your mother died for the whole Yi City.
If you insist on blaming her death
on me,
then do it.
I'll repay the Mei Family
with my life.
♫What kind of flower would never bear fruit?♫
Stop!
♫What kind of fruit never sees a flower?♫
Your Majesty.
♫Withstanding the stillness, you are a broken piece of me♫
♫I am the fruit to your flowers♫
You left years ago.
Why are you back now?
To get the Heart Flame,
you gotta rely on your real capacities.
What's your position
to be snooping around here?
Any position will do,
but it can never be a Yi citizen.
Since you're an outsider...
Wu Zhao,
arrest this intruder who dared
to trespass the palace.
♫Across thousands of miles♫
Your Majesty,
Lady Tian Huo is the guardian of Bright Moon Palace.
It's not the right time to mess with the Master of Bright Moon Palace.
Please think twice, Your Majesty.
Get lost!
Get out of the palace right now!
♫The pain of parting lingers♫
Get out of Yi City!
And never come back!
Once I get the Heart Flame,
♫ I light a lamp with no wick to carry me through the rest of my days♫
I'll never see you again.
♫Flowers in the wind, sand in the water♫
Your Majesty, you've been missing the Princess every day.
Now you finally met her today.
Why did you say those angry words?
She shouldn't be back now.
They have noticed him.
They won't let it go for sure.
At this point,
we have no choice but to play along with the plan
and advance it.
What about the Princess?
if she gets in the way,
show no mercy.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Senior Chong Zhao!
Where have you been so late at night?
Is Bai Shuo back?
I saw her going back to her room.
What happened?
Of course, you can think that way.
So,
don't make any reckless moves, and don't be delusional.
Zero in on looking for the Heart Flame and Five Contemplations.
That's all
I need you
to do.
That's right.
That's all.
Shuo.
I'm glad you're alright.
That monster...
Something is wrong with Yi City.
If there is no reason to stay,
you should leave immediately.
I know.
I saw
Fu Ling earlier today.
Sounds quite touching.
Fan Yue,
you're giving it your all
to protect the Desireless Stone,
not me.
Come in.
Did you see Hua Lin?
What did he say?
He denied his connection with the monster
and just asked me to get out of Yi City.
Looks like we need to grab
the Heart Flame real quick this time.
Although I don't know the King of Yi well,
he used to be a great figure with his reputation spreading everywhere.
As a father,
he hasn't seen you for seven years.
Yet he asked you to get out of Yi City as soon as he met you.
They might sound like angry words,
but he might be speaking the truth.
I'm afraid you've overthought it, Master.
He doesn't live up to his reputation.
He doesn't deserve to be a king,
much less my father.
No matter what,
the current priority
is to find the Heart Flame.
Why didn't you tell me that Fu Ling was there?
You'd definitely try to kill her if you saw her.
But that
wouldn't do you any good.
So,
you made a decision for me once again.
I just wanted to keep you safe.
That's your personal thought!
Chong Zhao,
I don't wanna quarrel with you because of this case.
I know I can't kill her now.
I will try to survive
and give a fatal blow to her and Zhen Yu in the future.
But Fu Ling came to Yi City.
This thing can't be as simple as it seems to be.
If you get any other information,
I hope you won't hide it from me.
Okay.
I promise you.
Good night.
If you need anything,
feel free to call me anytime.
Seems like
she can't completely break off with Chong Zhao.
Chong Zhao
can't get in the way of my plan.
What if he's in the way of something else?
What are you trying to say?
Nothing.
Please take a good rest, Master
♫The stars light up your eyes♫
♫You are my distant call♫
♫You are my first and last♫
♫My heart is trembling for you♫
♫In this moment where we embrace each other♫
♫Let's never let go♫
[Sihai Inn]
Lady Tian Huo, you've made a name with your prowess.
Yet your dining etiquette is so good.
Is it your Yi citizens' habit?
Don't talk when eating. Don't ask too much.
Sirs and madams,
a gentleman
just asked me to send you this box of cakes.
Please enjoy.
Where is he?
He just left.
Don't be too nosy.
Hua Yong.
[Hua Yong, Yi Clan, Prince of Yi]
Sister.
Don't call me that!
It's disgusting.
I told you
never to show up in front of me ever again.
I thought you came back
because you had forgiven me.
Forgive you?
Just a box of cakes,
and you want me to forget about everything from the past?
No, it's not like that...
Shut up!
I'm warning you one last time.
I've cut ties
with you.
If you show up again,
I will beat you up.
Stay out
of Tian Huo's business.
Who says I wanna get involved in her business?
Now that we've obtained the first Heart Flame,
I'm in a hurry to find the second one.
By yourself?
Can't I?
Where are you going to find it?
Since you haven't been honest with me, Master Fan,
why should I tell you everything?
Master,
what's wrong with her today?
Are you really letting her go alone?
She can walk by herself
and go anywhere she wants.
What if she runs into danger?
Danger?
It's her own decision.
There's no one else to blame if she dies.
Mommy,
what is this character?
"Citizen."
The "citizen" in "Yi citizen."
What's the difference between humans and Yi citizens?
There's not much difference.
They're all made of flesh and bones,
standing tall and upright.
It's you.
Why are you here?
I'm here to deliver the medicine for Hu.
Also,
I'm here to ask you something.
Hu, go play nearby.
I'll teach you to read later,
okay?
Okay.
Good girl.
What do you want to ask?
Do you know where the second Heart Flame is?
Heart Flames choose their owners themselves.
How would I know?
Then do you know there's a monster
in the city?
Did it attack you?
So, you knew it.
What is it?
No one knows what it is.
We only know that it first appeared
on a night seven years ago.
Seven years ago again?
That year, it bit many people in the city to death
and then disappeared for a long time.
After that, we heard about it from time to time.
Some said it was formed from the souls of deceased Yi citizens.
Some said it was a beast cultivated by an evil cultivator.
But there was no conclusion.
Later, His Majesty worried that there would be chaos among the people,
so he ordered us to stop discussing this matter.
Does it only come out at night?
Maybe.
No one has ever seen it during the day anyway.
Do you know anything else?
Don't ask too much
about Yi citizens.
I told you this
to repay your kindness to Hu.
Just now, you said
Yi citizens were no different from humans.
You were wrong.
Yi citizens' suffering
is not something Eternals, demons,
and you humans
can understand.
Go.
That's all I can say.
Your friend's been waiting for you over there for a long time.
Go back early.
It's not safe in the city at night.
Why did you follow me here?
Don't play dumb.
Don't act innocent after getting the benefit.
I knew you wouldn't let me die,
so I dared to come and go recklessly.
I advise you not to play your tricks
on me.
But you still came.
It won't happen again.
Got it.
It's getting late. Let's go back.
I don't want to meet the monster again.
Stop ordering me around.
Got it. Don't be so verbose.
I'm verbose?
You keep emphasizing your identity.
Aren't you verbose?
Say that again!
I dare not.
Your Majesty,
the first Heart Flame
has been sent to Bai Shuo as planned.
Bai Shuo is being protected by Fan Yue.
Even if Eternals and demons are not convinced,
they dare not speak out their anger.
Cold Spring Palace
has seen Yi City's good faith.
You're Lady Fu Ling from Cold Spring Palace.
Please forgive me for being disrespectful.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
You offered your blood as a sacrifice to King Yi's Sword
and made the two Heart Flames come into the world in advance.
The Grand Master was very touched.
Since we're cooperating,
we'll both benefit from it.
Surely I won't take it lightly.
Your Majesty, please hurry up
in case
something unfavorable happens.
It's over there, too!
Did you see the dark shape just now?
Hurry!
It's over there! Look!
It's over there!
-Over there.
What's over there?
A dark shape?
What is it?
It actually has an evil aura.
I think it must be an evil cultivator.
It's there, too. Look!
It's the monster from yesterday.
It went that way!
Over there!
Go after it!
Let's go! Hurry!
-Let's go!
-Let's go after it!
Don't you think it's suspicious?
The monster knew Eternals and demons wouldn't let evil cultivators go,
but it still came.
I know.
Yet you still want to chase it?
Only after chasing it
will we know what conspiracy is lying ahead.
Let's go.
Senior, shall we chase it?
You stay in the inn.
If anything happens, you can back us up anytime.
You two, come with me.
Yes.
Go!
-Hurry! It's over there!
-Go after it!
Hurry!
Over there!
Catch up with it!
Damn it!
The monster got away.
There's someone over there.
Where are we?
The Yi Clan Tomb.
The Yi Clan Tomb?
How come I don't see any tombstone?
Whose tomb is that?
Yi citizens have a custom
of burying the dead in the open without a tombstone.
However, it's not a Yi citizen buried in the tomb
but...
That's the Wutong Heart Flame.
-It's really the Wutong Heart Flame.
-Really?
Heart Flame?
Over there.
The quietness was so good.
Now, there are so many people
disturbing my peace.
Killing people
is not tiring.
Burying them
is.
What's going on?
Sir,
we are not here
to steal the Heart Flame.
Instead, we chased a monster here.
Since the monster is gone,
we shall take our leave.
Please forgive us
if we offended you.
Why are we leaving?
The Heart Flame is right over there.
It's dangerous here.
We'd better go back
and take some time to think of a solid plan.
This Heart Flame
is mine!
Calm down.
That's impossible.
Isn't there a Magic Restriction in Yi City?
Why can you use magic?
Are you a Yi citizen?
Master,
let's go now.
We can't leave.
Since you're here,
stay here
with me.
I don't care who you are.
I'm taking
this Heart Flame.
Tian Huo.
How did he turn into this?
This is what he originally looks like.
The Snow Lotus Holy Sword.
Could he
be...
Kneel down and bow.
Mr. Rong Xian.
How's that possible?
[Rong Xian, Eternal, Saint of Kunlun]
Didn't Mr. Rong Xian die 1,000 years ago?
How could someone who died 1,000 years ago still be here?
Rong Xian.
He's long dead.
I'll kill all of you, too!
Bastard Rong Xian,
I'll kill you!
Young Master Mu Jiu, why are you here?
[Mu Jiu, demon, Young Master of the Fox Clan]
How could this happen?
He is not Rong Xian.
He's just the resentment formed from Rong Xian's obsession.
Is he himself
buried in the tomb?
He was formed from resentment,
so he's not bound by the rules of Yi City.
We can't kill him,
but he can hurt us.
Doesn't that mean he's invincible?
We'll all die if we stay here any longer.
Let's come back for the Heart Flame
after finding a way
to eliminate the resentment.
The Fox Clan?
Get lost.
Get lost!
I must destroy this bastard's tomb today
to avenge the Fox Clan
and Saintess Ling Long!
Idiot.
Watch out!
Master, go.
Rong Xian's resentment is too strong.
My spirit shield won't last long.
Chong Zhao!
Don't come over here!
Bai Shuo!
Where are we?
Why are you in the Fox Clan's costume?
Yes.
Why are you in the Fox Clan's costume, too?
Well, you, too.
Who changed my clothes?
Why are you looking at me?
Could it be...
me?
Weren't we at the Yi Clan Tomb?
How did we suddenly get here?
Where are we?
[Kunlun]
This is my home, Kunlun.
Kunlun?
No.
Something's wrong here.
What's wrong?
Wuji Palace
was destroyed 1,000 years ago.
[Kunlun]
Wu.
I told you not to come, but you didn't listen.
If I hadn't sent the Fox Clan's letter of peace
up the mountain in advance,
you'd have been riddled
before entering the mountain gate
for breaking into Kunlun so rashly.
Who is she?
And who's Wu?
And you.
Qi.
Aren't you the most down-to-earth and stablest servant?
Why did you let the lady sneak out this time?
If anything goes wrong,
no punishment will be enough.
Qi?
Servant?
Me?
Lady?
What lady?
What family am I from?
What about me?
Who am I?
Look how dumb you are.
The Elder must have been out of his mind
to ask the three of you to help me steal the Snow Lotus.
Steal the Snow Lotus?
Especially you,
Ba.
You're usually the most impatient.
If Qi
hadn't been putting in a good word for you with the Elder,
he wouldn't have given you
the chance to make a contribution.
-When we enter Kunlun later,
-The Elder?
control your temper
and don't get into a fight on their turf.
Got it?
I'm Ba.
Ba is me.
Shall I say "got it"?
Aren't you usually good at quarreling?
Why aren't you talking today?
Say something.
Got it.
I won't quarrel with others.
What's going on?
The situation is unclear.
Let's listen more and talk less.
Young Chief Ling Long.
Our Sect Leader has received the Fox Clan's letter.
Please follow us into the mountain.
Ling Long?
[Ling Long, demon, Saintess of the Fox Clan]
Saintess of the Fox Clan!
Thank you.
Snow Lotus.
Saintess Ling Long.
Now I remember!
Let's go.
[Kunlun Sect, Eternal Race]
Everyone!
Hold your breath.
Concentrate.
As disciples of Kunlun,
always remember that the Fox Clan is vicious and cunning.
We, Kunlun,
see them as our mortal enemies.
Who can tell me what happened?
Wasn't I at Yi City just now?
How did I suddenly arrive at Kunlun?
Kunlun is the sworn enemy of the Fox Clan.
If I enter Kunlun,
it'll be like a sheep entering the tiger's den.
Stop!
What are you doing?
W-What are you doing?
Why is he walking over?
Is he going to kill me?
Should I make the first move?
But with so many of them,
I don't stand a chance!
Calm down.
No action unless
the enemy acts first.
Slacking off again? Start practicing now!
Practice?
Practice what?
As disciples of Kunlun,
we are practicing our swordsmanship, of course.
How did I become a disciple of Kunlun?
Kunlun Sword?
How could something so treacherous
end up in my hands?
Take it.
Make your move.
I'm full of demonic aura.
If I make a move,
wouldn't I be exposed immediately?
Could it be that
I'm going to perish here today?
If you are this lazy,
how will you kill fox demons in the future?
Make your move!
Let me test you.
Whatever.
If I die, so be it.
When did I learn the Kunlun Sword Technique?
Wait.
How did I become an Eternal?
Stop!
Rong Xian.
Wasn't Rong Xian at the Yi Clan Tomb just now?
If so, who is this?
What time is it now?
And who am I?
Sir.
Why are you fighting each other?
The Elder has ordered
for us disciples to practice our swordsmanship
so that we are ready to fight the Fox Clan any time.
But he slacked off
and refused to practice.
I...
I was just punishing him for a bit.
Why aren't you willing to practice your swordsmanship?
Why should I?
Is the sole purpose of spiritual cultivation and becoming a Kunlun disciple
to kill the Fox Clan?
Do we have nothing better to do?
I mean...
the Fox Clan haven't done
anything evil.
Aren't they just...
vain,
gluttonous,
and like to sunbathe every day?
There's no need to fight
the moment we meet.
Judging from what you said,
you seem to know a lot about the Fox Clan...
and seem to have some different views.
Great.
The Fox Clan sent its people to negotiate peace.
I am going to meet the Saintess of Fox Clan.
Come with me.
Saintess of the Fox Clan?
Could it be that...
Saintess Ling Long is alive in this damned place too?
Aren't you going to keep up?
You...
Cang Shan! Cang Shan!
It's useless.
They have entered
the illusion created out of Rong Xian's resentment.
Even if you break open Rong Xian's tomb,
you can only exist in the present time and space.
You won't be able to enter the illusion.
That monster
deliberately led the Eternals and demons towards the Yi Clan Tomb.
You wanted to make use of Rong Xian's resentment to kill the Eternals and demons.
Rong Xian's illusion
is the second stage of Wutong Martial Arts Contest.
If you desire the Heart Flame,
you must break through the illusion.
This is the rule.
Rong Xian's resentment has been building for a thousand years.
How can it be broken in a moment?
Well then, let's see if
Demon King from the Polar Region
lives up to his name.
I will say just one thing today.
If anything happens to our master,
I will certainly lead
our demons from Bright Moon Palace to crush Yi City.
At the very least,
Yi City has raised you.
You and your king have no grounds to speak of grace.
If my master does not return safely,
your entire city will pay the price.
I think I understand what's going on.
While Ling Ling is not here,
let's figure it out among ourselves.
This time, the Fox Clan came to Kunlun
seemingly for a peace negotiation,
but it's actually to steal the Snow Lotus of Kunlun
to extend the Chief's life.
But didn't Ling Long and Rong Xian
die a long time ago?
Could it be that the Desireless Stone
brought us back to a few thousand years ago?
This is not the true version of a thousand years ago.
This is the realm of illusion from Rong Xian's resentment.
Yi City's Magic Restriction?
This really is the realm of resentment.
What brought us in here was the Desireless Stone.
But what's trapping us now
is Rong Xian's resentment.
Why so?
If it weren't for his will,
we wouldn't have become
people who were already part of his memory.
Then, how will we get out?
If we follow his life until death,
this illusion will naturally be broken.
How could this be?
What if he lives for decades?
Are we going to remain here
and be foxes for decades?
The Saint wouldn't live for that long.
Oh right.
You're a Kunlun disciple.
Tell us then.
What happened a thousand years ago?