=Eight Hundred=
(Yingxiong Roller Skating Rink)
♪Today, I♪
♪Watch the snow
drift by in the cold night♪
♪Drifting afar with a chilled heart♪
♪Chasing in the wind and rain♪
♪Unable to distinguish
shadows in the mist♪
♪The wide sea and sky, you and I♪
♪Could we change? Who isn't changing?♪
♪How many times♪
Thanks.
Han Ning.
You're here.
Boss, give me two bottles of Jianlibao.
Alright.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
It's so crowded today.
♪The love in my heart,
who understands me?♪
♪Forgive me for being wild
and unfettered my whole life♪
♪I'm also afraid
that one day I might fall♪
♪Forsaking my ideals♪
♪Anyone can do that♪
♪What's there to fear
if one day it's just you and me?♪
Chief Liu.
You're here.
I'm here to report on my work.
Chief Liu, why are you...
Chief Liu, what's wrong with you?
(Yingxiong Roller Skating Rink)
Watch out.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you.
Next, I'm going
to perform another song for you.
I hope you'll like it.
I also wish you all
a great time here today.
=Episode 4=
(The Chain Trap)
(Fengyang Coal Mine Guesthouse)
Chief Liu,
quick, look.
What is she trying to say?
She's this sick,
why don't you take her to the hospital?
I can't manage all by myself.
I only think
of finding you when someone's sick.
I never think of going to the hospital.
Hold this, hold it higher.
Didn't we agree
that if I gave you the stuff,
you would leave?
I intended to leave.
I got robbed.
So what do you want?
What else?
Give me some more money.
And some more drugs.
I don't hit women.
Tell your Chen Hui to get over here.
Cut the crap with me.
What are you trying to do?
What else would I do?
Fifty thousand yuan
and five bottles of drugs.
It was fifty thousand last time,
and another fifty thousand now?
Are you crazy?
We can't give you fifty thousand.
I'm crazy?
When you tried
to blow me up with detonators,
weren't you pretty crazy too?
Who are you trying to scare, anyway?
Listen here, get the money ready
for me quickly.
You even have a knife?
Going to stab me?
Come on.
Stab me.
Stab me, come on.
Come on.
Weren't you capable? Stab me then.
Why the heck did you come back?
I was robbed.
Get another fifty thousand yuan ready,
plus five bottles of drugs.
I'll come to pick them up tomorrow.
Otherwise, you know what will happen.
How are you?
Are you okay?
Lu Yuan has gone mad.
Give me the knife.
It's okay.
Everything's fine.
I'm here.
It's over now.
You are...
Your fever has broken.
Rest a bit longer.
Did you set up the IV for me?
I am Chen Hongbing's wife.
My name is Ding Yue.
I'm a doctor.
Chief Liu,
you're awake?
Director Chen.
Are you feeling better?
Much better.
Her fever has already broken.
That's great.
Oh, right.
I couldn't find
any fruit for sale tonight.
Back at home, I searched for ages
and only found these two cucumbers.
So I brought them over.
Honestly,
how are you even running the station?
Aren't those cabarets and bathhouses
always selling fruit platters?
Look at how you handled this.
It's fine, really.
I'm not hungry.
Even if you aren't, you need to eat.
Chen Hongbing called me over
in such a frantic rush.
Since I didn't know
if you were allergic to penicillin,
I gave you an IV of azithromycin.
This medication is hard on the stomach.
Eat something,
and you won't feel so sick.
Exactly.
Listen to my wife.
You need to put
something in your stomach.
Honey,
I have to thank you.
It's all thanks to you tonight.
We're an old married couple,
so why the formality?
Go wash those cucumbers.
Yes.
You and Director Chen
are quite affectionate.
Thank you for today, Mrs. Chen.
Well, you came to Fengyang alone,
and you're a stranger in a new place.
Doing this for you
is the least we can do.
But
being away from home for so long,
doesn't your husband worry about you?
I'm divorced.
Oh, look at me,
asking things I shouldn't have.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Please get some rest.
I'll pack up my things.
Here,
have some of this first.
Have some cucumber first.
Just leave it there.
Director Chen, was there something specific
you wanted to discuss this late?
I wanted to talk about the case.
Never mind.
We'll talk tomorrow.
I'm fine now.
Did you find something new?
Not exactly a new discovery,
it's just that Yu Susu
is acting very strange.
From chasing sugar daddies
to dealing with the cough syrup...
Think about it. She doesn't lack money
or men.
So why would she marry
a miner from an illegal pit?
What is she after?
You're right.
When you piece it all together,
Yu Susu surely has issues.
Besides, Zhu Qiang has gone mad.
Why do all these strange things
happen around Yu Susu?
Mrs. Chen.
Are you feeling unwell?
No.
Let me ask you something.
Can drinking cough syrup
make someone go mad?
Cough syrup alone won't.
But if taken with stomach medicine,
it can easily affect one's mental state.
Are you sure?
Of course I am.
When I worked at the Workers' Hospital,
most of what we handled
were upper respiratory issues.
I know the contraindications
for cough syrup inside out.
Director Chen,
please make arrangements
for the hospital
to take Zhu Qiang's blood.
I have to report back
to the municipal PSB tomorrow anyway.
I'll take Zhu Qiang's blood
directly there for testing.
All right, will do.
Don't worry.
I'll have Limin arrange it tomorrow.
Okay.
Prepare another 50,000 yuan for me,
plus five bottles of medicine.
I'll come to pick them up tomorrow.
Otherwise, you know what will happen.
Have you got your things
and dialysis paperwork?
Don't worry, I have everything.
It's so early in the morning.
Why have you started painting?
I saw the wall was peeling,
so I wanted to repaint it.
Don't you have
an appointment with Lu Yuan later?
It's just a small job.
I'll be done before he arrives.
I've got nothing else to do anyway.
Just trying to distract myself.
Let's just do what
we agreed on yesterday.
Give him the money
and settle the matter.
If the money is gone, we can earn more.
Don't be impulsive.
Don't worry.
You were right yesterday.
We'll do as you said.
All right?
Director Chen.
- Chief Liu.
- Chief Liu, let me take that.
Thanks.
Zhu Qiang's blood samples
are in the car.
Good. When I get to the municipal PSB,
I'll have Tang test them.
Okay. Also,
my wife told me to tell you
to go to the municipal hospital
and get a proper checkup.
Fine. Thank her for me.
Oh, I have something to tell you.
Regarding Gao Ying's case,
give me the materials.
On my way back to the municipal PSB,
I'll submit them for you
to see if they can
be investigated together.
Chief Liu,
thank you so much.
I've even put together
some materials for this.
They're at Hui's roller skating rink.
Let's head over
and I'll get them for you.
Sure, no problem.
Let's go.
Hello.
What's wrong? Are you feeling unwell?
Lie down first. Don't move.
I'll go get the doctor.
Get him some tissues.
It's so early in the morning.
Why have you started painting?
I saw the wall was peeling,
so I wanted to repaint it.
Don't you have an appointment
with Lu Yuan later?
Let's just do
what we agreed on yesterday.
Give him the money,
and settle the matter.
Don't be impulsive.
Don't worry.
You were right yesterday.
We'll do as you said.
All right?
Miss,
I'm not feeling well.
I'll skip the dialysis for now.
I'm leaving.
Is the money and medicine ready?
It's all on the bar.
Count it yourself.
Who is it?
It's me, Hui.
Coming!
Warehouse.
Hide in the warehouse.
Dad.
Hui,
where did you put
Aunt Gao Ying's iron box?
It's in the warehouse.
Bring it to me, quick.
Dad,
I'll go get it.
Forget it.
There's no light in the warehouse.
You won't find it.
Dad,
let me get it for you.
It's fine, I'll do it myself.
Dad,
you won't find it.
Fine.
Leave me alone.
Dad!
What's wrong?
Look at the footprint
you left in the paint.
What's going on with this?
Just stay right there. Don't move.
I'll bring it to you, okay?
Hurry up.
The car is waiting at the door.
Okay.
I'm heading out now.
Clean this up quickly.
I know.
I'll see you out.
No need.
That's enough, Dad.
Take it slow.
Alright.
Hui, there's something I need to tell you.
What is it?
Your mom's birthday is coming up.
I want to get her a gift.
Why the sudden thought of a gift?
Your mom has been unhappy lately.
We need to cheer her up.
Help me think of what to get.
Sure, I got it.
I will tell you when I think of something.
That's it then.
Take care.
Okay.
Come out.
(No Entry)
Fifty thousand.
I've counted it.
Every cent is there.
Thanks.
Don't worry.
I definitely won't be
coming back this time.
Sir, could you please go a bit faster?
Get lost!
Call the police!
I want to make a report.
What's going on?
What are you shouting for?
I want to make a report.
You want to report something, right?
Have a seat.
Don't panic. Take your time.
What exactly happened?
- Just let me go, please!
- Sit back down!
You've tested positive several times.
Someone like you
gets at least three years.
- Let's go.
- I'll change this time, I swear.
I'll change.
What are you looking at?
What is wrong with you?
I'm asking you a question.
Weren't you reporting something?
Why do you want to call the police?
Dad.
How did you get here?
I came to find you.
To find me?
Come on in and let's talk.
Let's talk here.
Talk here?
Look at you, covered in all this paint.
What happened?
I accidentally fell while painting.
Got some on me.
What is it?
About what you mentioned before.
I've been thinking.
Doesn't Mom love watching
Demi-Gods and Semi-Devils?
How about we buy her a DVD player?
You came all the way here for that?
Silly kid.
Couldn't you have just called me?
That would've worked, right?
I was just about to go buy paint,
so I thought I'd tell you in person.
Things like this
are better discussed face-to-face.
Director Chen.
It's me.
Aren't you the guy
I dragged into the urine test
at the roller skating rink that night?
Yeah, it's me.
You little rascal,
what are you doing here?
Reporting something.
Reporting something?
What's the matter?
I lost my ID card.
You're calling the police
just for a lost ID?
Wasn't I in a hurry?
The people's police
for the people, right?
That's enough.
Get going.
I'm leaving now, Director Chen.
Go.
Is this your son?
What about it?
He's handsome.
Quite a talented young man.
He looks just like you.
Just go.
Dad, I'll be heading out now.
Alright.
Go change your clothes.
I know.
Wait a second.
Then,
just like you said,
go and buy a DVD player for your mother.
Okay.
You're quite something,
trying to kill me.
You... Kill...
Just now,
you were quite something.
Trying to kill me?
Kill?
Have you ever killed anyone?
If you've got the guts,
go in and kill me.
If your dad knew
his son was dealing drugs,
what would he think?
Where's the dignity
of the police station?
But you didn't report it either.
If you speak up, you're finished too.
Listen here.
I've changed my mind.
Get 100,000 ready for me.
You want 100,000?
Ten thousand yuan.
Not a penny less.
If you're short,
prepare to rot in prison.
If I end up inside,
don't even think about escaping.
Fine.
My life in exchange for both of yours.
It's worth it.
I wonder if that invalid of yours
would even survive in there.
Don't you touch Songge.
Didn't know you were such a romantic.
If you don't want
anything to happen to Songge,
then get the money ready quickly.
Ten thousand yuan.
Not a penny less.
Otherwise,
your dad,
the invalid,
and you,
you'll all die.
(Yingxiong Roller Skating Rink)
Think about your dad.
Think about your invalid.
Ten thousand yuan.
Not a penny less.
Chen Hui!
Chen Hui, where are you?
- Songge!
- Chen Hui!
I'm over here.
How are you?
It's all settled.
Where's Lu Yuan?
He took the money and left.
Hui,
you scared me to death.
I thought...
I thought you were going
to do something foolish.
How could I?
Like you said, we'll just consider it
paying for our peace of mind.
It's my fault.
I didn't handle it well
and made you worry.
How could I blame you?
It was my own carelessness
that let him see my face.
It's alright.
It's over now.
Everything's settled, so don't worry.
Why are you back so soon?
Doesn't dialysis take over four hours?
I was worried about you,
so I didn't do it
and I just rushed back.
That won't do.
You can't skip dialysis.
Come on.
I'll go with you for your dialysis.
(Fengyang Police Station)
Director Chen.
Chief Liu.
Why didn't you get some rest
when you went back this time?
I'm fine now.
The lab report is out.
Good, have a seat.
Besides Kejianin, Zhu Qiang's blood
(Jiangbin Municipal People's Hospital Lab Report)
did contain components of stomach medicine.
Right.
When I was coming back,
I made a special call to the hospital
to ask about it.
There's nothing wrong
with Zhu Qiang's stomach.
He's never taken any medicine.
That means
someone secretly put this stuff
into the cough syrup
and gave it to him.
Yu Susu gave
the cough syrup to Zhu Qiang, right?
Then she wanted to drive him mad.
She was murdering her husband.
Why would Yu Susu
want to harm Zhu Qiang?
And who killed her?
Master,
do you think there's a possibility
that Chi Huabo has been lying to us
from the very beginning?
Yu Susu never blackmailed him at all.
Then, why did Yu Susu harm Zhu Qiang?
So she could be with Chi Huabo.
Chi Huabo found out about it,
and fearing he'd be implicated,
he killed Yu Susu.
Are you stupid?
If Chi Huabo was afraid
that Yu Susu killing Zhu Qiang
would implicate him,
would he then dare to kill Yu Susu?
Wouldn't that be an even greater crime?
Can you use your brain?
We questioned the two people
most closely related to Yu Susu.
One is Chi Huabo,
and the other is Zhu Qiang.
Both of them claimed
they had never seen
that commemorative coin.
Then who gave the commemorative coin
found on Yu Susu?
And what is the relationship
between Yu Susu
and the middle-aged woman
who got the commemorative coin?
Yu Susu killing Zhu Qiang...
Perhaps there's another motive.
What motive?
I suddenly thought of someone.
We should go and ask him.
(Jiangbin Municipal
People's Hospital Lab Report)
Hongbing, I'm right
in the middle of a massage.
You're so...
Forget the massage.
Forget the bath.
Come here, hurry up.
Let me introduce you.
This is my friend, Huang Liang.
This is Chief Liu
from the municipal PSB.
Hello, Chief Liu.
Hello.
Alright.
Have a seat.
Director Chen,
you called me here in such a hurry.
What is this about?
Your family has lived
in Fengyang for generations.
Do you still remember
when we were kids,
your father told us about something?
He said some women
specifically look for miners to marry.
When the miners
have an accident underground,
they go to the mine owner for money.
You mean
Death Benefit Bride.
These are all things from the old days.
Tell us more about it.
What's the trick behind it?
Yes.
My father told me back then,
at that time,
the coal mines here in Fengyang
were all owned by rich landlords.
They were just illegal coal pits.
Cave-ins happened all the time.
Going down into the shafts
was extremely dangerous.
Some women
would specifically look for those miners
who were lonely old bachelors
and marry them.
If nothing happened,
they'd just live their lives together.
But if an accident occurred,
she would extort the owner.
This way of marrying among these women
was called "Death Benefit Bride."
Were there any Death Benefit Brides
who secretly killed their husbands
for the money?
It seems there were.
My father told me
there was a woman
who married six men in a row.
Not long after they got married,
those men died in the mine shafts.
Later, the woman left with the money.
I heard she even bought
a large courtyard
in the provincial capital.
But these are all legends from the past.
Would anyone still do this today?
Chief Liu,
illegal coal pits
don't have licenses.
So if an accident happens underground,
the mine owner will be sentenced.
Because of that,
everyone is willing
to pay for a private settlement.
Since there is profit to be made,
someone will be willing
to take the risk.
Even if they'd be executed if caught,
they are still willing
to do whatever it takes to get in.
(Hemodialysis Room A)
(Returning the call)
Did you find her?
I've contacted
the drug dealers from before.
No one has seen that woman.
So that means you didn't find her.
Didn't I say?
I've contacted everyone.
No one knows her.
Nobody knows her!
What are you shouting for?
Why are you so desperate to find her?
Even if you find her,
what can you do?
Every time I find one,
I will kill them.
Everyone who deceived me
must die.
Mr. Huo,
I have a way
to help you find the person
you're looking for.
Did Chen Hui send you?
♪I always thought
once we see the full picture♪
♪We could understand
each other with empathy♪
♪I always thought
the path we never took♪
♪Must have had more beautiful scenery♪
♪I always thought
once we see the full picture♪
♪We could understand
each other with empathy♪
♪I always thought
the path we never took♪
♪Must have had more beautiful scenery♪
♪Keep moving forward
and don't look back♪
♪The shore is only reached
by the road ahead♪
♪Too much debt has accumulated♪
♪Lit night♪
♪Unfortunately, the breeze in town♪
♪Can no longer catch up to the children♪
♪Times have changed♪
♪Now, everything♪
♪Is no longer what it used to be♪