Higher Value International School.
Wow. What a cool name.
From this day on, I will be studying here.
You can do this, Jay-jay. You can do it.
Hello dad, where is it?
I need it right now. Hello?
Wow. Seems like everyone here is rich.
Woah! A date at this early hour?
Can't blame them though.
The campus looks great.
This is it. Our new beginning.
We won't be a troublemaker here anymore.
We are graduating no matter what!
Wow! There's an escalator!
Is this a mall?
- Oh no!
- Hey!
I'm sorry! Sorry!
Sorry.
Okay, Jay-jay, calm down.
It hasn't even been five minutes and
you're going to wreck something already.
Remember? We're not going
to cause trouble this time.
Excuse me. Where is this?
Section E?
Uh-huh.
Ew.
Just go there.
There at the back.
What's up with her?
Judging me like that.
So what if I'm in Section E?
I know it's the last section here. Well,
my records weren't really outstanding.
What can I do?
I have no choice!
I'm sure there's nothing
wrong with being in Section...
Calix, hurry up!
You're too slow!
Move!
E?
Is that the building of Section E?
I think my map is right.
Was that guy just pranking me?
There was a fight in the gym, right?
Felix was there too.
I know that, I know that.
503...
Who are these people?
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
Is this 503?
The "3" just fell off, right?
Is this Section E?
Not here.
Go back to the Main Building.
But the guy told me...
Are you deaf? Leave!
How dare you shout at me? What if I
shove that lollipop down your throat?
Scratch that.
No more troubles, remember?
She looks so lost.
What is she thinking?
She thought she could just enter.
Calm down, Jay-jay.
Don't think about that Lollipop Guy.
There. This is how a
school building should be.
Who could study in a building like that?
It looks like a nesting ground for snakes.
I think I'm gonna enjoy this place.
Who is she?
I don't know. Why is she here?
Maybe she's a new classmate.
She looks hot, man.
She's not even that pretty.
I think she's lost.
It's okay, I'll talk to her.
Hi!
I'm Rakki. I'm the Class President.
Hello, ma'am. I'm Jay-jay.
No need to be so formal.
We're just the same age.
Sorry, Ma'am... I mean, sorry.
Are you new here?
Yes, I just transferred.
Can I see your registration form?
I was not informed that
we have a new student,
that's why we were all shocked.
Uh. Here.
Okay. Wait a minute.
Oh no. Jay-jay, you
went to the wrong class.
This is Section C.
C?!
Section C.
I'm sorry. They told me
this is where Section E is.
Sorry, Jay-jay. It's really not here.
That Lollipop Guy. He did that on purpose!
Guys, settle down. It's okay.
Stop it already.
Boys, boys, settle down.
Boys, settle down.
Excuse me!
Settle down now!
Settle down!
Miss Mariano.
Excuse me, sir.
I'm sorry for being late.
Come in. I thought you weren't attending.
Have a seat. Welcome to Section E.
Sorry, sir.
Someone led me to the wrong class.
Sorry to hear that.
But at least, you found your way.
Welcome to section E.
Class, she is your new classmate.
Let's welcome her.
Or... maybe you could introduce yourself,
Miss Mariano?
I'm Jasper Jean Mariano.
You can call me Jay-jay.
I'm a transferee from
Holy Saints High School.
Guys, listen.
Mr. President, maybe you'd like
to welcome Jay-jay?
Don't you have any
questions about our transferee?
Are you still a virgin?
Ooh!
Keifer!
Be serious!
You said question, Sir.
That's a question.
The teacher is asking for appropriate
questions. Maybe your IQ's just too low?
Ooh!
You want another question?
Okay.
When are you gonna leave our section?
When are you gonna leave this planet?
Why don't you go first?
Cause I'm the one who's gonna
make you disappear from this world.
Like you can.
Yes, I can.
Wait, wait, wait. You two, stop!
You have to stop!
Keifer, sit down!
Miss Mariano,
please choose your seat so we can proceed.
Alright, everyone.
Let's focus.
Today, we are discussing the creation myth
compiled by Mabel Cook Cole.
Told by the Igorot Tribe
in the Mountain Province.
In the beginning, there were no
people on the Earth.
Lumawig, the Great Spirit,
came down from the sky and cut many reeds.
He divided these into pairs which he
placed in different parts of the world,
and then he said to them, "You must speak."
Immediately, the reeds became people
Why does it seem like
there are no girls here?
Quiet.
Maybe the girls are all
absent. They probably
don't want to be
anywhere near these jerks.
Good morning, Mr. Santos.
Good morning.
Good morning, class.
Good morning, sir.
Who threw that?
Is this spit?
So nasty.
Who keeps throwing things at me?
Class. What is happening?
Sir, someone was throwing trash at me!
Okay, class.
Dismissed.
See you tomorrow.
3, 2, 1!
Hey! Stop it!
Hey! What are you doing?
Quit it!
Seriously? I'm done with you guys!
Why do those assholes
treat girls like scum?
Stop it.
This school would have been
perfect if not for those assholes.
- Girl, don't even think about it.
- Spill.
No.
One bento box, please.
She was hilarious earlier
when she entered Section C.
I heard you met the transferee.
What can you say?
She's very pretty but a little noob.
What?
What do you mean?
What happened was...
She went inside our classroom,
instead of Section E.
Oh my god.
That is so embarrassing
Shh!
Hi.
Hey! Aries, Ella. Come here.
We saved you a seat.
Hi! Join us.
Could you just please
serve it at our table?
Jay-jay, come here! You can join us too.
The transferee. She's the one
I was talking about earlier.
Come on. Join us, Jay-jay.
Hi, Baby.
Hi.
- Get a seat. Come join us.
- No, it's okay.
So, how's Section E treating you so far?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
They were actually nice to me.
They were nice?
No need to worry.
She'll fit right in Section E.
Go get a seat. Join us.
Oh, no. I saw them. They were four.
Just went to the bathroom. They told me.
- Are you sure?
- I'll go ahead.
Oh. Sorry.
Oops.
So clumsy.
She's so clumsy. Oh my god!
Right? She's not even pretty.
Aren't you just the best, Jay-jay?
Where will you eat now?
Might as well eat here.
Hey, guys! There's food out here!
Attack!
- This one's mine!
- Hey! Stop! That's my lunch!
That's mine!
Finally, food!!!
I'm sorry about my classmates.
They're rabid when it comes to food.
Hi. I'm Felix, by the way.
Not that too!
Don't put out your food yet.
What's wrong with them?
Don't they have manners?
Well... a little bit.
It's like a storm ravaged me.
We're not allowed at the canteen.
So when it's lunch time, and they find
food, they snatch it away immediately.
Now you know.
Can't they just bring their own food?
Or have it delivered!
Right?
Maybe you're forgetting.
We're in Section E.
They're really not the type to do that.
Whatever.
Hey!
I told you not to put out food.
Thanks for this!
Are you for real?
Miss Mariano, are you doing okay?
You know you can request to be moved
to another section, right?
Just let me know, okay?
Yes, ma'am.
- Good afternoon, Miss Cindy.
- Good afternoon, Mrs. Zaragosa.
Good afternoon, Ma'am.
Did I walk into a classroom?
This is a garbage dump.
I don't want to teach anymore.
Clean up this place.
I will attend a meeting first.
Is that what you wanted?
Alright, fine.
When I come back, and
this place is still a mess...
I will teach whether you like it or not.
Understand?
Answer me!
Yes, ma'am.
Where's the broom?
Just tell me so we can get it done already.
Hey!
Where are you going?
Miss Cindy told us to clean.
Hey!
- Come on!
- Bye!
Bye, Jay-jay.
Clean the room.
Hey!
Hey! This isn't funny anymore!
C'mon!
After stealing all my food,
you got the nerve to make me clean?!
- Assholes!
- Clean it well!
Calm down, Jay-jay.
You promised.
Remember your promise.
You could at least tell
me where the broom is!
Just look for it.
Keep cleaning!
Search for the broom.
Are you done?
Whatever!
Just let her be.
She'll finish eventually.
What is this, a rice cooker?
Oh!
A water dispenser...
Cups.
What is this, a kitchen?
So, these are the names of those assholes.
Christopher Saimon...
what a stupid name.
John Felix Collins.
Superman Andrada.
What the hell?
Mark Keifer Watson.
Ella Dianne Hyun.
This is off-limits!
Clean somewhere else.
Why? What's in there?
You're hiding something, aren't you?
Did you even clean anything?
Hold on!
I just found this! Can't you wait?
Don't shout at me!
But I want to!
Either you shut up,
or I'll make you shut up.
The way you argue...
You look like husband and wife.
How about a kiss?
I'll start cleaning!
Ouch!
You deserved that!
Stand up!
What are you doing, Jay-jay?
Is that Jay-jay?
Jay-jay! You're home!
So, how was it?
How's your first day of school?
Did you have a hard time?
It's fine, Auntie.
Was it really? Are you sure?
Of course, there's always an adjustment
period during your first day.
Come, let's eat.
- I'll help.
- Oh, don't you worry, dear.
I baked macaroni for you.
And muffins for dessert. So just sit down.
We're going to eat.
Are you sure you're okay today?
My first day was okay.
I don't have much catching up to do.
That's good. I was just worried about the
things I've been hearing about your section.
But since you told me you're okay,
then I'm good with it.
No, Auntie. My class is okay.
They're quite rowdy, but they don't
pay much attention to me.
Okay, very good.
Go on, eat.
- Don't be shy.
- Yes.
We're gonna eat, okay.
Thank you.
By the way, your grandmother...
Her recovery is okay,
according to her physical therapist.
I'm sorry that I'm staying here with you.
And sorry for being such a bother.
Don't mind it.
Everyone deserves a second chance.
Just make sure you don't
break your promise.
Yes, Auntie. I will graduate.
Good.
And I won't cause trouble anymore.
Very good.
Go ahead and eat.
Jay, can I ask a favor from you?
Can you talk to your cousin?
Ask him to come home.
Because I don't understand
why he's acting this way.
Would you please talk to him?
Of course, Auntie.
I will try to talk to him.
Alright. Thank you.
Eat up.
Okay, Jay-jay,
this is the second floor.
I'm sure those assholes wouldn't be here.
Especially their leader.
This place will do.
But in case they still pester me,
I'm gonna be ready for them.
You messed with the wrong girl.
I'll be fine here.
No one's taking my food.
Hey!
What's your food?
Lechong kawali.
Whatever it is...
give me some.
Wow. I didn't say you can have it.
You might be thinking
I'm desperate for food.
Tss!
Don't stare at me.
Am I staring at you?
I am doing no such thing!
You're taking too long to eat.
Why don't you just buy at the canteen?
We're not allowed there.
Why?
We're just not allowed in there.
Wow?
No thank you?
Tss!
What's this?
A list of food.
And what am I supposed to do with this?
Buy those for us.
And why would I do that?
Are you paying me to do your bidding?
Listen.
I don't like you here.
If I want you out, I can make it happen.
The only way you will survive
in this section is if you follow me.
You listen to me as well.
I don't like you either.
Since the day you led me
to the wrong section,
I've wanted to punch that
smirk off your face! So please...
Can we just get out of each other's way?
Maybe she wants to be led
somewhere else.
Jay-jay so thirsty!
Sleazy Jay!
Sleazeball!
Or maybe this is because of that 'Ella'?
You'll regret this.
- Good morning, class.
- Good morning, sir.
Did you read about
the precolonial period on your module?
Because we're having
a graded recitation today.
Settle down!
I will regret it?
And what could he do to me?
Does he think I'm afraid of him?
Good thing they're not
allowed in the canteen.
But me? I can eat
delicious food in peace...
Hey, Jay-jay!
Who are you talking to?
Who are you smiling at?
Oh, nothing.
I was just really excited to go
to the canteen and buy my favorite...
Luncheon meat.
- Luncheon meat?
- Yes, luncheon meat.
No, don't eat that.
It tastes bland.
Just order anything you want
except luncheon meat. Trust me.
Alright, then. No luncheon meat.
Wait a minute.
How are you holding up in Section E?
Have you made friends?
What's funny?
Sorry, it was just hilarious.
But... I'm good even if I
don't have friends there.
That's good to hear.
Rakki.
Hey, Kiko!
Let's grab some food.
Let's eat. I'm hungry.
- I don't know what to get, though.
- Yeah.
Hey. You're new here, right?
Kiko.
I'm Jay-jay.
Okay. Hi, Jay-jay.
She's the one I was telling you
about yesterday! Remember?
And you're from... Section E, right?
How is it?
It's alright.
You should get food with us.
Yeah, come on. Join us.
Let's eat together!
You can sit by me.
Yeah, exactly.
No, go ahead. I'm gonna take my food out.
Go on! Enjoy!
- Okay, bye!
- Bye.
Hey, Aries! Ella!
Come on, let's eat! I'm hungry.
Let's go. I'm so hungry.
Great. No one's around.
Psst!
No matter how hard you try to hide,
I can smell that from a mile away.
And soon, the others will too.
Shhh! Just be quiet!
Here. I'll just give you some.
Hey!
How about me?
Just shut up.
Keep it down.
Alright!
Hey! Give us some too!
Just keep it quiet, okay?!
Just the four of you, alright.
Hey.
- Yuri!
- You're here!
And who is this?
- Whoa!
- These are my favorites!
- You're really the best, Yuri!
- Thank you, man!
- Japanese food.
- Let me have a look.
Arigato!
Japanese!
What's wrong?
Do I have dirt on my face?
Hello?! Am I a ghost or what?
Who's that?
That's Jay-jay.
A transferee.
Where's Keifer?
Does he know about this?
He didn't even do anything?
He did do something, but...
But he still wasn't able to get rid of her.
You. Why are you still here and why are you
treating my classmates like dogs?
That's not what I'm doing...
Then what are you doing?
I'm giving them food.
You weren't here for a couple of days.
We haven't been able to get lunch.
Keifer did nothing?
Let's munch on this!
Who's that?
That's Yuri Hanamitchi.
He's our classmate.
Well, yours too.
Why did he only appear now?
He was suspended.
Went inside the canteen.
We aren't allowed in there, remember?
He's too cocky.
- How about this one?
- Is it sushi?
Hey!
- Hey, Yuri!
- What's up, man!
- It's Yuri!
- Glad you're back!
How are you, boys?
Yuri.
Here. A souvenir for you.
You really know me.
Bro, maybe you got
something for us too?
- It's all there inside.
- Really?
- Let's go!
- He said it's in there.
How are you, bro?
What's new?
Yuri, how's Japan?
How was it?
It's alright.
How's your grandfather?
The old man's still the same.
Fixing a few things in the family.
But enough about me.
So...
Jay-jay, huh?
She's getting on my nerves.
Have you tried scaring her away?
She's different.
We need to do something.
You know what happened the last time
we let a girl into the section.
She needs to drop out or transfer.
I don't care.
I want her out.
That's easy for you.
What sets her apart from
all the other girls before?
Trust me.
She's different.
We need to go hardcore on this one.
Thank you.
Oh, Jay-jay. What are you
standing there for? Let's eat.
Angelo, when did you come back?
At 3 in the morning.
I was headed to the condo
but I wanted to see Mama first.
Mama told me you were placed in Section E.
Yes, that's right.
Angelo, do you know anything
about Section E?
Of course.
Maybe you can tell me about it.
There wasn't a Section E before.
Until they had nowhere to dump
students with grave offenses.
Troublemakers.
At first there were just five or six
of them until the numbers grew.
Once you're placed in Section E,
you won't be able to leave.
You are forced to stay
there until you graduate.
I don't know if our batch
is the same as yours.
But ours was filled with hooligans.
Section E students can't be controlled.
And the school can't expel them
because they have backers.
Why are there no girls in Section E?
I'm not sure, but even then,
there really were no girls in Section E.
If there would be a girl, like you,
they manage to get transferred
back to normal sections.
Because girls aren't as unruly as the boys.
So if you play your cards right, maybe
you'll get transferred to a better section.
I think I'll stay there.
I'm okay with that section.
Up to you.
Good morning!
- Good morning, Ma.
- Good morning, Angelo.
Good morning, Ma.
Good thing you came to visit us.
How was your flight, son?
It's okay. Tiring, but just okay.
I'm glad you're here. Alright, let's
have breakfast. Jay-jay, go on and eat.
Sure.
Eat lots before going to school.
Let's eat.
Of all places, they really chose to
fight here. They're blocking the way.
Come on! Fight!
Excuse me! Just passing through!
If you wanna live, go away!
I will leave if you let me pass through.
Jay-jay!
We're classmates, right?
What? Go on, stand up!
Are you going to school?
Yeah. I'm going now.
Can I pass through?
Wait a minute. I'll just finish this.
They are all beaten to a pulp,
what's there to finish?
Not yet.
I want their face to be bloody.
They might be thinking
of getting back at me.
- You're so pathetic.
- I'll leave you then.
Sir, are you still okay?
Wait for me!
I told you to wait for me.
I might be late if I wait for you.
You won't be late. It's too early.
I'm Ci-N, by the way.
Whoops! Do you know
why it's Ci-N? I'll tell you.
My real name is Cinco Neith Peralta.
So, what I did was...
I took the C and I from Cinco.
And the N from Neith.
That's why it's Ci-N.
Look at me...
Ci-N Peralta!
Eyy!
Such a cool name, right?
Ever since I was a kid,
everyone's been calling me that.
And that's that.
So just call me Ci-N.
I already got it earlier.
What?
Nothing. I asked, how old are you?
I'm just 14. I'm still growing, you know.
14? Really? What are you doing here?
I was accelerated.
You're full of crap.
What?
Look, I did an IQ test before
and they told me my IQ was 160.
And then, they made me take a lot of exams.
They said I'm supposed to be at this level.
That's why I'm here.
I can even show you the exam results.
- Here, wanna see it?
- No, no need.
We can even bet on it.
My scores are unreal.
Way up there, in the 200s!
How about you show me your IQ test?
Alright, you smart-ass.
What do you want, a medal?
Just keep walking.
But wait. I have a question.
Is it true you're not
allowed at the canteen?
Don't remind me.
I'm already sad about it.
Why? What really happened?
Nothing. Nothing happened.
Come on, just tell me already.
I will tell you as long as you buy me food.
Okay, fine. I'll buy you food.
Really? Is that true? Promise?
Yes. I promise. Hope you die.
It's "hope to die."
Whatever!
Okay. Here's what happened.
There was a girl.
She and Keifer became a couple.
Was it... Ella?
Anyway...
She was in Section E before,
but she managed to get transferred.
She has strong connections at the school.
Then Keifer couldn't understand why
she suddenly became cold towards him.
And then, he saw her at the canteen.
- Kissing somebody else.
- What?!
Keifer had a meltdown.
He trashed the whole place.
The ending? Our whole section
got banned from the canteen.
Why only Section E? Shouldn't the school
also ban the two students who kissed?
She'll never get banned.
She's too favored by the admin.
That's why Keifer doesn't like newcomers.
He doesn't want any
trouble in Section E again.
Wow. Why does it feel like
it's my fault he acted up?
He dragged you all down with his mess.
Just don't tell me on me, okay?
And also, just prepare yourself.
Keifer?
He does not back down. I promise you.
Now that we've met, I want you to know
that I don't back down either.
It's your life. Just
don't put me in trouble.
Just don't forget about my lunch.
I'll think about it.
What do you mean? You already promised.
Hope to die, right?
Hope you die.
Hope you die? Hope TO die.
What do you mean, "hope you die."
What food do you want tomorrow?
Just tell me. Don't be shy.
Can you do crispy pata?
Jay-jay, don't you have any food?
Why are you being so stingy?
- Hey, Ci-N.
- Ouch! It hurts!
- Sit beside me, okay?
- Yeah, sure.
What happened to you?
It's still tender, bro.
Did you get into a fight again?
Touch it one more time,
Felix, and I will punch you.
Yuri's here again. And I still don't know
what kind of bully he is.
Should I have asked Ci-N about him too?
For now, calm down, Jay-jay.
Stay far from trouble.
I was on my way here right?
Then we fought.
I took them down.
You should've dodged their punches.
You really kept your word.
Because of that, we're friends now.
But keep it hush.
Secret Teammate.
ST.
At least now, I have an ST.
Secret Teammate.
Good thing the King of Assholes isn't here.
I should've been alone
here then! Irritating...
To Calix, From Mica.
Is this a love letter? How lovely.
Pink with a heart seal.
I'll read this later.
I'll save you for later.
Class, don't forget your
assignments for tomorrow.
Class dismissed.
- Yes!
- Finally!
Bye, ma'am!
Thank you, ma'am.
Is it sticky?
Stand up.
Ci-N! What is this?!
You're glued to the chair.
Come on. Aren't you gonna fight back?
Really?! You stooped to this level?!
I told you. You'll regret not following me.
This is just the beginning.
Ooh!
What are you saying?!
You're so childish!
Fight me for real!
- She wants a fistfight.
- Is she for real?
- Let's just go, guys.
- Leave her there.
You assholes!
Bye!
You can do it, Jay-jay!
Ci-N, please help me!
Hey, don't you dare.
Keifer will get mad at you.
We're going home.
Bye, see you tomorrow.
You'll leave me here after everything?
My hands are tied. I'll help you next time.
You're really going to leave me here?
Don't look at me like that, you're so ugly!
I will really kill you!
If you can get out of
there before I get home.
Just take off your skirt.
Hey! Hey, Felix! Come over here.
Help Ci-N! Get me out of here!
Hey, stop! You owe me so much!
I gave you food so many times!
Alright, we'll help.
Ready?
On the count of three, okay?
On the count of three or exactly three?
On fucking three!
Sorry.
One, two, three!
Wait, one more time.
One!
Two!
Three!
Wow, oh wow!
Nice ass, Jay-jay.
Oh, sorry.
Here, Jay.
Just wear this.
What's with the face?
Jay-jay! Hey...
don't worry about it.
Just go with me.
You know you can just transfer
to another section, right?
Jay-jay!
What happened?
Hi, Rakki!
Hey, wait for me.
I told you, didn't I?
Keifer doesn't back down!
And I also told you,
I don't back down either.
Me? Get pushed around?
They messed with the wrong girl!
Hey!
Hey, Jay-jay! What are you planning to do?
- You're too much!
- That was too funny, dude.
You went over the top with that
prank, I gotta tell you.
Hey!
Please stop.
What are you gonna do?
Jay-jay!
Jay...
Hey! Keifer!!
You think you can kick
me out of your section?
You wish!
Game on.
Jay-jay, what have you done?
Hey!
Are you insane?
What's this?
It's our order.
What makes you think that
I will follow you? Huh?
You wouldn't like it when we get hungry.
We bite.
If we get too hungry,
we might just eat you up.
Jasper Jean Fernandez Mariano.
Fernandez? Are you
related to Aries Fernandez?
I have more details about her.
Stabbed her classmate with a pencil?
Punched another student?
She fits right in Section E.
Oops!
Still dirty.
Is that funny?
I'm the class president. I don't clean.
And so what?
A class president who's
exempted from cleaning? Wow!
Are you a dictator? You're the one
who made this mess!
What's up with that re-election?
Just wait for it.
It's time for the re-election!
Isn't it fun? We even have an announcer.