[Fated Hearts – A Bite of Susha]
[On-set of "Fated Hearts"] [Arranging a meal for Yixiao]
Tell the kitchen to prepare a few more dishes.
Your Highness,
you helped her already—
and now you're treating her to dinner too?
[Tight-lipped—Say it!]
What...
Cut.
[Hmph] [None of your business]
Who said I'm treating her to dinner?
[Even he's not convinced himself]
Your Highness,
[One more time]
you helped her already—
and now you're treating her to dinner too?
What do you mean, "treating her"?
Don't I need to eat too?
Don't you need to eat?
Your Highness, I've already eaten.
[Conversation going nowhere fast]
[Subordinate's wooden expression says it all]
[Expressing deliciousness with pure facial acting]
[Satisfied]
Come on, try it.
It won't taste good once it's cold.
[Picks up food]
Seems like
you've taken care of quite a few girls before.
You've taken care of plenty of girls.
[A new plate of meat] [Voice full of grievance]
You didn't let me have any just now.
[Still sounding wronged]
Bet the pan-fried ones taste even better.
[A boy who can't resist good food]