What are spirits?
What? Why are you asking that now?
Yesterday, I heard our neighbor's
grandma telling my mom.
A girl they knew hung herself and died.
Later, that girl's spirit possessed her friend,
and she also hung herself and died.
Do spirits really exist?
That's all nonsense.
These old people have nothing
better to do at home,
so they go around gossiping
about such things from house to house.
Don't even think about it.
Spirits and all that are just trash.
But I'm really scared.
Boo!
Oh my god...
Why are you crying?
We have entrusted her to that Swamiji, right?
He is no ordinary person.
He is a great man who has crushed
even the most powerful evil spirits under his feet.
It's the girl's good fortune that you got to know
about this great man through me.
Don't worry.
The girl will definitely get well.
There he is... Swamiji! Swamiji!
What timing you have, Swamiji?
Swamiji, slowly, slowly. Please come in, Swamiji.
Swami!
Which grave did she go to this time?
Muniyamma, from the next village.
She burned herself to death ten days ago.
She went and slept near that grave.
Changing graves every day,
is she trying to change me?
I'll teach her a lesson.
What is this?
Are you playing games with me?
Are you trying to deceive and send me away?
Do you think I can't find out who you are?
This won't work!
Swami!
Oh my god!
Hey!
How much longer will you stay here?
Will you leave this girl or not?
Swami!
Don't hit me!
She's just a child, Swami! She will die!
Don't hit her!
Nothing will happen!
If you are patient now,
the spirit possessing her will leave.
Otherwise, you all will die!
Until you go back to your grave,
this will be your punishment!
(Chanting)
My dear!
Get up, dear.
Naina!
What happened?
I have been seeing her since childhood.
That girl's eyes, her sweet words...
they are still haunting me.
Maybe that's all that was written in her destiny.
We should accept it as fate and forget it.
It's not fate...
She was a small soul who didn't know the world.
She fell victim to human deception.
There are many such cheaters.
We shouldn't just let them go.
Fear will arise in such people only
when the public revolts and beats them with stones.
Okay, what do you want to do now?
We will do one thing.
Let's expose them.
How many did you bring?
Three people, Swamiji.
Your performance is declining week by week.
Uh... well...
Who are they?
Two young girls and a 45-year-old lady.
How much can we make?
Not much from the girls, but the old lady
has a lot of money, Swamiji.
And she's scared.
The more scared they are,
the stronger we become.
I'm feeling tense, man.
Maybe we should also go with them.
Who died recently in their village?
A girl named Mahalakshmi
failed 10th grade and jumped into a well and died.
In the neighboring village,
four female laborers died in an auto accident.
Hey! What are you doing here?
The bathroom is not here, it's that way.
Let's go.
Swamiji is coming. Swamiji! Swamiji!
Swamiji! Swamiji, Swamiji, Swamiji.
What is the problem?
His name is Bhupathi Naidu.
This is his wife, Sarojamma.
She has been acting crazy like this for a month.
You are an all-knowing wise man,
you must find out what's wrong, Swamiji.
Mahalakshmi!
Mahalakshmi?
Who is that, Swami?
A few days ago, a girl named Mahalakshmi from their village
failed her 10th grade, jumped into a well, and died.
Her spirit, unable to leave this world,
has possessed this woman.
Did you see?
The fact that Swamiji knew about Mahalakshmi's death
in their village means he is no ordinary man, Swami.
Did you see the Swamiji's powers?
If you had come a little earlier,
you would have found a solution sooner.
Time itself decides when
something should happen.
To get rid of that Mahalakshmi's affliction,
some pujas must be performed.
My disciples will tell you about the arrangements.
As you wish, Swami.
Let's go, Naidu garu.
Your wife will surely get well.
Look, they are coming!
I think they're caught. Quick, quick. Hop on.
Kalabhairavananda Swamy who deceived
people with magic and spells…
and whose lies led to a child’s unjust death…
was finally exposed by four friends.
Will you go or not
Hey Saithan
Leave her and go
Go
Go away from here
Leave Her
In a dargah in Hyderabad's whole city,
dangerous chemicals were mixed into the incense...
These days, girls aren't even getting
married if they step out into the streets.
and you've gone straight onto TV to reveal
the incident. Who will marry you now?
Mom!
Aruna is not merely our maid.
She’s family to us.
She’s been by our side for years.
Her daughter is died.
Mom, she has a sleepwalking issue.
If only we had waited for a few days,
it would’ve been gone.
Unfortunately, the Swamiji was cruel
and killed her in the meantime.
Nevertheless, I told her repeatedly.
To bring her to a hospital for a check-up.
She spoke of spirits and
took her to someone unknown.
There will be plenty of people who betray others.
We should watch our step.
Hey, do you know the crazy news?
Congrats, buddy!
I'm so happy!
Hey, Naina! Come, come, come.
Another member is about to be added to our group.
Who?
Little Aparna and Vinay is on the way.
Really?
Yeah!
- For real?
I came to know when i got doubt in morning
Congrats Dear
So happy for you!
Thank you!
Aparna... why are there tears in your eyes
at such a happy time?
You know, it's been five years since
Vinay's parents last spoke to him.
I've been through hell these five years with the guilty feeling
that he became distant from his parents because he married me.
Many times I felt that if I left him and went far away...
He would get close to his parents again.
But I didn't have the courage.
How could I leave?
He is my life.
But whenever I was sad,
he would lovingly console me, saying...
They will be angry with us only
as long as it's just the two of us.
But if we have a child, they will come and...
Reconcile with us even if we say no.
After all this time, that wish is coming true.
Marriage, kids... everything is fulfilled in our life.
What about you?
Will you ever tell Nayana that
you love her in this lifetime or not?
Hey, speak softly. She'll hear.
Let her hear. You won't express it anyway,
at least she'll know this way.
Hey, we've been friends since childhood.
Have you ever spent a single
moment without thinking about her?
For her sake, you even gave up
your dream of going abroad.
You took a small job that doesn't suit
you at all and stayed with us.
After doing all this, if you don't
at least tell her this...
Once it slips through your hands,
you can't get it back.
"That moon in the sky,
won't it land in your hands"
"If the word friendship exists in life?"
"Any distance becomes closer,
any hardship becomes pleasant"
"If the mantra of 'friendship' is in your heart"
"In a heart burning like a furnace"
"It comes like a cool moonlight"
"In a series of bitter experiences,
it shares sweetness"
"Friendship, it weaves so many little smiles"
"Friendship, it showers so many new colors"
"Friendship, like a dream taking form,
it stood right in front of you"
"Friendship, it sings lullabies like a mother"
"Friendship, it shows the way like a father"
"Friendship, it promised to be with you,
anytime, anywhere"
"So many unforgettable memories"
"So many unstoppable journeys"
"So many mischievous talks"
"are all outlines of friendship."
"So many beautiful poems"
"So many destinies of our own"
"So many indelible histories"
"Friends are our true assets"
"A hug amidst tears is friendship"
"The greatest of all is friendship"
"More than love in life, like a mother's love, it's a truth
that it reaches you through a path that cannot be found"
"Friendship, it weaves so many little smiles"
"Friendship, it showers so many new colors"
"Like a dream taking form,
it stood right in front of you"
"Friendship, it sings lullabies like a mother"
"Friendship, it shows the way like a father"
"Friendship, it promised to be with you,
anytime, anywhere"
Who is he?
He is our next target.
His name is Adhidev.
He's not like the godmen and
swamis we've dealt with so far.
Meaning?
He's a top neurosurgeon from America.
A neurosurgeon?
Yes.
He's an expert brain surgeon.
Father Indian, mother Pakistani.
They are also doctors.
A family that settled in the US long ago.
I can't believe it.
A person who did research on human
brains doing such things... it's unbelievable.
10 years back, his wife died
due to a psychological problem.
A case was filed against him, blaming him for it.
But the case was dismissed due to lack of evidence.
After that, he left America.
Nobody knows where he went or what happened to him.
He just vanished without a trace.
But the strange thing is, after all these years, he was seen
in a remote village on the Andhra-Orissa border, exorcising spirits.
What?
There is a leaked video about his wife.
This video was recorded on a CCTV footage
in her final moments before she died.
It's a bit disturbing. Let's watch it.
So, his wife became like that because of him?
No, I'm feeling scared for some reason.
Let's not get involved with him.
What we've done so far is enough.
Let's stop all this.
Stop it?
What we did until now is different.
This is completely different.
Because of sociopaths like him,
our society is becoming more poisonous.
No, there's no question of leaving him.
My opinion is the same.
Let's expose him.
No.
Hey!
Hey, Aparna!
- Aparna!
Even your mother is saying no.
Why are you so stubborn?
Shut up and come.
Shall we go?
I'm getting negative vibes
for some reason.
Think once, guys.
Why all this?
What if the same happened to our baby?
Why did you hit him like that?
Then what? Why did he speak like that,
without sense?
Let's go.
"Little Krishna, little Krishna,
with chubby cheeks, my baby Krishna"
Baby Krishna...
Hey! How much longer will it take?
I'm coming!
You've been saying the same for half an hour.
Shall we go, dear?
Come on, come on, come on.
Here.
Shall I get on?
Get on.
Uncle, wait a minute!
What happened again?
Hold on, I'll be right back.
Found it!
Look at this.
It doesn't look like we're going to a wedding,
it looks like we're going for his wedding proposals.
That's how heroic my son looks.
Alright, get on.
My mom used to say the same thing when I was little.
But now look, in your hands.
Auntie! We are going to the wedding,
take care of the house!
We will be back by night!
Oh Lord!
My daughter...
You have to save her.
We named her...
Shivamma,
after you, my lord.
Don't know what evil wind touched her...
The child is writhing in pain.
Dear!
Lord... you have to save her.
There's some Swami in the next village.
They say he exorcises demons and cures everyone...
So I was taking her there.
Lord...
With your grace...
Always watch over her, Swami.
Always watch over her.
Watch over her.
Bless her.
Lord!
Come, dear.
Come!
Lord Shiva!
Son, sit carefully. Hold on tight, dear.
Look, look!
Did you see? The squirrels are so cute, right?
Sorry.
Look, a turning is coming!
I'm saying sorry, right?
Sankranti festival is coming,
let's buy clothes for our son.
Let's go to the shop as soon as it's morning.
Sure, dear.
Hey, she's saying sorry, you know.
Why are you being so stubborn?
Hey!
Look at the monkeys, look!
They look just like your mom!
You...
At least you tell him.
Why are you angry at monkeys?
They're our relatives, right?
Dear!
He's going to fall.
Hold him tight!
Dear!
Son...
Lord Shiva!
He's fine, dear.
Let's go.
Punyavathi!
What happened?
Stop!
Brother!
Take care of the child.
Brother...
What happened?
- My wife.
She fell... Save her, brother...
Brother!
Help me, brother...
You stay here.
Punyavathi!
Oh god...
What happened, God?
Blood...
Oh God...
Lord Shiva!
Slowly...
Please make way, sir.
Slowly, child.
Come.
Swami...
Is it Adhidev?
Yes.
Don't you worry.
This is a disorder in the brain
caused by anemia.
Show her to a good doctor, it will be cured.
- Okay, Swami.
Come, dear.
A spirit has possessed her.
A ritual needs to be performed.
Swami...
Take her to the ashram.
It's because of people like him that human sacrifices
and black magic rituals are happening.
In the name of salvation,
they are driving people to suicide.
Swami...
My daughter...
No spirit has possessed your daughter.
It is just a health problem.
Show her to a good doctor.
So my daughter will get well, sir?
She will definitely be cured.
Swami...
May you live a long and happy life.
You can leave.
Okay, Swami.
Lord Shiva has listened to our pleas.
Nothing will happen to our child.
Yes, dear.
Dear!
Hey!
Stop.
Who are you?
Why did you come here?
What do you want?
We're the ones
who should be asking that question.
What is it that you want?
We've read about you.
Doctor Adidev.
Top neurosurgeon.
Why have you left all that and
are playing with these poor people's lives?
Sometimes, a purpose is born out of tragedy.
That purpose defines our life's destination...
Is destroying innocent lives in the
name of spirits and ghosts your destination?
Not to destroy, but to save.
In the external world you know,
humans have only two problems.
One is physical problems,
the second is mental problems.
There are many people out there to solve them.
But there is another dark world, unknown to you,
which you're even afraid to imagine.
People who can solve the problems in it...
Are very few.
That's why I took that responsibility.
After being so educated,
aren't you ashamed to spread
these superstitions among people?
Until it becomes our experience,
anything is a superstition.
The moment it becomes our experience,
it becomes a belief.
Once upon a time, I too...
More strongly than you, opposed all of this.
But my wife's death...
Introduced me to spirits.
Your own body...
Do you know how terrifying the conflict is
when a spirit that is not yours occupies it?
Like every nerve in you is being snapped,
like your body is burning in a furnace of fire...
Like hundreds of venomous snakes
are biting your body all at once...
While an unbearable gale swirls in your brain...
Unable to distinguish between night and day,
unable to know the difference between water and fire...
Unable to differentiate between a human and an animal...
With the boundaries of earth and sky blurring...
Left in a state of madness where you don't understand
what the problem is, how to explain it...
Or to whom to explain it...
Coming to me for help...
For these people,
this is the treatment I am providing.
People like you are destroying society by creating mass hysteria
about ghosts and demons, turning even good people mad.
So you're saying spirits don't exist?
Are you mad?
We're telling you they don't exist.
What if I prove that spirits exist?
The human soul is immortal, infinite, omniscient,
and does not die with the death of the body...
As Swami Vivekananda said.
In three days, I will introduce you to spirits.
Just like people, some places
are cursed right from their birth.
Later, they gradually become abodes for spirits.
This is one such place.
During the construction of this house,
the mason killed two of his workers and then killed himself.
After many inauspicious events,
this house was completed.
On the day of the housewarming,
there was a big function.
After it went off very happily...
Nobody knows what happened that night...
But the owner of this house...
Killed his entire family and then killed himself.
Even though people died,
hopes for this place didn't.
One person bought this house,
planning to turn it into a resort.
To dispel the fear among people about this place...
He himself first...
Came with his family to spend
ten days in this house.
Nobody knows what happened...
But two days later...
He killed his wife and children...
And then jumped from the top and died.
In those incidents, no one
who could tell what happened in this house survived.
But seeing all this, I understood one thing.
For many years, some evil spirits that have held
this area captive consider this place their right.
They are unable to accept the
arrival of humans into this place.
After all these years, you, who believe all this is trash,
have come before me.
If you can spend three days in this house...
And prove that there are no spirits here...
I will admit that the theory I've
believed in for so long is wrong...
And I will be ready to do whatever you say.
Are you ready?
We're ready.
Come.
Be careful.
I told you, the spirits here are very dangerous.
These arrangements are to ensure
no harm comes to your lives because of them.
The work is done, swami.
I've made some arrangements for you to stay here.
We shall meet again.
One thing.
Under no circumstances should you cross this
blocked-off area and go anywhere outside.
For some reason, I'm scared.
Why?
Some guy attacking us at the ashram,
the things that happened in this house...
Seeing all this, I'm getting some unknown,
uneasy feeling.
Look, stop labeling every
unknown uneasy feeling as fear.
Firstly, the guy who attacked us at the ashram
was some mentally disturbed person.
And, about this house?
Those are all stories he made up.
See, he's playing games with our minds.
He's an expert brain surgeon.
He's playing games with our brains.
So, be very careful. Okay?
Nothing will happen. Let's go.
Hey, why are you so scared?
I'm here, right?
Aparna, what... What happened?
What happened?
Vinay!
No matter what you say,
I'm not convinced for some reason.
Let's not stay here.
Let's go, Vinay.
Why are you scared?
My fear is not for myself,
but for our baby.
Nothing will happen to our baby.
You, me, our baby.
We'll be happy wherever we are.
First, just let go of all your fears.
Just think of it as we've come for a three-day outing.
Nothing will happen.
Let's go.
What happened again?
I smell something.
I smell something like burning skin, Vinay.
Aparna, this place hasn't been used for a long time.
Maybe that's why you're getting this feeling.
There's nothing here. Let's go.
- No, Vinay.
Something...
- Let's go, let's go.
Aparna, I'm telling you there's nothing.
There is some smell.
- Come.
Hi. What brings you here?
The ascetic said something would happen
if we crossed that place, right?
I came to see what would happen.
But Aparna looks very dull.
She is very scared.
Let her be scared.
Let all the fear inside her come out.
After three days, when she realizes there's nothing here,
courage will take the place of fear.
After that, she'll never be scared in her life.
Anyway, Vinay is with her.
In a way, it's her good fortune
that Vinay is with her.
Your future wife is also a lucky one.
As far as I know,
you too will take good care of your wife.
If you want, I'll give that girl
that guarantee during the matchmaking.
Is she saying it knowingly or unknowingly?
Hey!
What the ascetic said is true.
We crossed those markings and came out.
This happened.
Who are you?
I'm asking you.
Why did you try to attack them?
What is your connection to them?
Hey, I'm asking you.
Who are you?
Will you tell me or not?
Tell me!
I really don't know what that name is.
I'm not asking about this body you've possessed,
I'm asking about you.
My forehead is burning.
Let go!
Tell me.
Tell me your name.
Punyavathi.
What is your connection to them?
They are the ones who killed me.
Unjustly, they separated me
from my husband and my son.
How did it happen?
When I was going to a wedding
with my husband and son...
These three scoundrels hit our vehicle
while driving and caused an accident.
At that same time, he...
He came near me.
That's why I possessed him.
I won't spare them.
I won't spare anyone.
I will kill everyone.
In the end, if you get in my way,
I will kill you too.
Who is it?
Who are you?
Aparna!
Aparna, what happened?
What happened?
Why did she scream?
What happened, Aparna?
There...
There's something there.
Aparna, there's nothing there.
You must've had a nightmare.
No.
There's something there.
Aparna, there's nothing there.
No, it's just like me.
No!
Who, Aparna?
It's like I've been burnt.
Something is there.
Let's get out of here.
Okay, okay, okay.
- Please.
Okay.
Will you run away scared
just because of a bad dream?
You sleep peacefully.
Vinay, take care of her.
- Okay.
Okay?
Take care.
Let's go, please.
Aparna!
Nayana.
If you promise not to get angry,
I'll tell you something.
What is it?
I'm also feeling... I don't know...
a strange, uneasy feeling.
You too?
It's true, Nayana. A sort of...
an unknown smell, a scent is coming.
You're also talking just like Aparna.
It's nothing. It's already late.
Go and sleep.
What is this?
Kalyan!
Nayana! - You were right.
I'm getting that smell too.
Is it?
That smell... is creating a hallucination.
Just like Aparna, I got that feeling too.
That Adidev is definitely injecting some drugs...
Into the air and doing something to us, Kalyan.
Drugs?
Yes.
It's source must be somewhere around here.
Let's go, search for it. Come.
- Okay.
Didn't I tell you?
Where are you going?
Didn't I tell you it's dangerous to go outside this area?
Acting like a genius, you challenged us that you'd
show us ghosts in three days.
Is this the way you chose to scare us?
What happened?
We thought... you were smart and would use
some new method to scare us...
But we didn't expect you to mix mind-altering drugs
in that incense like these ordinary third-rate babas.
Drugs?
Then what's that incense setup in the house?
That?
It's a 'Homam' (fire ritual) performed
with a pure heart to the God of Destruction,
so that you wouldn't be harmed by the evil forces here.
What was used in it is only
pure 'Sambrani' (incense resin).
A lie.
If you didn't mix anything in it,
why would everyone here get
hallucinations at the same time?
Time itself will answer the question you've asked.
Look.
You're an educated person.
We all accepted your challenge
thinking you would prove something in these three days.
But you too played cheap tricks like all the other babas.
Staying here even for
a moment is like degrading ourselves.
I am saying that it is merely sacred incense.
But you are of the opinion that I mixed something in it.
Opinions are proven only after they travel with time...
Whether they are lies or truths.
But you are already accepting
defeat out of fear and running away.
Fear?
Yes.
Whether you believe it or not,
all of this was just an attempt I made for your protection.
Oh, you did all this for our protection?
Great.
Okay.
Then, whatever you did for our protection,
remove all of it.
We'll see for ourselves if we can protect ourselves or not.
If you're okay with this,
we'll spend another two days here.
In that case, are you thinking
your plan won't work out?
What I'm thinking about is the disasters
that are about to happen to you.
Enough with all these words.
If our conditions are okay with you, tell us.
Otherwise, admit that you've lost.
Swami!
Remove those things.
Who am I to stop what's destined to happen?
Wow, isn't the place amazing?
That idiot... Sorry, if we'd listened to that ascetic
and not come out, we would have missed it.
Look there.
If we go up that hill, set up a camp
and have a picnic, it would be...
After this is over, we should
go chill for two or three days.
But I didn't expect you to get so dull over such a small thing.
What happened to you?
Aparna...
Hey, you!
Aparna!
If you don't remember, I'll smash you.
Why are you getting scared like a little kid?
If you stay like this for a little longer,
you'll turn everyone into someone like you.
How cute is this!
What's that?
Aparna!
- Aparna!
Stop!
Aparna!
What's with her?
Hey, Aparna!
Let's go!
Kalyan!
Apar...
Aparna!
My dear child...
My dear... My dear child...
I'm your mother.
Hey!
Who the hell are you?
Hey, get out... leave him, you!
You leave him!
Hey, you leave him!
I'm telling you to leave him... leave him!
Leave him!
Hey, you leave him!
Let go!
Hey, let go!
Leave him!
Who the hell are you here?
Hey, I'm telling you to let go!
Who are you?
Leave him!
What's with you?
Leave my kid.
Let go of him.
Let go!
Hey!
Let go of him.
Let go of my kid.
Let go!
Will you go from here or not?
- Leave!
Hit him.
Will you leave or not?
Push him away!
Push him.
- Don't leave him.
Go away!
Where were you for so long?
Vinay, let's leave this place right now.
Come on!
Where to?
What do you mean where to? Home!
It's just one more day.
We can all leave together tomorrow.
Hey, are you crazy?
With all this happening right before our eyes,
why do you want to stay here like a madman?
I can't take it for another second, Vinay.
I am leaving.
Aparna, listen to what I'm saying.
What will you say? What?
Aparna, it's not what you think.
This is all a trap set by that holy man.
Hey, are you mad?
What do you mean a trap?
Okay, let's assume it's a trap.
The things happening here, that sky...
let's say it's all a trap.
But right before our eyes, a lamb died.
How horribly the other sheep were bleating?
You all saw it! Is that a trap too?
Aparna, listen to me.
It's just one more day left.
Are you really our Nayna?
For some reason, I'm suspicious of you.
You've been possessed by a ghost. That's why, despite all this,
you're foolishly staying here and planning to harm us.
Hey, Aparna, we'll leave in the morning.
How can we leave in this darkness, tell me?
It's just one night.
We'll leave by morning.
Is there any guarantee that
nothing will happen if we stay here till morning?
Vinay, I'm asking you for the last time.
Are you coming with me or not?
Aparna!
Please listen to me, Aparna!
Aparna, wait, Aparna!
Listen to my words!
Aparna!
Come, come, let's go.
Let's go.
Let's go, let's go.
You all go ahead. I will take her. Go.
Come, let's go.
My lovely son!
Go, go! Let's go!
He's coming! Let's go!
You go ahead! Be careful!
The one who attacked us at the ashram that day...
It was him, right?
Who is he?
IT's not him, it's her.
She? A woman?
Yes. Punyavati.
Yesterday, on your way to my ashram,
you unknowingly caused an accident.
At that time, a woman named Punyavati, who was
happily riding on a bike with her husband and son...
died in that accident.
Punyavati's spirit is inside him.
She wants to take revenge on you, who caused
her death and separated her from her family.
So a woman died because of us.
And that's why her spirit is inside him.
You've created a super story!
And you made him act so well!
Your story, his acting, the training you gave him...
Wow! No amount of credit is enough.
Really, hats off to you.
For a moment, I was genuinely scared.
So, you think after seeing all this, we'll believe in spirits,
bow at your feet, admit our mistake, accept defeat, and just leave?
But you missed a small logic.
We are not some uneducated fools to
believe all this, get scared, and run away.
This plan has failed anyway.
You'll need some other plans for tomorrow, won't you?
You may leave. Go think about it.
It's getting late, right? Go.
Come with a new plan tomorrow.
Come. Let's go.
Who are you? Don't come! Don't come!
It's me, dear... I'm your mother.
No, no. You're not our mother.
It's true, my child. I am your mother.
Don't come! I'm scared, sister!
- Don't do anything to us!
Sister! Don't do anything to us!
It's gotten dark, my child.
Let's go, come on dears.
Will you leave or not?
Go away from here, we're scared!
Why are you scared to see your mother, dear?
Sister... I'm scared... Sister...
- Why are you scared, my child?
I'm your mother, aren't I?
Come dears, let's go. I don't know who you are.
You're not our mother.
Go! Go!
- I am your mother, dear.
Why the fear? Come dears, let's leave.
I'm your mother, right? Please listen to my words, dears.
We won't come! We are scared!
Why are you crying, dear? I'm your mother, right?
Come, let's leave.
It's very dark, my child. Come, we must leave.
Please listen to me, dear.
We shouldn't be here in the dark.
Come, let's go.
What happened?
Some woman gave poison to her children
and then killed herself on the railway track.
Hmm.
What is it?
At least now tell Nayana that you love her.
What happened now?
Don't you know what happened?
For 20 years, it's been all about what she likes.
Even the dress you wear is of her taste.
Even to go on a small outing,
you check four times if she likes it or not.
In these 20 years, do you even have a life of your own?
Do you have your own likes?
You love her so madly,
but you won't even tell her.
Love might not have an expiry date,
but life does.
If we part now, we can never meet again.
I'm feeling very tired.
It feels like all my energy has been drained.
Vinay?
Hi.
Where are you?
What is it? You seem tense.
What happened?
Nothing.
I can tell.
Tell me what it is.
I said it's nothing.
Swear on me.
You're hiding something.
Tell me what happened.
Okay. If you don't want to, don't tell me.
Okay?
Nayana?
Tell me.
Vinay!
Why are you sleeping here?
I...
Kalyan!
What happened? What happened, Aparna?
Here... Vinay... Vinay...
Someone dragged Vinay away, Kalyan.
Someone took Vinay away.
Vinay!
From there... someone took Vinay away.
Someone took him.
What do you mean someone dragged him away?
Haven't you come out of the illusion that sanyasi created?
Hey! I'm telling you what happened right before my eyes,
why don't you believe me?
Someone dragged Vinay away from there.
Perhaps, that's what a spirit is.
Spirits really exist.
Kalyan, please do something and save Vinay.
Aparna! Don't be stupid!
How did you suddenly see spirits and ghosts
that haven't been seen for 25 years?
If you can control your fear for this one day,
we will win against that sanyasi.
Hey, are you crazy?
I'm telling you something really took Vinay...
and you're talking about winning and losing,
ignoring what happened here?
Something really took Vinay.
Vinay!
Vinay
Aparna!
Naina!
- Where are you going?
Let's go.
Kalyan! What happened?
Don't say anything, come.
Where?
Kalyan! Where are we going?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Why are we running?
Where's Aparna?
Aparna is gone.
I saw... I saw something drag her away.
Something dragged her away?
What are you talking about?
Yes, Naina.
What Aparna said is true.
There's something there.
Perhaps, the same thing took Vinay too.
It's true, Naina.
If what you're saying is true,
we must go to Adidev from here.
That's not it, Naina.
He is definitely the reason for this. He's doing something.
If we confront him, he will tell the truth. Let's go.
Hey Naina, please!
Listen to what I'm saying, Naina, please.
- Don't say anything.
Naina!
Naina, you... you don't know what happened.
Come on, Kalyan!
Just listen to me once, Naina.
Please, Naina.
Please stop, Naina.
Naina!
Kalyan!
Someone, please save him!
Please, do something and save him.
Please, do something.
Please, save him.
Do something.
He's drowning.
Do something and save him.
Please, do something.
Please!
I asked you to save him, and you throw ashes, you sanyasi?
I admit that I've lost.
We will leave from here.
We won't bother you again.
I'll fall at your feet.
Please save him.
Please, he will die.
He died a long time ago.
Not just him...
Your friends...
You too.
All of you...
Died three days ago.
No!
Three days ago...
on the way to our ashram...
While trying to avoid a bike...
You all fell into a valley.
What is it, sanyasi?
Are you trying to make me go crazy?
We... from the accident...
we escaped.
Hey!
She's saying sorry, right?
Why are you being so stubborn?
Hey! Look...
No, my child.
For some reason...
God did not give you that chance.
What's here
is only your astral bodies.
No!
I don't believe it.
Your journey in this life has ended.
Today is the third day since you died.
Your last rites have also begun.
That's why...
You are leaving one by one.
No! I don't believe it.
This isn't real.
I don't believe it.
Not just you...
In this creation...
No one who faces such
an unexpected, untimely death...
can believe it.
Until then, a person who lived happily...
with their wife, children, relatives, and friends...
if they suddenly face death...
Their state will be just as terrifying.
I don't know what bond or enmity of how many lives...
But you died trying to save them.
Trying to escape from you...
Punyavathi died.
No! No! No!
Just because you close your eyes...
The past doesn't disappear.
"Shiva, Shiva, Shiva, Shankara...
Look this way just once, oh Lord."
"This carnival of death and birth,
Is it just a game that you play?"
"Life and death,
Are the narrative you have penned."
"The great flood, the final doom..
the grand Poision you keep concealed."
"A drama, all a drama...
This is your play, O Eesha (Lord)!"
"Eesha..."
"You can reign over all the realms,
You can erase all sorrows."
"Within every soul that worships you,
You can make your divine abode."
"You can change your forms at will,
You can weave grand illusions."
"From those who know not right from wrong,
Do you still demand their sacrifice?"
"Why do you reveal
These divine plays (leelas) of yours?"
"And wherever I look,
I see the legends of your glory."
"A drama, all a drama...
This is your play, O Eesha!"
"Eesha..."
Do spirits really exist?
This is all nonsense.
These old folks, with nothing to do at home...
talk about such things
and roam from house to house, that's all.
Don't even think about it.
Spirits and all that stuff is trash.
Dont know, i scared so much
You are in a situation where you can't
understand the sudden death
Nature has tried to make you aware of
what happened through many events
I smell something like burning skin, Vinay.
I’m seeing an illusion… of myself already burned.
My dear.. Please listen to my words, dears.
We won't come! We are scared!
Why do you think I kept you in this house
for three days?
Like lost children, you came to me.
So that in these three days,
I could gradually reveal the tragedy that happened
And give you a peaceful departure.
But with hatred and anger towards me,
you couldn't understand me.
I feel like seeing my mom and sister.
(Chanting)
How mysterious is God's play?
There are no such things as spirits,
and to prove that, you came here.
And this happened to you.
(Chanting)
You have to leave, my child.
Earth belongs to the living ones.
Not for the dead ones.
Even Rama and Krishna couldn't escape it.
Ending their incarnations and
giving up the physical body.
Whether it's a revered one or a commoner,
Nature follows the same law.
(Chanting)
When we don't accept our death...
Death appears to be haunting us terrifyingly.
If we accept and depart peacefully...
That same death becomes like
an angel and takes us away.
Depart peacefully, my child.
New relationships and another new life...
Await your arrival.
Again, in a mother's womb, like a newborn baby...
Begin your new journey.
May it be auspicious.
May there be peace in the universe.
No!