My passion
is like a fire
burning through the desert
Going to do laundry?
Yeah.
I'll head over first.
Zhang Shu!
Off to play soccer?
Oh, right.
What time is it?
The Hua Country vs. Oman match
should be starting soon, right?
Fifteen minutes to go.
Fifteen minutes?
Thanks! I gotta run.
Yong!
Lin Wen!
What are you guys doing?
The Hua Country match is about to start!
You should've said
something! I totally forgot.
Brother Xiao-ming!
Where's Yu Lei?
He's across the hall.
Let's go check.
Yu Lei!
What's up?
Where's Yu Lei?
Right here.
I've got a good feeling
about today's match.
Me too.
If we win today,
we'll have 14 points total.
That means we qualify early!
Yu Lei,
the broadcast is starting.
What are you still doing?
Hurry up!
Today's match is huge.
Who wants to just listen to the radio?
Come on.
Let's go watch it on TV in the duty room.
I already cleared it with the dorm lady.
Let's go, everyone!
Let's go!
Move it, move it!
Time for the game!
Hurry up!
Go, go, go!
Wait for me!
Thanks, ma'am!
Here.
Come on, come on.
Give me one.
Me too!
And me!
Ready?
Team Hua!
Let's go!
It's starting!
Hurry, hurry!
The Hua national
team, with a fresh look...
Who's that?
The head referee from Singapore.
And there's the final whistle!
Hua country wins at home, 1-0,
defeating Oman!
With this, Hua country has officially qualified!
That's incredible!
We qualified!
Hua Country is the best!
Students, please calm down!
Show some restraint!
Stop smashing your thermoses!
October 2001.
Hua Country made it to the
World Cup for the first time.
They say that night,
hundreds of thermoses were
smashed at Ming Univeristy.
But for me,
the way I celebrated
was heading out into the
rain with my best friends
for a pickup game of soccer.
It was on that muddy field
that I met the person
who would eventually
define my entire youth.
Have you ever met someone
like that when you were young?
Someone who doesn't have to do a thing
to make you feel completely outmatched?
For me,
Chen Ke
was that person.
Come on!
Come on, Chen Ke!
Let's play!
Yu Lei,
are you crazy?
The ground is still soaked.
You really want to play now?
Come on!
Let's be crazy together!
We met,
fell in love,
and truly got to know each other.
But don't get the wrong idea.
Our beginning
wasn't exactly romantic.
Back then, I thought
this guy named Chen Ke
was cold, arrogant,
and clearly destined
to be my rival.
It wasn't until much later that I realized
he was the only answer
to all the questions of my youth.
"Feel What You Feel"
(Episode 1: Let's Make a Real Bet)
The sky is clear,
the autumn breeze is cool,
and students from all over
(Students today, pillars tomorrow)
are joining our campus
to pursue their dreams.
(A new start, the class of
2000, your dream starts here.)
It is an honor to meet you all
at the beautiful Ming University
and share in the joy of this new beginning.
Dad!
Hurry up!
You little brat.
August 27, 2000.
Sunny.
This was my first day at Ming University.
And on that same day,
a reckless boy
clumsily crashed into my life.
Hey!
Can you kick the ball back?
Sure.
Watch out!
I'm so sorry!
I didn't mean to.
Your clothes got dirty.
Let me help you clean it off.
It's fine.
Wait,
I'm trying to help and you're annoyed?
Talk about difficult.
You brat.
You're a college student now,
try not to be so clumsy.
Dad,
school hasn't even officially started yet.
Look at that student over there.
He didn't even bring his parents.
He's carrying all his own luggage.
Look at you.
Here, take this.
Well, you're the one
who insisted on coming.
Let's go.
Who are you?
Hi!
I'm Yu Lei.
I'm in Room 301 too.
So you're Yu Lei?
Does your family own a submarine or
something? Giving you a name like that.
[TN: His name sounds like "torpedo"]
I'm Li Ming.
I'm a sprinter.
From now on,
we should look out for each other.
Of course.
Alright,
you're here.
Looks like the whole room
is finally here.
Come on.
I'll show you your bunk.
Okay.
Thanks.
Hi.
I'm He Jin.
(#1, Chen Ke,
Economic Law, Class A)
We're roommates now.
I'm Chen Ke.
I think this is my bunk.
Oh, sorry.
I must have misread it.
Actually,
I've always slept by the window.
Do you mind if we switch?
I don't think that's a good idea.
The school already assigned them.
Oh, okay. Sorry about that.
By the way,
it's already lunchtime.
Why don't we
all go grab a bite?
Sure.
I didn't expect that only the
two of us to show up today.
The other two
might be locals.
They probably won't arrive until later.
Probably.
Hey,
you should try some of mine.
This braised pork is really good.
No thanks.
Braised pork is too greasy for me.
I'm not used to it.
There's a made-to-order stall over there.
Check the menu.
Maybe
we can go get a side of greens.
Don't bother.
But thanks.
Alright.
So, do you
play soccer?
Yeah.
If you're free this afternoon,
let's go kick the ball around.
Okay.
Come on, come on!
Let's drink!
Cheers!
Not bad, man.
Impressive.
Look,
here's the deal.
I've been here training
for a month already.
If you have any questions about the school,
just ask me.
Alright.
I heard
the public showers on campus
don't have any stalls.
Is that true?
It's true.
Then everyone's just... exposed?
It's a shower.
Everyone's naked anyway.
What's there to see?
That's not the point.
Now, if it were girls naked,
that would be something to see.
Brother,
you clearly haven't experienced
the bathhouse scrub-masters yet.
I highly recommend it.
You just lie there on the table,
and the master
scrubs you down like crazy.
It feels amazing.
Wait,
how do they scrub you?
Like, your whole body?
Yep.
From head to toe.
Inside and out.
They'll scrub every single nook and cranny
until you're squeaky clean.
Wanna give me a scrub?
Look at you.
Come on.
Drink up!
Liar.
Alright.
Let's head back to the dorm!
Guys,
we got everything we need, right?
How about this?
Since I'm free,
let's find an internet cafe
and play some Starcraft.
Maybe another day.
I've been unpacking all day.
Right now,
I just want to go back and lie down.
What's wrong with you?
You're too young to be this weak.
Do you want
me to give you a leg massage
to help you relax?
Get away from me,
you creep.
Look at you.
What are you looking at?
A beautiful girl.
A beauty?
You're right.
I'm gonna go get her number.
What are you shouting for?
That's my sister.
Your sister?
Thanks.
No problem.
You're Chen Ke, right?
A freshman at the Law School?
Yes.
And you are?
We met at the registration desk today.
I'm Zhang Han.
Sis!
What are you doing here?
I just went to your dorm
but couldn't find you.
I didn't expect to run into you here.
Let's go, Sis.
I have so much to tell you.
Sis, you had the whole day.
Why did it take you so long to find me?
I was just elected Student Union President.
I've been busy welcoming freshmen all day.
I just finished.
So, Lei-lei,
is your dorm all set up?
It's fine.
I've finished organizing everything.
The school mattresses are thin.
I figured you wouldn't be comfortable,
so I bought you a new one.
You weren't in your room,
so I left it with the dorm lady.
Don't forget to pick it up.
Okay, thanks Sis.
If you need anything else,
just let me know.
I'm all set.
Mom and Dad even bought extra stuff
for me to bring to you.
Hello, senior.
Hi.
That's good then.
What are you looking at?
Are you getting along with your roommates?
Of course.
Your brother is handsome and smart.
Everyone loves me.
Even the flowers bloom when I walk by.
See? They're blooming right now.
Don't worry.
I'll do great anywhere.
This is Ming University.
There are talented people everywhere.
Don't be so arrogant.
Who's being arrogant?
I was the top scorer in the
city on the entrance exam.
Could there really be
someone better than me?
Where?
Where are they?
There you go again.
In your class alone,
there's someone with
better grades than you.
Really?
I don't believe it.
Why would I lie?
In your class, there's someone named Chen Ke.
His entrance exam score
was the highest in the entire Law School.
There's always someone better.
The world is bigger than you think.
Try to be a little more humble.
So my class has someone like that?
I'll have to see it for myself.
You've already met him.
The boy I was just talking to.
Him?
Hello, everyone.
Welcome to the Economic Law program.
This semester,
each of you
has a blank sheet of paper before you.
Chen
Ke.
If you choose
hard work and perseverance,
then
you will find success and fulfillment.
But if you choose
laziness and retreating,
then what awaits you...
Height...
will still be a blank sheet of paper.
About 180 cm.
Not as tall as me.
A good start
is the beginning of success.
Entrance exam score...
You are at a point in your lives...
A bit better than me.
You can all become a
new version of yourselves.
Who are you drawing?
Does everyone believe in themselvves?
Yes!
Give yourselves a round of applause.
Alright, students.
Next,
let's have another warm welcome.
Chen Ke,
please come up and introduce yourself.
Hi everyone, I'm Chen Ke.
C-H-E-N K-E.
I live by the sea.
I build model ships,
read manga,
and play soccer.
Nothing special about him.
Just a bookworm.
And now,
let's welcome Yu Lei
to introduce himself.
Hi everyone.
I'm Yu Lei.
It's not 'Torpedo' like the weapon.
It's 'Yu' as in 'equal to'
and 'Lei' as in 'thunder'.
I love sports,
gaming, and anime.
If anyone wants to play CS
or needs someone for soccer,
just let me know.
Thanks.
Youth should look like youth.
We should let our
youth bloom to the fullest.
Students, time is short.
Next,
we need to choose a student
from our class
to be in charge of
class affairs this semester.
Does anyone want to volunteer?
Professor, how about me?
Yu Lei.
Does everyone think
Yu Lei is up for the task?
Yes!
Good.
Then for this semester,
Yu Lei
will be our class monitor.
I hope Yu Lei
will work hard
and contribute
to our class community.
Let's give another round of applause
to Yu Lei.
No problem.
Let's give him another hand.
Yu Lei,
are you sure you don't
want to shower with us?
No thanks.
You guys go ahead.
I'll just wash up here.
Alright, we're heading out.
Okay.
What's the deal with Chen Ke?
Why is my sister so interested in him?
Love is love,
no need to be generous with feelings.
No one needs to give me a golden age,
I want you right now.
I'm clearly the most handsome
and talented one here.
Hey, your washbasin!
Wasn't that Chen Ke just now?
What bad luck.
This is so annoying.
My sister actually thinks
Chen Ke is better than me.
Who even is Chen Ke?
Who is he?
Just a guy acting all deep.
What's so great about him?
He had that sour face on registration day.
So unapproachable.
And yet my sister remembered his name.
His introduction in class was so dry too.
Total bookworm.
He ignores his roommates too.
Clearly, he's not very popular.
I'm definitely the coolest one.
Yeah!
Brother Xiao-ming, when did you get back?
I've been standing here
watching you for a while.
Just watching you grin
while chatting with girls.
I'm the one who backed
you for class monitor!
Is this how you repay me?
You won't introduce
me to your pretty cousin,
and now you're sneaking around
chatting with girls online.
Keeping them all to yourself
is shameful, you know?
Brother Xiao-ming,
you've got it all wrong!
Let me explain.
Explain?
Explaining is just covering it up.
And covering it up
means it's definitely true.
Save it.
I sentence you to death by
hanging, effective immediately.
Brother Xiao-ming, Brother Xiao-ming!
I've got things to do.
I'll introduce you next time, okay?
You better not be messing with me.
Ming De University Club New Recruiting Area
Hey, come join us!
Come take a look!
Street Dance Club recruitment!
Check it out, everyone!
Street Dance Club welcoming new members!
Come on, come on!
Join the Street Dance Club!
Anyone want to learn how to street dance?
Learn about our Baseball Club!
Everyone!
Come on, come on!
Hey beautiful, want to learn street dance?
Ladies, come learn street dance!
Take a look, everyone!
Street Dance Club recruitment!
Hey, Thunder.
o o?
Wait, you're a guy?
I never said I was a girl.
I just thought
great souls were always androgynous.
If that's how you see me,
I'll take it as a
compliment to my soul.
So,
does that mean you've fallen for me?
Me?
Don't talk nonsense.
I have not.
Since our souls resonated online,
I'm sure
we'll have some chemistry in real life too.
Thunder, I'm fine with it.
Stop making excuses.
I'm not!
Don't go ruining my reputation.
Besides,
opposites attract,
like poles repel.
Did you even pass middle school physics?
Drama Club!
Comedy Club!
Check out the Comedy Club!
We even have a Baseball Club.
That's pretty trendy.
What is he doing here?
Who?
That annoying guy, Chen Ke.
What a buzzkill.
Yu Lei, what a coincidence.
Yeah, just checking things out.
Are you interested in baseball too?
It's alright.
Lei-lei,
how come you didn't tell me
you became class monitor?
Sis,
I was just about to go find
you at the Student Union booth.
I wanted to surprise you.
Alright.
Chen Ke,
I was looking for you.
Senior.
The school is hosting a freshman gala.
I know you're a Level 10 pianist.
Would you be interested
in representing the Law School
with a performance?
Are you jealous?
And you say you don't
have a sister complex.
Shut up.
It's not like that.
Sure, I'll do it.
Great!
I'll go get the application form for you.
You can even skip stones?
Tell me,
is playing the piano
really that impressive?
Playing at level 10?
Yeah, that's actually very impressive.
But
I became class monitor,
which is a big deal,
and she barely said anything.
Then she turns around and
only cares about Chen Ke.
Must be that chemistry I mentioned.
You...
To prepare for the 2000 Asian Cup,
the Hua men's soccer
team plans to play several
friendly warm-up matches.
That's it!
I'm definitely going to get even.
Guys!
Room 301 actually sent us a challenge!
To celebrate the 2000 Asian Cup,
Room 301 invites Room 312
to a 4-on-4 friendly soccer match.
Friendship first, competition second.
Losers buy the Cokes.
This is so sudden.
And surprisingly formal.
I have no idea either.
As soon as I got back,
Yu Lei from 301 handed me this challenge.
So, guys,
should we accept?
We're already here.
Why not?
What do you think, Chen Ke?
It's just a friendly match.
Let's play.
Alright, let's do it.
Let's show them what Room 312 is made of.
We'll crush them!
Yeah, crush them!
Come on, guys!
Victory!
President,
I've decided on my piece for the gala.
Here's the form.
Moonlight Sonata.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you, President.
Stop calling me President.
It sounds so weird.
Just use my name,
or call me 'Senior'.
Okay.
Thanks, Senior.
Sis!
I want to sign up for the gala too.
Show some respect.
Call me President.
Fine.
President Zhang.
Didn't you say
you were sick of hosting galas
after doing it for three
years in high school?
That was then.
Besides,
college
is different from high school.
I need to make a grand entrance.
Tone it down a bit.
Auditions are next week.
You two better be prepared.
Okay.
Yes, ma'am!
By the way, Chen Ke,
about the match this afternoon,
don't let Room 312 chicken out.
We won't.
You guys are playing soccer today?
Yeah, Sis.
Room 301 challenged
them to a friendly match.
You should come watch!
I'm busy this afternoon
with Student Union gala prep.
I can't make it.
Oh, okay.
Lei-lei, take it easy out there.
Don't go getting injured
right at the start of the term.
I know.
Chen Ke,
go easy on our Yu Lei, okay?
No problem.
Sis!
I don't need him to go easy on me.
Didn't you say your sister
was coming to watch us play?
Where is she?
I asked her!
I really did.
She's just too busy with the Student Union.
Well,
look over there.
See?
There are
plenty of other spectators.
Take a good look.
What kind of spectators are those?
Go Yu Lei!
Li Ming!
Legs feeling weak without any girls around?
Shut it, Liu Haibin!
Even on my worst day,
I can still outrun a shot-putter like you.
Right, guys?
Right!
What's the use of being fast?
You actually have to score!
My roommates
aren't exactly pushovers.
Well, sorry to say,
but today,
you're going home with a big fat zero.
Go!
Get the ball!
Break through the middle!
Pass it! Pass it!
Run!
Here, have some water.
He's barely even sweating.
Is he looking down on me?
Next half, we'll play man-to-man.
You go mark him.
Maybe.
Lei-lei, take it easy out there.
Don't go getting injured
right at the start of the term.
I know.
Chen Ke,
go easy on our Yu Lei, okay?
No problem.
Sorry,
I need to talk to Chen Ke for a second.
What's going on?
No idea.
Can you take this game seriously?
I am taking it seriously.
Besides, it's just a friendly match.
Do you think
betting just Cokes is boring?
Then let's make a real bet.
Whoever loses
can't talk to Zhang Han for a month.
Chen Ke is so cool!
Chen Ke is amazing!
What a goal!
It's 1-0!
What's the rush?
The ball is round, anything can happen.
Give it a rest.
Just get ready to buy us those Cokes.
You just wait.
Did you do that on purpose?
Brother Xiao-ming, Brother Xiao-ming!
Play the ball, not the man!
Don't do anything stupid!
Calm down, calm down!
Don't lose your head!
I didn't mean it! Calm down!
Yu Lei,
are you okay?
I was just defending normally.
Who knew...
You have some nerve!
Don't do anything stupid!
Wait, wait, wait!
I really didn't mean it.
Stop shouting, everyone!
Let me see
how bad it is.
Do you know what you're doing?
Yeah, I have experience with this.
It's fine, I don't need...
Just leave me alone.
It's not too bad.
Nothing's broken.
Quick,
I'll take you to the infirmary.
Come on.
Up you go.
Easy now.
If anything happens to
him, I'm coming for you.
September 7, 2000. Sunny.
That day's match
ended in total chaos.
Don't take it to heart.
I heard
He Jin stayed on the field
by himself for a long time.
It's okay, it really wasn't your fault.
He didn't say another
word to us that night.
Even though Yu Lei's challenge was strange,
at least
his injury wasn't serious.
Alright, Master Yu,
that's enough.
You've used half a bottle
of medicated oil in one go.
People will think
you're trying to deep-fry chicken wings.
Have some sympathy, will you?
What do you mean, deep-fry chicken wings?
Can't you see my foot is
swollen like a pig's trotter?
I don't know,
it doesn't look swollen to me.
It's been several days.
The swelling must have gone down by now.
It's a good thing Chen Ke
carried you to the infirmary.
Who knew he was actually a decent guy?
You guys don't get it.
A bone injury takes a hundred days to heal.
I'm done with you guys.
I'm going.
Going where?
To the bathroom.
We'll go with you.
I'm not going to the bathroom!
Then where? I'm going to the library.
Don't be so polite.
You don't need help?
I really don't!
Look at him.
What is he up to every day?
What is he doing here?
Should I say something?
Yu Lei.
Is your foot better?
About last time,
I'm really sorry.
It's no big deal.
Really.
I didn't even give it a second thought.
Quiet, please.
If you want to talk, go outside.
Sorry.
Sorry, Professor.
What's his problem?
September 14, 2000. Sunny.
Today,
looking at the note Yu Lei handed me,
"Sorry for making you go to
the trouble last time on the court!"
it felt a bit nonsensical,
but also kind of cute.
Will we become friends?
No worries.
For some reason,
I find myself looking forward to it.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
There's still the freshman gala.
I'm definitely going to win that one.
(Grand Hall)
(Ming De University 2000 Welcoming Gala)
(Next Episode)
Chen Ke's performance was canceled.
But why only Chen Ke's?
Why not anyone else's?
Why do you think?
It's rigged!
Beautiful souls will always
be drawn to each other.
They'll keep getting closer.
Just like...
You're from Yuanmou, Yunnan,
and I'm from Zhoukoudian, Beijing.
Can I call you my friend?
No.
My best friend.