LOVE NEXT DOOR
- Did the finishing materials arrive today?
- Yes, the insulation materials came in.
We're installing them now.
- I'll check it since I'm here.
- Sure.
SEOK-RYU
They say those who survive
near-death experiences
often have similar experiences.
Hi, what's your name?
In that fleeting moment,
their life flashes before their eyes.
It happened to me too.
You did great!
Great job!
You can have this.
Lock your door again,
and I'll break it down.
- Seok-ryu?
- Choisseung?
My gosh!
I…
like you.
You're being too hasty.
You could get really hurt.
Grab my hand, and let's go slow.
And…
in every scene in my life,
Seok-ryu was there.
A stone finish?
That's like a solid piece of rock!
A second later,
and you would've been really hurt.
Now that I think about it,
your surroundings aren't safe at all.
Rebar, brick, glass, and nails.
It's too dangerous.
Do you have to keep being an architect?
I'm sure you do. You love it,
so how could you quit?
Still, be careful. Wear your helmet
and put on some armor or something.
Jeez, it's making me so worried.
Why aren't you coming? What are you doing?
- You got third place.
- What?
You won an award
for a cooking competition.
What are you talking about?
I never entered a contest,
so how could I win?
I entered for you.
HEALTHY RECIPE CONTEST
Mr. Choi?
We normally don't allow takeout,
but I made an exception for you.
To whoever it is, deliver it quick.
Thank you.
But what's this poster?
We run cooking classes here too.
I posted it for our students.
Today's the last day,
so I was going to take it down.
HEALTHY RECIPE CONTEST
INSTRUCTIONS
FIRST, PAT THE CHICKEN BREAST DRY
SEASON WITH SALT AND PEPPER TO TASTE
BAE SEOK-RYU
So what do you plan on making?
Broccoli and chicken risotto!
BROC-CAULIFLOWER AND CHICKEN RISOTTO
I'm sorry I entered it
without your permission.
So I won an award?
Yeah, you came in third.
Show me.
THIRD PLACE
BAE SEOK-RYU
It was held
by the Korean Vegetable Association.
It's a small contest.
Anyone could enter online.
I just thought your food was so good,
so I thought it wouldn't hurt.
This is so annoying.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have done that.
I'm so happy that I'm annoyed.
What?
I've come in first
for so many things before.
But I've never been so happy
to place third in this random contest.
Really? Seriously?
Yeah.
I want to cook so badly,
but no one will take me,
and I have no place to go.
I said I wouldn't care
about what others thought,
but it was hard to do.
I thought, "Why am I like this?"
And I was feeling hopeless.
But this feels like the heavens
have given me permission to keep trying.
That's a relief.
I thought you'd check to see
who came in first and second first.
Who was first? Let me see.
What's their dish?
"Lee Su-a. Spring root vegetables
and five-grain nutritious rice."
It's not that innovative or anything.
SWEET LOVE
It's kind of traditional.
Let me see again.
You sure you're happy
about coming in third?
You scared me.
Why are you standing here like this?
Mr. Kang is off-limits.
Hey, if you're going to date him,
do it after I die, okay?
And just so you know,
I'm going to live until I'm 100.
Then, we'll be over 70.
"We"?
Did you just say "we"?
Mom!
If you want to live a long life,
stop eating stuff like this.
This is all because of you!
I can't take it out on you,
so I'm eating my stress instead!
Yes, all right.
- Hey.
- Okay.
- Hey!
- Yes, I understand.
Hey, can't you hear what I'm saying?
Hey! You can never date him!
I don't care if the sky falls!
Don't you even dream about it!
Even with a smooth path in life,
it's full of hardship.
Why would you bear kindling
and walk straight into the fire?
Mrs. Do!
Mrs. Do, I ate the snacks
you gave me yesterday
and brushed my teeth really well.
- Really?
- Yes.
And I smiled a lot.
I smiled at my friends and my teacher.
I smiled at my dad too.
I'm sure the bugs
making me sad are gone now.
You'll be late for school.
You should go, Yeon-du.
Yeon-du, let's go.
Let's go.
And we're off.
I know she's too good for me.
I know you'll worry too.
So I tried all I could
to cut ties with her…
but I don't think I can anymore.
Dan-ho.
Hey, go inside.
Why? Why are you locking me in? Wait!
- Dan-ho!
- Please go inside.
I think that'll be best for tonight.
You said you'd take me.
You said you couldn't quit me.
Okay?
- Go inside.
- Wait.
You said it yourself!
Go inside! Now!
I'm sorry for startling you.
I'll explain how everything happened--
I don't want to know.
- Sorry?
- I don't need to know.
And it won't change anything
if I did know.
Mo-eum has always been like this
since she was a kid.
She can't ignore anything
that looks pitiful.
If she was on her way to buy toys
and saw an old lady
in the street selling vegetables,
she'd buy all her vegetables instead.
Community Chest. Christmas seals.
She'd spend all her money
on those things for her class.
That's probably the reason.
She loves Yeon-du.
And she pitied seeing you
raise a child alone.
So shouldn't you have tried
to keep your composure?
Just because she acts that way
doesn't mean you should go along with her.
You have a child.
- Mother--
- Don't call me that!
I'll pretend I didn't hear
what you just said.
I hope we don't have any more
embarrassing moments as neighbors.
It's all set. Go!
It's hot, isn't it?
Why did you have to come in the summer?
I know, right?
So, how's the work?
I guess it's tough enough yet.
I thought it'd take my mind off it.
What?
Nothing. Another truck is coming in.
Gosh, they don't give us
a chance to breathe.
Hey, go to the back!
Here, take it. Your award.
Gosh, this is heavier
than I thought it'd be.
That's what the weight of an award is.
Is your hand okay though?
How long do you need the cast for?
I can take it off now. I just tweaked it.
That's a relief.
This hand has so many things to do.
What are you doing?
Maybe it was winning the award,
but we're getting tons of requests.
We're going to get super busy.
That's not good.
I wanted to decrease my workload.
What are you saying?
We need to strike while the iron's hot.
We're going to soar to the top.
- I'm going to get married.
- What? What did you say?
I'm going to get married.
Wait. With who?
- With Seok-ryu.
- Seok-ryu?
- Hey, your girlfriend was Seok-ryu?
- Act like you don't know.
Holy cow!
But how can this happen?
You're childhood friends.
You're like family.
- You can't do that.
- Myeong-u, be quiet and sit.
- I mean…
- Sit down.
Holy cow!
- So…
- Yeah?
- The thing is…
Like this. Ta-da.
I have to propose.
Do you know any good ways to do it?
You have experience.
Seung-hyo, I'm a professional.
My goodness.
Do you want me to teach you?
- First off…
- Yeah?
Go to a basketball… No.
A baseball stadium.
Then, between innings,
you're bound to appear on the big screen.
That's when you get down on one knee
and take out the ring you prepared.
Then, she'll start to weep!
She doesn't like crowded places.
And taking her there
would be a difficult task in itself.
There's another way.
A performance. Take her to see a play.
Once the lights go down
and the curtain rises, you tell her.
"Will you marry me?
No, let's get married."
Then, she'll start to weep!
Do women really like that stuff?
It's no joke.
See? Even Na-yun's applauding the idea.
Millennials and Gen Z approve.
I see.
- Do it.
- See?
If you want to be rejected
on the spot, do it.
Your marriage proposal
is only important to you.
Unless you're paying for their tickets,
don't ruin the show for others.
I mean, it wasn't my idea.
Just remember these three things.
No audience, a decent ring,
and a heartfelt letter.
But wouldn't that be too ordinary?
What's the point
if only that day is special?
Just make every day
you spend with her special.
You're right.
Thanks.
I'm more grateful.
I used to draw but saw a house you built
and fell in love with it.
It's what brought me here.
It was admiration at first.
And then, it became love.
Everything got mixed together,
so I became confused.
But I've decided on admiration again.
Na-yun.
Be happy.
That's enough for me.
I will.
I promise.
HEALTHY RECIPE CONTEST WINNERS
"Third place.
Broc-cauliflower and chicken risotto."
"Bae Seok-ryu."
I told Dan-ho that I liked him.
What?
- But he rejected me.
- What?
Still, I held onto him.
Hey!
But in the end,
he admitted that he liked me too.
Then, the mutual agreement was settled.
It's a happy ending.
Wow, what a sudden whirlwind.
Why does your story have
so many twists and turns?
But he told me he liked me
right in front of my mom.
My friend, I apologize.
I was so caught up in my relationship
that I neglected you.
Yeah. You're so precious to me,
but I had no idea so much happened to you.
Seriously, I was too neglectful.
I'm really sorry. I regret it.
I'm the one who didn't tell you.
Get off your knees.
You must've had it so hard.
My feelings were like
sour, bitter, and salty flavors.
Sometimes, it was so spicy
I thought I had heartburn.
Is this what love is like?
It's complicated.
Just like the durian candy you like,
it stinks, but it tastes good too.
This is why I've avoided love until now.
But despite that, you fell in love.
I'm screwed.
You like Mudflat Man that much?
Well…
I don't know if I like him
for being Mudflat Man or for being Dan-ho.
Which came first? The chicken or the egg?
I don't know anymore.
What about you?
You like Seung-hyo that much?
Yeah, I do.
She likes him!
Hey! What am I going to do about my mom?
I'm burdened with the same issue.
My mom said she won't allow it
unless it's over her dead body.
My mom would probably
make me the dead body.
This is so annoying.
SEOK-RYU
What are you up to?
Hello, ma'am.
You're the one who helped
fix my wagon last time.
Yes, you remembered.
I usually forget everything at this age,
but I do remember those who help me
since I'm so grateful to them.
It was nothing.
It's the same
with that reporter over there.
Gosh.
Right.
Goodness.
Wow, that was like a beer commercial.
Do you want another?
No, one can is my limit.
I see.
It seems I've wasted my life though.
I had no idea beer tasted this good.
Alcohol always tastes the best
after a day of hard labor.
The best makgeolli I've ever had…
was after I volunteered
to build homes for those in need.
- You volunteered to build homes?
- Yes.
I've been volunteering since college,
and now, I go whenever I have time.
Do you know if that organization
also does repairs
for houses in shanty towns?
Shanty towns?
You know the alley of shacks
on the upper side of Hyereung-dong?
That's where the elderly woman
from earlier lives.
I went there myself, and the conditions
were far worse than I thought.
Are you free next week?
It's a bit tight,
but I'll try to prepare as much as I can.
You're going to do it yourself?
Yes.
No, this wasn't my intention.
I wanted to know
if there was a way to apply.
I know.
But still, it'd be quicker if I did it.
Even expressing my gratitude
makes me feel bad now.
Come on. What are friends for?
Right. We did agree to be friends,
even though we're still being formal.
We're respecting each other.
But you're Mo-eum's friend too.
Yes.
Mo-eum and I like each other.
What?
But her mother doesn't approve of us.
I see.
I…
don't know what to do.
I see.
SEOK-RYU
I'm with Mo-eum.
Wait.
Hey, that's… Did you drink it all?
You said one can was your limit.
- If you need more, I can buy you--
- No, this is enough.
I'm so upset I could die.
I don't want to go for a walk.
Nothing relieves stress
like going for a walk.
Let's sit here for a second.
Let's rest a bit.
What's wrong with you?
This looks like a comfortable spot.
- Goodness.
- Hey, try to look pretty.
I'm not drunk, but why do you
keep telling me to sober up?
That can of beer you drank
was over five percent alcohol.
We can walk and get closer too.
- Us?
- No. What?
- What?
- Yes.
- What's with you?
- Goodness!
I can't believe
we ran into each other like this!
What a coincidence!
You're right.
This neighborhood's so small, isn't it?
Yeah, seriously.
- Is that the best you can act?
- I'm not an entertainment reporter.
But that was terrible.
See? I told you it wouldn't work.
Whatever. I've set the table for you.
So whether you can dance
or get married, you figure it out.
What?
Let's go.
Hey.
Good luck.
Let's go. Come on.
What in the…
What on earth?
Unbelievable.
- What are you doing?
- What?
Right.
- Have you been drinking?
- A little…
However, I'm very sober.
Me too.
I know I was really drunk that night,
but I remember everything.
So why didn't you call me?
Because of my mom?
I understand how she feels.
I would've said no too.
I know. Yeah.
I mean, who asks someone
to be their girlfriend,
which was…
practically a proposal,
by asking their mother?
I'm sorry.
I thought a head-on approach
would've been better than lying.
That's not what I meant.
You never told me you liked me.
You even rejected me
when I said I liked you.
But why did you say
those important words to my mom?
To make matters worse,
I'm the one who kissed you first--
Why did you stop?
I'm sorry.
After thinking about it,
I sweated a lot today.
Why does that matter now?
It didn't seem polite.
What you're doing right now isn't polite!
I like you.
After my family had that accident,
every day felt
like an emergency in my life.
But then, I heard a siren,
and a paramedic appeared.
She saved people.
And she helped Yeon-du.
That righteous woman saved me,
and I humbly admit I like her.
After hearing what you just said,
you really are a professional with words.
With the money I earn from my articles,
I'll buy you lots of good food.
You think you can handle it?
I… have a pretty big appetite.
I better write more articles then.
OUT OF THIS WORLD SNACK SHOP
Your takeout is ready. Enjoy.
Next is Seo Ji-yeong.
What the hell?
Did this place sprinkle gold
on their tteokbokki or something?
Why is the line so long
this early in the morning?
Number 57?
- Yes, that's me.
- Your takeout is ready.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
What?
- Mi-suk?
- My gosh! Honey!
What's this? What are you doing?
What?
What are you doing? Honey.
To buy designer bags, they say
you need to line up early outside stores.
They're doing it for tteokbokki now too.
Exactly, so why did you buy this?
We have more than enough here.
Bring over some of that tteokbokki.
Why? What for?
"Know thy enemy, and you'll never lose
in a hundred battles."
Let's learn about the enemy first.
Jeez.
What?
What's wrong?
What is it? What?
It's good.
Their food's good.
It's not good.
It's nothing compared to yours!
The flavor's too strong.
There's no subtle savoriness to it.
What's the point when business is bad?
- Most days are a swing and a miss.
- Gosh, people these days…
They only want strong flavors.
Their taste buds have been ruined.
Mi-suk, should I call it quits now?
What?
Never mind. I was kidding.
Gosh, I should cleanse the rags.
Yes, next Friday.
Would it be possible?
Really? Okay, thank you.
Yes, okay. Bye.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- You didn't order yet, right?
- Nope.
Thank you for the food.
It's so good.
How do they make this?
Is this a new work habit?
You'll be like this
every time we go to eat good food.
Probably. I almost forgot.
Mr. Yoon gave me
his list of good restaurants.
If only my stomach was okay,
I'd visit different restaurants
and film mukbang videos.
Why are you staring at me like that?
I was just kidding. Look at me eating now.
I mean it.
What about doing what you did before?
You made cooking videos in the US.
You can start again here.
No way.
People there didn't know Korean food well,
so I was just acting like an expert.
It'd be different here.
No, it wouldn't.
You'd do even better now.
There are already
so many talented people.
Also, NerTube channels these days
are so professional and high-quality.
How could I do something like that?
I can just film for you.
- You?
- Yeah.
Hey.
- Is it better with it off?
- Yeah.
- It's too bright.
- Okay.
Okay, that should do it.
I just have to press record.
What? Already? Wait!
What do I do first?
I've already prepared the ingredients.
Should I boil water first?
Wait.
No, I have to blanch the broccoli
and make the chicken broth.
Chef Bae, why are you so nervous?
This isn't your first time.
I don't know. I'm so nervous.
Do I look weird on the camera?
You're beautiful.
The most beautiful person in the world.
My confidence and self-esteem
are at an all-time low these days.
I'm so blue.
Then, let's make it red.
Hey, the camera's on.
Your food really is delicious.
I know that better than anyone.
I'm ready.
- Then, we'll start.
- Okay.
The dish we'll make today
is called Broc-Cauliflower
and Chicken Risotto.
Just from its name, it seems
like a healthy combination, right?
And honestly,
it doesn't sound too good either.
But today,
I'll try to break the perception
that healthy food doesn't taste good.
Miss, is something wrong?
I was rejected.
How could you be so honest about that?
There's no reason to hide it.
Still, wouldn't most people
be embarrassed to say that?
No.
I was proud to have a crush on him…
even though I'm burning calories
and my heart at the same time right now.
Drink as you work out. You'll lose
muscle mass if you're dehydrated.
No, thanks.
I'll drink it after.
You look like you need it now.
You look like you're about to cry.
But still…
- Don't fall for me.
- What?
A gym member and a trainer can't date.
I've decided to dedicate myself
to my work.
What's wrong with him? Is he crazy?
I'm home.
Here you go.
What's going on?
You said these would raise my blood sugar.
It's keto bread made with almond flour.
I had to go really far to buy that.
I guess you did want to say sorry to me.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Also,
I'm going to continue to be sorry.
Because I'm going to be with Dan-ho.
You little brat,
you just made me lose my appetite!
I told you that you can't!
Mom, Yeon-du…
isn't Dan-ho's daughter.
She's his niece.
- What?
- His parents and Yeon-du's parents…
They died in an accident.
That's why Dan-ho's taking care of her.
So what?
Does that change anything?
If she was his niece and not his daughter,
did you think I'd allow you to see him?
I didn't tell you to get your permission.
After going through so much,
they were the only two left.
They're each other's only family,
and I'm telling you this,
because…
I want to protect them.
Do you even know what that means?
You have to become her mom!
There are countless times when you want
to quit raising even your own kids.
You think you can care
for someone else's child like that?
Mom.
I…
still remember.
After Dad died,
you, my sisters, and I
were kicked out of Grandma's house.
You worked during the day
and studied at night
to pass your real estate agent exam.
When you started work while raising us,
you never once forced me to study.
You were never obsessed with grades.
Whether it was my career path or whatever,
you've always respected my choices.
Can't you try
to be understanding this time too?
I can't. Not about this!
Go on a blind date tomorrow.
And get married before the year ends.
I'm not going on a blind date, Mom.
You're so understanding
about everything else.
Why are you so old-fashioned
when it comes to marriage?
Because I don't want you
to live a hard life like me!
I want my daughter to marry
a man who lives a long life
and have a lot of babies.
I want you to grow old with him
as you watch your kids grow!
I want you to have
a happy and normal life!
Mom.
I'm happy right now.
Being your daughter
and working as a paramedic
makes me more than happy.
I like Dan-ho,
and I want to be with Yeon-du,
because I want to be even happier.
Just have one piece of bread.
Too much is hard to digest at night.
Wow, she didn't throw this out.
FALLING BLOSSOMS BY LEE HYEONG-GI
"How beautiful it is to see one leave
when they know it's time to go?"
When did you get down here?
You made this yourself
and gave it to me for my birthday.
You remember.
I think I was 22 or 23 then.
Gosh, that feels like a lifetime ago.
"As it heads toward lush, verdant growth
and fruitful autumn in the near future
my youth fades away
beautifully like a flower"
If life was like the four seasons,
are we in autumn now?
Well, we're probably
in the middle of autumn.
Still, don't you think we've managed
to bear some good fruit?
What?
Seok-ryu grew up well.
Dong-jin seems to be finding
his place in the world.
After enduring the blazing sun
and scorching heat,
I think our summer bore
truly precious fruit.
You're right.
Honey.
Let's close the snack shop now.
What?
You used to like poems,
and these hands drew so well.
But you picked pans over pens
to earn a living.
You've done a great job, Geun-sik.
Do you mean that?
Yeah.
So let's sort things out
before winter comes.
Let's live the rest of our autumn
admiring the foliage.
Then, how about going to Seoraksan
one more time with Seung-hyo's parents?
Forget it. So you can take
more awful pictures?
No, I have time now!
I'll learn how to take pictures properly,
and make you look good.
Then, Naejangsan Mountain.
I want to see other places too.
Sure, let's go there!
- Songnisan too.
- Songnisan. Okay!
But where's Naejangsan Mountain?
- Jeolla Province.
- I see.
- Where's Songnisan?
- And Jirisan.
Jirisan? How would we climb that?
Today's the day.
Hey.
What's going on?
Why won't the water come out?
Dad!
Dad, the…
The water won't come out in the bathroom.
Didn't your mom tell you?
The water tank is being cleaned.
It'll be off until noon.
What?
You want this?
YOON MYEONG-U
Hey, Myeong-u.
That?
Okay, good luck.
Bye.
Crap!
Come on!
Damn it!
Seriously?
Hey!
You brat!
You're the one who called us here!
- And you're late!
- Come on.
- Seriously?
- Sorry!
I stopped by at a travel agency.
Hey, look at this.
I asked for all the cruise packages
they had available.
Already?
You know,
you're actually really impatient.
Hey, we need to set a date
while it's on our mind
or it'll never happen.
- This is a premium package.
- Yeah.
We'll fly business class
from Incheon to Italy.
And that's where the cruise starts!
Hey, business class
would make this pretty expensive.
Hey, this will be
our first trip overseas together.
Think of it
as an early 60th birthday trip.
- Our 60th?
- This cruise starts in Italy.
And it includes Greece and Turkey.
- That's right.
- Jeez.
Hey. Come on.
There are tons of places
in Korea we haven't visited.
So why go all the way there?
What if we end up getting seasick?
Hey, motion sickness meds
work great these days!
That's right.
And in Korea?
- We'll travel Korea when we're older.
- Yeah.
You won't be able to visit Europe
because of your knees later.
Yeah, In-suk's right about that.
My body feels different every day.
And my knees creak.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Jae-suk, take a look.
Look at the color of the ocean.
Isn't it great?
Imagine meeting a man here.
- It's so incredible!
- Wow.
You're closing your shop?
That's why I told you to come.
The owner has gone mad today,
so eat as much as you want.
That's such a shame.
The tteokbokki
and these deep-fried peppers.
These are so good.
You can come to our house and eat them.
Now, I'll be free and hanging out all day.
I couldn't impose.
This is a deal I'm offering.
What?
Look,
teach me how to take good photos.
Okay? Do you know how much
my wife has nagged me about that?
Why did you have to
take pictures like that?
You've made life unbearable!
Is that so?
Okay, I'll make sure
to teach you those skills.
Thank you so much.
It's so empty in here.
And so, on that note,
let me show you
something really special to me.
My precious
I swear! Seriously!
I'll pay for the lessons with this today.
I'll open it now.
Is this okay in the middle of the day?
Come on. I'm the owner here.
And I said the owner's gone mad.
This is for my wife anyway.
So I'm paying for this course.
Then, I won't refuse.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Yeah, right there.
It makes you aware
of where all your internal organs are.
Wow.
It's very special.
Jeez, did you leave
something behind again?
Mrs. Do.
Yeon-du.
What brings you here?
I have something to give you.
What is it?
Here.
What's this?
It's a flower.
I only give this to people I like.
I wanted to give you one.
I used the prettiest colors to make it.
You want to give this to me?
Yes.
You didn't seem
to be smiling a lot lately.
What if you get bugs in your heart too?
Take this and smile.
Thank you.
My babysitter is waiting for me.
Have a nice day.
Okay, bye.
She's so sweet.
And I'm the worst.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Everything's ready. Here.
Thank you.
BROC-CAULIFLOWER AND CHICKEN RISOTTO
The number of views
isn't increasing at all.
HOUSE COOK MASTER BAE
79 VIEWS 1 WEEK AGO
Yeah, I wouldn't want to watch it either.
It's broccoli, cauliflower,
and chicken breast.
I wouldn't eat that either.
CHOISSEUNG
I forgot. We're supposed to meet today.
Choisseung, did you wait a long time?
Sorry!
I'm sorry for making you wait.
It's fine. You didn't have to rush.
Your hair's still wet.
What if you catch a cold?
It's okay. So what are we doing today?
First, let's get something good to eat.
I made reservations.
Nice!
I'm going to get fat because of you.
That's my dream.
What the heck?
Gosh, the rear's been wrecked.
What? Your rear?
Your rear hurts?
No, not me. Your car.
It's fine as long as you're not hurt.
Still, let's go
to the hospital just in case.
It's all right. I'm fine.
Let's go eat. I'm hungry.
Are you really okay?
Yeah, really.
Let's go eat.
So this is the building
you won an award for?
You've grown a lot, Choisseung.
You used to cower behind me as a kid.
You've grown so well.
You're the first woman
who's ever treated me like this.
Of course, you'll be the last too.
Hey.
But are you sure this place is famous?
There aren't any customers here.
- It's only us.
- Right.
It is a famous place.
There's a reason
why there are no customers.
- It's because today--
- Yeah!
Don't you know how famous our chef is?
You don't know anything.
I apologize.
It's fine.
I had a sensitive matter
to deal with today.
Allow me.
Today's first dish is bruschetta.
With top-quality extra virgin oil…
- It's fine. Please, take it.
- Right.
Excuse me.
Hey.
What? Right now?
Wow!
Yeah, okay.
Great job. You did great.
Is something the matter?
My baby was just born!
My wife has been in labor since dawn.
Wow.
Then, why didn't you tell me before?
I mean, I wanted to.
But everything had been prepared,
and it's such an important day.
- Gosh, but still…
- Wait.
Then, shouldn't you be going now?
Quick. You should go to your wife.
Yes, go ahead. Don't worry about us.
Then, I'm really sorry,
but I'll get going now.
- I almost forgot!
- Yes?
- Mr. Choi!
The cake's in the kitchen.
- Good luck today.
- Good luck.
- You too!
- Good luck!
Holy cow!
Wow.
Well, I guess we're done eating.
- Should we go home after this?
- Yeah.
I mean, no. We can't.
The chef's cake…
He made us a dessert.
How about we eat that before we go?
- Yeah, okay.
- Okay.
Thank you for the meal.
It's okay. I still have a chance.
It's fine as long as things end well.
For me,
the results are more important
than the process, right?
I can do this.
I can do this, right?
Let's go.
Are you okay?
You should've been more careful.
I bet that hurt.
Hey.
Hey, I'm glad you're here.
Goodness. I made acorn jelly.
Take some with you.
Goodness. I'd be so grateful.
Hey, I heard our husbands
are at the snack shop together.
Gosh, despite being neighbors,
they used to be so distant.
They're suddenly great friends. How funny.
I know.
Mi-suk, I have something
to talk to you about.
Go ahead.
You know the cruise trip
we agreed to go on? Let's go together.
I don't know. I'll think about it.
If this is about money, I'll pay for you.
What?
Why would you pay for me?
Well, because I want to go with you.
Also, it's not that much money.
Friends can do that.
No, they can't.
It's not like letting friends
borrow money.
Who would ever pay that much?
I've never heard of that before.
We're not just ordinary friends.
We've been friends for 40 years.
And most importantly,
I'm so grateful for you raising Seung-hyo.
You paid me for that.
What?
You paid me a salary.
I was paid for it,
so why be grateful?
Hey, that's still something
to be grateful for.
I can tell by how much he likes you.
You looked after him with such care.
That's true.
Yeah, I did.
When Seung-hyo
and Seok-ryu both got sick,
I took care of him first
and took him to the hospital first too.
Why? Because I was paid to.
I didn't want to be told I raised
my friend's precious son poorly.
Hey. When did I ever say that to you?
You didn't.
But I could silently sense it.
Whenever you paid me extra for the month,
whenever you gave me gift certificates
for the holidays to thank me,
do you know how miserable I felt?
Is that how you've thought of me
all this time?
- Did you even think of me as a friend?
- You probably thought of me as a maid.
If that weren't the case,
why would you pay for my trip?
Who are you to pity me?
It's not pity. It's friendship.
And if that's how you felt,
it's due to your inferiority complex.
- Inferiority complex?
- Yeah.
Are you done talking?
No, I can go on. Why?
No one thinks that way of you,
but you put yourself down.
That's an inferiority complex.
It's a complex!
Hey!
- Hey!
- You bitch!
You were always so arrogant!
- Hey!
- You constantly tried to teach people!
- You always looked down on them!
- With eyes like this!
- Let go!
How did you pretend to be my friend
while secretly hating me all this time?
Hey! Let go!
- Hey!
- You were two-faced.
But I believed you were my friend.
Hey! I'm the crazy one!
- Hey!
- Hey! Let go!
Honey!
- Honey, what's wrong?
- Honey, what are you doing?
- Let go!
- Honey!
- What's going on?
- What are you doing?
- What's wrong with you?
- Honey! Hey!
It's over between us now!
I won't hang out with you anymore!
That's what I wanted to say!
Don't act like you know me anymore!
That's what I wanted!
You leave the Lavender group text.
Yeah, right!
Jae-suk and In-suk are closer to me!
No, they like me better!
- Honey!
- Hey!
Tonight, let's go home.
We'll talk about this later.
There's no later!
Hey, it's over between us now!
- Okay, all right!
- Hey, you!
Give my food containers back!
Get out!
- I'm so sorry!
- My containers!
- Don't you worry about them!
- Sorry!
- Go!
- Hey, you!
- Quick!
- Who acts like that?
- Okay. That's enough.
- Let me go!
We still haven't eaten anything yet.
That's okay. We were going to film anyway.
It worked out.
Get ready for my new dish.
What? What are you looking at?
Seok-ryu, what's the matter?
My mother is currently
undergoing chemotherapy.
She needs proper nutrition,
but she has trouble eating.
I was looking for a healthy recipe
and tried yours.
It's been a while,
but she ate an entire bowl.
Thank you.
Your sincerity got through.
Yeah.
So why are you crying?
- Well?
- Because she's like me.
It was like that for me too.
My mouth was filled with sores.
Even drinking water was nauseating,
but everyone kept telling me
I had to eat something.
But to hear that someone enjoyed
the food I made…
I feel so moved.
It makes me want to keep doing this.
To those who've been in pain like me,
and to those who are still in pain,
I want to tell them it'll be okay
and that things will get better
by offering a bowl of comfort.
I bet no one could do that
better than you.
I'm going to work harder to make videos.
That's strange.
You're smiling so beautifully,
but I feel like I'm going to cry.
Why?
Now, whenever you make rice,
slice potatoes,
or season vegetables,
I think it might break my heart sometimes.
Back when you were sick
and couldn't eat anything,
I'm so sorry I couldn't be there with you.
I regret it so much.
So I was wondering…
Will you let me
spend the rest of my life with you?
What?
Well, this wasn't my original plan.
The flowers are at the auto shop,
the food is gone,
and the cake was ruined, but still…
Fortunately,
I still have this.
Seok-ryu.
Will you marry me?
I'm sorry.
I can't marry you.
No, I won't marry you.
I'm sorry.
That's right!
So Songhan Industrial Development
rejected our proposal last time.
Rejected? Says who?
- What?
- Well…
Songhan Industrial Development.
They can't proceed with construction
due to a scheduling conflict.
Right.
I see. I thought you meant something else.
Sorry, I misheard you. It was my mistake.
Excuse me, the CEO has a guest.
Which one?
You.
- Me?
- Yes.
Mr. Choi.
You said you needed pictures
of the shanty town, so I took some.
Mr. Kang.
So that day was strange from the start.
The dark clouds of anxiety
were gradually approaching.
It felt like a sign from the gods.
"You won't succeed."
"You're going to fail."
"She's going to say no!"
Then, you could've gone
with the option to postpone it.
- What?
Never mind. Continue.
In the end,
nothing went according to plan.
Still, just as I was instructed,
there was no audience.
And…
It wasn't a letter,
but it came from my heart.
And the bracelet.
Was it the bracelet?
Bracelet?
Na-yun told me to buy her a ring, but I…
I bought a bracelet instead.
I doubt that was the reason.
Then, what could it be?
Why would Seok-ryu reject my proposal?
I don't understand.
Maybe it was because she was hungry.
I heard women get sensitive
when they're hungry.
You're right.
That's it.
You're right. That's why.
Ever since she was a kid,
she could never stand being hungry.
That's why she'd always…
Gosh, I should've fed her
before asking her.
I'm glad I could help.
Thank you so much.
Seok-ryu.
Will you marry me?
That mean brat.
How could she bring all of these?
Jeez, look at all these containers.
I was crazy to make her all that food.
But to be precise,
I don't think she ever asked you to.
Maybe she did.
That rude brat.
Who is she to pay for my trip?
So what if she's rich?
How could she taunt
her friend with money?
But honey, I don't think
she was intending to say that.
No, that's how she is.
She acts nice and sophisticated
as she slowly ticks people off.
She's always been jealous of me.
She was so resentful towards me!
It didn't seem like that.
That's because you don't know anything!
Gosh, what a mean brat!
I mean, I suggested it with her in mind.
But she didn't appreciate
my good intentions!
How could she do that?
And another thing.
Jeez, she said…
How are things over there?
Things aren't good over here.
She must've thought so little of me
to have offered money like that.
She thinks I'm a charity case.
It's the same here.
I don't think her anger
will subside easily.
How can you trample
on good intentions like that?
Let's meet at my shop later.
I was sad Mi-suk was being left out.
Okay, I understand.
I was trying to help.
Hey, what are you doing?
- Are you listening to me right now?
- Yeah, of course!
I'm listening.
How could she distort things
and misunderstand me like that?
Why is the group text so quiet today?
Are they too busy to check their messages?
Now, they're going around together
out in the open…
I'll do it.
Yeon-du.
I'll teach you how to tie your shoes
so they never become undone.
- Hello.
Hello, little one.
Mo-eum. Goodness.
You'll get hurt
if you walk on your laces like this.
They keep getting undone.
Want me to show you a magical way
to keep your shoelaces tied?
Yeah.
Here we go.
Make loops like this
in the shape of bunny ears,
cross one ear over the other,
put it under and through,
and out to the front,
and pull them like this.
All done!
Now, you can fly out
as Superman 100 times,
and they'll still be tied.
Really? Yeah!
- All done!
Let's go!
All done.
I put a spell on it,
so they won't ever get loose.
Thank you, Mo-eum.
You're welcome!
They'll really stay tied this way?
Of course.
I tied them like this every day
when I was a kid.
Yeon-du!
Want me to do something fun for you?
One, two, three!
I'm happy right now.
I like Dan-ho,
and I want to be with Yeon-du,
because I want to be even happier.
Like this!
Mother.
Jung Mo-eum.
Why are you home so late?
- Well…
- I was waiting for you.
So I couldn't even have dinner!
Hurry and order some Chinese.
Okay.
Jajangmyeon or jjamppong?
What do you want to eat, Dan-ho?
I'll have jjamppong.
You eat japchae rice.
I'll order jjamppong.
Yeon-du, do you want jajangmyeon?
Yeah, I'd like that.
We have to order different dishes,
so we can all share.
That's the good thing
about having lots of people around.
Mom?
Yeon-du, want to go inside?
We can wash our hands
and wait for the food.
- Okay!
- Come here!
- There you go!
- Wait.
She's heavy. I'll carry her.
She's not heavy. She's too skinny to be.
Do you even feed her?
Yes, I try my best,
but I'm not skilled at cooking.
This won't do.
Starting tomorrow, I'll show you
just how astounding my cooking is.
Let's go inside.
Yeon-du!
Wait for us, Mother!
Goodness gracious!
I'll get the door!
Just a moment.
Gyeong-jong!
No one followed you, right?
I think so.
But is this place safe?
What if Mi-suk comes?
She doesn't come in the evening.
And she's so angry
that she's lying down.
It's the same with us.
- This may last a while. What do we do?
- I know.
I swear, they were fighting so fiercely.
I've seen enough women fighting
on Street Woman Fighter.
What was that?
Street Woman Fighter. It's…
It's a show. Don't ask.
You don't have to know.
Let's have a drink
while we come up with a solution.
I don't think we should.
- Really? Then, I'll drink alone.
- No, wait.
Jeez, I didn't mean it.
We shouldn't be laughing right now.
We have to be serious.
Gosh. Why does it taste so good today?
Goodness, the shop
should be closed by now. Where is he?
Hey, Ms. Kang.
Yeah, everything's fine.
No, not yet.
What?
He's with someone?
How could you do this to me, Geun-sik?
This is betrayal!
Choi Gyeong-jong.
ROOT DINER
- Hey!
- I grabbed it first. What are you doing?
- I grabbed it first. Hey!
- Move.
- Love shot!
Bae Geun-sik!
Gyeong-jong!
- What are you doing?
- We're closed today!
Romaine, chicory.
Frisée.
Rosemary, chives, blueberries.
Tomatoes, eggplants.
What should I make with these?
CHOISSEUNG
Hello?
Excuse me?
It's you again.
Hello.
Why do you two lovers fight so often?
He was sipping alcohol by himself
and passed out again.
You didn't even eat anything
while drinking,
so why are you so heavy?
Wait.
Hey, wait.
Hey! Sit here for a second.
- What?
- Sit down.
Hey, Choisseung.
- Choisseung?
- Yeah?
Pull it together.
Are you sobering up a bit?
It's Seok-ryu.
Hey.
You…
Why did you reject me?
How…
How could you say you can't marry me?
You're drunk.
Let's talk about this when you're sober.
For me…
Without you,
my life doesn't have any flavor.
You…
You're like my salt and sugar.
You're my sesame oil.
How could you…
Hey, wake up.
I'll leave you here if you don't.
You can't…
What?
What am I doing here?
This was as far as I could get you.
Seok-ryu.
Jeez, that was exhausting.
- Take yourself home now.
- Hey.
Tell me…
why you rejected my proposal.
You said we'd talk when I was sober.
I'm fine now.
I guess you didn't blackout.
You said you loved me.
Then, why can't you marry me?
We're perfectly fine the way we are now.
So why bother?
It could be even better.
I can become your roof,
and you can be my rafters.
We'll take shelter from the wind and rain,
and we'll get plenty of sunshine.
We can become stronger and closer.
And we can live
a long and happier life together.
Why…
do you think we'll live long lives?
It might not be long.
I may look okay now,
but there might come a day when I'm not.
Why would you think like that?
I don't want to either.
But I can't help it, Seung-hyo.
It wouldn't be strange
if I became sick again one day.
Who knows?
Something terrible
could happen to me tomorrow.
That's the same for me.
Did you…
forget about the accident I recently had?
And it's not just us.
It's the same for everyone else.
Life is finite,
and death is inevitable.
Everyone lives under the same conditions.
Seok-ryu.
I know what you're worried about,
and I can't tell you that it won't happen.
I'm not a god.
But there's one thing
I can tell you for certain.
I…
want to spend my life with you.
A hundred years.
Ten years.
No, if I can live for only one day,
it has to be with you.
Me too.
I feel the same.
To be honest, I want to so badly.
Then…
will you accept my proposal?
As long as you didn't return the bracelet.
What do I do?
I lost it after that day.
I'm just kidding.
It's at home. I'll go and get it now.
Aunt Hye-suk.
Mom…
SWEET LOVE
BITTER LIFE
LOVE NEXT DOOR
What's going on between you and Seung-hyo?
We're dating and it's serious.
She turned you down?
Is she out of her mind?
No. It can't be Seung-hyo.
Your parents are really upset,
aren't they?
Well, we've already been caught.
I don't care!
We're here too. Hi!
That's pretty cool, Choisseung.
You're like the architect
in charge of Hyereung-dong.
I saw on the snack shop's door.
It was a sign saying they're closing.
From now on,
Hye-suk doesn't exist in my life.
I'm against it too. I have no desire
to make him my son-in-law at all.
Will you marry me?
Subtitle translations by: Sue Mounce