It's bad.
Why-man must know what
we're up to because he's
sending us a message.
[beeping]
D-O.
Y-O-U.
[intense music]
Do you wanna die?
- Oh, snap.
- Ha.
Nice.
The enemy saved us the trouble
of initiating contact.
I like it.
Let's send a reply
in every language we know.
It's on.
Shouldn't we think
twice before pissing
off an omnicidal maniac?
Now, here's a thought.
Welp, he's rudely ignoring
my well-crafted overtures.
And he also stopped
sending those creepy signals
from the moon.
Yet it was far from
a fruitless endeavor.
Huh?
[GEN] We picked
up some fun facts.
To start, we confirmed
Why-man is acting with intent.
He likes to dole out
warnings, but has no desire
to respond to our messages.
He clearly thinks
he's superior.
Meaning, he likely
won't lose his cool
and rain down
a bunch of medusas.
Well, not in the immediate
future anyway.
[chuckles]
You're saying that it's only
a matter of time before Why-man
loses his patience,
so he should hurry and
get our butts up to the moon.
We'll knock on his door,
right at the signal's origin.
Wait, we're doing what now?
We're going to fly
there and land?
Like for realsies,
we're not just
going there to orbit
around the thing
and legit be hippity hopping
all over the surface?
What's the point
of going there otherwise?
It's the only way to secure a
face to face with old Why-man.
We're sailing around
the world, solely
to gather materials and build
what we need to get there.
A rocket engine, a spaceship,
and a space suit.
Those are the three
essential ingredients
for a successful lunar landing.
Our next destination
is in Spain.
We're grabbing some fluorite
in the city of Barcelona.
And what's that do?
Without that stuff,
we wouldn't be able
to construct the spaceship
or our spacesuits.
Ha ha.
Time to set sail
to the birthplace
of the Age of Discovery,
the Mediterranean Sea.
[theme music]
♪ ♪
[SENKU] Fluorite,
a mineral that
emits light when it's heated.
It's a fundamental material
in astronautic technology.
I want it.
Likewise I also
harbor a burning desire.
There's a treasure I've
long dreamed of obtaining
in the stone world.
Easure-tray?
Ha ha.
We'll be taming
the Mediterranean.
I won't stop until I get
my greedy hands on it.
My treasure.
A boatload of olive oil.
What about the fluorite?
Ha ha.
I desire fluorite
and olive oil.
Desire is noble, after all.
[RYUSUI] We'll sail the high
seas in our new ship
and get what we're after.
Every last thing.
Across the Atlantic to Spain,
the land of passion.
We're coming
for you, Barcelona.
Ha.
You're throwing
around so many names,
it's kind of hard to know
exactly what to expect.
Well, suffice it
to say, we're going
farther than you could fathom.
[adventure music]
♪ ♪
Color me surprised, we
actually made it all
the way here in just a week.
The new Perseus
truly is a marvel.
I hate to interrupt
your celebration,
but those olives
are calling my name.
Hey, Chelsea, do your thing.
Okey doke.
Stand back and let me cook.
I thought you said
we were in a big rush?
We'll need to set
up camp before we
can get rolling anyway.
Gotta have food,
clothing, and shelter.
So yeah, no reason
we shouldn't enjoy
a little Spanish sightseeing.
As though there are
any sights to see.
We're in the stone world.
Treasure map secured.
Then off we go.
Those olives won't
harvest themselves.
That pleasure will be ours.
Nice.
We'll leave the olives
to the king of greed.
He wants them, so there's
a 10,000,000,000% chance
he'll get them.
[relaxing music]
[rustling noise]
We'll throw the crushed
olives in a centrifuge
and squeeze out the oil.
Figures.
Even cooking is a science.
Say what?
Oh, I know what you're after.
One of those spinny
machines you told me about.
Finished.
It's done?
I'm starting to believe that
our master craftsman could make
stuff like that in his sleep.
[whirring]
It's time.
I've craved this moment
for so long.
At last, our dinner table
is about to become
exceedingly sumptuous.
[relaxing music]
Made with fresh extra
virgin olive oil,
las gambas al ajillo.
OLIVE OIL ACQUIRED!!
[relaxing music]
And over there, a dish I
called the carefree fisherman's
Mediterranean pasta.
Somehow that elaborate name
makes this even more exciting.
So good.
I didn't realize how much I've
missed the taste of olive oil.
Huh.
Finally feels like
we're in Spain.
If you want
to experience a country,
start at the dinner table.
Those of us from
Ishigami Village
have never had
anything like this.
This food is
so good, it's bad.
[relaxing music]
Gracias, amiga!
Huh?
"WE HAVE MORE IF YOU'D LIKE."
You're a freaking machine.
Since when do you know
how to habla Espanol?
I picked it up from the South
Americans that we had revived.
It was simple, though
I'm not yet fluent.
I firmly believe the first
step to building trust
with the locals is to show
respect for their culture.
And I totes
couldn't agree more.
You're def the host
with the most.
You're too kind.
Es delicioso!
I think he's saying
it's really yummy.
Sí, gracias.
Gracias?
I've heard that before, but
I don't know what it means.
A common phrase.
It means "thank you."
Muchas gracias!
And a big "gracias"
to you, too.
You know something?
Learning another
language is just a blast.
I'd say it's 10,000,000,000%
proper and otes-tay bad.
That's real impressive.
Yep, you're otally-tay
starting to sound like us.
We're reviving so many
people these days.
We gotta make sure
we can feed them.
[mooing]
Woo-hoo-hoo.
All this delicious food is
making me crave a sweet treat
to round it out with.
You're speaking my language.
[rumbling]
Huh?
[whimpering]
What the hell?
I'm friend, not food.
It's fine.
You're the scavenger
king, right?
You're used to being
chased by wild beasts.
And that's what makes
you the perfect bait.
This is really bad.
Wild bulls?
Keep running.
We're in Spain, with bulls.
That can only mean one thing.
[lively music]
[grunts]
[gasping]
[cheering]
[CHROME] When were you
planning to tell us you're
an atador-may?
[RYUSUI] Ha ha.
I'm not.
Chalk it up to hours
of gaming and pure guts.
[CHROME] I'm just glad those
guts of yours are still intact.
[mooing]
By combining
milk and olive oil,
we can make a delicious
Spanish sweet.
[relaxing music]
[giggles]
Let's toss in a dash
of potato starch
too, so they stay
chewy after cooling.
[jingling]
Are you paying us?
With coins?
[RYUSUI] We couldn't let all
that super alloy go to waste.
[FRANCOIS] Their worth is
derived from the inherent value
of the metal.
HARD CURRENCY ACQUIRED!!
[relaxing music]
I've never crossed paths with
such kind hearted youngsters.
You use your brilliant
minds and incredible science
to blaze a path
in this new world.
You have much power
in your fingertips,
yet you're using it
to rebuild our nation.
You've made no
attempt to conquer us.
Ha ha.
Hold your thanks.
It's not out of the kindness
of our hearts.
You happen to be
talking to the king
of greed who wants everything.
[GEN] He's not lying.
We're gallivanting
from one country
to the next in our attempt
to revive everyone.
I'm afraid we just haven't
the time to spare for conquest.
Working a job makes
you a professional.
Meaning, you deserve
to be paid accordingly.
That's how the Ryusui
Conglomerate operates.
And it doesn't hurt
that it gives us
control over the new
world's global currency.
I'm not exactly sure
what talking about,
but it sounds schemey.
I'm handy with a pickaxe.
I can help dig up
stuff or whatever
else you folks need me to do.
I can keep
the churros coming!
Ha ha.
Now we're talking.
I'm putting you folks
to work, gathering materials.
I want all of that fluorite.
[GEN] And we're back
to the greed angle.
I guess some things
never change.
This greed monster is going to
get us a mountain of fluorite.
[SENKU] Japan
completely exhausted
its supply of large
fluorite crystals,
but that's not a problem here.
There's more than enough
by the sea in Barcelona.
FLUORITE ACQUIRED!!
[adventure music]
I didn't know fluorite crystals
would be so clear and sparkly.
You're right.
They look cool when they
fluoresce under heat.
Their Japanese name
means firefly stones.
[MIRAI] A lens?
Like, for glasses?
This one was made
by polishing fluorite,
so it's different in refractive
index and dispersion.
So, point is, it's
a professional grade
lens with high
precision, making
it perfect for our ridiculously
upgraded fluorite telescope.
[GEN] Oh-ho-ho.
Antastic-fay.
I feel like I can practically
see the moon's craters.
Ha.
You know, if we were to make
a bigger one of these,
I bet we could even
spot Why-man up there.
[chuckles] Fat
chance we'll find
a crystal big enough for that.
And it'll be a while before
we're making it in a lab.
As soon as we get a lock
on Why-man's whereabouts,
we'll be flying this baby
straight up there to meet him.
You made a rocket?
Though, it's kind of--
[CHELSEA] That thing's
mega small, yo.
Pretty sure I'm the only one
of us who could fit inside.
You're not quite
as tiny as you used to be.
Oh, that's a good point.
You're looking
at a model rocket.
Now we just need to slap
on Xeno's jet engine prototype,
then pick a launching spot
and give it a test drive.
It truly is awe-inspiring.
I realize it's not to scale,
but seeing it with my own eyes
makes it much easier
to believe we're
making steady strides
that will eventually
take us from the stone
world to the moon.
We still have
something to figure out.
We're going to need
dead accurate trajectory
calculations, which means
the next city we need to build
is clear as day.
The city of Math in India.
The city of Math, huh?
Sure.
India has always been known
for having insanely advanced
mathematics education.
That's the reason they're
recognized on a global scale
for being stupidly
good at math.
Ha ha.
I want their computational
skills.
It's the only way
we're going to get
the precise calculations we
need for our big moon mission.
Yeah.
Well, seems we're
going to India.
Huh?
Wait a minute,
don't forget we're
all the way over in Spain.
How the heck are we going
to get to India from here?
We'll have to make
a lengthy trip to go
around the Cape of Good Hope.
That's bad.
[RYUSUI] Thing is,
we've got a little issue
to solve with the new
Perseus before we
can start our voyage to India.
We're burning through
fuel faster than expected.
At this rate, we
won't make it there.
Not without more fuel.
Don't sweat it.
It would honestly
be way freakier
if science always worked
out perfectly, you know.
Well, I guess we'll be
making a lot more fuel
out of organic waste, huh?
[RYUSUI] Looks like that
is the whole reason we
installed our own fuel plant.
But we're stuck here
until we have enough,
and that's not going
to happen anytime soon.
It could take months
or even a year.
[gasps]
Hold on.
It looks like the water
connects through this part.
If we can slip through
that skinny opening,
we're in the clear, right?
It's a bad shortcut.
You can't tell me that won't
solve our fuel problem.
That spot is called
the Suez Canal.
It was carved by mankind
to connect the two seas
and hasten long voyages.
I know I've heard about
something like that before.
Don't you remember,
the banana whatever?
The Panama Canal?
The one that was almost
fully dried up after some
3,700 odd years of neglect?
Interesting.
I can't help but wonder, it's
connecting two bodies of water
at the same elevation.
So the odds of it working are
totes better than in Panama.
Ha.
If taking that shortcut
will save us an entire year,
then as far as I'm concerned,
we have to try it.
Typical.
Kohaku's rushing
straight into danger.
I can still remember
the sting of having to give
up on that banana root.
This is our chance
for a grudge match
against those canal things.
I'm not big on waiting.
A huge part of me
wants to go for it.
That said, as captain,
I have to refuse.
We don't even know
if it's still connected.
If we charge in blind
without a sea map,
we could sail right into a dead
end and never make it back.
Am I wrong?
Way too bad we can't take
a little peeksy before leaving.
We do have the world's
all-time greatest
geographer at our disposal.
You trying to make
me blush over here?
If only Chelsea could get
a good look at it from far away
using some kind
of super-powered telescope
or something like that.
Huh?
[triumphant music]
[adventure music]
[CHELSEA] This view
is fantabulous.
It's primo supremo.
I can make a whole ass sea
chart of the Suez Canal
no biggie.
Well, how's it
looking from up there?
Can we make it
through the canal,
or is it all blocked
off like we thought?
Scribble, scribble, scribble,
scribbe, scribble,
scribble, scribble.
It's got a hardcore blockage.
Our errible-tay
luck strikes again.
Hold up.
Weird alert.
It's def super whack,
but it's not game over yet.
It looks like the canal
is still intact.
It's just blocked off
by a dam of debris.
The climate
probably changed a lot
over the last few millennia.
No kidding.
And there must have been
a period of heavy tree growth
for a while, but it
eventually had to end.
The trees floated
off after withering.
We have no choice
but to destroy the dam.
You do realize it's
20 kilometers away.
[CHELSEA] Sounds kind of risky
to start hacking at it.
Then we'll just
have to blow it up.
We'll need to secure
the whole route first,
or we risk getting stuck.
We can't sail the ship
there until the dam's gone.
Basically,
you're saying we're
going to need a nasty
explosion with a delivery
system that'll let
us blow up our target
from 20 kilometers away.
Can we do it?
I'm afraid to ask.
[lively music]
THE TEAM FIGURES IT OUT
Please tell me
you're oking-jay.
This can't be real.
- Huh?
THE VILLAGE TEAM
DOESN'T FIGURE IT OUT
Ahoo.
[SENKU] Oh, It's real.
We're going to use
our model rocket
to do the dirty work for us.
[XENO]
Science is power.
For example, I trust you
don't need me to tell you
that your little rocket
and a ballistic missile
are fundamentally
one and the same.
[chuckles] Just a few
thousand years later,
Xeno and I finally made
our first rocket together.
Ignition.
[whooshing]
[chuckles]
Do your thing, rocket.
[whooshing]
Ha ha.
We'll keep on wielding
the power of science,
and blasting our way
into the future.
[explosion]
[lively music]
Okey dokey.
[smashing noise]
Booyah!
You took a major L, Suez Canal.
[CHROME] This is bad.
We're taking a huge shortcut.
[RYUSUI] Ha ha.
Now we can set course
straight to India.
I still don't get
why we're going.
What exactly are we hoping
to find in this India place?
Excellent question, Kohaku.
We know how to make
a rocket now,
but we still need India's
mathematical prowess.
Once we find a way
to get precise trajectory
calculations, we're
off to visit Why-man.
Hell yeah.
[RYUSUI] We're after
the final puzzle
piece for our space mission--
a truly unparalleled
mind for mathematics.
I know just the person.
Humanity's almighty
mathematician.
[theme music]
♪ ♪
THE UNIVERSE IS WRITTEN IN
THE LANGUAGE OF MATHEMATICS
NEXT EPISODE:
THE UNIVERSE IS WRITTEN IN
THE LANGUAGE OF MATHEMATICS
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION.
PLEASE DO NOT IMITATE
WITHOUT EXPERTISE.