Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.xyz or dramacool.club
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
♪That day♪
♪Nothing stays together forever♪
♪I've quit romance♪
♪Who hasn't failed again♪
♪Crying in death♪
♪And in life♪
♪Even now♪
♪We keep learning♪
♪It's no surprise♪
♪Being happy is so hard♪
♪Weirdly, I became a role model♪
♪On the day we met again, we said hi♪
♪It was a reminder,
a test, and a complaint♪
♪Who can do anything without regret♪
♪I am all right♪
♪May you live in peace♪
♪Let the world roar♪
♪Sounds like a carnival♪
♪Being alive is never dull♪
♪How wonderful to be free♪
♪I became even better without you♪
♪Nothing can be perfect♪
♪We bless each other in pain♪
♪We nod and smile♪
♪May we both be well♪
= Love's Ambition=
=Episode 6=
(I'm downstairs, waiting for you.)
By the way,
there's something I want to tell you.
I'm getting married.
Marry whom?
Is it someone you knew from London?
No, it's not.
I'll introduce you two later.
Go back early.
Sir.
Sorry I'm late.
- Hurry.
- Okay.
Excuse me, may I ask
what dishes to cook today?
Garden salad.
Haven't we met before?
Jinda Group.
Do we know each other?
We met once at the company.
Hi, I'm Xu Yan.
Hello, I'm Fang Lei.
I'm Shen Haoming's fiancée.
His junior schoolmate.
We attended school together
when we were in London.
And our families have been
close friends for generations.
In that case,
you've known each other for years.
Sixteen years old.
Since sixteen years old.
So like his little sister.
Come visit us often.
We can go shopping.
Alright.
Lei, you're so good at it.
This looks so appetizing.
Can I try some?
- Of course.
- Thanks.
Delicious.
Are you busy later?
Let's have a meal,
so you can teach me.
Okay.
Xu Yan, thank you for treating me.
Between you and me,
no need to be so formal.
Let's meet up more often.
I'm glad
you care for me.
When I was abroad,
I was so young.
Haoming always worried I'd get homesick
and feared foreigners might bully me,
so he visited whenever he had time.
You're like his sister,
so it's natural.
He should've done even better.
I just started at Jinda Group,
and Haoming put me on his project.
Now I have to bother him again.
Do your job well,
then you won't trouble him, right?
Lei, don't drink that much.
Let's eat. They're delicious.
Seeing Haoming marry someone
so beautiful and accomplished,
I'm really happy for him.
This is my first time
attending a wedding,
can I be your bridesmaid?
Okay.
♪You once shone like the sun♪
♪The flowers bloomed and withered♪
♪Our palms connected when we held hands♪
♪Then tangled into waiting♪
♪I've lost those beautiful moments too♪
♪Passing through my eyes
a thousand times♪
♪I couldn't embrace that feeling♪
♪My love solidifies into amber♪
♪When you speak, the universe halts♪
♪Even fate grows still♪
♪How do you♪
♪Portray me♪
♪Till sunset, with smiles♪
♪Tears flow, no sorrow♪
♪When I look back♪
♪Will you wait for me♪
♪Like fireworks that loved♪
♪Rushing toward the stars♪
♪Undaunted by pain♪
♪Fearless of flames♪
♪Even if just a fleeting sparkle♪
♪We shed tears♪
♪Deep blue seas turn to foam♪
♪We regained freedom♪
Now, the newlyweds,
you may take the rings.
♪If you remember me♪
Haoming, as husband,
put it on her ring finger.
Bride, please take the ring.
As wife,
put it on Haoming's ring finger.
♪I love you, that's right♪
♪You changed me♪
Ladies and gentlemen.
Let's give a warm round of applause.
Now, the newlyweds,
you may kiss each other.
♪If you remember me♪
♪Then I'm pleased♪
Keep the applause coming!
Let us all witness this moment.
Congratulations on their marriage!
Grow old together!
- Congratulations!
- Please come in.
- Please, come right in.
Yan, you look stunning!
Yan, you're so pretty.
Haoming looks so handsome.
- Right?
- You look great.
Thank you.
Enjoy then!
Okay.
Talk later.
Congratulations!
Thank you.
They're having a wedding.
She looks like
Jiajia's classmate, Xu Yan?
A bit indeed.
It's her, right?
Mr. Fu?
Haoming.
Finally, you are married.
You married such a wonderful wife.
Yes, she's great.
Congratulations!
Your seat over there.
It's up front.
Xu Yan.
Thank you for the book, Mr. Xu.
Could you please sign it for me?
Alright.
Mr. and Mrs. Xu.
What a surprise.
Where's Jiajia?
She's too busy with work.
We came to visit relatives.
We're staying here,
planning to stay in Jingzhou
before returning hometown.
Never expected to meet you here.
Congratulations!
By the way, I have a gift for Jiajia.
Maybe you come with me to get it.
Yan, who are these two?
Let me introduce.
They are my college classmate's parents.
This is my husband.
Hello.
My father-in-law.
My father.
Hello.
Congratulations to you all!
You're such a well-matched couple.
- Congratulations!
- Thanks.
Since we met here,
if you don't mind,
come join us.
Would it bother you?
No.
Please, come in.
This way, please.
Please.
- What's your surname?
- Xu.
Same surname to Xu Yan.
Exactly, I'm also a Xu.
Surprise.
Hello.
Yan, I'll take him in.
Alright.
Come on.
Thank you, Dad.
Thank you, Mom.
Thanks.
Thank you, Ms. Ma.
Thank you.
Cheers.
Have a toast.
Here.
Come on.
Haoming. Congratulations!
- Cheers!
- Thanks!
Haoming, what a wonderful wedding.
You're a workaholic.
Was all this prepared by Yan?
So this toast shouldn't go to you.
To our beautiful and capable Yan!
To Yan!
Xu Yan has already had enough drink.
No more drink.
I'll take this drink for her.
Liquor?
Drink three glasses.
Yes, three glasses!
Come on.
Three glasses it is!
Good.
First!
Impressive!
Another one!
Second!
- Amazing!
- Good!
One more to go!
Alright.
Last one!
Third one!
- Another!
- The final one!
Mr. Shen.
Mr. Xu.
Honored to attend
Xu Yan's wedding.
We two...
Enjoy your drinks.
Thank you.
Thank you, everyone.
Alright.
Next table.
Come on.
Mr. Xu, you came to Jingzhou for...
For vacation.
Stay for a few days,
then go to hometown.
Why the rush?
Stay in Jingzhou longer.
I'm reaching retirement age,
planning to return and settle
back in my hometown.
Great.
The medical facilities, shopping,
and everything is much better.
Mr. Xu, what do you do overseas?
Architecture studies.
Construction?
Then you're in the same field
as my in-law.
Really?
What a double fate!
Cheers!
You look gorgeous.
One more.
Cheers!
Thank you.
Come on.
Yan.
Your classmate's parents
came here first time.
Go greet them.
Okay, I'll be right back.
Your dress looks lovely.
Come on.
How many more?
One last glass.
One glass.
I'll drink.
He has
deep expertise in architecture,
even wrote a book,
called... something...
Sustainable Building Design.
My father specializes in
sustainable building research.
My research focuses
on architectural mechanics.
Though in the same field,
our focuses differ.
Let's chat if you have time.
Absolutely.
Mr. Xu.
We've finally gathered today.
Why don't we take a photo?
You can show it to Jiajia. How's it?
Great idea.
Come on.
Okay.
Take a photo.
Alright.
I'll get Haoming.
Let's be here.
Alright?
This way.
This spot, okay?
You silly!
- I'm sorry.
Sorry, sorry.
Let me.
Look at this mess.
Here.
So sorry.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
I'm so sorry.
I live upstairs.
I'll go change.
- Sorry.
- It's fine.
We'll cover the dry cleaning.
We're so sorry.
Don't mind it.
The wedding matters.
See you.
Alright.
I'm sorry.
This way.
I'm really sorry.
I'll have them get you
a new suit.
No need.
I have one upstairs.
Okay.
Your turn.
Haoming.
Happy wedding!
Thanks.
- Congratulations!
- Thank you.
Let me introduce you.
She's my sister,
just graduated from law school.
- Impressive!
- Great.
You know what?
She's still single.
Be proactive.
What a coincidence!
Haoming and I go way back.
I'm single.
Add my WeChat.
Haoming, what's her name?
Fang Lei.
Miss Fang.
Add me.
Come on.
Add my WeChat.
Add my WeChat too.
Miss Fang, hello.
I'm Han Weiping, from legal department
of Jinda Group.
Can I add your WeChat?
It'd better
to keep in touch.
I'll add you.
Okay, okay.
Here.
Done.
Miss Fang, add me too.
- Here.
- Add me.
Add me.
Come on.
Let me scan too.
Miss Fang, add me.
Okay.
(At the infinity pool.)
(Think drunk people)
(drown easily?)
Being drunk in a pool isn't safe.
Come up!
I don't want to go back.
I need to sober up here.
Suit yourself.
Aren't you afraid
I'll drown like my sister did?
Don't ever say that.
It brings bad luck.
This is my wedding day.
Is this drama necessary?
Haoming.
Remember our first meeting?
I remember very clearly
what color you're wearing that day.
Even the sunlight that day
and the scent in the air,
I remember every single detail.
I thought I could let you go,
but seeing you get married today,
watching you walk down the aisle,
I realize
I can never let you go.
Shen Haoming,
I love you.
I'm married now.
Back off.
You mean that woman?
Don't think she's that naive.
She pretended to be close with me
once we met,
just to figure out our relationship.
That Xu Yan is calculating.
Why marry her?
Your performance at the wedding today
was quite dramatic.
No need
to overthink anything.
Just drop it.
Once sobered up,
go home.
Won't we miss our flight?
Relax.
Haoming.
Yan.
Leaving for your honeymoon now?
Yes.
You drank so much for me yesterday.
Feeling okay?
I was completely drunk.
Don't even remember
how I got home.
Right.
Last night,
did I cause any trouble?
No.
Glad to hear that.
Yan.
You two talk.
I'll wait in the car.
Haoming said
you're honeymooning in London.
There's a great steakhouse over there.
Haoming used to take me there often.
What places did Haoming
take you before?
Please sort it out and send it to me.
Don't go in the pool after drinking.
You could be drowned.
Mr. Shen.
Yan.
You're finally back.
We've missed you!
We brought souvenirs for everyone.
The driver'll bring them up
to you.
Got it.
Thank you.
Han Weiping,
Jinda Group's
newly hired legal consultant,
young and capable.
They met at our wedding.
Lei has good taste.
Let's go.
By the way,
let's go visit Grandma in a few days.
But we just got back.
It's fine. It won't affect work.
I've asked for leave.
Okay.
We can bring Grandma her gifts.
Alright.
♪It's no surprise♪
♪Being happy is so hard♪
♪Weirdly, I became a role model♪
♪On the day we met again, we said hi♪
♪It was a reminder,
a test, and a complaint♪
♪Who can do anything without regret♪
Grandma.
Yan.
You fell asleep?
I really miss you!
Let me see.
You've lost weight!
Again?
Haven't you been eating well?
You're the one who's lost weight.
No way. You...
Hello, Grandma.
I'm your grandson-in-law, Shen Haoming.
I brought you some gifts.
What a handsome man!
Welcome home.
Come in.
You didn't need to bring
so many gifts to me.
I can't possibly eat all this by myself.
I brought glucosamine for you.
It helps prevent osteoporosis.
Too much!
Haoming said
you need to keep taking this fish oil.
It helps lower your cholesterol.
Do you know?
Grandma.
It smells wonderful.
What's this?
This...
Fresh greens.
You city folks can't get this.
I picked them fresh
at the vegetable patch this afternoon.
You city people always talk about
green and eco-friendly,
and pollution-free.
What's that dish then?
Oxtail and taro stew.
Nourishing.
Grandma, you live here alone.
So Yan's parents...
Grandma.
This one.
I brought your favorite photo.
I'll hang it...
In the bedroom
where I can easily see.
Go on!
It's all greasy smoke.
- Don't stay here.
- Come.
Right.
Serve it up!
Look.
Is this okay?
It seems slightly tilted to the left.
Yan.
Is this okay?
Good.
Perfect.
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.xyz or dramacool.club
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Yan,
I prepared a room for you
with a double bed.
Why don't you sleep there
but squeeze into my bed instead?
I rarely come back.
I want to sleep with you.
You insist on sleeping with me.
You don't come back often.
Just sleep with him, will you?
Why sleep with me?
- Let me.
- It seems...
Hand over your hand.
It's that simple?
I can't make it right.
Let me help you.
Yan,
there's something
I need to tell you.
Your father hasn't been well recently,
and he did a body checkup.
The test results
said there's a tumor in his lung.
Is it benign?
It appears benign for now.
But the doctor said
he mustn't overexert himself
from now on.
As for whether this benign state
might turn malignant,
the doctor can't guarantee.
I know how you think of him.
But you didn't invite him
to your wedding.
Now that he's ill,
I think
you should
go visit him.
Is this length okay?
Perfect.
Okay, switch hands.
If you don't want to go alone,
I can go with you.
I understand.
Listen.
See?
When trimming nails,
you must cut the edges
like this.
Like this.
Otherwise, you'll get paronychia.
T-This is so difficult.
I always use
small scissors
to trim them.
Shen,
got up so early?
Work habits keep me rising early.
Come grocery shopping with me?
Okay, let's go.
You young people
run big companies
and chase grand career.
You need to balance work and rest.
Health should be your top priority.
Only when you're well-rested,
and well-fed
can you achieve great things.
Come visit more often.
The fresh air here does wonders.
Okay, I'll do it.
You know, Yan cares about you
most, Grandma.
You're getting old,
and it's hard to live alone.
Move to Jingzhou with us, okay?
No, no.
My legs still work fine.
I've lived here for my life.
I can't get used to the city life.
Don't worry about me.
Rest assured.
If you need anything,
tell us anytime.
Before you leave,
I want to say something to you.
Go ahead.
Every time Yan called,
she praised you,
saying you're great
and treating her well.
After I've met you,
you're exactly as she said.
I really like you.
We're a married couple.
I should treat her well.
Shen,
I've raised Yan since she was a kid.
I'm just an old country woman,
couldn't teach her much.
She might have
some bad habits or whatnot.
If she makes mistakes,
can you be more forgiving?
Okay.
Give her a chance to improve.
Okay?
Absolutely, Grandma.
I remember every word
you said.
Rest assured.
What do we buy later?
What would you like to eat?
I want oysters.
There aren't oysters here.
But we have fresh fish here.
Fish?
(For your treatment.)
(Password is Qiao Lin's birthday.)
We're here.
What do you think?
Blue bricks, gray tiles,
and bamboo groves.
Every inch of this space
seems to whisper
tales of tranquility and peace.
That's why
it's called Jingzhou's retreat.
As expected from
a top journalism student,
so eloquent.
Stop teasing me.
I just feel that in such spaces
we should speak poetically
to suit the vibe here.
In this vast city,
having such a serene corner
instantly soothes all anxieties.
It's truly wonderful.
I think in a completely different way.
Alright, tell me,
what do you think?
Here, look.
All the plumbing and wiring
needs renovation.
Behind you is the kitchen.
The bathroom
needs to get
the waterproofing repairs.
Why do you know this place so well?
You.
You'll be the lady of this retreat.
Work connections help you meet guests
and expand your network.
That's good.
But mere show interactions
aren't enough for real connections.
Off-camera relationships
require
maintenance too.
The location is excellent,
private and secure.
Perfect for hosting
gatherings with friends.
This will benefit your career.
Yan, listen.
The better you work,
the more influence
you'll gain at the network.
It'll benefit your anchor application.
You think I don't know
you practice broadcasting at 5 AM?
You're my wife now.
Whatever dreams you have,
I'll help you make them real.
Go check inside.
Come on.
Is it enough for a dining area?
More than sufficient.
In such prime location,
this space is sufficient.
I think we should
put cabinets here.
And dining area's here.
But these white walls seem too plain.
So...
(Soon, I'll be as tall as Dad)
The previous owners left
their child's height markings
on the frame.
How adorable.
When I was little,
Dad measured my height like this too.
These are precious,
so I kept them intact.
(You kid!)
(Stand still. Dad's measuring.)
Come here.
Do it again.
- No cheating.
- Hey!
Do it again.
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.xyz or dramacool.club
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Ready? Okay.
Stand straight.
There.
Move.
Come.
Come to me.
Last time was 133cm.
Now it's 134cm.
How much did you grow?
One centimeter.
Let's celebrate Lin's growth!
I'll cook you delicious dishes, okay?
I remember too.
Have a lipstick?
Stand still.
♪I like it when it's just me and you♪
♪I think by now you know it♪
♪About me and you♪
♪There's not a thing that I wouldn't do♪
♪Right now just to be here with you♪
♪I like you♪
♪Here in my arms♪
♪What already happened♪
♪Feeling so lost and feeling♪
♪So much distractions♪
♪Never imagined♪
♪You'd stay by my side♪
♪Comforting my sorrows♪
♪On the midnight streets♪
♪In shadowed corners♪
♪Remember that moment♪
♪You smiled and looked at me♪
Are my legs this short?
♪Just you and me♪
♪Enjoying the city life♪
♪Holding your hand♪
♪And I just want to tell you♪
♪Want to preserve this feeling♪
♪Forever in my heart♪
♪I like it when it's just me and you♪
♪I think by now you know it♪
♪Do you know, my dear♪
♪Not sorry if we ditch the crowd♪
♪Just hope you feel the same way too♪
♪About me and you♪
♪Like fireworks that loved♪
♪Rushing toward the stars♪
♪Undaunted by pain♪
♪Fearless of flames♪
♪Even if just a fleeting sparkle♪
♪We shed tears♪
♪Deep blue seas turn to foam♪
♪We regained freedom♪
♪If you remember me♪
♪Then I'm pleased♪
♪I just wanna take my time tonight♪
♪To do all the things I said I'd try♪
♪I go surfing, go diving, go driving,
and go flying to a different place♪
♪I go drink, go party, and go dance♪
♪Even if I'm lonely♪
♪Cause I just have been hurt
too many times♪
♪I'm giving it all to get nothing back♪
♪I was lost in the dark,
and it's too hurt to even see♪
♪See the world and how it flows.
We never let go♪
♪So I'll take my time♪
♪To reignite♪
♪The love I should deserve♪
♪When the time is right♪
♪You realize♪
♪It will all be alright♪
♪Cause I just have been hurt
too many times♪
♪I'm giving it all to get nothing back♪
♪I was lost in the dark,
and it's too hurt to even see♪
♪See the world and how it flows.
We never let go♪
♪So I'll take my time♪
♪To reignite♪
♪The love I should deserve♪
♪When the time is right♪
♪You realize♪
♪It will all be alright♪