WHEN THE PHONE RINGS
Let's go.
MEMORIAL GATE
Chief, I'm sorry. Excuse me for a moment.
Yes, what is it?
This is Yongju Silver Care Hospital.
We can't locate Mr. Na Jin-cheol.
Your number was listed
as the emergency contact, so I called you.
Okay, I'll be right there.
What's the matter?
There seems to be an issue
with my father-in-law.
Oh, no. Then you should hurry.
Use my official vehicle.
They'll get you there quickly and safely.
Oh, dear.
Are you okay?
What?
Why are they coming towards us?
- Did we do something wrong?
- No way!
We didn't do anything.
Hello. Thank you for your hard work.
You may leave now.
Pardon?
I'll come to the station
to file the report.
I'm sorry,
but what's your relationship with her?
We're family.
Excuse me?
She is…
my wife.
Stay here.
- My wife gave this case to me.
- He's Paik Sa-eon.
I have a favor to ask.
Yes, please go ahead.
I'll visit as soon as I can
to file the report.
In the meantime, please keep
our personal information private.
Yes, of course.
We'll ensure strict security.
Thank you.
By the way…
- Don't do it. Don't.
- I also have a favor to ask.
I know this isn't the greatest situation,
but may I get a picture with you?
If you keep your promise,
I'll take a picture with you
at the station.
I see. Okay.
- Well, then.
- Okay, see you again.
Go safely.
Your father's nurse…
has my number.
Anyway, we should move him
to a different nursing home.
How could he go so far?
From now on,
you don't have to worry about your father.
I'll take care of it.
You're making sounds.
Hong Hee-joo…
can make sounds.
You look so ugly right now.
I'm not telling you to stop crying.
Cry as much as you want.
One tteokbokki set with gimbap,
fish cakes, and sundae with the entrails.
Can I have one?
Come more often!
- Okay?
- I'm here!
I'm just happy to see you.
You get prettier by the day.
I was always pretty.
- Are you just getting off work?
- My goodness.
We don't have a show today.
What brings you here?
Well…
Oh, my.
Don't tell me…
Did you come hoping to run into me?
Come on.
We're visiting a site together
in a few days!
I was kidding.
Do you live in Yeouido?
Yeah, it's near the hospital.
Thank you.
Is it…
your birthday today?
- What?
- That looks like a feast.
This is one serving for me.
I see.
That day at the French restaurant,
it didn't even make a dent in my stomach.
Eat up.
Hey.
Interpreter Hong Hee-joo.
It's her, isn't it?
Your secret crush.
I could just tell that day.
You said you've been through
unrequited love like a fan before.
Remember?
Well… I'm curious about something too.
Spokesperson Paik Sa-eon.
Why are you such a big fan of him?
Well…
Me?
I didn't like him at first.
Actually, I was so scared of him.
ON AIR
Are you saying there are no standards
to regulate microplastics?
Yes, a bill must be prepared
through National Assembly discussions.
That's all that I've prepared.
Then, what could be
realistic regulatory measures?
Excuse me?
MICROPLASTIC SWALLOWING THE OCEAN
Well…
First, we should reduce plastic use
and use tumblers instead of disposables.
That would be more of an individual effort
and a recommendation.
What could be legally prohibited?
Well…
Anchor Na You-ri?
Aside from just raising the issue,
are there no concrete solutions prepared?
Well… I…
He's breaking in a new recruit again.
She looks like she'll cry.
Thank you for your presentation.
Come in by two o'clock from tomorrow.
You mean, two o'clock in the morning?
If you're to run it by me for review,
learn how to write it, and practice,
it's not that early.
You'll teach me yourself?
An anchor isn't a parrot
that simply reads off a script.
Plus, for the morning news, you should
come in by two to remove facial swelling.
Look at your face now.
You look like a soggy steamed bun.
He was scary,
but he was a good colleague
who taught me a lot.
But then one day,
he quit his job
and got appointed as spokesperson.
He even got married.
- Now it's hard to see him once a year.
- Who did he marry?
Sa-eon's family
is a famous political family.
His grandfather's a bigwig who's done
everything except for the presidency.
His father's
a strong presidential candidate.
His relatives are
former or current ministers,
prosecutor generals, mayors, lawmakers…
Naturally, he married the daughter
of a very influential family.
The eldest daughter of Chairman Hong
of Chungwoon Daily News.
Did you just remember
what day it is today?
Why a hotel room?
Wash your face. And blow your nose too.
Yes, this is room service.
I need to get it together.
I have to stay focused from now on.
Should we talk now?
Sit down.
Take out your phone.
Because from now on,
I want us to have a conversation.
- Not an interrogation?
- It's not an interrogation.
As you know,
someone's been messing with us lately.
Your car, my office,
and even your father's nursing home
this time.
I haven't requested
a police investigation yet.
But if this continues,
I'll have no other choice.
If you're the victim instead of me,
the police will start digging into you.
So before that happens,
tell me if you're hiding anything.
I guess there is something.
I could keep pressuring you
until I force it out of you, but…
I won't.
I won't do that, Hee-joo.
We're not close enough to interfere
with each other's lives, right?
Leave it at the door.
Eat this and rest.
Come down afterward. I'll go first.
You haven't settled from the shock yet.
You know you'll be very tense down there.
Don't overdo it. Just do as I say.
Another glass.
Relax.
What?
Ouch.
Do you have a plan?
It shouldn't just be
another regular meal today, right?
Didn't the aides make a plan?
I don't need a grand plan for this.
A disobedient child?
Just beat him until he obeys.
Don't worry.
You're here.
Why are you alone?
Where is she?
She's not feeling well.
Call her.
Did you not hear me?
Bring her here right now.
Let's eat.
I only have an hour to spare.
Didn't you have something to say to me?
Appear on a show?
Yeah.
A special on presidential candidates.
Just anyone does it these days.
You know, cooking, dancing, and singing.
Come when we're filming.
Come and sit.
Others bring their sons, daughters-in-law,
and even their dogs and cats
to promote themselves.
But our family…
The only thing I can boast about
is my son.
Have you still not heard from your sister?
Don't bring that up again.
You know, I really think
Chairman Hong tricked me.
He never intended to give us
his eldest daughter in the first place.
Right? He's so skeptical.
He's scared I might lose the election.
That's why he sent
his flawed daughter as a stand-in.
What exactly is your purpose?
Even if you were a bargain,
you should be able to earn your keep.
Why can't you do anything?
What are you doing?
It's rude. We're eating.
Bring it.
Welcome.
There's a paparazzi
taking pictures of guests here.
"Spokesperson Paik Sa-eon meets with
his father, Paik Ui-yong, for dinner."
"Will he join the election campaign?"
Is that the headline you wanted?
I'll decide whether or not to participate
in your election.
Coercion, threats, subtle manipulation.
Don't even think of it.
You little punk.
You arrogant brat.
You punk.
Do you know what will happen
if you keep acting like this?
The moment you step out of my shadow,
you could get crushed completely.
Do you really think I'm still in there?
What did you say?
Wait.
It's not you, is it?
What do you mean?
I know you'd do anything
to get me to surrender.
- So the thought crossed my mind.
- What are you talking about?
Make some damn sense!
I'll say one thing.
You're at the threshold
of being president, thanks to Grandfather.
The least you could do
is step over it on your own.
Don't whine
and ask me to push you.
What?
- Are you done?
- I am.
And I'll leave now.
Was this your plan?
You ruined everything.
That punk started it!
Damn it.
That damned punk.
I bet you…
want to divorce me.
You married me in place
of your missing sister and can't speak.
So you can't even defend yourself
when your in-laws spout nonsense.
They're people
who can easily replace their children.
So whatever they say,
don't listen to them or take it to heart.
PARK DO-JAE
Go inside.
Yes, go ahead.
The detective in charge
of the nursing home incident just called.
He said the blood analysis results
confirmed animal blood and fake teeth.
Animal?
Okay.
Also, I have a personal request.
Call…
Call him.
Sis.
No backing out in the middle.
You started this,
so you see it through.
Got it?
Sis!
I can't…
do this anymore.
Where are you going?
Is that trash?
Give it to me.
I'll take it out.
DIRECTOR HAN JIN-E
- Hey, Hee-joo!
- Hee-joo!
You can do this! Good luck! You got this!
Good luck!
Let's go!
To the president's office!
Thanks, everyone.
Don't mention it.
Dinner's on you if you pass!
Good luck! We love you!
I'll wish you luck too.
You'll pass.
If I get it, what then?
What do you mean?
We talked about this before.
If our families find out
I'm working beside you…
Hong Hee-joo.
How much longer
will you live as the obedient child?
Aren't you sick of others
telling you what to do?
It's your chance to try
with your name on the line.
Chicken out and blow it
or give up over what others think.
Do whatever you want.
Okay, then you should start thinking about
how you're going to handle
the aftermath if I get the job.
PARK DO-JAE
I looked into what you asked for.
CLASSY COUNTY
WE MEET ANOTHER FAMILY MEMBER TODAY
Looks good. Let's go with this.
Our spokesperson has never been this late
to work before.
Is something wrong?
He has matters to take care of,
so he'll be late.
- Hello.
- I have something to report.
- Me too.
It's urgent. I'll go first.
Mine's urgent too.
Mr. Park.
Yes, sir.
I'm the section chief.
I have something to discuss
regarding the voice modulation.
Did you find something?
If we analyze
the waveform and spectrogram,
I think we'll be able to determine
the pitch range, age, and gender.
We don't need the gender.
To be honest, I'm not curious
about that pervert's voice.
Just in case, it might be someone I know.
- That's why I want to unmask him.
- Okay.
I'll report it as soon as it's done.
Okay.
And this is regarding Ji Sang-woo.
A lot of his videos
are about unsolved cases
related to arson and bombs.
He seems to be very knowledgeable
about explosions and arson methods.
And currently,
he's appearing on HBC's Crime Report.
It's a mystery crime program.
"Crime Report"?
Okay.
- You're excused.
- Yes, sir.
Sir.
It's the final interview list
for the sign language interpreters.
HONG HEE-JOO
The interviews will start soon.
Will you join?
CANDIDATE ID
HONG HEE-JOO
It's your chance to try
with your name on the line.
Chicken out and blow it
or give up over what others think.
Do whatever you want.
Candidate 24, 25, and 26, please be ready.
2024 PRESIDENTIAL OFFICE
SIGN LANGUAGE INTERPRETER INTERVIEW
You'll conduct a real briefing
for the final interview.
It'll be a practical exam.
In case of real-time interpretation,
quick thinking and sign language speed
are especially important.
I'll play an existing briefing video.
Candidate…
number 24, Hong Hee-joo,
we'll start with you.
PRESIDENTIAL OFFICE
The 2020 Korea-Egypt summit briefing.
Korea and Egypt
have complementary industrial structures,
which offer great potential
for expanding trade and investment.
It is hoped that
the Korea-Egypt Trade and Economic
Partnership Joint Research MOU
will lead to an FTA
between the two countries.
Also, it was expressed that there's hope
for cooperative projects
to strengthen administrative capabilities
by sharing South Korea's
digital information expertise.
Furthermore, both countries agreed
to open a new chapter
of mutually beneficial cooperation
in key areas such as economic investment,
cultural heritage preservation
and management,
energy, advanced technologies,
and defense,
aiming to establish
a comprehensive partnership
between the two nations.
As emphasized, this will boost
our country's overall competitiveness.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Yes?
I understand.
SPOKESPERSON BRIEFING
Candidate number 24,
interpreter Hong Hee-joo.
I want you to answer
the questions I ask honestly.
Did you know the script in advance?
It wasn't simultaneous interpretation.
I noticed that you signed
before I even spoke sometimes.
How will you explain this?
I practiced to these videos.
If that's the case,
can we test you with a different video?
Yes.
For a healthy society,
all citizens must unite
in caring for and educating children.
This is something that all members
of society must participate in.
Enough.
Next video.
Our government has consistently expressed
its willingness
to engage in dialogue
to resolve the issue.
- Next.
- Diplomatic communication…
In the current situation where
business leaders are facing difficulties
and everyone is trying their best
in their respective positions,
- we must answer what truly…
- Next.
…serves the people…
To prevent further harm
to the victim's reputation
through reports where even the facts
have not been verified,
I ask that journalists exercise caution.
Did you practice to all of these?
Yes.
It'll be the same
with any other video you play.
Why have you memorized all the videos?
I practiced a lot with your videos.
They were chosen at random,
regardless of the year or content.
But your hands move at the same speed
and timing as my voice.
Is that a coincidence?
It's not just once or twice.
Interpreter Hong Hee-joo,
answer my question.
What did you just say?
Interpreter Hong Hee-joo!
I said I did it because I was crazy.
Wow.
She was crazy.
I was obsessed
with your briefings, Mr. Paik.
I've dreamed of becoming a sign language
interpreter for a government agency.
That became excessive…
This is the result of intense practicing?
How your upper lip and upper teeth move
when you set your articulation points,
I studied that a lot in particular.
I can predict consonants
from the sounds your tongue makes
against the roof of your mouth.
So, as soon as I open my mouth…
No, wait.
Your hands move faster
when you predict it?
And you studied it that obsessively?
I mimicked, practiced, and dug into it.
But…
can you not speak at all?
Personal disabilities
aren't disqualifying factors,
so she passed the document review.
And the job of an interpreter is to listen
and convey it with their hands, so…
If you get the job,
how will you communicate
with the spokesperson's team?
2024 PRESIDENTIAL OFFICE
SIGN LANGUAGE INTERPRETER INTERVIEW
I don't know why, but he's fixated.
It might take a while.
The interview is running behind.
I hope you understand.
Can you use sign language?
If you can't, I'll teach you.
You need to learn so you can see
whether we interpreters are conveying
your message properly.
If the nuance is off,
you can correct it right away.
Sign language isn't difficult.
If you learn it, there won't be issues
communicating with me either.
You're right. That's a good idea.
We'll discuss that if you get the job.
Finally,
I want to test you on something.
I'll read a document
that you've never seen before,
on the spot.
Can you do it?
Yes.
Then, let's begin.
Couple's Day…
is a national observance
established to remind us
of the importance of marital relationships
and to encourage
the building of harmonious families.
There's a couple here now.
The two have lived
without being able to open up
to each other.
Would things have been different…
if they had been more honest
and shown their true feelings?
If they try to make an effort now,
could they live
like any other ordinary couple?
Yet again today,
like how a mind game is played,
the couple merely tries to read
each other's minds.
The ironic thing is that
their behavior is surprisingly similar.
That's enough.
Let's stop here.
I can assure you,
there's no one better than me.
I can tell by a person's expression.
I know what you're going to say
and what you're thinking.
I mimicked, practiced, and dug into it.
Hong Hee-joo.
What are you…
CANDIDATE ID
HONG HEE-JOO
I did a good job.
Well done.
Classy County?
We should move him
to a different nursing home.
- …work this much?
- Tell me about it.
He's an anchor.
You weren't a farmer?
That'll be hard in old age too.
So true.
Ta-da.
Dried persimmons. Your favorite.
Yeah, they're good.
- They're from Sangju.
- Yeah.
Dad, do you like it here?
Tastes good.
It's much nicer than before, right?
Dad?
I'm sorry.
That will never happen again.
Don't worry, okay?
Dad, who did--
"Don't worry, Father."
"No matter what happens,
I'll protect you and Hee-joo."
He came here?
Warm, right?
So warm, yet so cold.
So harsh, yet so kind.
I can't figure him out.
I thought I knew him well,
but I don't think I do at all.
Today's sign language interpreter
interview evaluation.
Is the press release ready?
It's being finalized.
By the way,
about interpreter Hong Hee-joo
who had an interview earlier,
were you pleased with her or not?
Why do you want to know that?
Excuse me?
Because…
Everyone found out
you turned the interview room upside down,
so we made a bet for fun…
A bet?
For fun?
We were about to, but we decided not to,
and we won't.
What? A bet? No way.
In this crucial decision
to select an interpreter
to be the voice of our office…
By the way, I like her.
Interpreter Hong Hee-joo,
who studied you so passionately.
So do I.
I like her.
Pardon?
HONG HEE-JOO
Congratulations.
Thank you.
You didn't eat anything.
Not eating as an invited guest
is considered disrespectful.
Eat it.
My son…
likes fish.
Stop stuffing your face!
I didn't eat anything yet.
I told you not to act pathetic.
Learn from your sister.
Let's switch.
Eat it.
Slow down.
What's your name?
"Hong."
"Hee."
"Joo."
HONG HEE-JOO
"Hong Hee-joo"?
When did you grow up so much?
Thank you.
You changed my dad's nursing home.
He read it right away.
HONG IN-A
What are you saying?
You want me to go in In-a's place
at the wedding tomorrow?
Have you ever imagined that, Hee-joo?
You and I come from humble beginnings,
and now we'll be
the future president's in-laws!
Keep it safe.
If the real owner returns,
you might have to give it back.
Start.
SA-EON
What? Right now? At this hour?
Why?
No, wait. Don't overthink it.
Just answer it.
Hello? Sa-eon?
Hey, it's me. I only have three minutes.
I'll make it quick.
Oh, my.
By chance, did you just add water
to your cup noodles too?
No, I'm driving.
Oh, I see.
Ji Sang-woo I met the other day.
- He's doing a program with you, right?
- Yes.
Age 34. Yeonhui University College
of Medicine, class of 2010.
Director of Bliss Care Clinic.
Do you know anything else about him?
Did you run a background check on him?
Do you know anything about him
that's not on the website?
I have two minutes left.
Well…
Right. He lives in Yeouido.
Near the HBC building.
- And.
- And?
And…
He grew up in an orphanage!
An orphanage?
No! Never mind!
NURI DREAM CENTER
Is it Nuri Dream Center?
Formerly known as Sinil Childcare Center?
How did you know?
But…
why do you want to know?
I'm out of time.
Enjoy your noodles.
It seems you messed up again, 406.
You asked me before,
what do I get in return
if you get rid of Hong Hee-joo?
I'll answer that question.
What is it?
Hong In-a.
In-a needs a place to return to.
You and your family wanted
Hong In-a from the start anyway.
Hong Hee-joo…
is just a stand-in puppet.
There.
So get rid of Hong Hee-joo.
Before Hong In-a returns
and complicates things,
- take care of Hong Hee-joo--
- 406, you don't know anything.
What?
I'll only say this once,
so listen carefully.
Before Hong In-a disappeared,
the last person she met with
before the wedding
was me.
What?
I guess you didn't dig that deep.
When you two met,
what did you talk about?
We made a deal.
What deal?
Because of that deal,
Hong In-a can never become
Paik Sa-eon's wife.
What now?
I think I just got rid of
your motive for blackmail.
He met with In-a?
They made a deal? What deal?
You're still up?
I thought you'd be sleeping
after the stressful day you had today.
I owe you an apology
for underestimating you.
You did great.
But the official results
haven't been announced yet.
So don't get ahead of yourself.
Also,
I'm attending the Chungwoon Daily News
anniversary event tomorrow.
Why all of a sudden?
Do you know or not
that my sister is back?
You look beautiful.
- Hello.
- Hi, so pretty.
You know what day it is today, right?
I want something special.
Hello.
Look who it is.
Ms. Lee.
Can you have two clients
in one room like this?
I'm sorry. Show her to the waiting room.
We're a family.
You're always so busy.
I didn't think you'd make it to the event.
Just like last time,
I thought your husband
would be coming with a cute aide.
I want my hair to be higher than hers.
Make my eyeliner wings longer too!
CHUNGWOON DAILY NEWS
LEADING THE ERA, UNITING GENERATIONS
CHUNGWOON CULTURAL FOUNDATION SCHOLARSHIP
CHUNGWOON
LEADING THE ERA, UNITING GENERATIONS
CHUNGWOON DAILY NEWS
70TH ANNIVERSARY CELEBRATION
WITH THE PEOPLE
CHUNGWOON DAILY NEWS
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
We'll begin the cutting of the cake.
Congratulations.
I wish you infinite success
and development in the future.
Thank you so much.
You're the busiest man in our country,
yet you made it.
You flatter me.
We wouldn't miss
such a meaningful and joyous day.
But…
I don't see our spokesperson yet.
I wonder if the presidential office
is looking for a successor.
If he wants to join
the presidential campaign,
isn't it time he left his position?
Of course.
But as you know, he has so much ambition.
I'm not sure if he'll give up his career
and join me.
But still,
I'll try harder to convince him.
How delightful.
Yes, okay.
Hee-joo.
Come with me.
What's this about your dad?
The hospital called and said he was moved.
Is that true?
Your son-in-law moved him.
He did?
Are you telling me
he found out about your dad?
How could you let that happen?
What if the chairman finds out?
Aren't you going to ask why he was moved
or what happened to him?
I don't care.
Anyway, now that he's been moved,
I don't need to pay anymore, right?
That's much better.
Did you see Sa-eon?
He's in a whole different class now.
I know, right?
Is In-a not coming again today?
She hasn't shown her face in public
since she got married.
The president's daughter-in-law,
someone of great importance.
Such a big deal.
But In-a's sister is here.
- She's such an attention-seeker.
- I always found her a bit off.
She followed In-a around like a shadow.
So creepy.
- Another glass of wine?
- Shall we? Let's go.
Must be nice.
- Let's toast.
- Cheers.
CALLS
PAIK SA-EON
406, Hong Hee-joo.
He must not care about either.
Hello?
Speak.
Your fiancée disappeared
the day before the wedding,
and Hong Hee-joo stepped in instead.
How did you feel?
Well, I get it.
I'm sure it wasn't great.
It was similar.
Right.
What use is she? Who else would take her?
She's gloomy.
She has no social skills.
She's just…
the supplementary pages
that came with Hong In-a.
Yeah.
That's what she is.
Do you know what's funnier?
She always knew that too.
But she hesitated each time
even though she wanted to break free.
She didn't have the courage.
She hated rich families
but was comforted by luxury.
She cowardly succumbed to money.
Hello?
Hee-joo…
isn't gloomy.
She's observing her surroundings.
She doesn't lack social skills.
In general, people are rude to her first.
Also, she didn't succumb to money.
She just…
loved her mother.
There was a time
when I hated to eat or speak
with my mouth.
I was surrounded by greedy,
noisy, and bothersome people.
And she was the most quiet.
When I stared at her…
strangely, I could breathe easily.
What did you say?
Supplementary pages?
If you don't know, listen carefully, 406.
Hee-joo isn't supplementary pages.
She's a brand-new language.
She's repeated the same hand movements
thousands of times to become who she is.
People don't know that.
So don't talk about my wife like that.
Then why did you treat her
like she was invisible?
You say you know her so well,
then why did you do that?
Why did you tell her
not to think you were a couple?
WHEN THE PHONE RINGS
Okay, I'll take it now.
One, two, three!
That was nice. One more.
Wait. Can I shake your hand?
Of course.
Okay. One, two, three!
Thank you so much.
It came out great.
My wife will love this.
Sure.
Then, the report…
That's right.
I almost forgot.
Is your wife okay?
Thanks to you.
Thank you for your concern.
We're relieved to hear it.
She was so shocked that day.
I thought she was having a panic attack.
A panic attack?
Yes.
She was like…
Her face got so pale.
She was screaming so loudly too.
We were on the road then,
but I pulled over and let her out.
It would've been bad if we hadn't.
Wait.
What did you just say?
What?
Well…
- A panic…
- No, not that.
She screamed?
My wife did?
What is it?
What's wrong?
- What…
- Are you feeling sick?
Let me out.
We're on the road right now.
It'll be okay if you just let me out.
It'll be okay, so let me out!
Please, let me out!
I can't do this. Just let me out.
Just let me out.
Please, let me out!
WHEN THE PHONE RINGS
Why did you go that far?
Don't you have any?
Something you're hiding from me.
This is great for Hee-joo!
She's going to the presidential office.
What's a good gift
to give someone who just got a job?
I look forward to working with you.
Don't be surprised.
Gender of 406 is…
- A woman?
- Paik Sa-eon!
Subtitle translation by: Sue Mounce