Ouch!
shit...
Hey, are you okay?
Shit! Blood!!
What’s up?
Tai, there’s blood! Blood!
Champ, where are you?
At Sorn’s place!
What’s happening?
Champ!
Are you alright?
Where’s the blood?
It’s on my foot.
Here.
That’s a big wound.
Want me to call an ambulance?
Shit…
Tai…
please just tell me
where Jun is.
When you were doing stuff behind my back
you didn’t tell me
so why should I tell you now?
Tai…
just help him out, please.
You’re close with HR at the company.
That’s your hint.
If you still don’t get it
you’re dumb.
Damn…
how could I be this stupid?
If you two are gonna get it on,
make sure to lock the house, okay?
Hey,
what’s going on here?
I’ll go check it out, baby.
Who is it?
I want to see P’Penny.
We need to have a talk.
I need help.
You only come when you need help.
But how many times have you left her before?
You act like I’m the only one you’ve got.
I’m not being sarcastic,
just telling the truth.
Next thing I know you’ll say
you didn’t want Jun to be lonely or some crap like that.
I feel sorry for Jun,
If I didn’t know
you didn’t like kids,
I’d think you two were...
I’m looking for jun.
You know where he’s doing his internship right now.
Why?
Is...
I and jun.
Jun and I had a fight.
It been gone from home for more than a week now.
I don’t know where to find him.
Well...
What did tai say?
He helped Jun, of course.
Even Tai
helped Jun escape?
So what’s going on?
Do you actually
like a kid now?
So what, you came here
to ask me to put out a missing person alert?
Can you save the teasing for later
and just tell me where the hell he is?
Hey,
calm down.
Take it easy. Think clearly.
Hmm...
Tai said
Jun is still interning at the company, right?
Yeah.
Then it’s simple.
If not at the office,
where else could he be interning?
Our company doesn’t have that many branches.
You bastard,
you made a fool out of me!
Mmm...
focus!
Hey Sorn, haven’t found Jun yet?
He’s probably too out of it to think straight right now.
And...
so what?
It’s nothing.
I just feel bad for him.
Don’t overthink it.
Come here,
sit down, and stop frowning
your pretty face will wrinkle, babe.
What are you thinking about?
Sorn.
He finally realized how he feels, huh.
At least now
he knows he loves Jun.
Maybe it's a bit late,
but there’s still a chance.
is that Boss Sorn?
Dude—shit!
No way he’s here—move!
Quick, quick—hold on,
this is all I got!
Hello, Boss Sorn.
Yeah.
I’m here to see Jun.
Jun hasn’t been at the factory, boss.
Sorn, where the hell are you? You're still not at the office?
I'm out looking for Jun.
Dude, you're seriously losing it.
I'll be at the office later this afternoon, alright?
No can do. It's urgent. Get your ass here now.
Alright, alright. I'm on my way.
I’m heading off.
Okay, boss. Safe travels.
Is he gone?
Yeah, he’s gone, dude.
But how did Sorn know I was here?
No idea.
Boss Tai didn’t say anything.
Why the hell are we gossiping now?
Dude, if you saw Sorn’s face earlier,
I swear—he looked shocked.
He looked so rough I thought he was a forest bandit.
Maybe he’s changing his vibe.
Changing his vibe or heartbroken from not finding you?
What the hell, man—get back to work!
Oh, Sorn.
What are you doing here?
Oh,
I came to deliver a corrected order.
This one’s fixed.
Ah, I see. Thought it was something else.
Hey, are you looking for someone?
Oh, no.
Anyway, I apologize for the earlier mistake.
It’s alright.
Good thing you checked—no major damage yet.
Yes.
Thanks.
Hello.
yes, sure.
I’ll grab the documents and check the stock real quick.
Okay, I'm done. I'll head down in a sec.
Got it.
Got you now.
Let go, P’Sorn.
Did you miss me at all?
Hmph, no.
But I missed you.
But... I didn’t miss you.
You’re lying.
If I really missed you,
I would’ve come back a long time ago.
Then talk to me properly, would you?
I told you clearly
I don’t want to see you.
No want talk to you.
or be involved with you anymore.
But I want to be involved.
You don’t have to miss me,
but I miss you.
I’m sorry for what...
I did that made you angry before.
I...
I... didn’t think it would hurt you that much.
I didn’t mean to.
You never really mean anything you do, do you?
What do I have to do to make you forgive me?
You know I suck at apologizing.
I’ve been trying, Jun.
Ever since you left.
I really tried to find you.
If you're mad that I was late…
I’m sorry.
I tried everything I could.
But Tai didn’t help at all.
I had no one on my side.
Win!
didn’t say a word about you.
Even damn Champ
didn’t know a thing.
Because Tai didn’t say shit to anyone!
I like you, Jun. I really do.
Be honest
when you talked to P’Thanu,
you said there’s no way you’d like me.
do you really not remember?
Or are you pretending you never said it?
What else did you find out?
Tell me everything,
so I can clear it all up today—once and for all.
I said that to Thanu.
But now, I’m talking to you.
I’ll believe what I heard the first time, thanks.
Where are you going?
I’m not finished talking.
I’ve got work to do.
If you don’t, that’s your problem.
You’re so stubborn, Jun.
I tried to talk to you calmly,
but you won’t listen.
You reject everything
what the hell do you even want?!
I told you I like you,
but you don’t believe me.
I already told you we’re done.
Can you respect that?
Not even as friends or brothers?
Yes!
So that’s it? That’s what you want?
You’re really gonna cut me off?
Fine, I’ll just keep chasing you like this then.
Chase what exactly, huh?
Chase you! Woo you!
Hello?
Hi P’Yim,
this is Sorn.
Sorry, Jun was just discussing something with me,
From now on, don’t block my number
or my LINE.
You don’t have to answer or read anything,
it’s fine.
You’re such a pain…
I’ll come see you again tomorrow.
Want anything to eat?
I’ll bring it.
Yes, P’Tai.
Sorn found Jun, right? What happened? Did he do anything?
He didn’t do anything, but...
P’Sorn told me he likes me.
And what did you say?
I didn’t believe him.
You really want me to trust someone like P’Sorn?
I don’t know what to do, P’Tai.
I can’t help you with that.
You’ll have to ask your own heart.
I’m scared, P’Tai.
P’Sorn is... intimidating.
He might be scary, but deep down,
Jun want to open up to him, right?
Honestly,
if I could let him go, I would’ve done it a long time ago.
Then give him a chance to prove himself.
So you’ll know—do you love him because he’s Sorn,
or because he gives you what you want?
Okay,
thanks, P’Tai.
Jun knows the job.
He’s a sharp kid.
Let him take you.
Jun!
Can you take Mr. Sorn to check the stock over there?
He had to come down himself ‘cause they were rushing him.
I’m counting on you.
This way, Mr. Sorn.
Where do you usually eat lunch?
Is the food here any good?
I’ve never tried it.
I heard the curry rice place at the end of the alley’s good.
Wanna go?
Here, the documents.
Check them fast so I can do other stuff.
The house feels so empty without you.
Can you come back and live with me?
You can keep interning here.
I’ll drop you off and pick you up every day.
All I ask is...
Can you come back and live with me again?
Noo already sent the plush toy.
It’s waiting for you to come home and name it.
I missed you like hell.
These two weeks without you—more
Can you go back to being my Jun again?
Since when was I yours?
Since the moment I wanted you to be.
I asked—when?
Why do you even want to know?
If you can’t answer, then let it go.
I’m going back to work.
It’s hot, and you keep hugging me.
Then you answer me first
when did you start liking me?
Why do you even care?
You haven’t even answered how you feel yet.
Jun....
Well...
Don't come any closer.
Saying you like me doesn’t just make everything okay, you know.
You’re such a jerk.
I really thought...
I already thought that...
you liked me too back then.
That’s why I confessed to you.
Do you even know...
It took everything I had to gather the courage to say it.
You... damn it...
I’m sorry.
I didn’t know you were this hurt.
But you were drunk, so I thought you were just messing around.
I...
damn it...
Noo even warned me.
I know how you feel.
Now I know you’re dumb too.
Cry then insult me—nice timing.
Let go, Sorn—someone’s coming.
I’m not letting go.
Answer me—will you wait for me?
I brought this for you.
Here.
Oops.
You good?
Come on, be a man a little.
Come on, come here.
Let’s try again.
Try again, man!
Win.
Oops.
Jun!
Shit.
Ow!
What about Win?
Just a little scratch, bro.
Oww, it hurts a lot!
You’ll be fine soon.
Yeah, I get hit all the time.
Here.
Hey!
That’s my shirt!
You wiped with it—what am I supposed to wear back now?
You’re not even wearing it now.
Don’t you love being shirtless?
You’re flashing everyone.
The whole factory’s probably your fan club now.
don’t act shy.
Why take your mood out on me?
Just stay quiet. Show off that body.
Look, all the ladies and aunties are drooling.
I’m blushing.
Jun.
you need to see a doctor,
Even if it’s not serious...
you still should go.
No,
I’ll be fine soon.
How do you know?
I fall a lot.
I’ll be all healed by morning.
Fine, I’ll take you to the hospital myself.
No need.
I’ll take him.
You two are too close—you’d just take his side.
My car, let’s go.
Let’s go.
Not going.
Go.
Let go, Sorn.
If you don’t let go, I’ll really get mad.
You act like you’re not mad at me anymore.
Get in.
Okay, I’ll help him walk.
You’re so damn stubborn.
I’m way more stubborn than you think, Jun.
Let’s go.
Hey, grab his shoes for me, will ya?
Do you treat everyone you’re flirting with this well?
Of course, gotta take good care of the person I’m courting.
But I’ve never courted anyone but you, you know?
Even P’Tai doesn’t take care of me as well as you do.
I like you
I have to treat you right.
What are you even saying? You’re so... ugh.
Alright, I’m heading out.
Why are you giving me a lollipop?
If I wanna make up with a kid,
I gotta give them what they like, right?
I’m outta here.
He’s dead serious.
Ever since he went to see you at the factory.
I respect him for that, man.
Yeah.
What’s up, bro?
You’re getting too chummy.
yeah—hey.
Let’s go, Jun.
You seriously drive from the city every day just to pick up Jun?
Man, you’ve got it bad, boss.
Yeah, are you rich or what?
Your family make oil or something?
So what if I wanna drive to pick you up? Big deal.
Still, wouldn’t hurt to save some money.
Come on,
I’m already here—don’t waste the trip.
I didn’t ask you to come pick me up.
Yeah,
you didn’t.
I wanted to come myself.
I just wanted to see that pouty face for a few minutes
then I can go back to work and earn money to feed my wife.
Sorn! Quit running your mouth!
Gotta go.
Later, bro.
Take care of Jun, alright?
Win, you’re ditching me?
What?
Damn you, Win.
Jun,
let’s get going.
Why are you talking so nicely?
It’s giving me chills.
Well, every time I talk nice, you pay attention.
So I figured I’d use that to get your attention again.
Let’s go.
Thanks...
Don’t just thank me.
Give me something more.
Want me to bow with my foot or something?
You know exactly what I want.
Please...
before I head in to work?
Nope.
Don’t you feel sorry for me?
No, I don’t.
You didn’t feel sorry for me
when I was the one liking you alone all this time.
Always dodging the truth,
blaming everything else.
But now I’m clear about how I feel.
What do you want, Jun?
You wanted clarity
now I’m giving it to you.
But I need to know how long it’ll take.
Because if I have to keep chasing after you like this forever,
I can’t handle it, man.
I’ve been late for work almost every day lately
One day, I might get fired.
I’d have no job,
no money.
And then how would I buy you all your favorite food, Jun?
If it comes to that,
I’ll have to go back and work for my family.
But I don’t wanna be away from you. Not at all.
What if I have to fly to see you every week?
My mom would nag me until I go deaf.
I’d probably have to ask you to move in with me and my mom.
I like you this much
I’m not gonna give up on you easily, Jun.
I’m waiting to take you home... as my mom’s son-in-law, you know.
So…
this Saturday at 11, I was thinking of going to the mall.
If you’re free...
then…
Then...?
Figure it out yourself.
Don’t play dumb.
Idiot.
You’re up?
Going anywhere today?
Planning to do laundry... and clean up.
Wanna see a movie?
but I have to clean...
but I kinda wanna go too.
Don’t tell me it was you...
Bro?
What are you doing here this early?
It’s only 8 AM.
Looking for someone?
Jun?
He’s not here.
Then I’ll wait.
I made plans with him earlier.
Oho~ things
are moving forward, huh boss?
Man, I really hope so.
Chasing a kid
is exhausting as hell.
Didn’t you say you don’t like younger guys?
Look at you now
from morning to night!
I still don’t get when that spark even happened!
Aww,
that’s sweet, boss.
I’m out
enjoy your day!
Hello.
Jun, you free lately?
I’m trying out new dishes at the shop.
Wanna come eat?
I’ll come pick you up.
Wow, your shop must be rich.
giving customers a VIP pickup service now?
Huh? Who is this? Isn’t this Jun?
Let’s just say I’m his man.
And don’t bother calling again.
Whoa,
when did you get here?
I’m about to shower.
Jun!
What the hell!
Why are you in here? Get out!
Aside from me...
who else is trying to hit on you?
Can you get out first?
I’m about to take a shower!
Come on. Just answer me.
I’m naked, dude!
I’ve seen it all already.
Why be shy now?
Answer me.
Ugh...
No one!!
No one else but you,
okay!? Happy now?!
Get out!
Hey! Shut the door at least!
I’m not closing it!!
Damn it!!
Hey!
What are you doing?!
Jun...
I’m asking you seriously now.
Ask what?
Let me kiss you.
Please.
Please…
Wait!
Lips only!
No tongue!
Okay.
Hey!
I said no tongue!
I won’t!
Let me try again.
Hey!
Get out!
What is wrong with you?!
Why did you bring me here?
I just wanted to take a break.
My legs are sore from driving too long.
Were you happy today?
What did you say?
I asked—do you like me?
I used to, yeah...
but now, I need time to think.
But I like you.
So what now?
Didn’t you say
you’d make me your wife?
Now you’re just asking to be my boyfriend?
As if you’d say yes.
You didn’t even respond when I asked you to be my boyfriend.
And how did that make you feel?
Honestly? I’m disappointed.
I knew you’d say yes eventually.
just like when I told you I liked you.
I thought you’d say you liked me too.
you’d say...
you liked me too.
When I first met you,
your attitude was annoying as hell.
I really don’t get...
how a little brat like you
could get along so well with other adults.
Because...
they’re not as easily annoyed as you.
And now that you like me…
are you really okay with being with someone younger?
Are you really sure you like me?
I’m way younger than you.
I’m the same Jun.
you once said...
If I ever liked a kid
it wouldn’t be him.
Then let me ask you first.
when did you start liking me?
Two years ago?
Or when we started living together?
Well...
Does that even matter?
I think...
the fact that...
I confessed first
I like you.
that matters more.
I don’t know about that.
but I’m sure.
I liked you before you liked me.
What do you mean?
Those shoes…
why do you think I bought them.
if I didn’t care about you?
Well...
maybe you just saw me as Tai’s little bro?
Plus you said they were the wrong size.
Then why not give them to Win instead?
I lied—to Tai,
to you,
and to myself.
Then how do I know...
you won’t shut me out again?
Or...
Won’t deny me again?
That’s up to you, Jun.
If you want assurance from me.
but aren’t ready to accept it,
we won’t get anywhere.
We’ll just stay stuck right here.
Did you know?
Tai’s dad offered me a position in Vietnam.
But do you know why I didn’t go?
Because of your family?
No.
It was because Tai told me...
you were going to intern at the company in two weeks.
So I decided staying in Thailand was better.
I wanted to see that kid I left in the car two years ago...
the one I never said goodbye to.
I wanted to know if he kept the promise he made to me.
I wanna keep working at the factory for one more week.
What kind of married couple lives apart, huh, Jun?
Aren’t you even a little embarrassed saying that out loud?
Not at all. It's the truth.
He's waiting for you, you know.
Yeah? Well, I’m waiting for you right here.
I told you, I’ll be at your place on Saturday.
I’m sleeping in this room tonight.
I don’t approve.
I’m just too lazy to knock every time I wanna have sex with you.
God, you’re such a perv.