[intriguing percussive music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Orlick] Here's all you need to know.
Paulo Braga is perfecting tech
that can co-opt a person's mind
and turn them into an assassin
to kill Russian President Aranov
at the G8.
I've sabotaged the programming,
and there are only two people
in the world
who can get the code to work.
The other is a Korean hacker
by the name of Edison.
Edison was handled by the CIA.
[Orlick] And that intel will be stored
at CIA European headquarters in Rome.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, Bernard,
you want to break in there?
[overlapping shouting]
[Celine grunts]
I will make you a trade.
Mason Kane and Bernard Orlick.
You don't have any earplugs, do you?
[guards groaning]
- Ah!
- Later, homies.
What was all that
"turning everybody in" shit?
- I had to improvise.
- You fucked us.
- [gunshot]
- [Nadia grunts]
[grim atmospheric music playing]
- [agent speaking indistinctly]
- [Nadia gasping]
[agent] Just keep breathing, it's okay.
Stay with me.
[exhales sharply]
[electricity crackles]
[♪ T. Rex plays "Teenage Dream"]
[shouts indistinctly]
[grunting]
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
[vocalizing]
[singer laughs]
[elevator bell dings]
[in French]
Hello beautiful.
[in English]
Oh, you have blood on your shirt.
♪ To the teenage dream...
I'm not buying this genius idiot thing.
Yeah? Which part?
The idiot part.
So you think I'm a genius.
May I kiss you?
♪ My guardian angel's rung down ♪
♪ my telephone ♪
♪ The heat's on, mister ♪
♪ Can't you hear them scream...
[to "She'll Be Comin' Round the Mountain"]
♪ 3-4-5-8-8-1-2-3-9-8-4 ♪
- [buzzer sounds]
- [automated voice] Access denied.
Oh, come--
5-8-8-1-2-3-9-5-6.
♪ 3-4-5-8-8-1-2-3-9-5-6 ♪
♪ 3-4-5-8-8-1-2-3-9-9... 6 ♪
- [buzzer sounds]
- [automated voice] Access denied.
Shut up!
♪ The jet junk jiver speeds past
in his machine ♪
♪ But whatever happened to the teenage ♪
♪ dream? ♪
♪ A broken god ♪
♪ from a musty world ♪
All right.
♪ sweetly mouth-touched ♪
♪ an onyx girl ♪
♪ His prison bars ♪
♪ were very hard to clean ♪
♪ But whatever happened
to the teenage dream? ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
[automated voice] Access granted.
Thank you.
Okay.
Let's find out who you are, Mr. Edison.
I gotta learn how to type.
[exciting music playing]
Holy shit.
You sneaky little sons of bitches.
Now, that's a bait and switch.
♪ ♪
[phone chimes]
Hey, dickheads.
- Go! Go! Go!
- Move! Move!
[cackles]
[guard screams]
[guards grunting]
Yeah, that was actually kinda messed-up.
What's with you and sexy robot guy?
- Mason?
- Yeah.
There's nothing with us.
[in French]
Ah, please.
[in English]
There's something with you.
When you look at him, I can't tell
if you want to fuck him or kill him.
There's often very little difference
between the two.
So... which is it with him?
It's, uh, bang or bang?
What do you think?
- I think both.
- [engine starts]
[tires squealing]
Seal this place.
No one comes in or out,
or I will rip their head off.
What do we got?
He breached the network.
- Shit.
- [sighs]
Initiate full building lockdown,
search surroundings.
Someone with a sonic weapon
is targeting us on three.
And if you see Hutch--
You shoot him in the fucking face.
Oh, shit.
Didn't I give you the earplugs?
No, you didn't.
[tires screech]
♪ ♪
- Hutch!
- Go, go, go, go!
- [tires squealing]
- Hutch! Hutch!
[yells]
Ah, shit!
God, I'm hit!
Go get him, go!
[tires screech]
[car horns honking]
[arguing indistinctly]
Shit.
[Sharpe laughing]
- [propulsive music playing]
- [loud chatter]
♪ ♪
You mind if I sit down?
- Do I know you?
- [Sharpe] Tell me something.
What position would you call that?
[man and woman moaning on video]
You look embarrassed.
I wouldn't be.
That's a hell of a performance.
- [woman on video] Yes!
- What do you want?
- You want me to put this away?
- [Cash clears throat]
[tires squealing]
- [tires squealing]
- [horn honking]
[Bantam] Did you get 'em?
Negative.
I didn't have a shot.
You have it?
All right, who's Edison?
Ha-joon Yoo. Korean national born in '73.
Holy shit.
What, you know this guy?
He's one of the richest men
in South Korea.
He was a former hacker that went private.
Looks like we're going to Seoul, guys.
Probably not.
In two days' time, it's the Greenpeace
Annual Gala in Windsor,
which is a significant date
in the billionaire social calendar.
Ha-joon and his wife are huge contributors
to Greenpeace.
[Hutch] So, can you guarantee
that Ha-joon and his wife
are gonna be at this gala?
Better than that, Mr. Chicken McNugget.
They're gonna be hosting it.
[in French] Well, maybe
he's not so worthless after all.
[in English]
Yeah, I can speak French.
[in French] In fact,
I think it's the state of his face.
- He's got the head of an idiot.
- [laughs]
[in English] Yeah, like I just said,
I can speak French.
- I think, I think it's the forehead.
- [laughs]
[in French] You're right. He's got
a prominent forehead, like a Neanderthal.
I speak French.
[in English]
Shut the fuck up, you guys.
We're meeting Orlick in 30 minutes.
[in French]
This one has a face like a bitch.
A fucking bitch.
We all speak French.
[atmospheric music playing]
- [horn beeps]
- [dog barks]
[siren wails in distance]
[soft footsteps approach]
[in English]
They should be here soon.
You started without me?
It's been a long day.
A long month.
A long 40 years.
Did you know the world used to be a place
where things were very clearly defined?
Good and evil, right and wrong,
truth and lies.
And we, as spies, were supposed
to soldier into the murk, into the gray,
and see things clearly.
But for the last eight years, I have not
been able to see things clearly.
I don't know who's a threat
or who isn't anymore.
[Mason] Hasn't that always been the job?
Not knowing?
Just trusting what we believe in
and putting a bullet through anyone
who thinks differently?
I mean, isn't that
what you trained me to be?
That bullet?
Yes, I did.
2,562 people were slaughtered
in their homes.
What kind of person would do that?
Betray those people?
Do you have any idea?
No?
- Not a clue?
- Not a clue.
Hmm.
[glass clinks]
I went to her because the agency
was keeping my wife from me,
and she told me the organization
I'd devoted my life to
had killed my father when I was a boy.
I said I'd help bring them to justice.
What the fuck would you have done?
Probably something that wouldn't
have killed 2,000 innocent people,
but everyone's
a Monday-morning quarterback, aren't they?
She took it upon herself
to have them killed.
I had no idea who she was working for
or what she would do.
[haunting, mournful music playing]
Even after all that...
...she didn't get the guy
who gave the order.
It was an error.
Go on.
It was a miscalculation.
We were tracking a terror cell...
...and our informant sold us out.
I was given the wrong coordinates.
"I was given the wrong coordinates"?
That's the best you've got?
Because you killed my father, Bernard,
and you murdered 342 U.N. workers.
How are we not the same?
How are we not the same?!
I made a decision to help others.
It went wrong.
You made a decision to help yourself,
to feed your vengeance.
That's how we're not the same!
So, where do we go from here?
There is an asshole
that needs to be stopped,
and as much of an asshole as you are,
I need you.
And whether you believe it or not,
you need me, too.
How am I supposed to help you
if I'm always looking over my shoulder?
Don't worry about it.
If I shoot you, it won't be in the back.
[ominous music playing]
[contemplative music playing]
[in Portuguese]
Don't kill me!
If you don't play it right,
you won't learn.
Your turn.
What did you just do?
What will happen now?
You will beat me.
Oh, yes.
What piece is this?
The King.
Look at me.
The King is the piece
that you have to protect the most.
You cannot expose yourself like that.
But why?
Because the King is
the most important piece.
Just with the King alone,
you can still win the game.
But if you're the King,
you can still win without me, Dad.
[soft chuckle]
Look.
[sentimental music playing]
The King here is you.
You are my King.
I am
a Pawn.
Doing everything to protect you.
Give me a kiss.
I love you.
Me too.
[intriguing percussive music playing]
♪ ♪
[in English]
Ah, fuck it.
- [chimes]
- [buzzes]
Once more into the breach,
or fill my hole with your English dead.
Or whatever he said.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing, I'm in a good mood.
Morning, Bernard.
- Morning.
- [Hutch] Why are you smiling like that?
'Cause I'm a smiley type of guy.
You use more muscles to frown
than you do to smile.
[Hutch] Who told you that?
A-a doctor.
- Which doctor?
- A witch doctor.
You want to collect your barrel
of geniuses?
Yes.
Come on, gather round,
'cause this is excruciating.
Here's our mark, Ha-joon Yoo.
He and his wife will be cohosting
the Greenpeace gala tomorrow night
at the Plymouth Estate in Windsor.
We get in, abduct him, we get out.
Mr. Yoo will no doubt have security.
We just have to scoop him
before Paulo does.
How do we know Paulo knows who he is?
I'm sure he will pay a fortune
for that intel very soon,
so, Hutch, you and Celine,
you're gonna neutralize the target.
You two are gonna carry out the exfil.
- Frank and I--
- Francis.
Francis and I will be waiting outside
to transport.
- Got it?
- Yeah.
Just a couple of hundred billionaires, all
with their own private security detail.
What could go wrong?
We've seen worse.
[Joana] Aparna discovered
Edison's identity.
- Are you serious?
- Mm-hmm.
And?
Ha-joon Yoo.
- Ha-joon Yoo.
- Mm-hmm.
Wait, didn't we have dinner with him--
Saint-Tropez, last summer.
Seemed a little bit dull
for a genius hacker.
He'll be in Windsor tomorrow
attending Greenpeace's gala.
I'm gonna send her in there
to intercept him--
No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no.
You know how I love
a good party, don't you?
- Mm.
- It's too dangerous.
The future is a ladder of chess moves.
Every day I get out of bed, I think,
"What moves do I need to make today,
five years from now, 50 years from now,
to protect my boy?"
This is the move.
I would give my life for that child.
[whispering] Yeah.
You very well may.
So...
...tell me I'm a fool, then.
You are a fool.
Yeah.
Sometimes you have to risk your king.
It's the right move at the right moment.
[tender music playing]
And our resolve is unmatched.
Right?
I love you.
I love you, too.
♪ ♪
Okay, we good?
- I see you--
- That's great, yeah. That's-that's good.
Okay, you go.
- [clears throat]
- Wait.
I think you're supposed to have
your clothes on.
- I just...
- Oh, okay, all right.
Maybe try one that's, like, passport?
You ever get one of those passport photos?
♪ ♪
[grunts]
You good?
Eh.
Don't worry. Braga's a dead man.
Being on a mission to kill someone is...
[sighs] ...spiritually draining.
That's why it's my mission and not yours.
I don't have a spirit.
- I can't get drained.
- Yeah, but...
I don't like this mission for you, either.
I've made a career out of
putting down scumbags and pricks.
Okay? It's all I'm good at.
And I actually really enjoy doing it.
Braga's one of those guys
who forfeited his right to breathe
when he put out a hit on you
because you're a good person.
You're kind and, uh...
Yeah, you're a good person.
He's a piece of shit
and I'm gonna kill him for you.
[clears throat]
[Celine] And Citadel?
[exhales]
Citadel's just a means to an end.
I don't like lying to them.
Well, you don't have to.
I'll do all the lying.
[in French] Don't you think we should
tell them the truth about Edison?
I mean to say, we're a team now,
we all work together,
and if we start to lie to them
or deceive them,
then we're worth no more than Braga.
[in English]
We're talking about your life here.
[atmospheric music playing]
That's just too big of a risk to take.
You understand?
Yeah.
[pulsing music playing]
♪ ♪
[loud chatter]
There he is.
[speaking inaudibly]
- What are you doing?
We're married.
Married couples don't kiss.
Don't they?
Look around this room.
I could tell you who's married.
Married couples can't stand one another.
We kissed, when we were married.
- Did we?
- On the boat to Salerno.
We had a half bottle of gin,
we laid on the sundeck and we kissed.
That was perfect.
I erased those memories.
And I didn't even need you
to backstop me to do it.
We weren't really married.
You actually have to know
the person you're married to,
and I clearly didn't know you at all.
You knew the best parts of me.
- [Nadia] Why did you come back?
- [Mason] For Abby.
That's why Kyle came back.
Why did Mason come?
It was the right thing to do.
And now you want to save Abby?
- What kind of question is that?
- An appropriate one,
for the audience in front of me.
Especially now that you know
she's Celeste Graham.
Well, I knew who she was
like I knew who you were.
Who I was.
She's not that person anymore.
She's the mother of my child
and I love her.
You're not capable of love.
- I loved you.
- No.
[Nadia] You loved
that I loved you.
You loved the thought
that I actually believed you loved me.
And that I thought
you were actually capable of it.
You loved that I thought you were human.
And not some cipher or a fucking fraud.
- I loved you.
- No, you didn't.
I did.
Maybe I still do.
[tense music playing]
They're on the move.
♪ ♪
Staff only.
We're with, uh, catering.
We're the pigs-in-blankets men.
Darren?
♪ ♪
So, what do we do now?
We wait.
Mm.
Are you married, Bernard?
I was.
What happened?
I fucked it up.
Quelle surprise.
[laughs softly]
My daughter was very young,
and my wife and I were, um, struggling.
She wanted me to be around more,
she wanted me to be more present
when I was around and--
She wanted you to be normal.
Yeah.
And in our line of work, that's not--
In our line of work, there's no place
for normal, 'cause normal is a cover.
- And normal doesn't exist.
- Yep.
I met this woman.
I was stationed in Paris.
And I met her at Chez l'Ami Louis.
- You know the restaurant?
- I don't.
It's incredible.
Anyway, I ruined everything.
You see, it's hard
for a genius to be in love.
They think they should be alone.
They think they don't need anybody,
when, in actual fact,
a genius is a genius
due to their ability to make
the unreasonable seem reasonable.
And there is nothing reasonable
about love.
Well put.
Wait, are you calling yourself a genius?
Well, I would've thought that was obvious
by my repeated use of the word.
[chuckles]
[laughs]
- I met mine in Moscow.
- Ah.
In Chez McDonald's.
- Have you heard of it?
I have, yes.
I ruined everything.
[exciting music playing]
[speaking inaudibly]
Bernard should be in position.
Where's Hutch?
He's on it.
So why are you trying to play me?
- You're the one who's playing.
- Oh, please,
as if I can't see through
the "I'm still in love with you"
seduction act.
Is it an act?
You can't be in love
with two people, Mason.
So, why are you seducing me?
Into not killing you
or letting you kill me first?
Either. Both, if it comes to that.
What right do you have to kill me?
You think you deserve
to be alive more than I do?
Definitely.
You're a fucking monster.
- You're exhausting.
- Oh, please.
[Nadia] You slaughtered innocent people,
ruined so many lives, including mine.
You could've kept away
from the agency after you had Asha.
Let go of my hand, Mason.
But you didn't, you came back,
you boarded that train.
I came back for you, you fucking asshole.
For what I thought you were,
so you could be part of Asha's life.
No. No, see, you came back
- because you missed it.
- [scoffs]
Because you want this life.
Because without it,
you don't know who you are.
Your mother took your childhood from you,
you weren't gonna let Asha
take what was left.
You took what was left.
You took everything.
You know, I spent a lot of time
wondering why I loved you.
[tense music playing]
I think it's because when I was with you,
I didn't feel like such a monster.
You know, when I was with you,
by comparison,
I was doing all right.
♪ ♪
Oh. Sexy robot looks sexy.
I don't see it.
[over comm] What kind of man do women
really want to hang out with?
A red-blooded, all-American,
shit-kicking, gas-guzzling,
Coors-Light-drinking badass
- like me, or...
- [chuckles]
...a guy who looks like
he listens to Phil Collins
while he irons his frickin' underwear?
Oh, him.
Give me one good reason.
[in French]
He's got silky hair.
A square jaw.
Blue eyes.
[in English]
And he reads Aquarius.
That's four, but I can keep going.
I've got a goddamn...
[in French] Square jaw.
- [in English] All right?
- [laughs softly]
[suspenseful music playing]
♪ ♪
Hey, guys. How's it going?
You guys, uh...
The more that guy talks,
the worse it gets.
- [speaks Korean]
- [laughter]
Hey, have you guys, um...
Could I...
I-I've got some champagne here.
Could I give this to your guests?
- Sure.
- Great. All right.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
Here you go. Enjoy.
All right. Nice to meet you.
How long will this take?
Almost instant.
Boss. Paulo's looking for you.
[softly] Oh. Excuse me, darling.
- I'll be back.
- [tense music playing]
Let's go.
♪ ♪
She is about to regret
wearing that white dress.
Time to go.
I am.
[suspenseful music playing]
Paulo?
[Paulo] Ha-joon, brother.
I'm so sorry to pull you away
from the party.
It's such a good cause.
Greenpeace.
Protecting the planet.
Though, who are we kidding?
If we don't get our act together,
it isn't the planet that's gonna
feel something, it's us.
You and your kids, me and mine.
And so, I wanted to steal a tight five
with you to ask for your help.
- So set up a meeting.
- Not that kind of help.
Please, have a seat.
[silenced gunshots]
Have a seat.
[exciting music playing]
I know who you are, friend,
and I have a program
that needs to be finished.
And there's only one person
in the world who can finish it.
Edison.
[laughs softly]
[woman retching]
They never expect a woman.
[panting]
Who is that?
[tense music playing]
Hey.
[grunting]
[Celine] I am no one.
But you?
You are Edison.
[screams]
Come on, Frenchie, time to go.
All these years...
- [muffled grunting]
- ...your husband was the cover.
[grunting]
[yells]
[yelps]
[grunting]
♪ ♪
[whimpering]
[phone chimes]
[pulsing music playing]
Hmm.
You always did strike me as an idiot.
It seems like I should be negotiating
with your wife instead.
[grunts]
[haunting music playing]
[phone buzzes]
[phone continues buzzing]
[Orlick] How much are they paying you?
What?
How much are they paying you?
- I don't know what you're...
- [clicks]
[sighs]
[tense music playing]
Three million.
For what?
Edison's identity and whereabouts.
How did you know?
'Cause you're a desperate man.
And you have a terrible poker face.
And you have a privacy screen
on your phone.
- So what?
- And you also seem
like a "highest bidder" kind of guy.
So I'll give you four.
- Okay?
- Okay.
You do what I tell you
and don't try to fuck me again.
- All right.
- And you'll let me know
if anybody tries to outbid me.
Yeah.
[suspenseful music playing]
- [silenced gunshots]
- [grunts]
Don't make a fucking sound.
Glad to meet you.
I want my wife.
[frantic music playing]
What's happening?
Anybody.
[Mason] We have Ha-joon.
Coming down now.
We're ready for you.
Can we please just talk--
[grunts]
Drive.
[engine starts]
[dramatic music playing]
[exciting music playing]
♪ ♪