(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
[The Epoch of Miyu]
[Episode 24]
It's for your foot.
Thank you.
Let me help.
Lift it up.
[Banquet Hall]
Hold on to me.
Does it hurt?
Bear with it
for a moment.
All done.
Thank you.
[Banquet Hall]
Now, let's welcome Ms. Dianjiangchun!
I need to get in there now.
Okay.
[Banquet Hall]
-Dianjiangchun!
[The Amazing Vlog Producer Dianjiangchun]
Turn up the AC.
There are too many people here.
It's really stuffy.
Thank you all
for coming afar
for me and my book,
[Dianjiangchun
New Book Sharing and Signing Event]
"Chun's Daily Taste."
Thank you.
Xu Miyu!
Mr. Duan.
I was wondering
why I couldn't get a helper.
It's quite boisterous here.
Mr. Duan, I'll get you a helper
if you need one.
Well,
five or six people will come meet me soon.
I need you to lead them to me.
Sorry, Mr. Duan.
I'm afraid I'm tied up here.
To make sure the meetup goes well,
how about I ask someone else
to receive them for you?
Xu Miyu,
what do you mean?
Are my friends not worthy
of being received
by you, the lobby manager?
That's not what I mean, Mr. Duan.
I...
May I have
your friends' photos and names?
Ask my assistant for them.
Lu Xiaoyan.
There's a task for you.
It's about the book signing event.
What is it?
I've sent it to you.
Check it out on your phone.
Hello, enjoy your stay.
It's way too blurry, isn't it?
Mr. Ma Wenhui
is an important guest
for the upcoming talk.
It's been a long time
since he last attended a public event.
This is the clearest photo
of his that could be found online.
But don't worry.
He'll come to you when he arrives.
Your task is to bring him to the venue.
Got it.
I obtained some information about him
from the internet.
Why don't I send it to you?
No need.
You should do some research online
as well.
He's a complete stranger to us after all.
Better safe than sorry.
How do I have time for that?
I'm just an usher.
Am I even supposed to memorize
the guest's background?
If you're concerned,
assign the task to someone else.
Hello.
I can see here
that you booked a deluxe king room.
Is it correct?
Why does she have to be so hoity-toity?
Hello, I'm the lobby manager
of Purong Hotel.
This way, please.
Okay.
Have you noticed?
Ms. Xu has rushed
in and out several times today.
Serves her right.
She loves to show off, doesn't she?
Now she can do it all day long.
I just hope she can stay out of my hair.
Next, please!
Hello.
Your ID, please.
Where's my bag?
Next!
Hold on, miss.
I left my bag in the taxi.
All my personal documents are in it.
Could you make an exception?
I'm here for the talk
in the book signing event.
Sorry, sir.
There are over 100 attendees
of this event.
I need to verify your identity.
I advise you to call
the taxi company right now
to retrieve you bag.
You won't be admitted to the venue
without a valid ID.
But the talk is about to start.
Sorry, sir. There's nothing I can do.
Ma'am.
Sir, smoking is prohibited here.
If you are to smoke,
could you step outside?
Cleaning staff,
the reception area needs cleaning.
What am I supposed to do?
Well, this is...
Anything wrong? What happened?
Mr. Ji, we can't reach
the guest speaker now.
Ms. Xu is handling it.
Ms. Xu.
Mr. Ji.
I'll go with you to look for the guest.
Okay.
Ji Feng!
Ji Feng,
the talk will begin in 10 minutes.
Can you stick around and help me?
Mr. Ji, maybe you should stay
and assist Ms. Jiang.
I can go look for the guest on my own.
Are you sure...
you can do it alone?
Yes.
Okay. Call me anytime
if there's a problem.
I'll be off then.
Come with me.
Okay.
Did you receive
a middle-aged man with gray hair?
Lu Xiaoyan,
did you receive him?
Where has he gone?
H-He's gone for a smoke outside.
Hello,
hailing service?
Up next is a discussion.
Let's welcome Ms. Dianjiangchun
with a round of applause!
-Hurray!
Dianjiangchun!
[Always on the road
recording the flavors of the mortal world]
Hello, everyone.
Today's talk
was supposed to be held
between me
and my mentor, Mr. Ma Wenhui.
But unfortunately,
due to unexpected circumstances,
Mr. Ma couldn't make it here today.
Nonetheless,
I'm honored to have invited
a good friend of mine to the talk.
He's the general manager of this hotel,
who rose to fame online
for his saxophone performance.
Ji Feng, come up on the stage.
-Nice!
-Great!
First, thank you all
for not turning around and leaving.
Let me briefly introduce myself.
I'm Ji Feng,
the general manager of Purong Hotel.
I believe the essence of today's talk
isn't the topic itself,
but your very presence.
You showing up here is already meaningful.
It's just like a sentence in the book:
"Every meeting is a long-awaited reunion."
I'd like to interview Ms. Dianjiangchun.
Is there a story behind this sentence?
Mr. Ji is fishing for gossip
right after getting on the stage, huh?
[Nanxun Road]
Hello,
hailing service, right?
You found the bag?
Could you have it delivered
to the lobby of Purong Hotel?
I'll be there.
Mr. Ma said he'd like to pick it up
somewhere else?
Okay.
I got it. Thanks.
[Dianjiangchun
New Book Sharing and Signing Event]
May I ask a personal question?
Are the two of you dating?
You two really make a perfect couple!
[Dianjiangchun
New Book Sharing and Signing Event]
Hailin,
I'm terribly sorry.
Mr. Ma won't be back to the hotel.
It's okay.
We already have a guest for the talk.
They're dropping juicy gossip now.
I treasure each and every one of you.
So,
I don't want to lie to you.
The two of us...
used to be in love.
Have you two
considered getting back together?
Yes! Yeah!
To me...
Mr. Ji is a great work partner.
Among all the people
I've collaborated with,
I deem Mr. Ji as
the most trustworthy and compatible one.
As for the future,
I'll leave it to fate.
Just as expected of Dianjiangchun.
Look at the audience's reaction.
These fans have definitely
got their value out of coming here,
as they could witness
something so romantic.
Ms. Xu, look!
Mr. Ji, have you met Ms. Jiang before?
She and I...
went to college together.
[Purong Hotel]
Lu Xiaoyan,
I need you to write
a report about today's incident.
What incident?
What's there to write about?
I demand a detailed explanation.
First,
what was your attitude like
when you received Mr. Ma Wenhui?
Second,
why did he never come back
after going out for a smoke?
I've reported
to Director Bai about what happened.
You can go ask him for more details.
I am asking you now.
How could you drive away a guest
who came to you for help?
I-I didn't drive him away, did I?
I was just following the hotel's protocol.
ID verification
and the no-smoking policy
are clearly stated
in the hotel regulations.
Attitude determines results.
What kind of attitude did you take
when enforcing hotel policies?
The hotel also requires you
to do everything possible
to help guests solve their problems.
Did you help Mr. Ma look for his lost bag?
I was swamped just now.
How was it possible
for me to help a guest
look for a lost item?
Being busy is not an excuse.
Our hotel
accommodates
a large number of guests every day.
You can't treat anyone poorly
just because you're busy.
Today, you made this mistake
exactly because
you didn't take the task I gave you
seriously.
Let me say this to you again:
whether you like it or not,
I am the lobby manager
and your supervisor now,
which means you must
complete the tasks I assign you.
Lastly,
do you know how important
this book signing event is to our hotel?
The entire event could've been ruined
due to a small slip you made.
Could you have borne the consequences?
Isn't the talk going well now?
That's because
someone is fixing your mistake.
Tomorrow morning,
submit a written explanation to me.
Ten points will be deducted
from your performance rating this month.
Take it as a lesson.
What? A 10-point deduction?
I didn't mean to offend him.
I really didn't know
he was the guest speaker.
If I had known,
I would've treated him properly.
Miyu!
That's my sister,
the lobby manager.
Anyway,
you must take responsibility
for your mistake.
Miyao.
It's a real delight
to have gathered with you today
and had such a fantastic talk.
In the days ahead,
no matter how busy or anxious
you may be,
I hope
all of you can find your inner peace
in your stressful everyday lives.
I'd appreciate it if you could continue
supporting me and staying connected
with me.
Thank you, everyone.
Dianjiangchun!
Sorry.
I let out our secret without your consent.
You're not mad at me, are you?
Not at all.
Our hotel has benefited from this event.
For that, I owe you many thanks.
By the way,
are there extra copies of your book?
Why do you ask?
All our staff are your fans now.
I might as well take this chance
to buy 500 copies
for them as staff perks.
What a pleasure for me, Mr. Ji.
The pleasure is ours.
Thank you, Zhichun.
For what?
For being supportive of Purong Hotel.
Nothing gets past you, does it?
How magnificent.
This is really pretty.
What? I won't break it.
There's even a piano!
Get back out.
No entry.
That's a display for everyone, isn't it?
Let's go.
Honestly,
you look quite smart
in this uniform.
Is anyone pursuing you?
Five-star hotel guests
[Purong Hotel]
all have deep pockets, right?
Quickly find a decent one and marry him.
Thanks.
Miyao,
what on earth brings you here?
A certain matter, of course.
Can we eat and talk
somewhere?
How about the executive lounge
you brought Mom and Dad to last time?
Why not treat me to that place too?
I can't go to the HSKP Department
without cause,
since I work in the lobby now.
I'll be off work soon.
Let me get changed
and take you out for a bite, okay?
Out for a bite?
What do you mean by that?
Are you chasing me away
right after I arrived?
Am I embarrassing you or what?
No, that's not it.
Then what's the reason?
Anyway,
I insist on eating here today.
[Purong Hotel]
Hello, sir.
How may I help you?
I booked a room. Thanks.
Please wait a moment.
Today is no good.
There's an important event
in our hotel today.
I promise I'll take you to the lounge
next time you're here.
Next time?
That means I have to wait then, right?
All I have done
is wait, wait, and wait.
When you were divorced
and busy looking for a job,
I kindly spared you
from trouble out of pity.
Are you saying I have to make
an appointment for a chat
now that you've got your life together?
I don't mean any of that.
Just cut the chase.
What do you want this time?
What do you mean, "what I want this time"?
I'm your sister.
It's not like I'm here to rob you.
I'm actually here to beg you.
I'm begging you
to help your nephew,
given that the entire family supported you
through college in the past.
Will you chip in
to pay for
my son's international school tuition?
Sister,
part of my monthly salary
is spent on Mom and Dad's loans.
I'm unable to help you.
You're indeed different now from before.
Xu Miyu,
what a powerful lobby manager you are now.
Since when have you become  so heartless
and cold to your family?
You're living the high life
in a five-star hotel,
yet you won't lend money
to a family member in need.
Don't you have a conscience?
Miyao,
I, Xu Miyu,
can look you,
Dad, Mom,
and everyone else
in the family that raised me in the eye
and say I have a clear conscience.
I've devoted
everything I have to all of you.
The rest of my life belongs to myself.
I hope you'll stop disturbing me!
Besides,
this is where I work.
You'd better be respectful.
Hello, sir.
Here's your key card and passport.
Please keep them safe.
Okay, thanks.
Have a temper now,
don't you?
I need to go now.
You're not going anywhere!
Listen to me...
What do you mean by this?
You're not going anywhere!
Where are you going, Xu Miyu?
I won't let you go!
Xu Miyu!
Excuse me.
I just got off the plane.
I haven't eaten yet.
Would you go to dinner with me?
Excuse me.
Please have my luggage stored. Thanks.
Let's go.
Is
Mr. Tan...
Yes.
But not really.
Who's that guy?
Is he rich?
Do let me know
when Mr. Ma gets his phone back.
I must formally apologize to him
on behalf of the hotel.
Sure.
I'll arrange it for you.
Okay.
Is that Ms. Xu?
I'll walk you to the parking lot.
Let's go.
Is that Ms. Xu?
Ms. Jiang.
Ms. Jiang?
Photos from the talk are out.
Take a look.
Thanks for the hard work, Jiao.
No problem, Ms. Jiang. I just did my job.
Such tasty wine.
Can I have some more?
Thanks.
Mr. Tan,
thank you.
Look what a spread,
accompanied by nice wine
and beautiful views.
It's been a long, long time
since I had so much joy.
Thank you.
Easy with the wine.
Have more food.
Thanks.
Not too much.
Don't worry.
I'm especially happy today.
It took me so long to finally realize
that saying no
feels so liberating.
Today, I said no to my sister.
I also said no to a colleague of mine.
I had such a wonderful day.
Great.
Congratulations
on starting a life free of constraints.
Cheers.
Give it to me.
When I was little,
I listened to my sister on everything.
I hardly dared to contradict her
or go against her.
She was always the first one to enjoy
all the nice stuff at home.
She got the first bite of delicious food.
She got to wear cute outfits first.
I couldn't have any of those
until she got tired of them.
I even had to say thank you to her
and my parents
just because...
I dared not say no
or refuse.
After I grew up,
they asked me for money.
My sister...
asked me to get her husband a job.
Whatever difficulties I was going through,
I would always satisfy her demands.
But today,
when she came and asked me for money,
I said no.
I told her
that the old Xu Miyu who always tried
to please and pander to others
was already dead
and gone.
Now, I'm a free spirit
who's only living for herself.
I wish you could see my sister's face.
S-She was completely stunned.
She went absolutely livid.
But seeing her so angry,
I felt really happy.
Was that...
even right?
Thank you.
You did the right thing.
Trust me.
But are you
genuinely happy now?
Fine.
Let's say
you're genuinely happy now.
You've already said so much.
Why not continue
and pour your heart out to me?
Just think of me as
a canvas,
on which you can doodle as you please.
A canvas can't laugh at you, right?
Right.
A canvas can't laugh at me.
There's actually a painting
I'm longing to paint.
I thought about it
for a long time,
but I-I didn't
know where to begin.
I didn't think I was ready.
I even felt I was not worthy.
There was a moment
when I thought I might be ready.
But then I found out
someone else was drawing
the same painting.
The colors were bright,
and the idea was unique.
That said, every painter's
brushstrokes and emotions
are unique.
Really?
But that's someone else's unfinished work.
I'd hate to disrupt the process.
There are plenty of canvases.
You'll surely find the one
that belongs to you.
Trust me.
Because you deserve better.
♪ Life is full of ♪
♪ Countless crossroads ♪
Mr. Tan,
no one has ever cracked a crab for me.
♪ Chase joy too hard, and it slips away ♪
What an honor for me.
It tastes good.
♪ All those confusions ♪
Have more.
♪ No answers, no reasons ♪
♪ Throwing ourselves
into the tide of the unknown ♪
♪ Knowing when to advance or retreat,
yet still asleep ♪
♪ Rushing to ripen before our time ♪
Take this.
All of it?
♪ Sighing at partings,
who meets whom at which crossing ♪
♪ Busy and restless ♪
♪ No turning back, no stopping ♪
♪ Our path—do you see it now ♪
The livestream revenue
has been settled
with Dianjiangchun's company.
By the way,
I've also placed an order
of 500 signed copies
of her book.
The finance department
was very cooperative.
They didn't whine at all,
since we racked in so much money.
As for the lobby incident...
I've looked into it.
It was just someone's family affairs.
What family affairs?
Xu Miyu's sister came to see her.
They had an unpleasant conversation.
The food is quite good today.
What happened then?
What could've happened?
Her sister stopped making a scene
when she saw
Xu Miyu was taken away.
Don't worry.
I've notified the security.
They're aware of that woman now.
She'll be put under control
if she comes again.
I'm not asking about that woman,
but the one that was taken away.
Was she okay?
You mean Xu Miyu?
The girls at the reception told me
that her sister got physical with her.
Luckily, Mr. Tan was there to see it.
What did the security do?
There were so many employees in the lobby.
Did no one help her?
All security guards
were assigned to the banquet hall.
And don't you know
those working in the lobby?
They love nothing more than drama.
None of them like Xu Miyu.
They'd love to see her get humiliated.
She should've turned to me.
You?
What gives you the right to meddle
with her family affairs?
Your position as the general manager?
Feng,
Xu Miyu
was busy from morning till night,
without taking a break.
Then she finally got off work.
Isn't it nice
that someone is keeping her company?
How are the preparations
for the talk coming along?
The wiring is all set in the venue.
The cold buffet is getting ready.
As for the guest speaker,
I'll personally bring him
to the banquet hall.
Mr. Ji,
we can't reach the guest speaker now.
Ms. Xu is handling it.
Alright. Stop restraining yourself.
If you're concerned, go check on her.
♪ A flicker of dim light ♪
♪ A bowl of warm soup ♪
[Xu Miyu]
♪ People in the city ♪
♪ Squeezing into the hustle and bustle ♪
♪ The palms of time ♪
[How are you doing?]
♪ Grinding away the simple days ♪
♪ Sprinkling them into this busy world ♪
How are you doing?
♪ To be tasted, bit by bit ♪
♪ Embracing this radiant world ♪
♪ Keeps the heart from fading to grey ♪
♪ Life's joy, sorrow, cold, and warmth ♪
♪ Intertwined within the mundane ♪
♪ Let us bravely gather up ♪
♪ The forgotten past ♪
♪ There may be regrets ♪
♪ There may be loneliness ♪
[How are you doing?]
[East Changzhi Road] [Changzhi Road]
No way.
Did he really carry her up to his room?
Yes, bridal style.
I heard from the girls on that floor
that Miyu was completely wasted.
There was no way to wake her up.
Well, what's the nature
of their relationship then?
In the past, when Mr. Tan stayed
on this floor,
he didn't seem close with Miyu.
Who knows?
Celebrities are good at
keeping their love lives secret.
Just now when Mr. Tan went into his room,
he hung the "Do Not Disturb" sign
immediately.
Juan meant to find an excuse to sneak in
and take a peek,
yet she didn't get a chance.
If Ms. Xu spends the night there,
it means they're a couple, right?
[Camera 01]
[Camera 02]
[Camera 03]
♪ Love is truly not easy to obtain ♪
♪ I can't hold on to you
if you want to leave ♪
♪ I tell myself I'm not hurt
once things settle down ♪
♪ But I realize I can’t deceive myself ♪
♪ I always say
life is already hard enough ♪
♪ So what else is there worth trying for ♪
♪ Friends comfort me,
telling me to have a drink ♪
♪ But I’ve already started living
like I’m not myself anymore ♪
♪ I feel reluctant ♪
♪ I feel reluctant to recall
or forget those memories ♪
♪ I feel reluctant ♪
♪ I feel reluctant to grab on to anyone
and I can't breathe ♪
♪ I've been indulging myself ♪
♪ I always say
life is already hard enough ♪
♪ So what else is there worth trying for ♪
♪ Friends comfort me,
telling me to have a drink ♪
♪ But I’ve already started living
like I’m not myself anymore ♪
♪ I feel reluctant ♪
♪ I feel reluctant to forgive you
and there's nothing I can do ♪
♪ I feel reluctant ♪
♪ I feel reluctant to grab on to anyone
and I can't breathe ♪
♪ I've cut myself some slack ♪
[Ji Feng]
[How are you doing?]
[I]
[Thanks for the good work]
[I'll come for a look]
[Do Not Disturb]
[Cleaning Service Needed]
She's coming out.
Why is she alone?
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning.
Ying,
can you give me the guest complaint
register?
Sure.
Lu Xiaoyan,
when will you submit your report?
Good morning, Director Bai.
Ms. Xu, hurry to Mr. Ji's office now.
I'll handle the guest complaints.
It's time you dealt with the complaint
against yourself.
Okay.
Lu Xiaoyan,
finish your report quickly.
I'll read it when I return.
Did you do what the complaint says?
[A group complaint
about Xu Miyu's improper conduct]
[Lu Xiaoyan, Chen Fangjian,
Shi Huanhuan, Wang Deping]
Yes, I did.
Were you drunk last night?
Yes, I was.
Did you spend the night in a guest's room?
Yes, I did.
So this complaint is completely justified.
I was brought back here
after getting drunk.
I didn't break any rules or regulations
of the hotel.
I wonder what negative impact I've caused.
You're in the wrong
because you're a staff member of the hotel
and Mr. Tan is a guest.
As I said,
that happened during my off hours.
Is the hotel trying to dictate who I can
be friends with after work?
Friends?
Xu Miyu,
how capable of you,
for turning a guest into a friend.
Do you know how others think of you?
They can't wait to see you
be dismissed from the hotel.
I'll earn their recognition.
Recognition?
They've sent me
this joint compliant letter.
I'm certainly able to
suppress it
and keep you in your position
against broad objection.
But why should I do that?
Are you worth it?
You can't blame them for seizing
this opportunity to bring you down
since you invited your own trouble
by mixing work and personal affairs.
I mix work and personal affairs?
Then what about you, Mr. Ji?
Is your relationship
with Jiang Zhichun purely professional?
Aren't there personal interests
involved in your collaboration with her?
You have every right to demote me
or to dismiss me,
Mr. Ji.
But I have to say
I did nothing wrong
and I don't need anyone's protection.
What did you say?
Ji Feng.
Mr. Ji,
-you're needed in the meeting room.
-Not now.
Just come with me.
You'll know when you get there.
Ms. Xu, get back to your work.
You're free to go.
Yes, Mr. Xue.
Tan Jizhou wants to see you.