♪Just To Meet You, you fell for me♪
♪Just to meet me, into my trap you fell♪
♪Wanna try a breathless love?♪
♪Every move hits the heart, close and sure♪
♪Just To Meet You, you love my playful charm♪
♪Just to meet me,
my romantic little schemes for you♪
♪Wanna play another brand-new game?♪
♪Layer by layer, we close the gap♪
=Just To Meet You=
=Episode 7=
=Jiang Niannian Sets the Bait=
Master, please have some porridge.
Master,
Ms. Qingqing's manners and upbringing
are truly top-notch.
She's thoughtful too.
Look, the porridge's gone cold.
She hasn't moved her knees once.
Where's Ye Lang?
Father.
I didn't see my brother at work today.
He must be busy.
What's he so busy with?
Master.
If you ask me,
Young Master should
get engaged to Ms. Qingqing ASAP.
Ms. Qingqing is a Jiang too.
So outsiders won't gossip.
Besides,
she's so sensible.
She could definitely help him settle down.
Liu.
Make me some hangover soup.
So you finally came back.
She...
You...
What are you trying to do?
Young Master.
Look,
I was just talking to Master
about your marriage to Ms. Qingqing.
Ye Lang,
I feel dizzy.
That drink you gave me
was too strong.
I want to go rest.
I've said it before
Jiang Niannian is my only wife.
From now on, my daily needs
will be handled directly by her.
Ye Lang, what did you say?
Your wife?
Qingqing,
don't worry.
As for Jiang Qingqing,
I think you've got it wrong.
She's only my guest.
I'm not a guest.
Ye Lang.
You said I was your companion.
- I...
- Did I?
Then explain
what happened that day right here.
Know your place.
Finish this meal,
and you can leave.
Looks like Young Master
really cares for
Jiang Niannian.
Qingqing,
Master and I
truly hoped you'd marry in.
But Ye Lang's heart
is completely taken by your sister.
(Jiang Niannian.)
(I'll make you repay this humiliation.)
(That photo of Xiaodi)
(must have been sent by someone here.)
(Xiaodi is in their hands.)
(Sorry, Ye Lang.)
Mr. Zhong, you've worked hard for years.
From now on,
I'll prepare Ye Lang's medicine.
Preparing medicine
is no child's play.
Ms. Jiang.
Be careful you don't turn it into poison
and cause a disaster.
Ye Lang.
Right now,
you can only dance to my tune.
Try it.
You made all of this?
Yep.
See if you like it.
Don't wipe it away.
Have more sweets,
then life won't be so bitter.
My mom used to say that
when she was alive.
(Of course I know.)
(Because you told me that)
(in our previous life.)
Come on, try it.
Mm.
Also this one.
Ye Lang.
Ye Lang!
Someone, hurry!
Young Master coughed up blood and fainted!
(In Surgery)
His condition is critical.
It's poisoning.
I'm issuing a critical notice now.
Move him to the ICU for observation.
Poisoning?
Investigate it.
Do find out
who did this.
Master.
These past few days,
Ms. Jiang handled his meals.
Mr. Zhong.
What do you mean?
Jiang Niannian.
Ye Lang loves you deeply.
He even turned against Master
for your sake.
Why would you do this?
I get it now.
You're trying the same trick?
You want Young Master
to end up like your three ex-husbands,
don't you?
Keep a close eye on her.
If anything happens to Ye Lang,
we have countless ways
to make you
wish you were gone.
Ye Lang.
Young Master,
I'm sorry.
Dr. Zheng,
the body is here.
You may leave.
I've finally waited
for this perfect body.
Ye Lang,
you fooled me again!
Sorry to
put you through it.
(It's not that bad.)
(I did consider doing this.)
This is nothing.
But,
Young Master,
shouldn't you pay me now?
All good.
So wasn't it him?
Each packet of medicine
only differs by one herb.
I get it now.
These packets each contain a different herb.
Taken in a row, they interact
and create a slow-acting toxin.
It takes two or three months to hit,
hard to notice.
(No wonder I didn't discover it
in my past life.)
(Even Zheng Lu found nothing in this life.)
But that doesn't prove
Butler Zhong is the one behind it.
Then force him to make a move.
(Could it be the one who sent)
(Xiaodi's photo and told me)
(to kill Ye Lang was him?)
(In my past life,
there must have been more to it.)
What are you thinking?
Nothing.
I was just about to ask
what you plan to do?
Wanna know?
That costs extra.
Money really
is what drives you.
How much do you want?
500,000?
One more zero.
(Transfer amount)
Let me see...
Five million!
I should've realized Zhong did it.
He is in really poor health.
But Zhong Minghui had no motive.
Killing me
brings him no benefit.
There must be someone behind him.
So someone else wants you dead?
If you die,
make sure your body is mine.
Young Master.
Someone did come to see Mr. Zhong.
How could it be her?
Where's Jiang Xiaodi?
Who's Jiang Xiaodi?
Stop acting.
The day I was leaving,
someone slipped me Xiaodi's photo
and threaten me
to kill Ye Lang, that was you, wasn't it?
Me?
Threaten you?
Ms. Jiang.
You don't know the Li family.
You know even less about
Young Master.
What do you mean?
Using such a trick
to drive us apart
won't work on me.
Ye Lang isn't that simple.
He's best at playing the fool.
Careful.
You might be the one being baited.
Me?
What could Ye Lang want from me?
(So it wasn't Zhong Minghui who sent it?)
(Xiaodi.)
(Where on earth are you?)
Who are you?
Let go of me!
Little brat,
you're pretty sharp.
You will bring us trouble.
Mrs. Liu.
What are you trying to do?
I'm sending you to the pig farm.
♪Stitched-up lips
tear open a blood-red dusk♪
♪You return reborn,
seeing through all my cracks♪
♪This tenderness, a trap or a gift?♪
♪Still, I'd wager my next life on it♪
♪Just for a moment to recognize you again♪
♪You are the blazing light in my despair♪
♪Lighting the edges of my frozen wings♪
♪I burn myself,
leaping into an illusion of fire♪
♪Breaking free
from dead vines in the ashes♪
♪You are the brightest star in the night♪
♪Awakening my dormant fate♪
♪Freeing me from this half-life prison♪
♪As the bells shatter the past♪
♪Life finds its way again♪