[The Epoch of Miyu]
[Episode 8]
I just want to add you on WeChat
and ask you
some professional questions.
Sure.
Give me the dry cleaning fee first.
My custom-made suit
costs 3,280 yuan to wash.
Just give me 3,000 yuan.
Mr. Ji, you can't blame me for all this.
It was an accident.
And look how crowded
it is here.
It's her.
She pushed me just now,
and that's why I bumped into you.
How could I have bumped into you
from so far away?
Didn't you just nudge me with your elbow
so I couldn't stand firmly
and bump into Mr. Ji?
I remember now.
You are the one
who asked me for wine just now,
but found that I only had champagne
on my tray,
not the red wine you wanted,
so you turned around and left.
It's all my fault.
I only had champagne on my tray
and not the red wine you wanted.
It caused you to run to the dining table
so far away to get wine.
so you accidentally bumped into Mr. Ji.
It is indeed my poor service.
I'm sorry.
Nonsense!
Xu Miyu, do you believe
I'll file a complaint against you?
Miss,
may I ask—
how exactly is she
supposed to help you
spill wine on this gentleman?
Like this?
What happened?
Mr. Duan, they poured wine on me.
This is unbelievably rude.
You are not off work yet?
Who did this?
I didn't mean it!
It's her. She pushed me.
She did it on purpose.
Miss,
please speak logically, okay?
What does she gain by setting you up?
Are you going to marry her,
or support her or something?
Do I know you?
I came with Vivian.
Who is Vivian?
Step forward!
Sorry, there's no Vivian here.
I need to see your invitation.
Did you sneak in?
No.
I'll find it for you.
Where is it?
Seriously,
can you stop letting people like this
come in and ruin my event?
Sorry, Mr. Duan.
It won't happen again.
It's fine, keep playing.
It's fine.
Go ahead.
Come on.
Let's continue.
I'm sorry.
Every time there's a party,
there are always people
like this sneaking in.
Take off your suit
and I'll ask the hotel
to handle it for you.
Forget it.
Your laundry room
probably can't handle it.
I'll figure it out myself.
Mr. Ji,
please let me take the suit.
I know a dry cleaner on South Maoming Road
that specializes in high-end suits.
They do a great job.
I'll take it there right now.
Not too dumb.
Go quickly.
Have HSKP Department
cover the money for now—
charge it to my account.
Then please hold this for me.
Thank you.
The HSKP Department has good taste.
She's quite smart.
And she's got
her own charm too.
Is she from the executive floor?
What about that female chef?
Did she run away again?
Miyu.
Why are you here?
What's going on with you?
You didn't pass the internal referral
last time.
Didn't you say you'd look for another job?
How did you end up doing this?
And you didn't even tell me.
Jobs are not that easy to find nowadays.
I'm a housewife in my thirties
with a blank resume.
Nobody wants me anywhere.
But you shouldn't have to
work as a cleaner.
Tell me the truth,
are you in some kind of trouble?
No.
Nobody forced me.
I chose it myself.
I haven't worked for so many years,
I have to start from the bottom.
Don't worry, Qiaoqi.
I'm fine.
I told you I'm your ladder.
I've got your back.
Okay, you've got my back.
I'll remember that.
Go back to work.
I need to get busy too.
Let's talk later.
Sister, you scared me to death.
What are you doing?
Did you recruit Xu Miyu
to the executive floor?
Who?
Xu Miyu!
Xu Mi...
Didn't you ask me for a favor
during the interview?
Her resume didn't pass.
But seeing her like that,
I gave her a suggestion.
So I asked her
if she wanted to try
starting as an attendant.
She actually came.
No,
I asked you to help her
apply for the Marketing Department,
and you sent her to be an attendant.
Bro,
I treat you like a brother,
and you treat me like a fool?
Sis,
I swear to God,
I wouldn't dare treat you like a fool.
She seemed very anxious,
and she couldn't get into
the Marketing Department anytime soon,
so I thought of a way for her.
Do you think she ran into some trouble
and needs money urgently?
Did she tell you anything?
Hello. What are the last four digits
of your phone number?
What last four digits?
6453.
What kind of secret code is this?
Sir,
please don't be angry.
It's not a secret code.
It's a ride-hailing app.
Ride-hailing?
Uber?
Yes.
It's similar to Uber.
You just need to enter your destination
in the address bar.
It's too much trouble.
In the past, you just hailed a cab
and off you went.
Actually, it's not that troublesome.
How about I enter it for you?
Excuse me, Miss...
I'm from the HSKP Department
of Purong Hotel.
My name is Xu Miyu.
Alright.
Then,
thank you for your trouble.
Where do you want to go?
No. 18 Qinfang Garden, Aiguo Road.
Okay.
[Pickup: Purong Hotel]
[Destination: Qinfang Garden, Aiguo Road]
Is it here?
Okay.
It's already entered.
Please wait a moment.
The car will be here shortly.
That's it?
This should be the car.
This is great.
Thank you.
You're welcome,
Ms. Xu.
No, no.
Take it.
I really can't accept this.
Thank you.
Alright then.
Thanks a lot.
Goodbye.
I knew I wasn't wrong about you,
Xu Miyu.
Director Xue.
I heard you were assigned to
the executive floor.
How is it?
Are you used to the new job?
There are many things to learn,
but I'm trying my best.
There's always some hardship
at the beginning.
It'll be fine once you get through it.
You are a person
with professional aspirations.
Believe me,
you'll get better and better,
and go to the next level.
Thank you.
Keep it up.
Room service.
Hello, Mr. Ji.
Your clothes have been washed.
Thank you.
Don't you want to check
if it is clean
or if there is any damage?
It's fine. Thank you
for coming all the way here.
Wait a minute.
Do you remember the
good review thing
we talked about last time?
Yes.
So would this meet
your standards for a good review?
Do you ask guests for a good review
every day at work?
No.
I haven't asked anyone else.
So I am especially honored?
Why do you want my good review?
Because you...
Because you are
our esteemed Black Card VIP.
So?
I have cleaned the room
exactly as you asked,
quickly and well,
and I didn't disturb you, did I?
I've already received
two bad reviews this month.
If I get one more,
my entire bonus
for the month will be gone.
-So I…
-So a good review can cancel a bad review
and "buys you another life"?
Who taught you this?
Is it an unspoken rule
on the executive floor?
Yes...
I figured it out myself.
As a newcomer to the workplace,
instead of improving
your professional skills,
you spend all day thinking about this?
What does your bonus have to do with me?
How can you speak like that?
Am I wrong?
No,
you're not wrong.
I'm wrong.
I am unprofessional.
My mistake was overestimating your
pitifully small amount of empathy.
Sorry.
Wait.
Let me tell you,
if you want a good review,
you first have to
make the guests
genuinely like your service.
Making guests feel at home.
I don't need you to teach me.
Makes sense, though.
Mr. Ray.
Sorry to startle you.
I heard your voice
and worried you were in trouble.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
No.
If you don't need anything else,
I'll be going now.
Actually, if you need a good review,
you can come to me.
I'm very satisfied with you.
You smell really nice today.
Is it perfume?
I think you would look beautiful
in this dress.
[I think you would look beautiful
in this dress.]
[Please don't send such messages again.]
[I think you would look beautiful
in this dress.]
Ms. Zhang,
could you let someone else
serve Mr. Ray
from now on?
Why?
Didn't he specifically request you?
He is a bit strange,
always saying inappropriate things to me.
Miyu,
are you being too sensitive?
Mr. Ray is a foreigner;
there might be cultural differences.
But he really makes me uncomfortable.
No.
Well,
then just let him talk.
It's not like you're losing anything.
What can he do to an attendant anyway?
But...
Don't just stand here.
You already have two bad reviews.
And you still want to
be picky about customers?
Good evening.
Sir, let me scan the room key card
for you.
Please come in.
Just a moment.
Your photo.
Do you need any more help?
I need some quiet.
The last ten orders for this item today.
Come on, get ready for the link.
Three, two, one, link is live!
Miyu,
there's a promotion
in Dianjiangchun's live stream today.
Did you buy it?
No.
By the way, an old man checked into 1810.
He looks like he is in his eighties.
He doesn't have any family with him.
We need to pay more attention to him.
Don't.
That old man is very independent.
He came back from abroad.
I think his surname is Tan.
Right.
Mr. Tan.
I'm telling you.
That Mr. Tan
is different from
the old folks here in China.
If you reach out to help him up,
he would be very unhappy.
Anyway,
at his age,
it's not wrong for us
to pay more attention to him.
The old man is fine.
I think
he is in good health.
We don't need to worry about him.
I don't think he's in a good state today.
He looks like he has suffered
some kind of blow.
You are on duty today.
Keep an eye on him.
I missed it again.
Yin Xiang.
I know.
The next order is coming right up.
I'll go find a place with a signal.
It is completely cold now.
Room service.
Mr. Tan, open the door.
Mr. Tan.
Mr. Tan!
Tan...
Is anyone there?
Help!
[Zhang Cailu]
The number you dialed...
Mr. Tan!
Please try it again later.
Front office!
The guest in 1810 has fainted.
I need help.
Roger that. Administer first aid.
The front office will send someone
up right away.
Okay.
First aid.
There's no one on the executive floor.
You're the only one I can turn to.
What is it now?
The guest in 1810 fainted.
He needs first aid!
Can you help me?
Let's go.
Which way?
Right side.
He was lying on the floor when I came in.
I've called 120.
I also notified the front office.
Understood.
Sir! Sir!
Can you hear me? Can you hear me?
Lay him flat first.
Okay.
Here.
1001, 1002, 1003,
1004, 1005, 1006,
1007. No pulse.
I need to do CPR.
Step back a bit.
Give me some space.
Okay.
Mr. Tan!
Sir!
Mr. Tan, how are you?
Can you hear me?
The oxygen bag is here!
The oxygen bag is here.
Careful, slowly.
This way!
Help me.
Okay.
Help him up.
One, two, up.
Here.
Let me do it.
Leave it to me.
Okay.
Careful.
What should we do?
Bear with it; ambulance is almost there.
Why hasn't the ambulance arrived yet?
There's roadwork ahead.
They're stuck two intersections west.
Does anyone else have a car?
Take my car!
Okay.
Come give me a hand.
Be careful.
Hello, I'm a guest here.
Room 1812.
If you trust me,
[Purong Hotel]
let me drive.
Thank you so much, Mr. Ji.
Okay.
Sorry for the trouble.
Sister!
What happened to the guest?
How is the guest?
We're taking him to the hospital now.
Hurry back to your shift.
Wait, Sister.
I really didn't hear it just now.
I really...
I...
-Watch your hands.
-I wanted to check on him
as soon as I finished
watching the live stream.
[Emergency]
[Emergency Room]
Hello, Ms. An.
I'm Xu Miyu, an attendant
from the executive floor.
I've taken the guest to the hospital.
He's in emergency care now.
I don't know the exact situation yet.
[Emergency Room]
Do you need me
to send someone to help you?
No need. You don't have to send anyone.
I'm off work anyway.
I can keep an eye on things here.
Yin Xiang.
Remember to clean room 1810.
I've taken the guest to the hospital.
He's in emergency care now.
[Emergency Room]
If Ms. Zhang asks,
tell her to contact Ms. Anna.
Okay. Thank you.
Mr. Ji,
thank you for today.
Didn't you say
I have pitifully little empathy?
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have said that.
But you...
But what?
You were really helpful.
Thanks to you today.
Thank you so much
for helping us.
It's nothing.
In the face of life and death, there's no
such thing as being willing or unwilling.
I'm honored
that you thought of me.
It's getting late.
You should go back and rest early.
I'll keep an eye on things here.
Family of Tan Jiaming.
Here!
It's acute myocardial infarction.
[Emergency Room]
Fortunately, you performed CPR
and brought him in in time.
Our interventional surgery
went smoothly.
Now the patient
is temporarily out of danger.
Great.
When can the patient be discharged?
The patient is quite old,
so he needs to stay in the hospital
for a few more days of observation.
I understand, doctor.
Thank you.
[Emergency Room]
You didn't leave?
Thank you.
How many times are you going to say
thank you tonight?
Only one person needs to stay.
The ward is small.
Don't all crowd in here.
You go back first.
Ms. An's car needs to be returned.
I can keep an eye on things here.
Then...
Remember to eat.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work, Mr. Ji.
It's nothing.
Thank you for your selfless help.
Here, I'll give you the keys first.
Well...
Has the patient's family been found?
We're already looking.
We only know that
the patient is an ethnic Chinese
from the US.
He used a US passport when registering.
Other information is unknown.
We're already contacting the embassy.
Okay.
Let me know if there's any update.
What?
Nothing. I...
I just want to know
the patient's condition.
Okay.
Rest early.
[Outpatient Building]
Nurse,
how is the patient doing?
He's basically stable.
We'll give him IV fluids for two more days
to stabilize his condition.
Okay, thank you.
Mr. Tan, you're awake.
The sun is already out.
I'm well-rested.
Time to get up.
You can't get out of bed.
We are in the hospital.
In...
In the hospital?
How did I get here?
Who brought me here?
No wonder I kept
having nightmares last night.
I want to go out.
Where are you going?
Hello.
Are you Mr. Tan's family?
I'm his friend.
Who are you?
I'm Xu Miyu,
an attendant from the HSKP Department
at Purong Hotel.
Xu Miyu?
This stubborn old man
must have troubled you.
Not at all. It's my job.
Is Tan Jiaming's family here?
Please go through the
admission procedures.
I'll go.
Here.
Take this bank card.
The PIN is 330915.
Okay, thank you.
You even know how to hide it, huh?
If Jizhou hadn't
called me early this morning,
I wouldn't have come to the hospital
and wasted my time with you.
You had a heart attack!
Don't you know how serious that is?
It's an old problem.
Doctors just like to scare people.
They make it sound so serious.
Ms. An,
the guest in 1810
needs to be hospitalized
for observation for a few days.
His family has arrived.
[Nurse Station]
Okay, come back first.
I've already told Ms. Zhang
about your performance last night.
Thank you, Ms. An.
It's all part of my job.
Thank you.
Okay.
I'm sorry, Ms. An.
I was on shift rotation yesterday
and was with my kid for an exam.
My phone was off.
Sorry for the trouble.
It was no trouble.
I'm actually happy for you.
The attendant under you
is so responsible
and quick to react.
She handled
such an urgent situation
perfectly in no time.
The guest is out of danger now,
so we are all relieved.
The guest's family
even called from abroad
to thank our hotel.
The attendants on your executive floor
deserve the most praise.
No problem.
I'll definitely praise her
when I get back.
Excuse me, cousin.
Go help me get something.
It's in the jacket pocket.
Is it this?
Look.
Ahui
is already gone.
I went to his house yesterday morning
and happened to catch
the seventh day of his passing.
The one in the middle is Liang.
When I went to see him,
he just stared at me blankly,
shedding tears,
unable to say a word.
He has been paralyzed for a year.
In the end,
Ming
was taken to Shenzhen
by his daughter to settle down.
I am the only one left.
Decades have passed.
It went too fast.
[Gao Hong-19th Floor-Rest shift]
[Luo Qingping-18th Floor-Day shift ]
[Yin Xiang-18th Floor-Day shift
-Positive feedback]
Last night,
the guest in 1810
suffered a sudden heart attack.
Yin Xiang, who was on duty,
immediately reported to
the relevant hotel departments
and rushed the patient
to the hospital in time.
She is hereby commended.
Not bad, little Xiang.
Why didn't you mention such a big thing?
Treat us to a meal when you get the bonus.
Miyu,
don't be late again.
Got it.
Everyone, cheer up.
This month is
the service quality supervision month.
Don't slack off or be late.
If you ruin the reputation
of the HSKP Department,
I can't protect you in front of Mr. Feng.
Understood?
Understood.
Get to work.
Miyu.
Yin Xiang.
Don't you have anything to say to me?
I...
Miyu.
I didn't mean to steal your credit.
A life-threatening incident
happened last night.
I was afraid that if the management knew,
I would lose my salary this month.
Don't be mad.
Please don't expose me, okay?
You have it hard.
We all have it hard.
We both work on the executive floor.
We inevitably need to help each other out,
right?
I understand, Miyu.
I owe you this time.
Next time you need me,
I will definitely help you.
Take a break.
Thank you.
You are an interesting person.
When a bad review
that shouldn't fall on you
was pinned on you, you endured it.
When the good review
that rightfully belonged to you
went to someone else,
you still endured it.
Are you
a people pleaser?
I am not trying to please anyone.
I just think everyone
has their own difficulties,
and I don't want to
make things hard for others.
What is it now?
I want to ask you a favor.
Ask me?
Could you go to any room
on the executive floor
and get me a bottle of shampoo,
then go to the storage room
and take a new one—
one that has just been
logged into inventory?
Why...
Don't ask me why.
Just tell me if you can or not.
Sure.
But you can't tell anyone.
Because I only trust you.
[Shower Gel]
[Shampoo]
Miyu.
Ms. Zhang.
[1817 Empty]
[Conditioner] [Shower Gel]
Room service.
Come in.
Did you get it?
[Shampoo] [Storage]
Remember,
keep today's matter a secret.
You absolutely must not tell anyone.
Then I have a question.
Can you guarantee
that this
won't affect the hotel's
normal service operations?
Are you bargaining with a guest?
It's my duty.
Okay.
Don't worry.
Can we pause tomorrow's shipment
for a bit before sending it out?
The prepaid payment has already
gone into your pocket.
How can you cut off the supply?
The goods aren't ready?
It's not about the goods.
I'm worried
that doing this is too risky.
What if someone finds out?
Who could possibly find out?
There's an attendant
on our floor named Xu Miyu.
Xu Miyu?
Who is she?
A newbie.
A rookie,
and you can't handle her?
No.
I saw...
I saw her take a bottle of shampoo
from a guest room in a baffling way.
I don't know what she's doing.
And I didn't dare to ask.
I'm worried
she might have found out something.
Zhang Cailu,
let me tell you,
get things straightened out.
Are you the forewoman,
or is she?
You can't manage
a new attendant?
Do you still want to take your daughter
to the Maldives for New Year's Eve?
Yes, of course I do.
But I'm on edge every day.
The pressure is overwhelming.
My body can't take it.
Why didn't you say that
when you took the money?
You just want to make money
without taking responsibility.
If your body really can't take it,
stop doing it.
There are plenty of people who want to.
No, no.
I don't mean any of that.
I mean,
I definitely won't let
that Xu Miyu off.
In a few days, I'll find a random excuse
to fire her.
I definitely won't cause you any trouble.
I don't care how you do it.
Make it look good.
Don't delay my plans!
Okay.
Rest assured.
Miyu.
Um...
Are you
a people-pleaser?
Don't tell me you want to change shifts.
I don't have time.
I'm not changing shifts.
I...
I want to tell you something.
Here you are.
What are you talking about?
N... Nothing.
I was going to ask you something.
Was your leave for tomorrow
approved or not?
I don't need help.
Welcome to Purong Hotel.
After you, Princess.
Please.
Welcome back.
Mr. Tan.
We meet again,
Xu Miyu.
What is this?
This is a safety handrail
prepared for you.
Why wouldn't I be safe?
Am I that old?
How old are you?
Don't be ungrateful.
That's very thoughtful of you, Miyu.
Very thoughtful, Miyu.
I can use it
for exercise and fitness.
Be careful.
Watch out.
Mr. Tan.
You old rascal.
I am old.
Miyu,
you're really thoughtful.
Thank you.
Come here.
Take a break. Sit down.
[5:00 AM, Monday, Back Kitchen Door]
[Back Kitchen Area—No Unauthorized Entry]
[Loading]
[Deposit to someone]
You startled me.
Does it still taste the same?
Have you really not eaten
in ages?
That's going too far.
Are you even snatching food
from your senior?
Here, senior.
Boss,
another steamer of soup dumplings, please.
Coming.
You really do love eating,
or are you just pretending to
be nostalgic about home?
Senior, you are like a food map.
It's a pity you're in the
Finance Department.
You should go to the Marketing Department
or the sales department.
The F&B Department works too.
I'll take that as a compliment
on my versatility.
As for the skills of eating,
I will teach you slowly later.
Whatever I ask you next,
just answer it.
Promise me you won't pretend.
First question.
Why did you go to
the kitchen's back door today?
Didn't you encourage me to?
Yes.
I want to know
what today's Purong Hotel
has really become.
So, what do you think after seeing it?
The great tree of Purong
looks glorious on the outside,
but in reality,
it has been hollowed out
by termites on the inside.
Okay.
Second question.
Coming back this time,
what exactly are you here for?