(Support Admin Watch on www.kissasia.co, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
[This drama is fictional and any similarity
with reality is purely coincidental.]
[Production guidelines were followed
when filming children and animals.]
[Episode 2]
Is that my baby?
No, it's my baby.
I suppose the question was unclear.
I'll ask again.
Am I your baby's father?
Well... I don't know why you think that.
But it's not your baby.
So, let's just go our separate ways.
You keep being this flustered.
Given all the circumstances,
I'm certain I'm your baby's father.
So? What are you trying to say?
You mean... you're going
to take responsibility?
I will
take responsibility.
- Pardon?
- Let's...
Let's get married.
What?
[D-Day, Day 7]
Let go.
- Let go.
- No, I can't.
Just let go!
Don't let go.
Hey!
It hasn't been long
since I prescribed you medicine,
[Day 5]
but the cycle is fast.
Still having trouble sleeping?
Yeah, sleep has been...
I thought something happened to you!
- What?
- Do you know how many times I called?
You're a light sleeper...
What are you talking about?
I never got any calls...
[Si Hyeong (10)]
I drank too much that day,
so I probably slept well.
Drank too much?
Was there anything else out of the ordinary?
If you mean other things...
[Day 3]
Thank you.
Isn't it about time you act your age?
Wow, working for a liquor company
has its perks.
Using market research as an excuse
to frequent places like this.
Take me along more often, okay?
Here to have fun?
What are you doing? Looking for someone?
No, nothing.
Let's go.
Don't lie.
Is he scanning for tall, pretty women
with his handsome looks?
Hurry up.
Yeah, I'll go.
[Day 2]
Who is she that you're so eager to find?
You must've had some info,
either about her company or her name.
Are you even listening to me?
- Huh?
- Is there any reason
you absolutely have to find her again?
Like, you fell in love at first sight?
Me? Kang Du Jun?
Jeez.
I got curious about her
since I slept well without the pills.
And I have something to give back to her.
What nonsense are you
talking about with that weird face?
Weird?
So it isn't... why say that to me?
Wait, you slept well?
With who?
Who was it?
[Day 1]
[Kang Du Jun]
Huh?
What? This is my signature. Why is it here?
Hey! Come out here, please!
How could you do this to me, huh?
What did I do wrong!
- What's wrong with her?
- Why are you doing this to me?
[Kang Du Jun]
I'm sorry.
That check back then?
Wait.
So...
it was all the same woman?
[D-Day]
Uncle!
You startled me.
That startled me.
By the way, you must be really busy lately.
Last week, you only wished me
happy birthday, and that was all.
Have I ever forgotten your birthday?
What is this?
Take a look.
Wow, amazing! It's so pretty!
So pretty.
What do you want to eat?
Let's go get something delicious.
Today? I have somewhere to go.
Where?
I'll drive you, then.
Oh...
Why won't you tell me where you're going?
Is it something you can't tell me?
It's not that, but...
You clearly said you'd give me a ride, right?
No backing out now.
Let's go! Honk, honk!
Don't you remember anything
about the baby's father?
Well...
Oh? Manager!
Is she from your company?
Se Hyeon.
- Is this the punk you were talking about?
- What's wrong with you?
- Manager!
- What are you doing?
Do you know what you've done?
Manager, this is my uncle!
Ms. Jang Hui Won.
You left the baby's ultrasound photo.
I'll take responsibility.
- What?
- Let's get married.
What? Doing what?
- What?
What did I just say?
You said we get married.
Me?
Yes, you did.
That can't be.
You must have misheard.
Conclusion, yes.
'Let's conclude,' something like that, right?
Ha, seriously.
- Uh, what are you...
- Hold on.
I know it's sudden.
Let me give you some time to think.
For now, go home today,
and we'll meet again soon.
What's going on?
It seems like he's the one
who needs more time to think.
Ugh, whatever.
Even taking responsibility
has different scenarios.
Option 1. Don't get married,
and just pay child support.
- What is this?
- 10 billion won.
- 10 billion?
- It's child support.
If needed, I'll add 10 million won monthly.
Don't ask to see the kid later
or say anything else.
This ending feels a bit bitter.
Option 2. I raise the baby,
and she pays me compensation.
Can I hold the baby for a moment?
Who do you think I am?
Selling babies for profit?
Forget it!
No, that's not it...
No...
This is even worse.
Option 3. Get married
and raise the child together.
Why aren't they coming out?
What? I can't see anything. Why?
Could this really be my future?
No way!
Sir.
Welcome.
One B-set and a bottle of Try, please.
Alright, B-set. Thank you.
Yeah, this is when I spend money.
If not now, then when?
Guess there was a reason
I've been so on edge.
Thank you.
Wait... can I not drink anymore?
- Exams are over!
- Over!
[7 Years Ago]
Let's go all out today!
- Our friendship!
- Forever!
Should we really go home?
Ah, wait.
I don't want to go home.
Let's have just one more drink.
- Just one.
- You already had three bottles.
And I have first period tomorrow...
Oh, what? Mi Ran broke up, remember?
- She broke up!
- One more drink.
- Down for a convenience store run?
- Let's go!
- Here we go again!
Convenience store? I can't.
Oh, please.
- One more drink!
Okay, okay.
But you all have to promise
to have strictly one drink each.
- Hurry up.
- Let's go.
[2 Years Ago]
Hello, I'm Manager Jang Hui Won
from New Product Development Team.
[Jang Hui Won, Manager]
What? Jang Hui Won, you got promoted?
- I'd really appreciate your support.
- Oh, yes.
She's not just any manager.
She's the youngest-ever manager.
Applause!
What?
So cool.
- Cheers!
No...
I'm screwed.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Sir.
I mean, it's just that...
You can't do this to me.
Jeez.
Looks like you had a tough day.
This is the cognac I really treasure.
Drink this and shake it off.
Sir, just pretend you're doing this for me.
Instead, can you
drink and wow once?
Me?
Want me to do it?
Being a mom isn't easy, is it?
How did you know?
If you can't drink your favorite alcohol,
it's one of two things.
Either you're terminally ill,
or you're pregnant.
I had a child at twenty-two.
Back then, I was overwhelmed,
so I kept the baby without knowing better.
But when I think of everything
I gave up afterward,
- well...
- Did you regret it?
Well, I guess it depends on the person.
But if you're not prepared,
it can be really hard.
Even if the baby is adorable,
the child and my life are on separate paths.
It's complicated.
You seem troubled.
What does the baby's father say?
Well...
Sometimes, talking to
a stranger isn't so bad.
You can open up about things.
This baby wasn't planned.
At the most crucial moment,
a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity
has arrived alongside this new life.
It's something I caused,
and I know I have to take responsibility,
but I feel completely lost.
You don't need to feel guilty.
Would a child born out of regret
and unpreparedness really be happy?
If I were you, Hui Won,
I'd chase the opportunity.
Because dreams all have their timing.
Yes.
How about dinner tonight?
Let's have a quick meeting over a meal,
and I'll contact you again.
Okay.
Here are the resume and documents
of Jang Hui Won that you requested.
Good work.
[Jang Hui Won]
[Family Relationship Certificate]
[Jang Hui Won, Manager,
New Product Development Team, Taehan Liquor]
She's pregnant?
Interesting.
[Jang Hui Won]
Did you get home safely?
One, two, three.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Ah, that hits the spot.
- What about you?
- I'm fine.
You drink it.
If you keep giving everything away
like that, you'll be left with nothing.
You're always like this
with your wife too, right?
We're family.
She's the one I should look after the most.
Brother.
What does marriage mean to you?
- That's so random.
- Just asking.
You announced you'd marry
as soon as you started college.
Our parents have such
high expectations of you.
I guess I really needed someone on my side.
People say marriage is the end of your life,
but honestly, I'm loving my life right now.
My wife and Se Hyeon kind of complete
the anxious person I used to be.
Then what about me?
I've always been on your side.
Dear Du Jun.
So you felt left out?
Oh, come on, stop treating me like a kid.
Hey, avoiding me? I'm trying
to show you some love.
- No, no!
- Get over here.
- I really hate this!
- Hey!
Come here quick.
You need to be careful.
Watch your step, you'll fall.
Why am I so tired?
[Did you get home safely?]
Ugh, don't know. I'm tired.
You don't need to feel guilty.
Would a child born out of regret
and unpreparedness really be happy?
If I were you, Hui Won,
I'd chase the opportunity.
Because dreams all have their timing.
Right.
It took me so much to get this far...
[Study in Germany. This time,
I'm going. No matter what!]
What? Why isn't she reading it?
Did she at least save my number?
[Jang Hui Won]
Uncle! Uncle!
Uncle, are you out of your mind?
It's not just anyone, it's your kid!
And you won't even talk about marriage?
It's not that I won't,
but in a different way...
A different way? Like what?
Paying it off with settlement money,
or child support like that?
Raising a child requires so much care.
You think money solves everything
and you can just walk away?
You're completely selfish and irresponsible.
I'm so disappointed in you, Uncle.
But you're together
because you like each other.
Yet even now, you insist
on staying unmarried?
That's not it...
You won't marry because of me, right?
- Se Hyeon.
- You keep avoiding blind dates,
and refusing to get married.
I feel it's all because of me, and it hurts.
Manager Jang.
Guten Tag.
What, you don't know German?
Morgen!
- Ugh.
- He's just jealous you are going to Germany.
The results haven't even been announced yet.
From last year through this first half,
has anyone performed as well as you?
Seriously, everyone knows
the announcement's coming today.
Please stay calm.
Assistant Manager Choi.
She's saying this out of envy.
From what I see, it seems you are
the most jealous, Manager Nah.
I'm not.
- You're clearly jealous.
- Why would I be jealous?
- It's posted.
- What? Who is it? Me?
- The results are out.
- So who is it?
It's me.
I got selected.
[Final Selectee: Jang Hui Won]
Oh my goodness!
Congratulations, this is wonderful news.
You startled me, seriously.
Make some noise when you come in.
When did you get here?
I've been here since you were a baby.
Hold on.
Now it's not that you applied perfume,
but you practically bathed in it.
Well, as president, I have to maintain
some dignity, you know?
Wasn't today just a preliminary site visit?
Who are you trying to impress?
You're overdoing it. Way too much effort.
You, please put in some effort.
Why aren't you trying?
What are you relying on?
This is ridiculous.
I did put in effort. A lot of it, actually.
Alright.
From this angle, there's no issue here.
But here...
How should I put it... It's weird.
And it's strange and kind of bland-looking.
Hey...
What do you mean it's weird!
Jeez.
So what, is it...
'The final touch of fashion
is scent, not the face?'
You little punk.
- Aren't you leaving?
- I am!
Oh no, I got it in my mouth.
Jeez, you are such an annoying type.
By the way, this isn't about me.
But what's the psychology
of people who ignore texts?
It's simple.
First, they hate that sender.
Second, they absolutely despise them.
Third, they're insanely, maddeningly...
Hey, a fly!
- A fly!
- Whoa, hold on, I'm driving!
- There's a fly
- I know, I'm driving!
What? Someone dislikes you?
Have you ever seen anyone who dislikes me?
Oh, whatever.
We'll see who regrets it later.
Wow, Kang Du Jun.
Are you asking me for relationship advice?
My wife and Se Hyeon kind of complete
the anxious person I used to be.
I'll tell you about my love life.
- Back then...
- I've made up my mind.
About what?
I'm going to get married.
Huh?
Hey! Watch the road!
What... get married?
Hey, you said you wouldn't.
- I did.
- And now?
I'm just curious.
Thinking about it, morally
and cost-effectively...
It's better to get it over with quickly.
What nonsense is this? Explain it properly.
Did the chairman say he won't hand over
the company if you don't marry?
Or did your ideal woman suddenly appear?
What on earth are you thinking?
You won't marry because of me, right?
- Se Hyeon.
- You keep avoiding blind dates,
and refusing to get married.
I feel it's all because of me, and it hurts.
What is this even supposed to mean?
You... ah!
Is this some kind of strategic marriage
between companies?
Oh, I don't know.
Wait.
That might actually be better.
- Huh?
- Everyone around us
is in arranged marriages for show.
For us, marriage is just
another business move.
So why not go through with it?
Who knows? Maybe marriage
will fix my current instability.
You're seriously sick.
Let's go to the hospital.
Anyway, that's what you should know.
What, are you getting married by yourself?
Do you even have a bride?
I'm on my way to meet her now.
That bride you're so curious about...
Bride?
Are we going to church now or something?
No responsibility.
Guilty conscience.
A free life.
As you know, when our new president
arrives, he'll tour every floor.
Everyone, please keep things tidy.
- Environmental cleanup...
- Is she in shock from happiness?
She's been waiting for this moment.
Maybe the tension finally melted away.
- Right?
- And one more thing.
Our team's business proposal...
Studying in Germany.
My dream coming true.
Manager Nah, take charge of this
and organize it once.
Assistant Manager Choi, support him.
- Yes.
- And for the remaining staff,
- I was so close.
- you have the performance plan, right?
Organize that and report it to me.
Tak Soo, compile it and report to me.
Understood.
And...
Taking responsibility.
- Single mom, lack of money.
- About the new product proposal.
It was seriously lacking. Check...
Workaholic.
A lonely child.
A bad mother.
Understood.
- Looks like the meeting prep is mostly done.
- Alright.
He might start next week,
so don't let your schedules get disrupted.
And with Manager Jang leaving
for Germany, there's a lot to wrap up.
[Regular deposit]
This won't even come close to enough.
Manager Jang.
Manager Jang!
Are you even listening?
I'm sorry.
Oh, I can't drink this.
Switch with me.
This is warm milk.
Are you my aunt now?
Oh.
I'll keep it a secret at work. Don't worry.
- Um...
- My uncle
is not very skilled at things
outside of work.
Especially, when it comes to dating
and relationships.
He's kind of under-socialized.
Anyway, all that is just
because of his compulsion
to be perfect at everything.
Please look upon him favorably.
He says he won't get married,
and he acts overly conservative
about marriage,
but we all know that's not
how he really feels.
It's all because of me.
Ah.
So you don't know yet.
Anyway, you'll find out gradually.
He says he won't get married,
and he acts overly conservative
about marriage,
but we all know that's not
how he really feels.
It's all because of me.
What's that supposed to mean?
Why is he here?
And I told you,
things like who the CEO is aren't important.
But it's not that he's currently
managing operations,
it's about maintaining relationships.
We need to maintain those connections.
So first impressions
- are extremely important.
- Oh, no.
So in short,
for example, when passing
by employees like this,
you should smile and say hello,
but you don't smile...
Where did he go?
Du Jun!
Wait, why...
Are you okay?
Why on earth are you here?
Did you investigate my background?
Did you forget we agreed
to reach a conclusion soon?
So what exactly is that conclusion?
I've decided.
I'll marry you.
What?
Are you going to keep the baby?
Whether you give birth or not is your choice,
but regardless of that, I also
have responsibilities for my child.
So if you're going to keep it, let's hurry.
I'd prefer the wedding be held this year.
Hey.
It's not hey. I'm Kang Du Jun.
Fine, Mr. Kang Du Jun.
Looks like you've been
getting way ahead of yourself,
but I've never once considered marrying you.
My own issues are complicated enough,
so let's just go our separate ways.
Let's pretend
this never happened.
You can't just erase something
that already happened.
What I'm saying is...
What's so special about marriage anyway?
Marriage is business too.
If you really want,
let's write up a contract.
Of course, with the child's care
as the top priority.
What did you say?
Then I definitely can't agree
to a marriage like that.
Why not?
I've already made
future plans for the child...
You booked that place?
Yes, I pulled some strings.
Shh.
What?
Team leader, this place is locked.
But you said you booked it for this time.
President.
But we were together. Where did he go?
Is someone inside?
Oh no, what do we do?
It seems locked from the inside.
Then to the manager's office...
What do you mean? We just go out and explain.
No way.
This is the perfect situation
for misunderstandings.
I'll try forcing it open.
What? You're going to force the door open?
Call quickly.
Then try calling me first.
But I don't know your number.
Alright.
I knew it.
Haven't you even saved my number?
That's not important right now.
You don't even read texts
from unknown numbers?
Should I at least be grateful
you didn't block me?
Okay, okay. I'm sorry about that.
We'll really get caught like this.
Do something.
Ah, please.
Three!
Ah.
- Ouch, my nose!
- What the...
What's going on?
President?
Ouch.
Oh, President, I'm so sorry.
I didn't know you were inside.
- President?
- Manager Jang, are you even listening?
I'm sorry.
As you know, when our new president
arrives, he'll tour every floor.
Everyone, please keep things tidy.
He might start next week,
so don't let your schedules get disrupted.
Then that president...
I'm Kang Du Jun.
But why are you here?
And why are you here, Manager Jang?
Well, I mean...
I came for a preliminary visit. But I left
my phone in the car, so I borrowed hers.
Is that a problem?
No, of course not.
If you need to finish your call,
we'll go somewhere else...
President!
Then I'll take my leave.
Ah, right.
Your phone works perfectly fine,
so there's no excuse for not replying.
Oh, and,
answer calls from unknown numbers too.
Let's go, Secretary Go.
- Yes.
- Well...
- Secretary Go.
Yes.
Then, I'll get going.
Wow.
So that's why you were
desperately looking for her?
And she's from the same company?
Did you know?
She's got a baby on the way,
and she wants to pretend it never happened?
That's ridiculous.
A baby? You're going to be a dad?
It's not confirmed yet.
What do you mean?
Seriously, tell me.
It's not really my decision to make.
I've already prepared myself mentally.
What? Explain it properly.
I've been feeling kind of betrayed lately.
Ugh, seriously.
I misheard earlier, right?
Marriage and a baby and all that?
It's not certain yet, but you heard right.
When... when did all this even happen?
Marriage. A child.
How come it happened so fast?
And why didn't you tell me
about such happy news, huh?
I'm really hurt by this.
I'm not even sure you can call it good news.
What is it? What are you so worried about?
Why would I worry?
We've known each other for years.
That's the face you make
when you're really worried.
Think of me as your bamboo forest
and say it all.
I just know
it's not my decision to make.
If I were to become a real father,
if I were to have a baby,
I wonder if I could really
take proper responsibility.
You were right.
I guess I'm worried.
Do you remember?
My sister had nowhere to leave the kids.
She endured the pain until she collapsed.
You offered to take care of them.
Told her not to worry and go to the hospital.
It was chaos, remember?
When she got back from the hospital,
the house was a complete mess.
Both my nephews were hanging
off your broad back,
and they refused to come down.
I remember it was different
from raising Se Hyeon.
Maybe because they were boys,
their energy is unreal.
Ever since that day,
my back hurts when it rains.
You know what I thought watching that?
What? 'Kang Du Jun really can do anything.'
Something like that?
Yes, the Kang Du Jun I know
is someone who keeps his word no matter what.
So don't start worrying already.
You'll do great, okay?
As a dad,
and as a husband...
Jeez.
You're being unusually serious.
You're really putting on a whole show.
Ugh, just go already.
Well.
Do the dishes before you leave.
You are such an annoying type.
What? The president?
Whoa, no way.
Hey, isn't that a total jackpot?
Jackpot? What are you talking about?
He completely fooled me.
How many women must he have charmed
while hiding his identity?
Well, with that face, women
probably didn't leave him alone.
It's true.
But
don't you have something to tell me?
What do you mean?
Should I act like I know it or what?
Well...
Like... the guy you've been seeing lately.
Huh? What did you say?
That Min...
No, never mind. It's nothing.
What are you talking about?
What about you,
have you decided?
Looking at your face, I guess not.
Mi Ran, I actually got accepted
to study in Germany?
Really?
Hey, what's there to think about?
The answer is clear.
Right? That's the right choice, right?
Right, and honestly,
haven't you sacrificed
everything for that company?
Overtime, weekend work...
You're still young. Go study abroad.
Go study abroad first,
and then think about the baby later.
[Mom's Birthday]
I'm here.
Do they still celebrate your birthday
at school these days?
You probably already blew out the candles.
Even the department doesn't care.
Who would celebrate a part-time lecturer?
Still, in the past, you used to
get cake and letters.
You take it and eat it.
Throw it away or give it to someone,
do whatever you want.
I don't want to do things
I don't want to either.
It was your choice.
Whether it was a marriage forced by me
or whatever, it was your choice.
What are you trying to say?
I'm just curious.
Curious why I was so hated
for something that wasn't my fault.
If you regret it that much,
you shouldn't have had me.
Why give birth to me
and suffer your whole life? Why?
Yes, you know it well.
Giving birth to you was
a mistake from the start.
My life has been a mess
ever since then. Satisfied?
What?
Did you want me to say it wasn't?
Why bring up old stuff just to hurt me?
Is this why you came?
Just to upset me?
I'm pregnant.
That's why I came today.
Because you're still my mom.
Are you out of your mind?
Not even married, and you are pregnant?
Why would you say it like that?
If you're going to
get rid of it anyway, hurry up.
- Mom!
- Then what are you going to do?
Are you going to keep it?
Just a little while ago,
weren't you the one making
a huge fuss about studying abroad?
A choice?
You're going to walk the same path as me?
Do you really think
you won't be reminded
of everything you gave up
every time you look at that child?
Are you sure you won't regret it?
Do you think you'll be any different from me?
I want ice cream.
- Mom...
- Don't cry.
- Come on.
- Mom.
- I want that!
- Be careful.
Let's ride a little more.
Mom.
Mom...
[Obstetrics and Gynecology]
You were diagnosed with
an endometrioma a few years ago.
You clearly said pregnancy
would be difficult then.
It was indeed a difficult situation.
But seeing the yolk sac
perfectly settled in the womb,
this is truly a miracle.
Still, if you overexert or get stressed,
you risk miscarriage
so you must be extra careful.
If something happens to this baby,
there may never be another chance.
Young mom,
don't be too scared.
Mom?
Mom, I'm scared.
If you're scared, sleep with the light on.
When will you sleep?
I'll sleep when it's time, Hui Won.
You're old enough to sleep alone now.
Mom.
How long will you keep calling for me?
If it weren't for you, I...
I'm going inside later, so sleep first.
I'll come in after I drink this.
[Airplane Ticket]
If you're worried, shall I give you
a miscarriage prevention shot?
I...
I want to get rid of it.
You seem confused right now.
You don't have to decide today,
so take a few days to think.
Hui Won.
I brought some side dishes,
but you didn't answer...
Is something wrong?
Enjoy your meal.
What? Pregnant?
Hey, are you okay?
You said he was a stranger.
Then does that punk know?
Forget it, give me his number.
I'll deal with this scoundrel.
Ugh, stop it. What can you do?
What do you mean?
I should grab his collar
and demand responsibility.
I'm not a kid anymore.
What responsibility are you talking about?
I chose it anyway.
You chose?
What? Am I not allowed to?
Are you
really the Jang Hui Won I know?
And what about you?
I know everything too.
About you and Mi Ran.
I saw it, by chance.
Hey, wait.
Saw what?
You two are dating.
How could you do this without telling me?
That's not it.
I'm not dating Mi Ran.
But I even saw you kissing.
What?
Wow, it's Cha Min Uk!
- Hey, Cha Min Uk!
- Careful!
Did you drink again?
Yeah, team dinner.
Ugh, you reek of alcohol.
But I ditched the dinner to come see you.
I did good, right?
Good job. Get inside and rest now.
Oh, right, this.
You said you've been
craving my rolled omelet.
- Yeah.
- I added flying fish roe.
Make sure to eat it later.
Ah, I love it.
Ah, I love it! Cha Min Uk, you're the best!
Hey, Hwang Mi Ran!
Do you
want to go out with me?
- What?
- I'm asking you out.
I like you.
So you rejected her.
I didn't even know.
Enough about that.
What will you do now?
You're not actually going
to keep it, are you?
Are you even thinking
about marrying that guy?
No, it's not like that.
You always said
you didn't want to end up like your mom.
I don't want you
to make a choice you'll regret.
I know.
But I just need
a little more time to think.
Ah, what?
Call me if it gets hard. Even at dawn.
Got it.
Here.
Thank you.
Go.
Hurry.
- I'll leave.
- Go.
Do you like that man?
Oh, my! You scared me!
But how did you find my place?
Are you two dating?
No, it's not like that.
I just thought you two
looked all lovey-dovey.
Seriously, we're just friends.
Hey.
No, President.
How could you lie to me perfectly?
What exactly did I lie about?
Please pretend you don't know me at work.
Fine.
- What?
- I'll do as you wish.
But,
whoever your heart belongs to,
it's none of my business.
But I do expect us both
to take responsibility for our actions.
Does that make sense?
Jang Hui Won is pregnant?
[3 years ago]
This is our new employee, Cha Min Uk.
Let's all give him a round of applause.
Hello, I'm Cha Min Uk
starting today in the sales team.
I look forward to working with you.
Your desk is over there. Go take a seat.
Yes.
Hello.
- Fighting!
So how was your first day?
Wow, it was so hectic and nerve-wracking.
I didn't even know whether food
was going into my mouth or my nose.
If it weren't for the chocolate you gave me,
I would've been in big trouble.
That stuff is expensive.
I gave it to you because it's you.
But our connection is really something.
Middle school, high school, college,
and now we work at the same company?
Why? I like it.
Weren't we supposed to
stick together forever?
Huh?
My treat today!
- Cheers!
- Bottoms up!
Ah.
But you guys left early yesterday.
What time did you get home yesterday?
[You've received 2,000,000 won
from Taehan Liquor Bonus.]
Whoa, what's this?
What is it?
[You've received 2,000,000 won
from Taehan Liquor Bonus.]
[You've received 1,500,000 won
[To celebrate New President's inauguration]
Bonus?
The new president gave it to us.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Seriously?
[To celebrate New President's inauguration]
It's a bonus.
- A bonus!
- From the new president?
Huh? Here's President.
- He's handsome.
- So cool.
Wow, he has such presence.
Isn't he basically a model?
You're mine.
Oh, President! Welcome to Taehan Liquor.
Thank you for the welcome.
Ah, yes.
The door closes.
Hold on!
Are you getting on?
Ah, I...
I'll take the next one.
Alright.
The door closes.
Unbelievable.
Assistant Manager, you saw him, right?
Yeah, totally my type.
Even as a guy, I think he's impressive.
The bonus was such a pleasant surprise.
Right? He's young but so thoughtful.
And those shoulders...
His shoulders are so broad,
you could surf on them.
Assistant Manager Choi, did you break up?
Why? Can't I say he's my type?
Pfft, greedy much?
But Manager Jang,
don't you feel any urge to pursue
someone like our new president?
Whoever your heart belongs to,
it's none of my business.
But I do expect us both
to take responsibility for our actions.
Ugh, how annoying.
Hey, why is everyone like this with me?
Hey, Kim Tak Soo! Get over here!
Tak Soo!
Fine, I'll let it slide this once.
[Taehan]
- I'll get your beer ready.
- Oh.
[Yellow]
This isn't Try Beer.
No wonder it tasted...
Oh, dear...
We are planning to launch a new beer product
for the global market
within a short timeframe.
We are aiming to target
the global market soon
with plans to launch a new beer product.
Could you give me more specific plans?
First, we plan to research
each country's beer market.
Based on the results, we plan
to go full-scale product development phase.
How many people do you think
will participate in
today's market research in Japan?
This is the cold storage facility,
where proven-quality beer
is packaged into cans or kegs and stored.
It seems fairly well organized.
Secretary Go.
This place is totally disorganized.
Get it sorted out quickly.
This is the brew house where we
make wort, the main beer ingredient.
Since beer production involves yeast,
please pay special attention to hygiene.
Understood.
Oh! Wait, hold on!
Which floor are you going to?
Ah, I'm going to 15...
15th floor.
Oh, let me carry them for you.
- I'm fine.
- With those thin wrists of yours,
what if they snap
while you're carrying those?
Give them to me.
It's heavy.
Yeah, what?
Are you crazy? What if you mess that up?
Don't even think about leaving work today.
Fix it now and email it
to me. Get it together!
I'll get off here.
- Take care.
- Then, I'll get going.
Huh? Wait, don't you need these?
You should take them with you.
For the first half of next year,
we're exploring a plan
to develop a new product by reducing
the calories of our existing Try beer.
We're also considering
seasonal promotional items.
- Did you get dragged here?
- For that,
- Lighten up a little.
- we plan to collaborate with other brands.
We'll showcase collaborative products
with various brands to customers.
That concludes the briefing.
Call me if it gets hard. Even at dawn.
Got it.
Thank you for your hard work
preparing the presentation.
- Not at all.
- Everyone received bonuses last time, right?
Ah, we were extremely grateful.
We were all completely surprised.
Right? President, you are the best.
Then you should earn your pay.
I'm not saying work harder
because you got bonuses.
But you should at least work
to the level of your salaries.
If there's anything lacking...
Everything.
The annual 3-year new product design report
due every September is inadequate.
By now, winter promotions
should be finalized as a baseline.
Next half-year's product proposals
should've been ready too.
Based solely on today's briefing,
there are zero concrete cases.
Since it's our first meeting together,
please provide more
detailed enhancements moving forward.
Yes, we'll fix this.
Ah, one more thing.
Is the Germany program selectee
in this New Product Development Team?
Yes.
Our team's Manager Jang Hui Won was chosen.
Ah, I see.
Manager Jang Hui Won.
Yes?
Do you actually intend to go to Germany?
I know there are plenty of responsibilities
here requiring your attention.
Wouldn't it be overwhelming?
Jeez.
His personality is something else.
But why is he treating
Manager Jang like that?
Exactly. Manager Jang
really wants to go to Germany.
Right, Manager Jang?
You told me not to act like
I know you at work.
People might misunderstand.
I knew you were annoying,
but this is downright shameless.
Why would you ask that there?
Because I'm curious.
I have no idea what you think.
Since we're on the subject, let me ask.
Are you going to keep the baby?
I haven't decided yet.
Even if I do, I won't marry you.
You said it doesn't matter who I like.
Plus, it's a waste of time discussing this
with someone who views marriage as business.
And I'll never have a loveless marriage.
Let's just stop all of this here.
You're bold even without alcohol.
What did you say?
You said before, didn't you?
That it's your own business
and you'll take responsibility.
But...
Now that I know about it,
this is my business too.
So let's meet at least three times a week.
- What?
- Love. Let's give it a try properly.
Let's just say we both enjoyed it.
- Keep it cool.
- Cool?
I let it slide that she was with another man,
and this is how she treats me?
Either treat her well
or torment her. Pick one.
You're not seeking revenge, are you?
How did you feel about
the father of Hui Won's child?
Are you here to ask about that now?
Then what about taking it slow?
I don't want to stop.
The secret woman,
Kang Du Jun's illegitimate child.
We just need to frame it, right?
Because of you, our entire team
is about to be investigated.
Ow.
President, we've got a serious problem.