(Episode 2)
(Kaminichi University)
(Faculty of Engineering,
Department of Architecture)
Rei.
Dodging loan sharks?
Don't scare me like that.
I'm not running away.
(Unkown:
I never let my debtors escape)
I have to pay for car repairs.
Repair fee? How much?
For now, I'll take a part-time job.
15 hours a day,
1,200 yen per hour, six days a week.
What about sleep, meals,
and assignments?
That's impossible.
Haa...
Alright.
Enough.
You're wasting precious time.
We're late now.
- Whoa, oh my gosh!
- Wow, so cool!
Arashi.
Are there any other
distinguishing features?
Distinguishing features?
Beautiful, slender legs like an art.
Proportional chest.
A face that should be
national treasures.
What's going on?
First-year with bright eyes.
Found you.
Why are you...
Rei?
Let go!
I told you, I never let
my debtors escape.
Or would you prefer to settle it here?
You've already paid in part, on the bed.
On the bed?
Let's talk elsewhere!
Stop making misleading statements!
I'll pay the rest after
working part-time.
It won't be immediate, though.
Another promise you can't keep?
I despise people who
don't honor their promises.
When did I ever break a promise?
You've already forgotten?
I warned you the repairs
would be expensive.
And the boy who cried wolf
said he'd pay.
Who's the boy who cried wolf?
- You claimed it'd be free!
- Not free.
I said money wasn't necessary.
What nonsense.
You scammer! You're heart isn't human!
I hate disrespectful brats.
You mean adult,
think you can scare me?
- Arashi-senpai.
Where did Arashi-senpai go?
I want him to review
my rejected projects.
Maybe that way.
They said to come find him here.
Don't see him anywhere.
Too close! Move back!
What are you doing?
If you make too much noise,
they'll find out we're here together.
Call me Arashi-senpai.
Why?
Say it: ‘Arashi-senpai, '
'please let Rei go.'
No way.
What's your deal?
These eyes are unfair.
There's no choice but to beg.
Huh? What?
Am I being teased?
Alight. Let's think about
something meaningful.
Ummm...
Like...
I can't... Oh no.
I've reached my limit.
Arashi-senpai.
Please let Rei go.
"Rei will never..."
"talk cheeky again"
Say it.
Rei will never...
talk cheeky...
again.
Good boy.
Everyone has left.
I told you I'd collect my debts.
I also warned you to speak politely.
If you don't listen to me, I'll have to
resort to forceful measures.
You can leave.
You're not attacking me?
Even though I look like this,
I have standards.
Disrespectful kids aren't my type.
This humiliation…
I'll get you back.
I'll find your weak spot!
"Love in The Air -Premonition of Love -"
Welcome to "Love in the Air!"
Here's your afternoon trivia.
How long does a giraffe sleep?
Just one minute a day!
Their high blood pressure makes
lying down tough,
(Tall, long legs, perfect appearance)
a real weakness!
(Went to a world-class design competition,
became a top-ranking scholarship student)
(Has a car, know how to repair cars,
rich)
Ugh.
I'd rather know Arashi's weaknesses
than a giraffe's.
Giraffes, with four stomachs,
cries "moo", are actually part
of the cow family.
Maybe learning about their kin
will help you know giraffes even better!
That's it.
Man, your finish is top-notch as always.
Cheers to the best mechanic.
Thanks.
But seriously, can you stop
cornering better than the racers?
My confidence's already shaky
before the big competition.
Didn't think you were
the sensitive type.
Oh wow,
am I hearing things wrong?
I heard some background characters
from some group talked about
racing and cornering.
Amateurs in a competition...
I wish they'd quit it
because it degrades
the whole competition.
Speaking of the race,
it's a top secret competition,
they say the organizers
are super dangerous.
Oh yeah, totally legit.
If everyone heard the name,
they would definitely be scared.
So it's a race that no one
can have a say in it.
But well, my dad's close with the guy.
I've been to his house
and had dinner with him!
Wow, that's amazing. That's great.
In this competition,
I can take you to meet him.
Don't chicken out.
The sponsor is that famous...
What?
Rule number one,
never discuss race details in public.
Are you involved?
Whatever. Just like a racer,
I'll just show you the difference
in skill on the track.
So be prepared...
I think it's time to go home.
Hey!
If you're so scared, why don't you
go pray for rain and
hope the race is canceled?
I don't want it to be cancelled,
or I won't be able to experience
the exciting moment.
But rain? I don't hate it.
Isomura-senpai!
You're close with Arashi-san, right?
Well, he's a senior whom I respect.
- Why?
- What's his weakness?
Rei.
Weakness?
Even if I knew, why would I tell you?
He's my idol.
What? Damn it.
Hey, where are you going?
Sorry for earlier.
I apologize on his behalf.
Rinka, listen!
You can't trust Arashi.
How would you feel if someone
insulted someone you respect?
That is how I feel right now.
- Let's go.
- Yes.
What's wrong with you?
Don't fights with senior and your crush.
Well...
Ugh, I just can't figure out anything.
His weakness...
You really want to know about
Arashi-senpai?
Shikura.
You know something? Spill it!
Well, it's just a rumor...
Huh?
Really?
It's still just a rumor.
If you want to be sure, you have to
see it with your own eyes.
Please present your code.
I'm a friend of the host.
No code, no entry.
Damn it!
Hey, if you're not going in, move it.
Huh?
Hey!
Who do you think you're talking to?
No idea. Who are you?
I...
Ah.
Hello, Papa.
No. You see...
I was told that I can't get in
without a code.
Ah... Yes.
Thank you very much.
Yes.
You may enter.
Let's go!
What's with him?
Stay here. I don't want you
caught up in this.
Hey, Rei!
That troublemaker...
Yay!
Lost everything again! Screw this!
Relax, the main event's still to come.
Arashi's racing.
Arashi? Did they just say Arashi?
Excuse me,
may I check your pass?
I'm a local resident.
I heard the noise and
came to check it out.
Trespassing, huh?
Let go of me!
We've got a rat! Catch that kid!
There is an intruder!
A hero disrupting the race?
But if there's someone scarier,
there's one person right here.
I'm leaving early. Apologies.
What? You're leaving?
I'm prepared to take
appropriate punishment.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- This motorcycle is perfect.
All that's left is for a skilled racer
to fill what's lacking.
This isn't just any race,
we're racing together.
This one is not normal either.
It's special too.
Hey!
Oh no!
Let go of me!
I'm sorry, Arashi-san.
Arashi.
Bold of you to call me like that.
Troublemaker.
This is the biggest mess
I've ever been in.
Arashi-san.
- We'll take it from here...
- No need.
I'll handle it.
We're close.
Please keep an eye on him.
He's my boy.
I'm sorry for being rude.
We need to talk.
Ouch!
Oww!
Hey! Don't hit me!
Even my parents never did that!
Say something.
Kids need discipline.
Do you even realize what you did?
I...
If I wasn't there,
what would've happened?
Sorry.
I don't need apologies.
I'm asking you if you understand.
Do you want to throw your future away?
Any idiot should be able to
figure it out if he thinks
about it a little.
Even if they know it's an illegal race,
people will still turn a blind eye,
which means the organizer
is a dangerous person.
It's not hard to make
an idiot disappear.
- I didn't know...
- Not only that.
For adults,
apologizing and crying about it
won't make up for it.
Don't be naive.
You are also participating
in an illegal race!
You protected for me just now...
Aren't you in trouble?
I will take responsibility
for my own choices.
Because it is underground racing,
it is a place where people
want to risk their lives,
and who want to master
the art of maintenance.
As a mechanic,
I think learning from
underground racing is useful.
I am prepared to pay
for something important.
I didn't mean to give you any trouble,
I just wanted revenge,
that's all.
Idiot.
All you ever do is call me an idiot!
Is that all you can say?
I'm an idiot anyway.
You're right, I am unable to think!
Don't think I'm going to let you
get away with it.
Watch me,
I'm going to make you fall for me.
And don't call me stupid anymore.
I'm waiting.
Keep your promise.
Stay the night.
Huh?
This way, there's no way to turn back...
Trying to make me fall in love?
Fall in love?
Yay!
- Whoa!
- Go!
Wait, that's not Arashi.
A win's a win!
Thanks, man!
They're truly amateurs.
None of them can even hope
to challenge me.
No matter how we compete, I'll win.
Why don't you prove it, then?
Did you just say that?
You can bet on anything
on tonight's match.
Whatever you want, be it money,
fame, or lover.
Fuma! Come hang out with us tonight!
Wow, that's great suggestion.
But sorry,
I have something to do today.
Huh, why?
Were you angry just now?
- Can't you go?
- Sorry.
(Are you okay?
Not in danger, right?)
Dammit, what did I just say?
Want to take a shower?
“Not Just the Rain, but the Storm Approaches”
"Love in The Air -Premonition of Love -"
Did I accidentally fall asleep?
You're so good-looking it's annoying.
Serves you right.
Good night.