[Disclaimer:
All depicted events are fictional
and for entertainment purposes only;
viewer discretion is advised]
[Kanchanaburi, 2025]
[Napatsakorn Pingmuang]
[Harit Buayoi]
[Ausadaporn Siriwattanakul]
[Wannakorn Reungrat]
Khemjira...
[Matimun Sreeboonrueang]
[Phirunwat Promrat]
[Janistar Phomphadungcheep]
[Natthamon Jantraviphart]
[Nichapat Sujipinyo]
Sir,
that wasn't nice, you know.
Someone could get hurt.
- Hey, take care of this.
- What the heck?
- Come on, cheers.
- Are you alright?
- Hey.
- What's wrong?
- Thanks to the rain...
- What the heck?
The weather's so nice.
Are we drinking all night or what?
Yep, until morning.
I'm freaking tired.
Going home?
Aren't you working early tomorrow?
[Ubon Ratchathani, 2010]
Wait here, okay?
Hello, Grand Master Sek.
You haven't gotten any better?
I'm getting worse day by day,
but Khem is getting even worse.
Then, get him upstairs now.
Okay.
Khem!
Run away!
Go!
Hey!
Are you alright?
Kid!
Hey.
Are you okay?
Kid!
Hey!
Khem,
are you hurt, sweetie?
What about the puppy?
Where is it now?
It's safe.
I thought that ghost would've eaten it.
Khem,
you saw a ghost again?
What's wrong with me, Mom?
Am I sick?
Khem,
Do you remember asking me
why your name, Khemjira,
sounds like a girl's name?
My family is cursed.
Every male offspring
must die violently and unnaturally
before turning 21.
I'm sorry, sweetie.
I didn't expect it to be this bad.
Am I dying, Mom?
That's why we're here to get help.
Thank you for saving me, Grand Master.
Don't worry.
I'll cast a spell on you.
And after that,
you won't see any more ghosts,
okay?
Can we not do that?
Why not?
Aren't you scared of them?
If your spell works,
when Mom's gone,
I won't get to see her anymore.
If life gets harder
and tougher for you,
are you okay with that?
Yes.
(Incanting)
Always keep this with you.
Protect it with your life.
(Incanting)
Since you've chosen to see ghosts,
you'll also need to know
how to defend yourself from them,
okay?
(Incanting)
[Ubon Ratchathani, 2025]
[Welcome, MP Banjerd Nakarnkoon,
to Baan Nong Sin]
- Hello, sir.
- Hi.
Thank you so much
for the new road to the temple.
It's so much easier to get around now.
I'm just doing my job.
That's nice.
Everyone,
the MP will have solar panels
installed for our village soon.
Really?
Yes, soon!
That's fantastic, sir!
- Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
Come on here!
- Join us for some dancing.
- Come on.
- You're all really healthy.
- Let's dance to welcome the MP.
- Yeah, like that!
- Wow, everyone's so strong.
Come on, young ladies.
Whoa.
I hope to earn your trust.
- Alright, let's have some fun.
- We are.
- Dance to welcome the MP.
- Let's dance.
Jet!
Yes, Dad?
Didn't I tell you to go see your master?
I'm about to.
The music's just so exciting
that my hips can't stop moving.
- Aw.
- Just go,
- or I'll make you stop moving.
- I'm off now.
Should be there soon!
Go already!
Alright, let's enjoy ourselves.
Have fun!
- Please vote for me next time.
- Let's dance!
- Okay.
- Come on.
[Khem: Call me back
when you've got time]
[You missed a voice call on LINE]
You usually just see them.
But this one attacked you first?
He looked like he had lost his mind,
like he had just flipped out.
Even the amulet couldn't protect you?
I barely got through it.
I had to recite the spell for so long.
Does it have something
to do with your curse?
I'm actually on my way to see my master.
I'll ask for his help.
Thanks, Jet.
Let me know what he says.
You're leaving for Bangkok
tomorrow, right?
Have you told your father yet?
I'm about to.
I'll see you tomorrow.
(Casting a spell)
I'm here to say goodbye
to you and Father.
Wish me luck.
How funny.
I keep seeing ghosts everywhere.
And yet, Mom,
you never came to see me.
Everything happens for a reason, Khem.
Lately,
have you been struggling with anything?
Things are getting worse, aren't they?
I can sense it.
Whatever you do,
stay mindful and careful.
If it gets too hard to bear,
come back here.
You're almost 21 now.
Things are only getting worse.
I'll be careful, Father.
Please continue to protect him, Khae.
[I'm at my dorm now]
Oh...
Go help them!
That was close.
Jet?
Why are you here?
I was worried about you,
so I came here as soon as I arrived.
Are you alright, boys?
That almost hit my friend's head.
You should've been more careful.
I swear I put the box
down flat on the floor,
and the lid was closed tight.
We were both holding onto the ladder.
I honestly don't know how it fell.
What the hell?
How could it fall
if it was on the floor?
And the rail is way too high.
Must've been a ghost, then.
Come on, Jet.
No point in stressing over it.
Let's cool off with something cold.
It's on me.
How was this one?
Not as crazy as the last one, right?
Yeah.
She just looked at me.
Maybe she knew I could see her.
I wish I could see them like you,
so I could help keep an eye out.
Here,
it's a talisman from Master Paran,
the OG shaman in Ubon Ratchathani.
You're lucky I'm his number one disciple,
or you wouldn't be getting this.
Master Paran...
The one you asked
to read my birth chart?
What did he say?
"Khemjira
Chandrapisut.
Born on June 6th."
How is it, Master?
Let your friend know
he'd better hurry and do what he wants.
He has six months
until he dies.
Die? It's that serious?
But...
is there nothing you can do?
Haven't I told you?
I don't mess with anyone's...
karma.
You're craving something cold, right?
Cheng sim ei, shaved ice,
bingsu, or ice cream?
What do you want?
You can't fool me.
What's up with my fate?
Why are you sidestepping it?
I knew it.
In six months,
I'll turn 21.
Forget it.
Come on,
don't give up just yet.
I'm sure
there's gotta be a way
to break that curse.
I'm not giving up.
I'm just bracing myself.
Every meeting
leads to a parting.
The bas-relief sculptures around
the base of the Democracy Monument
were created by
Professor Silpa Bhirasri.
The monument was commissioned in 1939.
These eight panels
depict stories and ways of life
following the revolution.
The monument has four wings,
each spaced 24 meters apart,
symbolizing the date of the revolution,
June 24, 1932.
The focal point of the monument
includes a turret
with six doors.
There are many more details...
Student,
are you okay?
Your time has come.
- Your time has come.
- Hey!
Are you alright?
Uh... I'm okay.
The Democracy Monument symbolizes
progress and the future.
All the roads
extend from Ratchadamnoen Avenue
and lead to different provinces,
as we can see.
You wouldn't be of any help.
You'd be dozing off the entire class.
That's not funny, bro.
It started in Kanchanaburi.
Then, it was at your dorm.
Now it's even on campus?
It's like the curse
is trying to break you down.
I'm really worried about you.
Why don't you crash at my place
for a while?
If anything happens, I'll be there.
You're still with me?
Hey, Khem!
- Khem!
- Give me a sec.
I gotta go.
Hey, I'm Khem.
I live just across the hall.
Have you eaten yet?
Whoa...
Garlic pork with a fried egg!
It looks seriously tasty.
Wanna try some?
- Let go of me!
- Come here.
- I said let go!
- Come!
He's my son. I can do anything to him!
Why are you recording?
- Take him!
- You called the police on me, right?
Come!
Come on.
- Let go of me!
- Come with us.
Let go of me!
- We can talk somewhere else.
- Let go!
- What are you looking at?
- Come on!
- Go
- Just go!
You'll regret this.
How funny.
I keep seeing ghosts everywhere.
And yet, Mom,
you never came to see me.
Help me, Khem.
Khem, help me.
Khem!
This is seriously messed up.
My master's talisman
normally lasts for a year.
You're staying at my place tonight.
If something happens,
I'll help you right away.
- I'm okay.
- I'm not asking.
I'm telling you.
How am I supposed to live without you?
Jane,
- Khem is staying...
- Go ahead.
Hello.
Have you eaten...
Leave her alone for now.
Probably stuck on revising her project.
Come on.
Let's go.
What?
I was almost done!
Khem!
- Mom?
- Khem...
Help me.
Khem!
- Help me.
- Mom?
Help me, Khem.
Why always me?
Khem,
please help me.
Jet,
wake up and save Khem.
Please.
Khem!
Come to me.
Don't go.
(Chanting)
Jet, please save Khem.
Khem, come to me.
Let go!
I'm saving my mom.
Khem!
Khem, come to me.
Get a grip!
Wait...
Why am I here?
I don't know.
You almost fell, you know.
The amulet's lost its power,
and the talisman's worn out.
I honestly don't know
if I can handle what's coming.
Once the semester break starts,
I'm going straight back
to see my father.
I'm sorry, Jet.
I don't think I'll be joining...
the volunteer camp this year.
Why would you be sorry?
Your life matters the most, man.
Hey, guys,
listen up.
Put it down.
There's a storm hitting the south,
so the uni's concerned about our safety.
Looks like we might have to
cancel the camp this break.
- Jeez.
- What?
- How come?
- Everything's ready.
- Gosh.
- All are ready.
- What a waste of time.
- What about my alcohol?
Hey, leave it to me.
Can't we go somewhere else instead?
Yeah, right.
It's way too sudden.
Getting approval from the village
and sending a new request to the uni...
They'll take too long.
We can go again next year.
What, Jet?
He told us to listen.
I have an idea.
Hey!
Let's go to Ubon Ratchathani.
Ubon Ratchathani?
Well, my friend's been hoping
to go there for three years.
Is Jet coming back, Uncle Chai?
That's right, Master.
He called me the other day,
saying he wanted to bring his friends
for a volunteer camp here.
He mentioned wanting to stay
at your house, too.
So...
if I were to move up the ceremony
to welcome them,
would that be alright with you?
I'll find a new date for you.
Okay.
I'll take my leave, then.
Thong, Jet's coming back this break!
I know that already!
I was with you the whole time.
Master,
can you remove the spell
blocking Jet's sight this time?
We wanna play with him again.
- Please.
Yeah, like that. Exactly.
Lower your lips
and keep your cheeks nicely puffed.
Yeah.
Now, frown.
Sob, too.
I really have no choice.
Please,
can you...
help me,
Master?
Perfect!
Master or not,
even a heart of steel
would melt in front of this.
What are you staring at, Charn?
Which one do you like?
Khem or Jet?
No!
It's not like that.
I mean,
is there something weird
about those two?
Come on, you missed last year's camp.
You wouldn't know them.
They're really nice.
Especially Jet, he's hilarious.
What's so weird about them?
Charn, check this out!
Have you been to Ubon Ratchathani?
Look, there are seven
recommended dishes there,
- like pork sausages and Vietnamese soup.
- You took forever.
- Hey, you're in my way.
- Should we try them?
Move.
Sit here.
Ouch!
- Are you okay, Prae?
- It really hurts, babe.
- Too much love here.
- What's your problem?
Are you guys fighting now?
- Love is gross.
- Argh.
Alright, since you're all here,
let's hit the road.
Let's go!
You think it's okay?
Dance harder, come on!
Here we go.
I look stunning here.
Hey,
why are we taking this route?
It's a shortcut.
Our driver wants to get there quickly.
But this is...
What's wrong with this route?
Jet!
What?
Guys!
What's happening, Jet?
I knew it.
This route is full of anguished spirits.
My master's warned me not to take it.
We're really in deep shit.
They're everywhere, right?
There's evil energy all around.
Do restless spirits
usually haunt people this closely, Jet?
This is not usual.
Where are you going?
Why not chant and repel them?
We can't. There are too many of them.
Let's just drive away.
Sir!
Hey!
Sir,
wake up!
come on. Wake up!
Hey, what are you doing?
They're only after me, aren't they?
There's no point in doing that.
Stop that.
Let me go!
Master!
I knew
that if I, your number one disciple,
were in trouble,
you would come to help,
no matter where I might be.
Thank you...
Oh?
Why are you here in a spirit form?
Something's up at the village.
Hurry and wake the driver.
Make sure you get there before dark.
What?
Hurry, Master.
Chompoo's probably gone crazy already.
Chompoo!
- Chompoo!
- Stay away from me!
Chompoo...
Let me go!
I said to let go!
Go away!
- Just leave me alone!
- What's going on? Let's see.
- Let go of me!
- Chompoo!
- Keep her down.
- Piss off!
- What are they doing?
- Get your hands off me.
It's an exorcism.
Come on.
Chompoo!
Chompoo...
Go!
Right here.
Piss off!
- Go away!
- Hey,
- don't let her go.
- Hurry.
- Come on, sweetie.
- Go away!
- What's wrong with you?
- Don't move.
Come on, help us.
- Make sure it's tied firmly.
- Piss off.
I'm getting chills.
- You scared?
- I gotta take a dump.
- Let me go!
- Asshole.
Stay out of this.
This body belongs to me now.
What did she ever do to you?
Do not burden yourself
with further karma.
I won't.
I've loved her since I was alive.
Even in death,
I'm not leaving her ever!
(Incanting)
- Chompoo...
- Just let go.
Mom...
Set the one you love free
so she can be happy.
Come on.
Take her there.
- Together.
- Alright.
Slowly. Be careful.
- Take it easy, sweetie.
- Take the bag away.
The tray, too.
Keep your face up, sweetie.
This is my friend, Khemjira.
And...
action!
Uh...
Hello,
Master...
My face must be worn out by now.
If you're staying at my place,
get there before dark.
Okay.
What's up with you?
We even practiced that on the bus.
Follow him, guys.
Is that heavy?
Get their beds ready.
- Okay.
- Let me help.
Alright.
- Let's go.
- This one!
- We gotta hurry.
- Hello.
You can share a room with us.
- Yeah, okay!
- Whoa.
- That's dope.
- Let's do that, bro.
- I just saw...
- Who said that?
Hey,
you're staring at them again.
What's got you wondering now?
Where are they going?
Aren't you curious, too?
I mean...
Didn't you see them
talking to that shaman?
Exactly.
He insisted that everyone come here.
Right when we arrived,
there was an exorcism.
It feels like they set us up
to join some kind of cult.
Isn't that a bit suspicious?
Come on, Charn.
You've been watching too many movies.
Chill out.
Why bother worrying about them so much?
It's pretty far.
Right here.
They're here.
Jet.
Jet!
Dotty!
Come on.
- He has a dog?
- Come here.
- Come to me.
- Dotty.
Come on.
What?
What the heck?
- You know each other?
- Baby Dotty!
Paw.
Good girl.
So clever.
Go away.
You're not welcome here.
What, Master?
You told us to get here.
If we're not welcome,
we should just leave.
So it's you.
Get out of my place.
That guy...
Do you know him, Master?
Show your friend to the room.
Whatever you need, help yourself.
We need to talk tonight.
Okay.
Come on.
Jet,
is Master always this cold?
Well...
No.
He's usually worse than this.
This is him being soft.
But don't worry.
He might look cold,
but if someone's in trouble,
he always helps.
I feel like I'm a burden.
I should've...
never come here in the first place.
Come on, you're not a burden.
Get some sleep.
Hey, where are you going?
To face my karma.
Haven't been beaten in so long.
I really miss the good old days.
How about another one?
You just never listen to me.
I told you to stay out of it.
Well...
Khem's a good guy.
When I first met him,
it felt like...
we'd known each other forever.
By the way,
that spirit you drove away...
Was he Khem's karmic enemy?
No.
Now,
remember those frenzied spirits?
His true karmic enemy
has the power to control them all.
It's gone this far,
and you still want to help him?
Yes.
I stand by my words.
Please help him, Master.
If you don't,
I'm leaking your number.
I won't promise I can save him.
You'd better go keep him safe.
The night's far from over.
Master seems to care about Khem, though.
Didn't he say he wouldn't...
We'd better be ready, too.
(Chanting)
Be careful.
Don't worry.
He's on his way.
- He's here.
- That's him.
Here he is.
- Hey.
- Mister.
Is everyone here?
- Yeah, Mister.
- Yes.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- Alright.
- Go.
Everyone, are you ready?
- Yes.
- We are.
Let's do it.
They're here.
(Incanting)
Are you looking for me?
What has he done to you?
Can't you just let him go?
I shall never let him go.
This is Charn,
also a junior.
This is Jet,
my best friend.
We've gone through this bamboo grove
over and over.
My duty
is to take care
of the people in this village.
I'll do whatever it takes
to stop being an outsider in your eyes.
♫No matter how long time's passed,
you still have me♫
♫Through storms and stars,
together we shall be♫
♫Even if nightmares come,
we shall make them flee♫
♫With our hearts aligned,
we'll win gracefully♫
♫You still have me,
we're destined for eternity♫
♫Through storms and stars,
together we shall be♫
♫Even if nightmares come,
we shall make them flee♫
♫With our hearts aligned,
we'll win triumphantly♫