[theme music playing]
LOVE NEXT DOOR
[pleasant music playing]
[chuckles softly]
Why are you staring at me like that?
It just…
This feels just like a dream.
I can't believe it.
[taps forehead]
-Ouch.
-It's not a dream, is it?
You're right. It's real.
And we're together too.
It's strange.
[chuckles softly]
To be here like this together.
What's strange about it?
It's like a ticklish feeling.
I'm not sure exactly where,
but somewhere deep in my heart,
it feels like bubbles popping.
Me too.
Doesn't it tingle like there's electricity
moving through our bodies?
[Seok-ryu] Right. No, it's like this.
You know when you're about to get a shot
and they're looking for a vein,
so they tell you to clench
and unclench your fist?
It's that feeling.
It's love.
What?
That's love.
Come on. It's too early to say it's love.
It's taken 30 years,
but it's still early?
That is true.
But something about the word "love"
makes me cringe.
It's a bit embarrassing too.
[pleasant music continues playing]
I love you.
As my family, my friend, and my woman.
The kind of love
might have been different at times…
but there was never a time
when I didn't love you.
[door opens]
-[Mi-suk] We had a great time.
-Mom?
-Bye!
-Aunt Mi-suk?
[Geun-sik] I don't remember
how we got back.
We all went on a trip, but I don't have
a single picture to show for it.
It's because the camera doesn't lie.
That's how you look.
Take it up with your mother then. [laughs]
Gyeong-jong turned Hye-suk
into a supermodel.
He made her legs look so long.
But Hye-suk's…
It was the same when we ate crabs too.
Gyeong-jong picked the meat
out of each leg for her
and fed it to her.
And you?
You were busy eating for yourself.
That's because he's a doctor.
He's an expert at dissection.
-So he picked them clean.
-Did you forget?
You're a cook.
[crow cawing]
I wanted to go for a walk at night,
but you got drunk and passed out.
Why do you snore so much?
I don't snore on purpose.
[Seok-ryu] You're home so early.
[Seung-hyo] Hey, Aunt Mi-suk.
Did you have fun on the trip?
[dramatic music playing]
Jeez.
Aren't you two too old to be reading
comic books first thing in the morning?
[Geun-sik] Seung-hyo.
You like romance comics?
[dramatic music playing]
You're such a romantic.
-[laughing]
-[chuckles nervously]
Yes, a little bit.
Right. [chuckles]
-[Mi-suk] Hey, Seung-hyo.
-Yeah?
You missed a button on your shirt.
[dramatic music playing]
Seriously? Are you a kid?
You can't even button your shirt right.
-[Geun-sik] Come here.
-You're right.
-Why are you so clumsy?
-Gosh, how did this happen?
What a dumb mistake.
Mom! He asked if you had fun on your trip.
Ask your father.
What? Did you do something wrong?
-[Geun-sik] No, she wants to pick a fight.
-[Seok-ryu] Dad, just leave him.
-[Mi-suk] The soup's untouched. Seung-hyo!
-Yeah?
Go home and get your parents.
-We'll eat this.
-Okay.
Hey, go! Hurry.
-Yeah, do the rest.
-[Seung-hyo] Okay.
[Geun-sik] Princess Volume 20 is out!
We had no food at home,
so we were about to order out.
-Thanks for the meal.
-[Mi-suk] Sure.
We feel so bad.
You didn't even get a chance to rest yet.
-Gosh.
-[Mi-suk] It's fine with me.
But I don't know
about my hungover husband.
They say you shouldn't even
disturb dogs when they eat.
By the way, gomtang
is pretty good for hangovers.
[Hye-suk] Yeah, it's great.
How was the trip?
It was nice. It really lifted our spirits.
-Right, honey?
-Yeah.
You two should come with us next time.
Us two?
Goodness, we can't take just these two.
We need to make it
more lively and fruitful first.
What?
She means we should get the kids married
and all take a trip together.
Married?
-[Mi-suk] Yeah.
-What?
Hye-suk and I agreed
to find spouses for them.
[all chuckling]
[Geun-sik] That's so silly.
Did you sign a blood oath or something?
Honey, find someone suitable
at the hospital too.
-Right!
-Okay.
-[Hye-suk] Okay?
-I bet there aren't any.
I doubt there's anyone
who'd marry Seok-ryu.
Hey, Seung-hyo! You can't say that.
[Mi-suk] You ungrateful little brat.
-Why are you criticizing my daughter?
-[Geun-sik] Yeah.
I didn't think you were like that.
I'm upset.
-That's not what I meant.
-It's okay.
There's no woman who can put up
with his personality either.
[Geun-sik] Why would you say…
Seok-ryu, what's wrong
with Seung-hyo's personality?
[Gyeong-jong] Yeah, he's neat and polite.
He's nice since he takes after me.
I'm sorry. That's not what I meant.
This is how we usually get along.
We make fun of each other.
[Seung-hyo] Yes.
We're always teasing
and dissing each other like this.
I see. [chuckles softly]
So that's what it was?
Hey. That's right.
We'll end up feuding
if we fight over our kids. Let's eat.
[Gyeong-jong] Okay.
Thank you for the meal.
[Hye-suk] Gosh, I was so flustered.
[Seung-hyo breathing heavily]
[Seok-ryu] Wow.
-[sighs]
-I thought I'd suffocate to death.
[exclaims] I was so nervous
I could barely eat.
Well, we got through it,
so let's try harder from now on.
Hey, let's just be honest instead
and tell them we're dating.
No.
Things aren't good right now.
My engagement was called off.
And it hasn't been long
since Hyeon-jun came by.
It'll seem
like I don't take things seriously.
Ooh. [chuckles softly]
So I guess you have
pretty serious feelings for me?
Jeez, how can you joke right now?
Look, you don't have to worry about that.
I can explain everything really well.
No, it's not just that.
[exhales] It's going to get
really uncomfortable and annoying.
I mean, if my parents
find out we're dating,
then you can't come
in my room like this.
-What?
-[Seok-ryu] Think about it.
They'll ask what, when,
where, why, and how.
They'll watch our every move.
[amusing music playing]
They'll impose curfews again.
They'll be scanning
the neighborhood 24 hours a day.
If that happens,
we'll have to have a very wholesome,
innocent, and nice relationship
like little kids.
Let's keep it a secret.
Yeah, let's be strict about it.
We must never get caught.
That's what I'm saying.
[both chuckle]
[pop song playing]
Did you do well?
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey, we're in the middle of the street!
-Did you do well?
-Totally.
You're pretty from this side too.
[chuckles]
[faint laughter]
-Okay!
[chuckles]
[Seok-ryu exclaims]
You can do it!
[exclaiming]
[laughing]
[screams]
[chuckles]
-Let's check out the first floor.
-[Seung-hyo] Let's go!
-There's a claw machine too.
-[Seok-ryu] I love it! Let's try them all.
LOVE
[sighs]
What do I do with all of these?
Should I open group buying again?
No, I haven't promoted enough.
Short-form videos are the trend,
so I'll post one of me
taking it and working out.
[exhales]
[Mi-suk] Dong-jin, come eat some melon!
Jeez, Mom.
Melon's not important right now.
-I don't want any!
-Then don't, you punk!
I'll eat it all.
Is that punk going to drink
only protein forever?
-[phone vibrating]
-[laughing]
[indistinct conversation on TV]
That brat.
She didn't post any pictures
of the scenery. They're all of herself.
[In-suk] Gosh, Hye-suk!
Your pictures came out great.
Wow, look at that figure!
You're like a model. [chuckles softly]
[Jae-suk] Yeah,
change your profile picture.
It's your best photo ever.
[Hye-suk] You think so?
I didn't think they did me any justice.
They look better than you in person.
[chuckling]
[Mi-suk] Jeez.
We both went on the trip,
but I don't have a single picture to post.
Are you still going on
about pictures? Good grief.
I'd have to take 100 pictures
to even get one that's decent.
You didn't care if my eyes were open
or if my hair was covering my face.
You didn't even look.
I'm sorry, Mi-suk.
I was wrong, so let's stop.
I think my ears are bleeding.
-Look at this. Look at that composition.
-[sighs]
He took it from below,
so she looks like a model.
I'm going crazy.
Hey, you punk!
Come and eat some damn melon!
-Just like this.
-[Geun-sik] What are you doing?
Are you in a staring contest
with broccoli?
[Seok-ryu] Yeah.
Beans, spinach, and eggplants.
I'm in a war of nerves
with food I hate the most.
If you hate them so much,
why did you buy them?
My mom says they're good for your health
and keeps trying to make me eat these.
So you're going to buy and get rid of
all the vegetables in the world?
I'm developing recipes to try
and make them taste good.
You know when athletes
come up with their own moves
and the moves are named after them?
Yeah, like Kim Yuna's Yuna Spin
and Yeo Hong-chul's Yeo 1 and Yeo 2.
Yeah, so I'm thinking of making
my own signature dish.
So what do you plan on making?
Broccoli and chicken risotto!
Yikes. Just hearing it
sounds like the worst combination.
A little bit, right?
Hey, this kitchen is a sacred area.
What are you doing?
Should I stop?
No, keep going.
[Myeong-u] Why is the light on here?
Is someone in there?
[quirky music playing]
Goodness gracious,
you need to turn these off right away.
Goodness, the lights are on here too.
Young people these days
don't know how to conserve…
What's this?
What is all this?
Mushrooms, spinach, and celery.
Hey, these are going to spoil!
You should put these in the fridge!
Good grief.
Jeez. For crying out loud.
You said no one's here at night.
He probably came to get something.
He's always forgetful.
How much longer do we have to wait?
My exam's in two days.
I have to prepare for it.
You should've prepared in advance then.
What? You don't think you'll pass?
The written test was easy.
I'm worried about the practical exam.
-[chuckles softly]
-They said less than 30 percent pass.
Are you giving excuses
in case you fail?
Hey, there are three things
that don't exist in my life.
Flunking, failing, and rejection.
All right, then.
Stop standing there like that
and come here.
[Seok-ryu] Hiding and concealing.
My life's a roller coaster these days.
I like it. It's exciting.
You're the one who wanted
to tell the world that we're dating.
It seems you're enjoying this now.
The fun has yet to begin.
There's no end to the fun.
[music ends]
[Jae-suk] Hurry, you'll be late for work.
[gasps] Yeon-du!
-Mrs. Do!
-Yeon-du!
Yeon-du, did you miss me?
[Yeon-du] I did.
[Jae-suk] Me too.
Goodness, you look so pretty today.
Dan-ho, can't you just
let us take care of Yeon-du?
I'll watch over her well.
Thank you for the words,
but that's okay.
Her new babysitter's coming next week.
But I could help you until then.
[Dan-ho] It's really okay.
If I kept imposing like that,
I'd feel very uncomfortable about it.
Yeon-du.
You're not imposing at all though.
-[Dan-ho] We'll get going.
-[Jae-suk] All right.
-Bye, Yeon-du!
-Bye.
[Yeon-du] Have a nice day, Mrs. Do.
-[Jae-suk] Bye, Yeon-du.
-Bye, Mo-eum.
This won't do.
I must have a granddaughter.
Okay, ask your older daughter for a third.
Hey, go on a blind date.
Okay, ask your older daughter to…
-I don't think she should do that.
-It's a great opportunity.
I thought of asking Seok-ryu,
but it'd be a waste to miss out,
so you should go.
Seok-ryu will never go.
Of course, neither will I.
Why not? Why won't you go?
Is there someone you already like?
Wait.
Wait! You do have someone!
Who is it? Someone from work?
-Mother.
-What?
-I'll get going.
-Okay, but…
-Hey! Who is it?
-[exclaims]
Hey, tell me! Mo-eum!
[mellow music playing]
What's wrong, Yeon-du?
You suddenly don't want to go
to kindergarten?
No, I don't.
If I go, I'll have to wait until evening
for you to come and pick me up.
-How about I pick you up earlier instead?
-I don't want that either.
Then, you won't be able
to work because of me.
It breaks my heart
to keep you there all day too.
But couldn't you understand
for just a little while?
Can't I stay at Mo-eum's house?
I like it there.
Mrs. Do makes me yummy food.
And Mo-eum always plays with me.
I'll play with you and make it more fun.
How about we go bike riding
at the Han River this weekend?
-Really?
-Yeah.
So let's go to kindergarten, okay?
[Seok-ryu sighs]
[exhilarating music playing]
Students, please don't touch
the ingredients.
Just examine them with your eyes.
See if anything's missing
or if you need more of it.
Please check now.
We won't fulfill any requests
once the exam has started.
Any questions?
Then, we'll start the exam.
NATIONAL TECHNICAL QUALIFICATION
PRACTICAL EXAM
[microwave dings]
[inhales]
[mellow music playing]
[exhales]
Mmm.
-Are you eating that again?
-Yeah.
[Myeong-u sighs deeply]
-Are you seeing someone? Right?
-[Seung-hyo] Yeah. What?
I mean, you used to
eat lunch slowly like a French noble.
Now, you've only eaten this for days.
[coughing]
And you leave work exactly at 6:00 pm.
It's suspicious. It's not like you at all.
That's because I want to have
more of a life at night now.
Also, everything is
already mixed together here,
so I can save time.
And most importantly, it's good.
Mmm.
You know me. Once I'm hooked
on something, I stick with it.
Yeah, that is true.
Should I try that too?
-Yeah, go ahead. Try some.
-[Myeong-u exhales]
Which one should I pick?
The bulgogi one is good
if you can't eat spicy food.
[Myeong-u] Bulgogi? Okay.
Goodness, there's a spoon too.
[horns honks]
[car door opens]
[Seok-ryu] Choisseung!
What are you doing here?
What do you think?
I'm here to congratulate my girlfriend.
[chuckles softly]
-Here.
-[Seok-ryu gasps]
The results aren't even out yet.
Why are you congratulating me?
What's with the bouquet?
Unlike you, I believe the process is
more important than the result.
I'll kill you.
Even if you killed me,
that would be a happy ending too.
It feels like you're becoming
more and more naughty.
What? I'm updating
my firmware to boyfriend mode.
The newest version includes flowers.
You talk so smoothly.
I'll let it slide
since the flowers are pretty.
[pleasant music playing]
-[Seung-hyo] You're prettier.
-Don't push it.
I can't tell you apart from the flowers.
It's so confusing.
Stop or I'll factory reset you.
No, I don't want that. I'll stop.
[chuckles softly]
[Watch on www.kisskh.club or www.kisskh.asia to support Admin]
[Dong-jin] Oh. Hey!
It's been a while.
Yeah.
Did you go somewhere?
A business trip.
I have to go straight to work,
so excuse me.
I can't believe you have to go
to work on such a nice day.
This is why it's bad
to be tied down by a job.
Look at me. I'm so free and happy.
It must be nice to be
unaffiliated and unemployed.
I'm not unemployed anymore.
I've started on new work too.
This is a product I'm selling.
-I'll give one to you.
-No, thanks.
Don't refuse. Just take it.
-[Na-yun] I said it was fine.
-[Dong-jin] I'll get that.
By the way, do you work here?
This is my friend's company.
Who? Mr. Yoon?
No, his name's Choi Seung-hyo.
-Seung-hyo!
-[Seung-hyo] Hi, Dong-jin.
-Gosh, did I get something on me?
-[Seung-hyo] Why are you so sloppy?
-You're here too?
-[Seok-ryu] What?
I knew you couldn't be nice forever.
You're dead when I get home.
But what's with the flowers?
-They're mine.
-They're his.
A client gave them to me.
-But she stole them.
-I held them for him.
You're stealing flowers from people now?
Don't worry. I'll tell my mom on her.
No, you don't have to do that.
Mom? Sister?
Wait. Are you two siblings?
Yes, I'm embarrassed to say
he's my younger brother.
[amusing music playing]
But how do you two know each other?
Oh. She goes to my old gym.
[Seung-hyo] I see.
[Dong-jin] Who knew
we'd be connected like this?
Is the world that small,
or is this fate?
Seung-hyo, since I'm here,
can you show me around your office?
What? Sure. Do you want to see?
[chuckles nervously]
Wow, it's so nice. It's so cool.
It looks so expensive.
Why did you bring him here?
What else could I do?
I couldn't tell him to leave.
Why not? Hey!
Go! If you're done looking, get out!
Is this your company?
He didn't say anything.
-Why are you telling me to go?
-He wants you to leave too.
[Na-yun] Excuse me?
You said you were selling this, right?
Did you know this caused a stir
on social media recently?
[Dong-jin exclaims]
This is a very popular item
that's really hard to get your hands on.
But you got one
thanks to your connections.
Are you kidding? He didn't give me any.
That's not what I meant.
It caused quite a stir
because it was moldy protein.
You didn't know?
What?
[quirky music playing]
That can't be possible.
[sniffing]
-[door opens]
-[Seok-ryu] Mom!
[Mi-suk] What's going on?
Why are you dragging him by the ear?
[Seok-ryu] Dad's here too. Mom, Dad.
This punk messed up again.
Mom, I told you not to lend him money.
But you did, didn't you?
Not only did he lose all of that money
but he could get sued too.
-Sued?
-You know those boxes in his room?
I wondered what they were.
He's been selling moldy protein
that hasn't been approved by the MFD.
What? Mold?
[Geun-sik sighs]
What are we going to do with this bum?
Hey, you punk!
I should've disowned you a long time ago.
But I've put up with you
because of your mother, you punk!
Is that true?
-I didn't know either.
-[Seok-ryu] Hey.
Not knowing doesn't fix anything.
Let's try to deal with this first.
-How many did you sell?
-[Geun-sik sighs wearily]
[Seok-ryu] Tell me! How many did you sell?
Ten.
For all that big talk,
it's a pretty modest number.
No, it's for the best.
Before this gets out of hand,
call the buyers and apologize.
Refund all of their money.
-Okay.
-[Geun-sik] Good grief.
-That little…
-[scoffs]
I'm the one who was scammed.
Even after being deceived
for over a decade, I thought to myself,
"Things will work out this time."
"He'll do well this time."
"He's in his thirties and jobless,
but I can't be too harsh."
"What if he goes astray?"
"Still, he's got a good heart
and he's my son, so I should trust him."
But I've reached my limits now.
If you have eyes, go out and take a look.
Go see how hard people work.
[slow music playing]
But what about you?
Did you think making money
off of others would be easy?
How could you be so careless
and sell a product without checking,
especially one
that's meant to be consumed?
You're hopeless.
The way you think
has already become completely corrupt.
No, it's not.
I really wanted to do well this time.
[Dong-jin] I know it too.
I know I'm a burden on you both.
I'm not smart,
I didn't study well like Seok-ryu,
and I'm weak-willed.
I know you never expected
anything from me.
I know that too.
[breath trembling] That's why
I hated being a nobody.
[voice shaking] I wanted to succeed!
I wanted to make a lot of money
to buy Mom a nice bag
and buy Dad a new car!
Me too!
[whimpering] I wanted to be special too.
[sniffles]
-Hey, Dong-jin.
-[Dong-jin sobbing]
-[door opens]
-Goodness.
[breathing heavily]
[Mo-eum] Hey, Dan-ho.
Let's at least still greet each other.
I did greet you.
Not something formal like that nod.
You know, "How was your day today?"
"How have you been?"
Nice greetings like those.
I'm not going to do that anymore.
Wow.
That's so cheap.
I have something for you though. Ta-da.
Here, take it.
[slow music playing]
[exclaims]
I kept going back to what you said
at the campgrounds.
No, we can't. Never.
Yeon-du can't become your daughter.
And what happened that day was a mistake.
It has to be.
Why?
Because it can't happen.
But…
doesn't it sound awkward?
What do you mean?
I told you I liked you,
and you said it was something
that can't happen.
You didn't say you didn't like me.
I don't like you.
-What?
-You said you liked me.
So there was no need to be harsh.
I was being indirect.
You're putting me in a tough spot.
Then, what was that?
All of those ointments you gave me.
Wasn't that big bag your way
of showing how you felt about me?
You read too much into it.
The ointment was just ointment.
I see. [chuckles awkwardly]
So that's what it was.
Still, take this
since I'm embarrassed.
Well, then. I'll get going.
I forgot.
We're going in the same direction.
Uh…
I'll go first.
Take your time.
[slow music continues playing]
There are so many things
I have to stop liking now.
This is bad.
-[knock on door]
-[Gyeong-jong] Come in.
[Hye-suk] Are you busy?
No, I was finishing up
a dissertation I'd been reading.
-Is it important?
-[chucks aside]
Not really. Reading it is just a habit.
-What is it? Did you need something?
-No.
Just seeing what you were up to.
Wow.
I didn't know you had so many books here.
The window is huge too.
Yeah.
[quirky music playing]
[Hye-suk] But don't you think
this bed is too small?
I bet it's uncomfortable.
Since I sleep alone,
so a full-size bed is enough.
I sleep alone on a queen-size bed.
So I was wondering.
How about coming back
into the master bedroom?
What?
-You don't want to?
-No, I want to!
[Hye-suk] Goodness!
Gyeong-jong!
Gyeong-jong, wait for me.
Yes, I'm sorry.
I'll refund your money right away. Okay.
-[line disconnects]
-[door opens]
-What do you want?
-[door closes]
Why are you entering my room
without knocking?
You can do the same.
You once hung a sign on your door
saying you'd kill me if I came in.
-Because I hated you.
-Now, you're just openly saying that?
I thought Mom loved you more.
No matter how hard I tried
to be number one in things,
you were always number one to her.
No, I wasn't.
You were her everything.
She adored and was proud of only you.
You were the reason why she lived.
[sighs softly]
It's all pointless.
Hey, Dong-jin.
What?
I've lived for 13 months longer than you,
so I'm speaking from experience.
Not everyone can be special.
Most people just live ordinary lives.
[mellow music playing]
And the same goes for me.
So don't be too obsessed
with becoming someone great.
Just find what's valuable
to you in your life.
That's more than enough.
Take it from someone
who's been sick before.
That's so cheap.
You used your illness while lecturing me.
[Seok-ryu exclaims]
While I'm at it, here's one more thing.
I'm telling you since it seems
like you don't know,
but you're not weak-willed.
[Dong-jin] What?
You'd fight me to the death
over drumsticks.
Whenever we went to buffets,
you ate all the food and left devastation,
like a swarm of locusts.
But you survived a year
on just protein shakes and chicken breast.
That's what will is.
It was nice to see you work as a trainer
since you seemed so dedicated.
[mellow music continues playing]
I wasn't a trainer.
I was working to be one.
[Seok-ryu] So why did you fail the exam?
You should've worked harder.
[Dong-jin] You just said I did work hard.
-[Seok-ryu] All you did was try.
-What are you doing?
Everyone tries.
You should've done better.
-It's Seok-ryu.
-[Dong-jin] I wanted to pass too.
-[Mi-suk] She's with Dong-jin.
-What about Dong-jin?
-[Dong-jin] You think I want to be dumb?
-What is it?
-Quiet.
-[Geun-sik] What?
-[exhales]
-[window opens]
[knock on window]
What's wrong? Did you fail?
Hey, that's okay.
You can always take it again.
You can't just pass things
like that on the first try.
You won't seem human.
You're already like a fairy as it is.
From now on, [inhales]
just call me Tinker Bell.
-What?
-[chuckling]
Well,
this fairy passed the exam
on her first try!
I got my Korean Food
Craftsman certificate! [exclaims]
Holy cow!
Hey! That's insane!
Wait right there! I'm coming over.
Wow!
-Hey, that's not a door! You'll get hurt!
-Right.
This won't work. I'll go around.
[Seok-ryu] I'll see you later.
[pleasant music playing]
[Seok-ryu laughing]
Go!
What's with him?
[clears throat]
Did anyone follow you?
[chuckling] Am I
in Hyereung-dong or Hawaii?
Don't you think
that makes you look more suspicious?
We should be more careful
around the neighborhood.
You and I have
been hanging out together for decades.
We could be hugging each other,
and no one would find it strange.
That's true.
Hey! What if someone sees us?
[Seung-hyo] I told you.
No one will find it strange.
Congratulations.
You passed on your first try.
That's so like you.
I really am happy.
Much more than when I got into college
or when I got hired by Greip.
I'm happy that you're happy.
Now that I have my certificate,
I'm going to prepare for real and start.
I'll look for a job too.
You have to be careful in the kitchen
when you start working.
Water, fire, and knives.
[pleasant music continues playing]
Other men.
I'll think about the last one.
Men who cook have nice forearm muscles.
Unbelievable.
Architects have better forearms, you know.
[Seok-ryu] Wow, you're right!
What on earth?
Your veins are popping out.
Take a look. Look at these tendons.
Yeah, I'm looking.
Look at my adductors and abductors.
[exclaims]
Goodness. Great work today.
You too. Rest up. We'll see you tomorrow.
-Okay.
-[Jeong-u] What's with the suit, Ms. Jung?
Where are you going now?
I'm going somewhere. Bye.
Jeez, why are you so clueless?
What did I do?
Look at the color of her clothes.
She's in mourning.
[slow music playing]
THE LATE YEO JU-EUN
[Mo-eum] Hi, Ju-eun.
I'm here.
It's been a while, right?
Well, life's been so hectic.
[inhales]
No.
To be honest, that's an excuse.
I just…
kind of…
[inhales]
forgot about you.
THE LATE YEO JU-EUN
NOVEMBER 20, 1988 - AUGUST 2, 2021
You said there could still be kids inside.
And I still vividly remember
how you ran into that building.
Whenever I think about that,
I have a really tough time.
[sniffles]
[clears throat]
Right. We're the same age now.
I'll be older than you next year,
so I'm going to speak casually.
I'll get going.
I'll come back again.
[clears throat]
[slow music continues playing]
Yeon-du.
Say hi.
Hello,
Mom.
Dad.
[mellow music playing]
THE LATE KANG IN-HO, SEO JI-YEON
Mom.
Dad.
THE LATE KANG DONG-JU, LEE MI-JEONG
Ji-yeon.
THE LATE KANG IN-HO, SEO JI-YEON
And In-ho.
Have you all been well?
Yeon-du's grown a lot, hasn't she?
She's taller now and put more weight on.
She eats her carrots and paprika now too.
I know the alphabet too.
[chuckles softly] That's right.
She sings the alphabet song so well.
So don't worry about Yeon-du.
I'll always stay by her side.
I learned…
how to fold origami flowers.
I brought these for you, Mom and Dad.
Dad already…
I mean, Uncle Dan-ho already got one.
[mellow music continues playing]
Want to put it on
your mom and dad yourself?
We'll visit again.
Goodbye.
[exhales softly]
[music ends]
I didn't know I'd run into you here.
My first mentor was laid to rest here.
There was a fire at a school gym.
She went in to help.
She saved the day
and went to Heaven by herself.
She's so cheap.
I bet that was hard.
I bet it was harder for you.
I'm sorry I eavesdropped.
It happened so suddenly.
It was a family trip.
I had to cover a story last minute,
so I promised to join them after.
But…
[slow music playing]
Is this her?
[voice shaking] Yes.
She's my sister-in-law.
[whimpering]
[sniffles]
[sobbing]
[voice shaking] Sir.
[sobbing] There's a child!
[voice shaking] Where is she?
She's my niece.
She's still so young.
Sir… [sobbing]
They said my sister-in-law
had held onto Yeon-du until the end.
[slow music continues playing]
It's just Yeon-du and me now.
Is that why you decided…
to become her dad?
Yes.
To me, Yeon-du was a miracle.
But I guess she wasn't to others.
Our old neighborhood
was a place where our family
had lived for a long time.
But one day, a strange rumor
started to go around at her daycare.
She was the only one to survive
at the expense of her parents.
What? How could anyone say that?
[exhales]
Before Yeon-du could figure out
what that meant, I got us out of there.
We came to Hyereung-dong.
Would you like a hug?
I really want to comfort you right now.
But I don't know any moving words to say.
You must've been so lonely
this whole time.
-So I want to hug you.
-No.
I don't think we should.
Why not?
Because you still don't like me?
Because it still can't happen.
[chuckles softly]
[music ends]
RESUME
[inhales]
Okay.
HIRING STAFF FOR KOREAN RESTAURANT
APPLICATION SUBMITTED
FUSION RESTAURANT SILVER SPOON
HIRING KITCHEN STAFF
[pleasant music playing]
APPLICATION SUBMITTED
[sighs]
[door opens]
Knock, knock. Mr. Choi.
-A letter came for you.
-What letter?
"This letter originated in England."
"Send this to seven people
or you'll have bad luck."
-The invitation to Architecture's Night.
-Right. It's around this time every year.
[Myeong-u] Yeah.
Are we allowed to bring
a plus one this year too?
[exclaims] I knew it.
You have someone to bring.
I called it.
-Well, I didn't exactly say that.
-Bring her. You'd better bring her.
It's your chance to show off
how amazing you are.
Would that be necessary?
I'm always amazing.
Gosh, you're always so quick and smart.
But you'll be
even more amazing this time. Why?
The Jayeong-dong restaurant
you designed last year
was selected by architects
as Architecture of the Year.
Really?
You've won so many awards
you're not even happy.
This is no fun. I'm leaving.
I'm going home.
[Seung-hyo] Okay, bye.
By the way, Seung-hyo…
Yeah?
I must've sat for too long.
I was feeling stiff.
Yeah, sure. You know what? Never mind.
Just continue what you were doing.
[chuckles] You look so healthy.
-Bye.
-[Seung-hyo] Okay. Bye.
[upbeat music playing]
[door closes]
[chuckling]
Holy cow!
[exclaims]
Now, based on what we've practiced,
let's write down your favorite quotes.
[all] Okay!
[pleasant music playing]
Let me see…
HAPPY FAMILY, HAPPY LIFE
[sighs]
"Wander alone like a cow." Right.
[In-suk] That suits
you perfectly, Jae-suk.
Come to think of it, you resemble a cow.
-Moo.
-Wow.
Your eyes are as clear as a calf's.
-Look at me.
-[Hye-suk] Seriously?
-Hey, girls.
-I do have pretty eyes.
[Hye-suk] Hey, girls. Listen.
It's not a cow.
It's supposed to be a rhinoceros.
-[Jae-suk] Jeez.
-That expression is from Buddhist text.
Stop trying to show off again, you brat!
You wrote in French at the temple,
and you're doing it again?
[exclaiming loudly]
I don't even want to know!
Madame, be quiet!
I swear.
Hey. What did you write, In-suk?
[Jae-suk] "You were born to pass."
-I'm going to put it on Ki-hoon's wall.
-[Jae-suk exclaims]
Now, that's love.
[In-suk laughs]
-[In-suk] That was so fun.
-Wow.
Look at what's posted on the wall.
There are so many courses.
Yeah.
Let's take another one together next time.
Yeah, Spanish class sounds good.
Art history class seems good too.
And coding class sounds fun.
-Wow.
-Jeez, you take that.
Hey, how about yoga?
Hey, ukulele class. That sounds good.
-You take that.
-They all sound good.
Hey, it's so nice
now that Hye-suk's retired.
We can hang out like this all the time.
I did live a busy life before.
-I'm going to enjoy my time now.
-Really?
Then, in that case, let's go on a trip.
-What?
-A trip?
-[Jae-suk] Yeah.
-I already went to Seoraksan with her.
Not for just you two.
A trip with all four of us.
Let's go abroad.
-Abroad?
-[In-suk] Yeah.
Hey, let's go on a cruise!
I've wanted to go on one so badly!
Yeah, let's go on a cruise
around the Mediterranean.
-That would be pretty good.
-[exclaims]
How much does going on a cruise cost?
Around five to six million won?
Try to upgrade that idea a bit.
-It's that expensive?
-Let's wear dresses!
-Do they have parties?
-Yeah.
-[In-suk] Like the Titanic?
-[Jae-suk] Don't bring that up!
-Let's go.
-It sunk!
-Right.
-It did?
Did you watch the movie?
♪ Even if I work out
The raging winds of life ♪
Honey.
Why did you come here
instead of going home?
I just stopped by.
You had an arts and culture class
at the district office today. Was it fun?
Yeah.
It's lunchtime,
but there aren't any customers.
Well, you have days like this.
Hey, honey?
My friends want to go on a trip--
-Delivery!
-Hey!
How are you?
-[man] Good. Here's your order.
-[Geun-sik] Thank you.
[man] You've been ordering
less and less these days.
Gosh, it's been rough
because of the poor economy.
Has your revenue dropped
a lot too, Mr. Jo?
Well, I thought so too,
but a big chain snack shop opened
in front of Hyereung Middle School.
They've taken all the customers
in this neighborhood,
and they've been ordering a ton.
[chuckles]
I shouldn't have said that.
I'll get going.
Okay, bye.
Honey, what were you saying?
No, it was nothing.
Gosh, why would he mention that?
UNFORTUNATELY, WE WILL NOT MOVE FORWARD
WITH YOUR APPLICATION AT THIS TIME
WE WISH YOU WELL IN YOUR FUTURE ENDEAVORS
[phone vibrating]
[slow music playing]
[A-young] I got hired
at Kang's Restaurant!
[Su-jin] Holy cow!
That's a Michelin restaurant.
[A-young] I was lucky.
Let's celebrate soon. It's on me!
[phone vibrating]
[Seung-hyo] Where should we meet today?
Well…
Even if I go on dates,
I guess I can't escape my office.
I'm sorry.
But in return, I'll give you some of this
once I'm done making it.
[camera shutter clicking]
Why are you doing that?
I'm going to have it notarized
for when you make it big.
-Gosh, you're a money-grubber.
-[chuckles]
Before then, I'll taste this first.
[Seung-hyo] Hey. It's good.
I hate broccoli.
But I can't smell it. And it's so smooth.
I think it could be better.
It's missing something.
No, it's perfect now. It's really good.
No, aside from the oats and brown rice,
it needs something
to make the texture more fun.
Seok-ryu,
do you have time next week by any chance?
Next week? Why?
There's an annual event for architects.
-[Seok-ryu] Yeah.
-And there's a building I designed.
They said it won
for Architecture of the Year.
Really? Congratulations!
Thanks.
There's an awards ceremony that night.
My research advisors
and fellow architects will be there.
-Myeong-u's coming too.
-Nice.
Yeah, so…
I wanted to go with you.
I don't think I can go.
-What?
-[Seok-ryu] Well…
I don't think I belong there.
Why not?
Are you worried it'll be too awkward?
Or is it because you're still
not sure how we'll turn out?
-No, it's not that.
-[Seung-hyo] Then, what is it?
I was willing to give in
and understand not telling our families.
But do we have to hide it from others too?
I mean, it's such a small world.
Even Dong-jin and Na-yun know each other.
Who knows where we'd run into someone?
-So just for now…
-[clicks tongue]
[mellow music playing]
Are you mad?
No.
I'm sorry.
No, I'm sorry
for suddenly raising my voice.
I'm not mad.
-Really?
-Yeah.
I respect your decision, so…
don't take what I said too seriously.
Okay.
GYM
[sighs audibly]
[sighs]
[exclaims]
[Seul-gi] Come on in already.
What?
[amusing music playing]
Mr. Go, I was wrong.
I went on a fool's errand.
I wasted my time
with my head in the clouds.
[grunting]
You're not full of hot air anymore,
so it wasn't a waste of time.
Wipe it clean.
Yes, sir! I will.
[blows air]
[blows whistle]
Do it with sincerity!
Yes, sir!
[Su-jin] Wow, Kang's Restaurant.
It must be nice.
The food there is so good.
I can't believe it either.
But you're even more incredible, Su-jin.
You're opening your own place.
Well, that's why I wanted
to get the certification.
I signed a preliminary contract
with a real estate agent the other day!
Wow, congratulations!
You're all so amazing.
I didn't hear back
from any of the jobs I applied for.
Maybe it's because I'm too old.
[A-young] Maybe it's because your resume
is too impressive.
-What?
-That's right.
If an ex-Greip employee
applied to be a kitchen porter,
I wouldn't hire you either.
[gasps] It'd so be intimidating
to give you work.
You think so?
We're just saying
that's how incredible you are.
[both laughing]
AEA STUDY ABROAD CONSULTING
[mellow music playing]
THE BEST CULINARY SCHOOL IN AMERICA
AEA ENROLLMENT GUIDE FOR CIA
AEA STUDY ABROAD CONSULTING
Gosh, did you wait long?
-[Seung-hyo] No, it's fine. Hello.
-Hi.
Thank you for letting us feature
your building in the magazine.
It was nothing.
Our restaurant won an award,
so I'm grateful.
It'll help with business too.
I hope so.
I'll come here to eat next time.
Your lasagna was so good.
Oh. Would you like me to make some now?
No, not at all.
You're on break.
I couldn't ask you to do that.
I'm making it
because I want to taste it. [chuckles]
Then…
can I have some to take with me?
-[door closes]
-[Mi-suk] Goodness. What is all of this?
It's lasagna, ravioli, and gnocchi.
I got it from a very famous restaurant.
[chuckles softly] This is great.
I didn't want to cook.
By the way, is Seok-ryu home?
Yeah, she's upstairs.
I see.
This is great. He's so thoughtful.
[knock on door]
[Seung-hyo] Wow, I can't believe
I find even this cute.
I must be out of my mind. I'm sure of it.
[pleasant music playing]
[chuckles softly]
Gosh.
I've completely lost it.
Yeah, I'm insane.
Ooh.
She must've found what was missing.
CAULIFLOWER
[chuckles softly]
AEA STUDY ABROAD CONSULTING
What are you doing?
Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
I would've cleaned up
if I knew you were coming.
What's this?
It's nothing.
Is this the culinary school
Hyeon-jun mentioned?
Why do you have this?
It doesn't mean anything. I just have it.
You say that,
but you've researched a lot.
Let's talk outside. My mom will hear us.
[mellow music playing]
[exhales]
Are you going to leave me
to study abroad again?
I just looked into it just in case.
Right, but why would you look into it?
Do you know how hard it was
for me to let you go before?
We're finally together now,
but how could you… [sighs]
How could you think about that
without telling me?
The time I spend with you
passes so quickly that it kills me.
Even being next door
feels so far away for me.
How could you carelessly…
How could you think of being apart
without even batting an eye?
It does bother me.
It's hard for me to be away from you too.
It's not easy. It's tough for me too.
[sighs]
Don't you think
you're being contradictory?
You don't want to be away from me,
but you looked into schools abroad
behind my back.
I wanted to let you do
whatever you wanted to do.
[mellow music continues playing]
Because you're still hurting.
You have no choice but to be more careful.
So I tried to understand
when you wanted to keep us a secret.
I told myself I'd wait.
But I think I was mistaken.
This is all I am to you.
I was rejected
by every place I applied to.
Out of all those restaurants,
not a single one asked me
to come in for an interview.
I thought, "I'm still young
since I have a dream."
I wanted to start fresh.
I think I was too naïve.
I think…
being 34 is an awkward age
to start something new.
Also, I just got certified.
I was sick too.
Still, I wanted to keep cooking.
I thought maybe it would be better
if I got a degree.
I was looking for a breakthrough.
Maybe I was avoiding the problem.
Seok-ryu.
I didn't want to be embarrassed
in front of you.
I wanted to be confident
and graceful in front of you.
[slow music playing]
That's why I declined to go to your event.
Seok-ryu.
I'm not embarrassed by you at all.
There's no one more dedicated
and honest in life than you.
And for me,
I don't care what you do
or how you may appear.
I like you just as you are.
Thanks for saying that.
It makes me happy.
But I don't think that's enough for me.
I…
can't live off of love.
I'm sorry. I'll get going.
I don't want you to follow me.
I just need some space for a bit.
Just for a few days.
No, just one week.
Why?
I won't hide away in a cave,
but I'm embarrassed.
So I just want to disappear for a while.
Will you do that for me?
[car door opens]
[music ends]
[groans]
[Mo-eum exclaims]
[exclaims]
Ms. Jung, are you okay?
What?
It's the reporter.
The most determined
and firm reporter in the world.
The reporter, Kang Dan-ho.
-Wow!
-I think you're drunk.
You should go home.
I'll walk you.
[exclaims]
Oh?
[slurring] That's strange.
You have to transform into Mudflat Man
when your glasses come off.
Why are you still the same?
Where's your cape?
Where?
[in normal voice] You seem very drunk.
I'll buy a hangover drink.
[slow music playing]
[exclaims]
[slurring] Why are your words
and actions so inconsistent?
Why do you act the opposite
of what you wrote?
I mean,
you write your articles with righteousness
and courage like Mudflat Man.
But to me,
why do you act
like a timid and petty villain?
You're right.
I'm the villain in your life.
It'll be hard on you if you're with me.
I won't be able to protect or rescue you.
So things like Mudflat Man…
Just forget it
like a midsummer night's dream.
[laughs]
[laughing] That's funny!
-Hey, Dan-ho.
-What?
[slurring] To you, do I look like a pure
and innocent heroine
who wants to be rescued by Mudflat Man?
I'll take care of myself.
You, Mudflat Man,
should take care of your own feelings.
And this time,
it's not an accident. It's intentional.
Avoid it if you want. Damn it.
[groans]
[pleasant music playing]
[Mo-eum groaning]
Did you avoid it?
No, put me down!
[in normal voice] Stop moving.
You'll fall if you keep moving like that.
[Mo-eum groans]
The Earth is spinning.
I can feel the gravity.
[groans]
The ground is trembling.
[weakly] Like Baekdu Mountain…
The eruption.
Do you think there really is
a monster that lives in the crater?
[dog barks distantly]
Where shall we go?
-Put me down.
-[Dan-ho] Hello.
[Mo-eum] Hello.
By any chance…
Is that Mo-eum on your back?
[chuckles softly]
Goodness. Where on earth
did you go to get drunk like this?
You're such an embarrassment!
Who are you?
Who are… Mom?
It's my mom! [laughing]
She wanted to be
Spider-Man when she was a kid,
so she even put glue on her hands.
Now, she's all grown up
and putting shame on my face.
Pew, pew!
-For crying out loud.
-Pew.
[Mo-eum laughing]
-Why are you so drunk?
-That hurts.
Dan-ho, thank you.
I'm sorry.
I didn't raise my daughter right.
I wonder who on earth
would take this reckless girl.
You raised her very well.
[exclaims]
[Dan-ho] Also,
I'd like to take Mo-eum.
Excuse me? What do you mean?
I know she's too good for me.
I know you'll worry too.
So I tried all I could
to cut ties with her…
but I don't think I can anymore.
Dan-ho.
[music fades]
[chuckles softly]
[pleasant music playing]
[groans] I miss you, Seok-ryu.
BAE SEOK-RYU
[Seok-ryu] I just need
some space for a bit.
Just for a few days.
No, just one week.
I won't hide away in a cave,
but I'm embarrassed.
So I just want to disappear for a while.
Will you do that for me?
[sighs]
It's not good.
This is bad too.
Why is everything awful?
[pleasant music continues playing]
[exhales]
[exclaims softly]
[sighs]
[music ends]
What are you doing?
Along with the moldy protein,
I'm throwing out my pathetic past.
You're paying a steep price.
You better pay Mom back.
I'm going to pay her back
as soon as I get paid.
I'm working at the gym again.
I'm going to take
the certification exam too.
Really?
What's gotten into you?
I felt something after what you said.
I thought really hard
about why I was so delusional.
And…
it was all because I felt inferior.
I felt small and embarrassed,
so I didn't listen
and resisted for nothing.
I wanted to do better than you too.
[mellow music playing]
But we're family.
None of that's important.
[groans] It's so corny,
so I wasn't going to mention it.
I'm going to throw these out.
There we go.
For the Cheongyu-dong commercial facility,
the boundary restoration
and subdivision survey schedule is out.
You'll have to go
survey the site next week.
Seung-hyo?
-Mr. Choi?
-Yeah? What?
Uh, uh, sorry.
What did you just say?
[sighs deeply]
Are things not going well
in your love life?
What? Do you see cracks?
Is it about to fall apart?
Are you asking
because you actually know or not?
I don't know, but I want to,
so I'm asking.
I don't think I can go
to the Architecture's Night event.
What? Why not all of a sudden?
It's just…
Can't you accept the award in my place?
Look, I know I'm made for the stage,
but you need to accept that yourself.
Please help me out.
Also, I have to go right now.
Can we continue this meeting later?
Where are you going?
The site at Sehyeon-dong.
Isn't the frame construction
in the finishing stages?
Yeah.
-Take care.
-[Seung-hyo] Bye.
[door opens]
Darn, I've gained so much weight though.
I better detox to accept that award.
[supervisor] So the reporter wants
to work with us all day.
-And he wants to stay on-site?
-[Seung-hyo] Yes.
He writes his articles
after experiencing things himself.
How much work can I give him?
Just let him go through the motions?
No.
He'll work just like the other workers.
Just think of him
as a new, young employee.
-Teach him.
-[chuckles]
I better not go easy on him.
Bring him here.
[Seung-hyo] Okay.
Did the finishing materials arrive today?
[supervisor] The insulation materials did.
We're installing them now.
-I'll check since I'm here.
-Sure.
[phone vibrating]
SEOK-RYU
-[loud bang]
-[people clamoring]
EMERGENCY MEDICAL CENTER
[solemn music playing]
[exclaims]
Seung-hyo!
Seung-hyo, where are you?
[Seung-hyo] Over here.
[exhales]
Hey.
-Why are you crying?
-[Seok-ryu sniffles]
Didn't someone call you
to say I wasn't hurt much?
Jeez, I should've just called you.
I just had to sprain my right arm--
I love you.
[pleasant music playing]
What?
I said I love you.
Seok-ryu.
[exhales] I was such a fool.
[pop song playing]
I shouldn't have felt inferior
in the face of love.
Even if I can't live off of love,
it made me lose my appetite.
Everything I made tasted terrible,
so I couldn't practice at all.
I told you not to call me,
but I kept waiting for you to call.
Everything was a mess.
And that was just today too.
Do you know how scared I was?
I almost fainted from shock!
I almost passed out!
I'm sorry.
Why are you smiling?
If you scare me like this again,
I swear I'm going to kill you!
[breath trembling]
I told you I'd be happy
even if you killed me.
Don't say that.
[Seung-hyo] Stop crying.
Why are you crying?
Hey, I won't get hurt. I won't die.
No matter what happens to me,
I'll always be by your side.
-Got it?
-Yeah.
[Seung-hyo] So…
say it one more time.
What?
Tell me you love me.
I said it earlier.
Why are you asking for it again?
I love you, Seok-ryu.
I missed you so much,
but I wanted to listen to you,
so I didn't call
and waited as long as I could.
As soon as I got hurt, I thought,
"I'll be able to see Seok-ryu today."
[pleasant music playing]
It feels unfair that there isn't
an expression better than "I love you."
Because that's how much I love you.
LOVE
THE GREATEST HAPPINESS
IS TO LOVE OUT LOUD
ANDRÉ GIDE
[pop song playing]
LOVE NEXT DOOR
You won an award for
a cooking competition. I entered for you.
I'm sorry I entered it
without your permission.
So I won an award?
What about doing what you did before?
You made cooking videos in the US.
You can start again here.
-I'm ready.
-Then, we'll start.
You can never date him!
I don't care if the sky falls!
Mo-eum and I like each other.
[coughs]
[Dan-ho] I don't know what to do.
-I'm going to get married.
-With who?
[Seung-hyo] I have to propose.
Do you know any good ways to do it?
Today's the day.
Subtitle translation by: Sue Mounce