Do-hee.
-We--
-Let's finish decorating
the Christmas tree tonight.
I should also book the couple set
that we couldn't have last time.
I hope it's still available.
I don't think…
we can spend Christmas together.
Do-hee.
Save yourself…
from hell.
Gu-won.
By the time chilly winds
start blowing above ground in October,
heralding the coming of winter,
spring has already begun underground.
But that also means that by the time
beautiful cherry blossoms bloom in spring,
winter has already begun underground.
Even during our happy moments together,
perhaps our goodbye
had already begun.
EPISODE 15
THE END OF FATE
ZERO SUGAR IS THE TREND FOR 2023
Yes?
I've moved all your plans for this morning
to the afternoon.
Thank you.
I'll head to the office
after I talk to the prosecutor.
Will you be okay by yourself?
Shouldn't your attorney accompany you?
I'll be fine. See you in a bit.
Sir.
CHIEF PROSECUTOR'S OFFICE
Hello.
Ms. Do.
CHIEF PROSECUTOR CHOI WOO-SUN
Good to see you again.
I'll do my best
as my name suggests.
I'm sure you remember me.
I didn't know you were
the prosecutor in charge of my case.
I know.
What an interesting turn of events.
Please have a seat.
It's already been a week
since the suspect, Noh Suk-min,
jumped into the Han River.
Is his body still missing?
Yes.
Will the investigation be closed
when the body is found?
When the suspect dies,
the case is usually closed
since there's no one to prosecute anymore.
I heard
that you asked for
a transparent investigation.
There are still some questions
regarding Chairwoman Ju's death.
Since Noh Suk-min can no longer confess,
I want the investigation
to uncover the truth.
That's why you need…
a competent prosecutor like me.
My apologies.
I'm determined to shed light
on the atrocities committed by Noh Suk-min
and make sure such things
never happen again in this country.
I promise to get to the bottom of this,
no matter what.
-Okay.
-On that note,
-let's take a selfie for old times' sake.
-Pardon?
-Are you okay?
-Yes, I'm fine.
All right. Don't get a cold.
If it's not too much to ask,
allow me to post this on social media.
It is too much to ask.
Chairman Noh's body has yet to be found.
According to the police,
the search is proving to be difficult
as he fell into the Han River
from the rooftop of a building.
-Mommy.
Austin.
Justin.
-Mr. Han.
-Yes?
Ms. Choi.
I hear the body's still missing.
Hey!
It's already been a week.
I bet he's been eaten up by fish.
Chaebols must be wired differently
from ordinary people like us.
How could he do that to his family?
Chaebols sold their souls
to the devil, you see.
That's right.
It's the least one can do
to become a chaebol.
Ms. Do is a chaebol too.
She's different.
She's self-made.
-She wasn't born a chaebol.
-Exactly.
So she's different.
Anyway, seeing Mr. Jeong
used to be our biggest workplace benefit,
but I haven't seen him in a while.
Did he fight with Ms. Do?
-No way.
-You think so?
Anyway, it does feel
a bit empty in the office without him.
I agree.
He doesn't do much,
but he has such a strong presence.
The theater feels so empty,
although Director Jeong
was away all the time
and never spent much time here.
From now on,
you're the executive director
of Sunwol Foundation.
EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR PARK BOK-GYU
What's this about?
Are you in danger again?
I'm just…
going away for a bit.
I'll leave the foundation to you
until I get back.
How long will you be away?
Until Do-hee…
gets her happy ending without me.
Director Jeong.
When are you leaving?
As soon as I'm done here.
I hope you'll find peace
wherever you end up.
I asked myself this question.
"If I had known when to stop,
would I have been able
to be happy around you?"
And the answer…
was no.
I would've ended up like this anyway.
I'm not friendly enough
to be a human companion.
I would've eventually ended up biting you.
Do you know the story
"The Scorpion and the Frog"?
A scorpion wants to
get to the other side of the river,
so it asks a frog to carry it across.
But the frog is afraid
that the scorpion might sting it.
So the scorpion says,
"Why would I? I'd drown if I killed you."
The frog is convinced
and starts carrying the scorpion across.
But the scorpion gets scared
by the rough current
and ends up stinging the frog.
The frog asks, "Why did you do that?"
"Both of us are going to die now."
The scorpion answers
with a sad look in its eyes,
"I couldn't help it."
"It's just…
my nature."
It was a matter of time
before I ended up like this
because this is my nature.
This is who I am.
Yes.
You're right.
We would've…
ended up like this anyway.
Was his love poisonous as well?
If Do Do-hee put this on,
could she remember her past life
like I did?
That might change the course of events.
No.
Director Jeong always warned me
about my big mouth.
I should stay out of it.
Boss!
Hello there.
I was just looking for something.
I'm here to see the boss.
May I ask what this is about?
I have something important to give him.
Something important?
We opened a restaurant.
BLOODY DELICIOUS!
SUNNY SPOT RICE SOUP
"Sunny Spot Rice Soup"?
Yes.
We finally get to stand tall
before the boss.
-I see.
-So where is he now?
Well…
Boss…
Ms. Do.
It's time for lunch.
I'm not hungry. You can go ahead.
You're early.
There's still some time left.
I knew you'd be skipping lunch,
so I came early to eat with you.
I'm not hungry.
Well, I'm famished.
Eat with me, will you?
All right.
What are you so busy with
that you're even skipping lunch?
I was reviewing the rebuttal
made by the compensation committee.
I have to be thorough,
or the board will find fault with it.
It's a piece of cake
to come up with false accusations,
but proving the truth is an uphill battle.
Oh, I almost forgot.
I heard your company
is going to sign an MOU.
We're signing this week.
You're finally expanding
into the American market.
I bet Su-ahn's
going to be green with envy.
About Mr. Jeong,
is he really gone?
It's just that our contract expired.
We had agreed to be together
just until I caught the culprit,
and he got his tattoo back.
Everything's back to normal, that's all.
Hopefully, this will boost your energy.
It's duck.
I think Ms. Do needs
more energy than I do.
I guess it'll take time.
Romance may be fleeting,
but the heartache lingers.
Please take good care of her.
I will.
And I'll
take good care of you.
We should all take the stairs after lunch.
Every step you climb is supposed to
add four seconds to your life.
What?
Does that mean every stair you descend
takes away four seconds?
What?
Does it?
Whatever. Let's keep going.
What are you doing?
Something smells good.
The exercise is already paying off.
It's making you hungry.
-I'm hungry.
-See?
I'm hungry too.
Ms. Shin.
Are you eating out here alone in secret?
That's a lot of food.
Oh, my.
Thanks to the thorough rebuttal
that you prepared,
the committee is most likely to remain.
And I have you two to thank for that.
I didn't do much.
It was all thanks to Ms. Do.
-Thank you so much.
-Don't mention it.
You know what the committee
means to Mirae Group.
Both my father and Chairwoman Ju
would have wanted it to remain.
Madam Ju probably didn't foresee
that giving up on the investment
and acknowledging the industrial accident
would lead to an even bigger investment.
Probably not.
People back then
had little understanding of concepts
like business reputation
and crisis management.
Suk-min seems to have incorrectly assumed
that Aunt Cheon-suk
had orchestrated the whole thing.
Was I really her way out,
like Noh Suk-min said?
She may have taken me in
due to guilt and remorse,
just like why she established
the Industrial Accident
Compensation Committee.
Do-hee.
There's something
Aunt Cheon-suk said to me
when the sugar juice scandal
broke out against your company.
Here's the analysis of Mirae F&amp;B's
financial statements, as you requested.
I waited for Do-hee to leave
to give it to you.
I wonder where she gets
her stubbornness from.
I dislike it very much.
You love her way too much.
I never planned on loving her.
It was more of an unexpected accident.
The more I love her,
the more I suffer.
I didn't understand
what she meant back then.
But now I do.
The more she loved me,
the more she suffered.
Still, she continued to love me.
GRAND OPENING
SUNNY SPOT RICE SOUP
Welcome, boss… I mean, sir!
-Welcome, boss… I mean, sir!
I'll come back next time. Bye.
Wait, sir!
Please don't go.
Don't worry.
The boss, I mean…
Customers will come.
It's been a week since
Chairman Noh Suk-min jumped to his death,
and his body is still missing.
Despite the ongoing search
and investigation,
the police and the fire department
have yet to find any clues.
Could it be…
Meanwhile, the police are continuing
to investigate Chairman Noh
for possible additional charges.
It's okay.
I was alone from the beginning.
Everything's just back
the way it used to be.
It's warm.
Gu-won?
Congratulations.
This looks delicious.
Dig in.
This restaurant
is supposed to be really good.
Then be quiet and eat as much as you can.
-I should.
-Dig in.
Thank you.
It's really good.
-Let me pour you some.
-Please.
-Let's have a toast, Ms. Do.
-Sure.
Here's to our happiness,
optimism, positivity, and enthusiasm.
To HOPE!
-To HOPE!
HOPE…
Now that we're expanding into the US,
can we go on business trips to New York?
I'm going to study English really hard.
I've already signed up
for morning phone call English lessons.
Why didn't you tell me?
-To HOPE.
Let's go for another round!
The sun isn't up yet.
Let's just go home, Ms. Choi.
Another round at her place?
-What?
-Sounds good!
-Did you call for a designated driver?
-I did.
Will you be okay by yourself?
Of course. Why wouldn't I be okay?
I'll be absolutely fine.
I'm off.
See you. Thank you for today!
Go for another round!
-Get home safely, ma'am!
-Bye!
Please get her home safe.
Hey, get your act together.
Do you want me to have
the maintenance office replace you?
I'm bleeding.
Do you think this can hurt me?
No way.
I'm fine.
Careful.
That's what I'm talking about.
It's so nice to see you
beaming so brightly.
Get your act together.
I'll leave the rest to you,
my alter ego.
Please take care of me tonight as well.
My alter ego did a great job again.
Could my alter ego be better than me?
I'm bleeding.
I could've sworn I hurt myself last night.
Ms. Shin.
Yes?
I feel like Gu-won
is still hovering around me.
Many people feel that way after a breakup.
You're probably right.
I guess it hasn't sunk in yet.
Maybe I should become a nun.
You can't.
It's not you I'm concerned about,
but the convent.
Come in.
You should go home.
Are you going to work late again?
Yes. Thank you for today.
Ms. Do.
I also took refuge in work
right after my divorce.
I buried myself with work for days on end
as if I'd been possessed.
Back then, I believed I had to be okay.
And I thought I could become okay
by pretending.
But it turned out
that time couldn't heal everything
if I kept running away.
For time to heal my wounds,
I needed to stay true to my emotions
and ride out the pain and grief.
I don't think
people have to be okay all the time.
Nor can they be.
SEOK-HOON
Hi, Seok-hoon.
Are you skipping dinner
and working late again?
No, I'm not.
I already had dinner
and am now lying in bed.
I see.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
You're silly.
All right.
Get some rest.
Okay.
Ms. Shin!
Don't worry. Everyone's left.
I've been watching the whole time.
How long have you been waiting?
It's cold.
I'm not cold at all.
Why do you have that look on your face?
What look?
You look like you're so happy
that you're sad.
Let's go.
This is our song now.
"Safety precautions."
So it really is a manual.
I was just covering our faces
so he wouldn't recognize us.
I'll help you. We still have time.
This one symbolizes eternal happiness.
This one means
happiness that is meant to be.
And this one…
I love you, Jeong Gu-won.
I love you too.
Never say
you're going somewhere
far away alone again.
I'll grant your wish.
I'll never leave you
no matter what happens.
Gu-won.
Yes?
I just
wanted to know if you were there.
Keep calling my name.
I'll answer every time.
Gu-won.
What brings you here at this hour?
I missed Gu-won so much,
and this was the only place
I could think of.
If only I could catch a glimpse of him.
If only I could run into him,
even just for a moment.
But I don't know where to go.
I know nothing about him.
Even when he left,
I didn't get to say anything to him.
I didn't get to say thank you
or that I was sorry.
I'm the one who let him go.
The more I loved him, the more I suffered.
That's why
I let him go.
I think you need this.
It'll help whenever you miss him too much.
Young Master.
You must be
the famous Wolsim.
What did she do to get on the wrong side
of someone so powerful?
No idea.
She must be a real piece of work.
You tramp!
So what if you used to be
a government courtesan?
How dare you try to lecture me
when you should be obeying me?
That dirty little tramp
is looking down on me.
You're a lowly courtesan.
Do you even know who I am?
-Please calm down.
-Don't be like that.
-Calm down.
-Let go!
Come on.
Calm down.
She must think
she still works for officials,
acting all stuck-up like that.
She might hear you.
She's been here for days,
but she hasn't said a word to us.
A government courtesan
obviously doesn't speak our language.
To think
such a famous government courtesan
ended up penniless in this small village.
How does she bear it?
I'd kill myself if I were her.
I'm planning on doing just that.
But it'd be lonely to die alone.
Will you die with me?
Regardless of our rank,
we're all courtesans, after all.
No one in this room
gets to breathe freely.
In my next life,
I hope I will not be destroyed
by disdain and mockery.
I hope I can be myself.
Young Master Yi-sun!
Wait!
I heard a friend of yours died in Hanyang.
There's no courtesan here
without a story to tell.
Get ready and come out.
Have a drink, my lord.
All right, let's drink.
Let's talk in private
in the room over there.
Please have a drink, my lord.
Wolsim at your service.
Have a drink.
This is unacceptable!
She is said to have been haughty
in Hanyang as well.
What an insolent woman.
-Have a drink and let it go, my lord.
-Pour me one.
Life is pathetic,
and humans are contemptible.
What is the point of enduring another day?
My apologies.
I came over the other day
because I wanted to see you.
I apologize if I was being rude.
How exactly were you being rude?
I can't quite pinpoint it, but…
Please don't apologize
if you don't know why.
Wait…
I can't even kill myself when I want to.
Why does that silly man
keep getting in my way?
What are you doing?
My lady!
What a coincidence!
Is it?
COMMENTARIES ON GREAT LEARNING
Wolsim!
-Young Master.
-Wolsim.
Something to remember me by
while I'm away.
I'll never take it off
until you come back.
The last thing I see before I die
will be your face.
They don't treat us as humans.
It's not like they earned their nobility.
It was simply given at birth.
Just let it go.
Why should we remain silent
when we're treated like vermin?
How different can we be from them?
The world will change.
Once it does,
no one will face disdain or mockery
because of their class.
You seem to be in a good mood today.
I had a good dream last night.
I think I'll hear the good news
I've been waiting for.
I have no regrets.
I was planning on ending my life anyway.
Even so,
if only I could…
I love you, Wolsim.
If only I could see Young Master Yi-sun
for one last time.
Wolsim!
Young Master…
May he forget me…
so that his memories of me
will not bring him pain and sorrow.
I was…
Wolsim.
Yi-sun saved me
when I was going to kill myself.
Could he be there?
CONTRACT EXPIRATION
How…
I'm glad you recognize me.
I would've felt hurt if you didn't.
What do you think about my new face?
Do you like it?
You have nowhere to flee to.
You're wrong.
I can still flee to hell.
No!
I erased my face with my own two hands
so the damn devil
wouldn't be able to find me.
What do you want?
What do I want?
I want to destroy the two of you for good.
I've lost everything because of you two.
Money, reputation, family,
and even my face.
Killing you alone won't be enough now.
Get the damn devil here.
He shows up when you're in danger, right?
He won't.
He's left me.
Do you expect me to believe that?
Come out, Jeong Gu-won!
Come out if you want to save Do Do-hee!
You won't come out?
Get him here right now.
Scream, beg him to save you,
or do whatever to get him here!
You don't want to?
Then I have no choice
but to slit your throat first.
Gu-won.
Yes, that's what I'm talking about.
I knew you'd show up.
I'll kill you first.
No, Gu-won!
You'll burn away if you kill him!
Don't!
Stop it, Gu-won!
Gu-won!
No!
Yes.
Get my blood on your hands.
Gu-won!
Stop!
Stop it, Gu-won!
That's enough.
I'm okay now.
I'm okay now, so please stop.
Please.
Gu-won.
Everything's okay now.
I missed you, Do-hee.
I missed you too.
I missed you so much.
Do-hee.
Are you okay?
No!
Do-hee.
Do-hee!
No!
Please don't die, Do-hee.
"I can do all things…
through him…
who gives me strength."
Gu-won.
Do-hee.
Everything's okay now.
Gu-won.
Did you…
save me?
I saved myself.
No.
Why?
Gu-won.
Don't go.
Please don't leave me.
Please don't go, Gu-won.
Gu-won.
Gu-won!
Please don't go!
So that's the choice you made.
I can't feel him anywhere.
She had barely been holding on,
but she's fallen apart in the end.
What?
Will that brat Do-hee
really become the chairwoman?
The chairperson is coming.
You sure have a heart of stone.
Everyone around you died off,
but you don't bat an eye.
Merry Christmas, Gu-won.
Make a deal with me.
My wish…
Subtitle translation by: Min-jin Kim