Well, I’m in a relationship now.
I figured it out now.
It’s Gam.
Don’t break up with her.
I believe that we can both work as a group
and like someone at the same time
because both are part of our lives.
Since we have time, we
should have watched the movie.
Can we watch it next week?
Let’s not keep a five-meter distance
because even five centimeters
feels too far apart.
LOVE YOU TO DEBT LIFE,
ROMANTIC / 135 MINUTES
THAME AND DYLAN SONG DISCUSSION 6 P.M.
- 10 P.M.
THAME AND PEPPER DISCUSSION 6 P.M. THAME RECORDS THE DEMO 7 P.M.
- 8.30 P.M.
DRAFT THE MV REF 9.00 P.M. - 11.00 P.M.
What’s wrong?
Per,
help me.
So, you haven't watched
the movie with him yet?
Uh-huh.
Lucky enough, you’ve met
someone who understands you.
All right. I’ll help.
How about we move this to that day?
We must work hard all day one day.
Are you okay with that? See?
You can save this date and
go to the movies with him.
All right. I’ll call and ask him now.
Thame!
Let’s finalize the new single already.
So, will a breakdance be included?
You must decide as soon as possible.
The work scale is different, you know.
- I must quickly plan the work. - Thame.
I can’t decide until I get
to listen to both versions.
Record a guide demo for me, okay?
You can use the old lyrics.
Hey, it looks like we’ve
got a free day, right?
I’ll book that day then.
THAME - DYLAND RECORD THE SONG
So we can wrap it up quickly.
I’ll put mine here.
FINALIZE THE DANCE WITH THAME
THAME
Hello?
Po,
I’m sorry.
I still can’t make time for our movie day.
But if there’s a day I
finish my work quickly,
I’ll call you right away.
It might be a bit abrupt.
I really can’t promise when.
It’s all right. I understand.
I’ve been really busy these days.
But Per told me that
when he’s busy,
he will send Gam photos to
let her know what he’s doing.
Are you okay with that?
Yeah.
Okay.
But if you’re not familiar with doing that,
don’t worry at all.
I can handle it just fine.
And you’re not even going to ask me
if I can handle it just fine too?
Anyway,
I’ll make time to watch the movie with you.
I promise.
Yeah.
I’ll wait.
Sure.
Let’s stock up on a bunch of stuff, okay?
For late-night snacks and all that.
It looks like we have
to work all day and night.
Yeah. That sounds like a good idea.
I think we should stock up
on lots of ready-to-eat food
because someone who loves ordering food
is never around when
it’s time to work together.
Eh?
That’s because you guys split up and work.
I’m on my own.
How can I be with you all everywhere, huh?
So, we’re going to be busy
both day and night, right?
Of course.
Otherwise, we won’t be left
with any time to work on the MV.
Hey, but…
I think we can start working on our MV now.
But we need someone to help you, Thame.
I’m not available.
I’m not talking about you.
I’m talking about Po.
I think he can help us.
That makes sense.
- He’s a director. - Yeah.
I agree with that,
so our secret about making
music won’t get leaked.
Well done, bro.
How about his own work?
It seems he’s busy too.
Come to think of it, you’ve
already got a lot of work too, buddy.
Let’s put it this way then.
I’ll take care of the MV.
You’re acting strange, Jun.
Eh?
I’m just trying to help out.
Why are you so suspicious?
So, it’s settled now.
I’ll get going.
Hey, hold on. What about the welfare work?
Eh?
You all can help each
other with that, okay?
Bye-bye.
This way, it plays right into his hands
getting someone else
to do the work for him.
I bet he’ll just lie down and relax.
True.
I think I started to
feel sorry for Po a bit.
Per, why did you mention that?
Look.
I’m sure Jun is going
to give Po more trouble.
You… really can’t figure it out?
I said that
not because I wanted him
to work on it or anything,
I’m just trying to come up with an excuse,
so that he can come and stay close to you.
You can just work on the MV
and let him sit there and do nothing.
Shit.
That’s your plan?
Of course.
Now look at Jun,
taking the chance to slip away already.
Per,
this is your favorite, isn’t it?
Do you want it?
You did great, buddy.
But you’re totally not
keeping up with Jun, man!
THAMETEEMA: I WENT TO THE SUPERMARKET
Are you smiling at me?
Hey.
Who would smile at someone like you?
I smiled because…
You're missing Thame, aren’t you?
Can’t I?
It looks like you’ve gone too far, huh?
Anyway, if you miss him that much,
are you interested in working close to him?
What do you mean?
I’m now in charge of the MV thing.
Do you want to help me,
so you’ll be hanging around that area?
Are you serious, Jun?
But I have a condition.
You must really help
me ideate and work on it.
Well,
but I’m not that good at it.
Also, this is important work, isn’t it?
So? Does that mean you don’t
want to stay close to Thame?
I want to,
but do you think it’s a good idea
to let me do such important work?
So, you don’t want to be close to Thame?
That’s not what I mean!
But…
- I mean… - Ugh. You’re annoying me.
Don’t take too long
to make a decision, okay?
The chance is right in front of
you, so, will you take it or not?
Why do you have to use Thame as bait?
And is it working, huh?
Fine.
I’ll help.
Deal.
It’s settled, then.
I’ll send you references.
Work hard, okay?
If you don’t do it well
and it’s not impressive,
Thame will certainly be mad at you.
You silly!
Don’t you think I have my
own work to handle too, huh?
What work?
You don’t usually work.
I’ve never seen you work.
This is the first draft of the documentary.
Add the subtitles for me.
The deadline is the day after tomorrow.
Shit.
Why did he assign me the work at this hour?
THAME
Hello?
Are you busy now?
We can talk.
Jun already told you to
help with the MV, right?
Yeah.
Don’t worry.
I’ll give it my all.
This won’t make things
harder for you, right?
It won’t.
I won’t disappoint you.
I’m now preparing some references
to discuss with you tomorrow too.
When are you coming?
After work.
I think it’s around 6 p.m.
Okay.
I’ll wait to discuss it with you.
Yeah.
Today, I sent you five photos,
but you only sent me four.
Huh?
That’s it for now.
I’ll hang up.
Then roll.
- And then… - That works. Hey, yo!
- Yo! - Po!
Whoa.
It took you ages. Come now.
Let's see what work
you've gotten done today.
That’s strange. That’s super strange.
What?
What are these references?
Do you really understand MARS?
A cutting-edge concept is good,
but is this MARS’ identity?
Also, you said you'd finish work
by 6 p.m., but why are you so late?
The traffic was heavy, okay?
Do you know the phrase "buffer time"?
I can't deal with this.
Earlier this afternoon,
I still saw Jun sitting there
looking for lots of references.
Now, look at him, checking on
the work in such a serious mode.
It seems like he’s trying to mess with you.
He never stops his bad behaviors.
Back when I started
to get close with Thame,
he used to do the same thing.
Eh? Aren’t you listening to the music?
I’m just wearing them.
When it's something I don't care
about, I pretend I didn't hear it.
Wow,
the secret of the mysterious
land of the sky dragon
has been revealed, everyone!
So, does that mean you've heard
everything over all these years?
You should brief them with the song.
The song and the MV have
to be done together anyway.
Go already.
This is so outdated.
Look at what you’ve done.
I came to brief about the song.
Yeah.
Go ahead.
You don’t need to do that.
I briefed him yesterday.
It’s my work, so I can handle it myself.
You’re busy, aren’t you?
Go do your work.
Go.
- Go. - Jun!
But I want to brief you
on it by myself anyway.
It’s my work.
Are you going to brief
us? Brief me on it then.
Will you?
You and me. Let’s go.
Let’s do it now.
What’s your brief?
Come here.
You're such a liar!
You said you’d have me do the
work so I could stay with Thame,
but when the opportunity came,
instead of letting me stay with him,
you pulled him away to be alone with you.
You're clearly deceiving me.
Deceiving? Nonsense.
I asked you to help with the MV concept.
But look at you, always asking for Thame.
Can you become a director, huh?
Also, if I had you listen to his
brief, the work wouldn't get done.
Do you even know what
he was going to brief?
What?
All right. So, what do
you want to brief me on?
Yeah?
This song has a medium
tempo, with a BPM of around 94.
The mood leans toward pop, but
it still retains a hip-hop vibe.
For the rap sections, we’ll
probably incorporate rhymes like flip
and use a paradiddle rhythm.
Do you understand?
No.
See?
That’s why I had to
listen to his briefs myself.
Do you know the reason behind
everything I’ve done so far?
Nope.
Anyway, send me the correct references.
Keep them coming.
I’ll be standing by and
waiting for them tonight.
Okay?
Can I send you tomorrow?
Mick has just assigned me extra work.
I have to send him the subtitles tomorrow.
This is annoying.
You have too many excuses.
When are we getting
serious about this work, huh?
Excuses?
No. I really was assigned extra work.
Let’s put it this way.
Follow me.
Why did you bring me here?
To find a place to work.
Not many people come here.
Usually, it's for meeting up with
people you'd rather not have others see.
Is this why people gossip that you like
to secretly date but don't let anyone know?
You’re really good at gossiping.
If you were this good at work,
you’d probably be a CEO by now.
You jerk.
Here you are.
- Hello. - A table for two, please.
I'd like a private corner, please.
Please head inside.
This way, please.
What drink would you like?
Old-Fashioned, please.
How about you?
Well…
Let’s go with something simple, then.
Grand Martini, please.
Sure.
Hold on.
I just told you I’ve got some work to do.
Here you go.
Do your work.
Turn on your notebook.
Give me the work you
have to submit tomorrow.
I’ll handle it for you.
Anyway, today you still have
to sell the MV concept to me
because, in the end, you're the
one who has to work on our new song.
Why are you pressuring me like this?
You want to become a director, don’t you?
Bringing up the MV and
pressuring you like this
isn't to get you to meet Thame.
It's all for your own benefit.
I want to make you feel
that you can do it
and you can do it well too.
If you want him to love you,
won’t you do something to impress him, huh?
Can you not come up with a simple shot?
Come up with the idea
without having to be
concerned about the budget.
Don’t care what props.
Just enough to get the picture across
to show what kind of
image you're aiming for.
How about this?
It just doesn’t fit the lyrics.
Why must we need the brief then, huh?
I can’t come up with any ideas.
Stop complaining.
Keep working.
Hurry up.
Can you sing the song one more time?
Sure.
Would you mind if I ask you out?
Will you doubt me if I say I like you?
If your heart’s not taken, it’s true
It’s always you who takes my breath away
Baby
Would you mind if I ask you out?
Haven’t you forgotten that somehow?
Can I make you mine now?
I want to claim your heart today
Before someone else takes you away
How about this?
Interesting.
But I think we need to add something more.
Well…
Here.
Well done.
Hey?
What are you doing here?
I’m waiting for you.
You told me you went with Jun, so…
I see.
You’re here to check on our
progress with the MV concept, right?
Did you come all this way
just to follow up on it?
No, that’s not it.
Well…
Just forget about it.
Didn’t Jun drive you home?
That’s good.
Eh?
That’s it.
So, do you want to see the
idea we’ve come up with?
I’ll show you.
No.
Just head to your room.
Oh, okay.
Send me the last photo when you get home.
MV: WOULD YOU MIND?
So, that’s the idea.
What do you guys think?
Whoa, bro.
This is just right.
It’s perfectly right.
You nailed it.
You two are amazing.
It’s totally worth it that
you guys worked all day and night.
Great job.
Just to let you know, I
contributed just a little.
The main idea came from him.
Po is good at this.
Right?
WOULD YOU MIND? .WAV.
You’re gonna show…
- How’s that, bro? - Groovy.
I think it’s different from others.
This is what we call a catchy song.
- Airdrop it to me. I don’t have it yet.
- Eh?
- I don’t have it yet.
- Sure. I’ll send it to you.
- Found it? - Yeah.
Thanks, man.
THAME AND PEPPER DISCUSSION 6 P.M. THAME CHECK
BOTH TO MAKE SURE THEY ARE IN THE SAME DIRECTIONS
DANCE PRACTICE
LOVE YOU TO DEBT LIFE,
ROMANTIC / 135 MINUTES
Have you applied some sunscreen yet?
You two, after you’re
done, come help Pepper.
Stick your face out a little
Well,
I texted you.
About that movie screen time, right?
Yeah.
Since we’ve done working already,
you’re not too tired to watch it, right?
Not at all.
I’m good to go.
What a relief.
Why?
The movie’s about to leave theaters,
and lately, you’ve
been so into the MV work.
I thought you might’ve forgotten about it.
Hey, come on.
How could I forget?
Well,
it seems you and Jun get along pretty well.
Huh?
Getting along?
We fought all the time…
But, honestly, without Jun,
the work wouldn’t have
turned out like this.
You know what?
He’s super strict,
but he helped me with the idea
and also to get through the
work from my full-time job.
Give me a second. Mick called.
Yes, Mick?
Noted, Mick.
I’ll quickly edit it and send it to you.
What’s up?
I’m inviting you to the secret bar with me
to celebrate that we’ve
successfully finalized the concept.
Don’t tell me you never
thought about thanking me
for helping you realize how
well you could do your job?
Of course, I want to thank you for that,
but can I buy some snacks for you instead?
I have to watch a movie with Thame.
See?
You told me I must show him my improvement.
He already saw it.
That’s why we’re going on a date.
Thanks a lot, Jun.
I’m off now.
I need to edit the work for Mick.
Hey, let me ask you something.
When Po presented the
MV concept the other day,
you said Jun worked all day and night.
Were you talking about this MV?
What a strange question.
So, it’s this one, right?
I don't know for sure.
But by the way…
I don’t think it’s this one, Thame.
So, what was he doing?
As far as I know, he was
working on the subtitles.
Subtitles?
This one?
Shit.
You know about this too?
Eh?
Mick just sent this into our group chat.
None of you want to check it out, huh?
We’re this busy.
How can you make time to watch it?
My work is done, you know.
Jun is acting strange.
Thame.
I have something to talk to you about.
I want to talk to you, too.
Shit.
Guys,
here comes a big problem.
- What happened? - Look at this.
Would you mind if I ask you out?
Will you doubt me if I say I like you?
If your heart’s not taken, it’s true
It’s always you who takes my breath away
Baby
Would you mind if I ask you out?
Can I take a chance right now?
Will you say yes somehow?
I want to claim your heart today
Before someone else takes you away
It’s our song.
The promotion plan is as discussed.
Please take care of it.
You aren’t allowed to
come to the company yet.
You didn’t tell anyone to
get me out of here either.
I haven’t seen you act
like this for so long,
since the day I told you I
wouldn't continue with MARS.
That’s because you gave
MARS’ song to someone else.
It’s the song you even mentioned
that you wouldn’t want it.
Thame.
That song doesn’t belong to MARS.
The company owns it.
Huh? How come?
Dylan and I composed it.
Under Oner’s terms,
with the contract you're signing with Oner,
every song you and Dylan
compose will belong to Oner.
So, the company has
the right to use the song
however, with whomever,
and whenever we choose.
Don’t tell me you all teamed up
just to revive that song and
use it to negotiate with me?
You know it’s useless.
And we have already finished
discussing this matter since that day.
It was over because I believed you
that my members wouldn’t
want to do it anymore.
But it turns out that
everyone still wants to be MARS.
And I want to prove to
you that we can do it.
Also, we don’t need to leave anyone behind
just to become successful.
Fine.
Now tell me how you define success.
Total sales?
Engagement?
BA jobs?
If not, then what is it?
It's about how the TPOP world is going
to be the new wave in the music industry.
Do you think the reason I
separated you from the group
is because the market wants you?
The reason I separated you is
because you’re the one who can
take TPOP beyond just the local scene.
You’re the one chosen by Korea,
so this is an opportunity to
make people pay attention to TPOP.
The value you're creating isn’t just money.
You’re building the music industry.
What you're doing right now
is causing the company to
miss out on a huge opportunity.
Really?
You know me well, Thame.
I love this industry more than anyone else,
and I always look ahead,
focusing on the bigger picture.
What if my bigger picture
doesn't just include me?
You told me yourself that
what you want most is
the opportunity for TPOP.
And I believe it's not just
me who can make it happen.
MARS as a group can do it too.
What do you say?
But they only want you.
The contract only involves you.
That’s because, in the past, you've
only focused the spotlight on me.
But this time,
if I broaden that spotlight,
making every member shine and stand out,
do you think we stand a chance?
If you want the world
to pay attention to TPOP,
a group can get more attention
than just a solo artist.
Fine.
Tell me your plan, then.
I'll create a new song under MARS.
If my song beats Ice's song
and tops every chart,
then we'll all get to go there.
What if you fail?
You'll go back to fulfilling
the original contract, right?
Yes. I’ll do that.
But you know that Oner will
not help you with anything, right?
Just don’t get in a way.
Per, I’ve already talked to the company.
I need your help.
LOVE YOU TO DEBT
If you’re still waiting at the
cinema, just don’t wait anymore.
I think he already forgot
about his date with you.
Something happened.
Would you mind if I ask you out?
Will you doubt me if I say I like you?
If your heart’s not taken, it’s true
Head home. Don’t wait anymore.
You aren’t going to watch it anymore?
I’m sorry I’m late.
Did I make it in time?
I thought you were busy with the song.
I was.
But why…
But you are important, too.
I don’t want to break our promise anymore.
MAKE A SONG
Does anyone have any ideas?
I do. I want to make a love song.
What kind of love do you
want the song to be about?
Are you looking for song
ideas or trouble with me?
What did you fight with Jun
about? Nothing serious, right?
It is, actually.
Why are you avoiding me?
Can’t we just talk it out?
Why do I have to play
this stupid game with you?
Because it's going to be a long talk.
About both the song and Po.