That guy Fukami...
He just woke up and
left like it was nothing.
Still as cold as ever.
Good morning.
Morning.
Thanks for taking care of me on Friday.
Um...
I'm sorry, who are you?
What are you talking about?
Wait...
Fukami?
The Fukami I know
at the office is always...
So dorky.
He wears glasses,
and he's so gloomy.
He looks so... polished.
Wh...
What happened to you?
What's with the new look?
Well, it's been a while
since I went out for drinks,
so I thought I should try to look decent.
But I have no fashion sense,
so I asked my sister for help,
and she got a bit carried away.
She really went all out.
You're like a completely different person.
It's weird, isn't it?
Maybe I should at least
put my glasses back on.
No, it's not weird.
It's really not.
But in a moment like this,
I honestly don't know what to say.
Good work. I can't get a hold of that guy.
Wait, seriously?
Good morning, Kaji-san.
- Morning.
- What are you doing?
- Just taking a break.
- Which department are you in?
I'm in Tech.
What year did you join the company?
Sorry if this is forward,
but are you married?
No, I'm not.
Are you on Instagram or anything?
Fukami is suddenly very popular.
"Unexpectedly Naughty Fukami"
- I'm Fukami.
- Fukami-san, right?
Oh, can I get your LINE?
(Episode 4)
Is there something wrong with the system?
No, I haven't heard anything.
Weren't there a ton of
people in Tech just now?
Oh, yeah.
That's pretty unusual.
Tell me about it.
Hey, that guy is Fukami-san, right?
- He's so cute.
- Totally.
I wonder if he has a girlfriend.
Let's go ask him.
Go ask...
Fukami is "cute"?
No.
You guys have no idea.
Like how he'll suddenly
laugh at the weirdest times.
When I'm with you,
I feel like I'm not myself anymore.
Or how aggressive he gets when he's drunk.
Is this not okay?
I'm already getting a little hard.
All those sides of him...
They're supposed to be my secret.
Hypothetically.
Just thinking out loud here.
Even though it would never happen.
If I...
If I actually fell for him.
Didn't I tell you not
to fall in love with me?
We should...
stop being friends with benefits.
No way, no way.
It'd be such a waste to give up that body.
What if he...
What if he fell for me?
I've fallen for you.
But it's too much trouble.
Let's not see each other anymore.
That's a possibility.
Then...
What if the feeling was mutual?
That's a total mystery.
I can't even imagine it.
Besides,
I've never had that kind
of relationship with anyone.
Our personalities are too different.
I don't think it would work out.
So then,
this thing we have...
How long will it last?
How far will it go?
(Mr. Zero: I'm free on Friday)
He's the one asking to meet.
That's a first.
What does "I'm free" even mean?
He should be saying,
"Please see me."
When he's alone,
does he think about sleeping with me too?
I'm making coffee.
Want some?
Oh.
No, I'm good.
The shower's all yours.
I already showered at home.
You're back to your old self.
I don't know...
I couldn't really relax.
I'm relieved.
The side of him I don't
want anyone else to know.
The way his messy hair
clings to the back of his neck.
I guess...
I actually kind of like it.
Hey, you're gonna make me spill!
You...
You're pretty popular now, aren't you?
Wait...
Am I?
Don't play dumb after all that attention.
And then,
put your hands behind your back.
Like this...
Wait a second.
Stop it.
What is this even for?
I love the way you're
looking at me right now.
I'm not into this kind of thing.
That's not what it looks like.
Your body is being pretty honest.
I said stop.
That hurts.
Didn't you say last time
to just tell you if there was
something I wanted to do?
Huh?
I never said that.
Yes, you did.
Don't you remember, you drunk?
Shut up and untie me.
Let me take the lead for once.
As long as you don't hurt me,
I guess it's okay.
I would never hurt you.
Is this jealousy?
Or just possessiveness?
The Fukami only I get to see.
I want to touch you in the front.
Untie me.
Kaji.
No.
The only thing you're allowed to use
is my body.
Help me...
Please.
Even when I make him look like that,
the one who's really in control
is always him.
When I'm with this guy,
I can't keep my cool at all.
I overdid it again.
Why does it always
end up like this?
Are you okay?
Is something wrong?
Huh?
Don't "huh" me!
You seem like your mind is elsewhere.
If you're not feeling it,
don't force yourself. You can say no.
Who's fault do you think that is?
It's because you're always
messing with
my head!
Do you think I just come running
every time you ask to meet?
Wait, what?
I'm not here because you asked.
I just wanted to do it myself.
You just happened to message me,
and you were convenient.
Stop acting like you know me.
What do you even know about me?
We've only slept together
a few times, haven't we?
Well,
I guess that's true.
Hey.
Let's stop seeing each other for a while.
I understand.
In the past,
whenever things got complicated,
I'd just cut ties immediately.
It's just a casual game
to satisfy my urges.
Block them,
pretend they never existed,
and move on to the next one.
Dammit.
It always worked before.
It was always so easy...
How long is "for a while" supposed to be?
Dammit!
Promise me...
that you'll never fall in love with me.
If you're so worried
about me falling for you,
you shouldn't have been so kind to me.
(Next Episode)
I have a high fever.
Kaji-kun seems to have a high fever.
Let him get some rest.
I'm surprised you invited me over.
(Mr. Zero: I'm nearby. Are you home?)
Zero... so you're that "Mr. Zero."
I should've never slept
with you in the first place.