ADAPTED FROM THE NOVEL
HIDDEN LOVE BY ZHU YI
What's wrong?
What are you doing, Duan Jiaxu?
What did you call me?
I mean, what did you just do?
Given our current relationship,
you shouldn't be calling me Duan Jiaxu.
You…
I wasn't asleep just now.
I knew what you were doing.
So you weren't asleep, were you?
What did I do just now then?
Tell me.
Come closer. I won't say it out loud.
Closer.
Do you want to whisper it?
I don't know
what I've done either.
That was unexpected.
Even though I did that just now,
it doesn't mean
that I have feelings for you.
Got it? I mean…
I haven't agreed yet.
It doesn't mean you have feelings for me.
That means you took advantage of me.
Well, you took advantage of me first.
Are you saying
that no matter what I do to you,
you will do the same to me?
That's not what I meant.
If you do this again,
I will tell my brother.
Go ahead.
Tell him.
After all,
we'll have to go public sooner or later.
It's better to do it sooner.
I haven't agreed yet.
I've successfully brainwashed you.
Jiaxu…
Stop looking at me.
Jiaxu, you should leave.
I can't focus if you stay here.
Hi, everyone.
-Hello.
I'm an alumnus.
-I'm Wang Lin.
-The speaker is here.
The topic of today's sharing session
is future career planning.
Nice!
I know it seems early to talk about this
since you are only freshmen.
However, I believe in being prepared.
Left.
To the left. That's right.
What's wrong?
Yu Xin, look!
What is it?
Sangsang's crush attended her class!
-Look.
-Seriously?
Yes.
They attract so much attention.
-I like it.
-I bet I know why.
He bailed on Sangsang several times,
so he specifically came
to make it up to her!
It feels nice to walk around
on campus.
Didn't you take walks
during your time at university?
I didn't.
Why would I? I had no one to walk with.
Didn't my brother take walks with you?
Your brother taking walks with me?
Am I that desperate?
I'll tell him you said that.
If you enjoy taking walks,
I can keep you company today.
Chen Qiang, go for it!
Chen Qiang, you've got this!
You are the best, Chen Qiang!
-It's Weiwei.
-Chen Qiang, go!
-Want to watch?
-Enough.
-Sure. Let's go.
-Everyone knows he's your boyfriend.
Go for it!
Chen Qiang, go for it!
-You startled me.
-You guys are here too.
-Hi.
-Hi, guys.
-Hello.
-Are you here to watch the game too?
He said he wanted to watch.
Look at Chen Qiang.
Is that your boyfriend?
Yes.
Isn't he cool?
-Are you okay?
-Are you okay, Jiang Ming?
-Jiang Ming!
Can you still play?
-Are you okay?
-I'm fine.
I'm okay.
Are you hurt?
-Are you okay?
-Did you sprain your ankle?
Yes.
Elevate your foot.
-Use this iced tea.
-Apply it here.
Thank you.
You should go to the infirmary.
It's okay.
This is an old injury.
I'll be better after resting.
Now we're down one player.
Why don't you guys
find someone to replace me?
Hey.
Can you fill in?
Can I?
Can you play?
Come on. Let's play.
Let's go.
Get some rest.
Hold this for me.
Wait here for me.
You will defend him.
He's pretty good.
Hey! Nice shot!
Sangsang, your crush is pretty good.
That's not just pretty good, okay?
He's perfect.
Sangsang is being pursued
by such a perfect guy.
She's so lucky.
Good job!
Nice game!
Shoot!
Come.
Okay.
Yes! Nice job!
He's really good!
-Nice!
-Impressive!
It went in!
He's quite good.
Isn't that guy Sang Zhi's brother?
You misunderstood.
They aren't related.
Have some iced tea after the game.
Thank you.
-Here.
-Do you need a drink?
CHAPTER 17, FALLEN
I WANT US TO BE TOGETHER
Girls.
Do you have any summer plans?
Are you going home or traveling?
I'm not going home for the break.
No?
Where are you going then?
Chen Qiang and I have made plans.
We are going to travel
during the summer break.
Really?
That's so romantic.
-How nice.
-I previously made a game prototype.
A design company has shown interest.
I'm going to intern
at their company this summer.
-Really?
-Congratulations.
Interning during freshman year?
That's right!
It's a great company.
I have to seize the opportunity.
Sangsang, are you going home
for the summer?
I…
Or are you staying here with your crush?
He's too busy.
I don't think he has time for me.
I don't want to go home
for the summer either,
so I want to talk to my mom about it.
I think getting a summer internship
is better than staying at home.
Agreed. Totally agreed.
Yu Xin.
What do I need
to include in my resume?
It's important
to highlight your specialty.
Let me take notes.
And don't forget.
Aren't you good at system maintenance?
Put your system maintenance portfolio on--
-The first page.
-Yes.
-The most visible section.
-Yes. And then…
SANG ZHI
Sang Yan.
What do you want?
SILLY DOG
I don't want to go home for the summer.
I plan to get an internship here
to enrich my university life.
I don't want to waste my youth.
While I'm still young,
I want to try everything I can.
So
can you help me talk
to Mom and Dad about this?
If Mom still pressures you
to get married during Chinese New Year,
I'll speak up for you.
SANG ZHI
Let me ask you.
Is your postgraduate boyfriend going home?
Listen, you're coming home for the summer.
Listen to yourself.
I'm embarrassed for you
even through the screen.
SILLY DOG
Don't call me. I'm busy right now.
Sang Yan.
I told you.
I'm staying here for an internship,
for work.
It's not for dating.
Besides,
the person I'm interested in
is older than you,
but not older than Dad.
Don't be so petty.
Just because you didn't date in college
and can't find a girlfriend now,
you can't be jealous of me.
You need to be more magnanimous.
Don't get it wrong.
I'm not jealous at all.
I have a girlfriend.
Also, let me tell you.
Don't become stupid after falling in love.
When you met your online friend
during high school,
you were only young and rebellious.
You have to come home for the summer.
Listen.
I dare you to not come back.
I'll fly there and drag you home myself.
Who…
Who would believe
that you have a girlfriend?
You are just lying to me.
And besides…
Besides, I am staying
to work at an internship.
If you don't agree,
I will tell Mom.
You are so irritating!
Why didn't you invite Chen Qiang?
The professor told him to go
and retake the test.
-Let's have dumplings again later.
-Noodles.
-Dumplings!
-Let's have noodles again.
-Just once.
-It's really good.
Give me a minute.
Just a minute.
Where are you going?
What are you doing?
Jiang Ming.
Hi, Wangwang.
This is for you.
My mom said this works well
for bruises and sprains.
Thank you.
What is going on?
-At the basketball court yesterday,
-What is she doing?
you asked about Sangsang's brother.
It's okay.
Sang Zhi has found someone she likes.
I should be happy for her.
-Sang Zhi?
-I'm glad you're okay.
They are talking and smiling.
Thank you for the ointment.
I'll return it when I'm done with it.
It's okay.
I'm leaving now.
Okay.
-Bye.
-What was that?
-What's going on?
-What's up?
-What's the situation?
I knew it!
I could tell that day at the court.
You rushed to him when he was injured!
You are quite something.
So what's your plan?
Well…
What? Go after him if you like him.
-Don't hesitate.
-Yu Xin, you're catching on.
Get lost.
The video-editing course this semester
wants us to conduct an interview.
I was thinking of interviewing Jiang Ming.
Do you think
he will agree to it?
He's right there. Just ask him yourself.
-Right.
-It's a great opportunity.
The two of you
can spend some time together.
Good for you.
You've got some moves.
-Impressive.
-You are good at this.
Stop teasing me.
THE DREAM GAMES
Are you still in class?
Let's get beef noodles later.
Sure.
SANG ZHI
Are you off work?
Yes.
DUAN JIAXU
Do you not have classes this evening?
I have plans tonight.
What plans?
You said you have plans tonight.
I do.
I have to celebrate someone's birthday.
Happy birthday.
I forgot that it's my birthday.
I understand.
Old people don't like
celebrating their birthdays.
My dad is the same.
Yes, I'm getting old.
That's why
I hope you can help me get married
before I turn 27.
When you are 27,
I won't have graduated yet.
So who are you going to marry?
From the sound of that,
I don't think you refused.
So I'll take that as a yes.
You're so shameless.
Of course.
I'm pursuing a young girl
and someone as difficult as you at that.
Of course I have to be shameless.
So you think I'm difficult.
By the way,
did my brother, Qian Fei, and the others
wish you a happy birthday?
They don't even remember
their own birthdays.
Why would they remember mine?
So they haven't?
What about your colleagues?
Did they celebrate your birthday today?
They are all so busy.
They don't have time for these things.
Do you know what day it is today?
SILLY DOG
SENIOR
Remember to send me the design.
Who are you texting?
A senior classmate.
A senior classmate?
What does he want?
It's about a school event.
Is he handsome?
Morally upright?
Is he a head taller than you?
He has a girlfriend.
I'm just asking.
SANG YAN
Why is my brother suddenly calling you?
That's strange.
You're right. I'll reject the call then.
Answer it.
Hi.
Hello, Duan Jiaxu.
I just remembered
that it's your birthday today.
Yes. So?
Congratulations, buddy.
Even at your age,
you still don't have a girlfriend.
By the way, let me ask you a question.
I'm hanging up.
No, hang on.
Did my sister give you the gift?
Yes.
That one is from me.
That's all.
I'm just calling to wish you
a happy birthday.
By the way, let me ask you something.
Have you met my sister's boyfriend?
Boyfriend?
I told you. It's a postgraduate student.
I remember now.
I think I've met him.
What kind of guy is he?
The little demon is quite infatuated.
She plans on staying in Yihe
and not coming home.
-I don't know what charm he has---
-Sang Yan.
Was that my sister?
Are you two together?
Yes.
You…
You've wished him a happy birthday,
so you can hang up now.
Don't tell me you two--
No.
Don't overthink it.
You said no before I even finished.
Why are you so worked up?
I know what you were going to say.
That's enough.
You can hang up now.
Are you two having dinner together?
Yes.
I can't be a heartless friend like you.
Also,
why did you say
the gift was from you?
I bought the gift for him.
Isn't it a bit schmaltzy for a grown man
to celebrate his birthday?
Little demon,
don't stay out too late.
I'm hanging up now.
Just hang up.
Good night, buddy.
Have an early night.
Boyfriend?
What boyfriend?
I told him
that I'm about to start dating,
not that I'm already dating.
He misunderstood.
A postgraduate student?
Is it too late for me to apply?
How else will we explain it to Sang Yan?
Maybe we can tell him
that you broke up
with that postgraduate boyfriend
and got together with me.
That might work.
That definitely won't work.
When did I get together with you?
That's so weird.
You've already told your brother.
And you still won't admit to liking me?
Did you already know?
Know what?
All right, jokes aside,
let me ask you something.
Go on.
Do you really have no feelings for me?
Maybe just a little bit.
Okay.
Why aren't you surprised?
Don't you find it strange
that I have feelings for you,
but won't agree to be with you
and am making you pursue me?
You said it's only a little bit.
It's probably not strong enough
for you to want to date me.
What if I never agree
to be with you?
Then I will pursue you every day.
After all,
this might be the only relationship
you'll have in your whole life.
So whatever other young girls have,
Zhizhi
has to have it too.
Ms. Sang, everything is ready for you.
This way, please.
-Happy birthday to you
What is this?
-What is this?
-Happy birthday to you
Thank you.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
They are getting off work soon.
From here on, it's all on me.
Wait for me here.
I'll prepare a mysterious feast
for you.
I will come with you.
No need.
I'll go by myself.
It's very mysterious.
I'm making it myself.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
Thank you for your help.
Go home now.
Good luck.
MOM'S HANDMADE
LONGEVITY NOODLES RECIPE
Mushroom.
Cut twice.
Use a garnishing knife.
And then…
So is this my birthday feast?
You…
Why did you come inside?
Wait outside.
I'll be done soon. Very soon.
Are you sure you can do it by yourself?
It's very simple.
-You don't need any help?
-I really don't. Go out.
Good luck.
It's very easy.
It's fine. Don't worry about me.
Add these in.
Add the noodles.
How is it?
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
Let me try it.
Don't try it.
You can
just take a photo for a memento.
I haven't tasted it,
so I think…
Is it edible?
It's good.
It's good?
Yes.
No way.
Let me try it.
-No.
-Why?
You made this for me.
I have to finish it all by myself.
It must taste awful.
It's really good.
Stop eating.
This year, you can make three wishes.
Two wishes can be spoken out.
Keep the last one to yourself.
Wishes won't come true
if there are too many.
I only have one wish.
That's fine too.
Happy birthday.
-Thank you.
-What did you wish for?
You know what it is.
Well…
Your wish is too easy to fulfill.
The answer is yes.
Are you saying
that you will be my girlfriend?
That's because I want
to be by your side
for all your future birthdays.
Can I?
Of course you can.
Then
I will cut the cake for you.
The birthday boy eats first.
What?
I
don't really know how to do this.
You always call me old.
It's quite embarrassing
to admit this myself.
This is also my first relationship.
And it is also
my first time liking someone so much.
So
don't even think about dumping me.
Why do you keep staring at me?
I just didn't expect you
to say yes so soon.
I feel that today is very special.
How so?
Firstly, this is your first birthday
that I've celebrated with you.
And it's also our first day together.
From now on,
I'll always be by your side.
By the way,
there are some things
I feel I should let you know.
I don't think I've told you
about my family situation.
The thing is,
my mom has passed away.
And my dad
is in a coma.
He killed someone while drunk driving.
But I've paid off the compensation.
Right now,
I don't
own a house,
but I have a car.
I also have some savings.
I'm sorry
to bring this up out of the blue.
Please don't feel uncomfortable.
I'm not uncomfortable.
I'm just worried
that talking about these things
might make you sad.
Why would I feel sad?
But
I admit that I might be a bit nervous.
Why?
I'm worried that you will mind.
I don't mind.
Sang Zhi, is there a power outage?
I think so.
Okay.
Hello.
Girlfriend, are you free later?
Let's have lunch together.
I'm going to the library to study.
How about another day?
The library?
Can't you keep me company?
Another day.
All right then.
Bye.
What are you doing here?
The power is out.
There's nowhere to study.
Why didn't you tell me?
I was just about to go to the library.
I know which library you mean.
It's the one nearby.
There is very limited seating.
All seats will have been taken by now.
Then…
-There is a café up ahead.
-Come to my place.
Your place?
To study.
You haven't eaten, right?
Perfect.
I'll make something tasty for you later.
You can cook too?
I have a lot of skills.
Such as?
Such as…
Change into slippers.
You can study in my room later.
There's a desk inside.
I…
I can just study here.
I don't need to go to your room.
I'll be cooking here later.
Won't I disturb your studying?
What are you thinking?
I've already tidied up the desk for you.
Study well.
Jiaxu, what will you be doing
while I study?
I will
just be sitting here.
You'll just be sitting here?
I want to look at you more.
LUOKA BAKING
Welcome.
-Hi.
Excuse me.
Do you make personalized cakes?
Yes, we do.
I have a picture.
Can you make something like this?
Yes, we can.
When would you like to have it?
Is next Monday okay?
Yes. Let me take it down.
Miss, what is your surname?
Sang.
An eight-inch cake.
Miss, your phone is ringing.
Have you taken a photo?
Yes. Go ahead.
Hello, Mom.
Hi, Zhizhi.
I was outside just now.
I just got home.
Did you say something
about the recipe for longevity noodles?
Is it someone's birthday?
It's Jiaxu's birthday.
So it's Xiaoduan.
I'm studying in Yihe
and Jiaxu has been taking care of me.
He's all alone here.
So I thought
I would make longevity noodles for him.
But
I'm sure you make the most delicious one.
You're becoming more considerate.
Okay, I'll write out the recipe
for longevity noodles
and send it to you later.
Okay.
Bye.
Miss, take a look.
It will be an eight-inch cake
to be picked up next Monday.
Will you be picking it up yourself?
-Yes.
-Okay.
It's all set.
Thank you.