I’m looking for the kids who hurt my brother.
You have my heart now,
so take good care of it.
I don’t like you being in my life and changing it.
I don’t like that I miss you.
Be my boyfriend.
Give me a chance.
Fine, I’ll be your boyfriend.
You made me hit on a gunman?
Not a gunman.
A hitman.
They don’t just use guns.
Ruerat was behind the death of our parents.
If the two of us work together,
they’ll never catch us.
I’m sorry I didn’t have time to meet you two before.
It’s okay, Mother.
We know you’re busy.
It’s obvious what this is.
What more answers do you need?
So Ruerat really was behind our parents’ death?
Yes.
Your parents refused to sell him their lands.
He had them killed.
That was how you became orphans,
and I took you in.
Why didn’t you tell us sooner?
We could have dealt with him long ago.
Taking out someone of his status isn’t easy.
We must wait for the right moment.
I see that you two are ready now.
It’s a big job.
So I’ll give you what you ask for.
Get this done,
and if you want to take a long break,
or even quit,
I’ll let you.
There’s going to be a party.
It’s a good opportunity to carry out the operation.
I will have Keen take care of everything for you.
What do you think, Keen?
Yes, Mother.
It’s time to take revenge for your loved ones.
Get it done.
What’s wrong?
You look pretty bummed.
I’m just sick of work.
It’s just all admin tasks.
No challenge at all.
What do you want to do instead?
You’re pretty good at helping people.
You’re cheeky now, you know that?
I thought you liked that.
I do.
I’ll get you back for this comment after work.
How would you do that?
Keen.
Are you and Tanont going out?
No.
We were just chatting.
Just chatting.
Yes.
Good.
I thought you’d start dating
and leave me, too.
What’s with you?
Oh, it’s just hot
and uncomfortable in here.
Sorry.
That’s kinda the point of a sauna.
You seem strange today.
I’m fine.
I’m just not used to this.
It’s usually me running after you,
but now you’re with me.
You wanted us to be boyfriends.
Well, I’m your boyfriend now.
Or did you change your mind?
I don’t mind, you know?
I don’t like you that much.
I’ll get over it.
Bye, then.
Hey, hey.
Wait.
Are you sure?
Are you intimidated by me?
I’m not intimidated.
I just can’t believe my persistence actually worked.
It didn’t.
I told you.
We’re on trial.
Should we go back to your garage?
You’ve been to my restaurant too many times already.
Nah, let’s not.
The garage is messy and full of cars.
We can do it here and get it over with.
Well?
No.
Let’s go back to your garage.
You’ve been in my turf.
Let me be in yours.
If I don’t have to move again,
I’ll take you in, alright?
Let’s take a snapshot.
(Is he cute?)
(The cat is obviously cute.)
(But I’d rather see your face.)
Alright, baby.
Let’s take another one.
One, two, three.
(Who’s more adorable?)
(I can’t choose.)
(I want to kiss both cat and human.)
See?
I’m just as adorable as you are.
What do we say?
Should we let him give us a kiss?
Hmm?
(I’ll let you give me a few kisses next time, then.)
(Any updates on them yet?)
(Did you get in their house?)
He trusts me enough to go out with me now.
Well, be careful.
Tell your friend, too.
These hitmen hate just as hard as they love.
Geez, thanks for the fair warning.
I’ll put them behind bars before they catch up to you.
Don’t worry.
You could have had that!
Look!
Okay!
You want to play this?
I’m just gonna try this.
You know,
I was on the basketball team in high school.
Very popular with the ladies.
If I didn’t have my head wrapped up in other things,
I could probably have made it to the NBA.
You could have, huh?
You’re pretty amazing.
Is there anything you can’t do?
I don’t think so.
If I got someone as hard to get as you,
I think I’m pretty good.
Right?
Hey.
We’re outside.
What were you good at as a child?
I loved drawing.
I loved art.
I always got an A in my art classes.
PE was never my thing, though.
The only sport I do is swimming.
That’s the opposite of me.
I play basketball and football quite well.
Bison doesn’t like basketball or football.
What are you doing?
Taking notes.
I’m jotting down what you don’t like
so I know not to take you out on basketball dates.
What kind of date is that?
I’m sure some people do it.
You might not play,
but you can always cheer me up on the sideline.
I look pretty cool on the court.
It’ll definitely make you scream.
Didn’t know you stopped betting on footballs and hanging out at arcades now.
I stopped football betting ages ago.
But you used to do that all the time.
Don’t you remember?
That Manchester derby match
where you bet all your money on Manchester City.
You paid off your car with that money, right?
That was long ago.
I don’t do anything shady anymore.
To think you’re an upstanding citizen now.
How boring.
What about you, Bison?
You into sports betting?
No.
I don’t care for it.
Does working at a burger joint
pay you well enough?
How do you know where I work?
Well…
You brought Kant some burger the other day.
I assumed from that.
Alright, alright.
You’re all exemplary people here.
I’ll leave you alone now.
But if you’re ever interested in placing your bets,
you know where to find me.
It’s a nightly thing.
So I’ll always be ready for you.
He sure clings to you.
Was it very serious with him?
Is that why he dared say all that?
Come on.
It’s nothing to worry about.
That’s just how James is.
I’m not saying anything, am I?
He probably just doesn’t know me well enough.
I might need time to go and introduce myself.
What do you mean?
I was just saying that.
As if a waiter like me could hurt anyone.
Am I right?
Catch me if you can.
Well?
Am I the best or what?
It’s just a fluke.
Don’t let it get to your head.
Can I ask you something?
Did you become a mechanic
because you wanted to or because of your family business?
At first, I just wanted to help my dad out.
But when my mother died,
and he lost his bearings for a bit,
I was glad to have something I could talk to him about.
But after a while,
it just kinda grew on me.
Would you believe
I even won a car tuning competition?
I know.
How’d you know that?
It was on the internet, you know.
I’m gonna be honest with you…
You said you liked me from the moment you saw me.
What did you like about me?
I liked the feeling of chasing after you.
I’m a competitive guy.
Being in a race gives me adrenaline.
So you only hit on me for the thrill of it?
This ain’t car racing.
Of course not.
I like how you look, too.
I like that you’re so different from me.
It’s an opportunity to learn,
and it’s an experience, you know?
You haven’t won, you know?
The game isn’t over.
A guy like me
doesn’t know how to accept defeat.
Follow me.
Oh, Boss.
You’re back.
I’m just about closing up shop for you.
It’s alright.
Go home. I’ll take it over from here.
Yes, sir.
Where’s your father?
On a fishing trip with his buddies.
He deserves a break.
You’re quite the son, aren’t you?
You take such good care of your dad.
We’re all each other has.
When Mom died,
Dad became the most important person in my life.
You know what?
When I came out to him about liking dudes,
I was so afraid of disappointing him.
But you know what he did?
He tried to set me up with another mechanic at the garage.
And what did you do?
Look at me.
With my god-sculpted face,
of course I’d prefer to choose my own man.
And you chose me?
You wanna do it here?
Don’t tell me you never fantasized about garage sex.
That’s straight out of porn.
Well, wanna give it a shot?
Excuse me.
My car broke down.
Need it fixed?
I don’t have any money.
You can pay with something else.
He probably just doesn’t know me well enough.
I might need time to go and introduce myself.
Hey, Otto.
Can I ask you something?
Yeah, bro?
I haven’t heard from you in ages.
Which teams you wanna bet on tonight?
I didn’t call to place bets.
I wanna know if James is there.
He’s not here yet.
Why didn’t you just call him?
I did, but he didn’t pick up the phone.
It’s alright.
I’ll call him again.
(I see.)
(Strange.)
(Someone just came here and asked after him.)
Who?
(I don’t know the guy.)
(But he’s good-looking.)
Probably someone James’ hooking up with.
(Small and pretty.)
Okay, thanks.
What was that?
Hurry up, guys.
What happened there?
That scar.
This?
Just a little accident.
Will you tell me about it?
Why’d you want to know?
It’s just an occupational hazard.
I want to know more about you.
You don’t tell me anything.
Like the Rise Up support group…
Why do you go?
I lost my parents.
You can talk to me, you know?
I lost my mother to cancer.
You don’t have to tell anyone else.
My parents were murdered.
I’m sorry.
Let’s… change the subject.
You had any lovers before?
No.
My life isn’t exactly easy.
I don’t want to drag anyone along with me.
Does owning a burger joint
so difficult that you can’t date?
I don’t think anyone wants to risk their life with me.
What risk?
I mean…
The risk of the business going under.
You know running a restaurant isn't exactly a secure job.
Maybe you just need to find something else to do.
Do something that allows you to love
without risking your loved ones.
Style.
Kant?
Fadel.
Sorry for interrupting.
Kant, what’s up?
Why didn’t you call me up?
I did. You didn’t pick up.
What were you guys doing?
Yeah, well…
What do you want?
I need to talk to you in private.
Can I?
I’m gonna talk to Kant for a bit.
Sure.
I’ll wait outside.
What?
Bison is on his way to take out your old hookup, James?
Yeah.
What would we do if Bison actually hurt him?
You know Bison’s pretty hot-headed.
Crap, dude, worry about yourself first.
You could die any minute.
I can’t help you.
Someone is in danger, you know?
I had nothing to do with this.
You dragged me along.
By the way, I have a bad feeling about Fadel.
He scares me.
But I like his rough romantic side.
The hell?
This ain’t no time to confess your weird feelings.
I think we need Fadel’s help with this.
You want me to talk to Bison about your ex?
Not my ex.
But I did sleep with him.
How many times?
Once.
I was single so I slept around a bit.
But now your brother is the only one I’m serious about.
He gets furiously jealous.
James is a bookie.
It could be dangerous for Bison.
How can I even help?
I can’t exactly stop him.
But this isn’t bad, either,
he needs to see your true colors.
Won’t you help him out?
You’re my boyfriend, you know?
If you like me at all,
you have to help my friend.
Fine.
I’ll help.
But I can’t promise you anything, alright?
Of course, brother.
Good job, buddy.
But…
Once my brother makes up his mind about something,
even I can’t stop him.
He’s a mad dog.
Yo, anyone wanna try this?
Yeah, ain’t no way.
Don’t you even think about it.
(Yeah?)
Where are you?
At some larb place.
(Liar.)
(You can’t handle spicy food.)
Why’d you be at some larb place?
Tell me where you are.
I’m just running some errand.
Don’t worry.
I’m your brother.
Of course I have to worry.
I’m with some friends.
Bye.
Bison.
Bison!
What did he say?
Where is he?
He didn’t tell me where.
But I heard some people watching football.
Football…
Shit.
I have to go.
Thanks, big brother.
Wow.
I hope you’re not the jealous type like your brother is.
If you mean well, then you have nothing to worry about.
But if you’re just leading me on,
or trying to get something out of me,
you’re in for some serious bruises.
ZEUS
10K on Liverpool.
Oh?
It’s you.
Kant’s boy.
What’s your name again?
Bison?
What a freaking name.
Might as well be named “buffalo.”
What?
You’re going behind his back to gamble?
Are you putting up a good act for his sake?
I’ll let you in on a secret…
Kant is a freaking douchebag.
The good guy mask ain’t gonna stay on forever.
I’m not trying to be a good guy.
I’m here to talk to you.
You’re pretty crazy, huh,
to show up here on my turf?
Didn’t pick you for a jealous boyfriend.
Kant is one thing.
But I’m here to tell you to stop following me.
Think I didn’t notice?
What are you, an amateur stalker?
If you knew, why didn’t you tell Kant anything?
Because that’s not my business.
I was waiting for you to reveal yourself.
I looked you up.
You’re just a bookie at a shady betting house.
I have nothing to be scared of.
I’ll let Kant deal with you in his part.
But on my part,
you have to stop following me.
Bison!
You wanna try me, huh?
Well?
Here.
We’re in for some big win tonight.
Choose well, brother. We don’t do refunds, you know?
Otto.
Oh, Kant.
You said you quit betting. Why are you here?
Where’s James?
I need to talk to him.
James?
He went outside
with someone I don’t know.
Small, petite guy.
Same one I told you about.
Who scored that?
Oh, Kant?
Kant!
No need to wipe so hard.
If you’re impatient about Ruerat,
don’t be.
We can handle it.
You and I are in this boat together.
Ruerat is the last jerk we have to kill.
After that, we can live however we want.
But besides this Ruerat thing,
what the hell did you do?
What?
What are you talking about?
I’m talking about Kant’s ex hookup.
What did you do to him?
How did you know that?
Did Kant tell you?
He was afraid you would do something stupid.
Well?
What did you do to him?
You wanna try me, huh?
Well?
Do you?
I’m sorry. I didn’t mean to offend you.
Don’t kill me.
If you don’t stop,
your resting place is down there on the floor.
Alright.
I promise to stop following you and Kant.
What got you so hung up on him?
Did he promise you something?
No, he didn’t
He was just good to me when I had no one.
When I was down and out,
he was the only one who kept me alive.
He gave me money to get by.
I just couldn’t help but fall for him.
You stupid jerk.
Just ’cause he felt sorry for you doesn’t mean he loved you.
I will disappear from him now.
I swear.
Please don’t kill me.
Fine.
I won’t.
But you have to get lost.
And don’t tell Kant about this.
If I see your face again,
I’m putting one of these bullets through your skull.
Understood?
Okay.
See?
I dealt with him with calm and clarity.
I talked things out with him.
What’s the gunshot for, then?
Showing off?
I had to show him it ain’t no prop, right?
I don’t want to interfere.
But we’re asking for a break from work,
so be careful what you do.
Don’t cause trouble.
Yes, Dad.
You little shithead…
Hey.
I went looking for James at his workplace and his house.
But he wasn’t there.
You think that’s weird?
Maybe he just went out of town.
Don’t forget he’s neck deep in debts.
I don’t think it has anything to do with Bison.
You’re way too optimistic.
Did you forget what they are?
He’s a hitman.
I know that.
I was sleeping with his brother last night
all because you asked me to, didn’t I?
Yeah.
But I don’t want anyone else risking their lives.
I have to get this job done.
Come to think of it.
How would I even get through this?
I compromised my whole body,
and if we’re being honest,
I’ve already compromised half of my heart, too.
I’m beginning to worry about him now.
Don’t fall in love with him at all costs.
You’re one to talk
when Bison has you wrapped around his finger.
I know.
That’s why I’m trying to end things quickly.
Once those two get arrested,
we walk free.
Holy crap.
Hope it ends before either one of us kicks the bucket.
I shouldn’t have put my heart on the line for this.
Can you ask Fadel out on a double date tonight?
You don’t have to do anything.
Just make sure he stays with you at all times.
What are you gonna do?
Making use of my Fast and Furious skills once more.
What’s with your t-shirts?
It’s our team jerseys.
We invited you out for a bowling match.
Of course we have teams, right?
What’s KB?
Kant and Bison.
Here I’ve got F and S.
Fadel and Style.
I put your name first, you know?
You like that?
Do you like it?
Of course.
Blue is my favorite color.
Okay.
Noted. Blue is your favorite color.
I’m going to get changed.
Let’s go, Fadel.
No can do.
What now?
I agreed to a date.
I didn’t say I’d do everything you guys want to do.
Ugh.
What a killjoy.
I customized this shirt for you, you know?
How’d you know what size I wear?
I’ve touched you enough to know what your sizes are.
Come on.
Please.
We can’t have an S without his F.
F stands for ‘Fadel,’ not ‘fail,’ you know?
Come on, Fadel.
You’re here.
Might as well just go for it.
Fine.
But I’m taking it off as soon as we’re done.
Alright.
Take it off at my place.
Style, you.
Be right back.
Fadel!
Whoa!
I threw a strike, too!
I kinda feel bad, you know?
For asking your friend to hit on my brother just so we could go out.
But on the other hand, I’m glad I did.
I haven’t seen him so happy in a long time.
Your friend won’t dump him, will he?
I can’t say, to be honest.
But he did tell me he really likes your brother.
He said your brother is weird and off-putting.
Cool.
Hey.
Did you think I’d hurt James?
What do you take me for?
You even went to Fadel to stop me?
I remember how crazy you went at that PE teacher.
I was worried about you.
And…
I want you to trust me.
No matter how bad my past was,
I just want to be a better man for you now.
Stop that.
I wasn’t going to hurt him, you know?
I just wanted to talk to him.
He had been following us for a while.
Just be open with me about everything.
Finding out by myself later kinda hurts.
Okay.
I promise to tell you everything.
I’m okay now.
Come on.
What are you doing?
No way.
It’s embarrassing.
Embarrassing?
You weren’t embarrassed dancing at that host club.
What are you doing?
What dance is this?
Stay over at my place tonight.
Your brother and my buddy look good together.
I’d say they’re the perfect match.
I don’t need your accolade.
Even if I let him in now,
I still don’t trust him.
A guy like me doesn’t go trusting someone 100%.
Oh?
Not even me?
You’re at 80% at best.
I feel like you’re hiding something from me in the rest 20%.
What are you talking about?
What do I have to do to gain your complete trust?
It’ll never happen.
No matter how much you love someone,
I just don’t believe
that you can completely lay yourself bare in front of them.
You’re a difficult man, indeed.
Let’s sing.
For funsies.
No.
I don’t want to.
Go for it if you want.
What’s with you?
No one actually pays attention, you know?
This place is full of drunk people.
Let’s do it.
Let’s go.
No.
Quickly. Come on.
This song is a must.
Come on.
Hey, Babe, what’s up?
What?
Assaulted?
Are you alright?
Who did this?
Those jerks again?
I’ll be there.
Go hide.
What happened?
Babe got ganged up on by his bullies at school.
He’s hiding right now.
Is he okay?
I don’t know.
But I have to go.
I’m coming with you.
No.
I’ll be back in a bit.
I want to go with you.
I gotta deal with those kids.
I don’t want you risking yourself for me again.
Kant.
Do you want me to go with you?
No.
You guys stay here.
This is about my brother so I’ll deal with it.
We’re here to have fun.
Don’t let me be a killjoy.
I’ll deal with it quickly and be right back.
Be careful.
I’ll be right back.
Now that’s more like it.
He finally looks like someone trustworthy for once.
I’m going to Kant’s place.
He’s been gone too long.
He’ll be here soon.
I’ll call him.
I already did and he didn’t pick up.
I’m worried.
I’ll just wait for him at home.
I want to check out if Babe is alright, too.
He must be shaken.
Sure.
See you tomorrow.
Be careful.
Wait, you’re not coming home tonight?
Okay.
(The mad buffalo is heading to your place.)
Hey.
Kant.
Hey!
You scared me.
Sorry.
You carry a gun?
Fadel told me to.
We recently had a burglar.
What are you doing here?
I told you I’d meet you back at the bowling alley.
I came to see you.
You didn’t pick up any of my calls.
I got worried.
Sorry. My phone is dead.
Carry around a portable charger.
I don’t like it when you don’t answer my calls.
Okay.
It’s well noted.
How are you, Babe?
I’m alright.
They were ganging up on me.
If it was one on one, I might have taken them.
Kant made it in time.
Good.
Tell us when something happens, alright?
Of course.
Excuse me.
Did I scare you?
You think Babe knows you and I are dating?
I think he guessed as much.
Well…
Can I stay over?
Please?
Of course.
But let’s not be loud tonight.
I’ll cover your mouth if you’re loud.
I like that.
Hey.
Wait, you have a tattoo there?
I never saw it before.
This one?
My first tattoo, actually.
I did it myself.
But it turned out super ugly.
I’ve been thinking about getting another one over it.
Don’t.
It’s not ugly at all.
I think it’s pretty,
with its own story.
I love every story on your body.
Careful.
You know,
I’m really lucky to have met you.
I can feel that my life is about to change.
You know,
it feels so weird
every time I’m with you.
How so?
Sometimes you make me feel so scared,
and sometimes you make me feel so safe.
It wouldn’t hurt to be wary of me.
Like I said,
no one can truly lay themselves bare for someone.
The real me
might be scarier than you think.
Will you lay yourself bare for me?
I promise that no matter who you are,
I’ll still like you.
Words are cheap.
I’ll do that when you’re ready.
You can judge, then.
One day,
I’ll be your 100%.
I just hope you don’t get any new scars.
If you got everything you wanted,
I guess we’re done here.
Who said we are?
Let’s get this revenge for our parents.
And we can finally start dating without worries.
If they really did strike tomorrow,
and Captain arrested them,
what would we do?
Are you saying tonight is the last time I’d see him?
There are only two options.
If we can’t stop them,
we might as well have the time of our lives tonight.
Babe!