(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
[Fate Chooses You]
[Episode 8]
What are you doing?
Honestly, watch where you're going.
Don't drink the water.
It's poisoned!
Don't drink the water!
Why did he fall?
Is it really poisoned?
You should stay away from
a person like him.
Look, he fainted.
That guy was acting crazy just now.
There must be something wrong
with his mind.
Did he scare you?
No.
Thank you.
Stay away from
this kind of person in the future.
And don't ever be like last time—
walking into any shady roadside inn
in the middle of nowhere,
drinking whatever strangers hand you.
You really don't remember me?
What a bad memory!
Wait,
what's wrong with you?
Are you okay?
Looks like someone is resting inside.
Let's go in.
What's wrong?
Let's go.
No.
Do you really know me?
I am a bounty guard of
Dongzhou Prefecture.
I am here on official business.
We just happened to meet.
You are just a minor cultivator,
but you are quite on guard.
You know I'm a cultivator?
It's going to rain.
Let's go inside.
Come in.
[Li Si]
It's so windy.
I'm afraid there will be
heavy rain tonight.
Let's go.
Let's go sit inside.
[Lyu Yunsu]
The rain in these mountains
will easily make you sick
if you get soaked.
Sir, this young lady
by your side
doesn't look too well.
Could she have caught a chill?
Do you want something hot
to warm up?
No, thanks.
We brought our own food.
Thanks for your kindness.
You're welcome.
Thank you.
Do you want some water?
I don't want water.
I'll throw up if I drink it.
You're so weird.
You don't throw up when you eat pancakes,
but throw up just from drinking water.
What exactly do you want to do here?
I'm telling you, don't drag me into this.
My sect has rules.
We aren't allowed to
interfere in worldly affairs.
There are so many people here.
Even if you wanted to interfere,
you probably couldn't.
The wind is really strong today.
Maybe no one will come tonight.
That's hard to say.
Recently, merchant traffic along this road
has been unusually heavy—
more than 10 times the usual amount.
And this house
is the only place within 20 miles
where people can take shelter
from the rain.
Didn't we all happen to
come here by coincidence?
This place is in Hanzhou.
Bandits have been frequent
in recent years.
It's sparsely populated and desolate.
When I came here a few years ago,
it was still in ruins.
I didn't expect that recently,
the trade here
would become so busy—
actually even more active
and connected than before.
As for the reason...
Have you ever heard of
the Gongshan Jade Tablet
and the Immortality Pill?
Who doesn't know
about such heavenly treasures?
You should know that 50 years ago,
the divine doctor Su Taiyi
of Chongling Valley
announced to the public
that he could refine an immortal elixir
called the Immortality Pill
that could make people live forever.
Once the word got out,
the world was shocked.
All the major immortal sects
undoubtedly grabbed onto
a lifeline.
More than that.
Immortality used to
be the privilege of gods
and the ultimate goal
for many cultivators.
Now, no matter who it is,
as long as they take a pill,
they can achieve it.
Do you think those high officials
and nobles
and the royal relatives of
secular dynasties don't want it?
Thus,
various forces
exhausted all kinds of rare treasures
and spared no effort
to help Chongling Valley
refine the elixir.
In order to thank everyone
for their kindness,
Su Taiyi made 30 pieces of
Gongshan Jade Tablets.
They were distributed
according to each faction's
level of contribution.
It was said that
when it started to be forged,
those holding a tablet could
exchange it for the medicine
—and share immortality with the world.
Share immortality?
Easier said than done.
Is this immortality
something everyone can get?
Sir, I wonder,
if you also want immortality.
I am an official,
yet I can't even
afford a new pair of boots.
How could a treasure like that
ever fall to someone like me?
That's a pity.
Fifty years have passed,
and the Immortality Pill
is about to be forged.
Many disciples from immortal sects
and officials from secular dynasties
are passing through here
with the Gongshan Jade Tablet.
If you are interested,
you can wander around this road.
Maybe you can pick one up.
Pick one up?
Such a treasure is worth more than a life.
Who would lose it?
Fifty years have passed,
and things have changed a lot.
Many prominent families
and immortal sects of the past
have declined.
The things in their hands
naturally fell into the mortal world.
For such unowned items,
whoever picks them up owns them.
My surname is Chen.
I am a merchant.
Sir, may I ask,
since you are here
in your official uniform,
are you here to handle a case?
Indeed, I have a case to handle.
But whether it can be done
depends on whether everyone here
is willing to cooperate.
Sir, you must be joking.
Is it funny?
I am someone
who is terrible at telling jokes.
Is it really funny?
I see you are dressed well,
and your accompanying guards
are all highly skilled.
I wonder
what kind of business you are in.
Jiangnan is rich in silkworms
and fine silk.
I'm simply taking advantage of the trend
to make a living in the silk trade.
in the silk trade.
Silk business?
Such delicate items
are left out in the rain?
When I just entered,
I saw that the carriage outside
was not even covered with cowhide.
You are truly
an "excellent" businessman.
You look familiar.
Where are you from?
Lingnan.
Lingnan?
Recently in Lingnan,
there was a major case.
A group of escorts who lost their goods
killed their employer's family.
They even set a fire
and burned down the employer's house.
I wonder if you've heard about it.
Lingnan is a huge place.
We are ill-informed
and haven't heard of it.
Is that so?
What a pity.
A pity about what?
It's a pity that before I left,
I had already taken another bounty mission
and had other
official business to attend to.
Otherwise, I could've accompanied you all
to Lingnan myself—
to see whether,
on that scorched patch of earth,
there are wronged spirits
crying for justice at night,
or vengeful ghosts
coming to collect their debts.
It seems this old gentleman
has something to say.
I'm just an old man.
I live by the weather
and survive off the land.
What could I possibly have to say?
Don't sell yourself short.
The names of Xiyu Sword
and Shuangfeng Scissors
are known to everyone
in the martial arts world.
I have taken the bounty on you two
three times already,
but never had the chance to meet you.
Even in my dreams at night,
I think about your heads.
Everyone,
this one's a tough target.
Care to lend a hand?
Fine.
First, let's kill the hound of
the authorities,
then we'll deal with the cargo owner.
As for how to split the loot,
we can discuss that
after we finish them off.
I told you
that we can't interfere in
worldly affairs.
Who asked you to interfere?
You just sit tight.
Once I deal with them,
I'll cook noodles for you using his pot.
Do you want to live or die?
Are you also here to catch me?
Don't you know
what crime you committed?
Falling into my hands
is better than dying by their swords,
right?
Miss.
I thought you were fragile,
but I didn't expect you
to have such internal strength.
Are you also here to snatch
the Gongshan Jade Tablet?
Although I have no intention
to fight with you,
I cannot bear to see the weak suffer.
This lady hasn't provoked you.
You do your grabbing.
Why hurt her?
In some desolate mountain inn,
where would a merciful Bodhisattva
like you come from?
Let me use these scissors
to cut open her belly
and see
if she has
a black heart.
Give them the jade tablet.
I don't need to be cured.
If I give it to them, you will die.
Miss, you bravely intervened.
I am willing to entrust
the jade tablet I carry to you.
I only beg you
to take my young lady
to Chongling Valley.
Please,
let him go.
Miss.
She is a pitiful girl.
I feel a bit reluctant now.
Since you don't dare to do it,
why not give this opportunity
to me?
You don't look that good,
but you have a beautiful dream.
Sir,
you just said
you were not interested in
this Gongshan Jade Tablet.
Why did you go back on your word?
I am indeed not interested.
But I have to take this man
and the Gongshan Jade Tablet
on him.
Thief Li Si
stole the Gongshan Jade Tablet
of Lord Ling's Mansion.
The bounty is 20 taels of gold.
Since I took this bounty,
I must take you back.
I cannot go with you.
That's not up to you.
Together. Go!
Go! Hurry!
Honey,
let's go!
Go!
Can you escape?
You two black-hearted old killers,
since you
met me today,
how can I leave you alive?
Are you the Lord of Rust-Sword?
Exactly.
When you get to the underworld,
don't forget to tell the King of Hell
that I gave you this fate.
What do you want?
I can go back with you.
That's right.
But not the Gongshan Jade Tablet.
My young lady suffers from heart failure.
Medicine cannot cure it.
She needs
the Immortality Pill to cure her illness.
Everyone has their own difficulties.
But I am a bounty guard,
only responsible for catching thieves
and recovering stolen goods.
You don't need to tell me this.
My young lady
is the daughter
of General Lyu Jing.
[Chongling Valley]
Greetings, Grandmaster.
Are you
Zhu Yu?
[Zhu Yu of Chongling Valley]
Yes.
You are so old now.
I have no immortal perception
and cannot cultivate.
However,
I haven't seen you
for 50 years.
I'm already 62 now.
My physical body
is maintained entirely by elixirs,
so it looks quite "young".
Where is Su Taiyi?
The Immortality Pill
is about to be finished.
Master is in seclusion refining the elixir
on Mount Jiujue.
In seclusion refining the elixir?
Then why did he write
to call me back?
I wouldn't dare deceive you, Grandmaster.
Actually, in recent years,
Master has been looking for you.
No matter where he heard news,
as long as it sounded like you,
Master would send a letter.
This time, he heard
that someone in the capital stood
against the immortal sect Heavenly Talent.
Master wrote a letter as usual.
He didn't hold much hope at first.
But unexpectedly,
it really is you.
After you, Grandmaster.
[Jiujue Cave]
What is the meaning of this?
The Immortality Pill
is about to be finished.
Master needs to go all out.
To prevent scoundrels from coveting it,
Master specifically ordered me
to completely seal this door.
It's sealed quite tightly.
Is it useful?
It is.
A dragon-severing stone
was also set up inside the cave.
It can only be opened from the inside.
If anyone
tries to attack by force from the outside,
this entire mountainside will collapse.
By then, both the pill
and the people will be destroyed,
leaving nothing behind.
This Su Taiyi...
What's wrong?
Why are you sighing?
I'm afraid I won't be able to solve
this case of mine.
Why?
She's Lyu Jing's daughter.
Who is Lyu Jing?
He was a general
who guarded the border of
Beixiang for many years.
He was very brave and skilled in battle.
The year before last,
in the battle against
the barbarians at Laozhuang Station,
he led 2,000 soldiers
to defend the city for three months.
They ran out of food
and ammunition, and died of exhaustion.
I heard that the enemies thought
he was a cultivator
and wanted to
find his immortal perception.
But after cutting open his corpse,
they found that his stomach
was full of grass roots, tree bark,
and undigested incense ash.
General Lyu Jing
guarded the border for years.
His parents died early,
and his wife passed away.
I heard he only had one daughter,
who is mute.
I didn't expect it to be her.
What illness did that guy say
she has?
Heart failure.
Good people don't live long.
Is Beixiang always at war?
Do you know why I don't like
you cultivators?
Why?
You seem to be like us,
but also different.
It's like you live in another world.
We have our own rules too.
Must rules always be followed?
Of course.
What if the rules are wrong?
Every disciple
who enters the immortal sect
must follow this rule.
The immortal sects have been passed down
for thousands of years.
If everyone could
do whatever they want,
the world would have been
in chaos long ago.
So sometimes,
even if you don't like it
or don't understand it,
you have to comfort yourself,
telling yourself the rules can't be wrong.
Is that what they told you,
or do you actually believe it?
To our dynasty, General Lyu Jing
was a hero who defended our country.
But in the eyes of the enemy,
he was a fierce and terrifying opponent.
When the standpoint changes,
the mind changes with it.
In this world,
nothing is absolutely infallible.
Like the sword in my hand,
it looks ordinary,
but it is the greatest sword in the world.
I firmly believe this.
But do you think
I am right?
Forget it.
After today,
just pretend we never met.
♪ Spending a lifetime,
I ask myself what I first sought ♪
♪ What is it my heart truly desires ♪
Must rules always be followed?
What if the rules are wrong?
♪ Step by step up the immortal stairway ♪
To our dynasty, General Lyu Jing
♪ I hear the shame of parting ♪
was a hero defending our country.
But to the enemy,
♪ This immortal path admired by all ♪
he was a fierce and terrifying opponent.
♪ Can exist, or not exist ♪
When standpoints change,
mind change with them.
In this world,
♪ Once again I see
the world's cold indifference ♪
there is nothing absolutely infallible.
♪ Bending what I've cherished
all my life ♪
♪ Illusions and vanity blind the eyes,
how could one still care ♪
♪ Once again I see
the world's cold and heat ♪
♪ If no one shares
its sorrow and suffering ♪
♪ This path will only turn against
immortal laws and restraint ♪
Why are you still awake?
For me?
Thank you.
I throw up when I drink water,
but eating flatbread is fine.
Eating pears should be okay, too.
Thank you for today.
It's nothing.
You are a cultivator.
By the way,
are you going
to Chongling Valley next?
I happen to be going there as well.
We can travel together.
I...
I threw up when I drank water before.
I didn't expect I couldn't even eat pears.
I wasted your kindness.
Get some rest soon.
We have to hit the road tomorrow.
I'm fine.
What does this mean?
Thank you.
Get some rest.
Let's part ways here.
Part ways here.
Next time we meet,
don't fail to recognize me again.
Part ways here.
Why do you believe that sword
is the best sword in the world?
The sword seller told me.
You believe him?
I believe in myself.
Farewell!
Here.
Stop.
[Zhang Dahu]
Over here.
Let's go take a look.
Are you heading to Chongling Valley?
Yes.
Finally, you're here.
Are you from Chongling Valley?
Yes, I am.
Then you are here to...
I came specially to pick you up.
Let me briefly introduce it to you.
The healers in Chongling Valley
are mainly divided into 13 branches:
major internal medicine,
minor internal medicine,
wind disorders, obstetrics, ophthalmology,
reproductive disorders,
miscellaneous medicine, dentistry,
throat medicine,
bone-setting, acupuncture,
incantation therapy,
and trauma and swelling treatment.
What kind of illness
are you here to treat?
Can't hear, or can't speak?
Can't speak.
That would fall under throat medicine.
Or possibly the ear
and eye obstruction branch.
Miss, how long have you
had this condition?
No.
It's heart failure.
Heart failure?
Wait a minute. Heart failure...
Heart disease and chest pain.
You need to find Dr. Zhu for this.
He's good at treating this.
Doesn't she need the Immortality Pill?
Why would you need an elixir for this?
What kind of place
do you think Chongling Valley is?
It's a sanctuary for patients,
a palace for healers.
Every single one of them
is a master healer.
No matter what illness,
it will definitely be cured.
So Chongling Valley
can cure Miss Lyu's heart disease?
Absolutely.
Otherwise, why would you come
all the way here?
Put your mind at ease.
It's definitely a worthwhile trip.
Great.
You must be exhausted from the journey.
How about this?
I'll drive,
and you take a rest.
We couldn't possibly.
Don't mention it.
Once you're in Chongling Valley,
make yourselves at home.
By the way,
let me introduce myself.
My surname is Zhang.
Zhang Dahu.
Just call me buddy Zhang.
Thank you, buddy Zhang.
No problem.
Let's go.
Is it okay to put the carriage
here?
Don't worry.
Someone will look after it.
That's quite thoughtful.
Follow me.
Everyone,
please get on the boat.
With such a small boat,
and so many of us taking it,
will it be unsafe?
What if we fall into the water?
Don't worry, I take the boat every day.
Besides,
my reputation as a great swimmer
isn't for nothing.
No matter who falls into the water,
I can fish them out.
Let's go.
Miss, come.
Slow down.
Careful.
Take it easy.
Let's go!
Miss, are you okay?
Slow down.
It's fine.
We'll be there soon.
Senior Brother,
we agreed on this before.
Okay, okay.
I brought everyone.
Let them in.
Wait.
How did their carriage get in?
Look here.
I already got the number tag.
Come, please step inside.
You two,
let's have tea someday.
Okay.
Why aren't they lining up?
You should
respect the order of arrival.
Exactly.
Why can they cut in line?
They
already got a number tag at 3 AM.
Anyone with a number tag
can enter directly.
How can this be?
Young Master, we are here.
How could they get it in advance?
When can we go in?
Alas.
We need to walk faster.
If we make it in time,
we can still have a meal at Cunsu Hall.
Thank you for your trouble.
Thanks.
Don't mention it.
This is what I do.
Let's go.
[Zhu Yu: 7th-rank apothecary,
expert in heart disease]
With so many people here,
how long do we have to wait?
The medicine boy just said
we'll get our turn before noon.
Let's wait a bit more.
It's all sorted. Come inside and wait.
This is our number tag.
Hold it well.
We'll wait here.
When we're called later,
we just go in.
Do we also need to wait here?
Yes.
It'll be our turn soon.
After they call us,
let Dr. Zhu
examine her carefully.
We are here to participate...
What could be more important than life?
Let's treat her illness first.
That is true.
But...
No buts.
You wait here.
I'll go get you some water.
Wait for me.
What illness are you here
to see a doctor about?
Lung abscess.
Sorry to bother you.
You know Grand Tutor Rong, right?
I saw him being carried in,
almost dying.
And guess what happened?
Dr. Zhu saved him.
Dr. Zhu is really amazing.
Absolutely.
Dr. Zhu is the direct disciple
of the miraculous physician Su.
He has inherited all of Su's
true medical teachings.
Everyone,
you don't have to line up here.
You can come over
when your number is called.
It's the same.
I will call everyone's number.
I definitely won't leave anyone out.
Tea is prepared in the side hall.
You can go there to rest.
Excuse me...
Miss,
[Chongling Valley – Huaiqing]
how can I help you?
We are here to participate in
the Pill-Tasting Competition.
Do we need to line up here too?
Cultivators?
Yes.
Cultivators.
Cultivators don't line up here.
Next.
Number Jiachen may go in now.
Ma'am,
you're number Jiachen;
it's your turn for treatment now.
Okay.
Here.
Let me help you.
We have to hurry up.
Something doesn't seem right.
Excuse me,
why did you leave?
We are here to participate in
the Pill-Tasting Competition.
It's not here.
Pill-Tasting...
You are cultivators.
Cultivators have to pay too.
Pay for what?
You...
Taking the boat, guiding, getting numbers,
seeing the doctor,
you have to pay for all of them.
But
we didn't see the doctor.
You took the boat.
Does everyone have to pay?
Of course. What am I working for?
Here you are.
Is it enough?
Enough.
So cultivators can be reasonable too?
Since you've paid,
no taking it back.
No.
I want to ask where
the Pill-Tasting Competition is.
Longevity Hall.
Turn right,
and keep going up.
Okay, thanks.
Are you
also here
for the Pill-Tasting Competition?
My master is Xin Xiong. I am Xin Mei.
[Wang Yanqing
of the Wang family of Jinqiu]
Let's go up together then.
What's the matter, Miss?
May I ask, sir,
did you also come by boat?
What boat?
The boat to cross the river.
Why take a boat?
How else do you cross the river
without a boat?
There is a bridge.
Is there a bridge?
There is a bridge?
Lu,
when we came over just now,
I saw many immortal sects
coming to participate in the upcoming
Pill-Tasting Competition.
Do you think
Immortal Xin might have come too?
With her limited skills,
she shouldn't be sent to
participate in such an important event.
With Su Taiyi's character,
can he actually lock himself
in the valley all the time
to refine pills?
I just don't believe it.
Where are you going?
[In the desolate void]
[Where can one seek immortality?]
[Healing the World]
[Mr. Baiyun of Lingxu Sect]
[Cai En of Zigai Mountain]
[Zhi Bocheng,
Transit Commissioner of Jingzhou]
[Master Fu of Qingshan Sect]
[Longevity Hall]
Where are the people from Tianyuan Sect's
Solar and Lunar Cavern
and Xiaoyao Sect?
Master Gongyu from
the Solar and Lunar Cavern
is on his way.
He will activate the formation later
and project his image here.
Xiaoyao Sect is in Beixiang.
It's a long journey,
so they should be on their way too.
Did Tianyuan Sect inform anyone
when they will arrive?
Why are you looking at me?
How would I know
that Tianyuan Sect isn't coming?
I think
they encountered some accident on the way
and can't make it.
Why isn't Su Taiyi here yet?
My master is at Mount Jiujue,
cultivating in seclusion to refine pills.
It has reached the final stage.
It is crucial and allows no mistakes,
so he couldn't come in person.
How many pills
will this first furnace produce?
I'm not sure.
Then when will the Divine Doctor Su
come out of seclusion?
I don't know.
You don't know this or that.
Then why did you summon us here?
I gathered you all here today
mainly to count
the Gongshan Jade Tablets in your hands
and to distribute
the Immortality Pills next.
Senior Brother Zhu Yu
is in charge of this.
Zhu Yu?
Where is he?
Senior Brother Zhuyu
is still seeing patients at Suwen Hall
and will be here shortly.
[Su Taiyi of Chongling Valley]
Come.
Master,
everything is ready.
Good.
The Immortality Pill is not refined yet.
You are early, sir.
Master, Uncle Chu Ying,
you scared me to death.
I thought you were assassins.
Aren't you always extremely bold?
Are you still afraid of assassins?
I'm getting older.
Master, Uncle Chu Ying,
please come in.
My Lady.
Have you stared enough?
I'm sorry, Master Gongyu.
My friend is not a cultivator.
He doesn't know the rules here.
Then tell him
what he should do
and what he shouldn't do.
Who is he?
Master Gongyu
of the Solar and Lunar Cavern.
He has a bad temper.
Everyone is here to use
the Gongshan Jade Tablet
to exchange for the Immortality Pill?
Were their Gongshan Jade Tablets
also given by Chongling Valley?
Not exactly.
Back then,
the Twelve Immortal Sects fully supported
Divine Physician Su
in establishing Chongling Valley,
saving lives
and refining the Immortality Pill.
Later, based on each sect's contribution,
a total of 30
Gongshan Jade Tablets were distributed,
to be used for exchange
when the pills were ready.
With the rise of new forces
and the decline of old ones,
many Gongshan Jade Tablets
have changed hands many times.
So,
you have one too?
Yes.
Then which of the Twelve Immortal Sects
are you from?
I...
You came with her,
but don't know which sect she's from?
She's from the famous Xin Xie Manor
among the Twelve Immortal Sects.
Master, be careful.
Master, come, let me do it.
Your place is called Jiujue Cave?
Master.
Don't you have a powerful
and bloodthirsty
divine weapon, the Jiujue Sword?
I just borrowed its name
to call this place Jiujue Cave.
Sound mighty?
You are living a good life.
Where is the Immortality Pill?
There,
it's burning.