ADAPTED FROM THE NOVEL HIDDEN LOVE BY ZHU YI
Are you done?
I'm going to wash the towel.
Why didn't he give me a heads-up
before he opened his eyes?
He could've said,
"I'm going to open my eyes,"
and then opened them.
He suddenly opened them.
What the heck?
He gave me a scare.
Are you done?
Jiaxu.
I think you should get some rest.
Leave work for tomorrow.
Okay, in a bit.
Sorry, Sang Zhi.
You came all this way to suffer with me.
I don't mind.
Don't move.
I can handle it.
I'll turn the lights off.
Okay.
Here.
Use this pillow.
My clothes are over there.
Cover yourself with them
so you don't get cold.
Let's sleep.
WEIWEI
THE OTHER PARTY HAS CANCELED
DORM 202 GIRLS' GROUP
SANGSANG, ARE YOU OKAY?
CONTACT US WHEN YOU SEE THIS.
I'M HERE
I have a brother…
I have a relative
who is ill.
I won't be coming back tonight.
Don't worry about me.
JIANG MING
Sang Zhi, I'm outside the theater.
Are you here yet?
You can't sleep?
Do you need to finish listening to the voice message?
Jiaxu, why did you pretend to be asleep?
I was just quiet.
I didn't pretend to be asleep.
That is pretending to be asleep.
You were even eavesdropping.
Eavesdropping?
You're the one who played the message.
You're making false claims at such a young age.
I'm not talking to you anymore.
I'm going to sleep. Good night.
Can you fall asleep?
It's time for bed either way.
Come on.
Chat with me.
About what?
Finish playing that voice message.
Let me see
who wants to ask you out to a movie.
You don't know him.
I will once you tell me about him.
I'll judge him for you.
Why? We're just going to the movies.
I'm just worried you're naïve and might get played.
Well, I could spend all night
talking about guys.
There are so many of them.
Our Sang Zhi is so popular.
It's because I'm pretty.
Why isn't he saying anything?
Jiaxu.
Look.
People your age should be asleep
at this hour.
Don't always try to pry into the lives of young people.
You don't understand our world.
You won't get it
even if I tell you about it.
Fine.
I don't know anything.
It's all done.
Thank you, Sang Zhi.
Jiaxu, I'm going to class.
Let me know if you need anything.
I'll bring it tonight.
Perfect.
Go to my place
and get my laptop from my study.
The keys are in my jacket pocket.
I'll send you the address later.
What do you need the laptop for?
For work, of course.
But you're ill.
You should focus on resting.
Even if you do your work now,
your boss won't pay you extra.
It's too bad. I live for tech.
Got it.
But I still won't bring the laptop over.
I'll take care of the rest.
What's wrong?
Hearing you lecture me
makes me realize
that our Sang Zhi has grown up.
I am a grown-up.
I'm not a kid anymore.
Did you just realize that?
I'm off.
CHAPTER TEN, JOKE
GIVE ME A REASON TO FORGET
I'm here. Where are you?
Here.
I see you.
Good morning, students.
We meet again.
Where were you?
I can't believe you.
I brought you breakfast.
Eat it later.
Thank you.
How is your relative?
He's done with his surgery.
I think
he should be discharged in a few days.
I'll visit him after class.
Again?
Are you going to accompany him?
Well, I have to do it.
I'm also in Yihe.
I can't push it off to someone else.
Jiang Ming was disappointed that you didn't show up
and kept asking about you.
Chen Qiang told me about the tickets.
-They-- -Ning Wei.
Okay, the homework I assigned last week is due today.
Have you completed it?
The tickets were hard to get.
Two, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Three, two, three, four.
-Sang Zhi! -Five, six, seven, eight.
Four, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven. Stop.
Good morning.
You have sharp eyes.
Right, why didn't you join us
for the movie yesterday?
My relative suddenly fell ill yesterday.
I was taking care of him at the hospital.
Is he all right now?
He's fine now.
I'm sorry I couldn't make it.
But we can catch a movie some other time
when you're free.
Sure.
I'm free next weekend.
Well,
I'll treat you to a movie next weekend.
Okay, then I'll see you next weekend.
Yes. I'm going to warm up now.
-Bye. -Bye.
122 ABNORMALITIES
67.5 ABNORMALITIES
Then the characters are projected
-and the whole scene will-- -Hold on.
Hello, Jiaxu?
Hi, Siyun.
The logic in this part is too wordy.
The program won't run.
I don't have a computer with me right now.
Can you have someone
bring me one from the office?
I'll code this bit.
It's okay.
Focus on recovering.
I'll have them handle the other parts first.
It's fine.
I have nothing to do here anyway.
Jiaxu.
If your wound opens up again,
who is going to work for me?
Rest well.
JIANG YING
VOICE MESSAGE FROM JIANG YING
I'm sorry.
I know I was too emotional.
I'm sorry. I really will change this time.
I will control myself from now on.
Number 158.
Both of you look at the camera.
This must be his mom.
Nice to meet you.
I am Sang Zhi.
I think
he will need underwear.
Wait!
I'm going inside.
Thank you.
Jiaxu, it's me, Jiang Ying.
Jiaxu?
Jiaxu, are you home?
Open up!
Jiaxu.
You're here.
I didn't know you were in the bathroom.
It's okay. I can do it myself.
An old man has occupied the other bed.
He went downstairs for a stroll.
Hot water.
-Thank you. -Careful, it's hot.
You brought a lot of stuff.
It's not that much.
Two sets of clothes.
One is for when you're discharged.
The other can keep you…
Also,
I brought the stuff you wanted.
Thank you.
Jiaxu.
Don't stay up too late working.
You're still recovering.
Okay, I promise you.
Screens off at 10:00 p.m. sharp.
One hour left.
Hello.
-Hello. -Hello.
Have you eaten?
-Here. -Sit.
Not yet. I'll have dinner later.
Not yet?
-Sit. -It's already past eight.
I'm not hungry yet.
Stop putting away things. Go and eat dinner.
In a bit.
I'll order delivery for you.
I went to get your things
right after I finished class.
I haven't even sat down yet,
but you keep telling me to eat.
Why do you keep telling me to eat?
Boy,
is this your wife?
Sir.
How did you come to the conclusion that she is my wife?
She's beautiful.
-Here, Dad. -Okay.
Thank you.
Sir,
this is my sister,
not my wife.
I know your wife is pretty.
Sorry,
my dad is hard of hearing.
Dad, that's his sister,
not his wife.
A brother cannot marry his sister.
Are you two not married yet?
Boy,
you don't look young anymore.
Why aren't you married yet?
Don't keep the young lady waiting.
Sir.
Please stop making me laugh.
I have a wound on my stomach.
Boy, I'm not joking.
You need to get a move on.
Your wife is pretty
and so caring.
Look at her
carrying all these bags here.
You must cherish her
or else, you'll regret it later.
Okay, I understand.
He has poor hearing.
Don't mind him.
Just think of it as a joke.
A joke?
You shouldn't joke about these things.
Sir.
He is not my partner.
He is too old
to be my partner.
He is old enough to be my dad.
It's great to be a dad!
Once you two get married,
hurry up and have a child.
You'll settle down.
That is more important than anything.
I'm going to go eat.
Eat more.
Order more.
Why is your wife leaving?
My wife is going to eat.
To dinner.
That's not something to joke about.
Jiaxu.
Good morning.
Don't tell me you worked all night.
I shouldn't have brought you the laptop.
Jiaxu.
You've been hospitalized.
Why won't you just rest?
Do you really think you are Superman?
You've discovered my hidden identity.
What hidden identity?
How could you stay up all night?
Are you having a lovers' spat so early?
When is the wedding?
Sir,
we're not like that.
We're not getting married.
Are you not getting married?
That won't do!
She's a beautiful girl
and she is taking care of you.
How can you do this to her?
Okay, we'll do as you say.
We'll get married.
That's more like it.
You two are a perfect match.
You will be happy together.
I'll get you some water.
Sir, she's too young.
She's not of legal age yet.
-Stop this joke. -Maybe in two years.
OUTPATIENT BUILDING
Are you discharged?
That's right, sir.
Please rest well and recover soon.
All right. You two get along now, okay?
-Sir. -We will, sir.
We'll get married soon.
That's good!
Get well soon.
Take care of each other.
-Get along. -Let's go.
We're leaving, sir.
Stay together.
"We'll get married soon"?
You're the one who started this joke.
-I'll get that. -I've told you.
I'll carry it.
Are you really upset?
Don't make jokes like that anymore.
Well,
I've been in the hospital for so long.
I was bored.
I apologize.
Does being bored make it okay
to make jokes at my expense?
You're unbelievable.
You can wear my slippers.
I'll take that.
It's okay. I've got it.
Take a seat.
What do you want to drink?
I'm fine.
No need to tidy up.
I'll do it later.
Let's have dinner together later.
I'll see you off after that.
I'm going to use the bathroom.
When I heard your brother say
that you were coming here for university,
I was really happy.
The feelings that I've been hiding
for the past two years
probably
don't mean the same to him.
How old can you be?
You're still a kid.
Come when you don't have classes.
I'm an adult.
Don't trouble yourself for me.
Sir, she's too young.
She's not of legal age yet.
Maybe in two years.
He has poor hearing.
Don't mind him.
Just think of it as a joke.
Maybe in his heart,
we'll never be anything more than brother and sister.
That's why he can make jokes like that.
TAKE THE MEDICINE ON TIME
What are you writing?
Jiaxu.
You need to pay attention to your diet.
You can't have milk or eggs.
But you can eat foods high in fiber
to promote digestion.
Also, try not to sit for too long
while you work.
Get up and walk around for a bit.
But no strenuous exercise.
Don't carry heavy items either.
And…
No staying up late.
I know. Take a break.
Stay home and recuperate for the time being.
If there is anything you need to buy,
you can tell me.
I'll get them for you.
After this,
I have a lot of assignments to complete.
I need to go back and work on them,
so I might not be coming over as often.
One more thing.
You…
I want to treat you to a meal.
We can wait
until you have recovered.
You don't have to do that.
I should be the one treating you now.
Okay.
We'll talk about it later.
I'm leaving.
I'll send you off.
It's okay, Jiaxu.
-I'll go by myself. -I'll take you to the metro.
You don't have to do that.
I can go back on my own.
Bye, Jiaxu.
This is fine.
After all,
I'm just his little sister.
JIAXU
REMARK: JIAXU
EDIT CONTACT DETAILS
BROTHER NO. 2
NO STAYING UP LATE
THAT'S A LITTLE DIFFICULT
EAT ON TIME
I'VE EATEN
NO MILK OR EGGS
EAT FOODS HIGH IN FIBER
DON'T SIT FOR TOO LONG
GET UP AND MOVE, BYE
THE DREAM GAMES
So is that what happened?
I think she might really be upset.
But I can't figure out
the reason.
What's the big deal?
All you did was make a few jokes
to go along with that old man.
Siyun, what do you think?
What goes on in men's heads?
She's a girl.
It's normal for a girl to be upset.
Think about it.
You said she has always been prideful
and thin-skinned.
You joked about her relationship status.
Of course she would be mad.
You even said
she had a boy she liked.
That would surely make her even angrier.
I'm not the one who made the joke.
It was that old man.
She's taking it out on me.
You're clearly an accomplice.
She took care of you.
But you and the old man joked about her.
You're lucky she took care of you
until you were discharged.
I only wanted to indulge the old man.
It's all the same to her. All right?
Let me interrupt you guys.
Did you call Siyun and me over
just because of this problem?
This is such a petty matter.
I thought you had
actual relationship problems.
You had best pray that I don't.
Who else will help you with the game expansion?
Well, thank you.
How about this?
Find some time
and take her out for a meal.
Talk things through with her
and it should be fine.
Also, you should be more careful.
She's an adult now.
You can't joke about everything like before.
Got it.
Siyun is right.
End of counseling.
Get back to work.
I'll get it for you, honey.
Are you…
JIANG YING
Hello?
I told you not to contact me anymore.
Jiaxu, let's meet up.
I called you, but you--
I've told you.
Let's not stay in touch anymore.
So are you just going to abandon me?
Duan Jiaxu.
I'm busy. I'm hanging up.
JIANG YING
Do you want some more?
Are you scared?
No, I love this.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know you were afraid of chickens.
It's okay.
I'm not afraid of anything
except for animals with sharp beaks.
I see.
It was really big.
Do you need to wipe your sweat?
I'll use the restroom.
Okay.