=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 16=
Yan Zhang, Vice Lord of Xuling Temple,
did a great job planning for me.
Give him 10,000 spirit stones.
Farewell, Your Grace.
I haven't seen this sword in ages.
You're the new owner of the Deliverance?
You know
the former owner?
Former owner?
Isn't it just Hejia Jixi,
the forger of this sword
and Simu's aunt?
What?
Simu didn't tell you
the story behind this sword?
Looks like the two of you
aren't very close.
My Lady,
do you know about Simu's parents,
her uncle and aunt?
I got on very well
with them.
When the previous sovereign was here,
he called me Lady Jiang Ai.
Simu calls me
the way her father did.
Then can you tell me
about her childhood?
Young man,
it's not fun to inquire
about the Sovereign's past.
It's not for fun.
I want to know about her.
In that case,
how many spirit stones can you offer?
Spirit stones?
Money of the Void?
Information about the Sovereign
will certainly fetch a good price.
How come I didn't think
of this great business?
Young man,
a discount for you.
Half a million.
When you have enough money,
come to me for her information.
Half a million?
That doesn't sound cheap at all.
You aren't the only one
who adores Simu.
You'd better be careful.
Your Lordship,
we meet again.
You must be
that mortal general.
I heard you brought Her Grace
a lot of fun during her vacation.
Your short stay in the Void
is just a sign of her favor.
It seems your sovereign
speaks highly of me.
I just wanted to see
what Simu's place would look like.
She approved right away.
How dare you
call Her Grace by name?
How Simu and I call each other
is our own business.
You're in no position
to get angry.
How dare you!
The curfew begins.
Enjoy your stay.
(Sovereign's Hall)
I can't believe Simu has lived here
for centuries now.
Only your sovereign can eat me.
(Lake Cottage, the Void)
Didn't expect to find a place like this.
Duan Shunxi, how bold of you.
You fear no place, do you?
I didn't know you were here.
No offense.
Please forgive me.
This place is warded.
How did you get in?
Maybe this cottage likes me
and allowed me in.
Your Grace,
nights here are cold.
You'd really let me stay out?
How did you find me?
There's less
discordant aura here.
The scent of your sachet
is actually stronger.
What have you reflected on so far?
I was thinking.
When I kissed you,
you remained silent
and stared at me.
What were you thinking?
I was thinking,
"When I get my power back,
I'll make you regret it."
Furthermore,
I guess you were also thinking
why I kissed you.
You probably thought
I was lost in passion
and it was a passing fancy.
But soon you realized
that you were wrong.
You realized that I was serious.
So you didn't say anything.
Even today,
you only hung me on the palace gate
to scare me off,
rather than kill me.
Right?
That day, I was really lost in passion.
I thought you were so adorable
and I would never meet another girl
like you.
And I'd never feel the same
for anyone else.
I've calmed down these days
and thought about it.
That's absolutely true.
Young people usually
have fleeting affections.
It's not strange that you like me.
I've seen
a lot of men like you.
Among them,
you're the smartest one.
In that case,
you should think before you speak.
I've thought it over.
No, you haven't.
Do you really know me?
I want to know you.
And I'm getting to know you,
bit by bit.
This room, for example.
I guess it was the room
you once lived in
with your parents.
And the toys on the shelves.
They were your toys.
You shouldn't have come.
(Sovereign's Hall)
♪Falling down like snow♪
♪Joys and sorrows of the mortal world♪
♪Swept along by the daylight♪
♪The forms and hues of the mortal realm♪
♪Lingering for a fleeting moment♪
♪Was once touched by laughing tears♪
♪If I could live a simple life♪
♪For once♪
♪I'd be a guest in a sweet dream♪
♪Dawn and dusk rise and set♪
♪Longing to meet, yet parted by destiny♪
♪Let me wander through♪
♪Light and dark, without turning back♪
You know what?
Her Grace and Lord Yan Ke
are fixing Fusang Tree so early.
Their intimacy
makes us jealous.
Everybody knows their relationship.
Her Grace just hasn't acknowledged him.
♪Whether I stay or go, I'm all alone♪
With your spirit power,
the tree is growing stronger.
Simu, you must be tired.
Get some rest.
All right, Yan.
♪As stars shift and change places♪
♪A century is like a dream♪
♪Let me journey across them all♪
♪Without reincarnations♪
♪A lone lamp shines on the other shore♪
♪Accompanied by the abyss♪
♪Moments may last♪
Your Lordship.
Are you really surprised
to see me alive?
The spirit that attacked me yesterday
had the same aura as yours.
You just can't smell it.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Perhaps we should
talk frankly.
Your Lordship,
however much you hate me,
you shouldn't kill me.
If I died in the Void,
what would become of Simu's honor
and reputation?
You're merely a lowly mortal
and you may die in an instant.
What right do you have
to talk frankly with me?
I'm not a lowly mortal, actually.
I'm the only man the Sovereign
has brought back
in the past 300 years.
In the Spirit World,
only she can kill me.
Then you'd better
keep yourself alive.
Hey, young man.
Oh, it's you.
What do you mean by that?
You should say,
"We meet again."
I was sent here
as your servant.
What happened to you?
Don't mention it.
Song Xingyu
completely ruined me.
Having lost
all my possessions,
I'm now a servant.
So I end up like this.
You brought this upon yourself.
No one is to blame.
Young man,
you're in no position to talk.
I heard
you offended Her Grace
and were hung up there
for humiliation.
I would just be hung for a few days.
Your 600-year-old treasures
are all gone.
What?
Have you heard
of the backside
of the Void Mountain?
Why do you ask?
That's a forbidden area here.
Don't ask around.
Forbidden area?
Yeah.
Only Her Grace is allowed in.
Don't bring it up again.
Does Her Grace
usually live there?
Her Grace certainly has
her own sleeping hall.
Without her permission,
no one can get in.
The curfew will begin.
I'll come tomorrow.
(Zhaomu Pavilion, the Void)
This place isn't your house
where you can go anywhere.
Your Grace,
I'm so sleepy.
Let me get in for a nap.
It's spacious out.
Quite enough for you.
You'd really let me sleep out here?
You really make yourself comfortable.
Get up.
Stop pretending.
Get out of my...
Jiang Ai.
Your Grace.
Lady Jiang Ai.
What's wrong with him?
He's hungry.
A mortal can't live without food.
Time runs the same here.
He hasn't eaten anything for two days.
So he fainted from hunger.
Prepare a meal for him.
You're not really going
to keep him here, are you?
I don't want to keep him here.
But I can't let him die of hunger.
It's not easy to raise a mortal
in our world.
Feeding a mortal
will cost a great many spirit stones.
Whatever amount you need,
I'll approve it.
Simu,
why don't you just
acknowledge him?
He's handsome,
bold and cheerful.
He cares a lot for you.
If you ask me,
he loves you more than anything.
I can't let him stay forever.
When he recovers,
I'll send him back.
I get it.
Since you're awake, come and eat.
I never expected
to see mortal food here.
It's a vast world.
A table of mortal food
isn't exactly rare.
You don't dare?
I can't bear to.
After you're full,
stay here for a rest.
Thank you, Your Grace.
It's where the spirits live.
A mortal shouldn't linger.
Foxy.
You shouldn't have come.
Yan.
Got something to say?
Simu,
when will you
send that mortal away?
What do you think?
The sooner, the better.
Our world is no place for mortals.
And Fusang Tree hasn't recovered.
Spirits are piling up here.
Who knows what will happen?
We have no time
to spare for a mortal's fate.
Your Grace,
this mortal
has caused quite a commotion
inside our world.
If this goes on,
it's hard to tell if there will be
even more chaos.
How could you think
a mere mortal
would destabilize the Void?
If he really can,
I'd like to see.
Your Grace,
that's not what I mean.
Enough.
I have my own plans
about him.
Why did you get up there again?
Your Grace,
you said three days.
It's the last quarter.
You're hopeless.
You won't change anyway.
Get out of my sight.
This is a bitterly cold place.
No mortal can endure that.
He must not stay.
This is not your concern.
The chill here
has even invaded your veins.
You could've told me.
If I had told you,
wouldn't you have
sent me away at once?
Silly man.
What's so funny?
It seems ever since we met,
you've been healing me.
Or do you want to heal me?
No.
I never want you to get hurt.
When the moon is full,
the spirits' desires will grow strong.
These are their painful moans
for unattainable desires.
Scared?
Not really.
It's just a little bit noisy.
In the Void,
living without senses
might be a good thing.
The mortal's senses
will be infinitely amplified here.
You really shouldn't stay.
Life is short.
I want to live my way.
Even if you may die?
Don't be scared, Chang.
I'm getting you out now.
Spare me.
Chang,
you'll be free soon.
Don't be scared, Chang.
Take this decoction
and you'll be all right.
Don't be scared, Chang.
Just don't be scared.
(Zhaomu Pavilion)
Hey, young man.
Maizi.
Her Grace assigned me to serve you.
Young man,
you're the first one to live
in the Sovereign's room
over the centuries.
You're so favored.
If that's the case,
I'm indeed favored.
I've always wanted to ask.
You were a spirit in the Mortal World.
But why are you a mortal
in the Spirit World?
How did you do that?
If you want to know,
take me to Her Grace.
She'll punish the guilty spirit today.
That's too cruel
to watch.
(Execution Platform, the Void)
Fang Chang.
I'm going
to be annihilated, right?
Very well.
He Simu,
bring it on!
All you can do
is annihilate those
who you don't like.
Do you think
this will keep your throne forever?
they'll really obey you?
Everybody wants to replace you
when you're weak.
You only rely
on your mighty power.
A tyrant like you
- deserves to die!
- Fang Chang.
You violated our decrees
to assassinate the Sovereign.
Punishing you by law
is the exact way to uphold justice.
How dare you make wild remarks
to slander Her Grace!
It doesn't matter.
Let him continue.
I'm right here.
If you're able to kill me,
come and kill me.
I thought
you would have
more impressive last words.
Fang Chang, Vice Lord
of Shanling Temple,
colluded with a traitor
to assassinate me.
He violated Article 7
of the Golden-wall Decrees, Treason.
He'll be annihilated now.
Any objections?
He Simu,
I'm not the only one
who wants to kill you.
And him! Him!
All of them!
He Simu,
remember this.
The fate I have today
will be yours tomorrow.
A spirit has no senses.
Why is he in such pain?
That's the pain congealed
from spirit power.
It's a punishment for guilty spirits.
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪