♪Just To Meet You, you fell for me♪
♪Just to meet me, into my trap you fell♪
♪Wanna try a breathless love?♪
♪Every move hits the heart, close and sure♪
♪Just To Meet You, you love my playful charm♪
♪Just to meet me,
my romantic little schemes for you♪
♪Wanna play another brand-new game?♪
♪Layer by layer, we close the gap♪
=Just To Meet You=
=Episode 20=
=Risk It All For You=
I'll check the dressing room.
Mr. Ye Lang,
do you take this woman
to be your wife?
For better or for worse,
for richer or for poorer,
in sickness and in health,
in joy and in sorrow,
to love her without reservation,
to remain faithful to her,
forever and always.
Do you?
I do.
I do, too.
Why you?
Where's Jiang Niannian?
Ye Lang.
The priest already read the vows.
We're husband and wife now.
Why are you still obsessed
with a thrice-married woman?
Answer me!
Where is Jiang Niannian?
You're hurting me, Ye Lang.
Tell me
where she is!
She only brings you scandal and trouble.
I'm different.
I'm the one who's right for you.
Ye Lang, why can't you see that?
I was engaged to Jiang Niannian.
You're the one who's delusional.
Even if there was an engagement,
it should've been between you and me.
Did you forget that auction...
Enough!
I told you before
what happened at the auction was a show.
You just never knew your place.
That's not true.
But for Jiang Niannian,
you would've chosen me!
The only person
I've ever loved is Jiang Niannian.
Jiang Qingqing,
you have no feelings for me either.
You only care about the Li family's wealth.
I'll ask you one last time.
Where did you take Jiang Niannian?
Ye Lang.
How could I not have love for you?
Doesn't loving your money count?
Since you won't choose me,
then go to hell!
Li Hong. What are you trying to do?
I swapped the bride at Ye Lang's wedding.
Your sweet sister heard about it,
and rushed to put on the gown.
Li Hong.
Stop being so stubborn.
You're Li family's Second Young Master.
I'm not being stubborn.
Xue.
I'm doing this for us.
You and Ye Lang
are in the way.
Only by getting rid of you both
can Xue and I be truly happy.
Once you do,
there's no turning back.
I killed Liu Yexi myself.
It's too late.
Oh, right.
And your three ex-husbands.
I killed them too.
Using Liu Yexi's name,
I got them try God No.6.
The side effects made them
die in those "accidents."
So it was you.
I had no choice.
They had my whole business locked down.
And they wanted a bigger cut.
It was a total mess.
If I didn't eliminate them,
how could I build my own power?
Anyway, Liu Yexi is already dead.
With a flick of my finger,
I can make her take the blame.
She lived all those years,
and this is the only thing
she could do for me, isn't it?
Xue,
why don't you praise me?
You've lost your mind.
Xue,
don't worry.
I'll win everything for you.
Did you record
everything I just said?
Jiang Niannian,
I really like your spirit.
Since I like you that much,
let me tell you one more secret.
Take a look.
What is this?
Before the anesthesia kicked in,
your brother begged me.
He said,
"I'm begging you."
"Please don't kill me."
"Don't kill me."
"Don't kill me. My sister will find you."
Then what?
Jiang Niannian.
I've already got my new heart.
I'll never suffer from heart disease.
I can do anything I want now.
Oh,
Manlong's organ-trafficking dark web
was built by me.
At first, I just needed a new heart.
Never thought it'd make me this rich.
Li Hong, let her go!
Shut up!
Why laughing?
Second Young Master.
How's your
phone signal?
(Cruel Rich Heir Runs Dark Web Deals)
You're livestreaming?
You planned all this from the start.
No.
How did you know?
Looks like
you really don't know Ye Lang.
Ye Lang found out everything already.
So he set this trap just for you.
Seeing how miserable you are,
I'll kindly tell you one more truth.
You're not Liu Yexi
and Zhong Minghui's son.
You're actually the Li family's
biological son.
That's impossible.
You're lying to me!
How pitiful Liu Yexi is.
She spent her whole life paving your way.
And you sent her straight to ruin.
What a joke.
Liu Yexi
is just trash.
In this world,
the one who loves me most is Xue.
Xue,
you won't leave me, right?
Say it.
You love me, right?
I'm useless.
My fault.
I kept letting you down.
I'll kill Jiang Niannian right now.
Don't!
I know what you just said
was to stall for time.
You're expecting Ye Lang to save you?
Listen,
Ye Lang is already dead.
Ye Lang...
Why are you here?
What?
You're disappointed
I'm not dead?
♪Stitched-up lips
tear open a blood-red dusk♪
♪You return reborn,
seeing through all my cracks♪
♪This tenderness, a trap or a gift?♪
♪Still, I'd wager my next life on it♪
♪Just for a moment to recognize you again♪
♪You are the blazing light in my despair♪
♪Lighting the edges of my frozen wings♪
♪I burn myself,
leaping into an illusion of fire♪
♪Breaking free
from dead vines in the ashes♪
♪You are the brightest star in the night♪
♪Awakening my dormant fate♪
♪Freeing me from this half-life prison♪
♪As the bells shatter the past♪
♪Life finds its way again♪