Is there such thing
as a given fate?
If there is,
is it impossible
for us to escape the frame of fate…
that repeats itself?
EPISODE 12
THE SAVIOR OF DESTRUCTION
Good morning, Young Master.
It's a beautiful day, Young Master Yi-sun.
-Good morning, Young Master.
Young Master!
I used to be human.
My mere presence
was enough to inspire
the entire village's love and respect.
I was that special.
Young Master!
Young Master Yi-sun!
Stop whining, will you?
Stop calling my name. You'll wear it out.
Your tutor will arrive any minute.
You can't go flower-watching right now.
Your father will have a fit
if he finds out.
Everyone will be happy
as long as you keep quiet.
My mouth can't be kept shut.
It's structured that way.
Anyway, you can't go.
If you must go,
please don't step on me
because that hurts, but step over me.
For goodness' sake!
That's even better.
I'll have the scenery all to myself.
He really stepped over me.
You snuck out without telling me!
I had no idea!
He's so stubborn, isn't he?
The best spot should be
somewhere around here.
Wait!
It's cold!
My apologies for the interruption.
I came here
to take a break from my studies.
Please don't be scared.
I'm not a suspicious person. My name is--
Seo Yi-sun.
Every single person in this village
knows your name.
I suppose
I'm quite well known in this village.
On the other hand,
I've never seen you before.
I assume you came from another village.
Otherwise, there's no way
I wouldn't know a beauty like…
Then again,
I'm too occupied with my studies
to converse with any ladies.
That may be why.
Is that so?
That's not what the rumors say.
What rumors?
You're a precious only son
from a prestigious family.
You neglect your studies,
but your father
refrains from disciplining you
since you lost your mother
to an illness at a young age.
As a result, you're known to be
the most carefree loafer in the world.
You seem
very interested in me.
While you know everything about me,
I know nothing about you.
What is your name?
Young Master!
Young…
Young Master Yi-sun!
How could you just leave me…
Wait!
Why are you looking at me like that?
You got yourself another reason
to neglect your studies.
-Once I set my mind to my studies--
-In any case,
she's as beautiful as people say.
Do you know who she is?
I do.
Which noble family does she come from?
She doesn't come from a noble family.
She's a government courtesan
who recently moved here from Hanyang.
A courtesan?
I heard that she was well-known in Hanyang
for her dance skills and intelligence.
I wonder why she moved
all the way to this small village.
Was it to meet me?
What was her name again?
What is her name?
-Have a drink, my lord.
-Please have a drink, my lord.
-All right then.
-You look great today.
Wolsim at your service.
What?
This is unacceptable!
She is said to have been haughty
in Hanyang as well.
What an insolent woman.
Wolsim.
So that's her name.
My apologies.
I came over the other day
because I wanted to see you.
I apologize if I was being rude.
How exactly were you being rude?
I can't quite pinpoint it, but…
Please don't apologize
if you don't know why.
Wait…
Young Master!
I know you'd rather sleep than eat,
but take a break from lazing around
now and then,
or you'll ruin your health.
Who are you?
Are you still half asleep?
You've served me all your life.
But you never wake up this early.
-What happened?
-Seok.
I've decided to focus on my studies
starting today.
Why is that?
This is who I really am.
I'll get you some medicine.
"Xu Fan asked about benevolence."
"Confucius answered
that it meant to love others."
What are you doing?
My lady!
What a coincidence!
Is it?
I was reading The Great Learning
while listening to the waterfall
to appreciate nature
and study at the same time.
You must be here for the same reason,
but it'd be indecent of us to be together.
So you'll have to
take the spot over there.
This spot is taken.
"Xu Fan asked about wisdom."
"Confucius answered
that it meant to understand others."
COMMENTARIES ON GREAT LEARNING
Do you live here or something?
I seem to focus better when I study here.
It doesn't look like you're studying,
if you ask me.
"If the cause is not right,
the command is not followed."
"If the command is not followed,
the work is not accomplished."
How insightful!
Don't worry.
I'll go get it.
But it's dangerous.
I've trained in swordsmanship,
archery, and spearmanship for years
to strengthen my mind and body.
This should be a piece of…
A piece of cake.
I'll be right back.
But…
Don't you worry.
Young Master!
Stop there!
Wait for me!
Young Master!
Young Master Yi-sun!
I found it!
I, Seo Yi-sun, found it!
My lady.
Here's your shoe, my lady.
I found it.
What were you thinking?
Who cares about a shoe?
What if something bad happened?
Were you
worried about me?
Why would I worry about you?
Don't ever do this again.
Are you all right?
I've trained in swordsmanship,
archery, and spearmanship…
Give me that.
No, I will do it.
Dry your clothes first.
No, I'm almost done.
Nothing beats the warmth
of one's body temperature.
You'll burn my shoe.
Come on.
I'm cold.
What is Hanyang like?
I assume it's much bigger
and more exciting than this village.
It is much bigger,
more crowded, and noisier indeed.
So how did you end up here?
I'm sorry for being nosy.
I refused to dance
for a high-ranking official.
I may be a lowly courtesan,
but I can't seem to even move a finger
when I don't feel like dancing.
After I, a lowly courtesan, declined
the request of someone so powerful,
I'm thankful to even be alive.
There must have been a reason…
why you couldn't bring yourself to dance.
To think I get to enjoy seeing you dance
even when an eminent man couldn't.
I don't know how to repay you.
You've already repaid me.
Have I?
It's a firefly.
I love you, Wolsim.
I thought that you felt the same way.
It's time to wake up from this dream.
The most foolish human emotion
is love.
I don't mean this lightly.
I would like to marry you.
We can't get married.
Given my class,
I can be your concubine at best.
Let's elope.
If we run away--
We can't run away from the world forever.
As long as the world remains the same,
so will our fate.
Wolsim.
You said there must've been a reason
I refused to dance
and was expelled from Hanyang.
That day,
my dearest friend took her life.
She was
in a romantic relationship
with a nobleman.
Contrary to popular belief,
love can't save a person.
It only weakens us
and drags us into the depths of misery.
I'll show you…
that love can save a person.
If we must sink into the depths of misery,
I'd gladly…
do so with you.
Wolsim!
Wolsim…
Young Master.
What if someone sees you here?
I found something incredible.
SEVEN VIRTUES AND VICES OF CATHOLICISM
This is Western learning, isn't it?
That's right. This book says
that all humans are born equal.
Isn't that amazing?
Here, take a look.
We were in love,
but we had been struck
by the class barrier.
To us, the new learning
that spoke of equality
seemed like salvation.
-Our Father, Who art in heaven,
-hallowed be Thy name.
-Thy kingdom come.
-Thy will be done on earth
-as it is in heaven.
-Give us this day our daily bread
-and forgive us our trespasses
-as we forgive
-those who trespass against us.
-And lead us not into temptation,
-but deliver us from evil.
-Amen.
"The Lord is the ancestor of all beings
and the creator of all things."
"Therefore, all descendants of the Lord
may protect themselves
by relying on His love."
If we all are equal
as the Lord's children,
shouldn't we all speak the same way
regardless of class?
That's right.
Yi-sun.
Say that again.
Seo Yi-sun, you little brat.
Who knew being talked down to
would feel so good?
I hope this will spread throughout Joseon.
Then everyone will be addressed
by their first name
and treated with respect.
When that day comes,
we'll be able to get married.
When do you think that day will come?
Wolsim.
I'd like to pass the state examination.
Rather than waiting
for the world to change,
I'd like to change it myself.
Perhaps
we believed in each other
more than anything.
We were quickly swept up
by the fragile yet perilous belief
that we could be happy together
and infected each other
with the conviction.
Little did we know
the dire consequences that awaited us.
She's a government courtesan.
Her name is Wolsim.
Young Master has been
associating with Catholics, including her,
and I'm worried sick.
What should we do?
Wolsim!
-Young Master.
-Wolsim.
The journey to Hanyang will be difficult.
And I heard that bandits
are running rampant these days.
Please be careful.
Don't worry.
I'll come back safely and marry you.
The last thing I see before I die
will be your face.
Something to remember me by
while I'm away.
I'll never take it off
until you come back.
Please don't forget me.
I would rather forget myself
than forget you.
Young Master.
We haven't got all day.
Let's go.
Recently, a man abolished
the memorial service for his late mother
and committed the atrocity of burning
and burying the ancestral tablet.
This was due to the despicable teachings
of the vicious followers of Catholicism.
They take turns holding gatherings
called the Six Meetings in their homes
where men and women sit together
and spread immoral beliefs.
They go so far as to hold meetings
at courtesan houses.
It is extremely deplorable indeed.
The recent heinous incident happened
because no action
had been taken against them.
At this rate, this land of courtesy
built on Confucianism
with 4,000 years of history
will end up in the hands
of beasts and scoundrels.
To prevent that,
we shall behead them and display
the severed heads to warn everyone.
We shall also nail their doors shut
and burn their villages to the ground.
The nearby village is in ruins.
At this rate,
our village will be no exception.
It is clear that the Noron faction
is using the Catholics
as an excuse to bring us down,
but there's nothing we can do.
If sacrifice is inevitable,
we shall sacrifice only one person.
Cruel times arrived.
And in cruel times,
a scapegoat is needed.
To save their own lives,
people did not hesitate
to point the finger.
It's that courtesan, I swear!
-It's her!
-It's certainly her!
-I saw it!
Everyone is saying
that you're the only Catholic here.
But do you think
I'm after a mere courtesan?
This can't possibly belong
to a lowly courtesan like you.
Who gave it to you?
Answer me,
and I'll spare your life.
It is mine.
It has always…
belonged to me.
But there was
one person
who sacrificed herself
to save her loved one.
Hooray!
Wolsim!
Young Master…
Young…
Wolsim.
Love can't save a person.
It only weakens us
and drags us into the depths of misery.
I'll show you
that love can save a person.
If we must
sink into the depths of misery,
I'd gladly…
do so with you.
Thirsty for revenge
and blinded by fury,
I turned evil.
If heaven is where God dwells,
I refuse to go there.
I killed…
you.
My faith…
caused
her death.
Did you sleep well?
Here.
It's your favorite, pour-over coffee.
You look haggard.
Are you not feeling well?
I just had a dream.
A dream?
You said a demon didn't need sleep,
but you even had a dream?
What was it about?
I dreamed about when I was human.
Did you get your memory back?
A little bit.
What kind of person were you?
I'm curious.
I…
was in love with someone.
Her name was Wolsim.
So the dream wasn't about you
but your ex?
Gosh, I can't believe this.
Was she pretty?
Did you two have a happy ending?
Don't tell me you had a sad ending.
We had an ordinary
and insignificant ending
like everyone else.
I'll go wash up.
That's what I'm talking about.
Could you give us some privacy?
So you unlocked your memories.
I did.
I killed myself
so I wouldn't end up where you were,
but you turned me into a demon.
I needed a worker.
Not just in heaven but also in hell.
When your grudge against humans
met the needs of God,
a demon was born.
How could you reward my faith…
with such a tragic death?
Faith is an inherently dangerous thing.
Perhaps more dangerous than anything else.
Don't you even feel guilty?
How can you not feel guilty
when even lowly humans can?
Who are you so angry with, me or yourself?
Or could it be because of your fear
of fate repeating itself?
That you'll end up
making her suffer again?
What are you talking about?
As I said,
fate is bound to repeat itself.
That must be why your tattoo transferred.
That got you two entangled
so that the misfortune could strike again.
Shut up!
It's a fate that you created.
You're simply paying for what you've done.
Fate…
Director Jeong.
I think I found out about your past life.
Do you know what your full name was?
Seo Yi-sun.
How did you know?
My memories…
have returned.
Do you also remember how you died?
I understand you a lot better
now that I've learned about
Seo Yi-sun's unfortunate life.
No wonder you loathe humans.
Anyway,
if you remember everything now,
tell me about Wolsim.
She's Do Do-hee.
No way.
Our encounter
wasn't a coincidence.
Could it be
that you started becoming human
the moment you met her?
You told me your powers started acting up
and your tattoo transferred
when you first met her.
I must be right.
Until now,
we thought the loss of your powers
turned you into a human,
but it was the other way around.
In other words,
meeting a significant person
from your past life triggered your change,
and that's why your powers flickered.
It's a chicken-egg situation.
Are you going to tell her?
No.
It's best she doesn't know.
WOLSIM
Wolsim.
That rings a bell.
He seemed to avoid talking about her.
Does he still have feelings for her?
I just sounded like an obsessive wife.
I should watch myself.
Come in.
I've uploaded
the sales data for the new product.
Ms. Shin.
Let's say you've had memory loss.
How would you feel
if you suddenly got your memory back?
-That came out of nowhere.
-Just imagine.
Your old memories come flooding back.
You'd be very confused, right?
You'd be surprised and flustered.
The best thing one could do for you
in that situation
would be to patiently stay by your side.
I suppose.
Thank you for clearing that up for me.
My pleasure.
I saved the world.
I shed blood for all of you.
Do-gyeong.
Hang in there a little longer,
and your dad will get you out of here.
So take your medicine regularly
and take care of…
You knew everything, didn't you?
You knew everything…
but turned a blind eye.
You only care about yourself.
Do-gyeong.
I took the bullet for you.
I protected you.
You're…
the real evil one.
I've been good all my life.
That's why I'm not being punished.
Then…
what about me?
What about me?
What did I do wrong?
You…
disobeyed your father.
You didn't live the way he wanted.
That's why you're being punished.
You deserve it.
It's your fault.
Noh Do-gyeong!
Calm down, Noh Do-gyeong!
Calm down!
It's your turn now.
I'll take that one.
That one too.
It's for a good cause, right?
Yes, all the proceeds will be donated
to the Children's Welfare Association.
That's great.
I'll take this too.
Hello, Kim Se-ra speaking.
Mr. Jeong.
Thank you for the gift.
I'm fine now, thanks to you.
I didn't do it because I liked you.
But you're not telling me off
for being here again today.
Do-gyeong's psychiatric evaluation results
are out.
From intermittent explosive disorder
to extreme anxiety and depression,
he's in serious condition.
He was basically a ticking time bomb.
Had it not been for you,
Do-hee couldn't have made it unscathed.
Thank you.
And…
I'm sorry
for misunderstanding you until now.
There's no misunderstanding.
Hello, Detective Park.
Do-hee.
Do-gyeong's psychiatric evaluation results
are out.
Noh Do-gyeong…
is dead.
THE LATE NOH DO-GYEONG
Have some water.
I'm okay.
You must be in shock.
Please let me know
if I can help you with anything.
This can't be easy for you.
Thank you for coming.
He's the one who killed Madam Ju.
Of course I should see him off.
I should've apologized to you
in person sooner,
but I had a hard time accepting
that my son was such a monster.
I'm sorry, Do-hee.
I've failed as a parent.
So he killed himself?
He must've been overwhelmed
by the guilt for what he had done.
I don't think
his death makes up for what he did.
I promise to make it up to you
one way or another.
So for the sake of the company,
please keep a lid on this matter.
Are you worrying about the company
even in this situation?
My mother and your father
founded this company together,
pouring their blood and sweat into it.
Imagine if people found out
that my mother was killed by
her mentally ill, money-hungry grandson.
The company would take a huge blow.
Also, if this gets out,
everyone in the family will get hurt.
It's for the sake of both the family
and the company.
You're part of the family after all.
It seems like family means more to the one
who has more to lose.
See you soon.
Where's Noh Do-gyeong, that devil's spawn?
How could he kill his own grandmother?
Su-ahn.
Your son killed our mom.
It wasn't a heart attack.
It was murder!
Bring her back.
Bring her back right now!
I feel so sorry for her.
What are you going to do now?
Bring her back!
Let's go.
It's suffocating in here.
I'm sorry, Su-ahn.
It's all my fault.
Our poor mom.
Do you remember
what Do-gyeong was saved as
in Gi Kwang-chul's phone?
Abraxas?
I knew it sounded familiar,
and it's from the novel Demian.
"The bird fights its way out of the egg."
"The egg is the world."
"To be born,
one must
first destroy a world."
"The bird flies to God,
whose name is Abraxas."
Did Noh Do-gyeong have no choice
but to kill Madam Ju
in order to spread his wings?
That's his way of justifying his crime.
It's despicable.
Did he
really not know?
Do you mean Noh Suk-min?
How could he have been oblivious…
to what Noh Do-gyeong was up to?
I just don't understand it.
How about
we go see Madam Ju?
I've lost both my mother and son.
You're all I have left now.
We're not even that close.
We haven't been until now,
but let's try to get along
as each other's only family.
And Austin and Justin
are the only future heirs
of Mirae Group now.
Madam Ju.
It's all over now.
Even so,
nothing seems to have changed.
Noh Do-gyeong ran away from his sins.
And I'm still upset.
Will I be able to get over it
after time passes?
Tell me.
Can you get over everything with time?
You should know
since you've lived for 200 years.
You can't.
You just…
forget what happened…
for a short while.
I knew it.
I'll get going.
I promise to be in a better mood
next time.
Let's go.
So tell me.
Other than cotton candy and sunsets,
what else do you like?
I like all kinds of sweets.
It seems like sweets can make
everyone feel like a child again.
And…
I also like you, Bok-gyu.
You're silly.
These are tears of joy.
I almost forgot.
Here.
What's this?
Please come see our performance tomorrow.
-No thanks.
-Why?
We should keep our work
and personal lives separate.
I don't want to disturb your work.
Don't say that.
It'd mean so much if you came.
It's the sea!
-Hurry up, Ms. Choi.
-It's amazing!
We'll part ways after just one beer.
-You have to eat ramyeon at the Han River.
-It's the PR team!
We should have fried chicken too.
-Love isn't a crime, is it?
-Let's grab a spot.
Where should we sit?
Mr. Han, Ms. Choi, over here!
Nice!
This is so nice.
Hey.
Let's go somewhere else.
Why? I like this spot.
Can't you tell?
They're having an affair.
Are they?
-Let's go.
-What's with them?
It's not an affair!
My goodness.
Is she eating him up or what?
It's so violent.
Let's go.
What a shame. I like it here.
-Be quiet.
-Let's go somewhere else.
No, come back here!
SUNWOL FOUNDATION
You look gorgeous!
I love you!
-Ga-young!
-Please make a heart toward the camera!
Ga-young!
-You look beautiful!
-Wave at the camera!
I love you more!
I love you!
Please make a heart!
You look gorgeous!
-Please look over here!
-You're so pretty.
Wait a second, please.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I'm leaving Korea
right after the performance.
I won't bother you anymore.
Are you leaving for good?
I only had sad memories here
except for Director Jeong.
And now, he's no longer the exception.
Director Jeong and Star Jin
have to pose for the cameras.
Do me one last favor.
Please focus on your duties
as the executive director tonight.
Let's go.
Let's start again.
Executive Director Jeong Gu-won
is here as well.
Please stand close to each other.
Do you know why I got into dancing?
It's because of the painting
of the double-sword dance in the lobby.
I loved the look in Director Jeong's eyes
when he gazed at it.
There was this sadness and warmth to it.
The emotional look in his eyes
was so unlike him,
and I wanted it so badly.
I hoped that if I danced hard enough,
he would someday look at me that way.
That's why.
But instead,
he ended up looking at Do Do-hee that way.
Even though I've lost him to her,
I still have dance in my life.
I seem to focus better when I study here.
It doesn't look like you're studying.
I love you, Wolsim.
Seo Yi-sun, you little brat.
Who knew being talked down to
would feel so good?
The last thing I see before I die
will be your face.
I'll never take it off
until you come back.
If heaven is where God dwells,
I refuse to go there.
Gu-won.
Are you okay?
When I was human,
I killed people.
I killed a lot of people…
who loved me…
and whom I loved.
Was there a reason?
I'm not sure.
They had sacrificed…
the woman
I loved.
It's my fault.
If I hadn't loved her,
she wouldn't have died.
That's what frightens me.
I might…
make you miserable.
I'll be miserable without you anyway.
If I end up miserable either way,
I want us to be miserable together.
I'll show you
that love can save a person.
If we must
sink into the depths of misery,
I'd gladly…
do so with you.
Is there such a thing
as a given fate?
If there is,
I'm determined
to give us a happy ending this time.
Look at that!
Lord,
defend us in battle.
Be our protection against
the wickedness and snares of Satan.
Cast into hell
Satan and all the evil spirits
who prowl around the world
seeking the ruin of souls.
I saw the devil.
MY DARLING DAUGHTER DO-HEE
If there is such a thing
as fate,
within that inescapable frame of fate,
will we be
destroyed
or…
saved?
I don't want to repeat
my unfortunate past with Do-hee.
I'll make it a happy ending.
-I love you, Jeong Gu-won.
-I love you too.
Whatever you want, Do-hee.
There's not even enough time
to make you happy!
Happiness can sometimes be poisonous.
Let me ask you something.
Did you really not know
what Do-gyeong was up to?
Or did you just turn a blind eye?
I thought you were oblivious,
but were you only pretending?
Just how much do you know?
You think your parents died
in an accident.
They were killed by Ju Cheon-suk.
Subtitle translation by: Min-jin Kim