You really think you know everything
about Woo-seong, don't you?
What are you talking about?
I'm asking you
if you're ready to accept the truth,
whatever it is.
Some truths
come with pain the moment you learn them.
Pain…
that makes you wish you'd never found out.
So I'll ask one last time.
Can you really…
handle the truth?
Tell me.
Whatever it is you're hiding.
This isn't what you promised.
You said if I convince La-ik
to release his solo,
you'd give us a group album next.
So why is La-ik booked for another tour?
You know as well as I do
that La-ik's solo
isn't performing that well.
A tour is the only way to break-even.
Jae-hee and Young-bin,
they've been excited for a full album.
They practice every day, book rehearsals,
and that's the one thing
keeping them going.
What do you all
have to keep going for anyway?
The more La-ik earns,
the better it is for you.
You just split the money he brings in
and take it easy.
What exactly is the problem?
What did you just say?
Don't go to La-ik
and fill his head with nonsense.
His condition isn't good
these days as it is.
Don't make it worse.
Please stop contacting me like this.
- It makes me uncomfortable…
- I heard
your full album got delayed again?
I already told you,
Goldie has zero intention
of growing your team.
Even if you renew the contract,
the other members will just get shelved
while La-ik gets pushed again.
It's obvious.
If you come to our company,
we can help you make real music.
We can match whatever terms you ask for.
This isn't something
I can decide on my own.
- I need to ask the members first…
- And what if…
CEO Geum finds out?
Too many voices
will only derail everything.
From what I've heard,
La-ik and the others all listen to you.
So it's time to choose
for the team's sake.
They dance pretty well.
Yeah, but I think we're still better.
Well, of course we are.
Woo-seong! You ditched rehearsal.
Where did you run off to?
I cleared my whole schedule for today.
What schedule?
- Want some ramyeon?
- I'm good.
I already ate.
Ugh, they suck.
Seriously. They call that music?
Maybe when we make our comeback,
I should crush them.
Oh, right! Woo-seong,
did you see the group chat?
I posted one of those trending challenges.
How about we try it?
I think the fans would love it.
- Wow! Looks good!
- Right?
Good? We have an image, okay?
Pick something else.
Then the three of us can do it.
What do you mean?
We're Gold Boys, pick something else!
- There's a good one down here. Looks fun.
- If you don't like it, just don't do it.
La-ik!
Are you okay?
At this rate,
La-ik's actually going to die.
He does music shows every day,
then events,
and on his days off,
he's prepping for the concert.
We need to cut back his schedule.
Manager.
At this rate,
something really might happen to him.
Why are you suddenly saying this?
What? Did he tell you something?
- No, it's that he…
- Keep this between us, okay?
If the company finds out
I'm taking meds,
it will just turn into a hassle.
He…
looks really worn out.
Don't worry. I'll take good care of him.
Once this promo cycle ends,
he'll get a break.
- The CEO promised.
- A promise?
Hey, I've got a meeting.
Let's talk later, okay?
INCOMING CALL
This is the newly renovated space.
The mixing room
was designed by a German engineer,
and everything's tuned,
so you can hear
every instrument with perfect clarity.
You could say
it was made specifically for Gold Boys.
We're putting together
a full custom team just for Gold Boys.
Producers, engineers,
art directors, everything.
We'll set things up
exactly the way you've wanted to work.
All you need to do is say yes.
I'll do it.
I'll go ahead with the contract.
A very wise decision.
However,
we want Gold Boys as a full group.
Since Do La-ik is the main vocalist,
we'll need to bring him over as well…
You don't need to worry about that.
If I say it, he will do it.
Same with the other members.
Okay.
That bastard, Do La-ik.
I heard he secretly signed
with another company to go solo.
Where did you hear that?
My friend works
at the company he's been talking to.
It's solid info.
He even got a huge advance already.
I'm gonna drop it to the press tomorrow.
It's straight-up tampering.
- Once this gets out, that bastard's done.
- No!
Huh?
We don't know anything for sure yet.
I'll meet La-ik tomorrow
and check it myself,
so don't tell anyone until then. Okay?
What did you do?
How did something we talked about
among ourselves get out?
And when did I ever sign anything?
I only said it!
You did say it.
You said you'd sign,
and the other members,
including La-ik, would sign too.
I recorded everything you said.
I didn't mean I'd do it right now,
- I just…
- Woo-seong.
A verbal agreement is still an agreement.
You gave me your word.
If you keep backing out like this,
I'll have no choice but to make it public.
Imagine what people will say
once this gets out.
About you, and about La-ik.
They'll say all of you betrayed the team.
We don't want that, do we?
CEO!
You're terrible with alcohol,
why did you chug it so fast?
I'm not bad with alcohol.
It's because of the meds.
Do you still take meds?
And you still downed drinks like that?
I'm not drunk.
You said you had something to tell me.
What is it?
It's nothing.
We'll talk tomorrow. Get some sleep.
What do you think you're doing?
What were you doing
with Achi Entertainment?
I didn't violate any contract.
There's not much time left before renewal,
- and talking to another company isn't…
- Sure.
Customarily, that's not a problem.
But the law is different.
You haven't given a clear answer
- about our renewal yet, so…
- So you dragged La-ik's mother into this
and tried to make a big score?
- Sorry?
- La-ik's mother signed a contract
with them under his name.
And thanks to your verbal agreement,
the situation has turned
legally disadvantageous for La-ik!
- I didn't mean it like that…
- "Mean it"?
Your intentions don't matter at all.
What matters is
that if anything blows up,
I'll be sending the penalty fee
to both of you.
And since La-ik's contract fee
is much bigger,
my payout will be bigger too.
If he finds out about this,
what do you think will happen?
If I were him,
I'd want to kill you.
Woo-seong, you're heading
for real trouble.
You know that, right?
- I know.
- Knowing all that, you still did this?
You think La-ik's just gonna let it slide?
- La-ik is…
- He will believe me.
And he'll try to fix everything himself.
That's what I'm afraid of.
He's always sacrificed himself for me.
I'm afraid he'll do it again.
That's what scares me.
Why did you do this?
- If you'd told me earlier…
- I did tell you.
You just didn't listen.
But now that it's happened,
I'll take responsibility
for everything I caused.
And I'm getting out from under you,
no matter what it takes.
That's the only way
we can live the way we want.
Then go ahead and try.
It's going to be a big fight.
Be ready for it.
I never actually…
intended to charge any penalty fees.
I just wanted to scare him enough
so he'd never do something like that.
I regret it even now.
If I had known
that call would be the last time
I'd hear Woo-seong's voice,
I would never say those things.
Now, do you understand?
Why I had no choice
but to keep all of this hidden?
I believed
making that call public,
revealing Woo-seong's tampering
would only hurt La-ik.
They might twist it
into a motive for the crime.
So…
I ordered Jae-hee
to keep everything strictly secret.
La-ik.
I've watched you since you were a kid.
I hid everything because I truly believed
that you couldn't have done that
to Woo-seong.
I wanted to protect you.
But…
belief isn't evidence.
All right. I've told you everything.
Now it's your turn.
Did you really
not know any of this?
Are you…
sure…
you didn't kill…
Woo-seong?
You say
you stayed quiet to protect me,
but no.
You were calculating.
You stayed silent
because once this came out,
you were afraid of being suspected.
Let me tell you
exactly what you want to know.
I…
didn't kill Woo-seong.
La-ik, are you okay?
I didn't know.
I didn't know anything.
I was such an idiot.
What do you mean?
We're Gold Boys, pick something else!
- That one looks fun.
- Just don't do it then.
Why didn't I notice any of it?
How long had he been struggling
all on his own.
Oh, Woo-seong's here?
What he must've been feeling
coming to find me that night.
Hey, enough of the depressing stuff.
Let's drink.
I had no idea.
He was always smiling.
- So I just assumed he was fine.
- This tastes great.
I always just thought about myself.
Stop! I said stop!
- La-ik.
- Woo-seong, I…
I only saw my hardship and my pain.
Get inside. The concert's about to start.
No, but…
Take care of La-ik.
Woo-seong always thought about me
before himself.
But I…
I never once tried…
to look past that smile.
I always wanted to hear it.
It's even prettier in person, your voice.
Woo-seong was…
carrying everything by himself
without saying a word.
And I realized it way too late.
I feel so sorry for that.
Just because you're close to someone
doesn't mean you get to know everything.
For some people,
opening up is harder than staying silent.
Maybe he was one of those people.
Don't blame yourself too much.
Realizing it late
doesn't mean it was your fault.
Sometimes people's hearts are hard to see,
even when they're right beside you.
And maybe showing only a smile
was his way of being sincere with you.
Right now,
it's okay…
to be sad.
If you hold everything in,
it'll only hurt more later.
So…
don't force yourself to endure it.
Let it out little by little.
It's okay.
Reassignment? What do you mean?
This case is my case! Why all of a sudden?
Have you not seen what's happening?
The media, the public,
everyone's screaming
that we targeted the wrong suspect!
Even the Commissioner was briefed on this!
But I've handled this case from the start.
- I should be the one to finish…
- Hey!
If you cling to it now,
the entire prosecution service
gets branded incompetent.
If you really want to take responsibility,
hand it over to another prosecutor
and step back cleanly.
That's the best thing
you can do right now. Understand?
If you don't want to throw in the towel,
then indict Do La-ik.
Sorry?
But, Father…
public sentiment is already bad.
Indicting someone
when the evidence is this weak,
isn't that far too risky?
What if he's found not guilty?
That's for the court to decide.
We're prosecutors.
We don't deliver the answers,
we follow procedure.
If there's even a one-percent possibility,
you use it as grounds for indictment.
How's Jae-hee?
Same as always.
They're not allowing visits yet,
so I was just heading back.
And did you hear?
Your house and car,
- the creditors withdrew all the seizures.
- What?
It's becoming clearer
that it wasn't you who killed Woo-seong.
So I guess the creditors pulled out.
No one wants backlash
for going after the wrong person.
And honestly, getting you back
to work quickly is better for them too.
But, are you sure
you're okay with going back
to that house again?
I have to go back.
I can't stay like this forever.
La-ik, I'm heading out.
All right.
If you hear anything about Jae-hee,
let me know.
Bye.
La-ik.
Are you heading to work?
- You're leaving a bit late today.
- Yes.
I've got things I need to take care of.
So I should get going now.
There's a sandwich in the fridge,
and if you want something else…
I'll take care of it. Go on.
If it gets too suffocating,
you can step outside for a bit.
No, I'll stay here.
Go on, you'll be late.
Go on.
I'll go now.
INCOMING CALL
HONG HYE-JOO
MESSAGE
This is the last time.
I want to see you one last time
and say goodbye.
I heard about Jae-hee.
Are you okay?
I came because you said
you wanted to say goodbye one last time.
Are you going back to the States?
Yeah.
Most of my stuff is packed already,
but I'm yet to find a place for this one.
Seeing it brought back memories.
We were so happy then, weren't we?
Do you remember?
Back then, before you debuted,
no one recognized us, and we were free.
We can't go back in time, but…
we can start over from the beginning.
Like back then.
- Hye-joo…
- They're saying
the case will soon be closed
with Jae-hee as the lone culprit.
Whether it's true or not,
everything will wrap up soon.
But you know, right?
How people will look at you.
Can you really live with all that on you?
I'm not asking you to love me again.
I'm asking you to take your life back.
Somewhere completely new.
You're right.
Even when all this is over,
my life won't go back to how it was.
But running away isn't an option for me.
From here on,
I'm going to live as I am.
With the ones who believed in me,
stood by me
and told me I could.
My life is here…
in this moment, in this place.
I get it.
Thank you.
I think I can finally let go now.
Take care.
Be happy.
Yeah, you too.
GOSSIPFACTS
THE TRUTH WE CREATED
Assault…
ignores fans…
bad temper…
Isn't there anything spicier than this?
This one's the theft case for Ms. Jin,
this is the assault case for Mr. Park.
and Mr. Seong's defamation draft.
Check for any missing case numbers
or party info and send me the final file.
- Are you heading out already?
- Yes.
See you next week.
Yes, have a great weekend!
Clocking out?
What's all this?
Sweet and spicy, original,
Kkanpunggi flavor,
and even chicken gangjeong.
Did you raid a whole chicken farm?
Why did you buy so much?
You haven't been eating much lately.
And you eat chicken when you're down.
- You knew that?
- Of course.
I've been your fan for years…
I'll set things up.
Could you grab some plates?
Sure.
Se-na!
Chung-jae.
Smells like fried chicken…
Wow! Chicken!
Kkanpunggi flavor too?
Yeah, you like that one.
Why are you acting all weird?
If it's because of what I said last time,
don't be.
I mean, you can't ignore him.
I know you can't ignore
someone who's struggling.
And since when
have you ever listened to me?
Hey! Come on. It's gonna get cold!
It's been a while since I had chicken.
Something's wrong with the coke.
It's warm.
I forgot to put it in the fridge.
I kind of like warm coke.
It'll be warm in your stomach anyway.
- Seriously!
- Oh, my.
Seriously.
It's soaked.
I think I'm out of my mind.
Please understand,
she looks like
a perfectionist on the outside,
- but really…
- Hey!
It's too wet.
I'll go change.
Why didn't you finish
what you were saying?
Tell me. What kind of person is she?
What do you think she's like?
Well, hard to describe in one word?
Yeah, that's true.
- Always a bit clumsy.
- What?
Do you know how long
we've known each other?
- Since we were 12 years old.
- Twelve?
We're neighbors. Columbarium neighbors.
My mom and grandma
are right next to her parents.
That's where we first met.
I'm the same as you.
I was a troublemaker growing up.
Every time I got into something,
she defended me.
She helped me straighten out.
People think
she's cold and flawless on the outside,
but if you really know her, she's soft.
Too soft, so she let me stay here
when she didn't even know me well.
I know. I'm in a similar situation.
So you do know.
I thought maybe you didn't.
You know that she used to
kind of like you.
Just a tiny bit.
As a fan.
But that doesn't mean she likes you.
Who you are now and who she used to like
are totally different people.
So don't get the wrong idea.
Just be grateful. That's it.
I know.
I'm not stupid enough to misunderstand.
She's not helping me because she likes me.
It's because I'm in a bad spot
and she can't ignore someone like that.
I know that better than anyone.
But the problem is,
I'm not sure I can end it
with just being grateful.
Not like you.
Why aren't you two eating?
- Come on, eat up.
- Yes.
Where did all the drumsticks go?
How many did you eat?
- La-ik, how many did you have?
- Only two.
Here's another one.
Hey!
Why are you giving me
something you took a bite of?
You should've brought ice cups too!
There's no ice.
You go to the store and get some.
Come on.
I can do that.
It's fine. I got it. It's not much.
It was fun.
Eating together,
laughing, talking about nothing.
I guess I really missed that.
It felt good. It's been a while.
It's such an ordinary thing, though.
Yeah.
But ordinary moments…
are the hardest to have.
What if…
What if you weren't you?
If you were just some
random passerby or something,
- what would you want to do most?
- Something I'd want to do?
It's exactly the same.
You wanted to come here?
Yeah.
I mean, my childhood wasn't exactly happy.
But I always wanted to come back once.
Why?
I don't know.
I think it was
the most ordinary time of my life.
You told me to be a passerby today.
Maybe not out there, but here
I was just a regular student.
Shy, quiet.
Looking back, I think that was
when life felt the most peaceful.
Just a second.
Sir! Hello.
- Thank you.
- It's been forever.
- Right.
I didn't think
we'd actually be allowed inside.
Wait, were the desks always this tiny?
I know, right?
Everything felt huge when we were kids.
The school, the classrooms, the desks.
Wow, I must've been tiny.
You look like a kid sitting there.
I used to sit like this, never studying,
just staring out the window,
thinking about everything.
I kept thinking, "Tomorrow will be better.
"When I grow up, I'll be happy."
Actually, there's another reason
I wanted to come here.
SOONDAE - GIMBAP - EGG
- Thank you, ma'am.
- Yeah.
I came just in case. I didn't think
this place would still be here.
You've been coming here
since you were a kid?
Yes.
The fishcake broth here
used to be amazing.
I was always hungry and broke.
I'd pay 500 won for a plate of tteokbokki
and drink bowls and bowls of broth.
It is good.
If I mashed the egg yolk into the dish,
he'd scold me for more dishes to wash.
I think he knew.
No one came to pick me up,
so I ate tteokbokki here alone every day.
He'd give me extra fishcake
and a bit of fried food secretly.
I always wanted to come back someday,
once I became a decent adult,
and thank him properly.
You are a decent adult.
- Thank you.
- What?
- It's him.
Really?
He's still here.
Let's eat. It looks good.
- I'll eat the egg.
- Yes.
- So good.
- Tastes the same?
I can't believe how long it's been.
Chicken yesterday, tteokbokki today,
it feels good to eat properly again.
We didn't order this.
Thank you.
Prosecutor,
something just came in from the police.
It's the inspection report
for Choi Jae-hee's car,
but there's nothing special in it.
REPORT
The Deputy Chief
wants all related documents
passed on to Prosecutor Jang.
You can't keep resisting forever, sir.
What is this?
It's a scene photo.
They said the fall point looked odd,
so they took extra shots.
What exactly is odd?
The spot where he fell,
you can get there
with a sudden hard turn of the wheel.
But there were no skid marks at all.
So instead of speeding
and crashing forward,
they think the car rolled off slowly.
But the actual vehicle inspection
didn't show any signs of tampering.
The police questioned
Lee Young-bin as a witness, right?
Yes.
Here it is.
JAE-HEE WOULD NEVER KILL HIMSELF
Jae-hee would never kill himself.
Never.
It's not a drug
that knocks someone out instantly.
Consciousness drops gradually
over 20 to 30 minutes.
If he was driving,
he wouldn't have been able
to brake or avoid anything.
The same substance was found
on Do La-ik when he was arrested.
Tell the police to send
every supplemental field detail right now.
I don't think we should stay here.
If someone recognizes you…
It's fine, we can just run.
Let's go somewhere quieter.
Didn't you say I should be a passerby?
Just a normal guy?
Then why didn't you go
somewhere you want to go?
You said this was your favorite place
when you were a kid.
I got curious about
what little Se-na used to like.
Still…
And actually…
this is my first time at an aquarium.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
- What's that?
- A stingray!
- Wow, it's huge.
- Is that a shark?
I think so.
This is amazing.
- What?
- Nothing, you look cute.
Cute?
No, I mean…
The way everything amazes you like a kid.
So you're weak for cute things.
What?
Nothing.
Se-na, what is that?
Is that a fish too?
If you chop it up like this and eat it,
would it taste good?
Forget it.
It's embarrassing.
I used to come here a lot with my family.
Even when I was a kid,
they said if they sat me here,
I wouldn't cry.
I'd sit quietly for hours.
I guess you liked fish.
I don't think so.
Coming back today,
I remembered…
thinking those calm ripples
were beautiful.
So you liked dark, gloomy places
from a young age?
What?
I'm kidding.
It's La-ik!
- La-ik.
- Huh?
Let's go.
- It's him!
- Right!
- He's leaving.
- Let's follow him.
- Let's go.
- Let's move.
What?
He's not here.
- What?
- Where did he go?
Let's just go.
You must have been mistaken.
I'm sure he was here.
Let's just go.
Where did he go?
Let's go.
Actually, I first saw you here.
That's why I wanted to come with you.
This place means something to me.
Sitting here like this,
it makes everything feel unreal.
Woo-seong,
Jae-hee,
everything that's happened.
Sometimes I think about it.
If you hadn't been by my side
after everything happened,
what would've happened to me?
I used to avoid going out.
Partly because of the obsessive fans,
but honestly,
I intentionally avoided getting out.
I wanted to look perfect.
But today, I didn't think like that once.
Today, I wasn't Do La-ik of Gold Boys.
I was really just a passerby.
When I'm with you,
I keep ending up like that.
I just become me.
Like actually me.
It's really beautiful.
Yes it is.
Beautiful.
There's only ten minutes left.
When today ends,
I have to go back to being me again.
So are you sad?
No.
I just think you'll be sad.
This passerby was pretty good, right?
Cute, tough,
romantic.
I like cute, tough, romantic guys too,
but I like you just being you even more.
You said it yourself
that today,
you felt the most like yourself.
I think that's why I liked it so much.
Seeing you just be yourself.
So that means you…
You like me?
- What?
- You just said that.
You like me.
When did I say that?
You literally just said you like me.
So what? Should I not like you?
I meant as a person.
Seriously, you're so weird.
I like you.
Having these feelings right now,
I think I must be crazy.
But I can't hide it anymore.
My feelings just won't stop.
I like you.
I really…
like you, Se-na.
What this feeling I have for you is…
I'll wait as long as it takes.
Let's begin.
Did you see the news?
- Ra-ik's indictment just arrived.
- What?
Do you know how hard
she worked to get here?
It could all
fall apart because of you.
A murderer's daughter defending someone?
This time,
I don't want to leave her alone.
Subtitle translation by: Soyeon Kim