ONE MONTH EARLIER
I'd like you to do something
about this, Captain.
I've seen those symptoms before.
Sheesh...
Happiness.
I knew it.
Have you been making
time to see her lately?
I see.
Hmm... I guess we'll ask the guild
for a quest as an excuse again
and invite Happiness and
Cecilia to go with us.
Uh...
Could he not just invite
her on a date like normal?
A d-date?!
I have two superiors who can't even
ask the girls they like on a date.
My life sucks.
O-Okay!
Operation Go on a Group Date as
a Drastic Measure to Help Raven...
is underway!
Sunny day.
Isn't the weather just lovely?
Let's do our best to
have lots of fun today!
Hey, Duke, since when were
you and Irene a thing?
When I said we were giving
the captain a break,
she said she wanted to help.
I'm so excited! I hope we
find something good to eat!
All right, we're heading out now.
So where are we headed, anyway?
There's someplace Happiness wants to go.
We're starting with that.
Dying to.
WHERE?
Oh, you mean the famous spot
that just opened recently?
You nailed it.
A famous spot that just
opened? You don't mean...
LET'S GO TO A BAKERY.
Refuse.
LET'S GET LUNCH!
Too early.
That place will probably be crowded,
and if we go there, it
could lead to chaos.
Let's not do that today.
Break free!
Wow...
This looks amazing!
The king made it to celebrate
the Demon King's defeat.
Identical.
PLEASE DON'T LOOK.
Don't be modest.
I'm proud.
Looks like it's going well.
The plan's clearly a success.
Happiness, you have cream on your cheek.
Captain?
It is the captain.
But that voice we just heard...
Right?
I see. So sorry.
This is the first time
we've heard your voice,
so we were a bit surprised.
Rude!
Vice Captain, good to see you.
The captain's off duty today,
so don't worry about him. You
can continue your patrol.
Hah! He has not only his subordinate,
but a fragile girl defending him?
Please, go ahead and enjoy your day off,
"Sir Raven."
Um... Captain?
Raven...
Hey! Raven!
I'll bring him right back!
I'll go with you!
I don't blame him for being shocked,
but I didn't think he'd run away.
There were always some knights who didn't
like having a captain who didn't talk.
It was the vice captain who brought
them all together as a faction.
I'm still a rookie,
so there's only so much I
can do to stick up for him.
You've got it harder than I thought.
Over there!
This game of tag is over.
Let's head back to the others.
What's going to happen if I go back?
What?!
You're running away because
you got embarrassed?
So you never want to see
Happiness again, then?
That's...
I thought I was fine with it
as long as Happiness was happy.
What a letdown.
If you still insist on keeping
silent, I guess it is what it is.
He's all yours from here.
What's really wrong?
Lately, I've been reminded of
my own weakness and powerlessness.
You remember that quest
we did at the ocean?
That day, Happiness told
me she had a secret.
She seemed to be afraid of something,
so it must be a really big deal.
But how can I accept
whatever her secret is
when all I ever do is worry and fret?
It's the same with my voice.
All I've done is run from it.
If only I could
have the courage to approach
the girl I love, like you do...
Say what?!
Just who do you think I am?
I went out alone with the girl I love,
but I'm such a shy loser, I had
to wear a mask the whole time!
On your feet, Raven!
Those legs aren't just for
show, are they?! Hell no!
I know you're not that weak!
How do I know?
Because I, like Duke and Happiness,
have faith in you!
That bizarre mood you create
always cheers me up somehow.
I'm sorry, everyone.
I'm sorry I acted selfishly.
Forgiven.
Okay, now that the captain's
game of tag is over,
we're going shopping next!
I can't wait!
Happiness...
I know you can't rely on me now,
but I'll try harder so you can
entrust me with your secret one day.
Acknowledged.
A FEW DAYS LATER
Yoki!
What is it, Cecilia?
Happiness has gone missing!
What?!
Happiness did put in a
request for extended leave,
but this note she wrote is so puzzling...
Yep, it's written the way she talks.
What does it mean?
It says, "Come find me in
the forest in one month."
What forest is she talking about?
I think I might know.
Happiness must have something in mind.
Happy!
Hi.
Man, don't make me track you down
with my enhanced sense of smell.
Trust.
Everyone's worried about you, y'know.
I've made up my mind, so...
I'm going to tell him...
about me.
You're sure?
If Raven doesn't accept it,
you could lose everything.
I know.
They might want to investigate your
relationship to us and the captain, too.
If that happens...
I won't cause trouble.
This goes way beyond just causing trouble.
Me, Shiek, the captain...
We could all lose everything we've
gained since coming to Minerva.
Then again, you're smart,
so I'm sure you know all that.
I won't lie anymore.
I want him to know.
You can do this, Happy!
Shiek...
This is really important to you, right?
So I'll be rooting for you!
You feel the same, right, Duke?
That's right.
If that's how strong your resolve is,
don't worry about us. Just go and do it.
Thank you.
You gotta say something too, Captain!
But you guys summed it
all up so nicely for me.
I have nothing to add.
Useless.
Kidding. Captain...
Thank you.
Well, if it isn't Sir Raven.
How are you feeling today?
I feel just fine.
That voice...
You're being rude!
Why do you call me by name?
Huh?
I'm not such a fool
as to let a knight who disrupts
the order with his lack of manners
serve as vice captain.
Wh-What do you mean by that, Sir Raven?
You will call me "Captain."
My apologies, Captain.
THAT'S BETTER.
ONE MONTH LATER
It's been just about a month
now since Happiness went away.
Do you think she's going to...
It's exactly what you're imagining.
Duke should be taking Raven to
where Happiness is as we speak.
I didn't realize that Yoki was here.
Mother...
You told him about your marriage
arrangement, didn't you?
– No.
– What?
He has his hands full dealing
with his friends right now.
I don't want to give him
more to worry about.
Are you sure? Your future husband
has already arrived in Minerva.
Yoki is going to find out eventually.
I only agreed to meet him
per the king's order.
Once I meet him, I'll turn
down the offer right away.
Tell me, Cecilia...
How do you really feel about Yoki?
Yoki has nothing to do with anything!
Anyway, please don't tell him
about that without my permission!
Hmm... So you do feel something after all.
You're wrong! I just...
Silly.
If he really had nothing
to do with anything,
you wouldn't want to keep your marriage
arrangement a secret from him.
This is... Happiness's...
Come with me.
Where is Happiness?
Yoki, I have to kill you.
I thought if anyone could accept
her, it'd be you. What a letdown.
I could say the same about you.
You're not seriously...
There is nothing to discuss!
Explain what's going on!
I'm punishing you for hurting
Happiness! Steel yourself!
Wait!
I said wait!
What?!
He's stronger than before?!
So that's your true identity,
Yoki.
What did you do to Happiness, Raven?
I don't need to tell you!
That is...
enough!
Endless Dark!
Do you get it now, Raven?
You can't beat me.
But I won't give up!
Why are you so determined?
What happened between you and Happiness?
I promised her.
She said you plucked every feather from
her body to disguise her as a human,
and she asked me to give
you a beating for it.
Wha?
Huh?
That's what's going on. So let's do this.
Give me a break!
If you give me a beating with
that sword, even I'm gonna die!
Oh... Well, then, I'll just...
use the back edge.
That sword's double-edged!
Happiness!
Doot do-doo!
A mischievous spirit can
only take you so far!
Apology.
I'm sorry.
And? How did you two...
well... settle things?
Oh, well...
Duke led me to a certain forest, and...
You'll have to go on your own from here.
Duke?
You're gonna have to give
Happiness an answer yourself.
Happiness?
Happiness, are you up there?
Why... are you hiding?
Visitor. Gratitude.
Why did you want me to come here?
This is...
where I started.
And... where I ended.
So it's a place that means a lot to you.
Raven, I'm glad I met you.
Spending time with you is fun.
I'd like to be together forever.
– I also—
– No! Don't come closer!
I was scared.
I couldn't keep lying forever.
But... when I thought...
it might mean the end...
I'm sorry.
Raven?
I'm sorry I didn't notice.
You've been suffering
over this for so long.
You won't reject me?
Of course not. Because I love you.
I guess that's not a
sufficient reason, is it?
I-I...
love you, too.
Then everything's fine, right?
Yes.
That's so sweet!
That's way too sweet!
Sweeter than the sugar
cubes at Cecilia's house!
You two had a fairy-tale ending like that,
and you were talking about beating me up?!
All right. I get it.
Let me offer you my congratulations.
Saint Chains!
What's this for?!
Undo!
Oh! I'll put up a barrier
to keep monsters out.
Well, you two have a nice time now!
What a relief.
If, by some chance, Raven and
Happiness didn't work out,
we probably couldn't have tea
together like this anymore.
Cecilia?
Oh, I'm sorry!
Um... I'm going to be a
little busy for a while,
so I won't have much time for tea.
Oh, but it's only for a little while!
Oh, okay. Don't worry about it.
I'll be away from Minerva for a while.
Huh?
Yuga asked me to help him with a quest,
so I have to go to some mine somewhere.
I... see...
He kind of begged me.
It might take two or three weeks.
So at some point, you became
good friends with Yuga, too?
Huh?
Is Yoki here?!
Give Yoki to us.
Apprehend! Haul in!
Yoki, did you do something again?
They messed with me first!
Thanks for the tea!
I'll come by again!
Don't you run away!
Annihilate!
Honestly... You'd better.
Let's go, too.
Happiness! I'm happy for you!
Congratulations!
It seems we have a debt to
Yoki that we can never repay.
Thank you, Captain.