Wow!
What? Boracay?
Boracay is so beautiful.
I’ve been here a couple of times, but I don’t know why–
It’s more beautiful now.
Maybe you can finish that later?
Luna?
Where are you?
- Kalix! - Luna!
I admit, I was really hurt.
But I shouldn’t have walked out on you. I should have talked to you first.
Good morning, Ke!
This is Miguel, my boyfriend.
I never said anything about your men, Yanna.
What did you just say?
Hey!
- Yanna! - Hey!
Are you busy? Can we talk?
Yes, Dad. Come in.
I heard you declined the project of Mr. Martinez.
Dad, we have other architects that can do the job.
Why does it have to be me?
These kind of projects
don’t come very often.
The pay is good.
Besides,
this client has very good connections.
It’s not about that.
I know.
I know you have a past with him.
But can’t you approach it professionally?
I can be professional with Attorney Martinez.
But I don’t wanna work with him.
I’ve heard he protected an abuser, Dad.
You know what, I know Kalix used to...
be an associate of this notorious law firm before.
But they’ve since parted ways.
That shouldn’t define him.
Let me give you a different perspective, dear.
Do you still remember,
the fiasco that happened in the Cavite house?
Yes, what about it?
It was his law firm who settled the lawsuit for us.
Huh?
Yes.
Why didn't you told me this?
This is my project, Dad.
I’m sorry.
I know I should have told you earlier
but Kalix insisted not to let you know.
We agreed so that you won’t have to worry about it.
It was his law firm
who identified that the contractor was ordering substandard materials
which caused the house to collapse.
If it weren’t for him, our construction company might be closed by now.
So, I owe him now?
No.
Of course not.
I’m just saying that you should reconsider.
But if you’re really decided on declining, I won’t stop you.
I know where you’re coming from.
Hey Architect, your coffee's getting cold. Your face is begging for it.
It’s all messed up.
Well, your face is effortlessly messed up, you know.
So is it true?
Kalix was the one who helped us then?
They found out that we weren’t at fault.
Kalix’s team got us solid evidence
that cleared us from accountability.
But we still compensated all of the victims even if it wasn’t our fault.
Because that’s what’s right, Sevi.
We value our principles.
Unlike someone I know.
Like Kalix?
I mean, I’m grateful for what he did.
But it doesn’t change the fact that he’s still part of the abuser’s legal team.
And for everything else he did in the past.
Besides, I bet he’d be so hard to work with.
He’s such a demanding perfectionist so it’ll be hard to please him.
I get that, Luna.
This is definitely a hard situation for you.
Thinking about it…
we can’t deny how great this project is.
But at the same time,
it’s going to open up the past you and Kalix had.
Just know that whatever your decision will be,
I’m here to support you.
Good morning, may I speak with Attorney Martinez?
Good morning. Your name please?
Architect Luna Valeria.
Wait a second.
Do you have an appointment?
I don’t see your name in his list of appointments today.
I don’t have an appointment
but we have a possible project to do. So can you set up a meeting with him?
I’m sorry, ma’am. Attorney’s schedule this week is full.
If it’s urgent, you can go ahead and call him or just send him a message.
Luna: Hello, this is Architect Luna Valeria.
I’m here at the lobby of your firm. We need to talk.
Kalix: I can’t. I have clients. We can talk tomorrow.
Luna: It’s important. I can wait here.
Hello?
All right, then.
Architect Valeria?
Yes?
All good, now. Attorney’s secretary will be with you shortly.
Thanks.
Welcome, ma’am. Please come in.
So this is the office of Attorney Martinez.
Thanks.
Sorry, what’s your name again?
Jolly.
The cute secretary of Attorney Martinez.
The name suits you.
Oh, thank you, ma’am.
Is this whole floor the office of Kal– Attorney Martinez?
Yes, ma’am.
A lot of people wonder the same thing
since Attorney Martinez is quite young yet very successful.
He’s not just good at his work, he’s also very humble.
That’s why good karma just runs back to him.
Not a single person thinks badly of him.
Everyone you see here loves Attorney Martinez.
Oh ma’am, if only I was single,
I’d be hitting on him.
Do you have any idea what time he's coming?
I’m not sure on the exact time, ma’am.
I actually just squeezed this meeting in his schedule.
But don’t you worry, I’m sure he’ll be back anytime soon.
So, for the meantime, please wait here.
You want anything? Coffee, tea, water, chips?
I’ll just have water, Jolly.
Water. Sure, no problem.
Please have a seat, ma’am. I’ll get your water.
- Okay, thank you. - Okay?
Okay, I’ll be right back. Have a jolly morning.
Is this the one?
Impossible.
Really?
We’ll be together for Christmas–
in New York?
I can’t believe it!
Me too.
This is amazing.
Our families are both going to the U.S.
New York and New Jersey are pretty close to each other, right?
Yes! We can easily meet up there.
I’m so excited since it’s just going to be my second time going there.
I have a lot I wanna go to.
We can do everything you want there.
And we’ll do everything you want, too.
Everything?
Are you sure?
Don’t be silly!
But before that,
there’s something I want to do.
If it’s okay with you, I’d like to finally introduce you to my parents.
That way, we can ask permission from them personally.
Sure.
I’d love to.
I’ll show them that you’re safe with me.
Mom, Dad!
- Luna! - Hello.
Hello.
Mom, Dad…
This is Kalix, my boyfriend.
Hello, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
Perfect timing, we just ordered appetizers.
No, no. It’s okay.
Just sit down.
That’s fine.
Have a seat.
Order what you want.
Okay then. You want anything, Kalix?
You choose.
Thank you.
Just keep eating, Kalix. No need to be shy.
All right then.
So Luna, what’s your plan after here?
Nothing.
We had set this day just for this.
I actually wanted to introduce myself to you.
Oh, that’s nice.
So, I heard you’re taking Legal Management?
Yes, I’m planning to take Law school, too.
Law school.
Future lawyer. I see.
What are your plans after law school?
I’m planning to work as a defense attorney in a law firm.
After gaining experience and trust from the clients,
I’m planning to open my law firm too.
So, you’ll be focusing on criminal law, I assume.
Why so?
Why not, let’s say, corporate law?
I like a good challenge, sir.
A good challenge.
You like a good challenge.
What if a murderer wants to hire you, would you accept it?
D-Dad! What's with all the questions?
Innocent until proven guilty, sir.
Everyone has the right to be represented in court.
But whatever happens, whatever decision I make,
I’ll always choose my moral principles above anything else.
I like that.
I really like your answer.
It’s quite rare for someone to have set plans for the future.
Especially with kids these days.
You have a very thorough plan for your future.
So, good job.
Thank you.
Actually, your daughter helped me to dream bigger.
Are you saying that our daughter is part of your future?
Yes, sir.
I can assure you that I only date to marry.
And the only goal of dating your daughter is
to marry her, one day.
Of course, if that’s okay with you and Luna.
Oh, w-wait. Wait a minute, Kalix.
Let’s not talk about marriage. You're both still young.
Besides, my Louisse Natasha is still a baby.
Mom!
Just kidding, dear.
But Kalix, jokes are half-meant.
So, don’t worry about that yet.
Let’s just enjoy our meals for now.
- Let’s eat. - Here, Dad.
- Luna, want some soup? - Okay.
It was really good.
Here.
Thank you for the meal.
It was really nice meeting you.
Thank you for joining us, Kalix.
So, Luna…
He’s gonna take you home to the condo later?
Actually before leaving,
I wanted to ask for your permission.
If– is it okay if me and Luna meet up in New York?
Oh, you’re going to New York, too?
Yes ma’am, my family will spend the holidays there.
Don’t worry.
I’ll pick up and take Luna home.
I’ll take care of your daughter.
Wait, when are you planning to go to New York?
26th and the 27th.
We’re thinking of an overnight stay.
Just so we have time to roam around and rest after.
Yes and I’ll bring her back on the night of the 27th.
What do you think, Dad?
Kalix–
Just make sure…
that you have a Christmas present for us.
Okay?
And take good care of my daughter.
- I will. - All right?
Yes, of course.
So, it’s okay?
Yes.
Thanks, Dad.
Just behave yourselves.
Thank you so much!
What a mess!
What’s all this trash?
That’s why I called you to come over.
What for? Just seeing you is already a mess.
You talk too much, Sevi. You asshole.
Go start packing.
You asked me to come over just to pack your things?
Of course! What else could it be?
You could’ve just…
You could just call Kalix to do this so that I can also apologize to him.
Huh?
Apologize for what?
Well, we just beat his school the other day.
Camero!
What the heck.
I asked you to come here ‘cause I haven't been seeing you lately.
You seem to be quite busy.
Merry Christmas!
Wow!
Is this a bribe?
Thanks.
Where’s Ke?
She went home.
That’s why you’re the only one that could help me with this.
I’ll just give my Christmas gift to you when you get back.
When will you be home?
By the second week of January.
I’m extending my stay since
I’m meeting up with Kalix.
So, he’ll be in New York too?
Yes.
That’s why he’s not here, he’s already there.
By the way, I’ve already introduced him to Dad.
Wow!
I never realized you were that serious.
Of course, this is for long-term.
What did they say?
He liked him.
That’s why he agreed for us to meet in New York.
I’m so excited.
You know how strict Dad is.
That’s nice.
Well…
What’s gonna happen to all your other suitors now?
What?
I mean if I do have suitors, too bad for them! I’m taken.
You should find someone too, Sevi.
Wait, I forgot something.
Luna.
I’m really happy for you.
You’re so sweet, Sevi.
But you still make me cringe.
Hey! Stop.
This brat–
Take care in New York.
- Of course! - Don’t forget my shoe size, 11.5!
Yes, Ma! We went to a lot of places.
We just got home.
All right then.
Kalix!
Hi Aunty.
Yes.
I’ll take care of her.
Don’t worry about it. I have your gift right here.
All right. I’ll talk to you soon.
Bye, Aunty! Merry Christmas.
Luna.
Hello, Ma? All right, take care.
Bye! Love you.
I told you they’ll like you.
It’s amazing how it feels to actually see the paintings in person.
It really resonates,
I could feel it.
We’ll visit more museums soon.
Really?
Yes.
Give me a kiss.
We look so cute here.
You look cute there.
You know, it’s not my first time seeing the Statue of Liberty.
And everytime I do see it, it’s like, gives me hope.
It’s as if it’s telling you that
there is freedom and boundless opportunities for everyone.
I just hope,
that those boundless opportunities are actually for everyone.
I hope so, too.
But unless we learn from the past,
we’ll never be able to achieve that.
This is why I fell for you.
You're not only handsome, you also have great values.
Close your eyes.
- Why? - Just close your eyes.
Open your eyes.
What’s this?
‘Cause I know Christmas is all about giving
so this is my gift to you.
I know it’s just a mug,
but this will be a remembrance for us
‘cause I will never forget the memories that we will make here.
I’ll just make it up to you next time with a better gift.
There’s no need.
This is the best Christmas gift ever.
I’ll display this as a reminder of our first Christmas together.
A reminder of your love.
Wow, all this just with a mug as a gift?
Of course. Close your eyes.
Come on, close your eyes.
Think you’re the only one with a gift?
Sit down, hold on.
Open your eyes.
What?
Hope you like it, open it.
Wow!
Oh my god, this is beautiful, Kalix.
As soon as I saw that dress, I knew it would fit you perfectly.
Maybe you should wear it on a special occasion?
Luna,
I already met your parents,
and I think it’s time for you to meet mine.
I know I should’ve done this a long time ago but
but they were just too busy.
When?
Tomorrow.
I arranged a brunch with them
and it would be a really great holiday present if you’d come by.
Yes?
Yes.
- Yes? - Yes.
Why don’t you try it on?
Okay.
Thank you again.
This fits me perfectly.
Is it pretty?
You look great.
I’m now ready to meet the Doc Martinezes.
Together with my future
attorney and husband.
Really? Future husband?
Don't you like it?
Did I say that?
No. But,
would that be okay?
I would love to.
Try this. They say it’s really good.
It’s really good! Try it.
Oh?
Yes.
It tastes really good.
Taste it again.
Not that!
This one.
Aggressive.
Hm?
I am not, I just need a bit of human warmth.
It’s freezing, you know?
You’re craving me so much.
That’s not good.
I told you, I just need human warmth.
Next time, wear a skirt.
Wait, Kalix.
Can I handle this?
You’re silly.
I seriously haven’t done this before.
I know.
I’ll be gentle.
I love you, Luna.
I love you, Kalix.
Good morning.
How are you feeling?
I feel great.
Last night was wonderful.
Mom: We’re at the lobby.
Fuck.
Luna, fuck.
We gotta get ready.
Huh?
What’s wrong?
Mom and Dad are already downstairs at the lobby.
We can’t be late, come on. Let’s go.
Hey.
You will be fine.
Okay?
It’s my first time to meet my partner’s parents.
I don’t know what to do.
Look,
just like what you told me before meeting your parents–
just be you.
You can do this.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Mom, Dad.
How are you?
I’m good, how are you?
Fine.
Hi, Mom.
Mom, Dad,
this is Luna, my girlfriend.
Hi, Luna.
I’m Doctor Martinez.
Hi, Doc Martinez. Glad to meet you.
Please sit.
Where is Kio and Ate?
They stayed in the room.
Kio was so tired from our Staten Island trip yesterday
so they are resting in the hotel.
Too bad. I wanted them to meet Luna.
You’re late.
Yes, I know.
I’m sorry.
Well, it’s not even ten minutes, Hon. It’s fine.
I’m sorry, Mom.
I just didn’t hear my alarm.
Well, why don’t you order for the lady?
Yes, sure.
Luna, do you have any preferences?
I’m okay with anything.
I think you should try the risotto.
It’s really good. Right?
Yes.
- Luna, right? - Yes.
Where are you from?
From Manila. I’m studying Architecture.
Architecture.
Architecture?
Do you have a family business?
Like what are your parents’ source of income?
We have a construction firm.
Construction firm.
Mom.
Yes?
I think we should just order.
- Yes. - Yes?
Okay.
Waiter?
How are your grades, Kalix?
I heard about your five cuts and your 3.5 QPI.
Don’t worry.
I’ll pull them up this semester.
How did you learn about my cuts anyway?
Oh, Amethyst told me.
Why did you ask Amethyst?
Because Amethyst knows everything.
You go to the same class, remember?
And don’t tell me you cut your classes because
you’re so busy with your girlfriend.
No, Mom.
Or maybe you’re neglecting your studies
because you’re so busy flirting with her.
N-no.
Kalix, do you wanna be a good lawyer?
You think you’re gonna be a good lawyer
with your academic performance?
No offense, dear, okay?
I just think that Kalix had better grades
last year when he was with his ex-girlfriend, Amethyst.
Come on, Honey.
What, I’m just saying.
He’s gonna do better if he dates somebody
with the same goals instead of someone who’s a bad influence.
Oh dear, I’m not saying it’s you, okay?
It’s just a general statement.
That’s all.
I understand.
I’ll just go to the bathroom.
Excuse me.
Luna, wait.
Luna! Wait.
Luna!
Look, I’m sorry.
It’s not true. Amy was never my girlfriend.
It’s always been my mom forcing us to be together.
And about the absences, it’s all on me.
You had nothing to do with it.
Just leave me alone for now.
Luna, please. Let me explain, at least.
Explain?
Why didn’t you explain earlier when I needed you to defend me?
- I– - Why did you neglect your studies?
You could lose your dream because of me.
I’m not even that important.
You are important, Luna.
Not important enough to be defended from your mom, though?
I’m sorry.
I’m so sorry.
I can’t talk to you right now.
Luna.
Didn’t we promise?
Remember, we promised that we would talk it through whenever we have a fight.
Right?
I’m sorry,
I was too afraid of my mom
and too cowardly to defend you earlier.
I know I should have said something
but,
I was just too scared.
Ever since I was a kid, I was
always fearful of her and her high expectations.
All I did in my life is to please her.
Kalix, I understand.
I know how your mom is with you.
But what if she’s right?
What if you're really better with someone else?
That’s not true.
You make me better.
You, Luna.
But your mom wants Amethyst for you, not me.
Hey.
No one can ever stop me from loving you.
Not even my parents.
I promise that I will defend you and our relationship.
I am scared of my mom.
But I’m more scared of losing you.
Okay?
Can we make this work?
We can figure it out.
Together.
I promise I’ll make this work.
Let’s just fix this, right now.
How was New York, Luna?
Did you celebrate the New Year with a–
bang?
Yanna! You’re so perverted.
What's wrong with the word "bang"?
Why are you speechless?
Oh! No way?
- No way? - Oh?
- Hey! - The heck?!
I miss you guys.
I miss you too, girl!
Our Christmas break was just short but I still missed you all.
- I know. - Let’s just take a selfie.
All right then.
One, two, smile!
I missed you all, too.
Ke!
Ke…
I’m sorry, girls.
I was too defensive last time.
I know that you’re all just concerned about me.
I'm sorry for not telling you that I already have a boyfriend.
I’m really sorry for what happened during Christmas.
Ke!
I’m sorry, too.
I’m sorry that I pressured you to tell us things
even if you weren’t ready to talk about it yet.
I should have respected your boundaries.
I’m sorry, too.
I know I was too much.
I never doubted that we’ll patch things up.
I know we care for each other so much like real sisters.
Like real sisters?
What? I’ve always thought that we really are real sisters.
Hey! This will be the last okay?
This shouldn't happen again.
I got scared, I really thought that this was the end of our friendship.
Hey–
Come on, Via. Aren’t we in this for the long run?
Didn’t we say that we will all reach our dreams together?
We can do this!
Right, Ke?
Come here. This calls for a group hug!
Group hug!
I love you!
We missed you, Ke.
I love you, guys.
Come on. Let’s have lunch before we go.
Oh?
Why did you get a fruit shake?
Are we on an excursion?
I said I needed coffee and an energy drink.
Why so grumpy?
How many cups of coffee did you have?
That’s not healthy, you know?
You haven’t even had lunch yet.
It’s okay, Kalix and I are meeting up later.
We’ll eat at Noval.
How are you?
We’re still together.
Going strong?
Of course.
Happy?
Very happy.
That’s good.
You know what would make me happier?
I’d be happier if you’ll give me a copy of the readings I need from you.
You think you're that hot?
I am definitely hot.
That’s why Kalix fell for me.
I wonder why Ke’s mom is calling.
Hello, Aunty?
Why are you crying?
What?
Okay, we’re on our way.
What is it, what happened?
Ke was rushed to the hospital. Come on!
Let’s go!
There.
There’s the emergency room!
- Excuse me, excuse me. - Nurse!
Yes? Good evening, ma’am. How can I help you?
I was told that Kierra Ynares was rushed here.
May I have your name, ma’am?
How are you related to the patient?
Luna Valeria, we’re cousins.
We were told that she’s here in the emergency room, may we go inside?
My apologies, ma’am.
Her mom is already inside
and only one companion per patient is allowed.
- Please wait for a while. - But–
- Luna, it’s okay. It’s fine. - Please have a seat.
- Let’s sit. - Sevi.
Why? Why is she here?
How did Kierra end up here?
It’s going to be okay.
Kalix!
Hey.
It's okay.
I’m here.
What are you doing?
Those are my personal things.
Sorry. I just got curious.
I’ll just come back next time when you’re not busy.
Sorry!
- Sorry, sorry. - No, no.
No, it’s okay.
- It’s okay. - Sorry, I didn’t mean–
You hate me that much, Architect Valeria.
I’m so sorry, it wasn’t on purpose.
Those are very important client files.
Some even haven’t been digitized yet.
I’ll do anything to make it up to you. I’m really sorry.
Anything?
Yes, anything.
Okay, then.
Do my house in Tagaytay.
The nature of these injuries are suggestive of physical abuse.
Mr. Julian Miguel Villaflor brought the patient in.
This is all my fault.
Luna, don’t blame yourself.
We live in the same condo, Via.
How come I didn't notice
that something's going on with her?
About Kierra Ynares, she’s still in the hospital.
No medical certificate, no extension for deadlines.