I want your help picking a gift for Teerak.
I have no idea what to get.
I think you need to help him.
If he does this by himself,
he won't last long before getting caught.
- Alright.
- Giving him flowers will be romantic.
Right.
I'll book a restaurant for my surprise.
Can you come with me?
"To my Sea."
Babe!
Thank you so much, Fah.
Today has brought me so much joy.
I'm glad you liked it.
Let's go to sleep.
Goodnight, my Sky.
Goodnight, my Sea.
[Disclaimer: All depicted events are fictional
and for entertainment purposes only,
and viewer discretion is advised]
[Muenfah]
[Teerak]
[Real]
[Hia]
[Punlee]
[Ghlaijai]
[Type]
[Joy]
[Babe]
[Dom]
[Directed by Nathawat Piyanonpong]
Is it hard? You look so stressed.
- Dad!
- Yes, dear?
Why were you so loud? What?
I have an idea!
I need money to produce and sell this guy.
That's not a big deal.
What do you need it for? How much?
I'll give you the money.
No, there are things I need.
I need to earn the money on my own.
I just want your help talking to Uncle Wit,
and I'll take care of the rest.
Hold on.
What do you need the money for?
Fah's graduation gift.
Aw!
You're the rich one now?
Entering the world of buying gifts?
Let me tell you something.
If you're really becoming one,
it's good that you buy Fah a gift.
But you need to buy me some.
Buy Mom some.
Get some for Babe
and Grandpa.
Okay?
I don't have money, Dad.
You can't say that.
You need to buy gifts for all of us.
You get it, huh?
You need to be fair!
Okay?
Alright, I'll call Wit, then.
Aw, thanks, Dad.
Don't worry.
I'll always support anything you like.
Yay! I love you the most, Dad!
He's picking up.
Wit!
Right.
Can you spare me five minutes?
Alright, remember my son?
So, you're selling your art toy now?
Yes, it's in production.
Don't forget me when you hit it big.
May that come true.
If I do, I'll never forget you.
- Keep your word.
- Yeah.
I'll record it.
If it really works,
I'll save the money
for Fah's graduation gift.
You need to save the money?
Yeah, well...
he's given me so many things.
I want to give him some, too.
I'm serious, Lee.
I have to give him surprises!
Yeah, you got this.
Mm.
How about this one?
It looks like...
Is it a strawberry?
Inn! Noh!
- Hey, Teerak.
- Teerak.
- You're eating here?
- Yeah.
Got a table yet?
Not yet.
That's great.
There are just two of us.
Care to join us?
Right, join us, Teerak.
Let's do that.
Fah, I forgot to tell you.
They're Inn and Noh, my friends.
You met them
at the New Year party, remember?
- Hi.
Let's share the table with them, okay?
- Sure.
- Alright.
Ever tried a rambutan?
A rambutan?
Have some, Teerak. It's good.
You only do that to Teerak.
Give me some.
Do it yourself.
When did you guys become friends?
Since we were freshmen.
We worked in the same group,
but we rarely meet now
as we're in different majors.
That's unfortunate.
Yeah, you're right.
If you had chosen to live in the dorm,
we would have been roommates.
You're actually fortunate, Teerak.
He talks to his camera for hours.
The next thing he knows,
it's already midnight.
Well, that's work.
So you're an influencer now?
I'm happy for you.
Your dream's finally come true.
Aw.
It's actually because
you've always been there to cheer me up.
Otherwise, I would have already given up.
Come on, eat up.
Here.
Have some, too.
Okay.
This reminds me of the Open House.
Right, back then,
my hands were full of stuff,
and I had to take a motorcycle ride.
Inn even had to take me home.
I felt so bad.
Don't be, Teerak.
I was the one...
who asked you to stay with me.
I had no idea
what excuse I should tell Babe.
Well, you were dragging her brother
into trouble.
No, it was fun.
Right?
He liked it.
Yeah.
I'll fill it for you.
Okay.
Something's on your lips.
The sauce's on your lips.
I'll get you more sauce.
Thanks.
We've almost eaten everything.
Should we order more?
- Yeah, sure.
- Okay.
- How about this one?
- This?
Excuse me.
One of everything, please.
- Your sauce.
- Thanks.
Teerak.
Here.
Fah...
We're not alone.
Choo-choo-choo-choo.
You like ice cream, right?
Shall we get some?
Sure, let's go.
You're not having some?
I'm not a fan of sweets.
I see.
Teerak.
Well...
There's something...
I've been wanting to tell you.
I...
I have feelings for you.
It started when we were freshmen,
but I'm not sure if you...
I'm in a relationship.
I know.
I know that.
I'm not going to mess with you guys.
I just wanted to tell you how I feel.
Good? Is it enough?
Should I get you some more?
I'm good. I'm already so stuffed.
You're the cutest, my baby.
Fah,
why don't you come in? It's raining.
Do you want to tell me anything?
That friend of yours...
He likes you, doesn't he?
Did you hear Inn and me talking?
I followed you, so I heard it.
Yes.
He likes me,
but we talked.
He even told me we're an adorable couple.
I have feelings for you.
It started when we were freshmen,
but I'm not sure if you...
I'm in a relationship.
I know.
I know that.
I'm not going to mess with you guys.
Thanks.
You're one of my good friends.
So, does Muenfah treat you nicely?
Yeah, I love him so much.
I get that.
I'm happy for you.
You two are so adorable together.
Thanks.
I meant to tell you that as well.
If you feel uncomfortable,
you can let me know.
I'm jealous.
You were way too adorable,
so I didn't know how to act.
A combo set of sorry kisses.
Are you good now?
Well...
My boyfriend is so cute,
how do I stop myself from getting jealous?
Give it to me. I'll hold it for you.
It's okay to be jealous. I understand.
I also know...
that my guy's kinda hot.
So...
We need to communicate if there's a problem.
Yeah, understood.
Anyway...
I wanna know this.
Who's hotter: me or Inn?
It's you!
I like it when you're jealous. It's cute.
I also like it when your jealousy
makes you call me your baby.
You do?
Yeah, I like every name you call me.
So...
Can I have a kiss from my baby?
Should we go inside?
- Okay.
- We'll get sick.
I heard Fah was feeling jealous of you.
Yeah,
and it was bad.
If you're that curious, just join us.
- Okay.
- Right.
So, tell me about it.
What do you mean
he was jealous of you so badly?
He told me someone was hitting on you.
Yeah, it was Inn.
- What?
Inn?
We ran into him at a shabu-shabu place,
so we shared a table.
He then confessed his feelings to me.
I knew it. Something was off.
How was Muenfah, though?
Was he okay?
Well,
I told him I'm in a relationship.
And Muenfah was...
jealous.
He was jealous but not unreasonable, right?
We talked it all through,
and it's all cleared up now.
You did?
- Right.
- Okay.
That's good.
Muenfah's such a green flag.
He's my idol.
Yeah, I want a boyfriend like him.
You?
You wish.
Shut it.
You want some of this?
You must be
very stressed lately, right?
Yeah, I am.
I need to finish my project.
Don't worry, my Sea.
You're the best, my Sky.
You can do it. Trust me.
So...
when my movie releases,
you need to come watch it, okay?
Of course.
I'll be there for you.
So...
you got this!
- Thanks, my Sea.
- Yep.
Fah, I have an idea.
I'll take you somewhere to unwind.
- To unwind?
- Yeah.
I want to look after you, too.
Let's go on a trip.
I'll take care of everything.
You can just wait for it.
Okay.
I'll look forward to your getaway.
Let's go.
- Over there?
- Yeah.
Why are we going there?
Ghlai.
Yes, how can I help you?
Well,
I DMed you on Insta, but you didn't answer.
So, I wanted to get your contact instead.
Oh, Lee.
You look so nice today.
Just nice,
or nicer than that jerk?
Outstandingly nicer.
I don't know how to respond to that.
You're freaking cute.
I am every day.
That's right.
You're always cute.
So...
let's celebrate your birthday.
How did you know it was my birthday?
So, how did you know it was my birthday?
That's a secret.
And...
Why are you peeling so many shrimp?
I think that's enough.
No, I'm not done yet.
Eighteen, nineteen, twenty.
This is the last one.
Why twenty-one?
It's your age.
Lee, I'm sorry
I haven't been talking to you much recently.
I haven't finished studying for my exams.
That's alright.
You've been getting a lot of attention lately.
From whom?
Come on, a lot of people.
They're even flirting with you
on Insta comments.
I haven't read them.
If someone tries to pick you up
right in front of me,
what should I do?
No one can peel shrimp for you
better than I can, though.
Can I have another gift for my birthday?
Of course you can.
What if...
I want us to be more than just...
friends?
If you don't say anything,
I'll take it as our talking stage, okay?
With that status,
my heart's beating so fast.
Feel it if you don't believe me.
Wait, I haven't cleaned my hands.
Let me clean yours.
Fah, where do you think we should go?
How about Ko Racha?
I kinda wanna go to the sea.
Sure.
How about...
Railay Beach?
This one is also stunning.
Mm, that's nice.
Or the Emerald Cave? Do you know it?
It's the greenish water.
Choui Fong Tea Plantation?
Where should we go?
I'll find the hotel, too.
Or they'll be fully booked.
I'm fine with anything.
You can decide.
Prasat Hin Pan Yot?
Mm.
I'm okay with that.
How about...
Phu Lom Lo?
Hello.
Hello, Real. It's Yam.
Oh, what is it?
Are you going to the reunion party?
Next month, on the 8th.
The 8th?
I don't think I can make it.
We're having a graduation film screening,
so I'll probably be busy all week.
Oh...
when is that happening?
You didn't invite me, though.
Fine, I'll invite you. It's on the 11th.
I'll take that as an invitation, then.
See you.
Alright.
What's wrong?
Look at that face.
Why didn't you pick up my call?
Why did I need to?
I was already at your door.
Let's eat.
What's this?
You said, "Let's eat."
The noodles, not my lips!
I'll eat more than just your lips.
No, I quit.
Hey.
No, come on.
Hey!
What? Why?
Fine.
What? You want a fight?
Wanna do this, huh?
Hey, stop.
What?
I like this.
You do?
Hey!
Let's do it for real now.
Fah.
Here's the plan for the trip.
Here.
I wanna take you to see
some gorgeous mountain views
so that you can relax.
[Our Travel Route to Khao Yai National Park]
Whoa...
This is such a lovely-looking travel route.
Have you booked a place to stay?
I'm working on it. I've seen reviews of one.
Let me book it real quick.
Hello, I'd like to book
a room for this weekend stay, please.
Is there a room available?
We're very sorry,
the rooms have all been fully booked
for this weekend.
What about next month?
They're also fully booked.
They're all booked?
We're very sorry about that.
Are you interested in a weekday stay?
That's okay.
We're not available on weekdays.
Okay. We're sorry for the inconvenience.
Thank you.
They're fully booked until next month, Fah.
Don't be sad, okay?
We don't have to go there, honestly.
Just having you by my side
makes me happy enough.
I just wanna treat you
like what you've been doing for me.
Who says that you haven't done any of that?
Isn't just being together,
asking me
if I want anything,
if I'm tired,
and worrying about me,
considered taking care of me?
But that's...
Thank you
for taking care of me.
Moreover, don't worry.
I'll take care of you as well.
My Sky of my Sea is the best.
That tickles, Fah.
Can't I give you a smooch?
You can, but...
Let me do the same for you.
You're such a lovely partner.
You deserve a treat, right?
Huh?
What treat?
You want this, don't you?
How do you know?
This one's for you. Nom!
Isn't it tasty?
Here, let me feed you this.
Nom...
Can I try the salmon steak?
Uh-huh. Let me get you some.
Oh, watch for the bones.
Here you go.
Nom!
- Fah, would you like to try this?
- Yeah.
- Would you like to try this?
- Nope.
Choo-choo! Choo-choo!
What?
It's amazing.
It's still hot, too.
Here.
Can you stay here tonight?
Sure!
Fah! Someone's calling!
Can you answer it for me, Teerak?
Hello?
Fah, this is Yam.
Uh...
Please give me a moment.
Is that Lee? It's me, Yam.
It's not.
Let me give the phone to Fah real quick.
Hello?
Fah, it's Yam.
Who is that?
Hello?
How are you? Are you doing well?
What is it?
I'm inviting you to the reunion party.
It's on the eighth.
I can't come. I'm busy.
Is it because you're working on
the same project as Real?
Mm.
Well, I'm looking forward to
seeing the finished project.
You're coming to see it?
Yes, I miss you, Fah.
What about you?
Do you miss this ex-lover of yours?
Teerak.
Are you mad at me?
Fah, I'm feeling a bit bad,
and I don't want to feel this way.
What should I do?
What is it that you're feeling?
I'm possessive of you, Fah.
Even though I know that
you're not going anywhere,
I'm still possessive and jealous.
Thank you for being honest with me.
Do you remember that
you once told me that
if we feel uncomfortable
or if there's a problem,
we need to communicate?
I don't wanna act childish.
- But...
- That's okay, Teerak.
It's my turn to speak my mind.
I understand why you felt that way.
It's natural to feel that way.
Still, I can assure you that
I will forever be yours, Teerak.
I now understand what you felt on that day.
On that day?
Back at that restaurant,
you felt uneasy about Inn, right?
This time, I felt the same way about Yam
despite not knowing her at all.
It's true that I once dated Yam,
but we broke up a long time ago.
But she invited you to the reunion party.
Yet, I decided not to go there.
Do you wanna go, though?
I don't wanna do anything
that makes you feel uncomfortable.
It's only you who I wanna spend time with.
Since we're always together,
You won't get tired of me, right?
I won't.
I can simply
spend the rest of my life with you.
But...
Tomorrow,
I have to go home.
Why, though?
You're still upset with me?
Nope.
I just wanna work on my assignment.
You can work on it here.
I'm afraid that
I won't get it done here, Fah.
If that's the case, I'll drive you home, okay?
Can I have a hug before you go back home?
Once we finished the production,
I had no exams.
No exams or classes?
I had classes, but...
It was the beginning of the semester,
so I didn't have to do much.
But when a new production started...
I have exams.
Exams and projects.
- Good.
- Yeah.
Cause I have a midterm exam next week.
Okay, turn a bit and smile.
Look at him before saying hi.
Again, Inn and Noh.
[Root for them!]
Walk in again.
And action.
Look at him, smile, and say... "Sure."
- "Mm, sure."
- That's it.
Do you get it?
Yes, I get it.
Have some, Teerak.
[It's good]
You'll try to be the first.
They're setting up the next scene,
so I'm waiting right here.
[Chose the right spot]
- Yes?
- What did you say?
I'm not eating this alone.
I've got my boss.
Yeah, a bad boy.
Oh, Teerak.
Oh, Noh and Inn.
[Do I look cool, guys?]
I'm chewing air.
Nothing in my mouth.
[He's wanted]
♫Is it okay...♫
This won't work. The audio...
You know why?
Cause there's James.
He's always like this.
[Always loud]
Gems, focus on your script.
Stop talking to the camera.
- Inn and Noh.
- Okay.
Your dialogue, come on!
- Inn and Noh!
- Oh, Teerak.
Oh...
[Possessive gaze]
Okay, let's do a full scene practice.
Take your phone away.
Good.
Okay.
Good?
Great. Nice.
[Auau teases Save again]
No, I quit.
What? Hey!
Cut.
[Practicing first]
Ghlai's line's next.
Oh...
[Dropped something]
On your cheek.
[The rain came unexpectedly...]
[Some changes must be made to the script]
Dolly, cut two; take two.
Thomas, turn this way.
Oh, I didn't see him.
Sorry, bro.
Nice.
[Having a romantic moment]
Ready, set.
Hey!
[Got caught]
And action.
Cut.
Since we're always together...
[Does this help with the memorization?]
I just wanna work on my assignment.
[Motorcycle noise]
Hug him tight. Nice.
Spin around.
Hug him tight and spin.
That's good.
That's it. So easy.
I won't hear the dialogues.
Can you show me how to do Tai Chi?
This isn't working.
Gosh...
Jeez.
[What do I do?]
That's not true. I saw you.
He told us...
we had to dance.
What kind of dance?
He said Kong must do the Tai Chi dance.
- Do you know what it is?
- No.
- So I don't know how.
- So you're Thai
and chichi.
The card says that
at some point in time,
your partner will be pulled away.
I need to fly to Hong Kong.
I might have to be there kinda often, too.
Be sure to treat each other with love.
Congratulations to you, Fah.
Thank you.
I got you another gift, too.
However,
it's in your room.
A gift for you, Fah.
Me and a bow.