[Fate Chooses You]
[Episode 23]
Watch out!
Mr. Gui
was killed by me.
If you have the guts,
come and take my life.
Be good and come back
to Qianyan Cave with us,
and you'll suffer less.
You once told me
your master sent you down the mountain
to find your path
and survive your tribulation.
Yes.
Then does slaying demons
count as your path?
Does saving people
count as your path too?
They abandon mothers and keep sons,
raise Gu to harm others, murder and rob,
have no moral principles,
and disregard blood ties.
They claim territory as kings,
and in that tiny place,
commit the filthiest,
most shady deeds in the world.
How are they
any different from demons?
They are even worse.
So,
you must help me.
I need you.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to be the sharp blade
in my hand,
piercing the sky
that covers hell.
I want a beam of light to shine down,
illuminating all those demons
and burning them
with nowhere to escape.
Sheng,
I haven't seen you for so many years.
You really have improved a lot.
Jin Lun!
What a coincidence.
We meet again.
It's not a coincidence.
This place is called Wushui Cliff.
It is thousands of feet high
and bottomless.
Although it is called
Wushui (without water),
it's worse than having water.
What do you mean?
It's densely covered with insects.
Even Void Stage masters
who stumble in
will struggle to survive.
Just you?
It's us.
Golden Bracelet of Demon Suppression.
Tianyin Mountain's treasure
is actually in your hands.
Such a treasure falling into your hands
is really a waste.
Legend has it that this bracelet
can summon the power
of the Divine Dragon and White Tiger
and crush the flesh and blood
of those who enter the formation.
But your skill is lacking.
You are merely all show and no substance.
Although I don't have
the Divine Dragon and White Tiger,
I have the Yuanyi Twin Swords.
Can you still hold on?
I'm fine.
Sheng,
do you want to kill your own father?
He is your father?
Sheng,
didn't you tell your friend
your story?
Why?
Do you also agree
that patricide violates moral ethics,
something you're ashamed to even speak of?
Father?
Do you deserve it?
For so many years,
how many sons have you fathered
and how many women have you harmed?
I barely survived
from my mother's womb,
but I didn't expect
that on the day I was born,
I would fall into
another devil's den.
You look down on us
as if we're nothing.
In your eyes,
all children are just
your stepping stones
to ascend into godhood.
In this Qianyan Cave,
all ethics and familial bonds
are cast aside.
The father abandons his duty,
and children forsake theirs.
How twisted and disgusting!
Does a person like you
deserve to be called a father?
Whether I deserve it or not
is not up to you.
I gave you life
and a place to stay.
Even if you are full of resentment,
even if you live by my side
like a stray dog,
you are still my child.
Blood ties can't be severed.
Even if you refuse to admit it,
they will always exist.
When I first escaped,
I tossed and turned every night.
My senior sister used to tell me stories
to put me to sleep.
In those stories,
my favorite character
was Nezha.
To save the people, Nezha
killed the Dragon King's son.
But he was misunderstood by his father,
who blamed him
indiscriminately.
Filled with grief and indignation, Nezha
severed his bones to his father
and rent his flesh to his mother.
From then on, he severed
this ill-fated blood tie.
I envy him
for having such great abilities.
Unlike me,
even though I loathe you so much,
I still have to
live with this blood running in my veins.
However,
I later thought of
a good idea.
If you die,
won't this bloodline be severed?
So,
for me to get a good night's sleep,
please be merciful
and just die.
Jin Lun, help me!
You...
How is it?
How does it feel
to be wounded by the Bonding Curse?
Do you feel desperate?
Do you want to curse?
When...
When did you do this?
Good.
Very good.
You truly are my daughter.
Smart enough
and ruthless enough.
I'm going to kill you.
I'll kill you!
Then you must
have the ability to do so.
Times have changed.
Now I'm the hunter,
and you're the prey.
Your life is in my hands.
Do you have any other choice
except for begging me to spare you?
Do you think I'm afraid of you?
Will you
really sacrifice yourself for me
and die with me?
Sheng,
I really
underestimated you before.
In fact,
among the over 100 children,
you're the one
who takes after me the most.
Unfortunately,
you've still got a long way to go.
Jin Lun,
kill him quickly.
If I kill him, will you die?
Sheng!
Do it now.
I can't hold him off much longer.
Sheng!
Do it now.
Hurry!
It has worked.
Jin Lun.
♪ Hear the Gu curse
turn into cries for help ♪
♪ Blood-stained hand, sword drawn ♪
Jin Lun!
♪ Trapped in Qianyan Cave ♪
♪ Even hell must be broken free from ♪
Jin Lun!
Hold on to me!
♪ With every stroke of hatred ♪
♪ Let it grow into a dagger I wear ♪
♪ No need to show me mercy there ♪
♪ Let me take every blow ♪
♪ Drag my wounds through the hollow road ♪
♪ I'll pluck the passion
locked in my brow ♪
♪ At the end of the mountains,
I pick up fireflies now ♪
♪ Burn me down, I feel no pain ♪
♪ I believe Heaven sees all ♪
♪ Its wrath shines upon demons ♪
♪ But who will show me mercy? ♪
♪ I believe I'm innocent ♪
♪ Turned into dust and scattered away ♪
Jin Lun.
♪ I accept the blame of
numerous accusations ♪
Jin Lun!
♪ I offer no defense ♪
♪ I accept this as my only choice ♪
♪ I admit my heart
is as hard as iron and stone ♪
♪ Call me cold if you must ♪
♪ Until I die ♪
♪ I accept this trial of love
fate has given me ♪
♪ I take in both love and hate alike ♪
Soft white buns!
Steamed buns!
They look good.
Sir.
Have a taste.
How much for the steamed buns?
Take it.
Three wen for one, and 5 wen for 2.
That's expensive.
You call this expensive?
Can I get a discount if I buy more?
How many do you want?
All of them.
All of them?
Extracted from 3 taels of mint leaves,
it's guaranteed to refresh your mind.
It's not strong enough.
Take a look around.
See anything you like?
This one is just right.
This is a fine weapon.
Have you made your choice?
This feels very good.
Master,
are you willing to accept me
as your disciple today?
Master.
If you don't agree today,
I will ask you again tomorrow.
Master.
Then I'll go sharpen your sword.
Welcome, Sirs.
What kind of tea would you like?
Sir,
we are booking the whole place.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
Sorry for the trouble.
[Sifang Teahouse]
The Sihe Library
opens once every 5 years.
Each time it opens for 10 days.
So we must memorize
the complete "Unparalleled Secret Magic"
within 10 days.
For this trip to North Xiang,
we had 36 people in total,
divided into 3 groups.
But right now,
only 20 have arrived.
For those who didn't make it,
I'm afraid they never will.
Since we are here,
we can't let them down.
We have to memorize their parts as well
and bring them back to the Central Plains.
The "Unparalleled Secret Magic"
consists of 120 volumes.
Astronomy, Calendar,
Arithmetic, Craftsmanship, and Literature—
the volumes of each category vary.
Besides what was originally assigned,
who else
can memorize more?
For the Astronomy volumes,
I can memorize 3 more volumes.
Okay.
Chai Yu's 5 Astronomy volumes
changed to 8.
I'll cover
all 24 Calendar volumes.
Really?
Don't force yourself.
No problem.
Trust me.
Okay.
I can memorize 5 more Astronomy volumes.
That leaves Arithmetic and Craftsmanship.
Who else can memorize a few more volumes?
I can take 5 more Craftsmanship volumes.
Arithmetic.
I'll take 6 more volumes.
These are Mind-Awakening Pills
from Chongling Valley,
which can temporarily
boost your brainpower.
It takes time for the effects to kick in,
so everyone should take them
before setting off.
They will take effect
just as we arrive at the library.
Please remember,
although this medicine is potent,
you must not take too many.
A maximum of 3 pills per person.
Any more than that,
and your body won't be able to handle it.
Why did you take so many?
I'm getting old,
and my memory is poor.
Better safe than sorry with a few extras.
I don't need them.
I can remember.
This time,
no matter what,
we must bring out
the "Unparalleled Secret Magic,"
even if it costs our lives.
Everyone,
when
the library closes,
or when you feel
that you can no longer memorize
any more content,
come straight back here.
Lu Zhanying and the others
will provide pen and ink
for everyone to write it down.
We will always stay here.
If you have any problems,
just let us know.
As you go forth,
you will face many hardships.
What we do today
may cost us our lives
and may not even leave a mark in history.
But please believe,
this battle
is for the people of the world,
for the future of our race.
Your righteousness empowers our race.
I, Tai Shiqian,
pay my respects to you.
Empower our race.
No regrets even in death.
-Empower our race. No regrets in death.
The library is open.
Go, go.
-Hurry. Hurry up.
-Go.
The library is open. Let's go take a look.
-Yes.
-Let's go.
Everyone,
the road to the revival of the Human Race
begins here.
[Sihe Library]
[Unparalleled Secret Magic]
[Astronomy]
Lord of Rust-Sword.
Stop right there.
One.
Two.
Zhanying.
What are your orders this time?
Let me ask you,
where is the flower
I gave you this morning?
I threw it away.
Threw it away?
Where did you throw it?
It's right here.
Zhanying,
this flower is really beautiful.
Beautiful.
This mission is extraordinary.
Sending them to the library
is barely passing the first stage.
If the people
from the immortal sect catch up,
a fierce battle will be inevitable.
I was wondering
if we should send An
somewhere else.
I am a demon.
I can protect myself.
Don't be childish.
A demon's life matters too.
Whether sending you away
or taking you with us,
it's all for you to live.
If you die because of us,
wouldn't that defeat the purpose?
Then it would have been better
not to bring you along.
I don't want to leave.
I don't have a home.
I have nowhere to go.
I don't know
what big plan you are talking about,
but
since Master protects you,
I will protect you too.
Although my power is average,
I can serve tea and water.
At worst,
I can grind ink, do chores,
and deliver meals.
I won't cause you
any trouble.
All right.
If she wants to stay, let her stay.
She can just follow me.
I will protect her.
Then you'd better
take her as your disciple soon.
Otherwise, when this is over
and we part ways,
she'll have nowhere to go again.
That won't do.
I wade through blood
and corpses every day.
How can I take her with me?
Take her back to your home.
That depends on whether An is willing.
I think she just wants to follow you now.
What should we do?
Senior Sister asked you
to pass the message?
Don't take risks. Come back soon.
Come back soon.
I'm worried about you.
Where is she?
Lead the way.
I...
Sir.
What's the rush?
-Great! Great!
-Great!
Yes, drink more with the young master.
Come again next time!
How about
we go inside and look?
How could he be here?
In the Young Sect Master's heart,
there is only Senior Jiang.
It's impossible for him to be there.
[Tianxiang Restaurant]
-Young Sect Master?
Xu Feng sent a letter, saying
Lin Muhan has been found.
He is in Phoenix City.
In Phoenix City?
Where did they find him?
It didn't say.
But it said those
from the Wushuang Society
have already arrived in Phoenix City.
We need to hurry over there.
If we had intercepted
them on the way, it would've been fine.
Now that they are in Phoenix City,
I'm afraid a big fight is inevitable.
Senior Bai, don't worry too much.
They're just a group
of demonic cultivators.
How can we be afraid of them?
Makes sense.
Demonic cultivators.
You're awake.
Mr. Lu.
How do you feel?
Much better.
Still hurts a little.
You were badly injured,
so it naturally hurts.
Since you're awake,
why don't you take your medicine first?
It's bitter.
How could it be bitter?
You can't even taste anything.
How do you know it's not bitter?
I made the prescription.
Wouldn't I know if it's bitter?
Alright then.
I'll do it.
Where are we?
At a friend's house.
How long have I been asleep?
Five days.
How did they die?
I went to check their bodies
and found they were
poisoned by a Gu curse,
a very vicious type of Gu.
Once poisoned,
they can never get rid of it.
Someone killed their life-binding Gu,
so they died.
Who killed their life-binding Gu?
I don't know yet.
Don't worry.
I'm here.
By the way,
they destroyed the painting.
You like it?
If you really like it,
I can draw another one for you.
Really?
That's great.
From now on,
how should I address you?
Address me?
Lord Lu, Mr. Lu—
I can't call you those anymore.
Calling you by your full name
makes us seem distant.
How do your close friends
address you?
When I was
with my parents and master,
I was still young.
Besides Chu Ying,
I don't really have
any other friends.
Su Taiyi calls me Master.
Chu Ying just calls me Lu.
Then from now on, I'll call you
Qianqiao.
What's wrong?
You don't like it?
Yes.
I really like it.
No one
has ever called me that.
I'll call you that from now on.
Qianqiao.
Here are the clothes you asked for.
Thank you.
Please help the lady inside
change into these clothes.
Okay.
He's really...
Time to eat.
Not eating?
Sister-in-law,
you're awake.
Who are you?
Just call me Sha.
This is my home.
You were injured that day.
Lu brought you back.
I see.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Lu and I are as close as brothers.
His business is my business.
His enemies are my enemies.
His family...