In previous episodes,
Tsubasa and his teammates
earned their right
to participate in
the National Tournament.
However,
Wakabayashi cannot play
due to his injury.
He was furious,
but now,
he must continue to rest
while his teammates
play without him.
Tsubasa promised
Wakabayashi
they would win
all the matches
and he would be
ready to face Meiwa.
The coach gave Tsubasa
the ribbon,
making him the new
captain of the team!
And then...
Fellow players...
Let's play in
this tournament
showing honor and respect
to our opponents!
Let's play with passion
and a spirit of
good sportsmanship!
I'm here representing
Nankatsu!
My name is...
Tsubasa Ozora!
After a grand ovation,
the National Tournament
finally began!
And now,
the irony of fate
gave the first kick,
and Nankatsu
must now face Meiwa
in their first match.
Who will be victorious?
All right! This match is
very important!
I want you to give it
all you got!
-Yes, Coach!
Good shot!
Next player!
Here!
I won't let you down!
I'm sure that my foot
has healed by now.
I'm begging you!
Please wait until I heal!
We'll have to face Meiwa
in the first match.
But I don't care
what happens!
We will win this match.
I promise you we will win!
That's how it's done,
Tsubasa!
Yeah guys, that's right!
Focus! Let's leave
everything on the pitch!
-Yeah!
Team Meiwa...
Are you ready to
come on out?
Sorry for the--
Whoa!
Hey there, Coach...
it's time to go now.
Okay, go ahead, then!
I'll catch up to you.
It doesn't matter if I'm there
with you guys now.
MEIWA FC COACH
KOZO KIRA
He always prefers
to stay and drink.
A coach should not
behave like that.
Yes...
But even so, Coach Kira
trained Hyuga and Sawada
from the start.
That's made us
a very strong team.
He's a very good coach.
Kojiro, your only objective
is to win.
The end justifies the means.
Don't forget that.
All right.
Wow! There's
a lot of traffic today.
I've driven through here
many times, but I...
I've never seen it
like this.
That means that
today's game
has drawn lots of attention.
I bet that it will be...
very interesting.
I wonder who will be
the most outstanding player.
We will see that very soon.
We sure will.
[opening theme]
Episode 14:
Nankatsu versus Meiwa.
The matches
of the National Tournament
will take place on different
pitches simultaneously.
Before we start
the first match,
something that
we've never seen before
is taking place!
The stadium
is almost completely
full of spectators
that came to see the match
between Team Nankatsu
and Team Meiwa.
There are so many
people here, Roberto!
That's right.
There weren't this much
people in Brazil...
which is the country where
everyone loves football.
Hey, good thing
we arrived on time.
Yeah, and now we will see
who is the best of
these two teams.
Holy cow! There are
so many people here!
Hey, Taro,
don't let us down today!
Huh?
We will be here
supporting you, all right?
Thanks a lot, Hikaru!
I'll make sure I won't
let you down!
You can do it, Tsubasa,
you're the best!
This will be interesting.
Huh?
I wonder which of
these teams
will be the best rival.
Look, the players for Meiwa
-are coming now!
-Ohhh!
It's been a while, Nankatsu.
Kojiro Hyuga, that idiot.
You're the little twerp
who spoke moments ago, huh?
I'm going to show you
the true spirit
of the sport!
We are the team that will
win the National Torunament!
Since you are the team
we face
in the opening match...
you'll be the first to lose!
You stupid idiot!
Both teams
are now in their positions.
Team Nankatsu,
well known for
their excellent passing,
NANKATSU SC
are representing the Shizuoka Prefecture.
They use a 4-3-3 formation.
We know
their star goalkeeper
Genzo Wakabayashi...
will not play in today's
match due to an injury.
In his place,
Yuzo Morisaki.
Shingo Takasugi is
the leader of the defense.
It'll be very difficult
to get past them!
At the midfield positions,
we have Taro Misaki,
Mamoru Izawa,
and Hanji Urabe.
And at forward, we have
Hajime Taki, Teppei Kisugi,
and Tsubasa Ozora
as the Center Forward.
All right, guys!
I want you to leave it
all on the field!
-Yeah!
Their opponent today is Team Meiwa,
MEIWA FC
with a 4-4-2 formation.
Kojiro Hyuga,
a.k.a. The Tiger,
is their Center Forward
who's going to try to
score goals!
At his side will be
Takeshi Sawada,
the captain for
today's match.
Let's see how
this dynamic duo
will play together
on the pitch!
And in charge of
the line of defense today
is goalkeeper
Yuji Kawaguchi!
How crazy is this?!
There are so many people!
It'll be a great show!
Kojiro, now is the time.
Take control
during this match,
and impress them
with your power!
The match
between Nankatsu and Meiwa
is about to begin!
Meiwa will start
with the kick-off!
The referee takes
a look at his stopwatch!
There is no way
I'm losing this match!
Come here!
The captain
of Nankatsu, Tsubasa Ozora,
shows his superior
ball-dribbling skills.
But star player
Kojiro Hyuga
closes in to steal
the ball from him!
Meiwa's players look
very confident.
Tsubasa and Hyuga
kick the ball
at the same time!
And the ball
goes flying into the air!
The force of both players
sent the ball skyrocketing!
You little twerp!
-Taki!
-I got it.
You'll see, idiot!
What's this?!
My leg!
My leg's numb from
the impact with Kojiro!
Kojiro Hyuga can't move
to go get the ball!
Nankatsu now has
a golden opportunity
to score a goal!
Teppei!
Yes!
Now leave it all up to me!
The ball is recovered by
Takeshi Sawada of Meiwa,
who is
a fourth-grade student,
and we will certainly
be watching him closely!
No!
Takeshi!
Give me the ball!
What?!
-No way!
-What a beautiful play!
I can't believe Sawada
is only a fourth-grade boy!
Thanks to his skill,
Meiwa have the chance
to score the first goal!
It seems my leg
is no longer numb!
I'm with you, Takeshi!
This is
the true style of play
of the Meiwa forwards!
-Hey, Takeshi...
-Huh?
You've improved quite a lot!
Hi, Taro, great to see you!
Thank you!
Mr. Kira was my coach,
and that's why I play
like this!
He's the same person
who trained Hyuga!
Now, I'll show you
how much I've improved!
Takeshi Sawada
puts the ball
-through Taro's legs!
-How's that?
Huh?
But Misaki
has cat-like reflexes!
-Nice play!
-That's it, Taro!
Takeshi Sawada
couldn't get past
Taro Misaki!
Taro, you surprised me.
Misaki, if I would've
had the ball,
I would've scored
the first goal!
Huh? Whoa!
Excuse me, sir,
could you tell us
how Nankatsu's doing
in their match?
Taro Misaki
runs down field
at high speed!
There's no doubt that
he's a true prodigy!
You won't get past us,
Misaki!
Huh, what?
Taro Misaki stops
and sends a long pass!
The ball flies directly
toward Captain Tsubasa!
What an excellent pass!
Nankatsu has a chance
to score the first goal
of the match!
Okay.
What's going on?!
Tsubasa changes direction
toward Hyuga,
and it looks like
he wants to challenge him!
He will lose
his chance to shoot
going directly
toward him!
You think you can mock me,
you weakling?
Don't make me laugh!
I'll show you
who I really am, idiot!
What?
The... The ball...
It disappeared!
But...what's this?!
Ah! He did a--
Hmm...
Oh...
This is incredible!
Tsubasa mocks Hyuga
flipping the ball
in the air,
and it passes over him!
It floats over him
smoothly!
Tsubasa gets in and...
He puts
a shot on goal!
Yay, Tsubasa, you did it!
Goal!
Tsubasa scores
in three minutes
into the first half
of the match!
Meiwa will not win
this match!
It'll be Nankatsu!
What an impressive shot!
That was
the center forward
for Team Nankatsu.
He is practically
an unknown talent
on the national level,
who just scored
his first goal
against the mighty
Team Meiwa.
Huh?!
What do you mean
unknown talent, stupid?!
By now, you should've been
dreaming about him,
you ignorant commentator!
-That boy plays at
-Yeahs, that's how
-a high level for his age.
-it's done!
It's hard to believe he's
an elementary school boy!
On my count!
-We will, we will,
-we will win!
Very nice!
For this match,
I'm going to support
Team Nankatsu!
Defeated by
Tsubasa's incredible skill,
Hyuga looks completely
rattled right now.
We'll have to see if he
can regain his composure,
and launch
a counterattack to equalize!
Hyuga...
When you came to spy on us
during training,
you refused to watch
any longer.
If you had stayed,
you would've noticed
the innate talent
that Tsubasa possesses.
Forgive me, Kojiro.
It's my fault,
I let Misaki
take the ball from me.
Ko... Kojiro!
Yes, I know that look.
I can see it in your eyes,
my boy.
The eye of the tiger.
We'll be right back,
with Captain Tsubasa.
AFFILIATION: MEIWA FC BIRTHDAY: AUGUST 17 HEIGHT: 158 CM WEIGHT: 50 KG BLOOD TYPE: O
Meiwa will kick off again
to start the second half.
But Nankatsu
quickly takes the ball away!
After the goal,
the crowd fully supports
Nankatsu!
Now, it's my turn!
I'll score the second goal!
No!
Captain Hyuga!
What's wrong
with Kojiro Hyuga?
He's leaning on
one of the goalposts!
Teppei Kisugi shoots!
The goalie
can't stop it!
Will it go in?!
Off the post,
off the post!
No!
And Kojiro Hyuga
didn't even flinch!
Takeshi Sawada kicks
the ball off the bounce
and sends it
out of the box.
It's mine!
But Tsubasa
intercepts the ball
-and attacks again!
-Yeah, Tsubasa!
-Go, go!
-Come on Tsubasa,
-Come on, Tsubasa!
-keep going!
-You got this!
Meiwa can't stop him,
and it seems Hyuga
is a statue!
Why is he doing that?
Kojiro, wake up!
Tsubasa's approaching!
I won't let you
make a mockery of me!
Woah, Kojiro Hyuga
awakes from a trance
and heads directly
toward Tsubasa Ozora.
It seems he was
waiting for Tsubasa
to attack the net!
This... This will be
the second duel
between these
two players.
Hyuga heads directly
toward Tsubasa
to take away the ball!
You're not going
any further!
Take this!
Hyuga makes
a sliding tackle,
and Tsubasa tries to
avoid it!
Yeah, come on, Kojiro!
Wow!
He's trapped by Hyuga,
who stops him with his foot!
-Tsu... Tsubasa!
Tsubasa
falls to the ground,
but the ref doesn't
call a foul
and allows play
to continue!
What a brutal fall!
Hyuga's determination
seems to be taking over
the match!
Your team will not
win this tournament!
-Idiot!
-You'll see!
You'll pay for what
you did to Tsubasa!
Move to the side, idiots!
Kojiro Hyuga
gets ready to shoot!
What?!
From that distance?
Defend the goal!
Move it, guys!
Now you'll see
how terrible we are!
We are Team Meiwa!
What'd he do?
Where's the ball?
-It disappeared!
G... G... Goal!
The force knocks down
the goalie
and the ball's
in the net!
-Whoa!
You did it, Kojiro!!
Incredible!
He's so powerful!
Yes,
this is the true strength
of star player
Kojiro Hyuga!
Meiwa just scored
the equalizer.
We now have a tied match
on our hands!
No way!
He shot directly
at the goalie's face.
But why did he do that?
Very good!
That's how it's done,
my boy!
Yuzo, are you okay?
I'm...afraid!
You are an imbecile, Hyuga!
Nankatsu and Meiwa
are now tied
at one goal apiece!
It's a battle between
Tsubasa and Hyuga.
What?
Humph!
Aggression and passion.
-Huh?
-Nothing.
Tsubasa's style of play
is based on passion,
and Hyuga's style
is based on aggression.
-They're opposites.
-Ah, I see now.
But it's not just this.
Tsubasa enjoys
each movement on the field,
with a big smile
on his face.
And he moves as if the ball
were a part of him.
On the other hand,
Hyuga plays with
great determination...
and channels his spirit
in each shot
and turns into
a dominant player.
Exactly.
And plus, the coaches
from both teams
are also very different.
Yes, I know.
Tsubasa received training
from Roberto Hongo.
And Kozo Kira,
on the other hand,
is the one
who trained Hyuga.
Although there was
no professional league...
a foreign football scout
offered Kira
a spot on his team,
but he rejected it,
and nothing was known
about him for some time.
Both disappeared,
then came back as coaches.
Yes.
Anyway, we really only need
to pick one player.
The result of this match
will tell us
which of these two
is the outstanding player.
The score is still tied,
and Nankatsu is on
the attack again.
You got this, Misaki!
-You got it!
All right!
Ah! Takeshi Sawada
tries to steal the ball!
But Taro Misaki
won't let him get close!
Looks like Misaki
still has the advantage!
Taro!
Incredible!
Taro Misaki passes
to Teppei Kisugi!
Tsubasa!
And Teppei launches
a long pass.
That's it, Teppei, good job!
The ball is once again
controlled by Tsubasa.
Listen up!
I want everyone
to cover Tsubasa!
Don't even let him
take a breath!
Do you hear me?!
-Yeah!
Uh, uh!
Kojiro Hyuga
gives an order
to mark Tsubasa,
and the team runs quickly
toward him!
-Take this!
It's a barrage of
sliding tackles, folks!
Tsubasa's trapped,
but he is trying to
avoid them!
Ah, stop that!
That's a dangerous play!
They're not just
going for the ball,
they want to hit him, too!
They're
going after Tsubasa!
But he's able to
avoid them!
Ah, the defender kicks
Tsubasa in the knee
and he falls quickly
to the ground!
-No! Tsubasa!
Tsubasa's
on the ground,
and apparently this will
warrant a yellow card.
And now we see it!
-Do you see now?
-Oh!
We'll commit
all the fouls we can!
Don't even let this twerp
move an inch!
Uh, yes, Captain!
What?
As of right now,
you'll feel the difference
there is between us!
Mamoru Izawa is the one
who will take
the free kick.
They think we're weak!
We'll show them we're not!
Kojiro Hyuga
stops the ball
with his body!
Ah, but Tsubasa
runs directly at him
to take the ball away!
You're so annoying!
You would think the final
score would stay tied
given our abilities!
But that's a mistake.
Now, I'll show everyone
my power!
-Go!
-Whoa!
What a surprise!
Hyuga decides to pass
the ball.
Takeshi! Go!
-Take a shot on goal!
-What?
Yes, Captain!
Takeshi Sawada launches
a long-distance shot!
How stupid!
Even my grandmother
could stop that shot!
-Wait, what?!
-Huh?
Incredible!
The ball goes into
the net,
and goalkeeper Morisaki
barely even moved!
I'm...afraid...
-of the ball!
-Huh?!
Oh, so that was it!
Hyuga shot directly
at the goalie
to make him scared
of the ball!
Darn it, Hyuga,
how could you do that
to Yuzo?
Yuzo Morisaki
has no desire to
continue the match.
Unfortunately,
Nankatsu only has one goalie
and cannot make
a substitution.
Captain Hyuga is
very intimidating.
Yes, he is. Good thing
he plays for our team.
Could you imagine
if he didn't?
It's now two to one
in favor of Meiwa.
Now Nankatsu is behind
on the scoreboard.
Meiwa
attacks aggressively
and has control
of the ball!
Listen up!
Now anyone can score!
The goalie is just
an ornament now!
-Idiots!
-Yeah!
It looks like
Nankatsu's goalkeeper
is petrified!
His teammates
will have to block
-the opposition's shots!
-Here it goes!
-Yuzo, do something!
-Stop the ball!
This looks like
the third goal!
Ah!
The ball is stopped!
The center forward
of Nankatsu
intercepts the ball
skillfully!
That was a great play,
Tsubasa!
See that, Meiwa?
Our beloved Captain
also knows
how to play defense too!
-You see, Yuzo?
-Huh?
The ball is our friend,
so don't fear it!
What?
That nosy idiot!
No way!
You think the ball's
your friend, huh?
Well, if that's the case...
Here it is.
Kiss it!
Be careful, Tsubasa!
Be careful!
The ball
hits Tsubasa in the face!
If you love the ball
so much,
then how about you both
go into the goal!
What?!
Incredible!
Tsubasa stops the ball
with his hand and leg
against the posts!
No! Tsubasa!
See?
There's no need to fear it!
Tsubasa...
Oh...
Thank you so much!
Thank you, Tsubasa.
I will defend the goal!
-Now, I won't be afraid!
-That's it!
Good!
That's the spirit, Yuzo!
Nankatsu
has stopped another shot
thanks to the brave play
of their captain,
but Meiwa won't
stop attacking.
This time you won't save it!
Stop it, Yuzo!
I got it!
-Good job, Yuzo, you did it!
Yes!
The ball is my best friend!
I won't ever let it go!
Right, Tsubasa?
Right!
That twerp did it again!
He got his goalie to
regain his confidence!
Hyuga kicked the ball
directly at the goalie
to make him scared.
And then,
Tsubasa stopped the shot
with his face
on purpose.
But, why'd he do it?
It's obvious.
His intention was
to make the goalkeeper
to regain the courage
he lost.
Brilliant.
Tsubasa...
Really, thank you so much.
You don't know how happy
I am you are our captain!
Here you are, Tsubasa!
Take good care of
our friend!
Yes!
Now it's our turn to attack!
[ending theme]