So, what's up with you and Sun?
-You like each other.
-What are you doing?
But you're not girlfriends.
So, what kind of
relationship status is this?
I don't like Ongsa like this.
She's too pretty.
-Too gorgeous to handle.
-Wait!
-I don't know what you think of him.
-Stop. Just stop.
But I like you.
I already spoke my mind.
What do you want to do?
I like you, Sun.
Will you be my girlfriend?
Alpha!
I need your help.
Slow down, girl.
What is it?
Can I borrow a sheet mask?
Sun is video-calling me soon.
A sheet mask?
Human, can I borrow…
There's a panda in the house!
What was that?
Hello, Sun.
Crap! I forgot.
Well, well. Using face masks now, huh?
Like you're not pretty enough already.
I was preparing my skin for your call.
My girlfriend is always cute
regardless of how she looks.
Cute?
I'm… I'm not cute.
You're so flustered, you're stuttering.
Don't tease me then.
Fine. I'll stop teasing.
The stars are beautiful tonight.
Do you see them, Ongsa?
They're shining so bright.
I saw them.
They really are beautiful tonight.
But I think
no stars are more beautiful
than my girlfriend.
Hey! You're making me blush.
I'd love to stargaze with you.
Guys.
Can you please keep the thing
between Sun and me a secret for now?
It should be known just among us.
You're with Sun.
Why don't you want people to know that?
If they know someone like me
is dating Sun,
what will they say?
But what's wrong
with someone like you, Ongsa?
Sun is attractive, smart, and athletic.
She excels at all she does.
Now look at me.
I'm a loser. I suck.
I excel at nothing.
Humans always have complicated
and useless thoughts.
Listen to me.
Sun chose to date you.
You should care about her feelings
more than those of others.
I'm stressed.
It was hard enough before the confession.
Now that we're together, it's even harder.
And what do people
in relationships even do?
I don't know how to act.
It's so awkward.
I get her.
She's never been in a relationship before.
It can be difficult.
You humans
had never been in a relationship?
I know someone who can advise us.
He was once called
the master of worldly concerns.
Greetings, Luangpu.
Bless you all, my niece and her friends.
What is going on?
To what do I owe
the pleasure of this visit?
Is someone hapless again?
It's not haplessness this time.
It's love.
Luangpu, can you enlighten us on how
people in a relationship should act?
Do you think I'm a love guru or what?
Why did you come to me
regarding love issues?
But my mom told me you were
really something back in the day.
You're a man with years of experience.
Your mom exaggerated.
I've divorced myself
from worldly concerns.
But can you please recall your memories?
We don't know who else to turn to.
You're our last hope, Luangpu.
Love is all about feelings.
When you're committed
to being in a relationship,
nourish and take good care of
your significant other.
No lies.
But Mom told me that you…
Stop it. Don't talk.
People make mistakes sometimes.
But remember this.
Where there is love, there is lament.
Human monk?
Can we get something practical?
Something visually clear?
This is a worldly concern.
I can't help much.
However, in Buddhism,
there's a teaching for householders.
It's called The Four Principles
of Gharavasadhamma.
These are sacca…
-Goodbye, Your Holiness.
Oh my. They're fast.
I wasn't finished speaking yet.
You said we'd get something.
All we got was a sermon.
I honestly thought Luangpu could help.
I didn't know it'd be like this.
We came all the way here.
What a waste of time.
He must have truly divorced himself
from worldly concerns.
MERIT TIFFIN BOX
By the way…
You. Alien.
Why did you tag along?
Well,
I wanted to study the behavior of humans
when they're in relationships.
MERIT POSTBOX
That's Ton.
Hey, Ton. What are you doing here?
Hey.
My juniors.
I'm here to make merit
for my dedicated fans.
To celebrate 50,000 subscribers
on my channel.
Congrats, Ton.
Right. Thanks.
So, what are you guys doing at the temple?
Are you here for social work?
No.
I took Ongsa to Luangpu to get some advice
regarding worldly concerns.
Worldly concerns?
-Ongsa wants to know…
-Hey.
Let's not talk about it, Charoen.
What exactly do
people in relationships do?
Ongsa has no clue how to act around Sun.
You've just met the right person,
youngsters.
I, Mr. Ton, will teach you
just what people in relationships do.
Okay.
We've found a way, Ongsa.
What are you two doing?
Why are you looking so down?
Ton said
people in relationships go out on dates,
and that the first date
typically involves watching a movie.
And?
And it must be a romantic movie.
So?
When the crucial moment comes,
you strike.
Strike?
Put your mouth on the other person's.
Kiss.
What the heck, you guys?
I thought it was something serious.
This is ridiculous.
Why would humans
put their mouths on others' mouths?
The exams are approaching.
Sun might not be up for dating.
Ongsa, want to see a movie
at my place tomorrow?
What's the matter now?
Sun asked me to watch a movie
at her house.
Is this like a date?
It's our first date, isn't it?
Alpha, what should I do?
What should I do?
Alpha, why would humans put their mouths
on the mouths of other humans?
A meteor shower watch party at the school?
What are you thinking?
This is a once-in-a-decade opportunity
to see a meteor shower clearly.
If we don't set up the activity for this
Friday, we'll miss the chance.
It's unsafe to let students
come to school at night.
What if something bad happens?
I will ensure their safety.
It's my duty to do so.
You can't even ensure your own.
You're hapless and unlucky.
You trip and fall.
You can't take care of
a bunch of students.
Only members of the Astronomy Club
and the Mysterious Stories Club
will be allowed to come.
That amount, I can monitor.
That's still a lot.
You can't take care of them.
So because I'm hapless,
the students won't get to see
the meteor shower.
How about this?
If you want to set up this activity,
I'll help supervise.
Why would you help me?
You are unlucky, and I am lucky.
I can balance out your bad luck
and keep bad things from happening.
That's absurd.
How would that help? I don't believe you.
If you don't believe me,
walk out of this room and see.
Sorry, ma'am. I'm sorry.
See? Believe me now?
You need me, Teacher Bambam.
I'm so glad we're watching
this movie this evening.
I didn't watch it before
because I wanted to watch it with you.
Is it that good?
Yes.
I read the reviews.
Everyone says it was fantastic.
It made their hearts beat so fast
the entire time.
It must be really good for our souls.
Based on that info,
it's a romantic movie for sure.
Watching a romantic movie alone with Sun…
The thought of it…
makes my heart pound.
Today is full of good things.
One happens to be
this choc mint ice cream.
I love choc mint.
Is it that good?
Yes.
Have you not had it before?
Wanna try?
Holy shit.
This is like
an indirect kiss.
Well…
It's good.
Right?
Only people with good taste
love choc mint.
Ongsa.
Do you know that I never feel embarrassed
about being with you?
And I don't care about
what other people think.
I only care about you.
But if you're not ready
to tell other people yet, it's fine.
We don't have to tell anyone yet.
I don't want you to feel uncomfortable
just because we're together.
Actually, I'm worried that
I'm not a good girlfriend for you.
But I don't really know about the things
that people in relationships do.
Well,
just those things…
that people in relationships do.
Like what?
Is there anything you want me to do?
Anything?
Yes, anything.
I want…
I want you to
make a move on me.
What?
Make a move?
Come on, Ongsa.
Fight. Be bold.
Make a move?
Of course.
Once we get to the crucial moment,
the romantic scene,
prepare for it, Sun.
I will just get closer to her
and strike hard!
Yes, shoot them! Shoot them down.
That was unexpected.
Shoot it! Go left. Left.
Bang, bang, bang. Yes!
I didn't know you liked action movies.
I thought you meant a romantic movie.
You said it made people's hearts pound.
It does.
Isn't your heart pounding?
My heart is beating crazy fast right now.
Feel it. It's an adrenaline rush.
The crucial moment…
If you can't find it,
you can just make it, Ongsa.
Do it.
Make a move!
Shoot!
Sun.
I want…
Why did you slap me?
A mosquito. It was biting your cheek.
The first attempt failed.
Move on to the second.
Start over. Keep fighting, Ongsa.
You can do it.
Sun,
look at me.
Yes.
Hey.
Your brows are growing.
What?
Your eyebrows are spreading.
Should I trim them for you?
Sun, don't look at my brows.
Look into my eyes.
Hey.
Your lips are so dry.
-Mission failed. No kiss tonight.
-Let me grab some lip balm.
Done.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Ongsa, you're pretty good
at taking the initiative.
This Friday night,
I'm hosting a meteor shower watch party
at the school.
This is a miraculous event,
as it's the most visible meteor shower
we've had in 80 years.
It will be so bright that even people
in Bangkok will be able to see it.
So, I'm inviting you all to watch it
with me at school.
If it's bright enough
to be seen in Bangkok,
why not watch it at home?
Please let me finish.
There's a reason for this.
According to school tradition,
couples who view a meteor shower together
are said to have a lucky love life.
Our first school principal
got married to the one he confessed
his love to during a meteor shower.
Really?
Really.
You have to find out for yourself.
Humans are gullible.
So you're not coming?
-I am.
-What?
The first date was a failure. That's fine.
On the second date,
my kiss will make you weak in the knees.
I don't get Teacher Bambam.
Why would she want to host
a meteor shower watch party at school?
Right.
And Teacher Nida actually let her.
They're usually on opposite sides.
Teacher Bambam must have been
very persistent with her.
But what I don't get is, why at school?
I don't get that either.
That's because of
our school's mysterious tale.
That's why.
What tale are you talking about, Ton?
The tale that might give you a chance.
Chance?
What chance?
Mawin, my dear friend,
your chance is here.
What chance?
The chance for you and Tinh to happen.
Do you know anything
about the school tale?
No. What tale?
It's said that if we watch
a meteor shower with someone we like,
our love wish will be granted.
Who said it?
"Who said it?"
Teacher Bambam did.
Mawin.
This is a great chance for you
to get together with the person
you've had a crush on forever.
Ask him to watch it with you.
After that meteor night,
you and Tinh will become boyfriends.
Mawin, I hope you don't
believe this nonsense.
Mawin.
-Damn it, my friend.
-That's my boy.
Human.
Human senior.
How should I say it?
WA…
Why is it so hard to be human?
Hey! What are you…?
WATCH THE STARS WITH ME.
Oh, look. You're back.
Do you have to look that serious?
What do you say, human senior?
Wanna watch the stars with me or not?
Is this how aliens ask someone
to watch the stars with them?
I guess.
Pretty cute.
You want to watch
the meteor shower with me?
If I do, will you watch it with me?
Of course.
I want to see it with you too.
It's not every day that you get to see
stars with an alien, right?
How can I miss it?
Let's watch it on the rooftop.
Just the two of us.
This is like a date.
It's just stargazing, human senior.
Don't assume things.
Hey!
Will it really work?
Of course it will if you trust me.
-Are we really doing this?
-We are.
Trust me.
-Let's go. Go!
-All right, fine.
Tinh.
Oh, hey, Mawin.
What is it?
I… you…
It's…
"It's…" what?
Would you like to watch
the meteor shower with me?
You're asking me to watch
the meteor shower with you?
Right.
But if you don't want to, it's fine.
Why are you asking me?
Because…
Well, I…
-I…
-You what?
Well…
For your online content.
Content?
Um, content like…
Content like, "Watch the meteor shower
with the student vice president."
Hey, that's actually interesting.
Can I think about it first?
Of course.
Bye.
-He said…
-He said…?
-He would think about it.
-He would think about it!
-He didn't…
-He didn't reject you.
METEOR SHOWER DAY
Sadhu.
Angels high above, can you hear me?
It's the meteor shower day today.
Please come down
and give everyone your blessings.
Dear angels,
can you all hear me?
-Today is the meteor shower day.
-Who's chiming the bell so loud?
Please hear my prayer.
Hey.
Hey, Ton.
Ton.
Charoen.
What are you doing here, Charoen?
My mom asked me to bring Luangpu
this tiffin box.
He's not out
to receive food offerings today.
And you?
Why did you come here to chime the bell?
It's a noise disturbance.
It's the meteor shower night tonight.
So I came here to chime the bell,
asking the angels to come down
and grant everyone's wishes tonight.
I think you've
misunderstood something here.
What have I misunderstood?
Luangpu said
chiming a bell
is a kind of meditative practice,
not a way to summon angels
like you believe.
But according to my research,
it's what it's all about,
and those who told me were old people.
But you can't chime the bell
non-stop like this in the morning.
I can do it whenever I want
because I am Ton.
Do as you please then.
Will you excuse me?
Hold on.
Do you have a partner
to watch the meteor shower with?
No.
No one asked me.
But that's fine.
I plan to see it by myself at home.
Aw, poor Charoen.
It must be so lonely
to spend time by yourself.
No way, Ton.
You can't let Charoen, who's been gushing
over your handsomeness for so long,
be lonely on such a lovely day.
If we're done here, please excuse me.
I have to bring this to Luangpu
for food offerings.
Hold on, Charoen.
Tonight,
will you go watch
the meteor shower with me?
Oh, dear Lord.
It's almost time.
Why are the students not here yet?
It's because you told them
that they'd be lucky in love
if they watched meteor showers at school.
Not to mention bring up
the former principal's wife.
They are out watching the meteor shower
in pairs now.
What about our activity?
Bummer!
I brought a camera hoping to capture
some moments with the children.
It's just the two of us now.
Well then,
should we watch the shower together?
Sure.
Since we're here,
let's snap some photos together.
Move closer.
Teacher Nida,
what's with that look on your face?
Smile.
Right.
This is a bit hard.
How about I take the photos?
You're pretty clumsy.
Sounds good.
Where are the falling stars?
Move it over here.
There. We can see the stars now.
Ready.
Pretty.
We captured lots of stars.
But you need a bigger smile.
You have cute smiles.
Sure.
Hey, look. We snapped it
when the stars were falling.
Do you think
the tale Teacher Bambam told is true?
Humans are usually delusional.
It's good for humans
to be delusional sometimes.
Look! The falling stars.
Let's make a wish.
What are you doing?
Why are you writing on the ground?
I'm making a wish.
What?
By doing this?
Yes.
I'm making a wish in Morse code.
What are you wishing for?
Translate it if you want to know.
If what the human teacher said is true,
tell me how you feel, human senior.
Well, how do you write "2" in Morse code?
Dot, dot, dash, dash, dash.
Now read it again.
Human senior!
What?
When humans confess their love,
this is what they do.
This is it.
The benefits of being human.
Do you want to try?
Charoenporn.
Knock, knock. Is Charoenporn here?
Hey.
Charoenporn.
It's not the time for superstition.
What? But…
We're here to make a wish upon
the meteor shower, right?
There's nothing as magical
as these bougainvilleas from me.
Why are you giving me bougainvilleas?
Don't you know
bougainvilleas become more lively
in hot conditions?
Yes.
So?
You are so hot.
If these bougainvilleas are near you,
they must be lively,
and spectacularly beautiful.
What the hell are you saying, Ton?
From this moment on, I, Ton,
will not belong to everyone anymore.
Because I will belong only to you,
and you forever.
Something must have gone wrong.
Will you be my girlfriend?
No. I like it better
when you belong to everyone.
-Ton. Don't belong to me. Let go, Ton.
-Listen to me.
Let go. I said let go!
Goodbye.
Mawin.
Yes?
Where is your precious Tinh?
He's not coming.
He messaged me saying
he's binge-watching a TV series.
Teacher Bambam must have fooled us.
The tale isn't real.
But why are you here?
Well, I…
I came to give you these flowers.
So beautiful.
Yes, they are.
Are you cold, Sun?
I am.
It might be because
we're in the middle of a field.
An open space.
This is totally a scene
straight out of a romantic movie.
It's truly the crucial moment.
Why did you give it to me?
You must be cold.
It's okay.
I'm not cold.
Thank you.
What a handsome move, Ongsa.
But it's getting a little cold here.
Are you sure you're not cold?
I swear.
You don't have to swear.
Thank you.
If we kiss under a meteor shower,
it will be a super romantic scene.
Ongsa, you're so cold
your teeth are chattering.
Oh, gosh! You suck, Ongsa.
You can't even create a romantic scene.
What a loser.
Let's get warm together.
Is the Earth tilting or what?
Yes.
At a very good angle.
I don't mind it tilting more often then.
Ongsa,
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
Remember when you asked me
how people in relationships should act?
I think you can just be yourself
as you are right now.
You don't have to act cool
like heroes in movies.
Just be yourself.
Be who you are.
It's enough
to make me want to kiss you.
What did you just say?
Well,
what I'm saying is…
Hey. Falling stars!
Wow.
Though there may have been
some hiccups earlier,
this first kiss was so damn romantic.
You look extra pretty today.
Well, this is suspicious.
Aylin and I are girlfriends.
What?
My mom and dad asked you to come over
and have a meal with us.
And why did you only just tell me now?
Why are you up so late tonight?
You're usually sleeping by now.
I guess I'm so happy
that I don't want tonight to end.
-What time is it now?
-Human cousin is being weird today.
What's the matter?
Alpha must be tired.
Despite how she appears,
she's very stressed.
Why am I always the last person
to know things about you guys?
I know less than Luna does.
The student exchange program in the USA
that you asked about
is now accepting applications.
-Ongsa, is this how you want to play?
-Ongsa is crazy in love.
I can't imagine her not seeing you
for even just a few days.
I'm sure she would be devastated.