DEAR X
ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES, AND EVENTS
IN THIS WORK ARE FICTITIOUS
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED
WITH GUARDIANS PRESENT
Your husband...
Sung-hee.
Baek Ah-jin!
Ah-jin!
EPISODE 11: SAVE ME, MY GOD
Don't worry about anything
and get some more sleep.
Yesterday afternoon,
actress Baek Ah-jin was attacked
by her high school classmate,
Ms. Sim, who claimed to be a fan.
Baek was taken to the hospital
for treatment.
- While her life is not in danger...
- Sim Sung-hee. That bitch.
...she is said to be suffering
severe psychological shock.
Bitch!
The assailant, Sim,
suffers from schizophrenia
and has been receiving...
Actress Baek Ah-jin was attacked
by a female fan the same age as her.
What do you make of this?
It says the assailant was Sim
a former classmate
who suffers from schizophrenia.
And as soon as I read that
a case from 2023 that briefly
made headlines came to mind.
What case was that?
There was a classmate
who used the nickname "Simsim."
She posted an exposé on Ah-jin's past
only to delete it immediately.
Don't you smell something fishy?
- It smells very fishy.
- So it's not just me.
Yes, Ah-jin.
Other than the injured area,
the doctor says you're doing fine.
As for your movie,
I've coordinated things
so you can resume filming
once you've healed.
Are you okay with that?
It's not a serious injury.
If I take too much time off,
it'll only create unnecessary rumors.
I'll get back to work
after a short break.
About the crazy woman
who attacked you...
The police requested
a psychiatric evaluation
and the diagnosis was schizophrenia.
She'll be kept in a mental hospital,
so you won't have to see her again.
That's a relief.
So don't worry about anything now.
Just rest.
I'll take care of everything.
Okay?
Thank you.
I feel a bit more at ease,
thanks to you.
Good.
Let's talk again later.
I guess she misses me.
If you undergo laser treatment
every three to four weeks
the scar should become
barely noticeable over time.
The procedure takes
around 15 minutes.
Just relax your body
and stay comfortable.
I found Sim Sung-hee.
The classmate who stabbed your broom.
Here.
What happened to the reporter
who spread weird rumors on YouTube?
That's the thing. I looked into him.
But ever since that stream,
he's vanished without a trace.
Might've even left the country.
What? When did he disappear?
The day he live-streamed on YouTube.
And check this out.
Sim Sung-hee is being held
at Haemil Hospital.
You know Do-hyuk's ex-wife?
She was admitted
to that same hospital
after their divorce.
Wait a minute.
If I go to this Haemil place,
can I meet his ex-wife?
I'm afraid not.
No one's seen her
at the hospital for about a year.
So she's missing.
Gone without a trace.
Pretty much.
I pulled a few days' worth
of security footage
from Haemil Hospital.
I gave it a quick scan,
but nothing stood out.
NURSING RECORDS
NAME: SIM SUNG-HEE
MOON DO-HYUK, CEO OF SATURN
MOON PULLS OFF
ANOTHER MAJOR ACQUISITION
KNOWN FOR HIS AGGRESSIVE M&amp;A STRATEGY
ACROSS MULTIPLE SECTORS
HE RECENTLY ACQUIRED HAEMIL HOSPITAL
What the hell is he doing there?
Have you thought about
what you want to do next?
Not yet. I'm planning
to think things through.
Good. You've got plenty of time.
To be honest,
I never liked you writing books.
People say that
artists starve for a reason.
You might get lucky
and write a bestseller
but there's no guarantee
it'll keep selling.
I think the same.
I've been cooped up at home
for too long.
Let's finish this
and get some fresh air.
Jun-seo.
Help me out here.
Which one looks better on me?
I think they both suit you.
Really?
It's exhausting
when everything looks good on me.
Having to choose is so tough.
We'll take both of these.
Sure.
I'll ring you up.
- He must be your son.
- He is.
You two look so sweet.
Thank you.
I never thought I'd see the day
my son spoils me like this.
Are you finally
trying to be a good son?
You seem to be in a good mood.
Of course. Why wouldn't I be?
I knew you'd come back eventually.
You were just under her spell.
If not for that,
we would've gotten along just fine.
Don't you agree?
Do you honestly believe that?
Of course, I do.
Wait. Aren't you Mr. Yoon Seok-ha,
the author?
I'm Han Ji-gyu, a producer.
I've been trying to reach you,
but I couldn't get through.
I can't believe I ran into you here.
If you're done shopping,
may I have a moment of your time?
It won't take long.
- I'm here with someone right now--
- Son.
I'm fine,
so go ahead and talk to him.
He must be desperate
if he's doing this
in the middle of a department store.
I'll leave you two alone.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
See you at home.
I'm a big fan of your work,
Co-Offender Y.
How did you write something like that
at such a young age?
I was very impressed.
Every character in that book
has such depth.
But while reading your book
I couldn't help thinking
of the rumors about an actress.
- Rumors?
- Yes.
Recently, there have been rumors
about actress Baek Ah-jin.
You know she was recently attacked
by a high school classmate, right?
Hold on. She was attacked?
Oh, I guess you didn't know.
She wasn't seriously injured,
but the shoot had to be put on hold.
Anyway, after that attack,
rumors about her went viral.
Here.
THE SCARY TRUTH BEHIND TOP STAR B
Your book lines up perfectly
with these rumors.
So I wanted to ask whether your book
was based on a true story.
If it's actually about Baek Ah-jin
we're considering covering it
on our show.
I'm sorry,
but that book is purely fiction.
I'm afraid you're wasting your time.
Please wait.
Was Ah-jin really attacked?
Did you just find out?
Is that why you called me?
It's in hundreds of articles already.
Why are you asking me
when you're the one who ghosted me?
She's not badly hurt, is she?
Are you worried about her?
If you really want to know,
ask me in person.
RUMOR HAS IT THAT TOP STAR B
HAS SHOWN SOCIOPATHIC TENDENCIES
SINCE CHILDHOOD
SHE MANIPULATES THOSE AROUND HER
TO GET WHAT SHE WANTS
THE SCARY TRUTH BEHIND TOP STAR B
Ma'am?
Do you need something?
I have a bad headache.
If I ask for alcohol,
you won't give me any.
So could you make me
a cup of tea instead?
I'll prepare it right away.
How many people have died
because of her?
She deserved to get stabbed.
Shameless bitch.
Ma'am, are you all right?
Here's your warm herbal tea.
Right. Thank you.
I was just drinking tea.
Ma'am.
Why are all the doors broken?
The kitchen was a mess, too.
Don't you remember?
Remember what?
The doors to the study
and the kitchen...
You're the one who did that.
What are you talking about?
Do you really not remember?
You don't remember
a single thing you did?
She kept saying she wanted to kill me
so I divorced her.
Eventually,
she had a complete breakdown.
Now she's being treated
in a psychiatric hospital.
Maybe I treated her too well,
above her place.
Ma'am.
Would you like to go
to the hospital with me?
Do I look insane to you?
No, that's not what I meant--
I must have...
I must have drunk too much.
I must have blacked out.
It's nothing serious.
So I don't need
to go to the hospital.
Don't worry.
I won't lose my mind.
I told you.
I'm not like her.
I'm different.
So don't mention
the hospital ever again.
You can tell Do-hyuk
that I got drunk and made a mistake.
That's what happened.
Understood?
Yes, ma'am.
INCOMING CALL
Ah-jin, are you okay?
I was really worried
after reading the articles.
I'm so glad you're back on set
and filming again.
Thank you for worrying about me.
I'm so excited for this film.
With everything that's happened,
this might be our big break.
See you later!
Lord.
I spent...
every day drowning in my own tears.
I tried to let it all go
to forgive and move on.
Yet he lived on.
And I...
was left to suffer
in this agonizing Hell.
Is this
your answer?
Boss.
- What are you doing here?
- What do you mean?
You called me.
What do you mean, I called you?
Wait.
You seriously don't remember?
What did I say on the phone?
You were really anxious.
You said everything felt wrong
and that you needed help.
You said Do-hyuk
was doing something to you
but you didn't know what exactly.
Do-hyuk was doing something to me?
I don't remember saying that.
Ah-jin.
Are you okay?
Everything you're going through...
The nightmares, the memory loss...
This is clearly connected to Do-hyuk.
I'm sure of it. This is his doing.
I looked into his ex-wife.
She lost her mind after marrying him
and ended up in a mental hospital
after the divorce.
Now, she's missing.
- She's missing?
- Yes.
I also looked into Sung-hee.
A few days before she attacked you
she told people
she suddenly had a lot of money.
She even bragged
that she had met Do-hyuk.
What are you saying?
Sung-hee met Do-hyuk
before attacking me?
Do you know
which mental hospital she's in?
Haemil Hospital.
Do-hyuk acquired it a few years ago.
You think that's all a coincidence?
But Ah-jin...
Do you think your marriage is
a blessing or a curse?
Your husband...
So what if it isn't a coincidence?
What am I supposed to do?
Divorce him?
I can't.
I won't.
Why not? Why won't you?
- You could be in danger--
- Do you know what I did
to get here?
Everything I have,
I fought for with everything in me.
If I divorce him,
it all comes crashing down.
You want me to go back?
Back to people throwing eggs
and pointing fingers?
- Ah-jin.
- No.
No. I don't want that.
Why do I always have to suffer?
Why only me?
Why do I have to suffer?
All right. I understand.
I just want to live.
I want to protect
everything I've achieved.
I don't want to lose...
any of it.
Okay.
I'll help you.
Look at me.
If divorce isn't an option
we just have to put a leash on him
so he can't mess with you again.
Right?
I let it slide
when you broke the study door.
But this time, I need an explanation.
Why did you do it?
You even hurt your hand.
It doesn't look like you drank.
Is something bothering you?
Are you still scared that
Sim Sung-hee might come back?
It's not that.
Then...
are you dissatisfied
with our marriage?
That would hurt my feelings.
Because I really like you.
I want you...
to rely on me more.
I already am relying on you.
You don't want me
to become a helpless fool
who can't do anything
without you, do you?
If I become someone
indispensable in your life
I'd be honored.
Anyway, will you be able
to shoot tomorrow?
I'm worried.
Maybe I should get you
some herbal medicine.
Of course, I can. I'm not badly hurt.
Good.
But I'm still worried,
so I'll stop by the set tomorrow.
And I'll drive you home afterward.
Is that okay?
Long time no see.
- You doing all right?
- How is Ah-jin?
You're unbelievable.
If you were so worried,
why are you showing up now?
She's in danger.
What do you mean, she's in danger?
It's her husband.
Do-hyuk, that bastard,
is completely insane.
He's shady in more ways than one.
I think Ah-jin fell into his trap.
Do you have proof
for what you just said?
That's the problem.
I don't have any evidence
to prove that he's nuts.
Ah-jin called me not long ago,
saying something felt off about him.
But she doesn't even remember
making that call.
That's why you and I
need to help her.
Do you get what I'm saying?
I'm not sure.
It feels like we'd be interfering
with her life.
What part of what I just said
did you not understand?
Her husband--
You just said you had no proof.
Maybe you're the one
getting dragged around by her.
What?
You know how she is.
She's not easily satisfied.
She's living comfortably now,
and I don't want to disrupt that.
We don't fucking know
how she's living right now!
Jae-oh.
You think she's doing well?
Sure. Her life is fucking perfect.
Then why is she losing weight
and having nightmares every night?
She's trembling in fear because
she can't remember what she said!
- You need to calm down.
- Let go of me.
Fine. I'll handle this alone.
You can stay out of this, asshole.
Fucking jackass.
If divorce isn't an option
we just have to put a leash on him
so he can't mess with you again.
Hi, Ah-jin.
There's been a change in the script.
See you soon.
Director.
Why was the script changed?
We just had to change it
all of a sudden.
Ah-jin.
Have you been well?
You've really grown.
I missed you.
Ah-jin, are you okay?
Ah-jin?
Is there a problem?
No.
Ready, action.
Cut. Let's go again.
Cut.
I'm sorry. I'll do that again.
Ready, action.
I need a short break.
Come on.
You weren't the one who killed him.
You can do this.
Yes, you can.
Let's go again. I'm ready now.
Sure, okay.
ACTRESS BAEK AH-JIN
Get ready, guys.
- We're ready.
- Ready.
Action.
Ah-jin!
Ah-jin.
Cut!
Cut.
Go and stop her!
Ah-jin!
Check if he's okay.
Su-hoon, are you okay?
Wake up.
Excuse me...
Is he okay?
Su-hoon, are you all right?
ACTOR HWANG SU-HOON
CRITICALLY INJURED DURING FILMING
THE CAMERAS STOPPED ROLLING,
BUT SHE DIDN'T
BAEK AH-JIN IS CRAZY
VS IS BEING IN CHARACTER A CRIME?
MIXED REACTIONS ONLINE
Director, let me ask you one thing.
That rooftop house scene
wasn't in the original script.
Why was it suddenly changed?
The investor suddenly threatened
to pull their funding
and started making strange demands.
The investor?
Saturn.
The company your husband runs.
Ma'am?
Ma'am.
Mr. Moon just stepped out.
Where did he go?
He went to work out.
You got here earlier than I expected.
Why did you have the script changed?
Right.
I already told you.
I want you to rely on me completely
but you clearly have
no intention of doing that.
Turns out
I have to push you this hard
for you to come running to me.
Figures.
I guess leaking those cheap
tabloid articles wasn't enough.
So those articles were your doing.
Why are you doing this to me?
I gave you everything you wanted,
didn't I?
The least you can do
is make me happy in return.
I've always done my best for you.
This is really hurtful.
Take those articles down now.
If I take them down
does that mean you'll behave
the way I want you to?
Why should I live my life
the way you want?
Because I like you.
Unfortunately,
my ex-wife broke too easily
for all the effort I put into her.
But I feel like
you will stay by my side
with that pretty face of yours.
You'll keep me entertained,
just like you always have.
That's why I took you in
when you were so pitiful.
Fuck you.
You son of a bitch.
If you feel wronged...
Right. Think of it as punishment.
"Punishment"?
You said it yourself.
I thought I was being punished.
Why do you think
you're being punished?
When my mom begged me to save her
I just stood there and watched.
I thought all of this
was punishment for that.
You don't remember?
Is this a dream?
You didn't come to me before.
You acted as if
you'd never see me again.
Of course, this is a dream.
When you wake up
you won't remember any of this.
So?
Is it starting to come back to you?
Ah-jin,
I have plenty of ways to corner you.
Your past could be exposed
at any time.
And when that happens,
that fall is going to hurt.
That's the end of my patience.
If you don't want to lose
everything I've given you...
If you want to stay
right where you are
then I'm sure you know
exactly what you have to do.
Ah-jin.
You're a smart girl.
Shit.
This is Moon Do-hyuk.
You know who I am, right?
What is this about?
How did you get my number--
My wife isn't doing so well right now
so I'd like you
to look after her for me.
I'm a little tired after my workout
so I'm thinking of sleeping
at a hotel tonight.
Where is Ah-jin right now?
Just come to the address
I'm sending you.
Ah-jin.
You...
Let's get you out of here.
You'll catch a cold.
Jun-seo.
Do you know what I realized today?
I realized...
I could still be thrown away.
After all I've done...
After all I've done to climb up here
how can I still be someone
who gets thrown away?
How is that even possible?
Ah-jin, you need to calm down.
This is so humiliating!
I'm going to take it.
I'm going to take Do-hyuk's position.
I'm going to get rid of him
and take his place.
I can do it.
Right?
Jun-seo, help me. Please?
This is the man who had his ex-wife
locked up in a mental hospital.
He tracked down my number
and called me to come get you.
You know exactly how dangerous he is.
So what?
- What about it?
- You're the one who will break!
You're going to break before he does.
Why don't you see
how dangerous he really is?
It's not fair.
Why is he allowed to do
whatever he wants, and I'm not?
Why am I always the one
who has to suffer?
Why am I the only one
who has to fear hitting rock bottom?
Why?
I can do it.
I've got this.
Right?
I will...
I'll get rid of that jerk.
Why did I...
Ah-jin, what's going on?
Are you okay?
Where are you?
Jae-oh.
I can't hold on anymore.
Ah-jin.
Don't worry.
I'm going to fix everything.
I'm ready.
Jae-oh.
Why do you do all this for me?
You don't expect anything from me.
And you do whatever I ask you to.
It feels strange.
I don't understand it.
I just like being by your side.
Maybe it's because
I don't have much in my life
but you're everything to me.
Every time I help you
get what you want...
Every time I make things
easier for you...
you have no idea how useful I feel.
So go ahead, Ah-jin.
Use me all you want.
That's what I want.
You've finished your IV drip.
Let me take it out for you.
All done, ma'am.
You seem to be doing better today.
That's a relief.
Do I?
Why is that a relief, though?
After what happened
during the last shoot...
What happened?
I don't really remember.
It's best not to dwell
on the unpleasant things.
Forget what happened,
and good luck on your last shoot.
Hi, Do-hyuk.
Is today your last shoot?
Yes.
I'm going on a business trip tonight,
so I won't have time later.
But I wanted to congratulate you.
Thanks.
Do you feel all right now?
What do you mean?
You were mad at me last night.
I kept thinking about it.
When we were at the swimming pool,
you called me
a son of a bitch.
It was pretty intense.
What's wrong?
You must have dreamed that.
When did I go
to the swimming pool with you?
You don't remember?
Do-hyuk, are you teasing me?
I would never say something
that awful to you.
You were the one who held my hand
when I was struggling the most.
Get out.
Get out of the car, asshole!
You didn't get hurt
as badly as I'd hoped.
What a shame.
What the hell? Who are you?
You know me, right? Kim Jae-oh.
I'm the guy you tried to burn alive
when you set my office on fire.
I almost died that day.
So I'm here to return the favor.
I don't know
what you're talking about
but if you value your life,
you'd better drop that idea.
No, thanks.
I know everything now.
You're the one with the cross tattoo.
Who was the other one?
Moon Do-hyuk.
The obnoxious psycho.
I'll make both your lives
a living hell
until the day I die.
How does that sound?
Fun, right?
See you around.
Yes, go ahead.
Sir, we have a problem.
What problem?
Kim Jae-oh came to see me.
He said he knew everything
about the fire and threatened me.
He even warned me
that he would repay the favor.
So?
It looks like
he'll come after you too.
Should we eliminate him for good?
Some people don't know their place,
even when we treat them gently.
They never appreciate
how lenient we are.
Take care of Kim Jae-oh
however you want.
Just make sure
I never hear about him again.
I don't want his name
ruining another meal with my wife.
Get to it, then.
Wait, hold on.
- Come on.
- Seriously.
Why do you look so ugly today?
Which lane? I'm going jungle.
- I'm going jungle.
- Me too.
The worst player buys ramyeon.
- All right.
- Sounds good.
I'm right below Seung-jae.
- I'm safe.
- Isn't Yun-ho the worst, though?
- What are you talking about?
- He's the worst.
That's right, kid.
Just keep living like you are now.
Eat well, hang out with your friends
get your diploma
and get into a good college.
- He's the worst jungler.
- Come on.
You don't need me anymore.
No, he's better.
Hey.
We're all set over here.
Okay, thank you.
By the way
you set everything up
exactly the way I asked, right?
I told you not to worry.
Why are you always so suspicious?
Don't you trust me?
It's not that.
It's just that
this is really important.
Anyway...
Thank you.
Damn it.
Get him!
- Get him!
Stop him!
- Catch him!
Ready, action.
Open the door.
Why is it always so loud in there?
I'm settling this today
so stop acting like you're not home
and open up.
I knew it.
I knew you were home.
Why aren't you answering...
Oh, my gosh!
Please stop. I beg you.
- Grab him.
- Come here, you bastard!
I'll help you get to heaven.
DEAR X
Subtitles by Ho-young Yun