Black and white, black and white.
I'll win!
I won first!
You two play rock-paper-scissors,
the loser will be "it".
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
You're "it".
One,
two,
three,
four,
[Episode 3,
Love is a Game of Hide-and-Seek]
five,
six...
Ten!
I could only ever find Xiaoyang.
Found you!
Caught you all!
Xiaoyang could find me and Tuo.
Lu Junxi.
I got you!
Tuo...
could always find me right away.
He said I always fogot to hide my shadow.
That's why I was easy to catch.
Let's go play.
[Secret Lover]
Did you catch Tuo yesterday?
You like me.
You like me the same way I like you.
We grew up together.
Of course I'll take care of you
when you're sick.
When we were kids,
you went with me to the beach
to look for my mom.
Xiaoyang came along too.
In middle school, I hurt my knee
playing basketball,
and you carried me home.
What was I supposed to do?
Should I just leave you hobbling along?
Every time I stayed over at your place,
you insisted we sleep in the same bed.
That's because there was no guest room.
Let go of me!
You like me,
that's why you're always nice to me,
always looking out for me.
Stop joking around!
You've dated so many girls,
and now suddenly you're saying
you've always liked me?
How could I possibly believe that?
Why are you spacing out?
Hurry up and tell me.
Tell you what?
You two used to make up
right after a fight.
But now it's been days
of hiding and chasing.
This isn't a hide-and-seek game anymore.
Do you know
what ruins friendships the most?
What?
The silent treatment.
Tuo is stubborn,
but he usually apologizes first
when you two fight.
This time he hasn't,
which means he's really upset.
Aren't you afraid of
missing the chance to make up,
that you'll get more distant,
from "long time no see" to "never again"?
You care about Tuo, don't you?
Then talk to him properly.
We're a trio,
and we promised to always stay close.
[Tuo]
If this continues,
you might lose Tuo as a friend.
Tuo started the mess first.
He should be the one to apologize.
But you shoved Tuo to the ground.
Did you give him a chance to explain?
Explain what?
He suddenly grabbed Junxi.
He totally deserved it.
He did that because he likes Junxi.
What are you hesitating for?
Don't tell me...
you also...
Quiet!
Then tell us,
what do you want to do?
I'm going to take a shower.
It's raining again.
Am I really...
going to lose Tuo?
I wonder how long this rain will last.
Hold on.
Why does
my chest feel so tight suddenly?
Junxi!
Here we go again.
Remember to make up with him!
Oh, well,
he's such a troublemaker.
I'll walk you home.
I can go back by myself.
Let go!
I'll walk you home.
I said I don't need it.
Let go of me, Han Tuo.
Let me go.
We're here.
You can leave now, right?
What are you doing?
Why are you coming in?
Go take a shower first.
Don't catch a cold.
You had a fever yesterday.
You go first.
You first.
Or we can shower together.
Then I'll go first.
[Parent-Teacher Communication Book]
[Today's Homework
and Items to Bring Tomorrow]
[1 Math test; 1 Social Studies test;
1 Self-study test]
You still kept this.
Have some tea.
Oh, by the way,
our group order power bank came in.
I'll go get it.
I meant it when I said
I've always liked you.
♪ I am waiting, I am waiting ♪
I thought about giving up.
♪ I am waiting for you ♪
I even tried dating other people,
♪ Starlight sparkles all over your face,
you're so beautiful ♪
thinking it would help me stop liking you.
But until you said
you wanted to confess to Xiaoyang,
♪ When love turns into longing, can't get
over you, addicted to your wild side ♪
I realized
I was just lying to myself.
I only like you.
♪ Kissing the romance in the moonlight ♪
You're so popular,
how could that be possible?
I became popular because of you.
♪ The night breeze's so gentle and kind ♪
That's why I worked so hard to stand out.
Have you forgotten that
I used to be so introverted as a kid?
♪ Baby I am sorry, I am not alright ♪
I thought if I could become better,
more outstanding,
♪ The love I give is about to overflow ♪
you'd always keep your eyes on me.
♪ Crazy in love with you,
it's my bad, please come back ♪
You're bad at this game!
Left side.
Right side.
♪ Just let me zone out,
foolish and wide-eyed ♪
They're so good at it!
How did you get so good at it?
That's insane.
So impressive.
I'm scared of losing you.
Are you hungry?
I'll order some food.
It feels like...
something has changed between us.
How long has it been
since your dad came home?
I don't know, maybe two or three months.
It's fine.
It's better he's not here anyway.
What?
It's sweet.
Tasty.
Have some more.
Open your mouth.
Eat it.
[School of Design]
Last time you ditched me.
How long are you two going
to keep fighting before you make up?
What are you doing?
Tuo?
Let's go home together.
Looks like I don't need to worry.
So you two have made up...
No, you two are even closer now, right?
What do you mean "better"?
You're still playing dumb?
You confessed to him, right?
I told you so.
Congratulations.
What do you mean?
I've always known Tuo likes you.
I even encouraged him
on our way home yesterday.
I told him,
"If you like him, just say it out loud."
Seeing you two together
makes me happier
than falling in love myself.
Hey, we're at school.
Come on, let's go home.
Do you want to join us?
I don't want to be a third wheel.
I'm going to the library.
You two go home first.
-Bye.
-I'll go with you.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
Tuo, stop pulling me.
Ma'am, we're leaving.
Okay, bye-bye.
You're back.
Mom, let me help you.
Bring these up and arrange them.
Okay.
I'll leave it to you then.
Tuo.
Auntie.
Come here.
Give us a hand.
Senior,
could you please check if this is okay?
Yeah, we're good friends.
We really want to join the club together.
Why don't we go take a look
inside the drama club?
-Sure. Thank you.
-Thank you.
Especially the self-introduction part,
I'm not sure if 200 words is enough.
Senior, can I write like this?
It's fine.
No problem.
Senior.
Please check this.
Okay, okay.
Take your time. One by one.
I was here first.
Can you check mine first?
Lu Junxi.
I'm coming!
Excuse me, excuse me.
What are you doing?
Hey, watch out.
I'm not a junior. Can I still apply?
So weird.
Senior, we were here first.
Club recruitment isn't just for freshmen.
Great, so I can aapply then.
Here's my application form.
Why is she cutting in line?
We were here first!
Senior, it's our turn!
She needs to wait in line, right?
Junxi,
your department TA's looking for you.
It's urgent. You'd better go now.
Okay.
I'll go right now.
Senior, you're leaving?
Where are you going?
Thank you all
for signing up for the drama club!
Just leave
your completed forms on this table.
Thanks again!
Thank you.
Senior, I...
Senior!
Senior, don't leave!
How can he leave like that?
Should I leave my application here?
Stop messing around, I'm playing a game.
Just let me hug you for a second.
Don't be silly,
this level's tough...
[Hurry and log in, the raid's starting!]
I almost forgot,
I promised my friends
to team up for a raid today.
I'm leaving now.
What's more important, me or your game?
[Drama Club's Welcome Party]
Pass it over.
Grab one for me.
Guys, let's give a round of applause
to welcome
our new club members!
Shall we?
Come on, applause!
As for the pizza,
one slice each.
We're on a tight budget.
Thank you, senior.
Senior, would you like some?
There's an empty seat here, senior.
Would you like to sit with us?
It's okay.
Senior, I saw your last performance,
it was really amazing.
And your outfit looked so cool!
Did you style it yourself?
Senior, could you teach me acting?
Your necklace looks great today too.
Senior, you're really talented,
could you teach me?
Where do you shop for all that stuff?
Food delivery?
Okay.
I'll go get it.
I'll go with you.
Sure.
I'll come too.
No need.
Youmei and I can handle it.
We need to discuss about...
the performance.
[Club Office]
Why didn't you let me come along?
It's just picking up food.
Go ahead and
keep taking care of your juniors.
They're always chatting around you anyway.
What are you doing?
This is school.
Don't act like that all the time.
He Youmei.
What's up?
[Club Office]
Why are you here?
Junxi told me to come
to the welcome party of drama club.
What about you?
I was going with Junxi to pick up food,
but Han Tuo dragged him away.
Did you see him?
Nope.
I'll go get it with you.
Let's go.
Are you angry?
Tell me about it.
You get jealous over everything.
We almost got caught by He Youmei earlier.
Let her catch us then.
If everyone knows we're dating,
then no one would try to hit on you.
Or... you don't want that?
I just feel like...
going from best friends to lovers
happened too fast.
Can you give me some time to adjust?
Before I get used to it,
please don't kiss me
whenever you feel like it.
I like you,
so I want to kiss you.
Don't you feel the same?
Let's play rock-paper-scissors then.
If I win,
you'll do as I say.
You can only kiss me when I say it's okay.
No kissing or touching,
until I say it's okay.
Fine.
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
I won!
I actually won!
I have a condition.
What is it?
Only for one month.
No kissing or touching
unless you agree,
but you have to do one thing
that I really want you to do.
Deal.
[In the Next Episode]
Don't listen to Tuo's nonsense.
We didn't do anything.
Isn't that Tuo's sweater you're wearing?
Are you seeing anyone?
I...
If not, be with me.
Did you really do nothing,
or did you do everything?