WHEN THE PHONE RINGS
3 YEARS AGO, WEDDING DAY
That bedroom is yours from now on.
I won't be going into that room.
I'll use the room near the entrance,
and I don't want you in here either.
Did you not read my text?
I told you there was no need
to prepare meals.
I don't know when I'll leave work,
so don't wait up.
What if…
I had told you back then
that I felt at ease
with you in this house,
that I was glad you became my wife,
and that I couldn't sleep a wink
because of you…
Hong Hee-joo,
do you like being married to me
or not?
If you don't hate it,
how about we slowly…
get to know each other better?
Instead of dedicating it
to hatred and revenge,
if I had dedicated my life
to love and happiness with you…
I'm now paying the price
for not doing that,
Hee-joo.
EPISODE 11
I can't find Hee-joo! We were together.
I'll find her.
Hee-joo!
UNKNOWN CALLER
Paik Sa-eon.
I'll kill her.
I'm really going to kill her.
Your wife.
Hee-joo, don't worry. I'm coming.
- I'm coming right now.
- Don't come.
I told you.
For once,
I want to protect you.
Just remember this.
I love you…
so very much.
Hee-joo.
I love you.
You crazy bitch! Again with that?
Do you remember?
Once you start,
you see it through to the end.
That's what you said.
Since I started it,
I'm going to end it.
I'll make sure
you never make him suffer again!
Hee-joo…
Hee-joo!
NO VEHICLE ENTRY
- Hello?
- We found it.
You said you found it. What did you find?
I don't see the car.
Well…
It seems the car
was going very fast
at the time of the accident.
It hit this guardrail
and went straight down.
Also,
we found this
at the scene.
I think…
we should start the search.
What happened?
Where's Hee-joo?
Did the car…
fall down there?
No way.
- Hee-joo!
- Honey, calm down.
Calm down, honey!
Will you start the search right away?
Why did you spare him and let this happen?
Bring that bastard to me right now!
What the hell are you saying?
Who says I spared him?
Your father tricked me!
That sly old fox!
That's enough!
What's the point of blaming anyone now?
Since when did you care
about your children?
Don't you know
you brought this upon yourself?
You can find Hee-joo, right?
Please, find her. Hee-joo…
Hee-joo.
Hee-joo…
My mother didn't come.
What?
Yes, we checked them all.
We don't see her.
We checked all the mourners' dashcams,
but Professor Shim Kyu-jin
wasn't on any of them.
The back gate cameras
are for real-time monitoring,
so they weren't recording.
I understand.
NO RECORDED VIDEOS
Yes.
The dashcam footage
from Professor Shim's car
has been deleted.
Seize and recover it,
and check her phone and location data
to find out where she was
during the accident.
Okay, I'll request a search warrant first.
What are you doing here?
What are you doing?
You haven't been crying.
You don't know whether your son
is alive or dead right now,
yet you didn't come to the scene
or cry.
You're something else.
Why…
should I cry?
Your father, Paik Jang-ho,
said my son fell into the water
and drowned when he took him fishing.
We searched the entire lake,
but the boy was nowhere to be found.
I struggled in agony,
not knowing whether my son
was alive or dead,
beating my chest
as I cried and cried again.
Whenever I heard
that a body had been found washed up,
I ran barefoot to the scene.
I already did that
more than enough 20 years ago.
And now,
isn't it your turn…
to experience that pain?
Since Spokesperson Paik Sa-eon's
press conference…
4 DAYS SINCE THE ACCIDENT
…search operations have continued,
but Ms. Hong Hee-joo
has not been found yet.
Rescue authorities have announced plans
to expand the search area downriver.
NEXT NEWS. HOUSING LEASE SCAMS HAVE…
What's going on? Why did she stop?
You-ri, keep going!
Dear viewers,
we earnestly ask for your cooperation.
Please lend your attention and support,
so Hong Hee-joo can return
to her family's arms as soon as possible.
You think it'll be okay?
I'm fine.
I still have a lot of energy left.
No, the weather.
They said it won't rain.
Surely the sky won't turn against us.
Let's pray.
I'm not religious.
I've never prayed this much.
Me too.
By the way, when are you going to ask me?
About what?
Whether or not I knew
Hee-joo was Paik Sa-eon's wife,
and why I didn't tell you if I did.
You told me to hear it for myself.
Were you talking about Hee-joo?
Yeah. I'm sorry.
Why would you be sorry?
Hee-joo should apologize.
"Did you have fun
fooling me all this time?"
"You really went too far."
I'll confront her.
I will get an apology from her.
Hee-joo's in big trouble.
She's really going to get it.
Hey, you know what?
Hee-joo can talk too.
She can… what?
She talks really well.
She's got a great voice too.
This won't do.
- Step on it?
- Yeah.
Let's find Hee-joo quickly.
I need to find her
and hear that voice for myself.
VOLUNTEER GROUP
Shall we gather around?
Okay.
Let's get started for today.
Everyone, please stay alert,
be careful, and stay safe.
- Let's begin.
- Okay.
HONG HEE-JOO
PRESIDENTIAL OFFICE INTERPRETER
Ms. Han…
I'm so sorry.
Something got in my eye.
There they are. Over here.
Sorry we're late.
You're all here today as well.
Thank you for your help.
I should be thanking you.
You are all stepping up like this,
and I'm so grateful.
By the way, where's Sa-eon?
Yeah, he's normally at the scene.
He received a call
and left only a little while ago.
To where?
We don't know. He left in such a hurry.
EVIDENCE
CHAIN OF CUSTODY, ON-SITE EVIDENCE
Please check
if it belongs to Hong Hee-joo.
ON-SITE EVIDENCE
Downstream from where these were found,
there's a dam.
She hasn't been found
even after searching this area…
- So the chances of survival--
- You can tell me…
when her body is found.
Excuse me?
You can save that…
for when her body is found.
We still need to search more.
What about the search warrant?
We still don't have it?
I just got a call about that.
It was rejected.
It's hard to prove the charges
with just suspicions or statements,
and as you well know,
she is the wife
of the leading presidential candidate.
She's also the prime suspect.
Request the warrant again.
There's a way to get it.
Twenty-four years ago,
my son went to the lake
with his grandfather
and never came back.
We were unable to find his body,
and we couldn't…
accept our child's death.
So,
we couldn't register his death.
Then, one day,
at the fishing spot my son used to visit,
we met a child who had grown up there
without parents or even a name.
He's the Sa-eon who's with us now.
Sa-eon was the same age as our son,
and to us,
it felt like fate.
- Is it this way?
- Yes.
I'm Jang Hyeok-jin with HBC.
I have a question.
Why didn't your biological son
search for his parents,
and why is he seeking revenge
against Spokesperson Paik Sa-eon?
You can ask questions later…
It's fine.
I'll answer your question.
Among people,
there are rumors that my son
threatened Spokesperson Paik
and made death threats.
But they are not true.
My son has not been
in a sound state of mind
since the lake accident--
The blackmail and murder threats
are not true?
There's audio of your son's voice
and phone conversation recorded
on the spokesperson's dashcam
during Hong Hee-joo's kidnapping.
That's not all.
There are testimonies linking him
to the Sinil Childcare Center
abduction and murder cases.
Shall we hear it?
I first saw him
near the Presidential Office last year.
What is that?
A statement from the suspect's accomplice.
Let's listen further.
It was the first time
I'd seen someone with such animosity
toward Paik Sa-eon.
Damn it!
Get him out of here.
Paik Sa-eon, get out here!
Paik Sa-eon!
What's going on?
That man kept insisting
on meeting the spokesperson,
- trying to barge in without permission.
- Let go of me, bastards!
I'll be back!
I promise!
I'll kill Paik Sa-eon myself!
I wondered, "Is he a victim too?"
"Will I be able to
make use of his hatred?"
I followed him around for a few days
to see if we shared the same goal.
That's when
I saw him head to an important location.
An important location?
He knew where the orphaned children
and my brother had gone missing.
That's why…
I was sure he was a victim like me.
Who are you?
Why do you want to take revenge
on Paik Sa-eon?
He said he grew up at the fishing spot.
Paik Jang-ho
brought the bodies of the victims
his grandson had killed
to the owner of the fishing spot…
Take care of it!
One day, just because
he saw his grandson's face,
Paik Jang-ho tried to drown him.
Since then,
he's been living in an impaired state.
He said he wanted revenge
on the Paik family
for making him that way.
It was all a lie, though.
Sure. Take it.
The police already have it.
Now, everyone!
Two people are missing at the moment,
and their fate is unknown.
Right now,
we shouldn't be swayed
by baseless rumors or fake news…
How can I help you?
Are you Shim Kyu-jin?
I am.
I'm Detective Kang Hyeong-cheol
from the Violent Crimes Unit.
You're under arrest
as a suspect in a murder case.
What are you saying?
- Wait!
- Shim Kyu-jin…
You have the right to remain silent
and the right to an attorney.
Anything you say can
and will be used against you
in a court of law.
- Take her.
- Move!
- Move aside.
- Wait!
HEE-JOO
SPEAKER
The phone you called is turned off.
You'll be directed to voicemail.
Additional fees may apply after the beep.
I…
wanted you to live
a different life from mine.
To live without hardship,
marry into a wealthy family,
wear beautiful clothes,
and indulge in luxury.
That's the life I wanted for you.
I thought it was for your own good, but…
But no matter how hard I try,
I can't remember it.
I don't think I ever saw it.
Your smile, Hee-joo.
Why are you doing nothing?
You should be doing something!
Why?
Are you afraid that stepping forward
will expose the deal you made
with Chairman Paik 20 years ago?
Fine.
If you can't do it, I will.
This tragedy between our two families.
The world deserves to know
why it happened.
Will doing that…
change anything?
What will change if we do nothing?
You saw what happened when you did nothing
after losing your son 20 years ago!
Honey!
What does this mean?
What's wrong?
PAIK UI-YONG'S WIFE ARRESTED FOR MURDER
What… For murder?
Who did this wench kill?
She didn't, right?
Not Hee-joo, right?
So,
has a body been found or something?
- What body?
- You said it was a murder charge.
Didn't you bring me here
because I killed someone?
Before that,
are you prepared to lose your badge?
I could get you fired
for defamation or abuse of power,
if I wanted to.
Have we found a body?
Do you think you're here for murder
of the missing Hong Hee-joo?
Do you admit to the murder charge?
How…
did you get this?
Grandfather's signet ring.
He gave it to me a few days
before he passed away.
A few days later,
I returned it to him.
I told him it wasn't right
for me to take it then.
That's when the video was taken.
Right before Grandfather passed away,
that moment of truth.
BACKGROUND CHECK
SHIM KYU-JIN
Kyu-jin.
You've gone through a lot…
living as my daughter-in-law.
Now…
you're asking for forgiveness?
Forgiveness?
Are you talking about…
the sin of sending your son to his death
with my own hands?
There's one more.
The sin…
of replacing my son with yours.
So,
you knew all along.
I didn't at first.
As soon as my son died,
you brought an orphan
and shoved him into my arms,
telling me to raise him as Sa-eon.
But as I watched that child
become more and more like you,
I saw
how lovingly you gazed at him
and how proud you were of him…
I couldn't help but know.
The joy and glory that comes with raising
a child should have been mine,
but you enjoyed it instead of me.
No.
I spared you the pain
and tragedy you would have faced
if your child had lived.
Until the very end,
you still won't ask for forgiveness.
Then,
I'll do it for you.
Forgive me, Father.
People…
tend to tell the truth
when the final moment comes.
That's why I kept this.
For the moment
when your lifelong secret
finally comes to light.
You are…
indeed Paik Jang-ho's son.
So, you'll make me pay the price
for killing your father.
I didn't record it for him.
I've been saving this for the day
the ugly truth of this family is exposed.
But I never imagined
I'd have to use it
not to ruin someone
but to save someone.
Mother.
Now, tell me.
Where's Hee-joo?
What did you do with her?
The police already have your phone
and dashcam.
It'll work in your favor if you confess
before the evidence comes out.
You know that better than anyone.
OVERALL PROGRESS
CONNECTING TO ACQUISITION PROCESS
But…
I'm curious about something.
Fine.
Let's say I had her kidnapped.
But what you really want to find
isn't her body,
it's her alive, isn't it?
So tell me.
Is there any reason
I should keep her alive?
I'm not keeping her as a hostage,
so why would I keep her alive?
If it were you, would you have
bothered keeping her alive?
Yes, Professor. I found them.
What should I do with Hee-joo?
What?
I understand.
If it were you,
you would've kept her alive.
For me.
For you?
You said it before.
The pain of not knowing
whether he was dead or alive,
struggling, pounding your chest,
crying and crying.
Whenever a body was found
floating in the water,
you ran barefoot in that agony.
You said it was my turn now.
Right.
I did.
That wouldn't have been enough for you.
You would've gone even further.
You would have looked for a way
to torment me,
the son of Paik Jang-ho,
until the very end.
How's it going?
- We have security footage.
- Pull it up.
The one on the right.
Zoom in.
You haven't eaten anything for days.
Are you planning to starve to death?
Why?
I could've had you killed.
Instead,
I brought you here and saved your life.
So why are you trying to die?
Because I know what you're up to.
What I'm up to?
What's that?
He's probably searching for me
like crazy right now.
One year.
Two years.
And then, after about ten years…
he'll probably give up,
thinking I'm dead.
He'll just come to accept it.
Then, one day,
after more than 20 years have passed…
You want him…
…to eventually find out,
after all these years…
…that his beloved, whom he thought
was dead, was actually alive.
Then, I'll mourn the days
we couldn't be together.
Filled with regret
and sorrow,
he will beat his chest in despair.
For me,
you would've prepared that final pain.
If it were you.
We found Hong Hee-joo.
- Check the address and move quickly!
- Yes, sir!
SEONGNANG POLICE STATION
PROFESSOR SHIM KYU-JIN ARRESTED
FOR MURDERING PAIK JANG-HO
If…
anything happens to me,
take care of the rest, Mr. Min.
Save my son.
And
kill her.
Please…
Hee-joo, hold on.
Ms. Hee-joo!
Run away.
Hurry.
NO ENTRY
If it was for you,
I thought I wouldn't mind dying.
But…
I miss you.
I wasn't afraid of dying,
but the thought of never seeing you again
was terrifying.
Are you outside?
Who are you?
Open the door.
Open it.
Open it right now!
Do you
want to play with me?
Let's play.
There's a lot of fun stuff here.
Let's play with these.
Let's play!
Stop!
When I get out of here,
I'm going to kill you!
Open it! Open the door!
- Open the door!
- Open it.
I'm going to kill you
when I get out of here!
- Open it!
- I saw everything.
You two exchanged glances.
Don't move!
- Don't move!
- What are you doing?
What are you doing?
Something felt off, so I followed you.
- Who knew you'd come here?
- Open it!
Who knew you'd hide him here?
Open the door!
Now.
I will pay
for my actions myself.
Open…
that door.
Open the door!
It's been a while, Father.
What's this for?
Are you going to shoot me?
He…
takes after you a lot.
Mr. Paik!
It was great to see you.
Goodbye.
Father.
Sis.
Sis!
Why did you leave me behind?
Let's play some more!
Help. Help me…
I found you.
Hee-joo.
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
I'm okay.
Let's go.
Let's go home.
It's all over now.
It's not over.
He's nearby, and he has a gun.
Get out of here.
We'll search the area and arrest him.
Thank you.
Okay.
I'm going to follow the spokesperson.
The rest of you split up
and search the area.
Be careful. The suspect is armed.
Request backup from the nearby precinct!
- Yes, sir!
Hee-joo, you have to stay awake.
Let's go to the hospital.
Just hold on.
Where are you going?
Let's play.
Paik Sa-eon, get out of the car.
Hee-joo.
Listen to me.
Don't get out of this car. Stay here.
No, don't go.
Get out!
No! No…
I have to end this.
Don't come out.
This is between us.
Don't drag her into this anymore.
Do you think you won?
But…
did you…
really win?
I never wanted to beat you.
I told you.
I didn't want to take what's yours.
Yeah.
You just
want to live happily ever after
with Hong Hee-joo.
But…
do you remember what I said before?
I told you
I wanted
to see you suffer properly.
Aren't you guilty of anything?
Of course, you are.
You're the son…
of Paik Jang-ho,
a man full of sins.
What's that?
Suspect sighted.
Requesting backup.
Yeah!
That's it.
That is the face
I wanted to see from you.
Put the gun down!
Hong Hee-joo,
do you like being married to me
or not?
If you don't hate it,
how about we slowly
get to know each other better?
I'd like that.
I like you.
What?
I've liked you
for a long time now.
Since when?
When we were kids.
Since the moment
you carried me on your back.
I should've told you
when you were still by my side.
I shouldn't have hidden it
or kept it a secret.
I should've told you
that I've liked you for such a long time.
It's so pretty.
- Something's burning!
- What?
No!
My steak!
Oh, no.
What do we do?
Look at the smoke!
- It's on fire!
- It's all burnt. What do we do?
I can't see the steak!
It's okay.
Only now,
after he's gone,
do I regret belatedly.
The number you called is not in service.
Please check the number and try again.
PAIK SA-EON
What did he…
hear that day?
What made him…
look at me with such sad eyes?
INCOMING CALL
INTERNATIONAL CALL
Hello?
Is that…
you?
Subtitle translation by: Sue Mounce