=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 34=
Commandant Wu,
how is your injury?
General,
sorry I let you down.
I've heard about it.
What exactly happened there?
At that time,
Captain Meng and I
were raiding their main forces
according to your splitting strategy
when we were nearly ambushed.
Those Chong soldiers who attacked us
were very weird.
They seemed
fearless of pain.
What's worse,
when we retreated,
many enemy assassins
suddenly appeared
out of nowhere.
We were caught
completely off guard.
The All-Knowing was there.
What was our loss?
By the time I realized the problem,
we had lost 40 percent of our forces.
I didn't dare to get bogged down,
so I led our troops in retreat.
Commandant Wu,
the battlefield is unpredictable.
You did well enough.
I'll send scouts
to find out what happened.
When I offered you presents,
you'd at least give them a good look.
Now when I think of it,
these common things
really don't suit you.
I've made you
a queen's crown by myself.
Won't you try it on?
The one who wanted this crown
was killed by you.
Yan Zhang trained those puppet spirits
for you, didn't she?
She was completely devoted to you.
When you killed her,
you didn't even bat an eye.
You've found out.
My queen's crown
will only be yours.
You so-called love
makes me sick.
Here it is again, the same old look.
Simu,
the first time I saw you,
I fell in love
with your disdainful look.
From then on,
I could hardly forget that.
But I don't like it
when you look at me
as if I were an ant!
It fits you perfectly,
my queen.
Simu,
I've spoiled you too much.
Get out of here.
I will
have these things replaced.
No matter how many you crush,
I'll just have them replaced.
No need.
I don't like dead things.
Why is His Lordship up there?
Isn't it inappropriate?
During Her Grace's seclusion,
for the sake of convenience,
from this day on,
I'll be the acting sovereign.
All of you shall obey my orders
without fail.
Does this come from Her Grace?
Yes, Your Lordship.
You...
Your Lordship,
the 24 Temples and the Ascension Pool
have been searched.
Jiang Ai hasn't been found.
I've sent my men
to search all the valleys.
I believe we'll find her soon.
You may leave too.
Do I have the honor
to ease your worries,
Your Lordship?
What do you think
is a dead thing
and what is a living thing?
In my opinion,
dead things are in the Void.
Living things are
in the Mortal World.
This cup is originally
from the Mortal World.
Then why is it a dead thing
in our world?
Perhaps because
it was never meant to belong here.
Flowers for sale.
Flowers.
Miss, would you like some flowers?
No, thank you.
- Living things?
- Flowers.
(The Void is a dead land.)
(Earthly things)
(can't survive here.)
(But I'll force them.)
It's done.
Xu,
get some rest early.
I'm all right now.
You should go to bed.
- But...
- I'm fine now.
(Back in Weizhou,)
(we suffered heavy losses.)
(I must make)
(a new strategy)
(to retake Weizhou)
(and avenge our dead soldiers.)
Chenying was right.
Great Ancestor wouldn't want
to see you like this.
Luda has become
the High Priest.
I don't know how,
but he made his army
fearless of death.
We're at a stalemate
with them.
My injury is no big deal.
I examined the enemy's blood
on Commandant Xia's weapon.
I found out they were poisoned.
With this poison in their wounds,
the soldiers won't feel the pain
and they'll fight until death.
Luda used poison
to manipulate his soldiers.
What a great cost.
To win this war,
he has gone insane.
We both have suffered losses.
The war is deadlocked.
Why don't you calm down
and think carefully?
Don't let panic take over,
or you'll take the bait.
If Great Ancestor returns
and finds you dead,
your future will be ruined.
So will mine.
What's happening with Simu?
Something must be wrong with her.
Still won't tell the truth?
The Void...
Something indeed happened there.
But not very serious.
If the Sovereign vanished,
the Mortal World
would definitely suffer.
Great Ancestor
wouldn't allow such a thing
to happen.
General Duan,
you must stay alive.
Before she comes back to you,
you have to be alive.
I must stay alive too.
Let's go.
(Simu,)
(I await your return.)
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
(Xiazhou)
(Five years later,)
(Duan Xu led the Liang Army)
(to conquer Yingzhou, Tanzhou,
Ruzhou, and Mozhou.)
(But heavy forces of the Chong Army)
(still besieged them menacingly.)
(Young Xue Chenying)
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
It's almost time.
Don't give me that look.
I don't do this for you,
but for Simu.
Get better quickly.
I've wanted to ask.
Everyone in the Void
wants to be the Sovereign.
Why did you
submit to He Simu?
In the past 300 years under her reign,
the Void has been the best
I've ever seen.
No one else can be a better sovereign.
Since you told me
what happened during her reign,
I've been thinking.
If I had managed
to be the Sovereign,
the Void under my reign...
It might be
as terrible as it is now.
The real sovereign should
go back to the throne.
Any news on the Left Token?
Haven't found it yet.
What about Jiang Ai and Bai Sanxing?
Still searching.
It's been five years.
You haven't even found two spirits!
Your Lordship,
as long as Jiang Ai
still holds the Token,
we can't open
the spirit stone storehouse
to get any stones out.
She's been hiding for five years.
Our spirit stones
are almost used up.
And yesterday,
a large number of spirits gathered.
They attacked the 24 Temples
and ransacked them.
Luckily, I led my men
to execute them.
Outside the Sovereign's Hall,
chaos has been everywhere.
That's right.
Your Lordship,
we located Jiang Ai.
(Ascension Pool)
Yan Ke,
since you're here,
why don't you come out?
Give me the Left Token
and I'll let you leave the Void.
I don't want to be hunted down
by the Starhaven Sect
in the Mortal World.
Then you stay here
and get annihilated!
Yan Ke,
how dare you appear before me?
Does Simu know you brought out
your old lover?
Let me ask you this.
If Simu finds out
you killed her father,
what will you do?
What...
You even killed your own kind.
You're really merciless.
It was you
who killed He Simu's father.
But you stayed by her side deceitfully
and asked her to kill me,
the only witness to the truth.
If He Simu finds out,
she'll tear you apart.
That's why you were so nervous.
So you weren't scared
that Bai Sanxing would find you.
You were scared
that Her Grace would know the truth
after she met with Bai Sanxing.
You talk too much.
300 years ago,
I might have feared you.
But being stuck in there
for that long
has left you far weaker than before.
Leave.
(Left)
You can't get away.
The whole Void
will soon be mine.
Simu,
I suddenly remembered.
Today is the day
we first met 300 years ago.
We should celebrate this anniversary.
That day, as I remember,
thousands of spirits rebelled.
You held the Kunwu Blade
to suppress them alone.
That was the first time I saw you.
You were shining brilliantly.
Simu,
you always say
I want supreme power.
You are wrong.
I want both,
you and power.
Without you, I couldn't
govern the Void well.
Without you,
everything would be meaningless.
Today really is a day
worth celebrating.
300 years ago,
my father suddenly died.
I had no choice
but to take over the Void.
And today,
I'll kill the one
who murdered my father.
You... You know that?
I heard what you said
on the Void Mountain.
I've done a lot of things these years.
This is the only thing
I never want you to know.
Back then, I wanted to be the Sovereign.
So I had no choice
but to kill him.
But for your sake,
I've been the Right Hand
over the past 300 years
and never complained!
Yet you still don't accept me.
So I have to lock you here.
But all these things
no longer matter.
Simu,
I'll make it up to you.
You love the Mortal World, right?
I wouldn't mind uniting
the two worlds.
Wherever you want to go,
I'll go there with you.
Just don't leave me.
You killed my father.
Does it
really matter that much?
If I hadn't killed him,
would things be different
between us?
There's no if!
This is where your father
established the Golden-wall Decrees.
You want to avenge him, don't you?
Then let's end this
right here and now.
Stop the pursuit.
That was my oversight.
He pretended to fight me
just to grab the Glazed Pagoda
to hide his aura and make his escape.
He's out of reach now.
You were expelled from the Void?
Who allowed you
to talk to me like this?
You came here
to seek my help, didn't you?
Help?
You don't deserve it.
In that case,
I won't hold you back.
You're merely a pawn.
I can give you power,
and I can take it back anytime.
You'd better get that straight.
Don't think being the High Priest
means you have nothing to worry about.
If the North Chong falls,
you'll perish with it too.
Duan Xu never loses a battle
simply because he has a pact
with the Sovereign.
No wonder in Youzhou,
his power was unmatched.
That's right.
The Sovereign is back on the throne.
The course of the war will be affected.
What should I do?
When I'm around,
you will succeed.
All you have to do is follow my orders.
Simu,
you're finally back.
Bai Sanxing,
what are your plans for future?
Will you still fight me
for the throne?
It depends.
300 years ago,
I rose against He Yicheng.
Then now,
I could do the same.
I'll be waiting.
Feel free to try.
Back then,
I naively believed Yan Ke.
I thought he meant
to help me,
so he killed He Yicheng
and spread rumors that he died for love.
To my surprise,
he then
worked with you to trap me.
Not until he and Jiang Ai
lured me into the Prison
and the three of you attacked me
did I realize
that everything was just his trap.
Unfortunately,
it was too late.
I never believed
my father died for love.
You were arrogant and rebellious,
but you never took advantage.
If you had killed my father,
you would have told everyone.
You didn't need that excuse.
I won't get over it
until I capture Yan Ke.
From this day,
hunt down the traitor Yan Ke.
Restart the curfew.
Thoroughly investigate
all riots over the past five years.
Severely punish those who violated
the Golden-wall Decrees.
Yes.
Move!
Officer, I heard...
Her Grace ended her seclusion
and restarted the Decrees.
Is that true, officer?
Orders from Her Grace!
Riots in the past five years
will be investigated!
- Excellent!
- Great!
Move!
This is great.
Her Grace is back.
I'm finally safe.
Great!
Her Grace is back!
Awesome!
The Left Token is back with me.
The spirit stones have been
orderly distributed.
It's been five years.
I'm so happy to see you
safe and sound.
It's been five years.
You're still as exuberant
as before.
How I envy you.
You faithless traitor.
For five years,
you worked for Yan Ke
and lived quite a prosperous life!
How could you still come?
Under Your Grace's orders,
I went undercover with Yan Ke.
He...
It's the evidence of the violation
of some lords who submitted to Yan Ke.
Please see the truth.
So you weren't loyal to him,
but worked as a spy?
Of course I wasn't loyal.
I endured all these years
just for this day
when Her Grace returned
and set things right.
What a surprise, Yun.
You pretended so perfectly.
For all these years, I misjudged you.
Come on, I'll kowtow to you.
Hey, Leiqi.
It doesn't matter.
We all work for Her Grace.
You may rise.
Thank you.
This is great.
Her Grace is back.
The Void will be back to normal.
So this is how
they have a meeting now.
Interesting.
(Liang)
Deliver the intel to Wu Shengliu.
♪Touched memories linger like shadows♪
♪Scattered reflections
sink into my heart♪
♪If I could softly call you like this♪
♪As gentle as a fleeting embrace♪
It's been five years!
Do you know how worried he is?
You...
♪A lifetime is given
for a name to be remembered♪
♪There are passions and pains♪
♪Hope we'll experience them together♪
♪Before we forget or grow apart♪
♪Even if the day gives way to night♪
♪Grows dim and fades away♪
♪What would come of it?♪
♪I care for no one but you♪
♪I'll come near and run to you♪
♪To heal the deepest wounds♪
♪Miracles, eternity, and radiance♪
♪Worth more than any barren land♪
♪I might as well
spend the rest of my life♪
♪Walking with you through eternity♪
Simu,
is it really you?
Are you really here?
It's me.
♪Though apart, my thoughts still swirl♪
I summoned you many times.
I know.
But you didn't come.
Now, I've come.
♪Before we forget or grow apart♪
♪Even if the day gives way to night♪
♪Grows dim and fades away♪
♪What would come of it?♪
♪I care for no one but you♪
♪I'll come near and run to you♪
♪To heal the deepest wounds♪
♪Miracles, eternity, and radiance♪
I'm all right.
♪I might as well
spend the rest of my life♪
♪Walking with you through eternity♪
Never before had I been
that restless.
I couldn't reach you.
And I didn't know what was happening.
Don't worry.
If anything had happened to me,
you would have known.
If I had been annihilated,
the world would have fallen into chaos
and disasters would have raged.
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪