You killed Tubu?
Yes.
He insulted the Consort,
so I killed him in a moment of anger.
I know I am at fault
and am willing to be punished.
Your Majesty is wise.
You foresaw that they
would not be peaceful
after the Pale Tribe incident.
So you asked me to plant a few spies
around them,
and that prevented a major incident.
Your Majesty.
Tubu's family rose in power.
The Hongchuan Tribe alone
commands 10,000 elite cavalry.
Now that he has died so suddenly,
I fear it will cause unrest
among the tribes,
making them think
Your Majesty is using this
to eliminate dissidents.
Well done.
I have wanted to kill him for a long time.
Rise.
General Shiyan.
You were right.
I am indeed using this matter
to eliminate them.
Pass my order.
Except for the Hongchuan Tribe
and the offending tribe elders today,
the rest of the tribes
will be exempt from this year's
taxes and conscription.
These old foxes—
Which of them isn't shrewd
and opportunistic?
I am giving them benefits.
I don't believe
they would turn down what I offer,
but rebel with the Hongchuan Tribe.
[REBIRTH]
[Episode 28]
I have followed Your Highness's orders
and washed Lord Cheng's cloak.
But this bloodstain has seeped
into the lining.
No matter how I wash it,
there's still a mark.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
This way, Your Majesty.
You've been wronged
by what happened a few days ago.
Your Majesty has already stood up for me
and punished the offenders.
How could I feel wronged?
I meant
those rumors.
All they were saying was
that you're merely a figurehead,
having the title of a Consort
but having none of my favor—
I even have no desire for you.
If they didn't think so,
they wouldn't dare treat you like this.
Don't you
feel wronged?
I do not.
I want to apologize to Your Majesty.
Your Majesty has never
had feelings for me,
and we have never
consummated our marriage.
It was I who used every scheme
and unbearable means
to seduce Your Majesty.
Your Majesty wanted to silence
the elders of the tribes in Great Yan,
so you played along
and granted me the title
of Consort Helian.
Please punish me, Your Majesty.
You were right.
But you know those tribe elders
in Great Yan
are trying everything they can
to send their daughter
to my side.
Do you know
why I chose you?
The reason I schemed to get close
to Your Majesty
was that the Helian Tribe is weak,
struggling to survive
among the other tribes.
I want to bring glory to the Helian Tribe.
And Your Majesty chose me as your consort
for this exact reason.
A Consort from the Helian Tribe
will neither break the balance
among the tribes
nor pose a threat to Your Majesty.
I will stay tonight.
I didn't choose the wrong person.
From now on,
you're not only going to be someone
useful to the Helian Tribe,
but also someone useful to me.
Are you willing?
Greetings, General Cheng.
Is Consort Helian resting?
General Cheng,
His Majesty is spending
the night here today,
and they went to sleep early.
Is there something you need?
[Zhenhuangcheng, Great Yong]
The royal family is
on an ancestral worship journey.
Clear the roads and close the doors.
Anyone who dares to proceed
will be executed!
Stop, stop.
Your Highness.
You are pregnant.
The journey will be too strenuous for you.
Although you were brought back
by His Highness the Seventh Prince,
the Thirteenth Prince is currently
in His Majesty's favor.
He is even handling
the royal ancestral worship,
while His Highness the Seventh Prince
was punished by His Majesty
and was sent to guard the border.
Let's not get involved in this.
We should keep a low profile
and return to the mansion to rest.
You are quite clever.
Thank you for the compliment,
Your Highness.
Who could speak for me,
and whose side I'm on—
It is not something a lowly maid
like you can discuss.
Move the palanquin.
Who is blocking my way?
[Jia Meng]
Princess, you shouldn't care who I am,
but rather what I can do for you.
You are sinking into an abyss of pain,
but I can let you see
the person you miss.
Omniscient and omnipotent Faceless God,
as your most loyal follower,
I pray to you.
May you forgive his sins,
take pity on his pain,
and let the departed soul
return once more.
Chun'er.
I'm back.
Li Yan.
Can you hold me...
and our child?
Why did you leave me?
Where did you go?
I want you to stay with me.
It's too painful to be alone.
Chun'er.
You are the most precious
and beloved person
I have in this world.
But
I'm the only one left in this world now.
Even you, right in front of me,
are just my illusion.
You know what?
I'm so scared.
I'm so cold.
Can you hold me?
Just once,
for the last time.
Chun'er.
You have to live well.
For me,
and for our child.
Li Yan.
Li Yan!
Chu Qiao,
I will never let you go as long as I live!
Your Highness,
the Faceless God let His Highness leave.
The Faceless God
is an omnipotent true god.
As long as you devoutly believe in them,
they can return the dead to you.
I thought it was some amazing trick.
Turns out you're just a lying sorcerer.
It's nothing but a simple drug.
Do you really think you can fool me?
Your Highness.
I wouldn't dare.
I'm of low status.
I'm just a follower of the Faceless God.
I can't possess the power
of the Faceless God,
so I resorted to using knockout drugs.
But the Faceless God
is the almighty true god.
You are a noble Princess,
the chosen one,
and someone closer to the Faceless God.
If you devote yourself wholeheartedly
to the Faceless God,
their will shall descend
and fulfill all your desires.
If so,
why don't I take you to see
someone closer to the Faceless God?
Didn't I say
only one of you can live?
Why didn't you listen to me?
How disappointing!
Your Highness the Thirteenth Prince.
I came to teach you
how to govern a country,
I didn't come here to drink
and feast with you,
nor to watch you torture
and kill maidservants
for fun.
Grand Tutor,
look clearly.
I'm just practicing archery.
This is hardly amusement.
I never miss a shot. My aim is perfect.
Your Highness the Thirteenth Prince,
you're…
slaughtering innocent people!
Your Highness!
The Thirteenth Prince is the Son
of Heaven's Mandate.
He may do as he pleases.
Greetings to Princess Chun'er.
So you're Zhao Chun'er.
Your Highness,
you should call me sister.
Lift your head.
This maid
not only tore my clothes earlier,
but also bumped into me.
I was just about to settle
the score with her.
It would be too merciful for
Your Highness to kill her.
I want her to live in agony,
unable to live or die.
Your Highness, spare me!
I've never met Your Highness before,
how could I—
Guards!
Take her to the Zuixian Tower.
Your Highness, have mercy!
Spare me, Your Highness!
Please, have mercy!
Amusing. Most amusing.
Your Highness is too kind,
letting these servants
rant and rave before you.
Sister Chun,
I've only heard others speak of you.
I knew you were an interesting person,
yet I never imagined you'd be so
stunningly beautiful.
I have something even more interesting.
Would Your Highness care to
come see it with me?
It's just an ancestral shrine.
What's so fascinating about it?
Don't be hasty, Your Highness.
Come with me.
O Almighty Faceless God,
hear the prayers of your believers.
Reveal your true form to the world,
guard the peace of all realms,
and abide with me forever.
On this statue…
I see myself on this statue!
I see my own face!
Only those chosen by the Faceless God
can see their own faces
on this sacred statue.
Your Highness,
you are the Son of the Faceless God,
the incarnation of the Faceless God.
In the future, you shall not only be
King of Great Yong,
but ruler of the entire world.
General Qiu Lin!
By the General's order!
Step aside at once!
By the King's order,
General Qiu Lin is stationed
at the Northern Garrison.
Without the King's decree,
he may not enter Ximengcheng.
Without decrees from both the King
and General Meng En,
no one is permitted entry.
General Qiu Lin.
Long time no see.
General Meng,
perfect timing.
I left Ximengcheng less than a month ago.
How is it that
everything has changed so
drastically here?
What do you mean, General Qiu Lin?
I don't understand.
Don't play dumb.
You know full well the guards
of Ximengcheng
once took orders from me.
A month ago,
I was ordered by the King
to garrison the north.
Yet upon my return,
I find Ximengcheng has fallen
into new hands.
General Meng,
tell me —
who issued these ridiculous orders?
Who freed my slaves?
Who turned my own men
into yours?
All of this is by the King's will.
I am only carrying out his orders.
I intend to find out
exactly what he's planning.
General Qiu Lin, you know full well
the consequences
of trespassing in the inner palace
without the King's command.
I refuse to believe
I will never be allowed to see the King.
General,
are we just going to leave like this?
The more they block us,
the more dirt they're hiding.
Then what should we—
In seven days,
it will be Ximeng's Fire God Festival.
King Ximeng will stand before his people
to pray for blessings.
They can hide for now,
but on that day,
no matter how great the secret,
I will expose it to the light.
[Seven Days Later, the Fire God
Sacrifice Ceremony]
Today is Ximeng's Fire Worship Day.
Our King Ximeng and
all people of Ximeng
are blessed and protected
by the Red Fire God.
Today we gather to thank
the gods for their gifts.
The gods have accepted our offerings.
Let King Ximeng pray for us.
Traitors!
How dare you impersonate King Ximeng!
Seize them!
Surround these men!
Not one escapes!
You think a mere mask lets you pretend
to be King Ximeng?
Let's see what kind of fool
you've put in his place.
This…
You tricked us!
Zhuge Yue!
Insolent Qiu Lin!
How dare you rebel!
I knew it was you.
But you are only the King's shadow.
The real King Ximeng
died by your hands long ago, didn't he?
Qiu Lin!
How dare you question the King's identity!
What?
The King is dead?
Slandering the King is a capital offense!
Shut your mouth!
Who do you think you are to speak?
Foolish blind fool!
Thirty years ago,
I fought side by side with
King Ximeng right here,
conquering this land.
How could I not know his true face?
Zhuge Yue,
use your head.
Can that face of yours
possibly pass for a man past forty
with a disfigured face?
Ximengcheng has stood for
nearly twenty years.
King Ximeng can't possibly be this young.
But no one has ever seen
what he really looks like.
Maybe…
he's different from ordinary people.
They say King Ximeng
is horribly disfigured,
which is why he wears a mask.
But this face doesn't look
frightening at all.
I've seen this man before.
He's really just a slave
taken to be King Ximeng's double.
Zhuge Yue,
I knew you wouldn't admit it easily.
So I've brought a friend for you.
Bring him forward!
Who is that?
It's King of Lingyue!
He's King of Lingyue!
What's he doing here?
That's right.
This is King of Lingyue.
When King Ximeng conquered this land,
he took in his clan.
He was fortunate enough to see
the King's face beneath the mask.
Today we shall have him identify
who this man truly is.
You've heard everything.
Speak.
Is this King Ximeng you knew?
Speak truthfully,
and these delicious buns are all yours.
Tell me — who is this man?
Do you recognize him?
Is he King Ximeng you knew?
Speak! Speak!
Speak!
He is not King Ximeng.
Louder!
He is not King Ximeng!
Zhuge Yue.
You heard him.
Now everyone who has seen
His Majesty's true face
has denied your identity.
What else can you argue?
Do you still remember who you are?
Li.
I'm sorry.
Can you forgive me?
At the highest point of Mount Wumu,
we were to meet at sunrise.
But I came too late.
Li, I'm sorry.
At the highest point of Mount Wumu,
we were to meet at sunrise.
But I came too late.
Please forgive me.
King of Lingyue has long lost his sanity.
Li, I'm sorry.
I came too late.
How can his words
be trusted?
I came too late.
Li, I'm sorry.
Qiu Lin.
Using the words of a madman
to overturn King Ximeng,
what are you really plotting?
Useless lunatic!
I have fought in wars for many years.
I have brought unnecessary tragedies
to many tribes.
But now,
Ximeng has reformed.
From now on, not only the Lingyue Clan,
but all other tribes
may keep their own customs
and govern their own strongholds.
Except
that slavery is no longer allowed,
everything else remains the same.
Annual tribute will be cut in half.
Cut in half?
Is it true?
No idea.
It is true?
I just came from General Qiu Lin's estate
and found something strange.
The abolition of slavery
in Ximeng is known to all.
How is it that you
know nothing of this, General,
and yet keep hundreds of slaves
on your own estate?
General, are you openly defying
the new policies of Ximeng,
or do you have some other motive?
New policies?
When even King Ximeng is a fake,
what kind of darn new policy is there?
Are you questioning
whether King Ximeng is real,
or are you unwilling to abolish slavery,
resenting that King Ximeng
has harmed your interests,
and using this as an excuse
to commit regicide and rebellion?
That's bullshit!
Let's go.
Long live the King!
May all tribes of Ximeng
unite as one and prosper for generations!
Long live the King!
Ximeng has reformed.
From now on,
there is no need to kneel in obeisance.
Long live the King!
May all tribes of Ximeng unite
as one and prosper for generations!
United as one, prospering for generations!
[Six years ago]
Run!
I learned this game
from a foreign merchant
newly arrived from the Western Regions.
The wolves in our hunting grounds
have been starved for 3 days,
their eyes already red with hunger.
We can shoot these beasts,
or we can shoot other people's slaves.
So, is it interesting?
Zhuge Huai.
Isn't this game a bit too cruel?
They are just a few young slave girls.
If Your Highness can't bear it,
I will personally visit another day
and send you a new batch.
Our Zhuge family has plenty.
Run!
Zhuge Huai!
Have you lost your mind?
Run!
Heir Apparent Yan,
what do you mean by this?
Since this is an archery contest,
killing and saving
with arrows are the same.
Bite her! Bite her!
Heir Apparent Yan.
Are you deliberately making
things difficult for me?
We each rely on our own skills.
Young Master Huai, why lose
your temper out of embarrassment?
Run!
Great!
Be careful!
Zhuge Yue.
Now this warm sunlight of equality for all
has finally melted the frozen ground
once bound in chains.
These medicines
were all prepared by Xiao Ran.
Make sure he takes them on time.
Only then can
the Blood on Snow poison in his body
be completely cleared.
I entrust
King of Lingyue to your care.
Let's go.
I'm not going back.
I'm going to find Li.
King of Lingyue.
Here.
Li is
waiting for you at Mount Wumu.
She has been waiting
for you for a long time.
If you don't go back soon,
she will be angry.
I'm going back.
Li is waiting for me at Mount Wumu.
I'm going back to find Li.
I'm going back to find Li!
Let's go.
I'm going back.
I'm going back to find Li!
Shiyi and I
will escort them
to the mountain pass ahead and return.
Why do you think King of Lingyue
gave me the green-eyed bird?
The Queen of Lingyue once told me
that in their language,
the green-eyed bird
means trust.
The gemstone used for its eyes
is a rare stone
of the Lingyue Clan.
It can test a lover's sincerity.
Each person in a couple has one.
It's because if either of them lies,
the stone will glow.
If you don't believe it,
we can test it.
Let me ask you a few questions.
You must answer them truthfully.
Alright.
Zhuge Yue.
Up to now,
how many women have you liked?
Three.
Three?
The first
was a maidservant
from Qingshan Manor of Great Yong,
named Xing.
The second?
The second
was the leader
of the Xiuli Army in Great Yan,
named Chu Qiao.
And the last one?
The last one
is now my Queen Ximeng.
Now it's my turn to ask.
Xing.
Up to now, how many
men have you liked in total?
Three.
The first was free and wild,
bold and unrestrained.
He was an eagle of the skies.
Yan Xun.
And the second?
The second
was charming and carefree, full of spirit.
Sadly,
he died young.
You liked Li Ce too?
I was lying to you.
I didn't like the first two at all.
I only like the last one.
He is
a block of ice,
cold and aloof,
utterly clueless about romance.
Who's this
cold and clueless block of ice
you are talking about?
He's right
in front of me.
He's also a strikingly handsome man,
graceful and refined,
yet still a block of ice.
Why are you so petty?
I learned it from you,
you clueless block of ice.
[Yunlai Inn]
General Cheng.
Your Highness.
This was picked up from Tubu that day.
I forgot to return it at the time.
Today I came especially
to return it to Your Highness.
You mended this?
In the future,
please be more careful, Your Highness.
If there is nothing important,
it would be best not to leave the palace.
If anything were
to happen to Your Highness,
it would also be
His Majesty's loss.
That would mean
it is our responsibility as well.
You called me out specially
just to say this?
Yes.
I understand what you mean, General Cheng.
The jade pendant has been broken.
Just throw it away.
Your Highness.
Why did you come out so quickly?
You left behind the cloak
you meant to return to General Cheng.
I heard Ximeng has
discovered a black gold mine.
Can you really give up everything
and run away with that slave girl?
Then shouldn't the wound
from Qingshan Manor
heal as well?
Jing Xiaoliu.
Why can't you do it?
Why must you push me like this?
Please forget me.
Just pretend that I really
died in the frozen lake.