This is a work of fiction.
Underage drinking is strongly prohibited and illegal.
Scenes involving alcohol with forceful consumption and shameful acts are not encouraged. Please view this as a comedy. Furthermore, all characters appearing in this work are of legal age.
Grand Blue Dreaming
This work is an original copyrighted material
of the Content Provider. Unauthorized reproduction
or distribution of this work in any form or manner is prohibited. Some viewers might find this work disturbing as it may contain strong language, a degree of violence or adult situations. Viewer discretion is advised. Please watch it at your own risk.
The story, names, characters and incidents portrayed
in this work are fictitious. No identification with actual
persons, organizations, religions, places and products is intended. The Content Provider, the producers and related parties shall have no liability, as to the accuracy, legality, safety or suitability for any purpose of the information provided in this work. The views and opinions expressed herein do not reflect the views and opinions of the Content Provider, or any of its affiliates, partners, subsidiaries, or Licensee.
MIYAKO AIRPORT
We've arrived!
-So this is Miyakojima.
-It's pretty far away.
Riding a plane within the same prefecture is weird.
This island is closer to Taiwan than Japan.
No wonder it was so far!
-Sorry.
-We didn't notice we were doing it.
We're going to dive now. You can't drink.
You guys fit right in now.
Hey, you guys!
It looks like you arrived safely.
-Thanks for coming.
-No problem.
We got here last night.
-You got here pretty early.
-We're going diving in the morning.
We wanted to get here a day early.
We're looking forward to Otori afterwards even more.
-Otori?
-It's a drinking custom from Miyakojima.
-Haven't you heard about it?
Otori is one of the main reasons
we came on this trip.
WHAT IS OTORI!
-So that's what it was!
By the way, I saw some rumors on the Internet
that some restaurants put out signs saying
"No Miyakojima people."
Is it because Otori is too wild?
That's just an urban legend.
No one would drink and act that badly.
You're right....
NO PaB MEMBERS
-What did you guys do last night?
-Well, enough of that.
-It's finally time to make your debut as divers.
About that. Actually...
He had a fever yesterday and stayed in bed.
-Really?
-So you didn't get your license?
This is embarrassing...
-I was looking forward to it a little too much.
-What do you mean?
Getting sick on a trip? Like a little kid?
That's why I can't go diving with you.
-I see.
-That's too bad.
Wow, it's so fast!
The wind feels really good!
What did you say?
You're too close!
-The amateur is getting excited.
-What?
I heard you!
You've only done it twice yourself!
Want me to teach the amateur
how to behave on the boat?
Stop it! There are other people here too!
All right, everyone.
Let's begin our meeting!
Okay!
That's what it's going to be like.
We're planning to dive to a depth of 17 meters
for 40 minutes.
All right, everyone. Please get ready!
Okay!
Okay, okay! Let's go change in the dressing room!
-What are you going to do?
-About what?
You have to have a license to dive 17 meters.
I'll be okay.
They're letting me join their trial dives
for the first and second dives.
What about the third dive?
Everyone's planning to go on three dives.
I'll just wait on the boat.
Maybe I should ask them to let me join them too.
-Why?
-I'm not confident I'll be able to dive well.
What are you talking about?
The guys will help you, and you have her too.
The ocean is so beautiful here.
You should go as far as you can.
Okay.
Everyone who's here for the trial dive,
gather here please!
Bye. Have fun!
Go slow and stay calm.
Let's equalize pressure.
Okay!
The sea turtles came really close.
That was amazing!
We were lucky to see a parent with a child.
It's as amazing as 2D!
Were you able to see it, Iori?
-No. Too bad.
-We took pictures. Here.
It looked like this.
I wish I could've seen that up close.
If you get your license,
you'll have another chance.
Work harder next time, junior.
Hearing you, of all people, say that really pisses me off.
I'll get the tea.
This looks just like the aquarium.
I want to see it up close next time.
He can't see it from over there...
That was so magical.
It makes me wish I had a camera!
The light is just right at this time of day.
You don't get to see that every day.
Where's Iori?
He said he was going to rest on the deck.
I see.
Iori has been pretty quiet today.
You're right.
Maybe he's feeling sick.
-Nanaka.
-What's wrong, Chisa-chan?
I'm going to skip the third dive.
My ears ache.
You know, Iori...
It's too bad you couldn't dive with everyone today,
but this isn't the last time.
We're going somewhere shallow tomorrow
where you can do more trial dives.
That's right!
I got tickets to the aquarium
at work the other day.
If you want...
Chisa.
The boat really rocks back and forth...
I should have taken the motion sickness pills
like they told me to.
Waiting on the surface before diving...
-That's pretty rough too.
-Iori.
-What?
-Are you just seasick?
What do you mean "just"? I feel horrible.
-Come on.
-Sorry.
Well, you know, Chisa...
You're a good woman.
What? What are you talking about?
You were thinking about me when I was left here alone.
Well, not really.
Don't worry, Chisa.
I'm not going to hate diving
just because of this.
I see.
Diving is amazing.
-I never imagined it'd be fun on the boat as well.
-The boat?
When we were coming here just now,
I thought to myself...
Talking about what you saw underwater...
Eating lunch together on the boat...
Feeling the breeze and the sunlight
while the boat moves...
It feels amazing.
The guys are usually loud, but they're so relaxed.
They're like sunbathing cats.
It's too bad I could only participate in the trial dive.
-But I want to come again.
-I see.
You didn't go on the third dive either,
so you would want to come again too, right?
Well, yeah.
If you treat me.
You know I don't have much. How can you say that?
I'll take you if I win the lottery.
I'm not going to get my hopes up.
All right, everyone! We're done diving now!
Let's head back to land!
Okay!
Hey, everyone. Listen.
It's about Otori.
One of the main reasons we came to Miyakojima.
The restaurant we were planning to go to is closed,
so we had to cancel those plans.
-Otori means endless drinking, right?
-Yeah.
We escaped an endless World Championship.
It's going to be a peaceful night on Miyakojima tonight--
But, we don't come to Miyakojima every day.
So let's do our own Otori!
Hey, don't go so crazy, freshman.
Well, then. Let's begin.
What do you mean, "our own Otori"?
-Don't get so agitated.
-We're about to explain.
We're going to drink from the same pot.
Especially since it’s a special trip.
You mean like eating from the same bowl?
-By the way...
-It's hard to find a drink that everyone likes.
That's true.
It would be sad if not everyone has a good time.
I guess you're right.
We want to make good drinking memories.
-So we came up with an idea.
-To be fair...
we're going to drink something everyone hates!
That's what you're doing to be fair?
We're going to spin this pot,
and have you pour in your favorite drink.
When you do, say a few words. Whatever you want.
A few words?
In Otori, you're supposed to say a few words.
Like, "This is for the beautiful island and the ocean!"
I see.
We're going to say a few serious things first.
We all come from different places,
but we have gathered together
in the same time and place.
I'm happy we could ride on the same boat,
and drink from the same pot.
Everyone here is a comrade and a friend.
Even if life leads us down separate paths,
the time we spent together will never disappear.
As a memory of your youth!
Don't ever forget today!
SPIRYTUS (96%)
Yeah!
-Idiots!
-What do you mean, "memories of youth"?
You won't remember anything after drinking so much!
I'll never forget the time I spent with you guys!
SPIRYTUS (96%)
-Why are you pouring that in?
-You don't really plan on remembering this, do you?
-I-- Azuma...
-Yeah?
-What's wrong, Azuma?
-I...
spent all my time studying chemistry.
I don't know what to say at times like these.
So at least...
I'm going to do whatever I can!
ETHANOL (FOR SANITATION)
Don't put that in!
We were just joking.
If we put this in, the alcohol percentage would go down.
ALCOHOL CONCENTRATION 60%
It's stronger than disinfectant alcohol?
That's not supposed to be drunk!
If we do a toast with that,
there's no guarantee we'll survive!
Now it's come down to this...
Let's put some water in and act like nothing happened.
Let's lower the alcohol percentage to a safe level.
Hey, you guys go too.
-Okay!
-Sure!
My eyes!
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Hey, hey! What are you doing?
-Sorry.
-Don't worry about it.
You’re not mad at me?
No one in PaB would get mad
over something as trivial as that.
Yokote...
Then I'll put mine in too.
-Hey, Iori!
-Knock it off!
Elbowing you is okay, but not this?
You're getting mad about the wrong thing!
-Then at least...
-How about this?
AWAMORI (60%)
Well, I guess I can accept it.
-Wait, you guys.
-You have to say a few words first.
Oh, you're right.
What's wrong, Kohei?
I can't come up with anything.
What? You're not good at things like this?
What should I do?
Why don't you introduce yourself?
Okay. Then...
I can say my name, my hobby, and my favorite quote.
That's good enough.
All right, freshmen.
Let's have a few words.
-Okay.
-Name, hobby, favorite quote...
Name, hobby, favorite quote...
Thanks to this club, I realized how great--
-Kohei Imamura!
--is, even though I used to hate it.
-Even though I got dragged into--
-Anime and games!
--at first, I think it's really great now.
I'll work hard so that someday,
I'll be able to say--
-Kohei, marry me!
--I'm going to do my best!
Knock it off!
-What are you doing?
-That's what I was about to say!
That was a good speech.
They talked about how they grew closer to each other.
All right. Everyone has a drink, right?
-They didn't have to fill it this full.
-Look, Kitahara.
This explains how to do Otori right.
What? That means...
If we show them this...
We don't have to drink like this!
Hey. Look at this.
About Miyakojima Otori.
The leader says a few words and takes a drink.
After that, everyone drinks when it's their turn.
Finally, the leader drinks again,
and says a few words again
before switching with the next leader.
This repeats for each person.
-I see.
-That means...
We have to do at least twelve toasts!
We don't have enough alcohol for that.
Let's put all of this in.
I didn't expect that to happen!
-We're used to strong drinks!
-You're right.
The important thing right now is...
the strength of mind to avoid drowning in alcohol!
-Great, guys!
-That's it!
We've seen this many times already.
-They look like they're having fun.
-This is so relaxing.
What's wrong?
-We're out of booze.
-Already?
No wonder. You drank so much.
Thanks for going out to buy some.
Sure.
Sorry. Everyone else is drunk.
It's too much to carry alone. Help me.
Oh, you're right.
Hold on. What are you doing?
Oh, sorry. I didn't notice.
Aren't we going?
I wasn't trying to tell you to put on your seatbelt!
My first trip to a tropical island...
Night has arrived.
The sky high above and the wide sea set me free...
Maybe that's why...
this idiot...
went outside naked.
I can't believe this!
I didn't notice. Don't be so mad.
What's wrong?
He got out of the car dressed like that!
It was really warm.
No wonder.
Resorts feel so liberating.
It happens a lot.
Why are you all agreeing with Iori?
-But, Cakey, think about it.
-What?
A tropical island, a starry sky,
going for a drive with a guy...
These are the memories of youth you wanted, right?
Maybe if the guy wasn't a half-naked pervert.
I see. Sorry.
-Do you understand now?
-But even for me...
-Going fully naked is hard.
-I wasn't trying to say you didn't strip enough!
You don't have to take your clothes off
when you drink, do you?
Stop looking at me like you don't know
what I'm talking about!
Hey, hey. Have a drink and relax.
Come on.
That's my...
What was in that?
The leftovers from Otori.
I diluted it though.
But it's still over 30 percent.
But this isn't bad either.
It's quiet now.
-What?
-You woke up?
Hey, Iori.
-What's wrong?
-Iori, you're...
-really dull, aren't you?
-What do you mean?
What's dull about me?
You are dull!
You didn't notice
what I was trying to tell you.
What are you talking about?
I thought about it.
You're dull, so you wouldn't get it even if I told you.
I have to show you through my actions.
Cakey, are we about to get to the true end?
I can't take it anymore!
If you don't get it no matter what I say,
then I'll just--
I'll watch. Take it off.
Oh, so that's what you meant.
-Now that you say that--
-Oh, I see. I see.
Or else...
I'll take it off for you!
Wait! Calm down!
You're next, Kohei!
What?
That was bad.
It was just one drink. She totally changed.
If you hadn't gotten out of the car naked--
Then you should have gone shopping!
There you are!
Oh, no!
Oh, dear...
I can't get TV reception.
-You're recording it anyway, right?
-You bastard.
Don't you know it's important to see it live?
-No.
-But...
Now that I think about it...
I never imagined I'd join a club like this.
I think it suits you well.
Are you trying to start a fight?
I joined because you tricked me!
I tricked you? Don't say that.
Are you trying to say it's not true?
-No.
-Hurry up and go.
Your wish came true, right?
-What do you mean?
-You said it, right?
You said you thought the life of your dreams
was waiting for you at college.
This is like a dream, right?
Yeah. You're right.
-More like a nightmare than a dream.
-That's right.
What? You don't know when to give up!
Chii-chan, where did you get those?
At the convenience store.
Wow, nice shot.
The image quality is good, but...
What a huge gap.
I like both of them.
That's exactly how we are.
What are they doing?