( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(Lee Na Young)
(Jung Eun Chae)
(Lee Chung Ah)
(Honour)
(Supported by the Culture Ministry
and Korea's Creative Content Agency)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and animals were
filmed under production guidelines.)
(About 40,000 sexual assaults
occur annually in South Korea.)
(Sex crimes)
(Abuse-of-power sex crimes
by superiors occur daily.)
(Victims still forced to be silent,
causing secondary victimization.)
(Denial and inaction
leave the victim isolated.)
(A lukewarm response)
(The isolated victim)
(Breaking the silence)
(Accused of being a "seductress")
(High schooler victim
versus Actor Kang Eun Seok)
(Is Kang Eun Seok a sexual offender?)
(5.2 percent of adolescents
report experiencing sexual assault.)
(Voices break the silence,
demanding change)
(Fans defend Kang Eun
Seok: "We believe in him")
(The "perfect victim" myth)
(One must cry in fear or run away.)
(Victim's info leaked,
escalating secondary abuse)
(Hyun Jin: Arrived at the courthouse)
("Debate," Live showdown at 2pm!)
Yes, I'm here.
Heading in now.
I just got here too. Let's do this.
(Witness support office)
(Honour)
Actor Kang Eun Seok, known
as "the nation's son-in-law,"
is now sending shock waves
after being sued by a minor,
a high school student, on charges
of sexual assault and battery.
Mr. Kang! Do you admit to
the sexual assault allegations?
Did you know the victim was a minor?
- Had you not met the victim before?
- Mr. Kang!
Do you admit it?
This is ridiculous, Attorney Hwang.
Why must Yoo Jeong go to court?
We already recorded her video statement.
That jerk, Kang Eun Seok...
He demanded she appear in person.
He won't accept her video testimony.
So the victim has to show up just
because the accused demands it?
Yoo Jeong's a high school student.
How can she testify with him there?
I've requested a privacy screen
and confirmed it's been set up.
She'll also be using the
judges' private entrance,
so she won't have to see
Kang Eun Seok's face in court.
What kind of justice system...
It's messed up, right?
But if you fall apart,
what will Yoo Jeong do?
We're strong. And his
dirty tricks won't faze us.
We have to show her that. Right?
Yoo Jeong.
Are you in there?
Attorney Hwang, I just want to go home.
We will.
Right after you bravely testify
and get this weight off your chest.
There's nothing to be scared
of. Just think of it like our practice.
I'll be right by your side
through the entire trial,
and you won't let them
get to you or scare you.
Because we've prepared
for every possible question.
All you have to do is tell the truth.
Let's go.
Attorney Hwang.
Yes?
It's nothing.
In many sexual assault cases,
their testimony is the only proof.
What if a victim falsely claims
they were raped or molested,
exaggerating their testimony
or trying to frame the accused?
Without cross-examination, how
can we challenge that testimony?
Should we trust testimony by
default just because it's from a minor?
A defendant's right to a defense
is guaranteed by the Constitution.
From a judicial standpoint, I
believe this ruling was correct.
Attorney Yoon, what is your
response to Attorney Lee's opinion?
I'm sorry, what was that?
What did Attorney Lee say?
About the defendant's right to a defense.
The right to a defense?
It was so dreadfully
boring, I'm afraid I tuned out.
Attorney Yoon.
You're not taking this debate
very seriously today, Attorney Yoon.
Why don't you try me again?
I'll be sure to listen this time.
- The nerve.
- Don't want to? Then I'll ask one.
Yes. Go ahead.
Attorney Lee, why are you even here?
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm just wondering if you're here to
drum up business, like on YouTube.
"Win Rape Cases. Beat a Rape
Case." "Acquitted of Child Sex Crimes."
You made a fortune on sex
crimes and bought a building with it.
So why bother coming on TV?
Oh, the mortgage.
Interest rates went up? Are
things getting a little tight?
How dare you speak to
me like that, Attorney Yoon?
But you do the same thing, don't you?
You use these kinds of insults, threats,
and intentionally badger
victims in the courtroom.
Seoul Eastern District
Court. Case 2023 Gohap 452.
"There was semen on your skirt."
"Isn't that proof you
took off your underwear?"
Suwon District Court. Case 2024 Gohap 875.
"The day after your boss raped you,"
"you went to work and a team dinner."
"Is that how you'd expect
a rape victim to behave?"
Seoul Southern District
Court. Case 2024 Gohap 1102.
"You were on depression medication
after the assault. Why call 911?"
"You didn't want to die, did you?
You were just acting, weren't you?"
Just exercising the defendant's
right to a defense, right?
Bravo.
Over 80 percent of sexual assault victims
face secondary trauma in court.
And because of that secondary
victimization in the courtroom,
they end up dropping their cases.
That's the impact of the
Constitutional Court's ruling.
"You liked it, right? Why not run?
How could a victim possibly smile?"
That kind of nonsense
is what children now
have to hear in a courtroom.
(Courtroom 413)
That's it.
Yoo Jeong.
Now, witness.
Witness, you claim that on the day
you met the defendant at Club Eyes,
you were sexually abused
and beaten at his home,
and you took a month
to heal. Is that correct?
And is every part of your
testimony so far unequivocally true?
- Yes.
- Why did you go to his home?
You knew you'd be
alone with him, didn't you?
Did you not implicitly consent to have sex?
He said he was going to
give me a tour of his place.
And I took him at his word.
Witness, you're not a virgin, are you?
Objection. The question's
irrelevant and inflammatory.
The question is to ascertain if
the witness sufficiently resisted.
- Overruled. Witness will answer.
- Darn...
He's every bit the scumbag I expected.
Don't get rattled.
Stay calm.
The entire time he was raping me,
I begged for my life and
never stopped fighting back.
The photos of my
injuries are proof of that.
(Evidence: Photos of
Jo Yoo Jeong's injuries)
You're doing great.
(Haeil Law Firm)
In the past month, because
of the Kang Eun Seok case,
378 articles have been published
linking him to LnJ and Haeil.
And online negativity toward
Haeil has increased by 35 percent.
Why is it always sex crimes?
LnJ is already a money pit,
and you'll bring a swarm of
flies into our own backyard?
Then what should we be doing,
making wine in a pickle barrel?
LnJ was founded initially to
help female victims of crime.
As you all remember, that
was decided ten years ago,
with this board's full approval.
Besides, are you sure all this heat
is just over the Kang Eun Seok case?
From where I'm sitting, it's about
the Dongsung Chemical cover-up.
Or was it because of the acquittal
of the vacuum sterilizer company?
CEO Kang...
In the past decade, Haeil funneled
over ten million dollars to LnJ.
If you're going to speak that
way about a public interest firm...
What then? Should I go hold a bake sale?
If you make the powerless
suffer with one hand,
then you need to wipe away
their tears with the other.
We may not be profitable, but I
save you money in the long run.
On top of that, I also launder your image.
Social value, public
interest, human rights.
Is there any other subsidiary
that boosts our CSR score like LnJ?
Kang Eun Seok's company is
planning to acquire S Entertainment.
And Haeil was supposed
to get a piece of that.
But thanks to you and your
team, the acquisition rights
will now go to Myeonghan, the
firm defending Kang Eun Seok.
Do you have any idea how much
money we just lost because of LnJ?
Is the Kang Eun Seok case
worth taking this kind of hit?
Yes. Even if his company offered
us half of Korea's entertainment world,
I would still insist on taking this case.
And why is that?
Because that man
is a total jerk.
Stop Myeonghan from winning
the Kang Eun Seok case.
Or I'm cutting LnJ's budget by 50 percent.
That's not where you belong.
You're wrong.
This is exactly where I belong.
It's been ten years.
Isn't it about time you stopped
wasting your life and came back?
After ten years, it's about time
you learned to give up, Mom.
Don't forget. I raised you to lead Haeil.
It's the same argument
every time. It's so exhausting.
For all your complaining, you
seem to handle them just fine.
LnJ has been around for ten years now.
An attack like this is no big deal anymore.
So this is what you have
to show for your ten years?
See? Like I said, an
attack like this is no big deal.
Wait, you're not even going to
wipe this off before you get in?
You think they'd have used
something that just wipes right off, Mom?
(Witch)
Has the defense concluded
its cross-examination?
No, Your Honor. I have
one last, crucial question.
(Witness stand)
Witness.
Is everything you've said
so far the absolute truth?
Yes, it is.
Then let me ask you this.
Witness. Are you absolutely certain
you met the defendant at the club?
Answer the question.
Did you meet the defendant at Club Eyes?
This is the Club Eyes entrance
CCTV and the entry log from that night.
Nowhere in this footage,
or on this log can we find
the witness's name or face.
And there isn't a single witness
who saw the two of them together.
Objection, Your Honor! This
wasn't disclosed in discovery.
Counsel, please submit it as evidence.
Prosecutor, prepare a
response for the next hearing.
Witness.
Did you or did you not
meet him at Club Eyes?
Answer the question, Witness.
Witness.
Answer me.
No.
Then can you tell the court
where and how you first met him?
Witness, you must answer the question.
How did you first meet the defendant?
Yoo Jeong.
This witness made false statements
since the initial investigation.
She claimed a famous Korean actor
sexually assaulted and battered her.
How can we possibly trust her
one-sided testimony any further?
Witness, where did you meet the defendant?
As I've already stated, I
was extremely intoxicated,
so I have no recollection.
Could she have seen you were
drunk and approached you intentionally?
I suppose that's possible.
There's no way she
wouldn't have recognized me.
That would explain everything.
If she was after his
money from the start...
That's baseless speculation.
Counsel, you may only speak
when you're recognized by the court.
Wait.
I do remember something now.
The sound of her voice.
An Americano, please.
Jun Hyeok?
Attorney Yoon.
I haven't seen you in
ages! What brings you here?
I'm meeting someone.
Working on a story?
You should've hit me up
when you were in the neighborhood.
Your breakup with Hyun
Jin is no reason to cut us off.
You're so cold.
I've just been busy.
You made a big splash
again today. Are you okay?
Why wouldn't I be? The
networks are happy with ratings,
the public has a new target, and
I love having a bigger audience.
It's a win-win.
Hyun Jin's doing well, by the way.
Just in case you were wondering.
Glad to hear it. We should
grab a bite sometime.
I'd love to see CEO Kang too.
(Jo Yoo Jeong)
Hang on a second.
5887?
(Jo Yoo Jeong)
I've got to run. I'll be in touch.
What's the story?
Jun Hyeok, you're on Jo Yoo
Jeong, aren't you? She's our client.
Talk to you later.
(Kang Eun Seok is innocent!
(Punish the lying accuser!)
(Kang Eun Seok is the real victim!)
(Scales of justice are tilted.)
Attorney Yoon. You're back.
Are these from Kang Eun Seok's fans?
- Yes.
- Leave them. They brighten it up.
(Until Kang Eun Seok's name is cleared...)
We never leaked that picture
of Kang Eun Seok's hair loss,
and of course we weren't
the ones who posted it...
- Keep up the good work, everyone.
- That wasn't us.
Yes, this is the LnJ Law Firm.
If you keep acting like this,
- Yes.
- We'll have to take legal actions.
I understand that,
but you can't just be so unreasonable...
You're back?
Yes.
- How was court?
- A nightmare.
Let's talk about it when
Shin Jae gets here.
(Jo Yoo Jeong)
We've got another ton of
comments to save as PDFs today.
- For Yoo Jeong?
- No, for you.
You've got Kang Eun Seok beat.
Seriously, the comments
about you are way worse.
Makes me so proud.
Nothing about Yoo Jeong's
identity has been leaked online, right?
I'm keeping an eye on it.
- How was the committee meeting?
- Same old, same old.
My blood sugar is crashing.
- Let's get some food.
- What should we get?
Something delicious.
- Can this food get any better?
- Never.
This tastes like what we
used to eat after school as kids.
This is the only thing I
crave when I'm stressed out.
But why would Jo Yoo Jeong lie?
If not at a club, where? A
dating app? Social media?
No, that's not it.
They even ran forensics on his phone.
The prosecution said it was clean.
And Yoo Jeong refuses to say a single word.
If we can't figure out where they met,
Kang Eun Seok is just going to walk free.
I thought you said you hated spicy food.
And I thought you were on a diet.
Don't you know I've
been all talk for 20 years?
Exactly. That makes me
a good friend for 20 years.
Hey, thanks to you, I
haven't dieted since college.
Here, eat up.
Anyway, if we lose the first trial,
Kang Eun Seok will likely counter sue.
She won't talk, even
facing perjury, false charges.
What is going on?
I think Jun Hyeok has been
in contact with Yoo Jeong.
- Did you see Reporter Lee?
- Yes, I saw him on my way in.
He seemed to be doing well.
I'm sure he is.
Wait, what do you mean?
Jun Hyeok's in contact with Yoo Jeong?
I saw him get a call from her.
I think that's why he was here.
Why don't you go talk to
him? He might know something.
What's the big deal? It's for work.
Yes. We broke up ages
ago. I'll go talk to him.
You deleted his number,
didn't you? Want me to send it?
Yes.
(Lee Jun Hyeok)
What do I do? The trial
was a complete disaster.
Maybe it's better to
tell the truth, even now...
But you know what will happen.
If I tell the truth,
they'll come after me.
I'm terrified.
What am I supposed to do now, Reporter Lee?
(Hyun Jin)
If it's too late, I can
come back another time.
Come on in.
You look good.
I am. I'm happy.
Help me.
That's what I came here to say.
You've been talking to Jo
Yoo Jeong, haven't you?
I can't figure out where Yoo
Jeong met Kang Eun Seok.
She's terrified of something
and refuses to talk.
At this rate, the charges against
Kang Eun Seok won't stick.
You know something, don't you?
Everything you know
is everything I know.
Jun Hyeok. We were
together for seven years.
We were together for way too
long not to know when you're lying.
Help me out. Please.
More tea?
I'm telling the truth.
I met Jo Yoo Jeong through
the Kang Eun Seok case. That's it.
So there is something else.
Something much bigger behind Jo Yoo Jeong.
I got you this in France, remember?
Nike, the goddess of victory.
- That's...
- You said
it brought you good luck.
You'd put it here for a big scoop.
Like the presidential
candidate's slush fund scandal.
And when you broke the story
on that secret political advisor.
What is it? What exactly
are you digging into?
You should leave.
Look me in the eye and tell me.
What is it?
A sex trade scandal.
Sex trade?
You mean Yoo Jeong met Kang
Eun Seok through prostitution?
So it's not just a simple case
of prostitution. How big is this?
If this gets out,
it'll turn the entire country upside down.
- What?
- I can't tell you more. Not yet.
It'll put you in danger too.
I promise you'll be the first
to know when the time comes.
But not now.
You're unbelievable.
Why do you still have this?
Are you crazy?
I've regretted it ever
since. The way we broke up.
I never should have come here.
This is wrong. We shouldn't
see each other again.
What more is there to say?
I missed you.
I must be crazy.
I'm crazy.
Seriously, Hyun Jin. You're losing it.
(Shin Jae)
- Hey.
- Did you meet with Reporter Lee?
A prostitution scandal?
So that must be why Yoo Jeong
wouldn't tell us where they met.
She was afraid the
prostitution part would come out.
This is going to hurt our case.
So what do we do now?
Nothing's changed. Jo Yoo Jeong
was clear that she never consented.
Does meeting through prostitution
mean it's okay to rape someone?
Anyway, it seems like the scandal is huge.
Even Jun Hyeok seemed overwhelmed by it.
So you just backed off and left?
Are you kidding? Of course not.
(Cheongdam New Pair SH 5pm)
I think he has another
source besides Yoo Jeong.
If Yoo Jeong won't talk, we
should try to approach them.
By the way,
nothing else happened, right?
What do you mean?
Never mind. Just asking.
- Good work. Get some rest.
- Hey, wait!
- Why are you so late?
- What?
Don't you have the night shift today?
I just stopped by. You
know what tonight is.
Hang on. I'll wash up and be right out.
- Hey, Hyun Jin!
- Yes?
I left out your folic acid
too. Go ahead and take it.
- Stay strong, Kang Eun Seok!
(We love you, Kang Eun Seok.
(Stay strong, Kang Eun Seok.)
Mr. Kang, what verdict are you expecting?
How are you feeling ahead of the verdict?
I have faith that the truth will prevail.
Depending on the verdict, what
are your plans for the future?
Do you have any last words for the court?
Case number 2025 Gohap 308.
For the defendant, Kang Eun
Seok, we will now deliver the verdict.
- Here he comes!
Mr. Kang Eun Seok was
acquitted in the first trial.
As the victim's attorney,
do you accept this verdict?
We hear his side plans a counter
suit for false accusation and defamation.
Will you continue to represent the victim?
The "High School Honey
Trap" is a big trend these days.
Have you heard of it?
Yes, I've heard of it.
In an article you wrote.
But I'm sure you've also heard
of "Trash Reporter," haven't you?
I'm guessing you hear that one a lot.
This isn't the Supreme Court.
This was only the first trial.
We'll see who's lying when
we take this all the way.
And when the truth comes
out, there will be a price to pay.
(Kang acquitted, Lack of evidence)
(Kang, "I'll return with good work")
(Despite acquittal, public
outrage remains high)
(Kang Eun Seok's Trial Ends, "Not Guilty")
(Her claims nearly ruined him.)
(He's rich, so he's not guilty)
(Trial Over: A Pyrrhic Victory? Law
versus Public, A Renewed Debate)
(Concerns Over Secondary Victimization)
(Kang Not Guilty, Questions Remain
Kang's Apology and Silence at Court)
I'm sincerely grateful
for the court's fair ruling.
However, one person's malicious
lie almost cost me everything.
I hope that no one else has
to be victimized so unjustly,
and I will continue to live
proudly, refusing to bow to injustice.
I also want to thank my fans, who
have supported me through this,
and I promise to repay you
with great work in the future.
(Poor Kang Eun Seok.)
(Latching on for money. Get a life.)
(Anyone want to see the
seductress's face and name?)
(Hot Girls Available. Book
Now. 20 Percent Off Special)
(Attorney Yoon Ra Young)
The person you called is unavailable.
Leave a message after the tone.
She's not picking up.
I guess I should go check on her.
Let's leave her be.
It looks like she doesn't
want to see anyone today.
Just leave her be.
Jo Yoo Jeong needs to realize
the consequences of her lies.
But public opinion is terrible.
Will the prosecution really appeal?
If they won't, we'll make them.
The key to the appeal
is proving where Yoo Jeong
and Kang Eun Seok met.
If we can't prove that,
there's no point in appealing.
Any word from Reporter Lee since then?
Then we have no choice. Next plan.
Cheongdam New Pair.
SH.
(Cheongdam New Pair SH 5pm)
- What about the signed receipt?
- The director said he lost it.
Normally, we don't have
to bill them from here.
You're expected to get them condoms,
what's the big deal about a bar tab?
Tell me about it. I wish they'd just
pay their darn tab on their way out.
July 12.
SH...
(Seon Hwa)
Are you sure it was July 12?
Oh, my gosh. Oh, no. What am I going to do?
- It must be next door. Sorry.
- Seon Hwa, someone's here for you.
A consolation drink for the losing team.
How gracious. A defeated soldier
receiving a drink from Your Majesty.
You're going to appeal, right?
Come on, you know the deal. First,
Jo Yoo Jeong is not cooperating,
and her testimony is full of holes.
I'll patch them up.
My boss is already giving
me looks to drop the case.
I can smooth things over with him.
Anyway, how long are you going
to keep up this little charity project?
You're the heir to Korea's top
firm, so why play in this dinky office?
Cut it out and go back to your palace.
Then what about you, who's trying
to call dibs on a spot in my palace?
What should I do about
that, Prosecutor Lee?
Anyway, no matter what you do,
an appeal is out of the question.
- Kang Eun Seok is a beloved star.
- Here's the Kang Eun Seok file.
Public opinion is too against us.
You have to bend with the wind.
I don't want to get my neck
chopped off for nothing. Get it?
I'll change that too.
What?
The direction of the wind.
From a headwind into a tailwind.
I'll set the table. All you have to do is eat.
You people are ridiculous.
If you're so curious about
my talk with Reporter Lee,
why don't you ask him yourselves?
Why are you coming after me?
That's it. I'm calling Reporter
Lee to ask him what this is about.
- If you're really his friends.
- That's enough.
Do you ever have to
deal with difficult clients?
What about the owners?
Ever had one refuse to pay?
Think carefully.
It can't hurt to know a lawyer, can it?
Fine, spit it out. Why are you here?
You saw the news, right?
Actor Kang Eun Seok was
acquitted of raping a minor.
We want to know where
Kang Eun Seok met the victim.
That jerk, Kang Eun Seok.
He's still up to his old tricks.
You've met him?
Is there a girl working in
Gangnam who hasn't sat on his lap?
That jerk is a total sicko.
He only goes after
underage girls. That scumbag.
Did it happen to you personally?
If there's any way you
could testify for the appeal...
Lady, I'm on probation, okay?
You want me to admit I sold my
body? Are you out of your mind?
Besides, you'll never be
able to nail Kang Eun Seok.
You see this?
You know how I ended up like
this? It was all Kang Eun Seok.
When I got busted for drugs,
I ratted out everyone I knew.
But only Kang Eun Seok's
name vanished from my statement.
I wonder why.
Who in the world is backing Kang Eun Seok?
You know, don't you, Seon Hwa?
That's why you met Reporter Lee.
That girl, Kang Eun Seok's
victim. Just leave her alone.
She could get seriously
hurt because of you.
I need 1,200 dollars.
My fee for a session. You
made me miss my next client.
You saw the verdict from
the first trial, didn't you?
If Yoo Jeong is wronged like this,
will you really be okay with that?
Hello.
Her personal info was leaked?
Just this, please.
That's 3.2 dollars.
(Jo Yoo Jeong)
(Jo Yoo Jeong, 18. Gyeongseon Girls' High)
(29 Yeonbuk-ro 63-gil,
Seoul. Semi-basement. Get it?)
(Can she even show her
face? Going to her house now.)
(Darn, she's totally my type, though)
(Beware of honey traps.
(Let's teach her a lesson.)
(5 mins away. Coming, Yoo Jeong.)
(Who were her lawyers? Trash them.)
(Best Comment: Hope
property values don't drop.)
(You have a new notification)
Yoo Min, don't come home today.
Whatever you do, don't come home today.
The "High School Honey
Trap" is a big trend these days.
Have you heard of it?
Yes, I've heard of it.
But I'm sure you've also heard
of "Trash Reporter," haven't you?
This isn't the Supreme Court.
This was only the first trial.
We'll see who's lying when
we take this all the way.
And when the truth comes
out, there will be a price to pay.
(Kang Eun Seok Acquitted of Sexual Assault)
Come on in.
Thanks for coming all this way.
Can I get you something to drink first?
No, I'm fine.
Should we get started right away?
One at a time? Or all at once?
Where on earth have you been?
What about your phone?
My battery...
Eat. Even if you don't have an appetite.
I had the posts taken
down. I'll keep monitoring it,
and I'm suing every single
person who's slandering you.
I want to die.
Why should you die?
Kill, don't die. That's the
mindset. To spite them all.
If you're tied up, bite. If
they gag you, headbutt them.
Don't waste time on dying,
figure out how to survive.
That's what I would do.
Did you meet Kang Eun Seok
because he paid you for sex?
I know you know this, but
lying and being so reckless
was a terrible mistake.
But the one who should be ashamed
is Kang Eun Seok, the
man who paid to buy you.
And the ones with more
to answer for than you
are the adults who didn't teach you
how dangerous and wrong that was.
We are going to fight
for you until the very end.
But
you need to start helping us too.
Do you understand what I mean?
Okay, good. All right, then...
First, let's get you something to eat.
So, is Jo Yoo Jeong
at your place right now?
Yes. I waited until she
was asleep before I left.
When I'm done here, I'll ask
where she met Kang Eun Seok.
- Is she okay?
- How could she be? She's only 18.
The trial was closed to the public,
and she never came to our
office to avoid exposing her identity.
So what kind of jerk leaked her identity?
Swhat?
Kang Eun Seok arrested on drug charges?
Our tenth anniversary
present. Do you like it?
But I heard Lee Seon Hwa
clammed up when the cops arrived.
Yes, it seemed that way.
Some big shot must have gotten to her.
So?
So, I went to see the Chief of Police.
You definitely knocked
him down a weight class.
For the appeal, we fight a
junkie, not the beloved son-in-law.
You head to the hotel. I'm
going to the police station.
The police station? What for?
I don't know. Maybe I should
get Kang Eun Seok's autograph?
I won't be able to once
he's behind bars, right?
You know, sometimes I think.
I'm so darn glad she's our
friend and not our enemy.
I bet Shin Jae thought the same thing.
About you, when you turned
the tables on my stalker.
Hang on.
Hey, it's me.
Are you free tonight?
Look, about the other night...
It was a mistake. A one-time thing.
I'll give you the files.
I've changed my mind.
Be at my place by 8pm.
You look better on screen.
What a shame. I was
so looking forward to this.
You, on the other hand,
are just my type, Attorney.
You should've shown up in court sooner.
It would've given me
something to look forward to.
Sorry. I'm not into long-distance.
Prison is just a little
too far from my place.
The evidence I turned over to the
Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency.
Security footage of you at an ATM in
a Seocho-dong convenience store
depositing drug cash.
Video of you at the fire hydrant
across from the Maegun Hotel,
picking up five bags of
meth from a dead drop.
Two grams of meth and some
weed were found at your place earlier.
And I'm sure you know what
your hair follicle test will show.
And?
But there's one more thing I
haven't turned over to the police.
Turns out you were a dealer
in the entertainment industry.
You were quite generous with it too.
You know the sentencing difference
between use and distribution.
So, what do you want in exchange?
Who's backing you?
Where did you meet Jo Yoo Jeong?
Come on. You're obviously bluffing.
I'm holding a straight flush.
Who in their right mind folds
that to take a garbage hand?
Is that so?
If people find out where you met
Jo Yoo Jeong, your game falls apart.
What are you saying? You're
barking up the wrong tree.
Thanks for confirming that for me.
I wanted to hear it from
you myself, Kang Eun Seok.
So it wasn't just a rumor. A
sex scandal to rock the nation.
Are you really going
to leak that? Right now?
Actually, I already leaked it.
I see things through to the
end, even with a losing hand.
And I've never lost.
(LnJ 10th Anniversary Gala)
- Business is going well, I trust?
- Yes, it's going great, thank you.
Welcome.
- Please see our guests are seated.
- Hello.
- It's been a while.
- Good to see you.
- You as well. I'll see you later.
Counselor.
I'll come say hi again later.
Okay.
Hello.
It's been a while.
You've been well, I hope.
Did you hear? Choi Min Hye got a job.
She said she'll stop by when
she comes to Seoul next month.
Guys, we got a letter from
Seon Mi. She passed her GED!
- Gosh, good for her.
- Who sent the wine?
It's a 2005 vintage.
(Congratulations on your 10th anniversary.)
- I bet it's from the alumni.
- Right. It's from the school.
Gosh, seriously...
Ten years just flew by.
But I don't think I could do
this for another ten years.
We have to play by my mom's
rules to survive another ten years.
Should we go to Jeju for
our 20th? Just the 3 of us?
Forget that. We should go to the Maldives.
- Rock, paper, scissors.
And the opening remarks
go to Yoon Ra Young.
- Seriously?
- I got LASIK. I hate flashes.
I'm heading back to the party.
You two come down in a little bit.
What are you doing?
You're not trying to
sneak out alone, are you?
I'm going to get our present.
Our tenth anniversary present.
- A present?
- Jun Hyeok's promised files.
We can win the appeal.
I'll call you.
- What?
- Hwang Hyun Jin.
What?
Don't do anything stupid.
What's your problem? I
said I'm just going for the files.
And make sure the boss lady is happy.
Knock them dead up
there, all right? Goodness.
(Congratulations on your 10th anniversary.)
- Mom?
- CEO Baek, come say hello.
This is my daughter.
You know who he is, right?
The man making waves in IT.
CEO Baek Tae Ju of The Prime.
- It's a pleasure. I'm Baek Tae Ju.
- I'm Kang Shin Jae.
Why don't you introduce
him around? Mingle a little.
So you're single?
Your mother said the same about you.
As it happens, here's
someone you should meet.
- Thanks for coming.
- Of course.
Let me introduce you.
This is CEO Baek Tae Ju of The Prime.
And this is my ex-husband.
I'm Han Seung Hun.
Baek Tae Ju. A pleasure.
I trust you've been well?
I'll be right there. Go on ahead.
And then there's...
Look. There he is.
Over there is my ex-ex-husband.
The second son of the Hanje Group.
Should I bring him over?
I take it your ex-ex-ex-husband
couldn't make it?
Well, I've only managed
to get divorced twice so far.
Though I think my mother
is hoping I'll go for a hat trick.
Mr. Baek,
I'd like you to meet someone.
Shall we head over there?
Of course. And congratulations
on your tenth anniversary.
I'll see you around, then.
Right this way.
I never imagined this would become
a reunion for your ex-husbands.
How could I not invite
them on a day like today?
They're the greatest
contributors in LnJ's history.
If it weren't for my first marriage,
LnJ would never have existed.
And if it weren't for my second,
you would've cut me off
financially ages ago, you know.
I'm not going for a third one, Mom.
So don't waste your breath.
Jun Hyeok, I'm here.
I'm coming in.
Darn it.
Lee Jun Hyeok.
First, I'd like to thank you
all for the last ten years.
Without the help of all of you here today,
we never would have
survived these ten years.
Most of all, I'd like to thank
someone for their constant support.
CEO Seong Tae Im of Haeil,
let's give her a round of applause.
Thank you.
If we couldn't land a
kick, we'd throw a punch.
If a hook didn't connect, we'd use a jab.
And when even a jab wouldn't
work, what choice did we have?
We spent the last ten
years fighting tooth and nail.
But now, after ten years of that,
we can land a hook, and even a kick.
That's the kind of world we live in now.
If we've played even a small part
in making the world a better place,
then for the next decade,
and the one after that,
we will gladly continue the fight.
On the side of the weak and the just.
Shall we all raise a glass?
- To LnJ!
(Honour)
I killed someone.
Jun Hyeok.
Lee Jun Hyeok!
Are you saying you're a
suspect in a sexual assault case?
You brought evidence here?
Are you out of your mind?
That ship has sailed. Now
figure out how to stay afloat.
It was stuck in the
mattress. We only found one.
- It was me! I killed him!
- Jo Yoo Jeong.
- Stay away!
- Why you're doing this
I will find out no matter what.