It's all my fault.
Is there any
tunes you want to hear.
Anything is fine.
This courier station
never lacks
heartbroken souls.
Come on, put it this way.
I've seen Miss Gu busy at the granary these days.
at the granary these days,
truly hardworking.
Being busy is good.
Cause there would be less worry.
Well,
I wonder
if the water transport has been cleared.
Cleared? It's all silted up.
Those large thousand-liao boats on the canal
simply can't get through.
So we have to go by land.
Then what can we do?
If grain prices keep rising,
will people still be able to live?
Whether we live or not doesn't matter.
The real problem is Jiubian.
If a war breaks out,
and the soldiers have no provisions,
that would be the end.
I heard that there in Shanxi,
it is drought to this day.
Lord,
we just got word
the grain convoy
is not far from Tongzhou.
You called it right.
They
indeed used the Ji family's fleet.
They're using
my relationship with the Ji family.
Thinking even if we find out,
we won't dare make a fuss.
Stick to the original plan.
Follow closely,
but don't alert them.
Yes, sir.
Greetings, Mr. Ji.
Second Brother.
[I thought you were in Sanhe.]
Why did you come back?
The grain convoy is arriving today.
Of course I have to.
Second Brother.
Every time I come to the granary,
I see you here.
A young lady like you
isn't afraid of getting tanned?
I have no shortage of jewelry.
Not jewelry.
It's your favorite scallion-shaped candy.
Thank heaven.
Finally smiled
Mr. Ping told me
you ordered people to inquire about
the shops in Shanxi.
When did you
become interested in Shanxi?
Since you're here, Second Brother,
please help me keep an eye on it.
I want to go out for a walk
to clear my head.
- Jinzhao.
- [The grain carts are here!]
[The grain carts are here!]
[They're here!]
Come on!
[The grain carts are here!]
[Prepare to unload!]
[Count all the grain first.]
Each one,
shall collect their pre-ordered grain
with their original receipts.
Give me the silver,
and I'll give you the grain.
I know what everyone's worried about.
My lord said,
not a penny up.
That's good.
The Ji family is kind!
Unloading unloading.
Okay, okay, okay, unload,
unload, unload.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Quick! Quick!
That man looks familiar.
He looks like those bandits from the southwest.
Are you sure?
I gambled with them at the casino.
It seems like they are.
What should we do?
The grain truck is destined for Miyun.
Go on, get out of here.
Oh god, can you stop making trouble?
My sister clearly told you
half of this grain
is for the capital.
How dare you take it?
How dare you!
Because those grain merchants in the capital
are paying too little.
Do you know
how hard I worked
to get this grain?
I don't care.
I only listen to my sister.
You guys, those things...
Get up.
Okay.
I won't argue with you.
Let's go to Grandmother for judgment.
Fine! Let's go!
Let's go!
It looks like they've noticed, too,
that something is wrong.
Such a noise.
I am afraid that it will alert them.
They're desperate outlaws.
The Ji family may be in danger.
Well,
you take some people
and keep following the grain carts.
I'll check it out.
I can see it clearly.
They're those bandits from the southwest.
And those sacks
don't have rice in them at all.
They're swords!
What should we do?
Looks like they're trying
to use our grain team
to smuggle weapons into the capital.
Smuggling weapons is a felony
So, Jinrong
You go and report the news to Jinzhao.
Tell her what's going on here.
She'll know how to find the Mr. Chen.
I'll try to keep these bandits distracted.
Then I'll send men to the Tongzhou Garrison
to gather men.
We'll surround the granary from the outside.
No matter what,
we can't let these weapons
leave from our granary.
OK.
I'll go right now.
Go ahead.
Get me one.
Jinzhao.
The goods have gone wrong.
Go find Mr. Chen Quickly
I told you
grabbing me won't help.
Move!
You're using me
to blackmail Chen Yanyun,
aren't you?
Move! Move!
You're wrong.
The Ji family is nothing but
servants to the Chen family.
Since ancient times
servants die for their masters.
When have you seen it
the master works for his servants,
isn't it?
Otherwise
why would you kidnap me
without your master showing up?
Shut your mouth!
Move!
Take me
won't just fail to blackmail Chen Yanyun,
it'll get you killed.
Instead of losing both people and money,
why don't
we talk this through?
Shut up and walk.
Stop!
Don't come any closer!
Or I'll kill her!
Let her go!
Let her go,
you still have a chance.
Your real target is me.
Let her go,
and I'll go with you.
Go over there.
It's a cliff behind you.
No way out.
Let her go.
My life is worth more than hers.
Impressive.
A civil official like you
actually has some guts.
Let her go.
Throw your sword over here!
Mr. Chen.
Don't worry about me!
Hurry up!
Step back!
Back further!
Don't move.
Don't try to play tricks.
Don't hurt her.
Jinzhao!
Hold me tight.
Jinzhao.
Are you all right?
I think I sprained my foot.
Anywhere else
is uncomfortable?
No, only the foot.
Mr. Chen, are you hurt?
The cliff is not high.
and the ground is soft.
I'm fine.
May I take a look?
It hurts.
Fortunately, it wasn't dislocated.
A tendon was caught.
I can knead it out for you,
but it might hurt a little.
Can you bear it?
Feeling better?
Much better.
It's nothing serious.
You'll be fine by tomorrow.
But don't walk too far for now.
It's not a deep drop,
but we can't climb back up.
Don't worry.
It's not dark yet.
Jiang Yan and the others will be
able to find this place in a while.
What are you doing?
You'll see.
Soon,
Jiang Yan and the others will see the smoke
and find us.
What are you staring at?
You've
saved me so many times.
This time,
I'm the one who got you into this.
They were after me all along.
Jinrong said
the goods were tainted.
Could it be
related to them?
They wanted to use
my ties with the Ji family
to smuggle weapons out.
I see.
You seem
different from
two months ago.
Why?
Talk less,
and
smile less.
I really feel much better.
Good.
I heard
you've bought a lot of properties
in Shanxi,
and invested in a major bank.
I didn't mean to pry into your affairs.
It's just that
major banks in Shanxi
handle the empire's grain and silver.
By imperial order,
any change in shareholding
must be reported
to the authorities.
Why the sudden interest
in Shanxi?
I've been
thinking lately
about my future.
After much thought,
I think Shanxi
might be the best place for me.
You don't mean...
I plan to comb my hair up*
[Women who refuse marriage and choose to remain single]
and move to Shanxi
to run a business.
Because of your mother.
Yes.
Indeed,
it's partly because of my mother.
But
not entirely.
The sages teach:
In marriage,
harmony is the most precious.
Marriage only makes sense
if it benefits both people.
That's the right way.
But when I think about myself,
I truly can't see
any benefit
marriage would bring me.
So
I've decided not
to take that risk.
I'm sorry
I shouldn't have
said all this to you.
What you've said
never crossed my mind.
I don't know how to respond.
But you're right.
Something
is only worth doing
if it brings benefit.
So...
When will you go to Shanxi?
I haven't decided yet.
But
if I do go,
I'll wait until
my grandmother passes away.
Miss! Mr. Chen!
Mr. Chen! Miss!
Mr. Chen! Jinzhao!
Jinzhao!
Mr. Chen! Miss!
Mr. Chen!
Jinzhao!
Miss! Jinzhao!
What should we do?
Mr. Chen!
How could this happen
in such a short time?
Look!
Smoke over there!
Hurry over!
Let's go!
Come on!
Mr. Chen.
Is he dead?
He wasn't as lucky as us.
We had leaves to cushion our fall.
He hit the rocks.
It killed him.
Mr. Chen.
Look inside his shirt.
Is there something there?
Silver notes.
Xinlong Bank, Guiyang Branch.
There's a letter too.
These bandits
were definitely planning this all along.
They must have targeted your family
from the very start.
May I see it?
[Miss,]
[this is a new prescription from Divine Healer Xiao]
Miss Gu?
Jinzhao?
This handwriting is exactly the same
as the Divine Healer Xiao
who treated my mother.
You mean...
The physician Ye Xian hired for you?
Yes.
His name is Xiaoyou.
Ye Xian's master.
Xiaoyou.
What does he look like?
High nose, narrow eyes,
thin lips like a blade.
That's right.
He grows a lump
on his left earlobe.
It's true.
No wonder I couldn't find him
no matter how hard I looked.
I was wondering
how to protect the Marquis of Changxing's mansion.
I was blind to it.
You've been looking for him?
Yes.
Xiaoyou is not his real name.
His real name is Xiao Qishan.
He was the top advisor
to the late Prince Chengqing.
But
He's Ye Xian's master.
Does that mean Ye Xian,
and the entire Marquis of Changxing's mansion,
are all involved?
Yes.
[Jinzhao!]
[Mr. Chen!]
Besides the Ji Mansion staff,
all available constables and guards
from Tongzhou government
have gone out to search.
[Mrs. Ji also paid handsomely]
[to hire escorts from]
[Weiyuan and Fuyuan Escort Agencies]
[to help with the search.]
[We didn't waste any time.]
All the bandits have been caught.
They confessed:
only two leaders
are from the southwest.
The one who kidnapped Miss Gu
is one of them.
These two leaders
take direct orders from Xiao.
The rest
are just bandits
recruited along the way.
Did they confess
where these weapons
are being delivered?
To a manor
outside the capital belonging to Prince Glorian.
Just as I thought.
Mr. Chen!
Should we keep quiet
about Xiao Qishan hiding in the Marquis' mansion?
Should we not talk about it for now
I spoke out of turn.
By the way, you said
only two leaders
are their own men.
The rest are hired hands.
Then gather another group
and deliver these weapons
secretly
to Prince Glorian's manor.
Pretend nothing happened.
Can you do that?
It should be done.
I can handle it discreetly.
I'll go arrange it now.
Good
Why are you here?
Your ankle just healed.
Walk slowly
I know
Mr. Chen,
I don't think Ye Xian
knows about Xiaoyou's true identity.
If he knew,
he would have
hidden him away.
He'd never let him
treat my mother openly.
He must be kept in the dark.
That makes sense,
but
do you have proof?
Even if Ye Xian doesn't know,
what about Lord Changxing?
Is he also clueless?
To be honest,
I don't believe
that
Lord Changxing would rebel.
Because
he and the late Prince Chengqing
are sworn enemies.
Years ago,
when Prince Chengqing's rebellion failed,
Lord Changxing
beheaded him
on the battlefield.
Is that true?
So
belief alone
isn't enough.
Xiao Qishan has been sheltered
by Lord Changxing's for years,
and he is Ye Xian's master.
On these two counts,
Lord Changxing
can't escape blame.
Then...
do you have a way to save them?
I have no way.
I know you want to help Ye Xian,
but this is of grave importance.
You
me,
the Ji family,
the Chen family—
if we get caught up in this,
one wrong move
and we'll all be destroyed.
Do you understand?
I understand.
Mr. Chen, we're ready to leave.
Let's go.
Then you
go back early too.
Aren't you entering the city?
I must return to the capital.
Jinzhao.
Let's go back too.
I'm not going back,
Jinrong.
I have something urgent
in the capital.
Lend me two horses.
Cover for me
with Grandmother,
please.
All right.
Then,
be careful on the road.
I will.
Give it to me.
Giddy up!
Miss,
are we betraying
Mr. Chen
by sneaking back to the capital
to warn the heir?
No.
As long as we don't get him,
the Ji Mansion, or the Chen Mansion involved,
it's fine.
Giddy up!
Minister Ye,
take a seat.
I
speak no idle words.
Since Father fell ill,
the palace has been in turmoil.
All sorts of ghosts and gods appear.
I've even heard repeated claims
that I am too young
to rule the dynasty,
and Father should pass the throne to Prince Glorian.
Your Highness,
you trust me too much.
If I cannot
tell loyal from traitorous,
perhaps
I truly am unfit to rule.
I know
the whole of Lord Changxing's
are loyal subjects.
The words
the Empress has said so many times,
and so has Mr. Chen.
Mr. Chen?
Yeah.
Mr. Chen said
that among all military nobles,
only Lord Changxing
would never betray Father.
Once
I could consult him,
Unfortunately,
these days
Mr. Chen is away on assignment.
I had no choice
but to
invite you here
in Frost's name.
I am at Your Highness's command.
I shall not shrink from death.
Your Highness,
what is this?
This is the map of the palace secret passages.
One end connects to the Eastern Palace,
the other to the Imperial Garden.
I tell you of this passage
just in case of emergency.
If
the crisis comes,
I—
If that day comes,
I will risk my life
to keep Your Highness safe.
My lord,
a letter from Guard Li.
She's back.
My lord.
You've grown even more rude
after months apart.
How dare you
drag me here
without
even bowing!
Qingpu,
keep watch outside.
Yes, miss.
I need to talk to you.
It's about your master,
Divine Healer Xiao.
I don't believe you.
This is nonsense!
Many people
have identical handwriting.
You condemn him as Xiao Qishan
and falsely accuse him of treason
over one note!
I asked him to treat your mother
for you,
to see your mother
and this is how you repay me?
Ye Xian,
Listen to me,.
I don't want to hear a word!
Miss,
we risked everything
to ride back through the night
to warn him,
and
he's so ungrateful!
He grew up
with Divine Healer Xiao,
they're like father and son.
It's normal
he can't accept it.
But he's smart—
he'll know I'm not lying.
I won't talk nonsense.
My lord...
Did you hear that?
Yes.
My lord,
Do you believe it?
I ask if you believe it.
Did Master really lie to me
all these years?
I don't know,
but I don't think Miss Gu would lie.
Miss Gu will not lie to me.
They all say
Xiao Qishan
incited Prince Chengqing
to rebel.
I didn't believe it before,
but now I see—
right after the prince's defeat,
he defected to the
Lord Changxing's.
He's a crafty man.
I was shocked
when
I heard the news.
But
from what we've found,
Prince Glorian and Xiao Qishan
are colluding in treason,
along with Lord Changxing.
Master,
what's your view
on Lord Changxing's involvement?
With Xiao Qishan there,
Lord Changxing cannot be exonerated.
Arrest him if we must.
Do you want to protect him?
No.
But Lord Changxing
has won great battles
and commands immense respect in the army.
If he's gone,
who
will defend Jiubian
if war breaks out?
Jiubian
will not fight soon.
The treasury is full—
can we not train new soldiers?
Jiuheng,
you're bright
but inexperienced.
To improve,
you must think long-term.
Take a long-term look
Yes.
Mr. Chen,
as you expected,
Miss Gu rode back to the capital
right after we left,
and went straight
to see Ye Xian.
Ms. Jinzhao!
You're back!
Ever since
you and Mr. Jingrong
went to Tongzhou,
Lord Gu lost his post.
He spends all his days
at taverns,
ignoring everything.
Now Ms. Lan
handles all household affairs.
While you were gone,
I had your courtyard
and Jinrong's
cleaned every day.
You must be exhausted from the journey.
I've told the kitchen
to make
longan and red date soup
to nourish you.
Thank you.
If you have something to say,
say it.
I've come to apologize, Jinzhao.
I've reflected
these days—
I was foolish and blind
to right and wrong.
It won't happen again.
Please,
please forgive me.
I'll obey you
from now on,
whatever you command.
That doesn't
sound like you.
Get up.
What do you want?
JInzhao is such a cheerful person,
that
I'll just say it straight.
I heard that
before you left for Tongzhou,
you signed a paper with Lord Gu
saying he can't interfere
in your or Jinrong's marriages.
It's up to you.
I also want to be like you
and Jinrong
in the future
if Lord Gu uses my marriage
for gain,
please help me.
You do not agree?
I don't agree to make a deal with you.
Because it is not necessary.
And I don't need
you listen to me in everything.
Your marriage.
I don't want to get involved.
Looks like you
still won't forgive me.
Whatever.
It is useless to talk more.
Time sees people's hearts.
Miss,
do you think
she's telling the truth?
Whether it's true or not,
from what I know of her,
she probably means it.
Sometimes I feel sorry for her.
She's pretty pathetic, too.
Unlike me,
she has no grandmother to rely on.
Now
she only has herself.
I wonder
how Ye Xian is.
Greetings, Young Lord.
Is Mr. Xiao here?
My lord,
Mr. Xiao and Lord Changxing
are in a meeting.
I bribed the night-soil collector
to sneak into the manor and check.
There are two full chests
of sharpened swords and spears,
plus smoke bombs—
all military-standard.
It appears
Mr. Xiao was right in your speculation.
Prince Glorian harbors evil intentions.
[He's plotting something big.]
[Yes.]
[Looks like I guessed correctly.]
[It is indeed the Young Lord.]
Now that you're here.
Just come in.
Is Father meeting with Mr. Xiao?
Or else,
I'll come back later.
No need.
You've grown up.
The Marquis'
will be yours one day.
We are deliberating today.
Come and listen too.
Come in.
How did you know
Prince Glorian is buying weapons illegally?
Actually, you don't know
I've been ordering Mr. Xiao to secretly monitor
Prince Glorian's Mansion.
These days, Prince Glorian
has been close to Yun Tao, Commander of the North City Garrison,
and Lv Ming,
Chief of the Left Jinwu Guard,
Last month, he even gave
Commander Yun
two beauties from the Western Regions.
That's too much to say.
No amount of water to drink will help.
I remember you
are not very talkative before.
Before, I lived in the mountains.
Apart from you,
there were only monkeys.
Not much to say.
What are you staring at me like this?
You secretly helped my father to spy on
Prince Glorian's mansion.
Such a big thing.
Why do you keep hiding it from me?
Not intentionally to hide it from you.
Just think you're still young.
There's no need to tell you.
Why are you looking for me
in such a hurry?
Gu Jinzhao.
She came back from Tongzhou.
I want to see her,
but I don't want to go empty-handed
or
with some cheap gift.
So,
is there anything
that can be handled.
[What good things]
[can I have here?]
[I only have bows,]
[daggers,]
[hidden weapons,]
[and poison.]
[This slingshot is a new one I made.]
[Take it if you want it.]
[I don't want this.]
I remember the slingshot you
gave me back in the day.
Did I send you a slingshot?
Yeah.
When I went back to the Capital that year.
I've just been there for a day,
and I wrote to ask you to come and pick me up.
I waited from the first day of the new year to
the fifteenth day of the first lunar month.
You're finally came.
[Ye Xian.]
[Master.]
[What's wrong?]
[Why are you unhappy?]
[Look at what Master gave you.]
[I don't want a slingshot, ]
[I want a bolt.]
[You're too young.]
[Master promises you,]
[when you grow up]
[Master will give you crossbows.]
[A word is made.]
[You have such a good memory.]
[I don't remember at all.]
[Take this slingshot.]
Forget it.
I'd better look for something else.
Well.
He's acting strange today.
My lord,
I'm looking for Ms. Jinzhao.
Well?
You were right—
someone is following us.
You're finally willing
to believe what I said.
Yes.
I'm afraid of being suspected,
so I came under the pretense
of returning Baopu.
Is there a side gate?
I want to see Chen Yanyun,
immediately.
There is a small door to
the north of our house
direct access to the small alley.
Particularly concealed.
I'll take you right now.
Mr. Xiao,
tell me in front of my father
Prince Glorian is hiding weapons
and colluding with
Commander of the North City Garrison,
and the Jinwu Guard.
I think,
it seemed like he was helping my father
guard against his rebellion.
I trust Jinzhao wouldn't lie.
But in this way,
Xiaoyou basically told my father
everything.
This plot.
I'm a little confused.
Could it be
Xiaoyou did not betray Lord Changxing?
But those weapons
It was clearly
he shipped them to Prince Glorian.
What I don't get is—
Xiaoyou asked my father to guard against
Prince Glorian
but at the same time,
he secretly serving Prince Glorian.
What is he trying to do?
Lord Ye is loyal to the country.
He hates traitors above all.
He beheaded Prince Chengqing
on the battlefield
years ago.
Nowadays
he knows Prince Glorian
have the heart of rebellion.
How could he sit still.
He will surely gather troops in the dark.
Be ready to escort the Emperor at any time.
But in this way,
Lord Ye's actions
will be
the evidence of his future conspiracy.
This
is probably what Xiaoyou planned.
At the moment, the Marquis Mansion is
in a hopeless situation.
If Prince Glorian rebels,
Lord Ye will certainly
bring troops into the palace to escort the Emperor.
If he does not go in.
It would be tantamount to treason.
Advance
will also be deemed treason.
Mr. Chen.
Is there any way to break it?
There is a way,
but it is extremely dangerous.