Hello, sir.
What are you looking for tonight?
We’ve got several newcomers this week.
Some of them just got here, even.
Whatever it is you want, I’m sure we have it.
88, you’re up.
Your drink, sir.
You must have been tired
after a long day on the road.
Sure am.
Traffic was bad today.
It always is.
My leg’s so worn out from hitting the brake all day.
Why don’t you let me…
give you a little massage?
Not too fast, sir.
Let’s wait for the food to arrive.
We can go all out with no interruptions after.
Sing with me, then.
How are you feeling?
It feels so good.
Do you like it rough or do you
prefer something gentle?
I don’t mind both ways.
I think your food is here.
Go take a look.
You’re always right on time, man.
What?
You two know each other?
We do.
A bit too well, I suppose.
Who the hell are you people?
We’re the guys who’ll take you to heaven, sir.
How many times did I tell you
not to dress up on the job?
You stand out like a sore thumb.
But I like it.
We’re off duty so I can just be myself.
Not everyone wants to dress like
it’s always a funeral like you do.
Well, black makes me blend in easily.
If you sneak around in the color you’re wearing,
people would recognize you right away.
What’d you do if you got caught?
Don’t worry about me.
Worry about your job.
Did you check the security camera?
I always get my job done, don’t I?
’Kay.
I’m off, then.
It’s Friday.
I’ve got plans.
Plans?
You going out?
We literally just clocked off.
Shouldn’t you be laying low?
Are you my brother or my father, Fadel?
You nitpick too much.
Because you give me so many reasons to.
The streets are littered with cops out there
and you don’t give a damn.
What’d you do if you got caught?
Have I been?
I never make mistakes, do I?
I do what I have to do.
Now I want to do what I want to.
Can’t I just live a little?
Fine.
Just be careful.
’Kay.
Bye.
My ride’s here.
Hey.
Hit it.
Bye-bye.
[OLD FART]
Hey.
What’d you think of this tattoo?
Ain’t it a classic?
Are. You. Listening. To. Me?
The hell’d you do that for?
Should I get this tattoo?
It’s not bad.
I can make it look better, though.
It looks a bit too cartoonish here.
I guess.
What’s with you tonight?
You’re with your best friend,
but you keep looking around
for your next body count.
Aren’t you a damn player?
For real, man.
Quit it with your one-night-stands
and just get a real lover.
But I’m not looking to commit.
I’ve got my hands full as it is.
I’d rather someone I can just chat with,
someone I can count to split in the morning.
It’s easier that way.
But you’re in no position to call me out
when you’ve been playing around just the same.
This is why we’re friends, man.
I don’t know what you’re talking about.
I’m just making sure
I’m still at the top of the game.
That guy’s cute.
Which one?
The shortie in red.
What are you waiting for, then?
Go for it.
Be right back.
Left behind, once again.
Shift the weight to your other leg just a bit,
and I bet you could have made it a strike just now.
Thank you…
for the unsolicited advice.
Feels like I just got politely told to get lost.
I’m sorry.
I’ll be straightforward.
I was just making small talk
because I thought you’re cute.
See, that ain’t so hard, right?
No need to be patronizing.
Weren’t you trying to teach me how to hit a strike?
A bit close, huh?
Thought you wanted to throw a strike.
See?
Alright.
I’ll admit you’re good at bowling.
Anything else to show off?
Why don’t you come with me and find out?
Your place?
Can’t. I live with my little brother.
How about your place?
Can’t. I live with my big brother.
We’ll book a hotel, then.
Okay.
Deal.
(Sorry, man.)
(I’ll see you at your garage.)
(The tattoo’s on me.)
Oh, bastard.
Shit!
Ugh, shit.
You alright?
I am.
My car isn’t.
Were you distracted or something?
I’m sorry.
Are you drunk?
I’m not.
I literally had one can of beer.
Hey, that’s already one too many.
You shouldn’t even be behind the wheel.
But I’m really not drunk.
I was just texting my friend.
Texting?
You were on the phone while driving?
Be considerate for everyone else
on the road, will you?
Do you even have a driver’s license?
Of course I do!
Will you calm down?
How about this?
I’ll take responsibility for your—
It’s okay.
I got it.
No can do.
It ain’t like me to hit and run.
I’ve fixed the same model before.
I’ll get that tail light replaced
and throw a free checkup in for you.
Let me see.
Are you a mechanic?
Yeah.
My garage is called Style Auto.
Look it up.
Will you just let me take a look at the damage?
What’s your problem?
Let me assess the damage.
How else would I repair it?
The parts for your model aren’t easy
to come by, you know?
Listen.
I’m in a rush here.
I don’t have time for this.
I’ll bring it to your garage
when I can later, alright?
Come on.
It takes no time at all so let me—
I said I’m in a rush!
Fine.
I’ll see you at the garage.
Drive carefully.
You’re not the only guy on the road.
Thanks for the lecture, Dad!
Are we kissing before we even
know each other’s names?
Do we need to?
We’ll forget it tomorrow anyway.
Okay, then.
Perfect for me.
You got it?
You’re not doing this solo, you know?
Babe.
What time is it?
Don’t you have cram school?
Well, what time is it?
Why did you just come home?
I don’t mind, actually.
Do what you want.
You’re at that age, after all.
Just be sure to use protection, alright?
I don’t wanna be an uncle yet.
Think you’re funny, huh?
What are you reading?
Shakespeare.
You read everything he wrote?
No and not soon.
He wrote way too many books.
I’ll just keep reading until I get to see
one of his plays in the UK one day.
Determined, aren’t you?
Yeah.
I’m off to school.
Alright.
I ain’t picking you up.
Don’t come home so late.
You’re one to talk.
Who the hell did you take that tongue after, idiot?
Our gig last night.
[CRIME BOSS SHOT DEAD AT MASSAGE PARLOR]
We made headlines.
Crap.
Ain’t that cool?
Do they know we did it?
The point is to make sure nobody knows that, right?
Cops will just swamp here otherwise.
What’s with you?
You seem so bummed.
This place is ours, you know?
What cops are you even talking about?
Did you forget
who and why we had to move
our house and business here?
Hey, one, two, three, I ain’t a player.
I ain’t no player, but I sure am looking for trouble!
Yeah.
I know I’m a troublemaker.
But if being hitmen makes it so hard to live,
shouldn’t we just quit?
Do you honestly think quitting is easy?
So?
Are we supposed to live like this until we die?
I don’t want to kill people for a living my whole life.
Mother only wants us to kill bad people.
Those money laundering,
drug and human trafficking scums.
They deserve to die.
Please, Fadel.
After we get the next gig done,
let’s ask Mother for a little break.
I’ll take as little as a year.
I just want to live my life.
Please.
Keep dreaming.
Go clean the window.
Take the trash out.
Make sure to separate them.
Hey.
What’s happened to your car, man?
Shaky brakes, broken clutch, messed up gears.
It ain’t worth fixing.
Just sell it to me.
You’re not fooling me.
I told you one too many times this ain’t for sale.
My Dad left this for me.
Ain’t no way.
Didn’t you steal this car?
No.
I’ve cleared my name of car theft.
Look.
My hands are so damn clean now.
Yeah.
Well, how was last night?
Spill the tea, man.
Was he good?
Yeah.
I literally passed out afterwards.
Crap.
Lucky you.
Meanwhile, I hit some
jerk’s back bumper last night.
You alright? Everything okay?
I’m fine.
But now I gotta fix his car.
Let’s get back to your story.
Where were we?
How was it, again?
Everything was great.
But he just disappeared the next morning.
I didn’t even get his name.
I might as well have slept with a ghost.
It’s like he’d be real only in my memory.
Ain’t that weird?
You sure he didn't rob you last night?
Nah.
I’ve still got all my stuff.
Oh?
Oh, who’s that?
Is it the guy from last night?
Is it him?
Let me see.
It’s not.
Then who is it?
You keep secrets from your best friend now?
Stop it.
Yes, Captain?
You do know I’m not one
of your officers, Captain Chris?
You can’t keep making me work for you.
Last time you told me
that if I got you the drug dealer,
you’d finally cleared my name.
I did.
I swept all your car theft cases under the rug.
No one will bother you with that again.
But I’ve got another job for you.
If you get this done for me,
not only will your criminal record be swept away,
I’ll wipe it clean.
What do you say?
Hey, what you got there?
- Crap!
- Follow him!
Shit!
Halt!
Stop!
Hands behind your back.
Stay still!
Stay!
If you refuse,
I might just reopen these cases.
You’re twisting my arm, Cap.
Think about it.
If you go to jail,
who’d take care of your brother?
As if I even had a choice.
What do you need me to do?
Get close to some hitmen.
Hitmen?
You think I’m James Bond or something?
How’d I even fight them?
I don’t want you to fight them.
I want you to learn about them.
I’m suspecting these two are responsible
for many recent politician and
business mogul kills.
If you know that much,
why not just go and arrest them?
No can do.
I need the bigger fish.
I want you close to them.
Do whatever is needed to get them to spill.
I believe you can do it.
Here’s their address.
Take a look.
Holy crap.
It’s the one-night ghost.
Tyle.
- Tyle, you idiot.
- Ouch, Dad!
What was that for?
With that loud music,
no wonder you couldn’t hear me.
Well, you didn’t call me by my name, huh?
It sounds like, “Die, die, die!”
Why’d you name me Style
if you’re not gonna call it?
So it was my fault for naming you so cool?
Look after the garage for a bit.
I gotta head out to buy some parts for a client.
Don’t just listen to music, okay?
Yeah.
Oh, it’s you.
How long have you been here?
Long enough to see you dance to the whole song.
Well?
What do you think?
Was I cool?
So.
Cool.
Fine.
I’m not messing with you anymore.
I almost thought you wouldn’t show up.
I just hope you can fix it like you said you could.
Of course I can.
Where’s your insurance claim?
I don’t have one.
Then how am I supposed to fix it?
You want me to pay for the whole repair?
You were drunk and on the phone
during the accident.
It’s your responsibility to pay for that.
Good thing it was just a rear bumper.
If it had been a man you hit, what would you do?
Relax.
I’ll fix it alright.
Give me your vehicle registration.
You got that?
No.
No insurance.
No registration.
Ain’t that suspicious?
How so?
It could be a stolen car.
How I came to have this car...
is my business.
Your business is to fix it.
I doubt it.
Don’t wanna get involved with some shady business.
Oh?
Is this your excuse to get out of this?
Relax.
I was just making sure.
I’ll fix it alright.
It will be as good as new.
Heart Burger?
Hello.
Welcome—
Oh?
That was amazing.
What a shame.
We won’t see each other again.
Welcome.
You work here?
Yes.
I own the place.
I must be the luckiest man alive
to run into you again.
To wake up to an empty bed that morning…
I thought I’d slept with a ghost.
Sorry.
I was in a rush.
It’s okay.
It’s karma, really.
I did that to so many people.
A taste of my own medicine, I suppose.
Isn’t it too much of a coincidence
that you just walked into my place?
My tattoo parlor is also in this area.
I see there’s a new burger joint
so I thought I’d try it.
Who’d have thought I’d run into someone…
so memorable?
What’s your signature dish?
Everything on the menu is great.
But our burgers are top notch.
We also have pastas and steaks.
One cheeseburger, please.
Hey.
What’s your name?
I might become a regular soon, you know?
Bison.
Cool name.
I’m Kant.
Take it. Take it. Take it.
Ugh, Fadel!
You’ve been gone too long!
Why didn’t we open an omelette restaurant instead?
Alright!
Oh, crap!
Shit!
Bon appetit.
It looks great.
Careful.
It’s sharp.
Thank you.
You can let go now.
You could’ve let me know you didn’t want the veggies.
It’s alright.
Just think of this as getting to know more about me.
Do you have delivery?
I might need to order this later.
Currently we don’t.
But if you want it,
I’ll be right at your door.
How about that?
I’ll take you up on that offer.
There’s one more thing I wanna ask you, though.
Yeah?
Will you go on a date with me?
You’re new in this area.
You might not know the place.
I’ll show you around.
You got ulterior motives or something?
If I said I wanted to be your boyfriend,
would you think it’s too soon?
A bit.
I appreciate the straightforwardness, though.
I like it.
Bon appetit.
Thank you.
There’s nothing to worry about that guy.
I’ve checked.
How could you be sure?
Did you check his household registration?
And why were you so close just now?
Of course I’ve checked him.
Inside…
and out.
Several positions, really.
You slept with him once and you let him come here?
You know damn well
how important this place is for us.
It was all a coincidence.
His tattoo parlor is in the neighborhood.
Coincidence, my ass.
Look.
He ate half of this burnt crap.
If he didn’t want to take you out,
he wouldn’t have forced himself to swallow this.
Take me out?
No way!
You think so?
Bison.
Listen to me.
Don’t trust anyone.
In our profession,
when someone approaches us,
it is wise to assume they want something.
Don’t be their victim.
You overanalyze everything, you know that?
Come on.
No need for a thorough checkup.
I always do a good job.
I guarantee it’s as good as new.
Actually, it might even be better than that.
I changed the parts for you, you know?
Why?
I liked the old ones.
I didn’t ask you to do that.
What?
I meant well
and you have a problem with that?
Fine.
Give me my car key back.
This?
Hey.
I think you left something in the car.
What is it?
What are you doing?
Why–Why are you taking off your shirt?
What are you, a pervert?
That’s a spare pin of my burger joint.
Give it back.
You flip burgers?
You certainly don’t fit the look.
What should we look like? With a bun on our head?
You do everything yourself?
Yes.
I do.
Now give me back my pin.
I need to get back to my restaurant.
I want to try your burger.
I bet it tastes divine.
Listen.
I don’t have time for this.
Give that back to me right now.
You want this?
Take it from me.
Fine.
Hey.
Careful with my nipples.
They’re sensitive.
Of course.
Hey!
That hurts!
Come back for our service!
Messing with you is so much fun.
From your car and how you dress,
you don’t look like
a typical tattoo artist, you know?
More like…
those uppercrust tattoo artists.
Hardly.
I just have enough to get by.
Oh, hey, can I ask you something?
Hmm?
How old are you?
29.
For real?
Should I address you differently?
I’m only 24.
If you want to, go ahead.
But if you do,
I should call you little brother.
It’s cute.
Nah.
I don’t know you well enough.
I’ll just call you what I call you right now.
It’s better that way.
Well…
Let’s get to know each other better today, shall we?
Are you more of a beach person or mountain person?
Beach.
We used to live near the ocean.
I love swimming.
Would you believe me
if I told you I’m afraid of the ocean?
Why?
Something happened when I was a kid.
I almost drowned.
Now I’m still afraid of it.
It’s understandable.
It must have been traumatizing.
I’m alright now.
You have a tattoo behind your ear?
Can I see?
K-A-N-T.
That’s how you spell your name?
Not really.
Originally it was spelled differently,
but I prefer this one.
Because it’s also the name of a philosopher.
It makes me look cool and smart as hell.
You know what Kant means in Thai?
It means, “the beloved.”
Too bad I have no one who loves me right now.
Hey!
This is mine.
Eat yours!
Thanks for the tour.
My pleasure.
I love being a good neighbor.
If I want you to show me around again…
My tattoo parlor is always open.
You can come over anytime.
And if I get hungry,
I’ll show up here.
What if…
I want to do what we did that night,
where should I go to?
What did we do?
I must have been way too drunk that night.
I hardly remember anything.
Well…
Let me give you a little reminder.
What the hell are you doing?
What?
We’re not doing anything.
Kant just gave me a tour of the neighborhood.
I told you he owns a tattoo parlor around here, right?
Hello.
Take these inside.
Put these in the fridge.
Why don’t you do it yourself?
Go.
See you around.
See you.
Come on in.
You go on ahead.
Fadel.
Go on ahead.
Well, excuse me.
Wait.
Yes?
Are you hitting on my little brother?
Yes.
Is that not allowed?
Why?
What do you want?
You already slept with him.
That should be more than enough.
My brother doesn’t need a boyfriend.
But he seems to like me just fine.
You’re full of yourself, aren’t you?
A bit, yeah.
He may like you,
but I don’t.
If you want him,
you get through me.
There’s no lead yet, Cap.
(Hey.)
(Why’d you sound so discouraged so soon?)
(You need to hurry up, though.)
(They just made another kill.)
Is it too late for me to back out now?
(You can’t.)
(Keep your eyes on your and your brother’s future.)
(You’re a smart brat.)
(You’ll find a way.)
(I know you can do it.)
Ugh, I know.
Bye.
Oh, hey.
Are you closed?
Yes.
But seeing you’re more special than the rest,
I’ll keep the place open all night long.
I’m just here to give you this burger.
I messed up the one I made for you the other day.
Fadel made this, so it’s going to taste great.
Is he likely to poison me?
No way.
He didn’t know it was meant for you.
No veggies, of course.
Hey, this is really good.
Unlike the one you made last time.
Speaking of which,
you and Fadel can’t be more different.
You don’t look anything like each other, either.
Honestly,
are you sure you guys really are brothers?
We are.
We have the same mom, but different dads.
It’s not weird that we don’t look alike, right?
Does Fadel hate all of your boyfriends?
I wouldn’t know.
I never have one.
Really?
Yeah.
You want me to believe
you’ve never had one boyfriend?
Yeah.
I never dated anyone seriously.
But the guys I hanged out with, like you,
I enjoyed their company.
What do I have to do if I want to be
the first guy to take you out?
Win Fadel over.
How should I proceed?
It’s impossible.
Fadel doesn't trust anybody.
He has no friends.
He doesn’t believe in love.
As long as he’s single,
so am I.
What I hear is…
if your brother has someone,
it’s possible between us.
I guess.
But whoever is going to take him out
has gotta be real crazy and bold.
What if I were to say
I know someone exactly like that?
Are you gonna ask someone to hit on my brother?
Yeah.
I’ll do anything
if it means we end up together.
Kant?
Oh, sorry.
Babe.
This is Bison.
Hi.
Hey.
That’s Babe, my little brother.
Ignore me, guys.
I’m just here to pick up my books.
What?
You want me to hit on that jerk?
That’s the guy I had the accident
with the other night.
That guy?
Yeah.
He’s your crush’s brother?
He’s in my way.
You need to help me.
You know I don’t usually feel
this way about someone.
No can do.
I don’t want to waste my time.
What a freaking poser.
He’s like a vicious dog.
I probably need to get
a rabies shot before getting near him.
No way.
I’m outta here.
Hey, hold on.
What do I have to do for you to help me out?
Should I pay you?
No way.
A man like me can’t be bought.
Unless…
Unless what?
Give me your dad’s car.
Oh, jerk.
Well?
If you’re okay with that, it’s a deal.
Fine.
I’ll do it.
Under one condition.
You have to make him
head over heels in love with you.
You sure about this? Are you?
That car’s your treasure, ain’t it?
Well?
If you get him out of the way,
it’s worth it.
I’ll do it.
Not just for the car,
but someone like him
needs to be humbled by someone like me.
Deal.
Thank you.
We’re closed.
Not so fast.
I haven’t made my order yet.
How’d you find this place?
Nothing is out of my reach...
if I really want it.
Wow.
American dining interior design…
I love it.
Hey, why don’t you buy me a burger in exchange?
In exchange for what?
For the repair, duh.
Aren’t you shameless?
You hit me and then ask me to treat you to a meal?
It doesn’t hurt to be generous.
My kitchen is closed.
I’ll have a beer.
We have time for that, right?
If you want a drink,
go to a bar.
No.
It just isn’t the same.
This place has some cool music,
and a really cool owner with a good taste.
One beer, boy.
Chop-chop.
Hey.
One more.
One more beer.
Won’t you join me, handsome?
One more, please.
You’re drunk.
I’m not.
I’m just tipsy.
Enough to make me so bold.
If we were in a club,
I’d be dancing so close to you.
I’d be dancing around you like this,
and then whisper in your ears:
“Wanna come home with me?”
That’s enough.
You’ve tested my patience.
I’ll send over the bills to your garage.
Now go home.
No.
If you want me to go,
give me a ride home.
You won’t go?
No.
Fine.
Still no?
No.
Then I’ll take you home.
What?
Let go!
Hey, what are you doing?
Let go of me.
Let go.
Hey, how could you treat me like this?
Let go of me!
Stop it!
Hey!
You can’t do that!
I’m a customer!
Hey, let go of me!
Let go!
Hey!
You can’t do this to me!
I’m a customer!
We’ll see!
I’m gonna take you out!
Shit!
You’re friends?
You promised you’d help me.
Find out what that crazy dog likes to do.
I’ll find a way to get to him.
You sure your friend knows what he’s doing?
I don’t believe anyone is
more shamelessly bold than he is.
Good morning.
Who sent you?
I like you.
It was love at first sight.
Ain’t that romantic?
Like we’re in a movie.
Let’s talk about us.
Are you asking me out?
What do you want me to be if not your boyfriend?
You have a lot to prove first.