(Uilhan Brewery)
(1. Malting, 2. Malt milling, 3. Mash tun, 4. Hopping)
(Kim Se Jeong)
(Highly passionate, highly sensitive)
(Lee Jong Won)
(Shin Do Hyun)
(Baek Sung Chul)
(Uilhan Brewery)
(Naro Beer)
(Brewing Love)
(This is a work of fiction.)
(Scenes with child actors and animals were filmed...)
(under production guidelines along with experts.)
(Funeral Hall)
I'm all right.
Gosh. I'm fine.
I'm...
Grandma.
He...
is hurting more over my ordeal than me.
(May she rest in peace.)
I guess everyone has a story that can't be told.
I don't.
- What? - What?
That came out wrong.
Where's Yong Ju?
- Will she be all right? - Of course.
Didn't you see her earlier?
She'll be fine.
(Funeral Hall)
Only today...
did I realize how awkward I sounded while crying.
I couldn't recognize myself.
When we cry,
we find it hard to focus.
Because while crying,
our minds wander off...
thinking we don't have time for this.
When we laugh,
we do so while thinking how hilarious it is.
That's why when you cry, you should cry your heart out.
Hearing that...
brings me to tears again.
Go ahead and cry.
Cry as much as you want.
(Brewing Love)
(Episode 9)
Ms. Beautiful Bang, your house is huge.
It's so big that I don't even know who's actually home.
Look.
Our house is the only one with the lights out.
We're a family of three,
but I hate how I have to enter a house that's dark.
I lived here for over 20 years,
but it still doesn't feel like home.
Do you think I'm being a spoiled brat?
- That's what others think. - No.
Not feeling at home in your own house?
That's sad.
Hold on.
Ta-da.
I turned the lights on for you today.
Oh Chan Hwi.
I'm no longer interested in men with secrets.
I keep picturing the future these days.
Buying furniture with you...
and having breakfast with you every day.
Like that, I keep seeing you in my future.
What's your take on that?
I...
To be honest,
I don't even know what my own future holds.
Got it.
I'll head inside.
(Hwi's Toast)
Sebastian.
Why are you not your boastful self today?
Is it because it's your first time in this kind of neighbourhood?
Likewise.
Sure.
Gosh. What on earth?
Look here, mister.
This isn't a place where you can randomly park your truck.
What is this nonsense?
I'm sorry. I'll move it right away.
What reason is there for a toast food truck to be here?
I apologize.
The neighbourhood was nice, so I stopped to look around.
Unbelievable.
Run along, then.
Who in this neighbourhood would eat this kind of food?
What will people think?
Of course. They don't go well together.
As if that's news.
(Jisang Liquor)
Yong Ju will be absent until the end of the week, right?
Yes.
I think she's been having a hard time...
picking herself back up after the funeral.
I called her a few times earlier, but she didn't pick up.
Why would you call her...
when I'm leaving her alone despite us being joined at the hip?
More people can be joined to her at the hip, you know.
You're not one of her people.
- We're quite close now. - We're way closer.
Sure. Whatever you say.
Darn.
(Indoor Exercises for Patients)
Let's go. Come with me.
- Chae Yong Ju! - Chae Yong Ju.
- Chae Yong Ju! - Chae Yong Ju!
- Welcome. - Chae Yong Ju.
- Chae Yong Ju! - Hurry over here.
- Chae Yong Ju! - Chae Yong Ju!
I used to play with the hoop back in the day.
Ms. Chae, I wonder...
if you've even tried rolling this hoop before.
It's a first for me,
so I don't know how it should be done.
Seriously? You haven't done this before?
Goodness me.
I should probably give you a leg-up.
How about I literally hop instead? Like this.
- Is this how you roll it? - That's right. There you go.
Hook it like that.
Guys, get ready.
You go first.
- All right! - What the...
- Nice! - Hey!
It's this way.
Over here. Why are you going that way?
Did I cross the finish line too soon?
- Of course not. - No way. You did great!
- Nicely done. - Why did he head that way?
- This wasn't the plan. - Darn. I think it all went wrong.
Of course not. Don't say that too soon.
The real event starts with the next game.
What?
I guess it's time for Baegok-ri's iron fist.
Go for it.
Go, Kim Soon Gwan.
- Chae Yong Ju! - You've got this.
Kim Soon Gwan, go for it!
(Baegok-ri Village Hall)
- What happened? - What is it?
I think my fingers just died.
Goodness.
- Wait! - Hold on.
- What? - What?
- That's one. - Just one?
- What the... - Not just anyone...
can live through this.
If it had been Ms. Chae, we'd have called for an ambulance.
Come on.
- He at least got one. - Sure. We respect that.
What...
Did I smash too many of them?
Who suggested this anyway?
You did.
As if. It was him.
- No, it was him. - You brought this up first.
I only suggested a game of roll the hoop.
Says the man who rolled it in that direction.
The finish line was over here.
Hey, she's smiling.
Today, we'll discuss...
what we can do to put Chae Yong Ju in a better mood.
At times like this, physical activities work wonders...
that don't require any thinking.
Ms. Chae was hanging in there. She's a tough one.
You're wrong.
She cried her eyes out.
Good for her.
She was trying too hard to keep the tears in.
Can you imagine how much she had to hold back?
Are you crying?
Meanwhile, my tear glands have been closed off.
Actually, they're operating again.
- Unbelievable. - They've been unclogged.
You too?
Bring her here this second.
- Our Yong Ju! - Our Yong Ju!
So what's the next game?
All right. Bring it.
Spin the hoop.
You have to walk while spinning the hoop.
How is this a challenge?
I told you this was a bad idea.
- Let's have fruit punch. - My gosh.
Come inside for some fruit punch.
I'm having fruit punch.
- Let's have fruit punch. - Fruit punch.
- Come on. - Yes, fruit punch it is.
Then, I'll get us some beer.
This will be the last time you suggest a sports event.
- Fine. - Got it.
That's right. No more sports events.
Who suggested it in the first place?
- How are you so bad at sports? - We had fun though.
What about this was fun?
- But... - You couldn't smash a single tile.
Says the expert at rolling the hoop.
I meant that I had done it before as a boy.
- Good for you. - What?
Cry some more. Just cry your eyes out.
These aren't emotions you can hold back.
I lost my parents and eldest brother.
I've lost most members of my family,
but I still haven't gotten used to it.
Exactly. That's why one should cry.
Cry and cry some more.
Then, a day of laughter will come,
and then you'll have an appetite again.
Those days will come.
Your heart needs to feel the pain.
Where did Yoon Min Ju go?
He only left to get some beer.
Goodness.
Look at you. You know how to cry now.
So what? Didn't you tell me to cry my eyes out?
Do you want me to hold you?
How can you say that like it's no big deal?
What if the others see you?
- What about it? - My gosh!
Fall into his arms if he's offering.
Who cares if we see you? What about it?
Why reject his offer when you want it too?
Couples from the old storybooks...
would be more open with their affection.
What are you talking about?
Why would I be in his arms when it's hot outside?
I'll cool off a bit.
She was in the Special Forces hunting down terrorists,
but when it comes to dating...
I say that she's never had a real boyfriend before.
I agree.
Boss, your hair will turn gray while waiting for her to give in.
I'll keep waiting then.
I'm fine just being next to her...
- You liar. - That's a lie.
Why couldn't you tell him that you wanted it?
This is due to a lack of practice.
How can I express my feelings...
when I don't know how to do it?
Love?
I only have experience loving my country and fellow soldiers.
Why is it so darn hard?
Darn it.
So tell me.
- Are you having fun? - Sorry?
You seem to be getting along with those on the TF team.
You haven't been reporting back to me...
because Chae Yong Ju told you not to!
Are you here with a delivery?
- We'll get going first. - Sure.
I'm here to make a delivery...
and to see Ms. Beautiful Bang in the process.
Ah Reum is currently...
getting an earful from our director.
What?
Darn.
- Can you deliver this for me? - What?
Is that the director's office?
No, it's this way.
Are you going to barge in there?
That's the power of love.
Bang Ah Reum.
You're a member of the Planning Team.
You're Bang Ah Reum of the Planning Team.
You were put on the TF team...
so that you could stop Chae Yong Ju...
from developing the new beer.
That's your job!
About that...
You can talk to Ms. Chae.
Hey.
Did you think I'd just sit at my desk...
if you didn't report to me?
I can stop the new product from being launched without you.
I just wanted to give you a chance.
Although, you did nothing but let me down.
- What do you mean... - Forget it. Get out.
Ta-da!
- Chan Hwi is here. - Why are you here?
- Did you hear everything? - Yes.
You got chewed out.
Can't you pretend you heard nothing?
I don't want to. I'm going to run away with you.
It must've ruined your day. Let's just run away now.
This darn company. I'm sick of this.
- Aren't you? - As my boyfriend,
shouldn't you have barged in looking like a tough guy to protect me?
I can't even protect myself.
The director...
scares me.
- Let's run away. - You'll have to wait.
I still have hours until I can clock out.
Hey, what are you doing? You're at work.
Hello, Chief.
Oh, look who's here.
- Is your leg okay? - Yes.
Oh, who is he?
You know, the man who got trapped in the mountain...
when there was a landslide.
Right, the YouTuber.
My goodness. Do you know how worried we all were that day?
Yes, that's why I came to thank you in person today.
You didn't have to bring anything.
- Anyway, take a seat. - Okay.
- Yes, you can sit here. - Over here, right?
The injury must've been quite serious.
- Talk. I'll bring you a drink. - Okay.
The last time I was here,
one of the ladies in the neighbourhood asked me...
what the toast truck was doing here. She said it was very out of place...
and that it was embarrassing.
I thought about it,
- and she was right... - What is that lady's problem?
That is total nonsense.
Who was this lady?
Ah Reum.
- Mom? - "Mom?"
Who might you be?
You look familiar.
The toast guy?
Mom, don't tell me you're that lady. Are you?
Hey, Toast.
Why are you holding my daughter's hand?
This is...
- He's my boyfriend. - Have you lost your mind?
Be quiet. Stop spewing such nonsense.
Go home!
What if the neighbours gossip? How embarrassing.
Hey! You need to leave now.
- Go. Go inside. - Mom, it hurts!
Hey, seriously. Hurry up and go inside.
My gosh. This is so embarrassing.
Hey! What are you, a rebellious teen?
Are you pulling an antic like this to get my attention?
I said nothing when you went on about getting married.
You're a smart girl,
so I thought you'd bring home a perfect guy...
because you wouldn't want to lose to me.
But what? That toast guy?
Are you kidding me?
How could you date such a good-for-nothing?
Watch what you say.
His name is Oh Chan Hwi. We're the same age and...
Like I care.
Hey, I couldn't even afford to buy myself a bag.
Colour? Design? Why would it matter?
It was a hand-me-down,
so I was just grateful that there were no holes in the bag.
I couldn't tell if it was a knockoff or authentic,
so people laughed at me. You know what that's like?
I didn't want you to experience that kind of humiliation,
so I made sure you were always surrounded by expensive,
pretty things from luxury brands while raising you.
That is how I raised my daughter.
And what? You're dating that toast guy?
You still don't get the difference between authentic and fake.
Chan Hwi is more authentic and amazing than anyone else I know.
You're embarrassed by me...
when I don't live up to your expectations.
But Chan Hwi...
always tells me that I'm beautiful no matter the circumstances.
Even when I feel like a big ugly mess,
he tells me that I look pretty.
How old are you?
You'd still fall for such a smooth-talking poser?
Sweet words do not put food on the table!
You're clueless because you've been living too comfortably!
You're at it again.
Mom!
I've never once felt comfortable while living with you.
Do you know that?
I would've introduced you to Chan Hwi sooner,
had I known you'd show this much interest.
Do you even know how long it's been since you last touched me?
Mom.
I'm actually glad this happened.
That brat...
I'm so embarrassed.
You're pretty.
I'm really embarrassed right now.
You...
You're so beautiful.
Yes, let's not get married.
My mom is right.
You're too good for my family.
You're from a wealthy family.
And you received so much love growing up.
Why would you want to marry into such a dysfunctional family?
This is me protecting you.
Run away.
Stop eating and feed your skin instead.
You're eating everything.
Whether I'm feeding my skin or my mouth,
it doesn't matter because I'm the one soaking it up either way!
I really didn't think I'd be able to handle...
this thing called life without my grandma.
But...
I'm not alone.
Can I...
call you ladies my aunties?
What?
We've been waiting for you to call us like that.
I didn't think it'd happen until our next life.
I'm Auntie Sook Ja.
Call me Auntie Young Ja.
Aunties!
Thank you.
You know this is all thanks to our boss' hard work, right?
Oh, boy.
Boss is such a handful.
He is!
Yong Ju might come across as strong, but she's very tenderhearted.
I'll have water ready.
If she cries again, have her drink water...
If you're going to do this,
why don't you just sleep next to her?
Love, my love
You really are killing us here.
Please take good care of her.
He tries not to show it,
but he must be very anxious now.
Don't make him wait any longer.
You'll waste all the precious moments if you wait.
Believe me.
- Goodness. - Is she sleeping?
Hey, Yong Ju. Wake up.
Yes, good.
Jjuan is in trouble.
- What? - Look.
She's so hot.
She married a guy and ran off with his money.
She ran away just a month after coming to Korea.
I guess she's been hiding here.
- What is this place? - Isn't she a celebrity?
- She works at a brewery. - The brewmaster is hot.
Are they a couple?
A hundred percent. I bet all my money.
Let's boycott Naro Beer.
- We're boycotting Naro Beer! - We're boycotting Naro Beer!
- We're boycotting Naro Beer! - Here's something more shocking.
- Is he really her husband? - Husband?
- They do not look like a couple. - I'm getting goosebumps.
Shouldn't someone tell him?
Where is Jjuan now?
The moment I first saw Jjuan, I knew...
she'd seduce him and take his everything.
Exactly.
Kim is a fool.
He's too nice. Don't even get me started.
This is why they say old sayings are never wrong.
You must be careful who you interact with!
- That's right. - I hear...
people want to boycott Naro Beer.
- What are we going to do? - What will you do about this?
Don't do this!
Must you flock here and cause all this fuss...
just because of some comments on the Internet?
If you have time for this, go home, wash your feet, and sleep.
Please leave now!
- Go! - Hey!
- Leave! - What will you do?
Leave now, please!
I uploaded the video because I thought Jjuan was very pretty.
I didn't think it'd cause something like this. I'm really sorry.
Gosh, listen.
We're just like any other ordinary married couple.
I don't understand what's happening all of a sudden.
I'm so frazzled now.
This is all my fault.
Hey, that's not true. Why would you say that?
As a YouTuber,
I sure know what to do when something like this happens.
You shouldn't just ignore it and let it slide.
This has sparked many people's interest,
and the viewers have the right to know. Right?
Just tell me everything,
and I'll upload a new video with all the facts.
Thank you. Okay.
But you know, we feel so awkward in front of this camera.
I don't know how I can talk in front of...
Jjuan.
Why did you run off with your ex-husband's money?
- Oh, boy. - What are you doing?
This is quite an effort you're making to talk some nonsense.
"The right to know?" What exactly do you mean by that?
Don't think you can cover up your mistake with some fancy words.
What are you talking about?
I'm just trying to help them. I came with good intentions.
Who will benefit the most from this?
Your video view counts. Am I wrong?
In my eyes, you're having fun now.
Their pain gives you pleasure.
You're the owner of the brewery.
Be honest. You must be upset too.
What if you have to shut down your brewery because of this?
Oh, my goodness.
- I'm really sorry. - We're sorry.
Don't bow your heads, you two.
You did nothing wrong.
I know you two are in love, and that's why you got married.
Love? She might be just trying to use him.
How would you know?
Scammers would do anything to scam you.
I know they're in love. I could tell at a glance.
I guess you've never seen anyone in love.
Come on.
(3 years earlier)
- Hey! - No.
You knew you couldn't get pregnant, so you should've told me.
Do you know that this is a marriage fraud?
I told you from the get-go...
that I was infertile.
I don't understand what you're saying!
You said it didn't matter.
That you loved me.
And it didn't matter at all.
That everything would be fine as long as I came to Korea.
That's why I came.
Go back to your country.
No!
What am I supposed to do if you just leave like this?
Darn it!
No one here will take your side.
No one even understands what you're saying.
Don't be pathetic. Just go back to your country.
This never happened.
No...
- No, don't leave me... - Hey!
What are you doing?
There, you got a little taste of Baegok-ri's iron fist!
She has someone right here. I'm on her side.
What are you going to do? I understood everything she said.
How could you do this to a woman?
Are you okay?
As a Korean, I apologize.
Please just think of this as bad luck.
I will help you with anything, no matter what.
Oh, no.
My gosh.
I'm fine.
I'm okay.
Thank you.
(Kim's Supermarket)
My goodness.
Seriously, why do you keep coming here?
If people see us together, they'll gossip.
They'll think...
I'm holding you hostage or something.
Oh, boy.
This is...
Why are you always here?
When we are together, people look at us...
Kim Soon Gwan.
(Kim Soon Gwan)
Come down, my cheeks.
No, this isn't right. I shouldn't smile.
Don't do this. Come down, cheeks.
I think you have a good chance at this.
I have a good chance at what?
Forget it if I got the wrong idea.
My goodness. I'm so busy right now.
(Kim's Supermarket)
Hey.
Did you come outside to wait for her?
This is wrong.
It is a grave sin.
Yes, it's a sin. All right?
What? When did I write her name like this?
I could go to jail for this.
How did I even do this? Oh, dear.
Why don't you pluck up your courage and tell her?
Hey, seriously.
You show up like this every day...
and confuse me. Why are you doing this?
Also, it's not like we have the kind of relationship...
where we share our personal feelings.
I think the two of you feel the same way about each other.
I'm not the type to meddle in someone else's love life,
but it'd be such a shame not to do anything about it.
My goodness.
Forget it if I'm wrong.
You keep pushing me like this.
Don't do this, seriously.
I can't sleep when my mind wanders.
And more, what do you mean by "you two are on the same page?"
I couldn't even see her face for the last couple of days.
From where I stand, she went back to her homeland.
Did she?
- I don't think so. - What?
Over there.
I know very well...
that expressing yourself frankly is not easy.
But how about making a move?
Maybe, it's her, who is waiting for the moment to come.
Do you agree?
Then, please.
- Oh, sorry. - Darn, you!
Even a snail would be faster than you!
All the elderly have been waiting!
What the heck are you...
doing?
Today is a good day. So, please, stop picking a fight.
Step aside.
This way.
Who are you?
Is she a celebrity? What brought you lady to such...
a lowly place?
Everyone.
We're going to be married soon.
She's still not good at speaking Korean.
So, please, look after her.
Please, introduce yourself to all.
Nice to meet you. I'm Jjuan.
- What? - Jjuan.
- I guess she's not a Korean. - I see.
Please, call her Jjuan!
Why should I make an excuse for our love?
"A fraudulent marriage"?
What a crap!
Cut the crap!
Whenever I'm with her,
an ordinary day without any special events is...
special to me.
I even hoped time would stop.
I was so thankful for everything.
It all looked so shiny and precious.
When I'm with her,
what people call nothing special...
turns into joy and happiness.
That's why we married.
You got it?
Didn't you say you liked me?
Did I? When? I couldn't have said that.
He...
is hurting more over my ordeal than me.
I hate to see that. Why step back again?
Don't make him wait any longer.
You'll waste all the precious moments if you wait.
I even hoped time would stop.
I was so thankful for everything.
It all looked so shiny and precious.
You know, I have something to tell you.
Yes?
I never knew this word made me this nervous!
Wait. I'll find my courage.
It makes me even more nervous than a high-altitude drop!
Yes. I feel it too.
I love you.
I love you, Yoon Min Ju.
I have...
loved you...
for every single moment.
(Uilhan Brewery)
Sweetie.
You're recently indifferent to me.
I may become sullen, then!
Don't be obsessed.
We agreed to have a casual fling only.
What's going on?
I don't know.
But why isn't Yong Ju coming?
Maybe, she's still not over it.
I'm worried that something happened to her.
Don't worry. She will come back full of vigour.
Hello, guys!
I'm sorry that I worried you all.
And thanks for waiting.
So, we don't have time to waste...
on new product development.
From now on, it's time to start again!
- Yes! - Yes!
(Uilhan Brewery)
(The 4th sample)
(The final evaluation)
(Uilhan Brewery)
It tastes much better than the third sample.
But it still lacks the body.
- Hey! - Yes!
Wait a minute.
You wore blush.
You got a new lipstick.
You bought everything new.
How did you recognize that?
Who are you trying to impress?
What about me? Do you recognize something about me?
I really don't know.
Come on. Are you serious?
You really don't notice anything?
Your glasses! It's your glasses!
I got it right!
Yes, it's your glasses. That's it, right?
Come on. You should easily recognize that I'm wearing different glasses.
- Wait, so it's not your glasses? - Come on.
I trimmed my bangs a bit.
How would I know that?
- So you wanted to go somewhere. - Yes.
Where are we going?
Yes!
Security on all fronts.
Security on all fronts? We're on a date.
Go!
Gosh, she didn't even make a sound when she took off.
Oh, my. What do I do?
That stings.
- Gosh. What was that? - Come on.
- Are you okay? - I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry. - Let's go.
- What was that? - I'm sorry.
- I told you to duck. - What were you doing?
- You should've fired more quickly. - Come on.
Eyes front.
- Quickly! - Well...
What are you doing?
Well, it looks like we don't have to look ahead anymore.
You killed them all.
It's already over?
You can't treat this game like a real battle.
Isn't this how you play this game?
This is not going to be easy.
- We had so much fun today. Right? - Yes.
Get home safely.
Right! I must have spilled some food on my shirt during our meal earlier.
I must wash it. I really should.
At my house?
- Yes. This is my favourite shirt. - What?
Should I turn on the TV?
Did you have a good trip to the...
I mean... Should we have some fruits?
Yes, that sounds good.
Right on.
Why are you acting so awkward all of a sudden?
It's like you've never had a guy over late at night.
My gosh, no.
Come on. Gosh, don't be silly.
You're right. So what?
What do you want to eat? What kind of fruit do I have?
Why are you going in there?
I'll help you discover...
everything that you like.
To make up for the time you spent not being yourself,
I'm going to find everything you like.
- What? - Oh, right.
There's a TV show I wanted to show. I must watch it.
You're not going home?
I'll go after the show.
Why do you want to watch a TV show now?
What about the fruit?
Oh, right! Yes. The fruit.
Do you want pears? You know what? I'll figure something out.
(3 percent, 4 percent, 5 percent, 6 percent, 7 percent...)
Are you guys done?
- Yes. - Yes.
Let's take a look. One, two, three.
(11 percent, 9 percent, 5 percent)
That's interesting. We organically divided into three groups.
Five percent, nine percent, and eleven percent.
Nice.
- My gosh. - How is it?
It's great.
- It went well. - Nice.
What? What's this?
Coffee. You like nutty coffee.
Thanks.
You're really not leaving? Aren't you busy?
I'm busy. There's so much stuff I have to do.
Okay.
How beautiful.
You didn't bring an umbrella, right?
I knew it. So I came.
Let's go.
My gosh. There are so many different records here.
I can't believe this is here.
I'm so excited. I love it.
What? They have this one too?
I listened to this all the time when I was in school.
No way. What's this doing here?
No way. I listened to this over 100 times. I'm not kidding.
- Really? - Yes.
You like songs like this too?
This is amazing.
What did you just do? Come on.
People are watching!
What?
("Everything I Love Will Make Me Cry")
("Your Name, Youth" by Movning)
(Music Notebook)
My gosh. You don't have to hold it.
I'm pretty good at riding a bicycle.
You said you were sad that you didn't have anyone...
to hold your bike when you were little.
You didn't forget anything I said.
I remember everything.
Come on.
One, two, three.
- There you go! - Let go!
- Gosh. - Yes!
I'm so good at this!
Come back now.
You made a really nice soup.
What's that?
Here.
What? What is it?
What? It's so cute!
Have you heard that we should make sure...
our everyday items are pretty to look at?
I'm not sure.
But what's the point if we use them every day?
I really like that idea.
Even when we drink water,
it would be great if we could smile while looking at a pretty cup.
Is that so?
It's about knowing what puts you in a good mood.
It's not about liking something in general.
Instead of just saying, "I like this song,"
say "I like listening to a song..."
"while having coffee in a pretty cup."
Like that.
Let's find ten things you particularly love.
We'll do it together.
- Fine. We'll do it together. - Yes.
When did my room get so pretty?
Grandma.
I've never had this feeling before.
I find myself looking in the mirror often these days.
I quite like myself.
I look pretty.
Funny, isn't it?
(Final sample)
All right. At last,
we have the final samples of our three beers.
Gosh, please! With the hope that...
our beers will be loved by the consumers,
let's name our beer.
- Okay. - Okay.
(SB)
(Do It, Uilhan Lager)
(Beer Naming)
Why are there so many beers in Korea?
All of our names overlap. And the good ones are already taken.
It should be easy to say but leaves an impression.
An eye-catching name people can remember right away.
Can you think of a name like that?
I'm low on sugar.
Here.
My gosh.
Goodness. That's nice.
Gosh, I feel awake now.
- All right. Let's keep trying. - Okay.
Yes. Let's just go with 1, 2, and 3.
They're a set already.
A set?
I see.
They vary in both colour and alcohol content,
but they're on the same team.
Doesn't this remind us of us?
"Us?"
Hold on.
(Together)
What do you think?
The word, "together," already has such a powerful meaning.
It suits the theme of our beer. Don't you think so?
It represents us, but it still embraces these three beers.
- Together. - Together sounds great!
- Hey, I love it! - That's a great name.
- The inspiration came from me. - What a surprise.
Good one.
- That was totally me. - My goodness.
All right. Let's begin.
Okay.
Right.
Then if the internal evaluation goes well,
will our product launch right away?
No. The final boss has to give us a green light.
The chairman.
I thought the chairman was going to attend this meeting too.
Yes. But his overseas meeting couldn't be rescheduled.
So he will taste the beer tomorrow separately.
The chairman must give us the final confirmation...
before our new product can launch.
But we can't overlook the internal evaluation either.
My gosh, today's evaluation will be really important.
Gosh, I'm nervous.
(Together, 11 percent)
At last, it's ready.
Good job, Ms. Chae.
You too, Mr. Yoon.
(Together)
All right. Today is our D-Day. Let's do our best.
(New Product Tasting Event with Uilhan Brewery)
My gosh.
- Thank you. - The aroma is great.
- This is nice. - Is it?
(New Product Tasting Event with Uilhan Brewery)
My gosh, this is nice.
- Really? - This is great.
- It's so good. - It's amazing.
- Really? - Yes.
- What is this? Everyone, try it. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thanks.
You're here.
(Together 5, Together 9, Together 11)
(New Product Tasting Event with Uilhan Brewery)
We did it.
Beer ought to be gulped down like this.
All right. Could you fill it up?
You heard the man.
Beer ought to be gulped down like this.
(New Product Tasting Event with Uilhan Brewery)
I can't believe this.
This can't be true.
(Jisang Liquor, Together Beer, Taste Survey)
(Special thanks to Bae Yu Ram for his appearance)
(1st Baegok-ri Sports Day)
(Brewing Love)
This is our last chance to stop the new product launch.
It will be difficult to launch the new product.
I will submit our beer...
to an international blind beer competition.
I'll be your family, Ms. Beautiful Bang.
Do everything with me.
Doesn't everyone carry a secret in life?
Do you think you can live with someone like me?
I'm only going to look at the man in front of me.
The man who had worked hard to get to where he is now.
I'll only be looking at you, Yoon Min Ju.