[whimsical theme song playing]
[whimsical theme song continues]
[twinkling chime]
-[air hissing]
-[ball pops]
[whimsical theme song continues]
[song concludes]
[fox squealing]
NO TAIL TO TELL
WOOSONG HOSPITAL
[sirens blaring in distance]
[panting]
EMERGENCY ROOM
[gasps]
-[woman] Oh!
-[groans]
Are you okay?
[Pagun] Are you all right?
[tense music playing]
[warbling echoing chime]
[Si-yeol] Hey, Eun-ho.
What… Eun-ho!
Where did she go?
[doctor] Clear the way!
[wheels rattling]
-What…
-Are you family?
Well, my friend is in there.
-Hyeon Woo-seok is in there, right?
-You can't just barge in.
I told you, I'm his friend.
I just need to check on him.
It'll only take a few minutes.
-Hey, you can't!
-Please!
[Sang-cheol] Aren't you Si-yeol?
Mr. Hyeon.
How's Woo-seok?
Is Woo-seok okay?
-[mysterious music playing]
-[Eun-ho] What is happening?
Why did Woo-seok suddenly collapse?
Is he really going to die?
Then what about Si-yeol?
Say something! I'm sure you showed up
because you have something to say.
Did you think tampering with human fate
was a trivial matter?
What?
-[EKG flatlining]
-[doctor] Charging 150 joules.
-[doctor] Clear!
-[thud]
[doctor] Charging 200 joules. Two, clear!
[EKG flatlining]
-[air pump hissing]
-[mysterious music continues]
[EKG beeping]
Sinus rhythm is back.
-Start a saline drip, wide open.
-[nurse] On it.
[Pagun] He's not dead. Not yet.
Not yet? What does that mean?
He will eventually die.
Just not today.
That's the fate
you gave him.
Does that mean Si-yeol's fate was…
To rise high, but burn out quickly.
That was the fate
Kang Si-yeol was born with.
On the other hand,
a long but difficult life
was the fate Hyeon Woo-seok was born with.
Then what am I supposed to do?
I don't like either option.
I don't want to make Si-yeol
watch his friend die in his place
or return to his original life and die.
There must be another way.
Change fate, twist it, whatever.
If they were given such a crappy fate,
there must be a loophole or something!
You still haven't learned a thing.
You recklessly tampered with human fate…
-[music fades]
-…caused an innocent man to die again,
and now you seek cheap tricks
to deceive Heaven?
-[ethereal choral music playing]
-That's right. I'll find a way.
That's how I've survived until now,
and I have no intention
of ever accepting such a crappy fate.
[sighs deeply]
The only thing I can give you now…
is this.
[intriguing dramatic music playing]
[Pagun] When this season ends,
Kang Si-yeol's true fate is to die
before he sees another winter.
So, before Hyeon Woo-seok
dies in his place,
fix this twisted fate
with your own two hands.
[ethereal voices vocalizing]
[gasps]
[tense choral music playing]
What on earth
am I supposed to fix with this?
You already know
what that dagger is
and what you should do.
Stab him with this. You have to.
[Pagun] Commit an unforgivable sin,
and turn all your cultivated virtue
to nothing.
If you stab your beloved with that dagger,
the twisted fate will return to its place,
and you can return to being
a nine-tailed fox again.
However,
if you leave this twisted fate as it is
and a man who shouldn't die
ends up dying instead…
I will personally
end your fate with that dagger.
Then, no matter what you do,
you will never return to being
a nine-tailed fox.
You'll live out your life
as a human forever, like you are now.
-[fox squealing]
-[music concludes]
EPISODE 10
FROM CHANCE TO DESTINY
His heart rate is back to normal,
and thankfully, he woke right up.
We were lucky he got
immediate emergency care.
They said it could've been worse.
[sighs] That's such a relief.
You must have been quite shocked too.
Yes.
It was all so sudden.
Si-yeol.
Thanks for rushing over,
even at this hour.
I appreciate it.
I wish you could see Woo-seok,
but they're running further tests
on him right now.
Is there another problem?
It's nothing like that.
Just standard procedure.
Judging by his condition,
I don't expect any lasting damage.
Don't worry too much.
Okay.
[inhales deeply]
Anyway, I should get going.
I'll let Woo-seok know you stopped by.
-See you around.
-Okay.
[sighs]
[soft pensive music playing]
[traffic rumbling]
It's a relief that he's still alive.
Yeah.
I'd feel much better
if I could've seen his face.
He should be okay, right?
[music fades]
By the way,
what kind of person
is this Woo-seok anyway?
What?
[chuckles softly]
I'm just curious.
Surely he's someone special
if you'd go as far as to give up
your wish for him?
Even now, you're worrying about him first
instead of how close you came
to never getting your old life back.
-[chuckles softly]
-[soft pensive music playing]
You make it sound
like it's some huge deal.
We're just friends.
And friends make sacrifices
for each other.
I get a little upset sometimes,
but I still worry about him.
[scoffs] Come on,
what kind of answer is that?
If he's that special to you,
I thought you'd tell me
about some hidden talent
or that he's actually a pretty decent guy.
Is that really all there is to him?
[Si-yeol] Hm…
Woo-seok is
kind of a coward.
He's great at giving
but awful at receiving,
and he's a little pathetic too.
He only wants me to see his good side,
so he hides
whenever things don't go his way.
He's got an inferiority complex.
[Eun-ho] What?
Then why…
But I still like him,
regardless of all that.
I bet Woo-seok feels the same way.
I'm selfish, self-centered,
and totally full of myself.
Woo-seok knows all that about me.
But that's how childhood friends are.
Even though we're pathetic and cowardly,
none of that matters.
I don't really get it.
Shouldn't you dislike each other
if you're all that pathetic and cowardly?
-I think you already know.
-What?
You like me, don't you?
It's not because I'm the best
or somehow special
out of everyone you've ever met
in your long life.
I became special to you
because you like me.
[chuckles softly]
I think that's what it means
to like someone.
[music fades]
What if…
[sentimental music playing]
…I couldn't go back
to my true form because of you
and had to live as a human forever?
Would I still be able to like you then?
What?
If your friend had really died today,
and you'd lost your chance
to get your fate back forever,
would you still not resent me?
Would you still like me?
Eun-ho, are you okay?
Did something happen earlier?
[chuckles softly]
Nothing happened.
[inhales deeply]
The thought just came to me.
Are you telling me to choose?
Kill Si-yeol, or give up who I am?
It may seem cruel,
but fate simply takes its course.
It does not concern itself
with individual human affairs.
[sighs deeply]
Then why are you telling me to choose?
If the will of Heaven is already set,
you guys should decide
whether to kill him or save him.
[music fades]
[laughs]
[tender string music playing]
I almost fell for your tricks again.
I keep forgetting
that you guys act
like you know everything,
but the truth is, you don't know anything.
You were just trying to trick me
into fixing these twisted
human affairs for you.
But I found another way.
So I'm not making that damn choice.
Once I get my powers back,
saving Si-yeol will be a piece of cake.
I'll just stay by his side
and protect him forever.
[tender string music continues]
[sighs]
I'm suddenly so tired.
Okay.
You must be tired
after rushing out with me like that.
Get some rest.
I'll wake you when we're there.
[exhales softly]
Si-yeol.
What I said earlier
wasn't just the alcohol talking.
What?
I told you I'd get your life back,
no matter what.
That's a promise.
So don't worry about it.
Get some sleep.
We can worry about that tomorrow.
[breathes deeply]
-[birds chirping]
-[tender string music continues]
[music fades]
[Eun-ho] Si-yeol, wake up! Come on!
What…
[yawns]
What's got into you so early?
We saw yesterday
that we're gaining spiritual power,
and now that we know how,
we need to hurry.
[yawning] Right.
We have to do good deeds.
-[perky music playing]
-Do you have a plan or something?
Technically, it's not doing good deeds.
I'm fixing the misdeeds I committed.
I made a list of everything
that came to mind, so listen.
[Si-yeol clears throat]
[Eun-ho] Chairman Jin of Pyeongchang-dong.
What misdeed did you commit with him?
Was it the late '90s?
There was some land Chairman Jin wanted
that the owner wouldn't sell,
no matter what.
So you forced him to sell it?
Yeah, since I took money
from Chairman Jin,
I had to do my part.
Where was this land anyway?
-Pangyo.
-[echoing wobbly clang]
What? Pangyo?
How could you--
I didn't know the area would boom.
It was nothing but rice paddies back then.
I should've bought some.
Unbelievable.
[Eun-ho] Assemblyman Park of Hannam-dong.
He was a real piece of work too.
[music concludes]
[Sang-cheol] How does it look?
Will this affect Woo-seok's career?
I looked it up,
and some players overseas play
with an implantable defibrillator.
Does Woo-seok need to go that far?
Well, depending on the cause
of the sudden cardiac arrest,
that might be an option.
We ran tests to figure that out,
but how should I put this?
[inhales deeply]
The results aren't good.
[dark pensive music playing]
[Woo-seok] Excuse me?
[doctor] He has
primary cardiac angiosarcoma.
What is that?
Simply put, it's heart cancer.
[Sang-cheol] Heart cancer…
[chuckles nervously]
No. Cancer in the heart?
I've never heard of such a thing.
Cancer cells
don't usually form in the heart,
so this is a very rare case.
It accounts for only 0.01%
of all cancer cases.
[Sang-cheol] Doctor!
Didn't you see the news?
Woo-seok just had
a medical check-up for his transfer.
Surely your test is wrong?
[doctor] Heart cancer is tricky like that.
There are no clear symptoms,
and it's so rare
that it's hard to detect.
How…
[sighs softly]
Then what do we do now?
There has to be a treatment, right?
We don't care how much it costs--
[Woo-seok] Am I…
going to die?
[doctor sighs]
It's too late for surgery.
And a transplant isn't a realistic option.
You said it's rare.
So you don't know much
about it either, do you?
You should look into it more
before giving up!
How can you call yourself a doctor?
How much time do I have left?
Six months at most.
It could be less.
[exhales shakily]
[Sang-cheol sighs]
[groans softly]
[sobs softly]
[scoffs softly]
[music fades]
[objects shattering, clattering]
-[tense music playing]
-[Woo-seok breathing heavily]
What did I do that was so wrong?
I didn't ask for too much.
I didn't ask to live like this forever.
I just wanted to live my dream for a bit.
[shouting] Why can't I even have that?
[Sang-cheol] Woo-seok.
Something's wrong here.
Dad.
This shouldn't be happening to me.
I know.
Calm down, and let's get retested.
That guy's a total quack.
You've been training since you could walk.
You can play a full match
without getting tired.
How could you have heart problems?
That's just ridiculous.
[Woo-seok] No. That's not it.
We can't go to another hospital.
We have to keep this a secret, Dad.
[breathes shakily]
-What?
-Pay off the doctor.
Do whatever it takes!
This can't get out.
What are you talking about, Woo-seok?
We need to get you tested again.
[Woo-seok] Si-yeol…
Forget all that.
[breathes heavily]
I need to see Si-yeol.
[music concludes]
So, these are all the misdeeds
you've committed?
No, not exactly--
[Si-yeol] Right?
I thought the list was too--
I only listed cases since Liberation.
I left out the Joseon era.
We need the clients to still be alive
for us to do anything.
-[quirky music playing]
-Right. I see.
You sure were diligent about making money.
-Anyway, what do you think?
-What?
Which one should we set right first?
[sighs] Man, I don't know.
There are just so many.
Even if we just pick a few easy ones,
I think the spiritual power
will build up fast.
[cell phone buzzing]
[Si-yeol] Wait.
[Si-yeol] It's Woo-seok.
[unsettling music playing]
[cell phone buzzing]
[music fades]
It's locked.
Just wait a second.
[keypad beeping]
[cell phone buzzing]
What's up?
Coach, the field is locked.
What?
Seriously, those guys.
I asked them to just wait a few days.
Pardon? Wait for what?
Never mind.
Look, there's no training today.
So just go home, rest up,
and take care of yourselves.
[Beom] Another day off?
We just got one yesterday.
You guys aren't in the best shape.
Hey, just do as I say and tell the guys.
[cell phone beeps]
[Yong-gil] Here you go.
-[hopeful music playing]
-Hello, sir.
-Who are you?
-[Yong-gil] Oh, right.
I sent you a text,
but I didn't get a reply.
So I took the liberty
of coming to see you.
[chuckles nervously]
Well…
I'm with Daeheung Citizens FC.
We're the soccer team
based here in Daeheung.
I was wondering
if you'd be inclined
to be our team's main sponsor.
-No, we're good.
-Wait, sir!
Please just take a look
and think about it.
Your company name
would be right here on our uniforms.
It'll really help your company's image
in the local community.
And it'll really boost employee morale--
-Excuse me.
-Okay.
Yes, I'm going.
Sir! I'll text you the details!
-[music fades]
-What did Coach say?
He said to go home.
-That there's no training today.
-What?
But we have an away game this weekend.
-Don't we need to prepare for it at all?
-[sighs]
I know. We really should train today.
-[fox squealing]
-Do you want me to open it?
-[group yelps]
-[quirky music playing]
Hey.
We saw you at Si-yeol's place yesterday.
-Hello.
-[Beom] Hello.
What a coincidence. You must live nearby.
We came to train, but the gate's locked.
[twinkling chime]
[padlock clicks]
That scared me.
What the…
This just…
It's open.
What?
[Gyeong-hun] Maybe this lock is defective.
It was definitely locked earlier.
Shouldn't we go in
and train by ourselves at least?
Hey.
Lock it again.
[Gyeong-hun] Hurry up and lock it!
As you can see, training's off,
so we're heading out to grab a bite.
Have you eaten yet?
[fox yipping]
-[music fades]
-[fox squealing softly]
[sirens wailing]
[knocking on door]
[exhales]
Hey, Si-yeol.
Hey…
Are you okay?
[chuckles softly]
Yeah.
I'm fine.
I just need to rest for a few days.
[inhales deeply]
Come on in.
Oh, okay.
You came together?
The thing is--
I know. My memories came back.
I know she's now human,
and that's why you can't switch
your life back.
I remember everything now.
Woo-seok.
This has nothing to do with Si-yeol.
I'm the one who had your memories wiped.
[Woo-seok] I know that too.
I'm not upset about it.
I don't have the right to be.
It's true that I wanted Si-yeol's life,
even for just a moment.
[sighs softly]
Si-yeol, I don't know
if you'll believe me,
but I didn't intend for this to happen.
You know I'm not that kind of guy.
I just wanted to live like this
for a few days,
then give it all back to you.
[sighs] But I couldn't stop
thinking about my dad.
So I just started getting greedier.
Honestly, that's how it felt.
[Si-yeol] I know, man.
I'd be lying if I said
I wasn't a bit upset with you.
But thanks for being honest with me now.
-[Woo-seok] Let's switch back.
-[dark pensive music playing]
-What?
-Let's switch back now.
Didn't you say you found a way?
Back when you erased my memory.
-Ah… It's not possible right now.
-[Woo-seok] Why?
Why isn't it possible now?
Woo-seok.
No, it's just…
[raises voice]
It's because I don't trust myself.
If I spend another day or two like this,
I'll start thinking this is my life
and get even greedier.
That's what'll happen.
Can you take responsibility for that?
If I suddenly end up
back in my life overnight,
how am I supposed to handle that?
[breathes rapidly]
This is really quite rude, you know.
We came to visit a patient
completely empty-handed.
What?
Go buy something, Si-yeol.
Do you like fruit?
Go get a fruit basket or something.
-Now?
-[Eun-ho] Yes.
I hate humans
who are rude.
-[music fades]
-[exhales deeply]
You know it too, don't you?
That you're going to die soon.
[soft pensive music playing]
-How did you--
-[Eun-ho] Keep it a secret from Si-yeol.
He cares about you more than I thought.
It's more than you deserve.
So you better hide
that you have ulterior motives.
Don't let him catch you like I just did.
[laughs]
I still can't believe I'm even doing this,
but I want to protect him.
If he believes in something
as cheesy as friendship,
I want to keep it that way.
Then…
you want me to just die?
Without doing anything?
Instead of Si-yeol?
If you don't want that,
make a deal with me.
-A deal?
-[Eun-ho] Yes.
I don't have much time either.
Just like you.
So I need you to help me.
[sighs]
[music fades]
[perky music playing]
[in English] Nice!
[screen beeps]
[in Korean] By the way,
this isn't a restaurant, is it?
Ah…
Eating black bean noodles
at a pool hall is the best.
Haven't you tried it?
No.
We made a bet on this two-on-two match.
After I win, I'll treat you to noodles
and sweet and sour pork, the full spread.
[twinkling jingle]
Sounds good.
-Your turn.
-Okay!
[in English] Yes!
[in Korean] All right.
[laughs]
[indistinct chatter]
Damn.
I guess I picked a shot
that's way too hard.
-[chuckles softly]
-[music concludes]
Or… maybe not?
-[chuckles]
-[fox squealing softly]
[footsteps approaching]
Si-yeol.
Eun-ho.
Why are you out here?
Let's go.
Wait, what about the fruit basket?
Visiting hours are over. Let's just go.
But I went all the way
to the store to buy this.
We can't just leave.
Why not? Just get a refund.
Why did you even make me
go buy this anyway?
You kept the receipt, right?
I know they'll definitely refund you.
[quirky music playing]
What?
[Beom clicks tongue]
[screen beeps]
Beom, we're going to lose at this rate.
[Beom] Oh man, this is bad.
I'm totally broke until next month.
Jeong-bae's going to order
egg-battered fried meatballs.
He's got such expensive taste.
What do we do? I'm broke too.
[sighs]
[echoing warble]
-["Geum-ho"] Excuse me.
-[yelps]
Yes?
Can I give it a try?
Have you ever played pool before?
-No, never.
-[music concludes]
["Geum-ho"]
But I think I get how it works.
[pool balls clacking]
[wobbly whoosh]
What do we do? We're already losing.
[whimsical music playing]
[Beom] We can't make a comeback anyway.
She came all this way,
so let's just let her play.
Oh man.
-[music rises]
-[Beom chuckles]
You shouldn't hold it like that.
Here, do it like this. Right.
Hold it like this
and bend down a little.
Right, just like that.
-Good.
-Okay.
Can I hit it now?
Yeah, give it a shot.
-Here goes.
-[fox squealing]
[twinkling chime]
[music falls]
[music rises]
How is that angle even possible?
[screen beeps]
I can go again, right?
Sure. Go ahead.
[scoffs]
[giggles]
[screen beeps]
[Chi-su scoffs]
What the…
[chuckles softly]
Is she a pro or something?
No, she said it's her first time playing.
-[heartbeat thumping]
-She's so cool.
[Beom and Gyeong-hun laugh]
-[Beom] We won!
-[Gyeong-hun] We did it!
-[clapping]
-[music fades]
Is it heavy?
A little.
Think of it as a workout.
You like exercising.
[chuckles] You have
an answer for everything.
Hey, aren't you going
to team training today?
They called earlier
and said the practice is canceled.
The team's in a bad spot right now.
Coach said he'd find
a new sponsor somehow,
but I don't think it's working out.
Really?
Since we're on the topic,
you know our trip this weekend?
I don't think that's going to happen.
Why not?
Well, usually for away games,
we head there a day early,
stay the night,
play our match, and then come back.
But since the team's broke right now,
we'll have to leave at the crack of dawn
and come straight back after the game.
So if you come, you'll just be exhausted,
and we won't have time to hang out.
So basically, it's a money problem.
Yeah.
We're here.
OH SEASON GROCERY STORE
[Eun-ho] What the…
Of all places, why did it have to be here?
Do you know this place?
I told you yesterday.
They worked me to the bone all day,
then threw me out and into debt.
-This is that shady store.
-[downbeat quirky music playing]
What?
I couldn't believe it
when you told me yesterday.
Since when do you just let people
walk all over you?
What choice did I have?
They wouldn't pay me.
Eun-ho, don't worry.
I'll make sure you get paid for your work.
-[echoing squeak]
-Really?
[Si-yeol] Of course.
What kind of people are they?
Scamming you
because you don't know any better.
[wobbly clang]
Just wait right here.
[neck cracks]
[echoing hoot]
-I'd like to return this.
-Of course, sir.
And I'd like to speak to the manager.
[employee] Why do you want to speak…
Is there a problem, sir?
Well, yesterday…
[music falls]
Wait, Yeon-su?
Do I know you?
-Well…
-[echoing chirp]
[quirky music resumes]
[sighs] It feels pretty reassuring
to have Si-yeol stepping up.
Si-yeol!
Hey, Eun-ho.
[echoing plop]
Over there.
What's going on here?
[music concludes]
What's going on with you two?
Since when do you two know each other?
Turns out, she's an old friend
from way back.
-[echoing chime]
-I never dreamed I'd run into her here.
-An old friend?
-Yeah.
How did you recognize me right away?
It's been nine years.
-[echoing squeak]
-[Si-yeol] Of course I did.
You really helped me out back then.
-[quirky music playing]
-Me? Helping you out?
[whistling whoosh]
Si-yeol.
You said you'd fight for me. What is this?
She's the one who ripped me off.
I know that,
but I don't think I can help you.
[echoing chime]
What?
I told you, I know her well.
Oh, right.
We were just about to go grab lunch.
You're okay with that, right?
"We"?
Yeah, Yeon-su and…
Oh, there she is.
Yeon-su!
Hello.
Yeah, hi.
So, what should we eat?
[wobbly chime]
[arms patting]
-[Eun-ho clears throat]
-[music concludes]
NOBLE AROM BILLIARDS CLUB
[slurping]
[Beom and "Geum-ho"] Mm!
[quirky rendition of "In the Hall
of the Mountain King" playing]
-[echoing chime]
-["Geum-ho"] Mm!
[mumbling] This is so good!
[both chuckle]
You've got something right there.
["Geum-ho"] Do I?
[echoing plop]
Hey.
Try the egg-battered fried meatballs too.
[wobbly whoosh]
["Geum-ho"] Okay.
Thank you.
This is good too.
-[echoing plop]
-["Geum-ho" giggles]
You should try this too, Beom.
Oh, I have. [chuckles]
[fox squealing softly]
[Beom] Thank you.
[echoing baby crying]
[sighs]
What is with this vibe?
It's a total disaster.
-Uh…
-[wobbly clang]
[sighs]
[music concludes]
[quiet chatter]
Eat up, Yeon-su.
Yes, you too, Si-yeol.
Ah!
Oh, right.
Don't you prefer wheat rice cakes
over regular ones?
I can't tell if these are wheat rice cakes
or regular ones.
-[soft quirky music playing]
-How did you know what I like?
Oh, that.
I just figured you might.
[chuckles nervously]
This is definitely wheat.
[scoffs] I prefer rice cakes.
That's odd.
Were we that close?
Even my husband doesn't know
I prefer wheat rice cakes.
You're married?
Of course. I have two kids.
Anyway, Si-yeol,
you're still playing, right?
Is it okay for me to ask you that?
-Of course.
-[echoing boing]
I'm just getting by.
[Yeon-su] Back then, I really thought
you should've made
the youth national team.
I saw so much more potential in you.
[Si-yeol chuckles]
-Yeah, well.
-[wobbly squeal]
Things just turned out this way.
But why are you working at that store?
You're so talented.
[chuckles softly] Talented?
I'm just a middle-aged woman.
[Hye-rim] No way.
Yeon-su is super talented.
We get foreign customers at the store,
and she speaks French and German.
She even negotiates all our supply prices.
Sales doubled since she started working.
Hye-rim, please. You're making me blush.
[mutters]
When I was working my old job,
I thought I was the best at it.
But when I got married,
had kids, and quit,
it wasn't easy to go back to work
after raising my kids.
You know, a gap in my resume.
[sighs]
Then, Yeon-su,
could you help our team out?
[wobbly whoosh]
What?
Our team's in a bit of trouble,
so we need a new sponsor.
Could you help us with that?
It'd be a chance for you
to get back into this industry.
I think it'd be good for you.
You're the best
at scouting and negotiating.
-I am?
-[Si-yeol] Yes.
-[music concludes]
-[Yoon groans]
[Yoon groaning, grunting]
-Jeez.
-[groans]
-[heavy thud]
-[Secretary Choi grunts]
[wheels rattling]
Wait here.
[pants] Yes, sir.
[grunts]
[sighs]
[ominous music playing]
-[door opens]
-[door bell jingles]
[Yoon] Man.
Why did you drag me out at this hour?
[old man tutting, grumbling]
I wouldn't sell this
for all the gold in the world.
Cut the crap.
A merchant sells for the right price.
I'm saying this
because this thing is cursed.
It bewitches all, even spirits,
but it devours human life.
Hm?
However, you have no life left to devour.
-[snickers]
-[old man] Fine. Take it.
[ominous music continues]
What? Just hand it over?
Yeah.
You're acting like it's yours.
[grunts]
-[suitcase thuds]
-[Yoon groans]
[Yoon] Two billion won in cash, as agreed.
Count it if you want.
It's fine.
[objects clattering]
[old man muttering]
It's cursed, so open it outside.
Don't do it in here.
Sure.
[menacing rumbling whoosh]
[music builds]
-[music stops]
-Thanks for lunch.
Of course.
I'll treat you next time, Yeon-su.
I'll take you somewhere better.
[chuckles softly] Sure,
let's do that. How much?
There won't be a next time.
I'll pay, so make this
the last time you meet up.
Hey, wait.
You're paying?
With what money?
You gave me all the money
from the AC yesterday.
Did I not tell you?
We don't have to worry
about money anymore.
What?
-[cash register ringing]
-[quirky music playing]
[whistling whoosh]
[whispers] Hey!
What was that?
Can't you tell?
It's a no-limit credit card. A black card.
I mean, where did you get it?
I took it from Woo-seok.
What?
Excuse me, you left this.
That must be mine.
-Here you go.
-A black card. [giggles]
-[door keypad beeps]
-[quirky music continues]
[door lock chimes]
[Si-yeol]
Man, why didn't I think of that sooner?
[door keypad beeps]
-[Si-yeol sighs]
-[door lock chimes]
Woo-seok's money is basically my money.
With that card,
I'll never have to worry about money.
You two seemed very friendly.
Real sweet.
-What?
-[echoing boing]
[imitating Si-yeol] "Eun-ho, don't worry."
"I'll make sure
you get paid for your work."
Then what was it you said again?
[imitating Si-yeol] "Don't you prefer
wheat rice cakes over regular ones?"
"But why are you working at that store?
You're so talented."
Hey, I was working there yesterday too!
[Si-yeol sighs]
Eun-ho, it's not what you think.
She worked me to the bone all day,
stiffed me, and treated me like dirt.
How could you take her side
right in front of me?
-[chuckles softly]
-What was she again? An old friend?
Are you jealous right now?
Well, I prefer regular rice cakes!
-[music fades]
-Okay, I'm sorry.
Next time, let's get rice cakes.
Whatever.
How do you make me feel
this petty at my age?
-It's pathetic.
-[chuckles softly]
[sighs]
-I'm sorry.
-[tender music playing]
I made you so upset.
I'm not a child.
Coddling me won't make me feel better.
I really am sorry.
Okay?
I just ran into Yeon-su
when I least expected it,
so I was glad to see her
but also felt bad.
That's why I acted that way.
Okay?
Why did you feel bad?
Well,
before my fate was switched,
Yeon-su was actually my agent.
She was one of Forbes'
30 Most Influential Women.
She was very successful.
But now she's working a temp job
at a local grocery store.
She was an agent?
No wonder nothing I said worked on her.
Exactly.
There's a reason I gave up
on getting that money back.
You just can't win an argument with her.
Even top club chairmen
in the big leagues absolutely shudder
when they sit down
at the negotiating table with her.
So a woman that successful
had her career cut short
because I switched your fate?
[Si-yeol] Hm…
[clicks tongue]
I suppose so.
She started out
as a football association employee,
then met me and became an agent.
Anyway, it's kind of surprising.
She used to be too busy
to even meet anyone,
so she never got married.
But now she suddenly has two kids.
-[scoffs softly]
-[sighs]
Relationships often change
a person's fate.
Meeting the right person
at the right time.
[music concludes]
Nothing in life is
more important than that.
-[sighs deeply]
-[cell phone buzzing]
What?
[cell phone buzzing]
You're the only one who would call me.
[Si-yeol] Hm?
[cell phone buzzing]
That's my number.
Right, your phones
must've gotten mixed up.
-Hello?
-[Hye-rim] Ok-sun?
Where are you right now?
I'll come get the phone right away.
Oh, it's you, Hye-rim.
[car horns honking]
What's taking her so long?
-Wait a second.
-[mysterious music playing]
I feel like I've seen this guy somewhere.
[Si-yeol] What?
Oh yeah.
This guy looks kind of familiar.
You too?
[Hye-rim] Ok-sun!
[engine revving]
[tires screeching, echoing]
[Yoon] Damn, what do I do?
There's no one around, right?
Yes. I secretly took a company car out,
-and made a mistake--
-[Si-yeol] You're lying.
[music intensifies]
[Si-yeol] That man.
The driver from Geumsu Group.
What?
[Pagun] A human has died.
Because of you.
Because you twisted human fate recklessly,
someone who wasn't
supposed to die has died.
[tense dramatic music playing]
[Hye-rim] Ok-sun!
[Eun-ho] Who is this guy?
[Hye-rim] That's my family photo.
We took it a long time ago,
when Dad was still alive.
[chuckles]
-[exhales]
-[music fades]
[dolly cart rattling]
I asked around,
and they say
Hye-rim's nickname is Hermione.
Hermione?
-[gentle music playing]
-["Geum-ho"] I don't know what that means.
But apparently, she works
every part-time job around here,
so all the shop owners call her that.
They said it's like
she has 48 hours in a day.
[Eun-ho sighs]
Just working at the grocery store
was exhausting enough.
But she delivers milk in the morning,
works at a cafe before noon,
and then at the grocery store
in the afternoon?
That's not all.
[Gyeong-hun] Hey, not there! Come up!
[Beom] Damn.
I can't see!
-You died because you were there.
-[Beom] Oh man.
["Geum-ho"] She also works
at a nearby internet cafe on weekends.
[Eun-ho tutting]
If you work yourself to the bone now,
you'll pay for it later.
[sighs]
Why is she working herself to death?
I actually asked her about that.
[twinkling chime]
[twinkling whoosh]
My dad didn't deserve to die that way,
and my mom suffered
a breakdown from the shock.
So I'm the breadwinner of our family.
Medical bills keep piling up,
and I want to finish college.
So I need to save up money fast.
So, what are you going to do?
What do you think?
You said her life
got screwed up because of me.
Then I should make it right.
[breathes deeply]
[Hye-rim] A scholarship?
But do students on leave
even get scholarships?
[chuckles] Technically, no.
But through the newly established
Eunho Scholarship Foundation,
you were selected as the first recipient.
[laughing]
I never applied for that. So how am I…
You were chosen based on strict criteria,
so you don't need to worry about that.
You'll receive
full tuition until you graduate,
a monthly stipend of five million won,
plus an allowance
to study a language during break,
and full funding
to study abroad after graduation.
Why?
Because you were selected.
SAEGANG UNIVERSITY
[sobbing] Thank you so much.
-[music concludes]
-[Hye-rim] Thank you.
You think she's doing a good job
with the scholarship thing?
Of course. It's not like it's hard.
Fixing everything at once
would be too overwhelming,
so we'll just do this much for now.
Next month, we'll fix up her house
and pay her mom's hospital bills.
I think we should.
[Si-yeol] Yeah.
If he were alive, I'm sure
he'd want to do that for his daughter.
By the way,
my grandma was so happy yesterday.
-[tender music playing]
-Oh, that. [chuckles]
We've got money now,
so I figured I'd spend some.
We always went empty-handed before.
Everyone at the nursing home thinks
I married into a billionaire family.
You gave gifts to everyone
at the nursing home
and prepared all kinds of food.
My grandma became a celebrity there.
[chuckles]
Generosity comes from a full stomach.
You've got to grease the wheels a bit,
so even if she loses at cards,
she'll still get some money back.
This is just one of those life lessons.
Thank you.
I hadn't even thought about that.
[chuckles softly]
Technically, it's all your money anyway.
[clears throat]
If she was that happy,
we can go again tomorrow.
[chuckles]
I can't tomorrow.
I have an away game.
Right.
I'll be back really quick,
so just wait a bit.
What do you mean? We're going together.
We agreed to travel after the game.
What? That was--
Wasn't it because the team was broke
that you were going early in the morning
and coming back straight after the game?
But we have plenty of money now.
Let's go on a trip.
-We got a black card.
-[cash register ringing]
[chuckles]
-[chuckles]
-[music concludes]
[team members chattering]
What is this?
It's a bus. I chartered it.
[wobbly boing]
Coach, she's from overseas.
She forgets to use honorifics.
-[chuckles]
-[quirky music playing]
Anyway, since the away game is tomorrow,
wouldn't it be better
if we all head down there now?
[echoing twang]
[wobbly warble]
I guess that's true,
but we don't have a place
for all of us to sleep.
I took care of that too, so don't worry.
[wobbly boing]
Oh, and this.
What's this?
We owe you from last time.
Reimbursement for the towing fee.
-[cash registers ringing]
-[Gyeong-hun gasps]
[wobbly clang]
But why are you giving me so much?
I added some generous interest.
Anyway, why are you all
just standing there?
Aren't we going?
I'm not sure what to do.
[music concludes]
[cell phone buzzing]
Yes? [clears throat]
[smacks lips]
[shouting] What did you say?
[inhales sharply]
Yes, okay!
Sir, can you please… pull over?
Hurry!
[brakes squeal, hiss]
Hey, Coach!
Where are you going?
Right, Si-yeol.
Something urgent came up.
I have to go somewhere,
so you guys head down first.
Then what about tomorrow's game?
Well, the game…
I'll handle my business
and head there at dawn or something.
-Just go.
-But…
[Yong-gil] Hey, taxi! Taxi!
But…
Take charge, all right?
Wait.
What the heck?
[sighs]
[Yeon-su] I called the coach,
and he's on his way.
-Really? That's good.
-[tense music playing]
[chuckles softly]
[exhales deeply]
[hesitates]
If you don't mind,
can I ask you something?
Sure, go ahead.
I admit we were looking
everywhere for sponsors,
but I never expected a huge company
like yours to step up.
Why would a huge conglomerate
like Geumsu Group
suddenly decide to sponsor
a fourth-division soccer team?
Ah… Well…
Because it interests me.
In more ways than one.
[tense music continues]
[sighs]
Looks like no one's here today.
[sniffing]
It seems like
they're traveling pretty far.
I'll stop by home, then go follow them.
[chuckles softly]
[twinkling chime]
[tense music continues]
[music fades]
Excuse me, who are you?
I didn't expect to find
another one hiding in a place like this.
[mysterious music playing]
[bell tinkling]
What is that?
This is called a vajra bell.
[music turns tense]
It channels divine energy,
so it's not meant to be used by humans.
But as you see, I've devoured
countless minor spirits and deities.
[faint eerie wailing]
[Do-cheol] So, I thought
I might try bewitching you with this.
[bell clangs, echoes]
[blood drips]
-[retches]
-[blood gushes]
[spirits gagging, coughing]
[bell clangs, echoes]
[music fades]
[Eun-ho] So I'm not making
that damn choice.
I'll just stay by his side
and protect him forever.
[foreboding music playing]
If the fate of a single human
is but a passing breeze,
then a human life is like a raging storm.
Even if you twist a single strand of fate,
once the storm rises,
everyone gets swept away.
Events you can neither predict nor stop
will come crashing down.
Can you truly handle that for a lifetime?
[music intensifies]
[thunder rumbling]
[thunder crashing]
[warbling chime]
So this is how it ends.
[thunder crashing]
[gasps]
[panting]
Eun-ho.
Are you okay?
[music fades]
[sentimental pop song playing]
[sentimental pop song continues]
[sniffles, sobs]
SPECIAL APPEARANCE BY HONG SU-HYEON
[sentimental pop song continues]
[fox squealing]
NO TAIL TO TELL
[Eun-ho] Should we just stay like this
and not go back?
[Si-yeol] If you try your best
to change things back and still can't,
I'll just accept it.
[Do-cheol] I bewitched the Seoraksan
Mountain fox, just as planned.
[Yoon] I heard you're
just an ordinary human now.
I'm going to start by targeting
the people around you.
-["Geum-ho"] Eun-ho!
-[Eun-ho] Geum-ho?
You know the thing I left with you?
My fox bead.
Where is it?
[sentimental pop song continues]
Subtitle translation by Susanna Kim