Thank you for
saving me earlier.
I think
I can take it from here.
I’ll go ahead.
Happy birthday,
happy birthday…
Happy birthday to you!
Wow!
We’re getting married
in a few months.
Congratulations!
The guy you were with
in Japan is a hot topic.
He’s Fly Asia’s CEO.
Did you bring a companion?
To watch you?
Do you have a boyfriend?
It’s just me.
My card holder is missing.
All my credit cards
are in there.
Have you seen a card holder?
Oh my god.
Let me know.
Yoga.
I miss yoga.
What the hell.
This is so embarrassing.
Me too. I miss y—
Yoga. I miss yoga too.
He’s clearly teasing me.
Really? Then we should
do yoga next time.
Wait.
This feels off.
Why the hell am I even
inviting him to do yoga?
Cy: Sure. Let me know
when you’re free.
Huh? He agreed? Weird.
Anyway…
Sam: Wait, going back
to the sweater.
Where can I meet you tomorrow?
Cy: I’ll be in
an outreach program.
We can meet there
if that’s okay with you.
Outreach program?
Am I really gonna go
all the way there
just to return his sweater?
But I guess it’s fine.
Sam: Sure, I can go.
Is 11 AM good?
Cy: Yes. I’ll send you
the address. See you.
Sam: See you!
Hey, that girl’s so pretty!
Wait, she looks familiar!
She’s the one from that Juicy
Cologne commercial, right?
Am I in the right place?
Hey. I’m already here
at the location.
I think I arrived too early.
What if he thinks
I’m too eager to see him?
But no rush!
I just had to make a stop nearby,
that’s why I came early.
Maybe he’s busy.
- Miss! Help me!
- John Eldin!
- She’s gonna give me to the doctors.
Mom, you said we were
just buying fish sauce
at the corner store.
My teacher said liars
go to hell. You’ll burn!
John Eldin, I swear!
You’re just like your father.
- Hurry up and get circumcised already.
- I don’t want to.
- I said get circumcised!
- No!
Let’s go! Oh!
Sorry, miss! I’m sorry.
- Come on now.
- No! I don’t want to!
John Eldin!
This is embarrassing.
Let’s go!
Please move here.
John Eldin, right?
It’s John Eldin De Guzman,
not Wright.
Ah...
Okay then, just John Eldin.
John Eldin, I don’t think
your mom meant to lie to you.
You should listen to her.
This is for your health.
So when you grow up, you’ll be
stronger and healthier.
But my classmate said it hurts.
I’m scared.
It’s okay to be afraid.
Everyone’s afraid of pain.
But you know,
I actually know the doctor who’s
going to do your circumcision.
He’s really skilled!
Yeah, right. You’re joking.
Hey!
It’s true! He won’t let anything
happen to you. I promise!
So, are you going
through with it?
Okay, since you said
he’s really good at it.
Mhm!
John Eldin De Guzman?
That’s you? Okay. Hi!
I’m Doc Clyden,
the super skilled doctor
who’s gonna do
your circumcision.
Shit, he heard that!
Let’s go?
Okay. Go, son!
- Let’s go.
- Go!
Thank you, Doc.
Be careful.
Is the doctor your boyfriend?
Your boyfriend?
- Huh?
- Your boyfriend?
All done, ma’am.
He’s back. Yay.
Well, does it hurt?
Nope. It just felt like
a dinosaur bit me.
You and your nonsense.
- Thank you, Doc.
- You're welcome.
Miss, thank you.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
Your doctor is really good.
Gosh, his eyes are so puffy.
Did he cry a lot inside?
Yeah, he did.
I was just prepping
the injection,
and he was already freaking out.
Hey, are you free?
Do you wanna have some lunch?
Uh...
I guess I’ve got time
for a quick lunch.
Okay, let’s go.
Sorry I brought you here.
It’s just that I have
to head back right after.
It’s okay. No worries.
The adobo here’s really good.
Too bad though.
You’re all dressed up.
What?
No, I dressed like this
because I have a meeting later.
Not because
I’m meeting up with you—
Just kidding.
- And now, he’s teasing me!
- By the way,
I watched your fashion show.
Congratulations.
- Really?
- Yeah.
You were amazing.
You really stood out.
Thanks, Cy.
I didn’t know
you actually watched it.
You know, I watched
your stories and—
Shit!
And...
I saw that you were
at the hospital.
Yeah. You know, I usually
watch everyone's stories.
Yeah, I was on duty that time.
But I just recorded the stream,
so I could still watch it later.
No rice?
Your fashion show’s done.
Are you still on a diet?
Wait.
There’s something on your—
You look like a hamster.
I always have to be
mindful of my figure.
You know, my manager’s
pretty strict about me
keeping my body fit.
To be honest,
eating this Adobo right now
feels like a cheat day.
It’s just that I get
full a lot quicker now.
You get full quickly?
But didn’t you use to always
finish everything I cooked?
Why the hell is he
bringing up the past?
My appetite’s just smaller
than it used to be.
That’s okay, as long as you’re
getting rest and eating well.
Samantha Vera?
Oh my god, can I get a picture?
Sure.
You’re one of my idols.
- Miss—
- Thank you so much!
- can we take a photo too?
- Yeah, sure.
Okay.
You’re so pretty in person.
I always watch your shows.
- You’re our idol.
- Thank you!
Can we take one more?
Oh.
Sam, don’t you have
a meeting? Let’s go.
- I’ll carry this.
- Thank you.
Sorry about that.
I kind of ruined our meal.
No, it’s okay.
I actually need
to head back too.
But I’m free next weekend.
Didn’t you say we’d do yoga?
Because we both miss it.
What the—
He actually
took that seriously?
Okay. I’m also free
next weekend.
Should we just
meet at my condo?
So it’s more private?
If that’s okay with you.
Yeah, sure. That works.
Okay.
Before I forget…
You can keep it.
What?
Then why did you
agree to meet me?
Isn’t it obvious?
I wanted to see you.
See you next week, Maui.
Take care.
Great job guys, at the meeting
earlier with Veluxe Apparel.
I mean, I’m surprised
they’re willing to adjust
and meet all our requests
for the shoot.
And it’s obvious.
They’re really eager
to work with you, Sam.
They wanna do the shoot
as soon as possible,
so we might need to adjust
our schedule next month.
He agreed to meet me just
because he wanted to see me?
What does that even mean?
And I actually invited him
to my condo?
And he said yes?
Oh my god.
What the hell are we doing...
Sam?
Uh... Yeah.
I feel like they really
are eager to work with us.
What are you saying?
I’m asking if you have
any leave requests next month.
Oh my god.
What? What happened?
You and Haze are trending.
Let me see.
Your photos during the
fashion show are circulating.
They think Haze is
your non-showbiz boyfriend.
I need to talk
to Haze about this.
I think Haze isn’t the only one
you need to talk to.
Sam, who did you have a lunch
date with a while ago?
You even ate at a local eatery.
- What?
- Whoever it is,
he’s also trending.
Oh my god. He’s—
He’s just a friend.
What should I do, Arah?
What if they invade his privacy too?
It might be better
if we just don’t respond
to anything about Haze.
It still seems like people think
Haze is your boyfriend anyway.
Okay.
Okay. I think that’s better.
After all, Haze is more used
to being in the public eye.
I’ll just talk to him.
As long as Cy doesn’t
get dragged into this.
So...
Who is this Cy?
And why are you
so protective of him?
Arah, I told you,
he’s just a friend.
Hey Sam.
You and I are
trending right now.
I know. Don’t talk about it.
Just avoid them.
Are you using me
as a cover-up?
Because I feel like I saw
another photo of some guy.
Uh...
I’ll also use you, then.
Huh? What do you need me for?
My desires.
What the hell?
Just kidding.
Being linked with you
will make my mom shut up
about wanting me
to get married already.
So,
let’s use each other
wisely, Samantha Vera.
Fine.
It’s a deal.
- Hey.
- Hi! Come in.
You can put your things there.
Okay.
This is the portrait Naomi
took years ago, right?
It is.
I’m kinda hungry.
Should we eat first?
Yeah, sure.
I brought some food too.
Okay.
Here you go.
Wow!
Sushi.
[sighs] There goes my
no-rice diet again.
Come on, it’s just
once in a while.
And I remembered
it’s your favorite too.
Of course. He used to make
those for me before.
Sushi?
Your special request.
This is my favorite.
Why is it so awkward?
Maui?
Hmm?
How do you date
when you’re a model?
There you go.
Finally, you looked at me.
I’d prefer it if you would
look at me instead.
So?
How?
My friends do it normally since
there’s nothing
to be ashamed of.
It’s just kind of hard
when the guy isn’t from showbiz
because the media
really messes with them.
I’m not asking
about your friends.
I’m asking about you.
I don’t date.
I’m way too busy for that.
Maybe when I retire, and...
I can finally give
quality time to my partner…
Hmm...
Okay.
I want to date normally,
you know.
Go shopping, go on a picnic
date, travel together.
All the normal
things couples do.
Well, that requires
a lot of time.
Yeah.
My love language
is quality time.
So, do you have plans
to retire from modeling?
Eventually.
That’s still a long way off,
but I’m already thinking
of starting my own business.
I want to open a club,
since I’m so good at drinking.
Well, you should.
That would be great.
You think so?
Of course.
Anything you do is beautiful.
And I’m proud of you
since you're...
starting to plan
your own future, and...
you decide what you want to do.
Thank you.
You?
Your turn to share.
What are your plans?
Well…
Finish residency,
take the exam,
then move on to fellowship.
And then I’m thinking
of pediatric cardiology?
I don’t know.
I’m sure whatever you choose,
you’ll do great
like you always do.
- Eat.
- Okay.
Now,
let’s do the downward
dog position.
We’re going down—
Exhale as you go up.
I can’t believe we’re
doing yoga right now.
I mean, this is the
reason why he came.
But I didn’t expect him
to be serious about it.
He even brought
a yoga outfit.
What?
Nothing. I was just copying you.
It would be more accurate
if you copied Max instead.
[sighs]
Now I’m even more conscious.
I want you to relax…
Inhale going down.
Exhale.
Relax.
What now?
Nothing!
Max, can you check
if my form is right?
Exhale going up…
Up.
And walk forward until
you reach a triangle.
What?
It’s kinda hot, right?
I think my AC needs
some cleaning.
Reach for the heavens.
Exhale.
Reach for the skies.
Maybe you feel hot
because you’re hot.
I’m what?
Hot.
Other side.
Down
Exhale.
All right!
That’s it
for our first session.
I think I’m gonna go.
- Okay, thank you.
- Thank you, Max.
I’ll just get the door.
I’ll just get my bag.
Special delivery!
Shit, I forgot.
Avi’s staying
with me tonight!
And of all people,
it had to be Haze
who dropped her off!
You okay?
Do you have a visitor?
Maui, is that the delivery,
the deli—
What are you guys doing?
Yoga.
I see.
- Cy, he’s—
- Lim.
Wow.
You’re the guy I’ve heard about.
Long time no see, Cy.
They know each other?
Interesting.
Can I join your yoga session?
It sounds fun.
- Auntie?
- Hmm?
Are you going to sleep now?
I think you should
join your friends outside.
I’m okay here alone
and I’m sleepy.
I’m kinda sleepy too, baby.
I’ll lie down for a while.
- Okay.
- Good night.
Haze and Cy,
together in my house?
How did we end up here?
What if Haze tells Cy
that we’re in a relationship?
After all, we agreed
to “use” each other.
Shit, no. I don’t want that!
Hey—
Have you known
Max for a long time?
You two seemed
really close earlier.
I knew it.
You’re jealous.
But don’t worry,
because he’s gay.
Exhale going up…
Up.
Sam,
I grabbed some beers
from your fridge.
I’ll just replace them later.
I tried to stop him.
Well, since the instructor
already left,
I was asking Cy to
show some yoga poses,
but he didn’t want to so—
How do you guys know each other?
We went to the same high school.
He was my junior.
I think
I made fun of him a lot
because he was a quiet kid.
Really, Lim?
Or were you just
so noisy back then?
Here, Cy.
Here.
Don’t tell me you can’t
handle your liquor?
I’ll go to the bathroom.
- Excuse me.
- Okay.
Hey, stop teasing him.
You’re acting like a kid.
You didn’t even mention
that he’s the ex boyfriend
that you’re busy falling for.
You didn’t ask.
And I didn’t know
you two knew each other.
Geez...
Stop it, okay?
- Hey, what are you doing?
- Shh...
I’m actually helping you here.
What?
I can drink.
Can he really drink or
is he just forcing himself?
Who is it?
I invited someone.
What?
Hey.
So,
Cy invited you?
Unfortunately.
Can I read while drinking?
Is that allowed here?
Hey, loosen up, KJ.
Gotta keep the mind sharp.
Mamma mia.
This night is getting
weirder and weirder.
So...
Cy, do you have a girlfriend?
Not looking for one.
Sucks to be single, huh?
Watch your words, man.
[laughing]
Someone’s hurt.
I thought you’re with Giselle?
I thought so too.
I guess we’re done.
I mean, It wasn’t anything
serious anyway. So—
Is it really a thing now?
You know, getting together
with your friend’s exes?
I guess it is.
Right?
Huh?
Why?
Bro, the justice system
is already messed up, right?
It’s like playing
survival mode out there.
- Right?
- It’s so unfair, man.
It doesn’t matter
how hard we try.
Yeah, screw that.
It’s just a hard field.
Sometimes I just wish
we had a nine to five.
Like do you realize
how hard it is for us
that every time we walk
into that office,
we’re holding someone's
future in our hands.
You’re right about that, bro.
Screw this shit! Like,
what kind of
responsibility is that?
I’m not even paid
enough for this.
Bro, and do you know
what hurts the most?
The poor don’t even
have a choice.
Shit. Only the rich
get to have a choice.
Whether it’s in healthcare
or in justice.
Right? It’s so frustrating, bro.
No matter how much I sponsor
or how much money I give,
it’s just never enough.
That’s the point.
It’s never gonna be enough.
It doesn’t matter what we do,
It’s never just gonna be enough.
- Screw the system, man.
- Yeah, screw the system.
- Screw the system.
- Okay, workaholics.
That’s why you two are single.
- What the hell?
- And you’re not?
Why do you have to put that in?
We’re not even
talking about that.
Insensitive bitch.
Why? Are you throwing
shade at someone?
- This guy’s drunk.
- Right?
Why are you saying—
Yes, I know we broke up.
- No.
- Yeah. I—
I don’t know, bro.
I don’t know what the hell
I did wrong.
What the hell!
This guy is drunk.
I should bring him home.
- No.
- Bro! Seriously! I gave everything.
- Right?
- Let’s go, let’s go.
Shit! This is the whole
country’s problem now!
- Screw the system, bro.
- Screw the system!
- Screw the rich and all that love shit.
- Screw the sys—
What, screw love?
No, love is good.
- It’s not!
- It’s—
I was right there.
- I was right there.
- That’s enough.
- Believing it that it was good-
- All right, all right.
that it was gonna
give you the damn—
- That’s enough! That’s enough.
- Okay!
That it’s gonna
give you the...
- All right, bro. Let’s go.
- passion for it, but it’s not!
- Enough.
- It’s gonna kill you inside,
- I’m telling you.
- No, I’m not!
Stop! Okay.
You’re leaving? You’re leaving.
No, I’m leaving too.
- No, stay there.
- Yeah. No.
No, you stay there.
- Come, I’m gonna save you.
- Kalix.
- Later, bro.
- Come on.
Stay there. Okay.
Get up, get up.
They’re all kind
at the beginning!
Okay, Haze— Kalix’s unit
is on the 23rd floor.
No, stop.
- Screw that, man!
- Okay.
- Be careful.
- Don’t touch me.
I’m not touching you.
- Wait.
- Enjoy the rest of the night, Sam!
Yeah. Your book.
Haze, 23rd floor.
- All right.
- Kalix, sleep okay?
Attorney.
Haze, don’t forget
to close the door.
Have fun, lovebirds!
Close it!
Cy?
Cy, wake up.
Summer?
What?
Shit. You’re so heavy.
One, two!
Fudge.
Wait.
Okay.
So heavy.
I’m sorry.
Get in that justice system.
- The what?
- Justice system.
What the hell?
- It’s messed up.
- What?
It’s messed up.
You’re drunk.
Hey, are you okay?
Do you want water?
Sam?
Hmm?
Am I stupid to you?
You probably think
that I’m a fool.
Is it fun?
Are you having fun?
Hey, I don’t understand.
What are you talking about?
Are you still drunk?
You know,
I am willing to accept
everything that comes with you,
but you’re becoming
harder to reach.
Everything’s gotten
so complicated.
No matter what I do,
I couldn’t be enough for you.
You still prefer someone else
because they have
more time for you.
Cy, it’s not like that.
I was probably
exhausting to be with.
That’s why you broke up with me.
I’m sorry for everything,
Maureen.
I got so busy chasing my dream
that I forgot
to show up for you.
I couldn’t even
celebrate your achievements.
I’m sorry if you felt that
you couldn’t rely on me.
Cy, that’s not true.
We broke up
because I needed
to focus on myself.
I relied on you a lot, Cy.
And you gave me
a lot of motivation.
It’s just that,
during that time,
we were both busy.
And I understood.
But during the worst time
of your life, Maui,
you didn’t rely on me.
When Naomi died, you didn’t
even reach out to me.
I thought—
I thought you were on duty.
Maui,
I was willing to drop everything
that day just to be with you.
Damn it, I was willing
to drop everything
just to be with you back then.
I even begged my parents
to not cancel the engagement.
We have to cancel
the engagement with Samantha.
We shouldn’t be
associating with the Veras.
No, I won’t cancel
the engagement.
We’re getting married!
Son, we’re in the medical field.
How can people trust us if
we’re involved with a politician
- like Stephen Vera?
- Mom!
Then you shouldn’t have arranged
our marriage in the first place!
Jesus!
Clyden!
You have to break up
with Samantha.
Or you don’t deserve
to inherit the hospital.
You don’t even care about
the future of our business!
- You are disappointing!
- Disappointing?
Because for once I didn’t follow
what you wanted to happen?
So, now what?
I’m no longer the ideal son?
Right.
You never really treated me
like your son anyway, did you?
I’m just one of your movable objects
that you can show off to anyone.
What did that girl do to you?
I can’t even
recognize you anymore!
I’m warning you, Clyden.
If you don’t break up
with Samantha,
you will lose everything.
Don’t disappoint me!
- My dear…
- Mom…
I know you love Sam
but choosing her as a wife
won’t be an easy task.
Especially now that their family
is involved in so many issues.
Are you really willing to
give up everything for Sam?
Even your dreams?
Thank you.
Out of all my students,
you’re the one with
the most potential, Dr. Ramirez.
Thank you, Dr. Tolentino.
Tonight, I have
a complicated surgery.
If you want, you can observe,
but you’ll have to do overtime.
It’s a big opportunity for you.
Doc! Wait a moment, please.
Here, doc. You left it
earlier at the lounge.
- Thank you.
- Take care, Doc. Thank you.
Are you willing to
give up everything for Sam?
Even your dreams?
Doc, thank you
for this opportunity but—
I can’t tonight.
Believe me, Doc,
I’m really grateful,
but...
I just have something
I need to take care of.
If it’s more important,
then I understand.
Auntie?
Clyden?
Hi, is Sam with you?
She’s not answering her phone.
We’re not together.
Why? Did something happen?
I have no idea
what’s going on with her.
She won’t even talk to us and
she won’t let us go to the wake.
Wake? What do you mean wake?
Oh my god. You didn’t know?
Naomi committed
suicide last night.
It was such a big mess.
Naomi…
I felt so useless.
I felt so hurt because
you didn’t reach out to me.
Maui, if you only knew.
I was willing to throw
everything away.
And that’s why
I couldn’t call you—
because I knew you were capable
of leaving it all behind.
And I didn’t want that for you.
I didn’t want you
to ruin your future.
The relationship
felt one-sided, Sam.
You’re always the one
making adjustments for us,
so why won’t you let me
do the same for you?
You always say you understand.
But right now,
please tell me
what’s on your mind!
Fine.
Screw you.
Screw all of you.
I felt so alone and left out.
I’m always there for everyone,
but I’m always alone
when I’m at my lowest.
And yes, the thing is,
I also like pushing
people away—
Because if they leave me,
then it’s my fault and
I have no one else to blame.
I always say I understand
because the blame is on me.
I don’t like asking
people for help
because I don’t want
to be disappointed
if they don’t show up.
So I just learned how
to take care of myself, Cy.
And I’m sorry if
I made you feel useless.
I’m sorry for not giving you
the chance to take care of me.
I’m sorry
for making you think that
the relationship was one-sided.
It’s my fault.
It’s all my fault.
I’m the one who’s useless.
God, I couldn’t even save Naomi.
Maui, I’m sorry.
I’m sorry I wasn’t
there for you.
I’m sorry I let you go.
I should’ve never
left you back then.
I’m sorry if
I couldn’t give you time.
I’m leaving for New York.
Okay.
Let’s just make the most of the
time while you’re still here.
You’re not going to stop me?
How could I?
You promised yourself, remember?
That you’re gonna
live for yourself.
And I want to
support you on that.
Come here.
I’m sorry.
Wow.
He looks more mature now,
but he looks even
more handsome.
It makes me happy
seeing him asleep
so peacefully like this.
Shit.
- Yanna!
- Why did you take so long to answer?
You’re probably hiding
a guy in here, aren’t you?
Is Avi awake already?
Yanna, wait!
Damn. There really is a guy!
You might wake him up!
Shit, what’s he doing here?
Is he still breathing?
What the hell, Yanna!
Mommy!
Baby, hi!
We’re going home.
Your daddy is waiting
at the parking lot. Okay?
- Okay.
- Go get your bag.
Go…
He’s handsome.
Hiro’s waiting. You should go.
Time to leave.
- All right. Baby—
- Wow, you’re really in a rush.
Why, are you
planning something?
Oh wait, something
already happened, huh?
- I thought so.
- No!
- And nothing happened, okay?
- What?
You really—
Baby?
Your daughter’s taking too long.
Baby!
Let’s go, baby.
Mommy.
- Say bye now.
- Bye, Auntie!
Give me a hug!
I’ll see you soon!
Enjoy.
Bye!
Oh! You’re awake!
Was that Avi?
Yeah.
Her mom picked her up.
You know,
at first I thought
she was your daughter.
What?
How could you say that?
She’s already five.
You saw it
in the records, right?
And we were still together
when she was born.
I thought you cheated on me.
Why didn’t you just ask me
instead of jumping
to conclusions?
Because I was scared
that it might be true.
Well, I’m glad everything
is clear to you now.
Avi’s mom is Yanna,
my best friend.
And her dad is Hiro,
Haze’s brother.
Don’t you like him?
Haze, I mean.
We’re just friends, Cy.
I admit, I’m comfortable
with him, but...
I see him as nothing
more than just a friend.
And you’re not
giving him a chance?
No.
He’s been with other women too.
Why are you even asking?
Are you giving me away?
Never.
Good,
because I’d be mad if you did.
Sam?
Have you ever actually
been mad at me?
No.
But I admit you hurt me a lot.
Even then, I couldn’t bring
myself to be mad at you.
I used to think
you just had a lot on your mind
and were too busy to notice
you were slipping away—
that our relationship
had been on the rocks
for quite some time.
As for me,
I was too understanding
to bring up any
of the issues I had.
And that’s exactly
what the problem was, Sam.
You couldn’t tell me
what was really on your mind.
I wish you could
open up to me more.
I want to open up to you more.
To be honest,
I’ve been so lonely.
My career’s doing fine,
but I’ve been
living in the dark.
Up to now,
I’m still angry at my parents,
and I miss Naomi so much.
I know.
Losing her was the hardest
thing that happened to me.
Even now, I still remember her.
Sometimes,
I see her in the audience
while I walk on shows.
But I have no one
to talk to, you know?
So sometimes,
I just wish I could
lean on someone.
Hey,
you can hold on to me.
Even if you let go
of me again in the end.
Just hold on to me right now,
I don’t care what happens after.
That’s a selfless
thing to do, Cy.
You should know that, right?
Can you spend your
next free day with me?
I want to see the dogs.
Sure.
They miss their mom too.
Why did you still kiss me?
What does it mean?
Because I still have
feelings for you, Sam.
Can you cuddle with me?
Because your behind
is brushing on my—
front.
In love or dating?
I’m just happy.
Hi, Avi.
Oh, hi.
Daddy said you only
kiss people you like.
Do you like Auntie?
You said we're going
somewhere fun.
I’m free for
the rest of the day.
Can Uncle join you guys?
You don’t get it.
We will have fun with—
Why? Can’t you have fun with me?
Samantha Vera?
Oh my god. It really
is Samantha Vera!
- Can we get a photo with you?
- It really is her!
- Can we get a photo?
- Are you together?