NO TAIL TO TELL
What the…
There's nothing in the bag.
You've been digging up this whole mountain
for three months straight.
Who… are you?
Where is Hanyang?
- What?
- I need to get to Hanyang today.
So, tell me. Which way is it?
Hanyang is that way.
Oh, that way?
But it'll take at least 20 days
to get there.
What?
Oh, I almost forgot.
Dig that up
and brew it carefully for half a day.
It will help with your mother's illness.
What?
This is an ancient tale.
I found it!
It is the story of a nine-tailed fox
who wished to become human,
spending her days cultivating virtue
on Myohyangsan Mountain.
Can you leave us for a moment?
Chun-sim stays.
Chun-sim.
That's you!
What did you do with Chun-sim?
Pardon?
What do you…
Look.
It's so obvious.
You seemed completely human,
yet your cunning is all fox.
How did you know?
Your scent.
I smell the earth on you.
The scent of Myohyangsan Mountain's soil
that I've known for centuries.
Have you been well?
I was just bored without you around.
By the way, don't worry about Chun-sim.
I bet she's dozing off in the kitchen.
All right.
How do you feel?
It's your long-awaited wedding day.
It still doesn't feel real
that I've become human
and will be wed to my beloved.
Goodness.
Fine, leave me behind
and go live a happy life.
Come here, Eun-ho.
Let me hug you. It's been a while.
Geum-ho…
This is usually where old tales end.
She finally became human
and married the one she loved.
And so, they lived happily ever after.
The end.
Get over here!
Wow, amazing.
Look at this.
These hairpins must be new.
Oh my gosh, they're so pretty!
Don't they look good on me?
- Geum-ho?
- Yes?
What's got you staring like that?
Well, look at you.
What?
So that's why
you wanted to come to the market.
You had an ulterior motive.
It's not like that.
If you're done looking, let's go.
My lady!
So we meet again.
Yes, my lord.
What a coincidence running into you.
Be happy, Geum-ho.
But I didn't know then…
That way!
…that human life is endlessly fragile,
and their happiness
shatters far too easily.
That life is hard,
and death is always near.
That was the future that awaited.
So in the end,
Geum-ho would not find happiness.
All because she loved a human
and chose to become one.
PRESENT DAY
And so, I became who I am today.
A nine-tailed fox
who refuses to love humans
and does not seek to become one.
That's who I am.
Why should I want to become a human?
So trivial, powerless, aging, sickly,
and in the end, doomed to die.
Here and now,
one life ends…
and another begins.
And this story began nine years ago.
EPISODE 1
AN INEVITABLE EVENT
Here! Over here!
SOSIN HIGH SCHOOL
HYEON WOO-SEOK
Pass! Over there!
Cover! I'm coming through!
NINE YEARS AGO
That's it!
He's good, isn't he?
That's Hyeon Woo-seok.
He just became a high school senior.
Since he was first selected
for the U-13 national team,
he has been the starting striker
across all youth squads.
Hey, Woo-seok! Pass!
- Pass!
- Cover this side!
Hey! You crazy idiot!
Woo-seok was open!
Stop messing around
and just pass the ball!
He's asking who that player is.
Which one?
- That one.
- Hey!
- Hey, that's a foul!
- The one messing around earlier.
That's Kang Si-yeol.
Gosh, that kid is just crazy.
He's all flash and no substance.
And he never passes.
He tries to do everything himself.
Hey, Si-yeol, you brat! Just tap it in!
Stop showing off!
Damn, that little…
Woo-seok, nice assist.
Assist.
You think what a coach says is a joke?
I told you to pass to Woo-seok
whenever you get the ball.
The new youth national team coach
came to watch Woo-seok play today.
The least you could do
is help your friend,
not get in his way.
How is me scoring a goal
getting in Woo-seok's way?
So why did you have to score a goal?
I told you to play defense today.
When did I tell you to score a goal?
You got carried away trying to stand out.
Straighten up.
You've never even paid
your club fees on time,
and you give me this attitude.
Good work.
- Hey, boys.
- Eat up.
Woo-seok's father is treating us,
so make sure you thank him
before digging in.
Gosh, Coach. There's really no need.
- Here, have some more.
- Hey, Kang Si-yeol.
LET'S GO, SOSIN SOCCER CLUB!
Dad, hold on.
- Sure.
- Hold this.
- Kang Si-yeol.
- It's fine. I don't want any.
Coach.
Yes, good to see you.
- Great game today.
- Not at all.
Here, use this to take the boys out
for a nice dinner next time.
Thank you as always, Mr. Hyeon.
- Thank you.
- It's nothing.
The contractor for Bannam Zone 2,
Korea's biggest redevelopment project,
will be named today.
With three top-tier construction companies
competing for the contract,
experts say Geumsu Construction,
embroiled in a power abuse scandal,
is unlikely to win, leaving the other two
as front-runners.
In other news--
Why did you turn it off?
I was listening to it.
I'm sorry, Mr. Lee.
Should I turn it back on?
The real issue isn't abuse of power.
It's subordinates getting out of line.
I pay you to drive,
so why aren't you focused on driving?
Mr. Lee, it's not that--
Are your ears perking up
because they're trashing me on the radio?
No, sir.
That's not it at all.
It's a red light.
What the heck?
Watch where you're going!
2016 SEOUL
BANNAM ZONE 2 PROJECT PLAN
It fell. What bad luck.
WELCOME TO THE CONTRACTOR SELECTION
GENERAL MEETING
Did you drive here yourself?
I ended up driving myself.
Mr. Lee, there's also
the board's decision to consider.
Are you sure about this?
You mean those old geezers
telling me to stay put?
There's no need
for you to get involved, sir.
It was always going to be
a difficult contract to win.
Now there's a risk that
you might have to take all the blame.
This is why you're just an employee.
- Just take off your shirt.
- Yes, sir.
- Should I hire a new driver?
- Sure, whatever.
Just give him some money
so he doesn't run his mouth.
Yes, sir.
This project is mine.
I want every son of a bitch
in the sticks to know
that Lee Yoon of Geumsu Group
personally won a 9.5-trillion-won project.
Then those old geezers won't be able
to call me a deadbeat anymore.
Mr. Lee.
Now is a crucial time,
with the group's succession on the line.
If you fail to win the contract--
You know that saying,
"there's nothing money can't buy"?
I used to think
that was just an expression.
But I was wrong.
There's nothing that money can't solve.
Seriously, anything's possible with money.
Dear fellow members
of the Bannam Zone 2 union,
To begin, we,
the executive team of Yeoni Construction,
would like to extend our deepest respects
to the union members.
BANNAM ZONE 2 CONSTRUCTION PROJECT PLAN
What, a deep bow? Give me a break.
YEONI CONSTRUCTION
I'm sorry, sir.
Hey, what did you do?
- Aren't they starting?
- What's going on?
- Jeez.
- What are they doing?
What's this?
Did they hire another celebrity?
My dear humans.
Allow me to intrude for a bit.
What is going on right now?
- What…
- Who's she?
It's a little noisy.
Don't panic.
Starting now, you will lose your voices.
Now, everyone focus on me.
Don't think of anything else.
I'm sure you're all very busy,
so I'll make this quick.
You must all be stressing over
who to vote for to make more money.
But really, does it even matter
who builds the new Bannam-dong apartments?
Don't overthink it.
Everyone on the left side,
just vote for Geumsu Construction.
As for everyone on the right,
do as you please.
Well then.
Oh, right.
Honestly, I feel a little bad.
I have a general idea of how much
you humans love your apartments.
But what can I do?
I have to make money too.
I'm sure you all understand
since we all love money.
Right? Bye then.
You. Follow me.
Oh dear.
Goodness.
- Grandma, let me.
- What?
All right, let's go.
I scored a goal today.
Oh my, well done.
- Is that it?
- What else should I say?
I'm just saying "well done"
because you did well.
My goodness, Grandma.
If you keep this up,
I won't spoil you when I'm older.
I don't care about that.
Well, I care.
Just you wait.
By the way, when do we need to pay
this month's soccer club fee?
I told you not to worry about that.
I'm exempt from the fees.
I'm the star player, you know.
Still, that's not how things should be.
Grandma, haven't you heard
of a full scholarship?
I don't have to pay a single penny.
Gosh, really?
Oh, my little boy, I'm so proud of you.
- Enjoy your meal. Take care.
- Thank you.
Here you go. Be safe!
Enjoy your meal.
SPEEDY DELIVERY SERVICE
Thank you.
What are you doing at this hour?
What about you?
And what's with that outfit?
I'm working my part-time job.
- What?
- I've got my eye on some cleats.
Jeez, you should be spending
your time practicing.
Just ask your parents for the cleats.
- Hey, wanna make a bet?
- Jeez.
What are the stakes?
- Hey, that was a clear foul!
- Goal!
You're out.
Goal!
- Left.
- Right.
It went in, right?
Goal!
Nice.
I was wondering why you were playing
like your life depended on it.
But is that it? A chicken breast?
I wasn't playing like that.
I just crushed you with my skills.
What? Are you hurt?
Hey, just hurry up and eat.
I want to get a few more deliveries in.
What, is this your thing?
A lazy genius?
I mean, you don't seem to be taking
private lessons like everyone else.
And you're working part-time at this hour.
But seeing you in action…
You asshole!
Hey.
A poor genius.
What?
You got the genius part right,
but I'm a bit short on cash.
My parents aren't around,
and my grandma's sick.
I see.
So while you're practicing,
I have to be out making money.
Hey, I didn't know--
But you know what's really important here?
Despite all that,
without any of those damn private lessons,
I still managed to kick your ass today.
You saw the goal I scored
during practice today, right?
Yeah, I saw it, you punk.
So don't get too cocky
just because you're on the national team.
When you get called up,
I'm gonna take your spot as striker.
When you get back, the starting lineup
might be totally different.
Why am I even talking to you?
Jeez.
Man, that's good.
You really don't want any?
I don't eat stuff like that.
Why aren't you eating?
That poor cow died for nothing.
I don't have an appetite.
I told you,
there's nothing to worry about.
This is important to me.
I'm sure it is.
You acted like a deadbeat,
and now you're
on your rich father's bad side.
And now your position as heir is at risk.
You seem pretty interested
in human affairs.
Because I've taken a liking to you.
You're rich,
and you look like a troublemaker.
I think you're going to become
a repeat customer.
Since we're on the subject,
who are your other clients besides me?
You seem pretty interested
in nine-tailed fox affairs.
Can I have this one too?
I guess that's a secret.
Then, what exactly are you capable of?
Judging by the fact that you need money,
it seems you can't do whatever you want.
Shouldn't I know
what you can and can't do
if I'm going to hire you again?
Humans are always like this.
All right, let me explain something.
What is this?
Where am I?
I guess calling you a "customer"
gave you the wrong idea.
That if you just give me money,
you can order me to do anything
and ask for whatever you want.
Simply put,
think of this less as making requests
and more like praying.
Whether or not I grant your wish
is up to me.
And how I choose to grant it
is also up to me.
How much I take,
and what I take as payment,
is obviously up to me as well.
I'm the one who asks questions, not you.
Even what you're allowed to know,
and how much, is up to me.
Do you understand now?
I'm telling you not to get cocky.
You pathetic little human.
But since we're on the subject,
I'll tell you one thing.
I have only one principle.
I avoid doing
even the smallest of good deeds
and only avoid doing major misdeeds.
Looks like you didn't get it.
This is important,
so I'll break it down for you.
I don't do good deeds.
No matter how trivial.
I can't risk cultivating more virtue
and accidentally becoming human.
As for wrongdoings,
I only avoid major ones.
Things like…
killing people.
That's the only thing I avoid.
I'm trying to avoid becoming human,
not trying to diminish my spiritual power.
SECRETARY CHOI
You can go now.
The voting results are out.
You should go get your picture taken.
Nothing beats a photo for showing off.
By the way, I already took the money
from the trunk of your car.
So don't worry about it.
A human's life
is like swimming in a sea of suffering.
From the moment they're thrown
into this unfamiliar world
until they rot away to nothing,
humans can never find
even a moment of peace.
Life is a constant competition.
It's a battlefield
where they can only climb up
by dragging others down.
And it's a hamster wheel
that never stops turning.
Human happiness
is but a fleeting illusion,
and such is the human condition
I have observed for hundreds of years.
But in contrast to that,
my life as a nine-tailed fox
is like a festival that never ends.
Hey.
Yes?
All the kids these days
seem to dress like you.
I used to dress like that 20 years ago.
- I guess it's back in style.
- Excuse me?
You.
Come shopping with me today.
Why should I?
Because I like the way you dress.
Besides, it's boring to shop alone.
Think of yourself
as a friend for the day, if you will.
What the heck?
What a weirdo.
Listen to me.
You're going to hang out with me today.
Yes, of course.
So, you're saying
you're a nine-tailed fox?
Really?
Come on, a nine-tailed fox?
There's no such thing.
You'd believe me if I used sorcery
and showed you my tails,
but I can't be bothered.
Just believe it. I'm a nine-tailed fox.
Oh, okay.
Oh my! Those look great on you too.
You think so?
I'll take these too.
Hey, I have a question.
What is it?
"Aren't nine-tailed foxes
supposed to eat human livers
and seduce men to drain their life force?"
Yes, how did you know?
It was obvious.
Do you think you're the first human
to ask me such questions?
Do you know how people
in the Joseon era used to speak?
You think they were like…
"Your Majesty,"
"How insolent"?
Do you really think that?
They didn't?
That's all just made up
by those TV people.
It's not as if they actually
lived through that era like I did.
So how would they know?
You make something up,
and humans just believe it.
Same with the tales
about nine-tailed foxes.
My goodness, that's truly amazing.
Look at everything happening
inside that little box.
My goodness, how fascinating!
RETURN OF THE LEGEND
NINE-TAILED FOX
People didn't think of us in this way
before that damn Return of the Legend.
Oh my gosh.
That scared the life out of me.
When humans cultivate themselves,
they're called sages,
while animals that do so
are called spirit beasts.
So why do foxes cultivating themselves
to become human get treated like monsters?
Do they think it's easy to self-cultivate
and train until we grow nine tails?
Nine-tailed foxes cultivate themselves?
Yes, just like how sages self-cultivate
and train to become immortals,
nine-tailed foxes have to self-cultivate
and train to become humans.
Think about it.
Why would a nine-tailed fox,
who's self-cultivating and building karma,
hunt human livers? If they did that,
they would lose
all the spiritual power they've earned.
Oh, I see.
You must have felt so misunderstood.
Anyway, that's all in the past.
I'm the only nine-tailed fox
left on Earth now.
I've lost all desire to be human,
so I have no reason to cultivate myself.
You're not trying to become human?
But you're a nine-tailed fox. How come?
Because I love the way I live now.
Sometimes, humans get the wrong idea.
They think that living forever
would be tedious and boring.
But when you actually experience it,
there's never a dull moment
because the human world changes so fast.
There's always something new and fun.
Shoeshine! Shoeshine!
YEAR 1930
Shoeshine!
- It's English.
- At our academy…
YEJEONG ACADEMY
ENGLISH
YOUR WEAPON FOR SUCCESS!
So this is how Westerners write?
This looks like it'd be fun.
What did that Westerner just say?
Hey, Teacher.
Speak our language.
I can't understand a single word.
What did you just say?
How am I suddenly speaking
in Joseon language?
Oh, Lord!
YEAR 1970
COMICS
MARTIAL ARTS, ROMANCE
THE COUNT'S BLACK SHEEP
FINAL EPISODE
THE END
What?
The main character dies?
What kind of ending is this?
Hey, you. Comic artist.
Hey, comic artist!
Who are you?
What's with this ending?
Is this the best you could do?
Draw it again!
THE COUNT'S BLACK SHEEP
FINAL EPISODE
What's happening?
THE END
SPACE ARCADE
MAKKEULLAE RICKSHAW
YEAR 1990
THE 4TH NATIONAL GAMING TOURNAMENT
PRELIMINARY ROUND
Hey, stop it! Stop following me!
You're such a cheap player.
Stop beating me.
Please, just stop.
Hey, don't make it so obvious!
It's no fun now.
Do your best, okay?
Play better, but not to win.
Is that so hard?
But, seriously,
is it really fun to live like that?
What?
I mean, what you're saying is
that in all that time,
you've never actually
accomplished anything.
What is that supposed to mean?
You don't think
I've accomplished anything?
I've learned everything
and played every game there is.
But no matter what you've learned,
you haven't followed through.
If there's something you don't like,
you just change it all.
- Or just scrap it.
- It's not like that.
And you don't have any friends
to shop and chat with,
so you just grab a random person and--
I said it's not like that!
Hey, take my side.
No matter what.
I envy you.
I wish I could live like you.
Just spending money and having fun
without a care in the world.
What?
Yes? What is it?
Forget it. Just finish your food.
I really chose the wrong person for this.
Can't she read the room at all?
What is it?
Why did you drag me out on a weekend?
Pick one. Whichever.
What?
You said there were cleats
you wanted to buy.
Don't save up with your part-time job.
Just pick them now.
And if I do?
You're going to buy them for me?
No.
I happen to have
a sponsorship deal with this brand.
It's a sponsorship
worth 20 million won a year,
but I can't use all of it
by myself anyway.
A sponsorship deal?
But you're not even a pro.
Dude, I'm a top prospect
for the youth national team.
They signed me a few years ago.
Are you going to pick one or not?
Do you think I'm a beggar?
What?
I'm fine.
I'm leaving.
Hey…
SONGWONGAK CHINESE RESTAURANT
That was so delicious.
Yeah, I guess you--
Humans are so pathetically weak.
Get up. Is anything broken?
No…
No, that's not it.
What happened?
But are you okay?
We ran into each other pretty hard.
You should try exercising
instead of just burying yourself in books.
You're pathetic for a guy your size.
Just go.
My apologies.
KING RAMYEON
How interesting.
What is?
That human over there.
I think he'll become quite famous
in the near future.
Famous?
Which one of the two?
That one over there.
I see.
But how do you know things like that?
I just do.
I sometimes see fragments of the future.
I can't see them whenever I want.
I don't know when, why, or what I'll see,
but whatever I see is inevitable.
That way!
Even I can't do anything to change it.
Anyway, that guy will become rich
and famous at some point.
So he might become one of my clients.
Oh, right.
You said you grant rich people's wishes
and get paid for it, didn't you?
Then, maybe you could grant my wish too?
You think I would do that?
You don't have nearly enough
to become my client.
But starting today, we're friends.
Don't you have, like,
a discount for friends and family?
Humans never fail to disappoint.
This is exactly why I don't bother
with troublesome human relationships.
I told you earlier.
You're just a friend for the day.
What?
What that means is…
you're going to forget
everything you did with me today,
everything we talked about,
and even my very existence.
Understand?
Yes, I understand.
Anyway, I had fun today.
You should get going too.
Hey, you guys.
Come carry this for me.
You're a beast cultivating yourself.
What in the world are you doing here?
Hey.
Are you really mad?
Look, it wasn't because
I felt sorry for you.
Hey, come on.
I'm sorry.
I guess now that I think about it,
I did feel sorry for you.
But it's not because I think
I'm better than you or anything.
I just wanted to help you out
after what you told me.
Hey.
- What?
- Wanna kick the ball around a bit?
What?
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
Sure, bring it on.
At cafés, you have to buy
one drink per person.
That's the rule
in the human world these days.
I'm…
a being far greater
than any rule made by humans.
I'm sure you are.
After all,
you're the Deity of the Big Dipper.
What brings you here all of a sudden,
interrupting my hobby like this?
You call that a hobby?
Of course. There isn't anything
more human and fun than spending money.
If you enjoy living like a human so much,
why won't you become one,
while deceiving the eyes of Heaven?
You're missing the point.
Who said I want to live like a human?
Squeezing into the subway to go to work
and working for over ten hours a day,
only to collapse into sleep
from exhaustion.
Even if you make a few bucks like that,
you don't have time to spend it.
That's what it means to be human.
A moment of sweetness,
and a lifetime of bitterness.
But life as a nine-tailed fox is kind of
like spending money on a pay-to-win game.
You get to enjoy all the fun stuff
without any of the inconvenience.
I wonder if the big shots up there
would even understand what I'm saying.
Since they're just so divine and all.
You're still wicked and irreverent.
Oh, whatever.
Anyway, I don't think we're
on good enough terms to sit and chat.
Let's just get straight to the point,
Lord Pagun.
So?
You want me to become human already?
Are you asking why I'm still like this
when all the other nine-tailed foxes
have already become human,
lived out their lives, and died?
I refuse.
If that's all, I can go now, right?
I'm going to go home
and unbox my new stuff.
Your scale
is tipping.
That can't be.
I put an insane amount of effort
into keeping that balance aligned.
I even earn my own money
just to appease all of you up there.
So how could the scale be tipping?
There will come a time
when you must choose.
Whether to become human
or be forever annihilated.
Don't make me laugh.
They may be deities,
but how dare they threaten me?
Let them try.
Do they still think I'm the same
naive fox who believed everything
the ones above told me?
They won't get their way.
Even you guys don't really get
the so-called Law of Heaven, do you?
Because it's so vague and messed up.
Well, there's one thing
I know for certain.
"Heaven's net is vast and wide,
yet nothing slips through."
You may think
you're outside of Heaven's influence,
but nothing ever escapes notice.
Ha!
Save the sermon.
That was Daoist teaching, actually.
Excuse me.
- Get up!
Mr. Lee!
- We love you!
You're the only boss we have, sir!
- Lee Yoon!
What was that? I can't hear you.
Louder!
- Lee Yoon!
Everyone, drink up!
- Drink up!
Hey, are you okay?
Gosh, let's call it a day.
Hey, it's my turn though.
Damn it.
Fine.
Unbelievable.
I can't believe they're still
trying to boss me around at my age.
Today just keeps getting worse--
What? Who was that?
Wow, it was like a missile.
Hey, I'll go find the ball.
You go on ahead.
- I'll come with you.
- It's fine. You go.
Bye.
Man, where did it go?
Was it you?
Are you the owner of this ball?
Yes, I am.
Thank you.
- Wait.
- No need to thank me.
- Hey--
- Go. We're done here.
Excuse me!
Wait, you're that kid from earlier.
Were you kicking a ball around this late
because I told you to get some exercise?
You don't look it,
but you're quite obedient.
What is she talking about?
Anyway, you shouldn't go around
popping other people's balls.
Well, I couldn't pop your head, could I?
Since I'm a self-cultivated beast.
Unbelievable.
Hold on.
They don't usually pop that easily.
It's not some kind of balloon--
That's because you are a weak human.
What did you say?
Wait, who do you keep calling weak?
Can't you tell just by looking?
I'm an athlete.
Is that so?
I may not be much right now,
but in a few years,
I'm going to be a really famous athlete.
Right.
I don't think so.
- What?
- Famous?
Which one of the two?
That one over there.
Maybe your friend, but not you.
I saw it earlier.
What are you--
Your friend is going to be very famous.
He'll be a world-class player
and make a lot of money too.
I'm certain. The future
never changes after I've seen it.
But as for you…
I don't see anything at all.
Who are you to say that?
You don't know anything about me!
You'll just be a nobody.
You might become a mediocre player
no one remembers,
but any success beyond that…
It's just not in your future.
So don't get your hopes up
and dream too big.
That way, you won't get hurt.
This…
This woman is a complete lunatic.
It's cruel, I know.
But that's just how human life is.
It's not like life is being
especially cruel to you.
So don't take it too hard.
Man, I did it! Damn it!
I'm Lee Yoon. Who's going to stop me?
Move! Damn it!
- Did you hear that?
- I don't know.
Maybe there was an accident.
It has nothing to do with me.
Oh no, oh no… What…
I have to get out of here.
Hey!
Stop! I said stop!
Damn it.
I said stop!
Woo-seok!
Woo-seok.
OPERATING ROOM
You can't come in.
PLEASE DISPOSE OF TRASH HERE
Damn it.
Jeez.
Seriously.
What am I going to do?
It'll probably be fine.
He seemed drunk.
He was stumbling when he walked.
So you suspect he was intoxicated.
Okay, we've requested
all the security footage from the area,
so we'll identify the vehicle owner soon.
- How may I help you?
- Well, I…
Yesterday, I…
ran someone over.
Bong-chang just went to turn himself in.
There won't be any problems for you, sir.
It's not him.
It wasn't this guy.
I saw him.
- Sir.
- Yes?
Are you sure you were the one driving?
Yes. I secretly took a company car out,
- and made a mistake--
- You're lying.
You weren't the one
who caused the accident.
I saw everything!
Why are you lying? Seriously!
Let go of me!
Sir, we have a problem.
Bong-chang just called.
He said he couldn't bring himself to lie
and asked if we could just forget the deal
in exchange for returning
all the money we gave him.
What are you talking about?
Why the sudden change?
He said there was a witness.
Bring that bastard here right now.
- There's one more thing--
- What is it this time?
I received a call from the police station.
They said you also need to come in
for questioning as a witness, sir.
How the hell are you…
Damn it!
How could you handle this so poorly?
I apologize, sir.
Get out.
Pardon?
I'll handle it myself from now on.
Get out.
Jeez.
I WILL GRANT YOUR WISH
Wow.
It's you again.
It must be nice to be rich,
summoning me again after just one day.
Maybe I didn't charge you
enough yesterday.
This time, it's a very simple job.
But it's urgent.
What a shame.
I was thinking of taking a break
for about ten years.
An annoying old geezer
has been pestering me lately.
So, I'm rejecting your request.
I'll pay you double
what I gave you yesterday.
I guess I'll rest
after I handle this quickly.
What is it?
URI GARAM HOSPITAL
Who are you?
You again?
It seems we're deeply connected by fate.
The soccer ball from yesterday, right?
But how did you know I was here?
Right.
I'm here to tweak your memory a bit.
What?
Look straight at me. Don't look away.
About what you saw last night…
Wait a minute.
This can't be happening.
No way.
Their fates have switched?
What is this now?
You're still wicked and irreverent.
Your scale
is tipping.
NO TAIL TO TELL
I said I lost a huge chunk
of my spiritual power.
You're going to help me.
I mean, what are you exactly?
This beauty. And this mystique.
- A demon?
- A nine-tailed fox!
But no matter how much
I think about it, I just don't get it.
What did I do that was so wrong?
A human has died. Because of you.
Kang Si-yeol.
How much does he really make?
Apparently,
he makes 500 million won a week.
I'm so proud that I am me.
Long time no see, Si-yeol.
Did he seriously not recognize me?
You want to catch that hit-and-run driver
and make him pay, right?
I killed someone!
- Jeez!
- So, tell me. Whatever it is.
What's your wish?
Subtitle translation by Susanna Kim