This series features fictional characters
and content based on cases of depression.
Real-life symptoms and behaviors
may vary from person to person.
For more info or psychiatric consultation,
call your local area's mental health hotline.
Those with depression or similar symptoms
should watch with a close companion.
I... caused trouble again, didn't I?
I'm sorry for telling you I was fine.
Pobmek, I need your help with something.
I'm going to see my father.
Come with me?
No matter what happens,
I'll always be by your side.
I heard that couples often get
to know each other better
when they travel together.
This is our first trip together.
And it really is just like they say.
Didn't I tell you to turn back there?
See? Now we're lost.
I've been holding the steering wheel
for six hours.
My butt is getting all sore.
I got foggy-headed and missed the turn!
Thank you.
Whoa.
This is completely the wrong direction
from where we're headed.
Look.
I pinned the wrong location.
See?
I knew it.
Yeah.
It's my fault.
I can't even drive.
I can't even read a map right.
Hey.
That's not what I mean.
Even though we've been together for so long,
there are still things that surprise us.
Solar is more sensitive than I thought.
I guess I need to be more patient
and try to understand him better.
Let's stay here tonight.
We'll figure it out tomorrow.
Solar!
What's wrong?
There!
What?
Shoo it away, Solar!
Uncle.
Sun?
How did I end up here?
You're not afraid of geckos, right?
Go shoo it away for me.
Go.
Go, go, go.
He switches to Sun
without falling asleep again?
Yeah.
I feel bad for Solar.
For you too, man.
Yeah.
Did you guys find out anything else?
I checked the address on that old letter.
Looks like it's really Mr. Sarun's address.
But the bad news is
he already sold the house.
Looks like he was having
some financial problems.
But don't get discouraged yet.
I have good news.
I found his new place.
It's a fruit orchard.
Looks like he became a farmer.
Wait.
But he used to own a toy factory.
How did he end up a farmer?
We have no idea.
You guys go check it out.
I'll send you the location.
I just sent it.
[Sarun's Plum Mango Orchard]
You really can fix anything, Uncle Sarun.
If you hadn't told me
you were a businessman from Bangkok,
I'd think you're just one of the locals.
Oh, I can't fix everything.
You said
it keeps turning on and off by itself.
The timer's broken.
We'll have to buy a new one.
I'll call and order one from Bangkok now.
Sarun, some people from Bangkok
are here to see you.
Delivery is fast these days, huh?
Sir!
Stop!
Hey!
Sir, stop!
- Sir!
- Dad, stop!
It's me.
I'm your son, Sun.
I'm sorry for running away earlier.
I thought you were my creditors.
Do you live here?
How did you end up here?
Well...
Go away.
Come on.
Don't mind it.
It's been here for a long time.
Uncle.
Sun?
Dad.
- Dad!
- Hey.
Dad, where's Mom?
What did you say?
I'm asking where Mom is.
Well... I have something to tell you.
It may sound a bit fantasy-like,
but this is the reality we're facing.
Sun.
Is this really you, Sun?
Yes.
You want to see your mom, right?
I do.
Do you remember the last time you saw her?
I remember she had just gotten off work.
We were about to go home together,
and she said this to me.
Having you is the reason I lost everything!
Is that all you remember?
Do you remember anything else?
What's wrong? Do you have a headache?
I'll get you some medicine.
I'll be right back.
How are you feeling?
Are you okay?
I feel kind of uneasy.
Sir!
- What are you doing?
- Running away, obviously!
- Running away?
- Yeah!
- Running away from what?
- Dad!
What are you doing?
You want me to take responsibility, right?
I'm too poor to be responsible for you.
Hey!
Ouch!
Sun! Are you okay? Are you hurt?
I'm not hurt, but my dad sure will be.
Solar?
Solar!
He's really fit for his age.
Dad!
How much longer are you going to
keep running from me?
I still don't even know
what I'm going to say to you, Dad.
I just don't want to run away
from my problems anymore.
This is the letter
you sent to Teacher Pranee.
I already read it,
and I understand why you left me.
I just...
wanted to come and apologize.
I'm sorry for being the reason
Mom made that decision.
Let's go.
Wait, don't go yet.
Can you come with me, Sun?
These are some of your mom's things
that I kept.
I was saving them for you, Sun,
just in case we ever saw each other again.
Is this all you're giving me?
I'm leaving.
Sun.
You think you're the reason Mom did that,
but I don't agree.
Okay, I know I have no right
to change the way you think,
but I can assure you
that you're not the reason.
If you came here to ask
why your mom decided to do that,
it's because of me.
Solar, which animal do you think
needs special care?
A baby bird.
Why do you think so?
Because it can't fly on its own yet.
And what about a lion cub like you, Solar?
Do you need special care too?
I know it's all about video games these days,
but toys are tangible.
They're still in demand.
How about you let me know
your decision later?
Alright, bye.
Teacher Pranee.
Sir! Come here.
I think I hear people
arguing inside the house.
- Inside the house?
- Yeah, for a while now.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
Answer me.
Why couldn't you hold onto it?
- Huh?
- Hey.
What happened?
See for yourself.
Sun,
do you want to sit down and play?
Come on, it's okay.
Do you want to sit down and rest?
I'll clean this up.
After your mom went on maternity leave,
her show got cancelled.
She probably wanted to feel seen again.
Come on. Waist twists!
Arm circles!
But that chance kept slipping further away.
Another person I felt just as much for
was you, Sun.
I'm fine.
[Enjoy eating, my hero]
I have fangs to protect myself.
Oh, you're the best, Little Solar.
Solar is fine because
he has fangs to protect himself.
Yay!
I did everything I could to get your mom
a chance to talk to the station.
I hoped she could get her show back,
and feel proud of herself again.
Okay.
So our family could be happy again.
Are you happy for your mom? She got a job.
But things didn't turn out the way I hoped.
I still admire your show,
and everyone else does too.
But after you went on leave,
things are different now.
Times have changed, okay?
It's okay.
Let's come up with some new ideas
to pitch to them.
You've done it before.
I'm sure you can do it again.
Right, Sun?
Yes, you can do it, Mom.
Okay?
Let me take this call.
Hello?
Got it.
Actually,
I was there that day,
but I can only remember bits and pieces.
It must've been painful for Sun.
But for me,
that pain didn't end that day.
After that incident,
Sun didn't regain consciousness.
Even though the doctor said
Sun was out of danger,
they didn't know when he would wake up.
Leroy proudly marched into the forest.
Teacher Pranee was so worried about Sun,
and came to visit him often.
And then, a miracle happened.
Who's Sun?
My name's not Sun.
I'm Solar.
Solar means bright sunshine,
ready to heal everyone's heart.
You don't remember anything?
Who are you, Auntie?
Are you my mom?
I'm sorry I left you...
without telling anyone, Sun.
All I left you was that first letter,
and the money from selling my company.
Actually, I wrote many more letters, but...
I was too afraid to send them.
Because every time I thought about that day,
when you woke up as someone else,
it reminded me that my son wanted to escape.
Who would want
to be with a terrible father like me?
It's actually me...
who was the reason
your mom decided to do that.
It's not your fault...
Mom made that decision.
It's not your fault either, Sun.
Solar,
look behind the photo.
What's this key?
It's the key to the toy box.
But I don't know why your mom put it there.
These past few years
have been the worst of my life.
I don't understand
what's really going on with me.
I feel like...
I'm worthless.
It's gotten so bad
that I don't even know who I am anymore.
It feels like I'm not myself anymore.
Even though I've been trying
to be myself again,
it's just too hard.
I'm so exhausted.
I can barely take it anymore.
Mom, you're going back to work, right?
Probably not.
Having you is the reason I lost everything!
Sun, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean that.
Little Sun,
your mom asked me to tell you she's sorry.
She didn't mean what she said.
From now on,
she'll be more careful with her words.
Please don't be mad at her.
But I know how much I matter
to both your dad and you.
You two are the only thing
that makes me want to keep living.
I love your dad,
and I love you so much, Sun.
But the person I forgot to love the most...
was...
myself.
Please don't cry, my hero.
Sun,
is this really you?
I remember everything now, Dad.
Mom didn't want to leave us.
She did that to protect me.
I know you've done everything...
to take care of me, and to take care of Mom.
I know it,
and Mom always knew it too.
So,
let's live happily...
for her.
Okay.
Sun is going to be asleep for a while, huh?
Yes.
Alright. Here.
These are plum mangoes from my orchard.
Take them all and share them
with your friends in Bangkok.
Thank you so much.
But I didn't prepare anything for you.
Oh, don't worry.
Taking care of Sun and Solar
is already more than enough.
Thank you.
It's Solar who's been taking care of me.
Without him,
I don't know what my life would be right now.
Wait.
Here.
- What's this letter?
- It's not a letter.
It's a list of places to visit.
There are a lot of great spots on it.
Thank you so much.
Enjoy your trip.
Sir,
whenever it's convenient for you,
please come visit us in Bangkok sometime.
Okay.
What are you doing hiding here?
Just getting some air.
Hey.
Do you think it's weird?
Weird?
What's weird?
I'm not as good at this as I used to be.
It's not like when Little Sun does it.
It's probably because you're you,
and Sun is Sun.
I think Little Sun understands now
that he shouldn't have suppressed his pain,
and created me to forget his painful past.
When Sun remembered everything,
and accepted all that happened,
I could feel that...
he'd finally let it go.
He's healed now.
If Sun is healed,
and you're the identity he created,
then why haven't you gone back to being Sun?
Where did he go?
It seems like Little Sun has gone back
into my heart,
and fallen into a very deep sleep.
It's like he chose
to let me live my life from now on.
Why would Sun do that?
I think he wants us to be together.
You're saying...
Little Sun and I
don't have to switch every other day anymore.
Sun wants me to be with you every day.
That kid always knows too much.
Before we split up for work today...
After everything was resolved,
- Hi.
- Solar looks happier.
- Nothing's weighing on his mind anymore.
- What?
I think it's working now, Dad.
Oh!
Hey!
Yay!
And it's probably not just Solar
who has changed.
You're pretty good.
- Thank you so much, Dad.
- How do you know how to fix this?
Excuse me.
Is there anything I can help with?
Do you usually sweep before you mop,
or mop before you sweep?
But some things never change.
- Bye-bye, Dad.
- Bye-bye.
[The seller's asleep!
Please pay via PromptPay]
Solar! What's wrong?
There!
Hold on.
You're not even taking a shower.
Why did you come in here?
Actually, I snuck in to write you a postcard.
I was about to write you one too.
What were you going to write?
Well,
I was going to compliment you
on how you managed to let go of your trauma.
That's all.
What about you?
What were you going to write to me?
I just wanted to write
that no matter how much we've been through,
there will always be new things for us
to learn about each other
and for me to get to know you better.
Without you,
I don't know how I'd live.
Thank you so much.
Thank you so much, too.
Go. I'm going to take a shower.
You're going to trick me
into thinking you're showering again.
This time, I'm standing guard.
Look who's playing the discipline teacher.
Okay.
Just make sure standing guard is all you do.
I thought you said
you were just going to stand guard.
I changed my mind.
And it's probably just like Solar said.
We'll always have new things
to learn and get to know each other better.
As long as we don't run away from them
and keep holding each other's hands,
that's enough.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
If Sun came to the beach,
what do you think he'd do first?
Thank you so much
for bringing Sun and me
to the beach like you promised.
I want to play in the water
with both you and Sun, I guess.
Hey. Solar.
Teacher Solar is about to propose
to Teacher Pobmek!
Do it!