Stop bothering me.
Did you bring any soap?
- No.
- Nice game out there.
Hurry up.
I know, I know.
- Hey Li Ming, what a coincidence.
- You're here.
Looking good. Look at those muscles.
I'm solid as a rock.
Why is this part so soft?
Get lost! Who cares about it being hard?
Chen Ke.
I didn't realize you were so pale.
What are you doing?
You pervert!
What?
You never shower with us,
but you'll shower with Chen Ke?
I... I'm just getting used to it.
Used to what?
You're still wrapped in a towel?
Just take it off already.
It's just a shower.
- Why go totally naked?
- Just take it off.
Seriously.
Look at you.
I'm just kidding.
[Episode 3: I kissed you because
I wanted to show my affection and blessings]
♪ I secretly cover your eyes ♪
♪ And let you guess who I am ♪
Stop it.
I'm here for something serious.
Lately, you and Chen Ke
have been joined at the hip.
I thought you'd forgotten me.
Now you finally remember me?
It's all your fault.
That crappy movie you showed on the trip...
Now whenever I'm close to a guy,
it just feels weird.
So you're blaming the movie?
Then let's just watch it again.
Again?
You want me to suffer more?
Don't you get it?
It's called exposure therapy.
Last time, you only saw the beginning,
and your mind started racing.
Maybe once you finish it,
you'll realize it's actually a beautiful,
tragic love story.
Maybe then you won't be so restless.
Who's restless?
Play it.
[The End - A movie by Wang Kar Wai]
Why such a big reaction?
You...
Okay. The movie's over.
How do you feel?
If you don't feel anything, then...
No.
Nothing special.
That was sudden.
What are you two doing
hiding in here with the curtains drawn?
I know.
You're sneaking a peek at some porn.
- Why didn't you invite me?
- Who's watching porn?
That's all you think about.
Get your mind out of the gutter.
Xiao Ming,
we just borrowed a Wong Kar Wai film.
Want to join us?
Nah. Too artsy for me.
I wouldn't get it.
Showing him art is a total waste.
Like casting pearls before swine.
[Chen Ke is calling]
Where are you going, Yu Lei?
Chen Ke asked me to practice baseball.
Hey.
I've got nothing else to do.
Let's play some games.
Do you know how to play Counter-Strike?
Who plays such violent games?
You're such a gorilla.
Go on, get out of here.
I think you should spend your time showering.
You stink.
Me?
Do I really smell that bad?
Stop being so picky.
Why do you keep smiling at me?
Is there something on my face?
It's nothing.
I just figured something out.
What?
Does it have to do with me?
Yu Lei, you're here to play too?
Welcome!
We're just here to watch.
Hope we're not interrupting practice.
Not at all. Chen Ke, show Yu Lei the ropes.
We're always looking for
more people to join the club.
- Thanks.
- No problem.
What's going on?
It's not like this in the anime "Touch".
It's okay. It's simple.
I'll show you.
Come here.
October 15, 2001. Sunny.
Today, Yu Lei seemed really happy.
When I asked him why, he wouldn't say.
But seeing him happy
makes me feel good too.
So, this is what having a close friend
feels like.
Want to try the stance I mentioned?
What stance?
The one from the book.
You mean the traditional one?
So you like it old school?
Is there really a difference?
Come on, one more time.
Okay.
- Hand me that balloon.
- A bit higher.
- A little more to the left.
- Don't mess it up.
I got it, no problem.
That's about right.
Be careful.
Time flies.
I can't believe Christmas is almost here.
I remember when I was a kid,
it was my grandma's favorite holiday.
But ever since she passed away,
my family hasn't really celebrated it.
That's easy.
We can celebrate here at school this year.
It'll be fun.
Forget it.
It's right during final exams.
Everyone will be busy studying.
Who's going to think about Christmas?
[Victoria Italian Restaurant]
[Christmas Plans with Chen Ke]
[Chen Ke calling]
December 20, 2001.
Cloudy.
Final exams are coming up,
but Yu Lei is busy with something.
He's nowhere to be found
when I asked him to join me for revision.
Aren't we friends?
He didn't even say a word.
Is this seat taken?
No, go ahead.
I'm heading out.
Chen Ke.
Hey, senior.
Why are you eating alone?
Where's Yu Lei?
Even I can't find him.
I asked him to join me for revision today,
but he didn't get back to me.
He's probably busy with something.
What's he being so secretive about?
Isn't he studying for the final exams?
By the way,
the school orchestra has a show on the 24th.
I wanted to invite you guys.
Since you're here,
I'll just give these to you.
The 24th?
Yeah.
- We'll be in the middle of exams.
- I know.
It's the last day of your exam week, right?
Don't worry.
The performance is in the evening.
It'll be a good way to relax.
Okay. Thanks, senior.
Yu Lei, what were you so busy with today?
Me?
I just went out to buy some things.
- Why?
- Didn't you see my page?
I forgot to bring my pager today.
Never mind.
I wanted to ask you to study with me.
I'm sorry. I...
It's fine.
Just don't disappear like that next time.
- Got it.
- By the way, are you free on Christmas?
Me?
On Christmas?
I might have some plans.
What plans?
Don't worry about it.
Just some personal stuff.
Hey man, you're back.
- Yeah.
- Exams are coming up.
How's the studying going?
Exams?
What exams?
Are you serious?
Final exams are next week.
You really had no idea?
Buddy, you have to help me.
You've got to help me out!
He Jin, give it a rest.
Can you keep it down?
Seriously.
Go study in the hallway.
Don't keep everyone awake.
Just go to sleep.
I have my own way of studying.
We're all just trying to study.
Battle, battle... protest, protest...
Actually,
you don't need to memorize everything.
Look at this chapter, and this one.
The professor emphasized on these.
I'm sure they'll be on the test.
It's okay.
Don't put so much pressure on yourself.
Thanks.
Who needs your charity?
[Focus on this topic]
Alright, class.
Ten minutes left.
Please finish up your answers.
[Heng Tai First High School]
"Zhang Han invited Yu Lei and me to a show."
"I'm heading there now.
Whoever gets back first,
please let him know."
What's this?
Looks fancy.
Chen Ke...
He Jin!
Why are you using Chen Ke's skincare?
I'm not, I'm just looking.
Don't tell him.
This brand is actually pretty good.
If you want it, buy your own.
Where's Chen Ke? I haven't seen him.
I think he's on a date.
- With who?
- How should I know?
Xiao Ming, you're crazy!
Yu Lei, he's lost it.
- Just bear with it.
- Count yourself lucky.
He already kissed the rest of us.
You're the only one left.
What? You guys aren't happy?
I'm showing my gratitude.
Thanks to you, I'm sure I passed.
No doubt about it.
No way. I'm too happy.
I have to kiss you again!
- No, no, no!
- Stop it! Run!
No one's getting away!
Give me some sugar!
Help!
Are you okay?
Buddy, I didn't mean it.
Check if anything's broken.
It's fine, don't worry about it.
These are for you guys.
Here, Xiao Ming.
What's this? Let me see.
It looks nice.
- Here.
- Thanks.
Yong.
- Thanks, Yu Lei.
- Oh no.
I was so focused on the exams,
I didn't get any gifts.
- What should I do?
- It's okay.
As long as you're happy.
I don't care about that.
Guys, the three of us can
just each give him a kiss.
Guys, that's really not necessary.
- Get him!
- Come here!
I give up!
Tell you what, let's go out and celebrate.
Dinner, drinks, and karaoke.
Whoever goes on a date is a loser.
A total loser.
Let's go.
Still pretending to study?
- What are you talking about?
- Stop snatching.
Let's come back here next time, okay?
Sure.
Come on, what are you looking at?
Must be nice.
When will I ever get a girlfriend?
You traitor.
- Aren't we enough for you?
- Exactly.
It's not the same.
How is it different? Get him, Xiao Ming!
So you're too good for us now?
How dare you look down on us!
Stop looking and hurry up.
[School Orchestra Recital]
- Not bad.
- Sounds great.
Yeah.
Dear Ke Ke,
I bet you're wondering what I've been up to.
Well, here's the answer.
I was getting this Christmas gift ready,
and planning today's date.
I'm sorry for neglecting you
these past few days.
But by now, we should have
already had a great dinner
and seen a movie.
I hope when you see this gift,
you'll feel like it's been a perfect day.
Stop drinking.
You can't handle it, so why try?
Seriously.
That jerk Li Ming.
He said whoever goes on a date is a loser.
Then he just ditches us halfway through.
But he didn't say he was going on a date.
Are you blind?
Didn't you see the look on his face
when he answered that call?
It was disgusting.
What's up?
Someone's over there.
I think it's Chen Ke.
Looks like he's looking for you.
We'll head up first.
Be safe.
Why didn't you put on a coat?
I...
What if you catch a cold?
I just wanted to see you.
Thanks for the gift.
I was in such a rush, I forgot my coat.
I thought you were on
a date with my sister.
Why would you think that?
She gave me two tickets for the both of us.
But lately, I thought you were
ignoring me on purpose.
So, I was upset and didn't tell you.
But I left a note on your desk.
A note?
But I went to your dorm.
I didn't see any note.
And He Jin didn't say anything.
Chen Ke, I'm the one who should be sorry.
I wanted to surprise you so much
that I forgot to consider your feelings.
In the end, the surprise turned into a scare.
It almost became a huge mess.
I... I'm at fault too.
I should have just talked to you.
With all these misunderstandings,
we almost missed each other.
What's going on?
Is this an apology convention?
Yeah. At least we're together now.
The shops are still open.
Come on. Let's go celebrate.
I almost forgot to give your coat back.
Don't catch a cold in this weather.
It's okay, I'm not cold.
See? I'm still steaming.
Oh, right. I forgot to give you your gift.
What is it?
When I saw the scarf you gave me,
I wasn't sure what to get you in return.
So I bought this.
It's a serum.
I hope you like it.
I didn't know you were so bold, Chen Ke.
Running out without a coat
just to buy me a gift?
What are you talking about?
I'm just missing a jacket,
not running around nude.
Even if you were, I wouldn't mind.
Alright, stop it.
Go on. Open it.
Okay.
Do you like it?
You're so thoughtful, Ke Ke.
It's fine. I'd love anything you give me.
I'm going to take it out now.
Go ahead.
Come here. Follow me.
Okay. I'm really taking it out.
- Merry Christmas. Ta-da!
- I got one too?
- Me too!
- I hope you like it.
- I'll love anything you give me.
Keep it down. Don't let anyone hear us.
Is it okay for us to be hiding here?
Maybe we should go back to the dorm.
It's fine.
Look how happy they are.
They won't notice us.
Guess what it is.
Something I'll love, for sure.
Wow. I really do love it.
See? I knew you would.
Here. See if it looks good.
Let's try it on.
- Not bad.
- What do you think? Pretty good, right?
It's beautiful.
So pretty.
Here. Can you put some on me?
- Sure.
- Here.
Hurry up.
- Don't get it everywhere.
- I'll put some on too.
It's smudging.
What?
It's fine. Does it look good?
Yeah.
Why do you smell so good today?
Let me smell.
Come here.
Oh, Rose! Are you going to jump?
No! Don't do it!
Give me your hand!
Oh, Jack! Don't come any closer!
Stay back!
Oh, Rose...
Don't jump!
The snow down there is freezing.
You'll definitely regret it.
I've made up my mind.
I'm jumping right now!
- Fine. You jump, I jump.
- Don't let anyone see us.
There's no one here. One more kiss.
Stop it.
Hey! Get back to your dorms!
Look at the time!
Hurry, let's go.
- Go, go.
- Let's go.
Careful.
Slow down, baby.
It's so slippery.
Hurry up.
Carry my things.
Watch your step.
Let's go.
How did they...
Lights out soon!
Get back to your rooms!
Or I'll mark your names down!
How did we even squeeze into this tiny space?
I have no idea.
But now I know what it feels like
to run for your life.
Hey, you two! Stop there!
Stop chasing me!
I'm not in a relationship!
I told you we shouldn't have kissed.
We aren't even a couple.
Why were we hiding?
Then why did you kiss me?
You scared me.
I...
It wasn't really a kiss.
I just accidentally bumped into you.
And then I thought...
you're actually a good kisser.
Alright, that's enough.
But foreigners kiss all the time
during holidays.
Isn't it just a greeting?
But if two people are really close,
isn't it natural
to want to be physically close too?
And if two people are physically close,
doesn't that mean
they want to be close mentally?
Look, handshakes, shoulder-grabs,
hugs, and kisses...
they might look different,
but they're actually all the same.
They all represent intimacy.
Is intimacy only for couples?
Can't friends or family show it too?
Is that how it works?
Of course.
I kissed you because I wanted to
show my affection and blessings.
And you didn't push me away
because you accepted them.
See? We're perfectly in sync.
Alright, Ke Ke.
Merry Christmas.
[Enjoy the winter holidays]
This is the only time we have
before the break.
It's not like we won't see each other again.
We'll be back after the holidays.
Yeah.
Alright.
I really have to go.
Have a safe trip.
Take care.
Ke Ke! Wait!
What now?
I just realized I haven't
given you my home number.
Here. Give me yours too.
This feels like that long,
dramatic goodbye in "The Butterfly Lovers".
So, which one of us is Liang Shan Bo
and which one is Zhu Ying Tai?
What are you talking about?
That was a man and a woman.
But we're both guys.
I suspect Liang Shan Bo
wanted to be with Zhu Ying Tai
even before he knew she was a girl.
Alright. I'll stop teasing you.
Go on.
Happy New Year in advance.
Bye.
[Next Episode]
If you like it, I can teach you.
I'll pass.
Look at my hands.
They're like bear paws.
Your hands are cute.
They don't look like bear paws.
People who are close
probably do want to be more intimate.
No wonder when he put that scarf on me,
I had the sudden urge to kiss him.