What really makes
Christmas special is
the people you spend it with.
You probably know me already,
so I won’t bother
introducing myself.
Do you think
there’s pain there, Sam?
It’s a ruthless
world out there, Maui.
Then what do you want me to do?
Should I just follow
everything you say, then?
You’re the one who
fucked up your own life.
Just in case anything
happens to us,
you need Clyden.
You’re the only
good thing in this world.
You two are so cute,
I hope you never break up.
Go.
You’re gonna miss your flight.
Cy!
You really think I’d let you go
to Singapore alone?
Of course, I’m coming with you.
First out of the country
trip together.
We’re gonna have so much fun!
Yes! Singapore, baby!
So here’s the shots.
- Good, that’s good.
- Right.
- Sam, this way.
- Okay.
Hi, Sam!
- Lena, hi!
- Very nice to meet you here.
Nice to meet you, Lena.
Hello.
Nice to meet you
as well. Please.
Have a seat, please.
We’ve had a lot of
really positive feedback
from different brands
we showed your portfolio to.
You’re a real standout, Sam.
You’re exactly what
these brands are looking for -
versatile and fresh.
That’s right.
The demand for a model like you,
it’s really high these days.
And you’ve got a real future
here in this industry.
I mean that. We’re really
excited to work with you.
Thank you, I’m equally excited
to work with you all.
This means a lot to me.
But I just want to be
upfront about something.
Sure.
I’m happy to take
international bookings,
but I'd prefer to
remain Manila-based.
It’s definitely possible, Sam.
We can work with that.
But we wanna be
transparent with you.
The demand here
in Singapore is high.
You might find yourself
flying frequently in and out.
Could be New York, could be L.A.
Anywhere in the world.
You’re gonna have to juggle
a really tight schedule.
That means both
Cy and I will be busy.
But this is a
once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
I’m sure Cy will
support me on this one.
Yeah, it’s okay.
I can handle it.
Great! We’re all set then.
Are you free for
some headshots later?
Yeah, I'm ready.
Fantastic, thank you.
Can you tilt your
head to the side?
Like this?
Your turn, love.
Hi love, you did great today.
Thanks for coming
with me to the shoot.
You eased my nerves.
But.
I feel a bit guilty because
instead of resting,
you still came with me.
Love, don’t feel guilty.
That’s exactly why I’m here,
to support you.
Okay.
Let me make it up
to you tonight.
Really?
How are you gonna
make it up to me?
I’ll shower first.
Hurry.
And hey, don’t sleep
on me, okay?
Of course.
Love…
Huh?
Oh shit.
Oh my god.
Sorry, I fell asleep.
Why didn’t you wake me up?
I was tired too.
That’s why I ended up
falling asleep as well.
I’m sorry.
You looked so excited yesterday,
and I just ended up
sleeping on you.
Was it really me
who was excited or you?
Hey, it’s okay.
We’ve got the whole day
to ourselves anyway.
So let’s go out on a date.
Sure. But first,
let’s finish where
we left off last night.
There are a lot of people here.
The view would
look great at night.
Yeah.
It’s so nice here.
But let’s still
take a picture now.
Have you been to
Singapore before, love?
Yeah, why?
Then why do you act
like it’s your first time?
You’ve been taking
photos non-stop.
It’s my first time with you.
I want to document everything,
every moment we have together.
What a sweet talker.
Come on, I really mean it.
Cy...
When I start getting
international bookings,
I’ll be busy.
And I’m sure, you’ll be busy
with your clerkship too.
Are we going to be okay?
Love...
Of course, we’re
going to be okay.
It’s normal for us to be
busy chasing our dreams.
But we’ll work it out.
Maybe we should set a specific
day just for our quality time.
Yeah, we should. And it has
to be non-negotiable.
We shouldn’t schedule
anything on those days.
All right. I agree!
I feel scared and
excited at the same time.
This is it.
This is the start of us
making our dreams come true.
And I’m happy to go
through all these with you.
How sweet!
Open the package from your dad.
Okay.
It’s so nice!
- Yeah.
- Wow.
It’s nice.
- Let’s try it on you.
- Okay.
You look like
a respectable doctor now.
Why? Didn’t I look
respectable before?
I don’t know.
Just kidding.
Let me try it on you.
Why is your heart
beating so fast?
You heard wrong.
Your heartbeat never lies, Maui.
It never lies.
Wait, I’m sorry...
I got an email notification.
Okay.
It might be from the agency.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, Cy!
What?
You know
"The Lab by Blanc Doux”?
That popular skincare brand?
Yeah.
They want me to be
a model for their product.
- Really?
- Look!
- Let me see.
- Yeah!
Congratulations, love!
Oh my god, I’m so happy.
I’ve waited so long for this.
Thank you, Cy.
But I think this might be
the start of our busy era.
I know,
but we promised to have our regular
date every Sunday, right?
But don’t think
about it just yet.
Focus on the opportunity
that’s right in front of you.
I’m proud of you.
Oh my god. I’m so happy.
Guys, final touches.
And pose.
Nice! One more!
- Especially if we suspect—
- Smiling...
Hey.
Good morning. Are you going out?
Yeah. Early morning shoot.
And you?
- Just about to sleep?
- Yeah.
All right, you take care.
I love you.
I love you too.
- Good night!
- Good morning.
Love?
Hey.
Love.
I’m ready.
It’s our date night.
Yes.
Do you still want to go?
Should we skip?
'Cause I’m sleepy.
Okay,
- let’s just do it next time.
- Okay.
All right, let’s just
go to sleep.
Goodnight.
Samantha.
Please come here.
Please sit down.
Maui, I’m your mother.
So don’t treat me
like a stranger.
Let’s stop this petty fight
and let’s start talking.
I agreed to let you model,
didn’t I?
What more do you want from me?
Should I thank you for
letting me do what I want, Mom?
Sweetheart, it's not like that.
What I’m trying to say is
that I support you.
So, can you please stop
giving me the cold treatment?
Besides, your dad and I are
going through so much already.
Why?
Did something happen?
No, don’t worry about it.
You know how it is in business,
there are lots of traitors.
Don’t worry about it.
What’s important, Maui, is that
you and Clyden are okay.
Because if you
and Clyden are okay,
you’ll be fine.
Just trust me, okay?
You’re getting
good at this, huh?
It’s therapeutic, Sam.
Especially when
I’m doing this with you.
How’s your therapy lately?
Are you taking your meds?
I’m good. I’m also doing
well in school.
That’s great to hear!
How about you?
How’s your modelling gig?
Things have been hectic,
but I’m having a lot of fun.
Lately, I’ve even been
practicing my walk.
But I still feel
super self-conscious.
I often make mistakes.
No wonder no one’s booked me
for a fashion show yet.
Just be patient.
You’ll book a fashion show soon.
You’re beautiful.
You just need a little bit
more confidence.
You know why?
It’s because you slouch.
- Really?
- You need to...
- You need to—
- Yeah.
- I should keep my body straight?
- Yes.
- Like that.
- Can you show me?
Okay…
You know what,
I’m the older sister
but in moments like this,
you’re more mature than me.
And I’m lucky
to have you, Naomi.
I’m luckier to have you, Sam.
Now, keep mixing that.
Wait.
Hi, Lena.
Sam, great news!
There is a show that needs
one more model this week.
We recommended you,
and they loved your portfolio.
They want to meet you ASAP.
Plus, Giselle will also
be there. So, are you in?
Oh my god, a fashion show?
Of course, I’m in!
Awesome!
Rehearsals have started,
so you need to fly here
tomorrow afternoon.
Is that okay?
Yeah. No worries,
I’ll fix my sched.
Good. Then I’ll book
your ticket. See you, Sam.
Yeah. See you.
Bye.
Oh my god, Naomi! I’m so happy!
I heard everything. See?
I told you, just be patient.
Yeah.
I’m so blessed.
Blessed to have you.
- So excited!
- Me too.
Okay. Go, Sam. Show me.
- Show me.
- Okay. I’ll show you.
Like that or like this?
Okay.
Sam, you need to be
more confident.
So that’s how it’s done.
But I feel like
you’re actually better.
No.
Okay.
Dr. Ramirez, we need to talk.
Doc Lucas, what happened?
Did you inform Mrs. Cruz
that she needs to get a blood
test before the treatment?
It’s not noted in her chart.
Sorry, Doc. I wasn’t able
to relay it to the patient.
Seriously?
Mrs. Cruz was supposed
to have her treatment today,
but now we have to postpone it
because you didn’t inform her
about the blood test.
Sorry, Doc. It was really
an honest mistake.
An honest mistake?
You know, one mistake
can cost someone’s life!
Look,
I know you’re a Ramirez.
But lives are on the line here.
Let this be a lesson.
And please,
make sure this
doesn’t happen again.
Sorry. I’m sorry, Doc.
Guess what, Yanna.
I used your grandmother’s
recipe for my champorado!
But I added dark chocolate
to make it extra chocolatey.
Wow, your champorado
is so fancy,
dark chocolate and all!
You know it tastes
even better with dried fish.
Of course, I added that in.
Damn it, Sam. It’s only
six in the morning,
and you’re already
making me hungry.
Why did you cook so early?
Cy’s coming home from duty soon.
It’s been a while since
I’ve had breakfast with him.
Our schedules have
been really tough lately.
I have a flight
later this afternoon,
and I’ll be gone
for more than a week.
Is he going to take you
to the airport?
I don’t think so.
He doesn’t know it yet.
I’ll tell him later.
You know what?
I’m so excited
to see his reaction
since it’s my first
fashion show.
He might get too excited
and come with you.
Sounds unlikely.
He’s busy with clerkship.
But you never know.
Last time, he actually
went with you, right?
Well,
it would be nice
if he could come.
Love?
Wait. I’ll talk
to you later. Bye.
Love! You’re here!
Good news! I have
something to tell you...
Love,
maybe later.
I’m really tired.
I’m going to rest first, okay?
Sorry.
But I’m leaving in a few hours.
Hey, love,
I finally booked my first
fashion show in Singapore,
and I’m flying this afternoon!
I’m so nervous,
but I’m also excited.
I didn’t wake you up
because you were fast asleep.
I cooked champorado
and dried fish for you.
It’s in the fridge.
I also fed the dogs.
See you in a week, love.
I love you.
Girl, don’t worry, you got this.
You look amazing, and
you’ve improved so much...
Especially the walk.
Exactly!
It feels like you’ve
been doing this for years.
Thank you!
I’m still learning, though.
Hi, love.
Good luck on your fashion show.
Sorry I won’t be there.
I’ll make it up to you
when you get back. I love you.
Here, so you won’t
miss me too much.
But I already miss you.
I’m nervous.
This is my look for the show.
Do I look okay?
The show is about
to start in 5 minutes.
Here’s the link again!
Wish me luck, love.
He might be on duty.
Goodluck on
your first show, Sam!
I’m watching right now.
I’m so excited for you!
You must be so nervous but
remember I’m cheering for you!
Smile, be confident,
but also, don’t forget to enjoy.
Models, models, get ready!
The show is about to start.
Wait for it.
Doc Ramirez, you’re all smiles!
Is that your girlfriend?
Yeah, I’m watching her
first fashion show.
- It’s being streamed live.
- Girlfriend?
Oh my god, doc!
Can we watch too?
Are you done with work?
Yes, doc.
- We’re off duty now.
- Yes.
All right then. Here...
- It just started.
- Oh, wait, Doc.
Let’s just watch
on the laptop instead.
Let me just set it up.
Beautiful circles…
And very nice. Okay!
This is our star.
Don’t lose her.
There you go.
And Samantha, I wanna see
Samantha right now.
Doc Ramirez, you’re being called
to report to the ER.
You guys go ahead
and keep watching.
All right, Doc.
And everything’s stunning.
I guess he missed the show.
Sam!
What can I say?
You did a great job today.
Thank you. I was so nervous.
Nervous? You didn’t
look nervous at all.
I would love to have you
in my next show.
Really? Wow. Thank you.
I’d love it too.
That’s perfect.
I’ll tee everything up
with my agency
- and get you all the details.
- Okay, thank you.
- Girl!
- Hey!
You were so good.
Did you have fun?
Thank you.
So this is what
it feels like, huh?
While I was walking
on the runway,
I felt like I belonged here.
‘Cause you do.
You’re such a natural.
I was so amazed.
You looked stunning.
By the way, are you going
to the afterparty?
I can’t.
My flight back
to Manila is tomorrow,
and it’s super early.
That’s too bad.
The guys won’t get to experience
a Samantha Vera party.
Maybe next time.
My schedule’s just
a bit tight right now.
Okay. See you soon.
See you!
Cy!
Cy?
Maui, I’m sorry.
I got called into
the hospital last minute.
Let’s celebrate next time, okay?
I’ll make it up to you. Sorry.
Thanks for watching Avi,
by the way.
I finally got
to finish reviewing.
No problem.
How is it?
It’s tough.
It’s hard being
in my senior year
while taking care of a baby,
but I’ll manage.
What about you?
It’s a miracle you’ve
got free time right now!
Yeah.
I have vacation days
after my fashion show.
Isn’t Clyden gonna look for you?
Don’t you guys have
a celebration today?
Wow, that was deep.
What happened?
Yanna, we’ve been so busy
that we barely even
talked to each other.
Clyden wasn’t able
to watch my fashion show.
I mean, I get why, but
I was really expecting...
we’d at least celebrate
when I got back,
since he promised.
But nothing.
I feel like.
I’m in a long-distance
relationship
even though we live
in the same house.
We haven’t even had
a proper conversation in weeks.
I just… I just
miss him so badly.
I get it. It’s really hard
when time’s the enemy.
But what if you
don’t wait for him?
Plan the date night yourself?
Even just a quick
dinner or something,
as long as you two get
to spend time together.
You both need that quality time.
Go for it.
Hey, when are you free
for a quick dinner?
I was about to message you.
I’ll be able to get off
early today.
I’ll reserve a table for us
at a restaurant if you’re free.
What do you want for dinner?
Yes, I’m free!
I would love steak tonight!
All right.
See you, love.
We’re having dinner tonight!
See? It worked out!
Go on then, get moving
and doll yourself up.
Remind your fiancé just
how irresistible you are.
Exactly.
- I’ll see you.
- I’ll see you. Bye.
- Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Message me.
No need.
It’s fine, we’ll make a video.
Bye!
Hey.
I have a report
I need to finish.
It came up suddenly.
I’m sorry.
Okay.
Wait. I’ll be back.
Hi, ma’am. Here’s your steak.
Thank you.
This tastes good.
Just like how Cy
cooks steak for me.
Sen. Vera Faces Plunder Charges
as Wife Investigated
for Illegal Drug Imports.
Hey, did something happen?
My parents.
I was actually
informed about that.
Did you just find out now?
I’m sorry.
I need to see my parents.
Honey, you’re here.
What the hell is happening?
Mom? Dad?
Maureen, calm down, okay?
Is it true?
The accusations
against you? Huh?
Answer me!
Look, we have money, okay?
Everything’s gonna be okay.
We have enough money.
What the fuck, Mom?
They’re already having
you guys investigated.
What?
Are you just gonna pay
everyone off until
this all goes away?
Maureen, stop being a burden
and stay out of this!
Can you just listen
to your mom, Maui?
We already have many problems,
don’t be one of them!
Just go back to your fiancé!
So, all the accusations
against you are true?
You can’t even answer me.
Fuck. I knew it.
I’ve known for a while
that you were involved
in something illegal,
and it’s true.
Do you even care how many people
in this country are struggling?
And you’re not even ashamed
of stealing from them?
- You disgust me!
- Stop it!
Stop it!
Stop being a burden, okay?
Stop it, Maui.
Everyone was right
about you, Dad.
- You’re a useless politician.
- My god…
A bad father...
You’re a criminal!
Stephen.
Hon...
Don’t you dare act
holier than thou.
You benefited from
my money, too!
Your education,
the roof over your head,
the clothes on your back.
That all came from my money!
That money isn’t yours!
It’s the people’s money,
and every day,
I feel fucking bad
being your daughter.
Stop! Stop!
Stop please, hon!
Don’t you dare hurt her again!
Naomi.
You fucking little child.
Enough.
Go back to your room!
- Let her go!
- Stop it, Maui!
Don’t even try!
Stop being kind to this girl,
just because you pity her!
Pity?
She’s my sister!
Oh my god. She’s not!
If you don’t stay
away from this girl,
I swear, what happened to
her mom will happen to you.
Yes, Naomi. You heard me right!
You.
Ever since you came here,
you’ve brought nothing but
bad luck in this house.
Maui, let’s go.
We’re going home.
Naomi, come with me.
No!
Naomi!
Where are you going?
I’m just going to get
some fresh air outside.
You think I’m a fool?
You’re not going out!
You will never have
the same freedom
that Maui has.
I’ve already accepted that
you’ve taken away my freedom.
What really matters to me
is that Sam cares for me.
Oh my god!
You actually think
she cares about you?
Oh my god, Naomi.
You’re a charity case.
But do you really deserve it?
After years and years
of her trying and trying,
but you kept pushing her away.
Now, go back to your room.
Now!
It’s not good to act out
on your emotions, Maui.
Do you actually hear
yourself right now?
You say that because
you’re not in my position.
You don’t have problems
with your parents.
Me?
I’m not struggling?
You don’t know a thing.
You don’t know a thing about
what I’m going through right now
so don’t act
all high and mighty!
I’m sorry, I shouted.
I need to breathe.
Just give me some space, Cy.
I read the news.
Are you okay?
How do I endure all of this?
Luna, it’s so hard.
It’s way too hard.
I’m sorry you’re
going through this.
Life really loves
messing things up.
There are times when
it really feels like the
universe is picking on you.
But life goes on.
Everything will be
okay eventually.
Just hold on, okay?
Hold on to us.
Hold on to the people who are
willing to hold your hand.
The ones who won’t let go.
Auntie...
Hi! Sorry I barged in.
It’s okay po.
What brings you here?
If you’re looking for Cy,
he’s not here.
He’s at the hospital.
Well, I’m not here for Cy.
Have a seat. Let’s have a talk.
I want to speak with you.
Okay.
Well, I’ll make this short.
To be honest with you,
Cy hasn’t been talking
with us at the moment.
Cy hasn’t been talking with us
since his dad decided
to cancel the engagement.
Well, you know what’s going on
with your family.
Of course, we’re just concerned
about our business.
We’re in the medical field,
and that can get political, too.
A lot of people trust us.
And we can’t risk our family’s
reputation just to be,
you know, associated with yours.
I understand.
You know...
Cy strongly disagrees
with everything,
but his dad threatens
to cut off his inheritance
if he doesn’t go along with it.
But he doesn’t care,
he wants to be with you.
You know, Sam,
Cy has a really bright
future ahead of him.
Very bright future.
But,
the problem is,
he loves you so much.
I just don’t want him getting
dragged into your family’s mess.
So please, as a mother,
I’m begging you,
stop the engagement.
Wait, I’ll be back.
Chef, thank you so much, really.
Sure, sir. I’m sure
your fiancée will like it.
Thank you.
Please serve it over there.
Thanks again.
As long as we’re together,
we’ll get through this, okay?
This is the first time
I’ve ever felt like
I was treated
as part of a family.
Sam!
Goodbye.
I’ll see you later.
No matter what happens,
I’ll stay with you.
Cy, please.
Let’s end this. Please.
Maui, you're just tired.
I was using you.