You're moving in with Tuo?
Yes.
Uncle decided to sell the house
and move to Kaohsiung,
but Tuo wants to stay here,
so Uncle told him
to take care of things himself.
I see.
The company where I'm interning
is too far from home,
and commuting between school and work
takes up so much time.
We can't get proper sleep,
so we often doze off in class.
That's why I thought
Tuo and I could live together
and find a place
which is convenient for both of us.
The internship is just temporary.
Just bear with it, and it'll be over soon.
Honey.
It takes three hours round trip every day.
Could you bear with that?
It takes that long?
Yes, Dad.
Besides, you always say
Tuo is more independent and mature,
so I could learn from him
if I moved in with him.
Yushu left,
and now even Junxi wants to move out.
Yushu left home
because he had a fight with you,
but now Junxi is discussing this with you.
The situation's completely different,
okay?
Alright, alright. I agree.
Thanks, Dad.
[Episode 8: His Lies &amp; His Panic]
[Secret Lover]
Daddy.
Junxi.
Yushu,
you...
Tuo.
Yushu.
Long time no see.
Are you really moving back home?
Well,
I had some bad luck.
The braised food shop went under
because of the pandemic,
and I've had trouble
finding jobs since then.
I'm three months behind on rent,
and now
the landlord has kicked me out.
What about your wife?
We're divorced.
A month ago.
I can only count on you now, Junxi.
Please help me take care of Xiaozhou.
Look,
his clothes, snacks,
toys, dishes, everything's here.
Just help me take care of him for one day
so I can go back
and have a proper talk with Dad.
If you take Xiaozhou with you
to talk to Dad,
he might be more reasonable.
We just moved in ourselves,
and we haven't even unpacked yet.
You know Dad's temper.
What if he tries to hit me?
What's more important, my dignity
or unpacking your stuff?
I know you're the best.
Talk to Dad properly then.
Don't argue.
These are the signature braised dishes
of my shop.
Just help yourselves.
It's not good.
Don't eat it.
Xiaozhou!
Alright, that's it for today's class.
Yushu will surely get a good beating
from Uncle this time now that he's back.
That's exactly what he was worried about,
so he asked Junxi
to take care of Xiaozhou.
Xiaoyang, are you ready?
Busy bee, want to grab dinner together?
I need to go back
and help Junxi look after the kid.
A kid?
Who did Junxi have the kid with?
It's his nephew.
Just kidding.
Tuo.
Junxi has been having a hard time lately.
Help him more
with taking care of Xiaozhou.
What do you mean?
Xiaozhou.
That's Uncle Tuo's ruler, not a toy.
I don't care.
Walk slowly.
You'll fall.
Don't jump up and down.
It's dangerous.
Alright.
I'm coming to catch you!
Got you!
Pay your rent or get out!
-Who are you?
-Landlord Superman.
Landlord Superman?
Who's the landlord?
You're back.
Let's eat.
Come on.
Let's wash our hands and have dinner.
Okay.
Can you eat by yourself?
Yes, I'm five years old.
Here.
Junxi.
Today in general studies class,
Xiaoyang said...
Uncle.
Let's go to the park after we eat.
Dad always takes me to play in the park.
Alright.
We'll go as soon as you finish eating.
Take your time.
Catch it, Xiaozhou.
Come on.
Here it comes!
Great catch!
Go pick it up.
Come on, go pick it up.
Hurry!
One more time.
Look.
The plane is taking off.
To the left.
Look over there.
[Recording]
Let's wave.
Little brat.
That's mine.
Come on.
Come on, hit me.
Retreating!
I didn't expect you to be so good.
Backup!
Let's switch. I'll catch you.
One more time.
Uncle, give me a kiss.
No kissing.
He's mine.
Mine. Uncle is mine.
Mine!
He's mine!
Uncle, you're mine, right?
What are you saying in front of a kid?
Come on, let's go take a bath.
He's finally asleep.
He's truly an angel when asleep,
but a little devil when awake.
I wonder how Yushu managed
to take care of him alone.
I want some too.
Xiaoyang said you've been
having some issues with your internship.
♪ I am waiting, I am waiting ♪
♪ I am waiting for you ♪
♪ Starlight sparkles all over your face,
you're so beautiful ♪
♪ When love turns into longing, can't get
over you, addicted to your wild side ♪
You haven't
looked at me at all today.
♪ Kissing the romance in the moonlight ♪
♪ The night breeze's so gentle and kind ♪
♪ Baby I am sorry, I am not alright ♪
♪ The love I give is about to overflow ♪
This isn't appropriate, is it?
We'll just keep it down. He won't notice.
♪ Crazy in love with you,
it's my bad, please come back ♪
♪ Just let me zone out ♪
I need to pee.
Uncle.
Uncle, I need to pee.
Uncle, hurry up. I'm about to wet myself.
I need to pee.
Hello?
Yushu, you're coming to
pick up Xiaozhou?
Okay.
See you soon.
Let's go.
Dad really hit you?
Yeah.
He grabbed a stick, trying to beat me up.
Good thing my reflexes were quick.
He only landed one hit.
So that's what happened.
You ungrateful child.
How dare you come back?
I...
Honey, stop it.
Let's go.
We're going back to stay with
Grandpa and Grandma.
Say thank you to Uncles
for taking care of you yesterday.
It was hard work.
That's not true. I was good and brave.
I slept by myself at night.
Unlike Uncles,
who slept hugging each other.
I let Xiaozhou sleep in my room yesterday.
You could have just slept with Xiaozhou.
Why did you go sleep with Tuo?
So you two
have that kind of relationship?
You're overthinking it.
We're just friends.
I see.
Well, we're leaving now.
Goodbye, Uncle. Goodbye, Uncle Tuo.
Bye-bye.
Goodbye.
Alright, let's go.
We're going to see Grandpa and Grandma.
We're leaving.
Bye.
Yushu didn't figure it out, did he?
No, he didn't.
You two have been living together
for almost a month
and only now thought to invite us over?
Everyone's been busy,
and you two have busy schedules, too.
It's alright. Celebrating one month
of living together is nice too.
Junxi, how did Uncle and Auntie
agree to this?
Well...
Don't tell me you told your family
you're just roommates,
learning to be independent or something?
No way! I got it right?
Out of ten couples who live together,
nine use that exact excuse...
-He Youmei!
-So old--
Old-Fashioned.
Just eat your fried chicken.
I'll go get some beers.
Don't mind He Youmei.
She always talks like this.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
You want me to tell you everything,
but what about you?
You never tell me anything.
I don't have anything to tell.
Weren't you being bullied
at your internship?
Did Xiaoyang tell you that?
Was that a message
from your company just now?
[You and Tuo are dating, aren't you?]
I'm so hungry.
It ended before I had my fill.
You're the one to blame,
for talking improperly.
You ruined the party.
I didn't.
They just felt guilty themselves.
It wasn't my fault.
By secretly dating like this,
they're just leaving a backup plan
for their relationship.
They're not deliberately
trying to keep it a secret.
Who knows?
This kind of secrecy always
leads to trouble.
I'm talking from my experience.
If you don't believe me,
just wait and see.
Love that can't be spoken aloud
won't survive challenges.
It's like ice cream—
under the sun, it melts in an instant,
leaving nothing.
He Youmei.
Did something happen to you before?
Scared you, didn't I?
I just read all this in comics.
I'm starving. Let's go get some ramen.
I don't like lying.
If it hurts, it hurts.
If you want to cry, cry.
Smiling and saying you're fine
doesn't make it true.
If I say it hurts,
would you blow on it for me?
Blow on it?
Like this.
Blowing on it won't help.
If you don't face the wound,
it won't disappear or heal.
No matter how many times you blow on it,
it will still hurt.
If you keep acting like this, be careful—
I might fall for you.
You little fool.
Which ramen place do you want to go to?
The internet café.
Are you crying?
No, I'm not.
He Youmei, you crybaby.
I'm not.
Your nose is running.
No, it's not.
Yes, it is.
See for yourself.
I want to eat
something spicy.
The spicy ramen.
Shame on you.
[Don't ignore my texts.
Don't beat around the bush.]
[I have a question.]
[You and Tuo are dating, aren't you?]
[Don't ignore my texts.
Don't beat around the bush.]
[Tell me the truth.]
I told Yushu
that I fell asleep
playing games in your room
and told him not to overthink it.
Or should I say
that I'm used to hugging stuffed toys
when I sleep,
which is why I was hugging you,
and tell him not to have wrong ideas?
Or should I say...
I shouldn't have pressured you.
Tuo.
You're with me
just to go along with what I want
out of pity.
Don't talk nonsense.
[Incoming Call from Mom]
Hello?
Mom.
What?
[Toilet]
Junxi.
This way.
You can't even drink water.
I want some ice cream.
Still thinking about having ice cream
at a time like this?
Mom.
Didn't Dad pass out?
He was already awake
when we got to the hospital.
The doctor said it's gallstones,
and they've scheduled a
minimally invasive surgery for tomorrow.
Yushu.
I've brought Dad's stuff.
Check if anything's missing.
Mom.
I'll stay here with Dad tonight.
Go home and get some rest.
You can come back tomorrow morning.
Right.
My condition isn't serious.
Go back and rest.
But...
No "but"s.
Go home and rest. It's okay.
Alright, alright.
Then you two must
get along peacefully, okay?
No fighting.
I'll come back after class tomorrow.
Dad.
You don't drink enough water.
I'm so busy every day.
When do I have time to drink water?
No one's ever there to help me.
Mom, I'll go get some water.
Okay.
Why do you want to get water?
Your mom just said I can't drink water.
Don't be angry.
Talk nicely.
I'm getting it for Mom.
Get along peacefully.
Alright, stop nagging.
[Ward]
Seems like Yushu hasn't told
Mom and Dad anything yet.
Thank goodness.
What am I even doing?
Dad is sick in the hospital,
yet I'm still worried about myself.
All I can think about is
whether they've realized we're dating.
I...
Sorry.
Why would you say that?
[Ward]
Let's break up.
[In the Next Episode]
Sacrificing yourself for the other's sake.
[Toilet]
How noble, you coward.
Getting angry out of embarrassment?
Why is dating so exhausting?
What if Mom and Dad can't accept it?
Would you still insist on being with Tuo?
Mom.