NO TAIL TO TELL
Thank you.
Are you asleep already?
She must've been really tired.
Man, what on earth am I thinking?
Hey, wake up.
Hey.
What's this?
Why am I suddenly…
- You!
- What's wrong with you?
Didn't you say you lost
that wooden-handled dagger yesterday?
I didn't lose it. It just wasn't there.
Then why was it in your hand?
What? I told you I don't have it.
I saw it. You just used it to--
Just now? What did I do?
You used it to--
You were dead asleep until a second ago.
Why are you suddenly
rambling about the dagger?
Did you have a weird dream or something?
A dream?
I mean, you just woke up
and started talking nonsense.
It wasn't a dream.
It was more like a prophecy…
No, no… wait a second.
I'm not a nine-tailed fox anymore.
I'm just human.
My spiritual power
and abilities are all gone.
And I suddenly see the future?
That's impossible.
So it really was a dream.
Seriously, what are you doing?
I was scared for a second.
Maybe it's because
I'm running on fumes.
What a crappy dream.
What did you dream about anyway?
None of your business.
I don't even want to think about it.
Dream or not, I'm still pissed.
You've got a lot of nerve.
Oh my.
What's her problem?
She's something else.
A real piece of work.
Si-yeol!
Wait for me.
OVERNIGHT WITH THE MOON
GUESTHOUSE
You only have one room left?
Don't be ridiculous.
How could that be?
Who'd even stay in a dump like this?
Only a "dump" like this
would even have a room left.
And you came the night
before the long weekend.
Go somewhere else then.
Please give us a moment.
Come with me.
What is it?
We've been looking for hours,
and this is all there is.
What choice do we have?
Sleep on the street?
Why would I need to?
Instead of this dump,
let's go to a five-star hotel.
Jeez, where would we even get the money?
Let's just stay here for the night.
- No.
- Why not?
It's dirty, cramped, and most of all…
it feels sketchy.
What feels sketchy?
What, me?
What are you even thinking?
You must be joking.
You're centuries older than me.
Give me a break.
- No, it's not that.
- Then what?
It's…
It's just that earlier…
Fine. Let's take it.
I just had a bad dream,
but it's probably nothing.
Let's go.
Seriously, what is wrong with her?
Why did I suddenly have a dream like that?
With the way Si-yeol picks on me,
no wonder I'm having dreams like that.
Jeez.
What… is that?
What? This?
What are you going to do with that?
Get back at me or something?
What are you talking about?
The owner brought this over
so we could have some fruit.
Oh, really?
Oh boy.
I guess you do have a shred of conscience.
What?
I don't know what you dreamed about,
but it's probably just guilt
over how you treated me.
That's not it.
Sure it is.
See? Guilt always catches up with you.
If it's bothering you,
I guess you really are human after all.
Here.
Could that be it?
Being human is such a hassle.
I've lost my appetite.
Oh my gosh.
Do you really think you're up
for another hike tomorrow?
I don't know.
What is that?
Stay still.
That's part of being human.
You get sore when you use muscles
you don't normally use.
You'll get used to it.
I won't need to.
I'll do whatever it takes
to get my old life back.
Here too.
Don't hold back. Put plenty on.
- Nice and cool, right?
- Yeah.
The soles too.
Not there, you dummy.
OVERNIGHT WITH THE MOON
GUESTHOUSE
Oh my.
You're still up?
I'm so sore I can't sleep.
What are you doing out here at this hour,
looking all pathetic?
I've always wanted to try this.
Just having a beer like this at night.
I won't be able to do this
once I have my life back.
Why not? Just go for it.
Life's short enough as it is.
You know what the human body's like now.
If you just do whatever you feel like,
you'll never get to do
what you really want.
It's just one beer.
What difference does it make?
A big one.
An athlete's body
is like a finely tuned machine.
Everything you eat,
how often and when you eat,
and even your sleep cycle all matter.
It all shows
when you're out there on the field.
You're so dramatic.
Are all other humans like you?
No. That's why I'm the best in the world.
What?
Give me one.
Since I'm human now, I want to get drunk.
Why have you never had a drink before?
Does alcohol weaken
a nine-tailed fox's spiritual power?
As if.
No matter how much I drank,
I just couldn't get drunk.
Have you ever seen
any other nine-tailed foxes?
That must be lonely.
I have.
So I wasn't really lonely.
It was just the two of us for a long time.
- Then where is…
- She died.
After becoming human.
I see.
So this is what getting drunk feels like.
It's a bit cold at night.
A fragile human,
still trying to act tough.
You seem to keep forgetting,
but you're just a human woman now.
Oh, I get it.
This is like a human male hitting
on a female. It's called flirting.
Flirt… Are you nuts?
Give it back.
- Give me--
- Hey, no take-backs.
It's nice and warm.
Look, let me be clear.
This is not flirting.
It's called manners, okay?
Don't be shy.
With my looks and charm,
of course you'd fall for me.
I am a nine-tailed fox, after all.
You are unbelievable.
Okay. I'll pretend I didn't notice.
Notice what?
I shouldn't have given you the jacket.
It's so warm.
Do you know the name
of that constellation?
No, what is it?
I'm asking because I don't know.
It's pretty.
EPISODE 5
THE CHANGER, THE CHANGED, AND THE LACKING
Woo-seok.
What are you doing up this late?
I just couldn't sleep.
Couldn't sleep? Why?
Because I'm scared.
It feels like when I wake up,
everything will just vanish.
Like a dream.
Like a mirage.
We'd pass as hikers now, right?
Of course. Let's go get stranded.
Why are there so many people here?
The owner said today's the start
of the long weekend.
We won't get stranded
with this many people around.
One small scream,
and people will swarm in to save us.
Coming through.
Seriously.
This isn't going to work.
We need to go somewhere secluded.
Man, I'm dying here.
How much farther?
In my experience,
we'll end up deep in the woods
if we go a little farther.
We can rest there until nightfall.
Are you okay?
What?
Yeah.
I can't take another step.
I think we're officially stranded.
I couldn't find the trail even if I tried.
I'm so sleepy.
You can't sleep out here.
You'll freeze to death.
- Just a little nap.
- Absolutely not.
Hang on.
Try some of this.
It'll wake you up.
Yes, I think it's working.
That's good.
When is she going to show up?
The sun went down ages ago.
Hey, what if…
What if there's no nine-tailed fox here?
What happens to us then?
What?
I mean,
I was just thinking
that the newspaper article
was from 28 years ago.
Maybe she's become a human like you.
No way.
Becoming human isn't that easy.
Considering I didn't even know
there was a nine-tailed fox here,
she can't be more than 300
or 400 years old.
No way she's turned human yet.
Right?
- Yes.
But…
it's freezing.
Yes.
- Should we--
- Should we head back?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Okay… grab your stuff.
Why do humans have such poor night vision?
I can't see a single thing.
Seriously, where are we?
Oh no.
Can we call those rangers
from yesterday?
I haven't had signal for a while.
Am I really going to die?
Out here? Right after becoming human?
We're not going to die.
I can't die here. I'm Kang Si-yeol.
Si-yeol! Where are you?
Si-yeol!
Si-yeol.
Are you okay? You're not dead, are you?
I'm not dead, but I think I'm done for.
What?
I sprained my ankle.
- Check your phone again.
- Okay.
What?
No!
Do you need help?
Geum-ho?
Is it really you?
How can you be…
All this time, I thought you were dead…
Hey, what's wrong with you?
Do you know me?
What?
How do you know me?
Right. I forget this is what they do.
I was being naive.
You can't be Geum-ho.
She became human and died of old age.
What kind of sick joke is this?
Did I do something wrong?
Are you pretending not to know,
or do you really not know anything?
Just who the hell are you?
Well…
I'm just a fox cultivating myself
in the mountains.
Right. Of course.
This must be the will of Heaven.
And I'm just the fool dancing to the tune.
Hey, where are you going?
Don't follow me!
It's dangerous that way.
That's not a trail humans use.
She said it's dangerous.
What's wrong with you?
I told you not to follow me.
Hey! You--
That little…
Show yourself. I know you're watching!
Come out right now!
Stop hiding like a coward and face me!
Why do I have to be human?
And why is a nine-tailed fox that looks
just like Geum-ho showing up now?
Who the hell is she?
What do you want from me?
What are you doing?
I sprained my ankle earlier.
I need to catch up to her fast.
It should feel better now.
Is this fun for you?
Treating me like your toy?
Right.
I bet I'm just a pawn on your chessboard.
Setting up all these schemes
and messing with someone's fate
is just how you do things.
But you know,
I've got my own way of doing things.
I just ignore everything you say
and do whatever the hell I want.
You already knew that.
I don't know why you turned me human
or what you want from me,
and I don't even know why you sent
someone who looks just like Geum-ho.
But whatever your plan is,
I'm not playing along.
I'll fight back with everything I've got.
Hey!
Hey.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
You scared me. Seriously, you're…
It's cold out.
Hey, you.
Go start a fire or something.
Excuse me?
- Got anything to eat?
- Oh! Just a moment.
What was that about earlier?
Nothing. Just a misunderstanding.
A misunderstanding?
You made a scene like that
over a misunderstanding?
That's right.
Oh, come on.
That was way too dramatic.
If that nine-tailed fox
had a nasty temper like yours,
we'd be dead by now.
What's wrong with my temper?
I'm just saying we're the ones
who need help right now.
Why pick a fight
when we should be sucking up to her?
You're the one
who needs to suck up to her, not me.
And I didn't start the fight.
The ones above are
picking a fight with me.
What are you talking about?
I told you last night.
There was another nine-tailed fox
that I lived with for a very long time.
And?
That fox is the spitting image of her.
I knew her for centuries,
and yet even I was fooled for a moment.
Right after I become human,
I run into a fox
who looks exactly like her.
That's no coincidence.
They must be up to something.
It feels like they're just
openly toying with me,
and it pisses me off.
Well,
let's not overcomplicate things.
Keep it simple.
What? How?
Let's solve my problem first.
So even if you're annoyed,
just suck it up and be nice to her.
If she refuses my wish,
are you going to take responsibility?
- You little--
- Hey…
Here, have some of this.
What is this?
This is Fischer's ragwort, that's mugwort,
wild chives, spring cabbage,
coastal hog fennel, shepherd's purse--
That's not what I mean.
You want us to eat this raw?
I washed them in the stream.
Gosh, I guess you're a vegetarian.
Is this what you normally live on?
What are you, a goat?
I'm a fox.
I mean, why would a fox
live on just greens?
Did your mountain god say
you can't self-cultivate if you eat meat?
Not really. I mean, I've lived
on this mountain for so long.
So whenever I try to hunt animals,
it turns out I either know them
or know someone who does.
I can't exactly eat my friend's
great-great-granddaughter.
True.
- What?
- Hey, that's not important.
This is great. So fresh.
You know, I eat a ton of salad too.
Look at that!
We have so much in common.
Please, eat up.
All right, enough.
Stop stalling and tell her why we're here.
Right.
The thing is,
we didn't exactly get lost.
We actually came here looking for you.
Looking for me? Why?
Because I have a wish.
What is this?
What's happening?
You can't just do this all of a sudden.
How can you do this?
HYEON WOO-SEOK, MY STORY
What's happening?
It didn't work.
Excuse me?
I just tried, but it didn't work.
Why didn't it work?
Something was just happening!
Why did it stop?
Well, actually, I--
Just how old are you?
How long have you been a nine-tailed fox?
About 500 years.
Then why can't you pull this off?
I've never done anything like this,
so I didn't even know it was possible.
Well, can't you just
teach her how to do it?
- No, I can't.
- Why not?
She doesn't have enough spiritual power.
It's not about technique.
Come on, that makes no sense.
She healed my ankle just fine.
She was teleporting all over the place!
So why can't she do this?
You can't compare a fate-altering spell
to those cheap party tricks.
Jeez.
Beats me why
a 500-year-old nine-tailed fox
has so little spiritual power.
Well, the thing is--
No… no, this can't be real.
Look.
Just try it one more time. Please.
Maybe it'll work this time.
Well…
It won't matter how many times she tries.
She lacks power. Were you not listening?
Does this not matter to you?
Whose fault is it that I'm in this mess?
Do I look like I'm having fun right now?
I'm in this mess because of you!
You're blaming me?
Obviously.
I should've just let you die back then.
- Hey!
- What?
Please don't fight--
- This is all your fault.
- What?
You're a nine-tailed fox.
How can you be this useless?
Well, actually, I'm not a nine-tailed fox.
What? Come again?
I kept trying to tell you,
but you kept cutting me off.
What? Then what are you?
I'm not a nine-tailed fox.
I'm an eight-tailed fox.
Eight tails.
What?
CALL
SI-YEOL
The person you are calling is unavailable…
What? Why is his phone off?
What the hell is going on?
Five, six, seven,
eight.
There really are only eight.
I should have known.
No wonder she seemed a bit lacking.
What is an eight-tailed fox anyway?
I've never heard of anything like that.
If a nine-tailed fox has nine tails,
what do you think an eight-tailed fox is?
A fox with eight tails.
You know that's not what I meant.
They all start out pretty much the same.
Just an ordinary fox
who suddenly starts thinking.
"Why are they human,
while I am nothing but a beast?"
"How can I become something more?"
Once a fox reaches that enlightenment
and begins to cultivate themselves,
they start to shed their animal form
and become closer to a human.
For centuries,
as their enlightenment grows,
they gain one tail after another.
So, since she's missing a tail,
she's still more beast than human.
She hasn't trained enough
to be a true nine-tailed fox.
How do you know so much about this?
Because I went through it myself.
All that waiting.
All those years of dreaming.
Pardon?
I was a nine-tailed fox
until just a few days ago.
Though now I'm stuck being human.
Wait, so what happens now?
What about me?
Can't I go back to the way I was?
We'll have to find another way.
Since she's clearly--
It's you. The one I've been waiting for.
What?
I've been waiting for you to come.
For over 200 years, sis.
What are you talking about?
The mountain god told me before he left
that someone would come
to take care of me.
You think that's me?
Yes! Though I didn't think
it'd take 200 years.
Still, since you came all this way--
I think you've got the wrong idea.
Please tell me, sis.
How can I become human like you?
What?
I want to become human
as soon as possible.
Wait.
Where did that nice nine-tailed fox go?
Or was it an eight-tailed fox?
"Nice nine-tailed fox"?
Then am I the bad nine-tailed fox?
Where did she go, anyway?
Who cares? She probably went on her way.
I'm tired. Let's head back down.
Is it all right to just leave
without saying goodbye?
I mean, isn't she your kin or something?
Why say goodbye
when we won't see each other again?
Are you going to stay and live here?
Okay, fine. Let's go.
Man…
Don't go off alone. It's dangerous.
Hurry up.
Are you changing hotels again today?
Damn it.
Yes.
Today's the chairman's birthday.
Shouldn't you at least attend the dinner?
Forget it.
It's not like anyone wants me there.
Did you look into what I asked for?
Well, Mr. Lee.
Is what you're looking for
the name of some organization?
What the hell are you talking about?
I said, the nine-tailed fox.
You know, the fox with nine tails.
Didn't I tell you to find out everything
about the nine-tailed fox?
Mr. Lee, those things aren't real.
What are you talking about? You saw it.
You were right there with me.
I was?
Hey… pull over, you bastard.
Never mind. Just leave.
Mr. Lee--
I said get out.
You probably think I'm crazy too,
and you won't even bother looking into it.
Mr. Lee, if word gets out
that you're looking into such things--
I get it, so please leave
and stop wasting your time on a nutcase.
Hey, wait!
Just… hold on.
Who are you people?
I've seen that bastard somewhere before.
Is he actually dying?
That's it.
I knew he looked familiar.
Secretary Choi.
Look into the records of the car accident
from nine years ago.
Pardon?
The kid I hit with my car.
Find out everything about who he is,
where he lives, and what he's doing.
Hey.
Did you have to be so harsh yesterday?
How can I become human like you?
I want to become human
as soon as possible.
Shut your mouth before I shut it for you.
How dare you say that to me
wearing that face?
- But sis--
- Don't call me that.
I don't know who you were waiting for,
but it isn't me.
I have no desire to help you in that way.
But still…
Whatever you choose to do with your life
has nothing to do with me.
So leave me out of it.
I can barely take care of myself as it is.
Do you understand me?
You're not the one I've been missing.
So I don't need to feel
like I owe you anything.
So don't ever show up
in front of me again.
She seemed hurt,
seeing how she left
without a word this morning.
You don't seem
to understand the situation.
We just got played.
We came all this way,
suffered through hell,
and now we're leaving empty-handed.
I guess so, but…
True, who am I to worry?
I'm a mess myself.
So, what's the plan now?
I'm going to go back
and dig through some old texts.
"Old texts"? Like, ancient books?
Yes, there are books on secret methods
for situations like this.
Oh, really now?
You don't remember any
off the top of your head?
How would I remember something
I read centuries ago?
Man, the international break
is coming up soon.
I really need to switch back soon.
Who cares about
some stupid ball game right now?
It is important.
It's an international match.
A game for the national team.
Honestly, aren't you
a Korean nine-tailed fox?
Where's your patriotism?
I've been around longer than Korea has.
Look, I don't know if you identify
with Joseon or Goryeo,
but we're still one people.
We are different species.
Don't give me that "one people" crap.
Come on, Ok-sun.
What? I'm not Ok-sun.
But I saw your ID at the police station.
- Your name isn't Eun-ho. It's Kim Ok-sun.
- I told you, it's not Kim Ok-sun!
- That damn old geezer just put whatever--
- That's just a typical grandma name.
Why be embarrassed about it, Ok-sun?
My grandma's name is Kim Bok-sun.
I'm not embarrassed.
I'm telling you, Ok-sun is…
My name is Eun-ho!
All right, I'll just call you Eun-ho.
- Ok-sun.
- Hey!
Why are you yelling, Ok-sun?
You'll burst my eardrums.
I'm not Ok-sun!
All right, Eun-ho.
I'll call you Eun-ho, okay?
- Ok-sun.
- It's Eun-ho!
That damn old geezer, seriously.
What is it, Si-yeol? What's wrong with it?
We're out of gas.
So put some in.
Look, I was debating whether
to tell you this, but…
What?
My wallet's gone.
- What?
- Listen.
I think it fell out
when I rolled down the mountain.
Then what do we do now?
Hey, here comes one.
What a rude bastard.
When I turn back into a nine-tailed fox,
I'll catch him and just…
We can't even call the insurance company
since my phone's dead.
Si-yeol, let's just walk.
What?
Walk home? Do you know how far that is?
Then are we just going
to stand here like this?
Start walking.
Look, we can't walk there.
Why not?
In the old days,
even frail little scholars
crossed mountains and rivers
to take their exams.
- Aren't you an athlete?
- Jeez.
I'm not talking about me.
I'm talking about you.
You can't use skills
like earth-folding anymore.
Please.
I've hiked Seoraksan Mountain twice
in this human body.
We must be near Seoul anyway.
It can't be much farther.
I give up.
So, what's your plan going forward?
What do you mean?
You're completely broke right now.
In the human world,
you can't do a single thing without money.
I don't know.
It's not like
I'll be stuck this way forever.
What about dinner tonight? And tomorrow?
- Are you going to let me starve?
- I'm sure there's cash at home.
I can't be completely broke.
Wait a second.
Don't you have a ton of money?
What?
Think about how much
you ripped me off just a few days ago.
You couldn't have spent it all already.
I still have it.
There we go then.
Let's just use that for now.
I'll pay you back
once I switch back to my old life.
- But it's at my house.
- Okay, let's go get it.
Actually, we can just crash
at your place for a while.
You saw the state of my place.
Yours has to be better than that.
Sorry, but we can't go to my house.
My house is halfway up
Myohyangsan Mountain.
Your house is halfway up a mountain?
Then I guess we'll just grab the cash
and find another place to stay.
I said, it's on Myohyangsan Mountain.
Okay, so what?
Is it really high up?
Higher than Seoraksan Mountain?
Don't you know where
Myohyangsan Mountain is?
GWANGHWAMUN
THE CLEAR WATERS OF BAEKDU
North Korea?
Your house is in North Korea?
Yes.
Myohyangsan Mountain is in North Korea?
And your house is hidden up there?
You heard me.
Why live there when there are
so many decent mountains around?
I was born there.
Myohyangsan Mountain
has always been my home.
It's humans who put up
barbed wire wherever they pleased.
Why take it out on me?
But you make all your money in the South.
Why didn't you just buy a house in Seoul?
Did you forget I could use earth-folding?
It's a dozen steps from home to Gangnam,
so why would I bother?
You can't be serious!
Seriously.
Isn't there any other way?
Right, what if we ask
that eight-tailed fox from yesterday?
We could just ask her to go get the money.
No one can find that place but me.
I put up a barrier.
A barrier painstakingly made
to evade the eyes of the deities.
You think some dimwitted eight-tailed fox
could get through that?
Give me a break.
You're no help at all, ever.
Gosh, Si-yeol.
How much longer do we have to walk?
My legs are killing me.
We haven't even been walking
for 30 minutes.
We have another 12 hours to go.
Jeez, this damn human body
is the absolute worst.
What's going on?
Why does it sting so much?
Be careful.
Just because it's not summer
doesn't mean you can't get sunburned.
We don't even have money for sunscreen.
Si-yeol, look at this.
Doesn't this work
just as well as sunscreen?
Still, you look ridiculous.
So you're not going to use it?
All right, give it here. I'll hold it.
See? Better than nothing, right?
I guess so.
Anyway, how much longer do we have to go?
You just asked.
Now it's 11 hours and 59 minutes.
What…
RESIDENT REGISTRATION CARD
KANG SI-YEOL
This guy…
Is that you, sis?
Is it really you? You came back?
Are we there yet?
Almost.
Good thing we met
a decent human along the way.
I seriously thought I was going to die.
When I get back to normal,
I'll have to bless that human
with a winning lottery ticket.
That's a good idea.
I wonder if he likes soccer.
I was thinking of giving him
tickets to the Champions League final.
I'm hungry.
You know, come to think of it,
you must've made connections
with quite a few humans over the years.
People may have forgotten me,
but it's not the same for you.
By any chance,
isn't there anyone you can ask for help?
There isn't.
Why not? There must be people
whose wishes you granted.
You said you hand-pick your clients.
Aren't they all as rich as I am?
They're rich.
They've got both money and power.
So? Let's go ask them for help.
We can pay them back double later.
I've felt this for a while,
but for a human, you sure seem clueless
about your own kind.
Like how you blindly trusted your friend.
What are you trying to say now?
I never trust humans.
Especially the ones with money and power.
You know why they grovel
and suck up to me?
It's only because I have power.
If they find out I've lost my power,
they'll try to get back at me somehow.
Humans forget favors quickly
but hold on to grudges forever.
Come on, surely not all of them?
There must be some
you're on good terms with.
Do you really think so?
I guess not.
You probably bullied them
the same way you did me.
I tamed them.
So they're easier to handle.
Anyway, I have to be more careful
with those who know who I am.
So watch your mouth, got it?
That's why you should've been
a little nicer all along.
What?
I said I'm hungry.
Jeez.
Seriously, what is going on?
Why isn't Si-yeol at home
or picking up his phone?
Tell me about it.
How can he borrow a car
and then ghost us for two days?
You don't think something happened
to Si-yeol, do you?
No way.
I'm the one with the problem, damn it.
I've got early morning
deliveries but no car.
You can take my car again today.
Your car is so embarrassing to drive.
Everyone stares at it.
Jeong-bae has a nice car.
Why are you embarrassed?
That's why it's embarrassing.
If it were just an expensive car,
I wouldn't be complaining.
But who drives a supercar
for an early morning delivery gig?
Plus, the gas mileage just sucks.
After paying for gas,
I make basically nothing.
But you know
my baby only takes premium, right?
I know, you jerk. Jeez!
But seriously,
don't you find that car uncomfortable?
What kind of car doesn't have a back seat?
Right? It costs a fortune,
but it's only half a car.
It's only got two doors too.
You rich kids…
Hey, take a look at this.
It hit the upper limit twice.
Just look at this stock.
It's going to bottom out,
then bounce back.
Just tell your grandma
to invest a little until then.
Thank you.
For now,
let's go inside and get some rest.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Woo-seok.
I'm sorry.
It took me so long.
Wait, how are you even here?
He probably ran his ass off in a panic.
I see you were together.
Why? Does that make you twice as nervous?
Seeing me next to Si-yeol?
Si-yeol.
I was blinded by greed and crossed a line.
I should've asked you face-to-face.
Honestly,
these past few days felt like a dream.
The life I never even dared to dream of
became mine in an instant.
- Woo-seok--
- I know.
It's all yours. It's your life.
I know I shouldn't be
doing this to you.
But just for one week.
If a month is too long, how about a week?
Let me play just one
international match next week.
Do whatever you want.
What?
It's not like we'll stay switched forever.
Spending a few days in your life…
wasn't so bad.
I've never had a chance to properly rest.
I'll just think of it as a break.
Really? You mean it?
Let's keep it like this for now.
That way, you won't have any regrets.
But when I say we need to switch,
we switch right away.
You can promise me that, right?
Yes, of course.
Thank you, Si-yeol.
I seriously won't forget this favor.
Sis, I found a way!
It's going to take some time,
but I found a way for you to turn back
into a nine-tailed fox.
Okay, let's talk about it later.
That means he can
go back to his life too, right?
Right?
NO TAIL TO TELL
You found a way?
What if I become a nine-tailed fox?
Then I'll have powers too,
so we can just switch our fates.
I think I should meet this Hyeon Woo-seok.
You've invited quite the ghost in.
So there's a chance we can't switch back
if that method doesn't work?
So doing good deeds
builds up spiritual power, right?
But how long will that take?
- Usually, it takes about 100 years.
- A hundred years?
Brace yourself.
We'll be slammed starting tomorrow.
Subtitle translation by Susanna Kim