(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
STILL SHINING
Please let me say goodbye
to Tae-seo in person before I go.
I know you guys don't come out
when it gets cold.
But still…
Mo Eun-a.
STILL SHINING
All the places in this town look the same
no matter how far you go.
Are we even getting close?
The fireflies…
I know they don't come out
when it's cold, but…
What are you…
doing here?
Hey, isn't that Tae-seo?
Tae-seo!
Im A-sol, get out.
Tae-seo, you drive instead!
You know where the restaurant is!
The road here is really confusing!
I'm tired!
I drove all the way here!
I'm so tired!
Who is he talking with?
I'm cold!
Come on.
Gosh.
He hasn't changed one bit.
I used to take really good care of him.
People thought he was my brother.
He looks more like me, not Tae-seo.
What are you talking about?
He's clearly a cuter version of Tae-seo.
I get that a lot.
We just have different vibes.
A-sol, let me pour you a glass.
Thank you for inviting us.
-It looks delicious.
-Right?
They have the best seafood ramyeon
and aged kimchi here.
They only bring out
the aged kimchi for me.
Tae-seo left Seoul right away
for your sake.
He didn't hesitate at all.
Now that I'm here, I can see why.
When he was in Seoul,
he always looked so worn out.
But here, the ocean's right there,
the sky's clear, and the air's fresh.
Man, it's nice here.
Wait, so that's what you meant.
"My dad looks at the sky at work,
and my mom looks
at the sky and ocean at work."
He said it was
the best job in the universe.
That's what Mom used to say.
You still remember it, Tae-seo?
Of course, he does.
Man, you were on crutches
the last time I saw you.
You walk so well now. I'm proud.
Come on. That's ancient history.
-Is your dad doing well?
-More than well.
Hey, come on.
You need to drive us back to Seoul.
I need to visit the hospital.
Tae-seo.
Just go.
Your guests came all the way here.
You should take them back to Seoul.
Even Hyeong-seok's here,
and he never comes.
You're making it awkward for him to drink.
Did you miss me that much,
my little brother?
Have a drink.
You can even drink now.
You're all grown up.
Oh, come on.
The lights on the bicycle were broken.
The girl on the bicycle earlier
was your ex, right?
So she lives in Gangneung.
She doesn't.
Then, where does she live?
I don't know.
Why did she come here?
So you didn't get to talk to her.
You must be frustrated and curious.
MO EUN-A
Why were you in Yeonwoo…
Tae-seo's here.
Yes, I'm here.
You must be having such a hard time.
Get plenty of rest
while you're on leave from the military.
What's this?
At least tell me if you're coming.
I didn't even eat before I came here.
Did you get to talk with Grandma?
She talked about
when I was in the military.
She'd always talk about
my middle school days.
Time must've passed for her.
Have you seen Eun-a
from the house at the end?
Why suddenly mention that name?
I thought I saw her.
I don't want you being pathetic.
Just live an ordinary life.
Get married and have kids.
Come visit from time to time.
Is that too much to ask?
I'm going to live alone,
and then send our grandparents off
to be with Mom and Dad.
I'll do all of that.
Did you see her or not?
You didn't even answer me.
I'm off.
Hold on, please.
Eun-a should be here by now,
but she's late.
She went out with that old, beat-up bike.
You need to hurry and find her.
Right.
What are you doing here?
I came to take a quick look
around our school.
I had no idea it had closed down.
Not that.
Why here? In Yeonwoo.
Are you staying here for good?
No, just for a bit.
I'm going to stay with Park So-hyeon.
This is great.
Even though I was worried
about running into you here,
I still wanted to tell you
that I was leaving to live with So-hyeon.
I wanted to say a quick goodbye
and tell you in person too.
And now, I got to do that.
My bicycle lights are broken.
You can follow me from behind then.
This is great.
I was worried
I'd have to push my bicycle back.
Remember the fork in the road
where we always used to split up?
Let's say goodbye there.
I really wanted to do this with you.
This is great.
When are you leaving?
Soon.
Since we've met,
let's say goodbye.
I really wanted to do that with you.
Bye, then.
I'm off.
It's me.
I know.
Nothing happened, right?
I…
I left you alone
with that colleague of yours.
It didn't cause trouble for you, right?
Why…
Why are you worried about me?
There's no need.
You had absolutely
nothing to worry about.
There was no need…
I guess so.
I can still picture that field
in my mind clearly,
so I wondered
if you'd finished things properly.
I wondered if leaving a place
you had poured your heart and soul into
wasn't too hard on you.
I wondered why you were
always forced to leave
when you never wanted to.
There was no need,
but I kept wondering.
Why is Park So-hyeon your mom?
Actually,
it's more that her mom is my grandmother.
She's a good person.
You didn't make a bad decision
because you felt trapped, right?
-When you feel trapped--
-No, Tae-seo.
I went to Tongyeong.
Your guesthouse was closed,
and I was told you had gone to your mom's.
I thought it was the mom
who lives far away
and likes noodles.
We missed each other.
We're really good at that.
OLD HOUSE IM A-SOL
I should hang up.
Granny's going to wake up.
Bye.
Eun…
Including meetings and a year-end party,
I had three events to attend.
The venue was around here,
so I just stopped by.
Were you drinking?
Yeah, just a little.
Sorry.
No need to apologize for drinking.
Should I go?
If you're tired, I'll go.
Let's go out for a drink.
I need to talk to you.
I wanted to finish what we were watching.
Sure.
I saw a bungeoppang place on the way here.
But there was nowhere to park.
I'll go buy you some.
You can sit.
Okay.
This is nice.
It's nice to relax together like this
after a crazy day at work.
Just one sip.
I can leave my car here.
Focus.
HAE-JIN
Hi, Eun-a.
Sorry for calling you at this hour.
It's kind of urgent.
Could you cover for me
for just three hours tomorrow?
You just need to check in
one guest at 3:00 p.m.
Gosh, sorry about the wait.
There was just so much traffic today.
Look at you dressed all properly
for just a few hours of work.
You're such a professional.
What do you want to eat?
It's my treat, so let's go.
I've got a bus to catch.
Did you really just come to help me out?
I'm touched.
You sure you're not here to see someone?
There is someone, right?
I knew it.
If you came to see them, you should.
I did.
Someone I wanted to see,
even for a moment.
I already saw him.
YEON NAMSAN
So-hyeon.
I might arrive later than planned.
I'll get back to you.
This is where I stop.
Trying to make things work,
intruding into your peaceful life,
and repeating this vicious cycle.
Enough.
Are you crazy?
Do you know how much the fees would be
if you canceled your flight now?
At the hotel you worked at ten years ago,
your former coworker
is now the assistant manager.
They're all waiting for you to come back,
not to mention my mom.
Everyone's waiting for you.
I'll go as planned.
I'll keep my promise.
Dad.
When you told me to live freely,
as if I was on a journey,
you meant that in life,
we can't stay even when we want to.
Things seem like they'll last forever,
but they don't.
And since life is full of such things,
when it's time to leave,
you meant I should just take off,
as if I was on a journey.
Now at age 30, I finally understand this.
MISSED CALL
EUN-A
MART
It's cold outside.
Give me one second.
When my dad and I first came here,
we had just one bag with us.
It's in the main bedroom dresser.
It should be in the bottom drawer.
It's a backpack that you use for hiking.
Can you get it for me?
Is this the one?
Yeah, it is.
This should be enough to take with me.
I thought I wouldn't be able
to take anything from here.
But I got something thanks to you.
You've never been
in our kitchen before, right?
This is the best part of our house.
I'm sure you didn't call
to show me your kitchen.
I went to Seoul
because I had something to do.
And since it's Seoul,
Yeon Namsan was right there…
I thought of you, so I called.
I called without even thinking,
but now that I see you here,
I think I know why I did that.
I guess I wanted to do this with you.
Let's go over there.
This is yours.
I finally got to offer you some tea.
I'm…
leaving on Friday.
That's pretty soon.
You were right. I felt trapped,
so Park So-hyeon became my mom.
That's what it took for me to allow that.
But to put it differently,
I was able to make up my mind
thanks to you.
I'd been thinking for a while
that maybe I should accept her as family.
My dad at least left me Park So-hyeon
before he left.
That's how I see it now.
I'm saying it's not your fault.
It's thanks to you.
That's how I've always felt about you.
It's all thanks to you in the end.
But you probably feel
the exact opposite about me.
If you go…
will you come back?
Right now,
I don't plan to.
Where will you be living?
At Park So-hyeon's mom's place.
The lady who'll become my grandmother.
They don't live together.
What about work?
I can work right away too.
Park So-hyeon told me
the hotel I worked at ten years ago
is waiting for me to return,
so I should go.
It's kind of amazing
that they still remember me.
I liked it there.
But…
If I hadn't gone there…
If I hadn't left…
That's all I kept thinking about
for the past ten years.
But I think I can finally go back now.
You'll have a place to stay,
your grandmother will be there,
and you'll have a job.
Why…
did you go to Tongyeong?
I couldn't understand
why things were like this between us.
Everything felt wrong.
You had every reason to do that.
My decision when I was 20 was wrong,
but yours was right.
Do you realize
we're worried about each other right now?
Because for us,
we can't make things hard for each other.
No matter where we are.
You're the only one in the world
who's like that.
I told you I logged into your account
and listened to music twice.
Both times happened here.
PLAYLIST
It was December.
I had caught a cold after shoveling
all the snow in the village.
I had decided on interning in Hawaii.
And I had finally accepted
that we broke up.
Then, when I gave up on everything
in Tongyeong and came here,
even before leaving for Seoul…
When I logged into your account…
Look at me.
…it felt like I was looking at you.
Even when I'm far away,
if I need to borrow your strength,
I'm logging into your account.
You don't mind, right?
If you go there,
will you smile like that?
I don't like her.
She's so cheerful,
completely unaware of what's ahead.
I like her.
Then…
I should try to be like her.
I'll do that.
I should go.
Eun-a, let's eat.
It makes me so happy to cook for you.
I'm done. There's a lot of things
to do around here.
What are you going to do today?
I'm going to drop by my house.
I just want to clean the kitchen.
You're going to go inside?
Just the kitchen.
Okay, already. I'll come visit.
-Thanks for everything.
-All the best.
It's been a pleasure.
I thought this would be
an invalid number by now.
Dong-sik told me you're leaving Korea.
I'm leaving soon.
If you have something to say, go ahead.
I'm sure you resent me.
I'm not really one to talk,
but back then, I thought you'd abandoned
the guesthouse you loved
because of that guy.
I was so angry,
wondering what my efforts were all for.
But once I'd calmed down…
-Back then--
-I didn't plan to go there and meet him.
I really did run into him
by chance in Seoul.
And I tried my best to bring
what I'd started to a proper close.
Not that you'd believe me.
Is that what you wanted to say?
To be fair, running into people happens.
You remember the girl I went out with?
Your roommate during your intern days.
I remember.
She said how you looked
in your hotel uniform
and in regular clothes
was really different.
She said you didn't look good
in regular clothes. It was ridiculous.
You said the same thing back then.
You said that excuse was ridiculous.
I ran into someone I dated in Gangneung
all the way in Geoje Island.
It does happen.
In all my life,
you were the first person
who listened to me so attentively
and respected what I said.
And I'm nobody special.
You're someone I care enough
to worry about.
I'm relieved you're going to live
with Park So-hyeon.
When I left this job,
I was wondering why I felt so empty.
It was because
you had been there at every step.
Without your feedback,
I found myself without dreams or anything.
I'd planned to just get by in life,
but I ended up pushing myself
to keep up with you.
For those ten years of my life…
only you know how hard I worked.
I'll vouch for that.
I'll be the one to vouch
for how you gave it everything you had.
That's enough for me.
Take care.
You too.
Actually, saying goodbye
over the phone isn't so bad.
Thank you,
Seong-chan.
Thank you too.
Bye.
Please come over here.
Happy New Year.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
NOVEMBER 9, 2024
Is a half-open drawer
really that big a deal?
Is this…
Is this supposed to be…
this painful?
Dad can barely breathe,
as if he's running a marathon,
and here you are complaining…
I'm on my way.
No, it's fine.
Let's not meet up today.
Owner of car 2017?
Hello? Anyone home?
A-sol?
What's wrong?
I need to get my car out,
but no one's answering.
Hi, Mom. I'm busy right now,
so I'll call you back…
Yeah.
No, I'm not busy. I'll be right there.
Mom, don't cry.
Okay, bye.
The car…
Tell them to move it.
I need to go to my dad right away.
A-sol.
He's okay for now.
My mom said he'll have bouts like this,
and then recover again,
so she asked me to bring some clothes.
Is there anything I can do?
I left it at your house.
But I wasn't expecting this.
You'll see when you go home.
I took it there
so you could work on it slowly,
but I think you'll have to hurry.
Okay.
I'll get going.
Tae-seo.
A few days ago,
that person with the bicycle…
She came to your house.
All I had to do was pick up my car,
but I went up to your house like a fool
and entered the passcode.
When I went back down, she wasn't there.
I must've been out of my mind.
I'm sorry.
Tae-seo.
It's my turn to hear it.
I really need to be ready now.
I don't have…
I don't have much time.
Tell me what you want to thank me for
right now.
I want to hear it now.
Do you want to take a walk?
The reason
why I'm grateful to you is,
thanks to you,
I can now hope for a warm goodbye.
As you know…
If the three moments of waiting
that are needed to make a frame
can all be done in a day…
-That thing I mentioned before…
-You mean my name tag?
JULY 2014
Thanks.
MAEUM STUDY CENTER
…I'll believe
that the sincere and heartfelt support
I gave you back then
went around and found its way back to me.
Please use hanji for the mat
and oak for the frame.
I want it to feel like my dad's face
is being warmly embraced.
I'm counting on you.
The snow has let up.
It seems it was snowing earlier
for your grandma.
Hui-seo's grandma's memory
keeps coming and going?
They said her brain is still recovering.
For now, her memory will be mixed up,
but it'll come back again.
When you get old,
ten years ago feels like yesterday,
and yesterday feels distant.
Your mind is all over the place.
They're coming.
Where is she?
I'm right here.
Welcome back.
Where's Eun-a?
Eun-a is from ten years ago.
Hwa-sun.
What do you want with Eun-a?
Eun-a.
Eun-a!
Give me your hands.
Gosh, you were clearing the snow.
Are you all right?
To her, today's the day
you cleared the snow.
You think Tae-seo made it there, okay?
Gosh, I don't know. I'm worried.
You cleared all the snow from our truck.
We had to send Tae-seo off
to the military all on his own.
There was nothing we could do.
Did it hurt?
It hurt really badly,
but I'm all better now.
That's good.
Well done.
I heard you're going to Hawaii.
Have a safe trip.
We'll check in on your dad often
so he doesn't feel too lonely.
I meant to tell you this.
It's been weighing on my heart.
Thank you.
Grandma?
It's me, Tae-seo.
You remember me, right?
Why wouldn't I remember you?
I'm back home safe and sound.
Eun-a!
My grandma's back.
-Not from ten years ago. From right now.
-What?
Get on.
It's right now. The present!
Yeah, I understand.
The Hangang River
has a lot of bridges, doesn't it?
It's so long.
You run there every day?
I'm usually sitting down
when I'm operating trains,
so it's a way for me to exercise.
Right. Good idea.
You need to look after your health
while you work.
Goodness, Eun-a!
How are you?
Eun-a. Gosh, Eun-a.
Welcome back.
You haven't changed one bit.
You're the same as well.
I'll redo your scarf for you.
Wrap it round and around, and then tie it.
There. Nice and warm.
Everyone here worried about you so much.
It's so good that you came back.
Well done.
I'll see you off tomorrow.
Let's say goodbye in person.
-Granny.
-Yeah?
You have to live well even without me.
It'll feel empty when I'm suddenly gone.
You're right.
It's been like a picnic lately,
eating and sleeping together every day.
But after a picnic,
you need to go live your life.
You can't keep pining for it forever.
You're right.
Thanks, Granny.
Let's take a photo.
-A photo?
-Yeah.
Photos look nicer with plants.
-I'm going to look at this every day.
-Okay.
Smile and say "Eun-a."
Mo Eun-a.
So beautiful.
I'm going to look at this photo every day.
I'll come to Dongjak Station.
Dongjak Station to Incheon is too short.
YEON NAMSAN
These are the views
from my everyday routine.
You wanted to see them too.
I'm…
going to do what we talked about together.
You're the reason I could make up my mind,
so I'll wait for you there.
You should go there,
be loved and appreciated,
and live a great life.
And when you ever feel like
thinking about a future that includes me,
let me know.
Let's say goodbye here.
Thank you for seeing me off.
This is…
the first time
we're saying goodbye in person.
Goodbye then.
Goodbye.
I love you,
Mo Eun-a.
Ladies and gentlemen, the next station is…
Please take a moment
to look out the window.
An ordinary view from our lives
may become an unforgettable brilliance
that could lead you somewhere,
somehow,
and to someone.
I hope that today
was another meaningful day
where you followed
the shining light within you.
You did a wonderful job
getting through the day.
The next station is…
1 YEAR LATER
CHEONGGYEONG STATION
MO EUN-A
Where we'll be…
-What we'll be doing…
-And with who.
STILL SHINING
Subtitle translation by: Hyesoo Lee