[BELL RINGING]
BOYD:
Previously on
From...
All you fucking do
is knock on our doors,
knock on our fucking windows!
You wanna play games?
Come get me!
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
My blood is your blood now,
motherfucker.
[SCREECHING]
You really did it,
you killed one of them.
TABITHA:
All this time,
I thought the children
were trying to scare me, but...
what if they're just
asking for my help?
Though Victor said his mother
wanted to rescue the children
locked in the tower.
I'm sorry.
This is the only way.
[SCREAMING]
Are you deaf?
I said, get the--
Where did you get that?
You're Victor's father.
HENRY:
My wife, Miranda,
started seeing things.
She said it was like
she'd been chosen
to free the children.
[SCREAMING]
[HORN HONKS]
But there's a town up ahead!
You just need to keep
going forward! Please!
[SCREECHES]
[GRUNTS]
Victor.
I didn't know
how to get home.
[VICTOR CRIES]
The Boy in White was
trying to tell Christopher
that to save the children,
he would have to
go through the tree.
Christopher wouldn't
go in the tree,
so I told my mother
what the Boy in White said.
It was my fault.
I was the reason
that she died.
She was trying
to protect you.
That's my job now.
We thought you were dead.
Your children
thought you were dead.
You owe it to your kids
to be here now.
This place
wants us to be scared.
How we take care of each other,
and how we always do our best,
that's what matters.
You're not pregnant.
I am pregnant!
I can feel it!
I'm not eating garbage
because I'm afraid!
It's making me!
Whatever is inside me,
it's getting stronger.
Help me, Elgin.
I can save all of you.
I can help you go back home.
FATIMA: Elgin, please!
Fatima's baby
is going to save all of us.
He's not gonna
tell you where she is.
You said that you weren't
gonna let this place break you.
This place has won.
[GRUNTS]
[SCREAMING]
What the fuck are you doing?
Boyd doesn't understand
how far he needs to go.
Sara--
She's in the root cellar.
BOYD:
I'm not gonna be
blindsided by this place again.
I need to see it.
FATIMA:
Those things
that come out at night,
they sacrificed their children,
because it promised them
that they would live forever.
JADE: Miranda had
visions of this place.
She's the only one who had
a connection to this place
long before she arrived.
It wasn't just Miranda.
When I was a little girl,
I saw this place, too.
[VIOLIN PLAYING MOURNFUL TUNE]
Anghkooey.
Remember.
Oh, God.
TABITHA:
The reason
I felt what Miranda felt
is because I was Miranda.
And Jade was Christopher.
We've come back
over and over again because
we failed the first time.
I need some time, honey.
JULIE:
When I walked
inside the ruins,
suddenly,
I was in a chamber.
[SCREAMING]
I think I was actually there.
You're a Storywalker:
someone who can visit
chapters of the story
that already happened.
What?
But you can't change them.
Dad! I think
this is when it happens!
Slow down.
No, no, listen to me!
I need to change
the story, Dad, please!
That was a hell of a song.
This didn't have
to happen, you know.
Knowledge comes with a cost.
[CHOKING]
Your wife shouldn't
have dug that hole, Jim.
[CHOKING]
No!
[SCREAMING]
[SIGHS] People are
such fragile things.
We have to stop
meeting like this.
When did you
come from this time?
[GASPING]
Didn't anyone tell ya?
There's no way to change
a story once it's been told.
[SIGHS]
Just you and me now, Jim.
I liked you,
I really did.
[WHISPERS] Fuck you.
[CHUCKLES]
You always tried so hard.
You carried so much.
It's a terrible shame you won't
get to see what happens next.
Because what happens next...
is my favorite part.
Would you like to know why?
[CHUCKLES]
[SIGHS]
["QUE SERA, SERA [WHATEVER
WILL BE, WILL BE]" PLAYS]
♪
When I was just a little boy
I asked my father
♪
"What will I be?"
"Will I be handsome?"
♪
"Will I be rich?"
Here's what he said to me
♪
Que sera sera
Whatever will be will be
♪
The future's not ours to see
Que sera sera
♪
What will be will be ♪
Now I have
children of my own
♪
They ask their father
"What will I be?"
♪
"Will I be pretty?"
"Will I be rich?"
♪
I tell them tenderly
Que sera sera
♪
Whatever will be will be
The future's not ours to see
♪
Que sera sera
What will be will be
♪
Que sera sera
What do you mean, they
sacrificed their children?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Those things in the woods;
they were people once.
They made a--
a bargain with
something horrible.
But I didn't see--
I-I couldn't see it. I--
ELLIS: It's okay.
It's okay. Hey.
[SCREAMS]
Hey, hey, hey.
You're okay. You're okay.
We gotta get her out of here.
Baby, we gotta go,
all right?
No. Boyd was here.
Where's Boyd?
I'll find him. Go! Come on.
We can't leave without him.
Fatima, we have to go!
Come on.
Ellis!
Please.
No. I'm okay, I can--
Hey.
[SHOUTS IN PAIN]
Hey! Help me. Hey! Hey!
I know, I know.
Hey, you're okay.
Come on. Kenny.
But, we can't--
He's gonna be okay.
Come on, baby.
All right?
We gotta go.
We're gonna be okay.
Come on.
It's okay.
Come on. I got you.
[FATIMA BREATHING SHAKILY]
ELLIS: I got you.
You good?
Yeah.
Okay, come on. Let's go.
[WOOD CREAKING]
Boyd?
Boyd!
[WHISPERS] Boyd?
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
Hey. Hey. Shh.
We gotta get outta here.
Okay?
Okay.
We gotta go that way.
Hello, Kenny.
It's nice to see you again.
No.Move, move!
Now! Move! Go, go!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Keep going!
Keep going! Move it!
We got it! Keep going!
Come on!
Hurry up.
Watch out!
What the fuck?!
How?! He didn't--
I know.
We-- We burned him!
We fucking burned him!
I know! I know!
My God. How did--
how did he even get--
The baby.
What?
I watched it grow.
'Kay?
I watched it stand up...
and smile.
You're--
You're telling me that Fatima
gave birth to that thing?
Is that what you're saying?
Yeah.
You good?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Can you just--
can you just please
tell me what's going on?
I will.
Donna!
Any word from Boyd yet?
[VOICES CHATTERING]
People are starting
to come back.
[FOOTSTEPS THUDDING]
I should go.
Yeah.
That's probably best.
Donna, what the fuck
is going on?
In here.
[WHIMPERING]
[DOOR OPENS]
Jesus.
Hey. Put that down.
She's here to help.
Oh, come--
for fuck's sake,
we all know it's not loaded!
Just put it away.
Now go. You got
nothing else to do here.
Fine. Then stay.
[SIGHS]
Elgin.
Elgin?
Kristi's here to help you.
Can you hear me?
I need you
to roll over. Okay?
Come on. Come on.
Just careful. Okay.
There. Come on.
Okay, now's the part where
you tell me what happened.
Sara took his eye out
with a screwdriver.
She had reasons.
Can you get me a chair?
Yeah.
Okay.
Thank you.
Okay, Elgin,
can you take
your hand away?
It's okay.
[EXHALES]
DONNA:
Can you stitch him up?
Yeah, I can do my best.
Donna, why--
Let's talk later.
[CLARA] Donna?
Yes! Just hold on, Clara!
Fatima's back.
She and Ellis
are coming up the hill.
Okay, okay.
What happened?
No, nothing! Nothing!
Back out!
Can I get some ice?
Yeah. Go!
[EXHALES]
Yeah.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Boyd! What--
What--
Boyd, what are we doing?
Shouldn't... we...
What the fuck is that?
What--
What is that?
What-- Boyd!
Okay.
Boyd.
Boyd, what the fuck
are you doing?!
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
This is every bullet
that we have,
taken from every gun
that's ever come through here.
I just need to make sure--
I just need to make sure that,
if push comes to shove,
we have enough.
Enough for what?
Between Colony House and town,
how many people
we got here right now?
I'm gonna need
a headcount. Thanks.
'Kay, whatever it is that
you're doing right now,
you need to stop.
Boyd, you need--
you need to stop!
Hey! We had one win, Kenny!
One goddamn victory,
and even that, we couldn't
get one motherfuckin'...
Okay...
what we just saw down there,
that means there is no way to
fight back against those things.
There is no way,
none, to win.
The day may come when
the only thing we get to decide
is how we choose to leave.
We can either let
those things down there
rip us to fuckin' pieces
or...
Or...
Right.
I just...
need to make
sure there's enough...
just in case.
Kenny, please.
All right.
Please.
Yep.
Forty-seven.
What?
I did a count when we were
doing interviews about Tillie.
We have 47 people.
Forty-seven.
Okay.
Let's take the ice away.
You must think
I'm a pretty awful person.
I might have
at one point, yeah.
And now?
Now I think this place does
bad things to good people.
Okay. I'm just gonna numb
your eye with the spray, okay?
It's gonna feel a bit wet.
It's okay.
[WINCES]
Uh, hey.
Can I get your help?
Yeah.
I just need you to
hold his head still.
I'm here.
Okay. Put these on.
Can you feel this?
Yeah?
Yeah.
Okay. Give it
a little bit longer.
Okay. So, just hold
his neck really still.
Like this?
Yeah, like that.
Right there?
Then, tilt it back.
I got you.
Once the baby was born,
we were supposed to go home.
If Fatima's back,
maybe that means it's done.
Maybe it's-- Maybe it's
still gonna work out.
Look, Elgin,
something here lied to you.
You're not the first
person it's happened to,
and you probably
won't be the last.
There's no version of
any of this working out.
All right.
You ready to go?
I'm gonna go as fast
as I can, all right?
Deep breath, deep breath.
Here, hold this.
I got you. I got you.
Hold this, Elgin. Here.
Squeeze it nice and tight,
okay? Here we go.
Okay.
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[WHIMPERING]
Okay.
You're doing great.
Okay, one more.
Just breathe.
Okay.
It's okay.
Okay. Steady again, okay?
[ACOSTA] Okay, got it.
Good.
It's okay. We got you.
I got you. I got you.
You're doing great.
[CRYING OUT]
[DOOR OPENS]
Mom!
Hey, buddy.
[KISSES] Hey.
Where's your father?
He's not back yet.
Wasn't he with you?
Yeah, yeah, no, he was.
Uh, we just got separated. I...
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Nothing, honey.
Let's-- Let's go home.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
[ENGINE REVVING]
[INDISTINCT YELLING]
The fuck?
MAN: Watch out!
Hey!
[ENGINE REVVING]
[GRUNTING]
Okay,
stay with your sister!
Why?Just stay here!
Fuck.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
MAN: Stay back, buddy.
Stay back.
BOYD: Shit. Goddamn.
What the--
Okay. Uh...
What do we got here?
All right.
Careful. Watch the glass.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey, sir?
Hey. Okay.
TABITHA: Oh, Jesus.
Can you hear me?
Can you--
TABITHA: Shh, shh, shh.
You're gonna be okay.
He's got a good strong pulse.
That's good.
TABITHA: You're gonna be okay.
Okay.
Don't move!
Don't move! Don't move!
Please help me.
Help me, please.
TABITHA:
We're gonna get you out.
Tabitha?
GIRL: Is he okay?
It's okay.
Is my dad okay?
Oh, my God.
Is he-- Is my dad okay?
TABITHA: Don't move!
Don't move your neck!
Okay.
Don't move your neck.
[HYPERVENTILATING]
Okay. All right,
sir, um...
Hey, you know-- Hey,
you go to the clinic
and tell them
we need the ambulance
here right now!
Yeah, okay.
Okay?
[GRUNTING]
Okay, do me a favor.
Got a shed on the other side
of the bar. Grab some tools.
We might have to
take this apart, okay?
Got it.
TABITHA: Don't move your neck!
Okay. Relax, breathe.
What's your name?
Sophia.
Hey, Sophia, hi.
I'm gonna put
this book in between
your face and this piece
of metal right there, okay?
Okay.
TABITHA: Wait. It's okay.
I just wanna make sure
it doesn't cut you
while we get you out, honey.
Okay. Okay.
[WHIMPERING]
Okay.
It's gonna be okay.
Just relax. It's gonna be okay.
SOPHIA: Is he gonna okay?
Yes, he is. Don't move.
Don't move your face,
please, honey.
All right. Is she okay?
We need to cut the seatbelt.
Sophia. Did I hear that right?
SOPHIA: Yes!
BOYD: Is that your name?Yes.
Okay. Sophia, Sophia,
does anything else hurt?
My neck hurts.
Your neck? Okay.
Shh, shh, shh, shh!
Hey, don't--
don't move your neck.
What about your legs?
Can you move your toes?
Move your toes.
Yeah.
You can? Okay.
Okay. Dad!
BOYD: Don't worry.
You're gonna be okay.
You're gonna be fine.
Dad! Dad!
BOYD: Okay. Okay.
Dad!
Please, wake up!
BOYD: Shh...
SOPHIA: Dad, wake up!
Don't move! Don't move
your face, please, honey!
I want my mom! I want my mom!
I don't wanna be here!
BOYD: Okay.
I want my mom!
BOYD: Sophia? Sophia?
Uh-huh. Yeah? Yeah?
We're gonna get you, okay?
Okay.
We just need you
to stay calm, okay?
Okay, but please just
take care of my dad.
We're gonna take
care of both of you.
TABITHA: It's okay.
It's okay.
Your dad is gonna be fine.
BOYD: We're gonna help
both of you.
It's okay. Stay still.
Okay? Here we go.
TABITHA: Stay still.
Please don't move.
Just breathe.
We're gonna be out.
BOYD: Real easy.
It's gonna be okay.
Just don't move.
It's okay. It's okay.
We're almost there.
Almost done.
[GRUNTS]
Okay?
What happened?
Car crash.
We can't get the door open.
There's a driver stuck inside.
Come on.
Pull.
Okay.
Dad?
No, no, let me put
my arms around you.
It's gonna be fine.
You're gonna be fine.
You're gonna be totally fine.
You're okay.
I'm gonna put my arm around you.
Is that okay? Come on, kiddo.
Dad!
BOYD: He's okay.
Dad! Please!
We'll get him.
We'll get him. Here.
TABITHA: You're okay.
BOYD: Stay right there.
You got her?
Yeah, I've got her.
Okay, here.
TABITHA: It's okay.
BOYD: Take her.
It's okay.
[SOPHIA PANTING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[ENGINE REVVING]
Get back. Get back.
Hey! Stop.
Great.
Hey, did you grab the gurney?
Look, we just
pulled the daughter out.
The dad is still inside.
He's breathing,
got a good pulse.
Is he talking?
No, no.
Perfect.
WOMAN: Out of the way.
Let us through!
TABITHA: Here we go.
Here we go.
You're okay.
Hey, you're okay. We're gonna
take care of your father, okay?
Hey.
It's gonna be okay. Hey.
Hi.
It's Sophia, right?
Yes, ma'am.
'Kay. My name's Marielle.
Are you a doctor?
I'm a nurse.
Okay.
She has it right here too.
Mm-hmm.
Got it.
Okay, perfect. Yeah.
[GRUNTS]
Okay, can you tell me
anything about the accident?
Was your dad
acting strange at all?
Did he say anything?
He-- He was. Um...
There was, um--
There was a tree on the road
and we were trying
to find a way around it
to get back
on the highway,
and then he-- he just--
he made a sound, and then
he just started shaking,
and then we started
going faster, and then--
You're doing good.
It's okay. It's okay.
I, um... I-I tried
to steer the car,
but he was just moving
so much and thrashing
that I-- I couldn't--
and then we just-- and then we--
Okay. You're good.
It's okay.
Please, please don't
let my daddy die.
No, no, no. It's okay.
Please don't let my--
I'm gonna give you a second.
Please don't let
my daddy die.
I don't want him to die.
It's okay.
You need to breathe. It's okay.
We're gonna take care of him.
[GRUNTS]
[STRAINS]
You guys should use a winch.
Ethan, stay with Victor.
Huh?
What?
A winch.
Can I help?
BOYD: Bring it.
Grab this.
JADE: Here guys.
BOYD: All right, gimme that.
Watch your hands.
JADE: Okay, uh, tie this up.
BOYD: Make sure it's tight.
Get the rachet.
KENNY: 'Kay, I'm gonna
grab the gurney.
Yep. We'll take it.
We'll take it.
Wait...
Wait for me.
All right. Right.
Just-- Get the seatbelt.
Yeah, I got it.
BOYD: Okay.
You got him?
Okay.
Get that on him.
Yup.
[GRUNTING]
Right here.
KENNY: Careful.
You got him?
JADE: Yeah.
KENNY: We good?
BOYD: One, two, three.
[GRUNTS]
BOYD: All right.
Good?
KENNY: Yeah.
BOYD: Let's get it.
KENNY: I got it.
RANDALL: Okay.
BOYD: Yeah. You got it?
All right.
Hey.
From what his daughter says...
Right.
...I think he had a seizure.
I'm not sure what's wrong
with him is actually medical.
What are you talking about?
The day I got here,
I watched Elgin
have an unprovoked
seizure right over there.
But, based on what
I've been told,
that's not entirely uncommon?
Oh, right, yeah.
Ethan had one the first night
he was here
and Sara had one
in the diner.
MARIELLE: Right.
Wasn't like this.
So, what do we do?
I mean, at this point,
bring him back up to the clinic
and hope he wakes up.
Okay.
Hey. I'm gonna stay up
at the clinic tonight.
Are you sure?
Yeah. It's gonna be
a tough night,
and one of us should be
up there with them,
and you need to go
see Fatima and Ellis.
Right. Okay.
Yeah.
Okay, yeah.
All right.
All right. I got the door.
Okay.
BOYD: You okay?
Where do you think
they're gonna live?
We'll have to wait and see.
Let's go home.
It's gonna be dark soon.
Where's Dad?
I don't know, but he'll
be here before dark.
Let's go. Let's go.
Come on.
Let's go. It's okay.
Hope they're okay.
JADE: Tabitha.
Jade.
We need to talk.
It's okay. Go.
Get inside.
We need to tell people.
Tell them what?
We have no idea
what happened out there.
We don't even know
if it's true.
You're gonna stand there
and tell me
that didn't feel real to you?
I don't know what I feel!
Sara tried to kill my son
because something out here
convinced her that if she did
that, we could all go home.
I'm sure that felt
very real to her.
No, no, no.
Hey, wait, wait.
Listen, that was different.
How?
Uh...
What's easier to believe...
that whatever
is keeping us here
put those thoughts
in our heads to torture us,
or...
that you and I have
been coming back here
over and over again,
for centuries,
trying to save children
that are already dead?
I mean...
Listen. We can--
We can go inside, okay?
You, me, Jim,
we can pull this--
Jim's not here.
Jim's not home.
What are you talking about?
It's almost dark.
I know. I know.
When he's back,
I'll talk to him.
Okay.
Hey, we need to talk
about what happened earlier.
Give me a minute--
Get your fucking hands off me!
Look. It is getting dark.
You can't just be
walking around.
I'm not going back
in there with you,
that's for goddamn--
I know, I know, I know.
You don't know shit.
You think you're
some kind of hero?
You're some martyr
who did what you had to do?
What you did to
that kid up there...
You're a fucking monster.
It...
I don't know what
you were before,
but that is what you are now.
All you people
are fucking monsters.
Sun's about to go down.
You spending the night?
If that's okay.
Yeah.
Uh, Kristi's upstairs
with Fatima now.
She just finished
stitching up Elgin's eye.
Right.
Um...
We need to talk about
what we're doing with him.
Boyd?
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I, uh...
You should
come upstairs with me.
There's something
you need to hear.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
["SEND IN THE CLOWNS"
BY FRANK SINATRA PLAYS]
♪ Isn't it rich? ♪
♪ Are we a pair?
♪ Me here at last
[METALLIC SLAMMING]
♪ On the ground ♪
♪ You in mid-air ♪
♪ Send in the clowns
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
♪ Isn't it bliss?
KRISTI: Okay.
We're all done.
You did great.
Am I okay?
Physically,
everything looks fine.
[GRUNTS]
Is there anything
you can tell me
about the... um...
the...
The birth?
Yeah.
What would you like to know?
About the terrifying woman in
the kimono that held me down,
or the thing
she pulled out of me
that you told me wasn't there?
[KNOCKING]
BOYD: Boyd.
Come in.
Hey.
How you doing?
What did you see
in the tunnels?
Did you find
the woman in the kimono?
I did.
I'm gonna head out.
No, stay. Stay.
You should, um...
You, uh...
You should hear this.
Okay.
Dad?
Yeah.
What's going on?
What happened down there?
So, uh...
by the time
I caught up to her, the, uh,
uh... the woman
with the kimono, uh,
she was in
a chamber with those--
those things from the woods,
and they--
they were all
standing around in a circle.
Um, and she, um--
she was holding the...
She put it in the center
of the-- of the room,
and, um...
it started to move.
And then,
it started to grow.
And it-- it kept... growing
until it got big enough...
to stand.
And then it smiled.
I gave birth to one of them.
ELLIS: No.
That's not what he's saying.
Dad, tell her that's not
what you're saying.
[GASPS]
This is not just one of them.
It's the one I killed...
that night at the clinic.
Jesus.
[RUMBLING]
[VICTOR STRAINING]
Victor?
Victor!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
What are you doing?
I'm dragging
this bed into my room.
I can see that.
You wanna tell me why?
It's-- Well, it's for my dad.
Uh, we're gonna
be roommates now.
Um, here, let me help with that.
Sorry about the noise.
It's okay.
It's been a while since
I've had a roommate.
I'm sure you'll figure it out.
Yeah.
Look. Listen.
Look at me. Now--
Boyd, are you sure
it was the same one?
Yeah.
Look, if Kenny
hadn't been there,
if he hadn't
seen it as well,
I'd have thought
I'd lost my mind.
But he said you
said something after,
something important.
I-I sa--
About something promising them
that they'd live forever.
It was just a glimpse, but...
I saw what they did.
Okay.
Those things in the woods...
I think I saw how they
became what they are.
They made a bargain
because something promised them
that they would live...
forever.
A bargain.
With-- With what?
I don't-- I don't know.
Fatima...
I don't-- What-- I don't know!
I-I couldn't see it.
Look, look.
Listen, listen, listen to me.
I know that you have
been through a lot,
but this is important.
[GASPS]
You think I don't know that?
I'm not--
I'm the one that...
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
I need a shower.
Hey, whoa. Hey, easy.
I need a fucking shower.
Baby, no. You need rest.
Fatima, don't.
You just need to rest--
FATIMA: No! I need a shower!
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
I told you!
I told all of you
that there was something
inside me,
something that...
I begged you to listen!
I don't--
I don't understand what I saw.
I don't know why I saw it.
I didn't--
There's nothing else
I can tell you.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Hey, it's...
Be honest, what do you...
think the chances are
he wakes up?
Uh... [EXHALES]
Given how long
he's been out for?
It's not even
so much if he wakes up,
but what kind of shape
he'll be in if he does.
Yeah.
Kenny?
Uh, do you have a phone? I, um--
I left mine in the car, and I--
I-I need to call my mom.
She's probably worried sick.
Yeah, um, there's, uh...
There's no...
There's no cell service here.
I could just go
down the hill. It's okay.
I-I don't mean...
I don't mean
here in the clinic.
MARIELLE:
I'm gonna go.
I, uh...
What's going on?
I-I need to call my mom.
I know. I understand, I do.
I...
I wish I could, um...
We need to have a talk...
about this place,
and about that tree
that you saw in the road.
JULIE: Mom.
Where is he?
Why isn't he back yet?
Honey,
your father's fine.
It's not like he's late
coming home from work.
Mom, what happened today?
Why won't you talk to me?
No, Julie, no.
I-I don't wanna talk right now.
Please!
I can't.
I can't talk to you.
I can't talk to you now.
Stop saying that! Please!
Mom, It's almost dark.
He's not home.
Please, why won't you talk--
ETHAN: Stop it.
Stop yelling at each other.
No, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Is Dad dead?
No!
No, honey. No, he's not.
[SIGHS] Maybe he didn't
realize how late it was.
I don't know.
Maybe he's at
the Colony House or the RV.
We'll see him tomorrow.
Well, what if we don't?
Well...
Do you remember
what Dad said to us,
the night that Mom
went to the Bottle Tree
and didn't come home?
He said all we have in this
place is what we believe.
So, we have to
believe good things.
Right?
Mom came home.
Dad will, too.
So, um, the monsters, they--
they come every night?
Yeah.
These-- These rocks,
they-- they protect you?
Uh, we call them talismans.
How do they work?
Don't! Don't, um...
Don't take it off the window.
Sorry.
It's okay.
It's just, um...
they have to be
hanging for it to work.
Why?
[EXHALES] Uh...
We-- We don't know.
We don't know.
I know how
this must all sound.
"The light shines
in the darkness,
and the darkness
shall not overcome it."
What is that?
John 1:5.
It means that,
um, God is with us,
even here.
I mean, um, how else can you
explain such a magical thing
to keep the darkness at bay?
Right.
Will you pray
with me, Kenny?
Oh, I'm not--
I'm not really, uh...
I'm not really religious.
That's okay.
God still listens.
Please?
Yeah. Yeah, sure.
[EXHALES]
Lord, please protect us
in this dark place,
where evil roams so freely.
Please stand by
my daddy's bedside
and let him wake
renewed in your love.
And please rest your hand upon
the shoulders of these people,
trapped here in this place,
who have taken us in
and shown us such kindness.
Be with them tonight,
O Lord,
and let your love
give them rest.
This we ask in your name.
Amen.
Uh, Amen.
Um, I'm gonna go sit with
my daddy now, if that's okay.
Yeah. Of course.
There are a lot of people
wanting to know
what happened down there.
Boyd? You hear what I said?
We had another car today.
A girl and her dad.
Looked like a...
like a pastor, maybe.
He had a--
he had a stroke...
or a seizure or something.
They crashed into
the Sheriff's Station.
The girl can't be more than,
I don't know, 15,
16 years old. She's, uh...
She's up at
the clinic right now,
waiting to see if her dad
lives through the night,
while Kenny explains to her
that whatever life
she had before...
is over,
that, now,
she lives in a place
where monsters smile.
That girl's probably
gonna die here.
Boyd!
BOYD: You know,
the only thing that gets me
out of bed in the morning
is the idea that...
maybe, just-- just maybe,
we can beat this place,
that maybe we can
get everybody home,
that, someday, maybe
the good guys actually win!
And then, I saw that
fucking thing in the tunnels!
The same goddamn smile.
That same...
And I realized--
I mean, this place has been
three steps ahead of us
from the beginning!
Just like you said:
the game's rigged.
Doesn't matter what we do.
Doesn't matter
what we sacrifice.
None of it means
a goddamn thing if we can't--
Hey, where you going?
I am not going anywhere.
None of us are.
Okay, no, fuck this.
Get out of my way, Kristi!
No, no.
You don't get to do this.
It's a pretty shit time
for you to start
feeling sorry for yourself.
Oh, is that what I'm doing?
Yeah, you are!
And you have
plenty of reasons to.
So does everybody else here.
But none of those people
are asking me to stitch up
people's eye sockets,
so I'm gonna need
a little more from you
than "These monsters
live forever,
so we're all gonna die."
Because it doesn't matter
how many people
I stitch back up together,
if they see you lose faith,
then that's when people
start hanging themselves
in the bathroom.
Can you guys
give us a second?
Yeah.
DONNA: Let's go.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Let's go.
Kristi's right, Dad.
Look, no matter what happens,
you are the one person
that nobody here can see...
Dad!
I can't do it anymore.
Ellis, I can't!
I'm falling apart!
Everything I've done,
every sacrifice we've made,
and if--
if I can't get you home,
then none of it matters!
Your mom?
It's...
Fuck, it can't be
for nothing!
I just-- I...
[VOICE BREAKING]
I can't fucking...
I cannot...
...any...
God.
[SOBBING]
ELLIS: I know.
I know.
[SOBBING]
[METALLIC CLATTERING]
What was that?
I don't know.
Mom?
What's happening?
[SOPHIA BREATHING DEEPLY]
[WHISPERING] Wake up.
That's better.
Blink twice
if you can hear me.
I know this must be
very confusing for you.
But it's important
you understand
that you played a very special
role in a very important story.
You see, um...
I couldn't come
to them as I was.
[EXHALES]
[LAUGHS]
SOPHIA:
Not with everything
they learned.
[GROANING]
[CRACKING]
[BONES CRACKING]
[GROANING CONTINUES]
[CRACKING]
[SOPHIA GROANING]
[BONES CRACKING]
What's happening
to you isn't fair.
Are you all right?
I'm lost.
Me too.
Would you like a ride?
When you stopped for me,
I know you did so
with kindness in your heart.
[GASPING]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
You must be so afraid.
I'm sorry you won't be here
to see what comes next.
It's always
my favorite part.
It's the part I wish
could last forever.
Would you like to know why?
This is when
they tear themselves apart.
[MUFFLED GRUNTING]