You've got this, Kitty,
You've pulled an all-nighter
It's just a test, Kitty,
Except, if Jiwon fails you,
and you'll scrub toilets in Portland
for the rest
No, no, stop,
Pencils down, everyone,
Seniors, don't forget to go to the lounge
Thank you, Thank you,
- Feeling good?
I spent the last week
- So, when are we gonna get our grades?
Yay! So soon,
No pressure,
Not like my future
Can you check my pulse?
I barely had time to study
But I'm getting paid today,
Ooh, So I'm hearing lunch is on you?
Oh, ha ha, Actually,
My mom found it while she was unpacking,
Is this our moms on a rollercoaster?
Yes, it's the French Revolution ride
Can you believe my mom ever had fun?
I like to think
Wait, stop, is that--
Yeah, that's Professor Lee with a perm,
This is so much better than a free lunch,
Wait, we should totally recreate
Yes, I'm adding that to my list,
- Hey, Hi,
Congratulations on finishing
You've all worked hard,
Some, harder than others,
And while I believe
I'm not above a little fun,
Which is why
Hm,
The Korean Furniture Museum!
Last year they went to the Stamp Museum,
This might be worse,
Uh, Professor Lee?
As riveting
I mean, who doesn't love a good ottoman?
But what if we went
This isn't a Socratic forum, Ms, Covey,
The senior field trip
Uh, there's lots of walking
which is physical education,
Please help me,
Lotte is one of the biggest brands
I mean, is there a better way
And, um, roller coasters
- I've literally always said that, So…
And you didn't object to Lotte World
when you were in high school,
Nice perm, by the way,
Never imagined you with ringlets,
Where'd you find this?
Yuri got it from her mom,
It looks like an amazing memory,
It was,
Lotte World it is,
We're going to Lotte World!
Call me crazy, but I think
Okay, Then you're crazy,
There he is, Man of the hour,
Congratulations on breaking
It's the fastest 100-meter hurdles
Thanks, Just had a good morning,
Jin, wasn't that your record though?
- Records were made to be broken,
Yikes,
- Are you sure you're okay with all this?
Told you, I'm happy for you,
Did you guys finish your applications?
Already?
Early apps aren't due
Yeah, but, you know, it's my dream school,
and Korean unis are getting
I have no doubt you're gonna get in,
Wait, are you kidding me?
Are you okay?
Uh, I just got my first direct deposit,
Where is the rest of it?
Girl, everyone has to start somewhere,
Did you see? My music video
What?! Seriously?
I know, right? And Jennie,
- No way, What? No way,
- No!
Hey, you are smashing it also,
Congrats to you for making it happen,
Thanks, Kitty,
Oh wow, Um, my dad just said
he wants to start recording Eunice's album
Oh, that's awesome, I can't believe
Yeah, I guess it means
What about you?
I know you love NYU,
Whoa, future talk? This is new territory,
Of course I've thought about staying
I don't know, Maybe,
I mean, I could get
See Jiwon and Imo-Halmoni all the time,
Maybe see Yuri get a raise,
And you and I still have
And I might just have
It could be kind of amazing,
But for now,
OP
'Cause I don't mind
Now, remember
- It's okay, They're not toddlers,
I'm so in!
Oh shoot, they're running,
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, Slow down,
Hello, hello, Please show your tickets,
- Eunice?! From the music video?
All the boys wanna see me
At the end of the night
I'm your number one "Eunit,"
Really? Thank you!
I can get you and your friends
Really?
They're gonna let us in the VIP line!
Thank you! Find me later
Thank you!
- I'm so excited!
Oh my God!
Wait, you two smile and say VIP!
- Oh, That is such a nice idea!
- VIP!
Nice! Yeah, great!
Where did everybody go?
Oh shoot, I just zoned out,
But you know what?
Maybe catch a ride or two,
We should totally get the school uniforms,
It'd be super nostalgic,
Professor Finnerty, we're the adults,
We're here to keep the students safe,
Come on, just one ride?
Mm,
Are you sure
- It looks, like, way bigger in person,
Do you know what happens inside
Kitty Song-Covey,
- You feeling all right?
Just occurred to me
so it might be, like, a safety hazard,
Trust your instincts, Kathy,
There's over 100
Why do you think they call it
Your head's too big as it is,
All right, you two,
I'll settle for frenemies,
- Never gonna happen,
Maybe I just, you know,
That's a great idea,
We'll all meet at the entrance at 10 p,m,,
- Let's do it,
- 'Kay,
It'll be the last thing we do,
In the park, Covey, Not in life,
That gives us a few hours,
Actually, you were right,
In fact, I was thinking
you and me, a night-long showdown,
- That is, if you can handle it,
It's so cute,
I'm sorry Praveena couldn't be here,
Yeah, I mean, she's off
You know that poli-sci program's
She's gonna run the world someday,
Uh…
She didn't say anything about that to me,
I only know about it because
Is that weird?
I think it's cool
Okay,
Oh, there's the Gyro Drop, Guys, let's go,
Are you kidding me? That line is insane,
That's how rides work,
Ugh, To be honest,
I've only ever done this
Yeah, Yuri and I used
I mean, no lines,
It was pretty nice, wasn't it?
It was,
Now I can barely afford to do my nails,
Ugh, I miss being rich!
How about this?
I'll be your personal concierge,
and you're still gonna have fun,
Okay,
You see? All those people rode the ride
You said it wasn't scary!
Oh my God,
Okay, maybe not elegantly,
Did you not see what I saw?
You could fly out during that bigass loop,
Then you're in the dark,
Yes, that's the fun of it,
I'm sorry, you were
What changed?
I don't know exactly,
You say you want
Then let's work our way up,
First, we start off
- It barely counts,
Then the bumper cars, Adventurous,
Then the Tomb of Horror,
The rush of adrenaline,
And finally…
the French Revolution,
How's that sound?
- Fine,
That wasn't so bad, right?
Let's go, go, go
Whoo!
We going, going, going
We ride
I'm feeling, feeling
We going, going, going we ride
We ride
Go big or go home
Whoo!
Oh no, No, I hate this,
I hate this very much,
If you can survive the Tomb of Horror,
- Okay, but that came out of nowhere,
Listen, this is the last step,
Tackling the fear of the unknown,
And is some random in makeup
Uh…
What?
All right, Covey,
You let me win a couple,
What? No, No,
Uh-huh, That's what I thought,
Ah, I don't know,
And I thought it'd be fun for us
- Don't you miss being on the track team?
Maybe it did sting when you beat
It's just… Since I've left,
Like I don't have a thing,
I'd be more than happy
because I love you,
I love you too,
Well, I did say it first,
Okay, let's go,
Breathe, Covey, You got this,
Holy crap!
Oh my God!
"After a whirlwind summer tour,
Eunice and her manager
"Her manager is Young Moon's son, Min Ho,
a promising producer
Hell yeah, your future's bright,
Damn, I didn't realize
Rome, Paris, Dubai,
Min Ho? Babes,
Zendaya's making her directorial debut,
Guys, Guys, grades are in,
Oh my gosh!
Okay, vibe shift,
Yes! I aced everything,
I still have a shot at SNU,
Got an A in Anatomy, obvi,
Ooh! Me too, Take that, Professor Choi,
Rip the Band-Aid off, Kitty,
Wait,
I need more time,
Any version of the future I want
NYU, which I've been dreaming about
and the fantasy of Seoul with Min Ho
I just need more time,
- Well, how did you do?
- I'm not ready for something this huge,
But our photo,
I'm sorry, I… I can't,
Well, if you're not going, I'm not going,
No, I'll feel worse
- So…
This isn't about the ride, is it?
You guys have fun,
See you at the exit, Sorry, Excuse me,
Sorry,
Excuse me,
What are you doing here?
I already told you, I don't do
Oh, So all that decapitation talk was
Not 'cause you were trying to get to me?
Look, I know you think
but even I have limits,
What am I supposed to think?
You've been messing with my relationship
Because you've been
Friendship? Come on, I'm not blind,
He's my best friend,
Look, there is a lot
When we were together,
A girl,
And I was trying to figure out
and it… it really got messy, and…
You… you wouldn't get it,
Actually, I do,
I broke up with Dae for Yuri,
when she was dating Juliana,
None of those were my brightest moments,
But looking back now, I can see all those
Well, mine got me further
And I'm pretty sure
Yeah, I think it is,
If I'm being honest, that is
The fact that a door could be closing
What do you mean?
If I blow it on these midterms,
the possibility of me
and the life that I love
And… Min Ho,
But I think the biggest mistake
would be to let my grades decide
I get to decide that,
Holy shit, I killed it!
I have to go tell Min Ho,
Marius?
For what it's worth,
Thanks, Kitty,
- Did you just say my name?
Oh, it's a thing,
Sorry, I'm just coming through,
Thank you, Just going this way, Thank you,
I'm sorry,
I'm so sorry, Excuse me, Min Ho!
I did well on my midterms,
I told you!
You're relieved now?
Yes, It means…
It's possible that you could be here
Yeah, it's possible,
You ready to take this ride with me?
Kitty! Kitty! Kitty! Kitty! Kitty! Kitty!
Why do you think I came back?
Yes!
Drop it
Uh…
Yep, Those loop-de-loops will get you,
Don't take my picture!
You were right, Lotte World is really fun,
Even these silly uniforms,
Sorry I was such a grump,
Wow, really? I couldn't tell,
Ms, Ahn? Eunice needs help,
I'm coming, Back to being the grown-ups,
Everyone! Hey, hey, hey! Everyone!
Okay, don't laugh,
But I've been thinking about joining
Are you kidding?
Aww, Oh, I left my bag at the gift shop,
Oh, yeah, I'll save you a seat,
Okay, today's been really great,
Okay, Okay, How about the truth, then?
Look, I know you're with Jin,
and I know I've been messing with that
But the truth is, I'm having a hard time
Because you're the reason I came back,
Q, you're the only reason I am here,
Checking your grades again?
Why were you so worried?
If I get even one bad grade,
there’s a chance that I won’t get
I know that's the path
but you have more options now,
I used to think I'd always be a VIP,
Honestly, today while we were out,
you showed me
Both of our lives are different now,
So give yourself permission to dream,
Okay?
I still can't believe you paid for this,
You could've just took
Okay, some things are worth the splurge,
Kitty, look,
Ah! It's perfect,
How did our moms manage to look cute?
Hey, you look happy,
- And electrocuted,
I love that I'm walking
But now I believe that
- Ready for bingsu?
You think that Eunice might want to come?
Uh, she said she was gonna crash,
That's fair, I guess
Wait, let me get my jacket,
Okay, I am ready to go,
Actually, um, I hate to do this,
- I know how you feel about him, but--
I'm gonna give him the benefit of
- I promise I'll make it up to you,
- Bye,
Today was an emotional rollercoaster,
to say the least,
But my life wouldn't be mine
Once upon a time, KISS was just a dream,
But now, it's home,
My friends are my family,
And Min Ho…
Well, there's no one else
So, what's wrong?
There's no one
There's no one like…
Min Ho?
And…
Eunice?
Min Ho…
I…
I think I'm pregnant,
Paris…
that night,
Oh no
Yeah, yeah
What would you do
If you were me and I was you?
If I just, if I just put your heart
Then tore you apart like it's nothing?
What would you say
If I treatеd you this way?
If I just
Hurt me like you
What would you do?
Oh, what would you do?