(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 31=
- Good!
- Go on!
Nice!
Block him!
Great pass!
Amazing!
He caught that too?
Charge! Charge!
- Charge!
- Go!
That was so fast!
It's in!
Well done!
- Good!
Good!
Wonderful!
It's in!
Well done!
- Good!
Nice teamwork.
Keep going.
Meng Wan,
I like you.
I know. I like you too.
Let's go play.
Meng Wan,
I'm serious.
I wanted to tell you in Liangzhou.
♪My wish might be♪
The match isn't over yet.
When it's over,
I'll wait for you.
♪I hate that I hesitated♪
♪And didn't dare draw near again♪
♪Leaving all behind♪
♪The sudden pause of words unsaid♪
♪How I long to hold
that silhouette close♪
♪After waking up, we walk back-to-back♪
♪Watching all that is unfinished
fade away♪
- The horse is startled!
- It's startled!
The horse is startled!
Watch out!
Move aside!
Move!
That was dangerous.
Exactly.
♪I hate that I hesitated♪
Is your back stronger
than a horse's hooves?
You're only a scholar.
Don't push yourself.
♪The sudden pause of words unsaid♪
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
♪After waking up, we walk back-to-back♪
Thank you for saving me, Mr. Fang.
♪All that is unfinished fade away♪
I am fine.
I'll go get some medicine.
Thank you, Miss He.
♪Let memories drift away♪
♪Alone, I gather them up♪
♪Like petals in the spring sun♪
♪Till the past falls still again♪
♪And turns to clear daylight♪
♪The wind returns with my dreams♪
Miss Duan.
Miss Duan,
you must've been scared.
This is a Calming Pill
to settle your nerves.
Thank you, Mr. Wang.
You're too polite.
Since our families are now joined,
we'll be one family.
We should get to know
each other better.
We may grow
even closer, right?
Mr. Wang,
please mind your manners.
Miss Duan,
when you dodged that wild horse,
you dropped something.
If it is convenient,
I can bring it to you.
How could I trouble you?
I will fetch it myself.
This way, please.
The Duan clan is full
of beauties.
Pretty, who are you?
- Get lost.
- You...
Mr. Fang,
what was it that I dropped earlier?
That was just a lie I made up.
I didn't see you drop anything.
I only saw you uneasy,
so I thought
perhaps you needed
an excuse to step away.
What makes you think I was uneasy?
Weren't you about to cry?
Cry?
Here.
Here?
Look closely.
This one is tear makeup.
It's the latest fashion.
I'm not about to cry.
Look.
Why make yourself
look like you're about to cry?
A smile
is far better than tears,
isn't it?
What would you know?
This kind of makeup
creates a frail,
pitiful look.
I don't get it.
I always thought
a lady so radiant
as you
would never need pity.
Mr. Fang,
you are better as yourself.
You need not imitate Xu.
Miss He.
He is fond of you.
Miss He, don't jest. I...
When the horse was startled,
everyone else ran away.
Only he rushed over at once
to shield you.
He nearly got badly hurt for it.
If you ask me,
seeing him like this,
I think he'd even die
for you
willingly.
Good. Well passed.
- Good.
- Nice.
Impressive.
Nice shot.
Xu, well done.
(Though she's from the jianghu,)
(she'd make a fine sister-in-law.)
What are you doing?
I meant what I said.
I like you.
After we returned to Nandu,
each time I heard
about your blind dates,
I'd feel anxious and upset.
Anxious that you'd say yes to another.
Upset with myself.
I'd liked you for so long,
yet I didn't dare to tell you.
Meng Wan,
I've made up my mind today.
I have to tell you.
Well...
Meng Wan.
What do you like about me?
I can't quite say.
But I just like you.
You can't even say
what you like about me.
Why should I believe you?
If I can say it clearly,
would you accept me?
Who said that?
Meng Wan,
I truly like you.
I like you for having principles,
being strong-willed,
always following your heart,
and acting with resolve.
I also like you
for never shrinking
before the foe.
Surely, I also like you
for being good-looking.
All right.
I hear you.
What do you mean
by that?
It means I heard you.
Then...
Does that mean you agree?
I never said that.
Then what do you mean? Be clear.
Why do you ask so much?
All right? I hear you?
Do you like how I look today?
Not bad.
Flames blaze; banners fly high.
A young man rides wild and free.
Good that you like it.
I wanted you to see
the vigor in this world
and the truest,
brightest me.
I saw through you
long ago.
Ten days pass quickly.
Time really flies.
Simu,
how does the Mortal World feel now?
This world
is truly a vivid painted scroll.
What a fine tune.
Yes.
Wonderful.
- Wonderful.
- A fine tune.
Truly exquisite.
Luoxian's Qin skill
is truly remarkable.
- Indeed.
- Splendid.
Yes.
Come.
Today, you seem
especially radiant
in quite fine spirits.
Do I?
You must be mistaken.
It's already the Hai hour.
Your shift ended long ago.
One more cup.
Go back and get some rest.
- But
- Cheers.
you still have guests.
Cheers.
An exception for today.
Let everyone here
leave fully satisfied.
Lately, in Nandu,
any curious tales?
The biggest tale
is about Wang Jin, right?
I heard
the Vice Minister
of the Judicial Review,
Wang Jin,
is actually a prince.
It's too late now.
He's now a prince
and not easy to meet.
Come, Wang.
Let's just drink
and enjoy the songs.
Splendid indeed.
I finally made it.
Given your identity,
you needn't come.
It's all right.
The guards are posted nearby.
Fang Ji,
you and Luoxian
should take care on the way
to Yunzhou and Luozhou.
Stay alert.
Fang Ji,
we will meet again someday.
Just as you expected,
His Majesty is pleased
with the manuscript
about Tianluo purification.
Now, Luoxian is a Commandery Princess,
sent to Luozhou as an instructor.
That will make things much easier.
Luoxian once promised me
to build another Wensheng Agency
in Yunzhou and Luozhou for us.
That will make Fang Ji's work there
much easier.
As Luozhou's Vice Commissioner,
Fang Ji will open the mines
once he arrives.
Lately, Chong's strife has eased.
They keep stirring at our border.
It's time for me to head north.
After Fang Ji and I leave,
the troublesome Nandu
will be in your hands.
Rest easy.
Though our armor is strong
and our horses are robust,
our cavalry still can't match
the Chong people,
who were raised on horseback.
You must find a way
to check their cavalry.
We seized
the three prefectures
while Chong was in turmoil.
Nothing will come
that easily again.
We must be fully prepared.
General Duan, how long
should this war go on?
As the saying goes,
five victories bring calamity;
four victories bring costs;
three victories bring domination.
If the war drags on too long,
the people and treasury will break.
Three campaigns
to reclaim our lost land
would be perfect.
Three?
General Duan,
your plan is truly bold.
Still,
it does suit your style.
(Lotusborn Pavilion)
Everything is ready.
Great Ancestor,
let us begin at once.
I've refined this soul candle
into this bracelet.
Whoever holds this bracelet
will control the master
of this soul candle.
Great Ancestor,
the bracelet is done.
Are you returning to the Void?
- Cheers.
Escorting this lad
has worn me out on the road.
Yes.
Camping rough day after day.
Still dreaming
of becoming a Priest?
Hiding a sacred robe is a capital crime.
Your post as Priest
has already been stripped.
Why do you need that?
Give it back. Give it back!
That is mine.
Give it to me.
Give…
How dare you glare at me?
Who do you think you are?
I...
- Die!
- Calm down.
I...
Move aside.
I didn't mean to.
I...
I'll kill you.
I knew
you'd need me.
Evil spirit,
leave at once.
If I leave,
you'll die by the blade
of some nameless foot soldier.
Can you accept that?
You are North Chong's
most gifted Young Priest.
Your faith is truer than anyone's.
You want all under heaven
to follow your faith.
It was people like Duan Xu
and the High Priest
who drove you to this end.
Your heart is full
of rage and unwillingness.
Yet you would still die
such a lowly death.
If you become the High Priest,
you won't only live,
but you can fulfill your long wish
and seize your own fate.
Seize my own fate?
That is the way of this world.
If you don't kill them,
they will come for your life.
Why me?
Why must it be me?
Your soul is pure and true.
You are fated for the Spirit World.
They fear
that you may gain greater power,
so they mean to kill you.
Impossible.
No way.
You're lying to me.
Everyone in this world
is waiting for you to die.
Only I
will keep you alive.
I will make you
become the High Priest.
I am Yan Ke.
When you call for me again,
remember my name.
(Yueran Fragrance)
The new master's fragrance craft
is far below Master Xuan's.
Milady.
Milady?
You're just a frail girl on Mafeisan.
Let's see how you can fight back now.
Being tied up is no fun.
Come on, I'll untie you.
What are you doing, Wang Qi?
I'm warning you.
I am a Duan legitimate daughter.
If you dare lay a hand on me,
my father and brother
will never let you off.
I know.
You're the pearl of your family.
So proud and aloof.
But my father is
the Minister of Revenue.
Yet you kept brushing me off.
You even slighted me
before Fang Xianye.
What is Fang Xianye, anyway?
A lowborn stray with no kin or name.
Shame on you.
Do you really think
your father and brother
can do anything to me?
Let me tell you the truth.
Once we have consummated relations,
for the sake of your good name,
your family will marry you to me.
When that time comes…
Just thinking of it delights me.
Duan Shunxi.
The mere thought of him angers me.
Because of him, my sister
is still missing.
Your family owes us.
How will you repay that debt?
Come on.
How dare you
press me on this?
Come on, yield to me.
Now, take off your clothes.
Don't touch me.
See? We're getting closer.
- Help!
- Come on.
Yes, just like that.
Help!
Don't struggle.
Don't touch me.
Let me go.
What's wrong?
Weren't you enjoying yourself?
Leaving so soon?
You're the one…
How shall we deal with him?
Shall we kill him?
No.
There are better ways
to torment a man.
Fangcao,
don't come closer.
Fangcao, Biyun, stay back.
Don't come for me.
Biyun, don't come closer.
Xiang, don't come near me.
I didn't kill you.
If I were found out…
Don't come near me.
A ghost!
Ghost!
He...
What's wrong with him?
He's trapped in ten days in an illusion.
Once he comes to his senses,
he likely won't go near women.
You...
Who exactly are you?
He Simu.
Miss He.
Thank…
Thank you.
(Duan Mansion)
Simu dealt with Wang Qi for you.
You knew all along
that Miss He is a spirit?
I knew.
And you still care for her?
You still want to be with her?
Jingyuan,
I know you're thinking of me.
You're my only sister.
You want me to be happy,
don't you?
I don't understand.
Why choose a love
that is bound to be thorny?
Can it truly bring happiness?
When you meet that person,
you will understand.
May I ask
which house you're from?
I was born to a humble family.
I'm not from any house.
My name is Fang Ji;
my courtesy name is Xianye.
How did you know Jingyuan
was in danger?
After I left the Prophet's Mansion,
I suddenly sensed your sister's aura.
I realized
she'd never go there,
so I went to have a look.
Just then, I saw
Wang Qi forcing himself on her.
I have dealt with Wang Qi.
Simu,
thank you for today.
Do you like it?
I do.
So much
that I don't want to leave you.
I was just about to say goodbye.
I'm going back to the Void.
I have been away for too long.
There are matters
waiting for me to handle.
Your sister-in-law
just learned who you are,
and you leave this mess
to me?
I have a feeling
I will be alone for years to come.
I'm not good at comforting people.
True.
When you're not acting mortal,
it's good enough
if you don't scare me.
Why didn't I scare you off?
I'm indeed leaving.
In a few days, I'll go
to gather troops.
Where will you go?
Have you decided yet?
What?
Do you know a place?
Shenzhou.
The people of Shenzhou are fierce.
They act overbearing.
Between families and villages,
conflicts break out easily.
For generations,
a feud has never ended.
Sounds promising.
When do you leave?
In about three days.
Simu, stay with me
for three more days.
♪Though apart, my thoughts still swirl♪
All right.
♪For a name to be remembered♪
♪There are passions and pains♪
♪Hope we'll experience them together♪
In 100 years
after I die,
you won't fall for anyone else.
Because you'll never find
another madman like me.
Will I be able to find one
after 100 years?
♪I care for no one but you♪
No.
But you'll forget me.
♪Miracles, eternity, and radiance♪
You'll point to my grave and say,
"I once truly cared"
"for this person."
♪Walking with you through eternity♪
"But now,"
"I can't even recall his name."
Simu,
remember me a little longer.
♪My thoughts still swirl♪
Remember me for another hundred years.
♪For a name to be remembered♪
♪There are passions and pains♪
♪Hope we'll experience them together♪
♪Before we forget or grow apart♪
♪Even if the day gives way to night♪
Duan Shunxi,
you've gotten so good
at playing pitiful.
♪I care for no one but you♪
♪I'll come near and run to you♪
You saw through me.
♪To heal the deepest wounds♪
♪Miracles♪
♪Eternity, and radiance♪
♪Worth more than any barren land♪
♪I might as well
spend the rest of my life♪
♪Walking with you through eternity♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪