[The Epoch of Miyu]
[Episode 7]
It's fine.
No one is here.
Are you here to laugh at me?
Yes.
I came up to laugh at you.
Keep doing it.
I'm not in the mood for your jokes.
You shouldn't be called Xu Miyu,
but Xu Eyu, which means harsh words.
Xu Miyu wasn't my real name.
My stepsister's name
has the word Mi in it.
So, my mom changed my name.
She said sisters should match.
Actually, she just wanted
to please my stepfather.
Then, I've been
called Xu Miyu
for over 20 years,
flattering them with sweet words
for over 20 years.
I thought sincerity could finally
win sincerity,
but I didn't expect
to fail miserably in the end.
I'm like a joke.
Have you ever heard of a bird
called Barnacle Goose?
They live in the Arctic Circle.
To avoid predators,
they all build their nests on cliffs.
But there is no food up there.
The fledglings that haven't learned
to fly yet
have to risk their lives
and jump off the cliff
for living.
From a hundred meters high,
they have to
land on their softest bellies.
Only the survivors can grow up.
What about the adult birds?
Do they just watch the little birds jump?
They just watch.
This is a lesson for every Barnacle Goose.
But on second thought,
they all survive on their own courage.
So, they will always just be themselves,
not someone else's appendage.
One day, they will stand high up
and look down on the abyss
they once conquered.
I kindly told you a story.
Are you secretly cursing me in your heart?
[Xu Miyu, 18th floor,
Daily shift, Bad Review]
Miyu.
Where did you go?
[Employee Schedule] [Staff Score]
I...
I had an emergency just now.
You accompanied your parents, right?
I heard
even the security guards were called.
That was a misunderstanding.
It's fine now.
Is it even a guess?
It must be her parents.
As an adult, she even has to
ask her parents to
beat the mistress of her husband.
She lives such a cowardly life.
Miyu.
The guest has checked out?
He just left.
The one who came to beat the mistress
wasn't my biological father,
but my stepfather.
And
if you have any gossip
you want to ask about,
I'm right here.
No need to guess wildly.
You can ask me directly.
Miyu, I wasn't talking about you.
Starting from the bottom
may seem like a detour.
But taking it step by step
might be more down-to-earth.
So, they will always just be themselves,
not someone else's appendage.
He holds a black card
and stays on our executive floor.
His judgement
carries a lot of weight.
Room service.
Good morning, Mr. Ji.
Is it convenient for me to come in
and clean the room for you now?
Then, I will start working.
If you find it noisy,
please wait in the bedroom first.
I will clean your room
as quickly as possible.
What are you doing?
I'm cleaning.
Can you be normal?
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Mr. Ji,
is there anything else you need me to do?
You can leave after cleaning.
Didn't I tell you to leave?
I see you've been busy all morning.
You may need a cup of coffee
to refresh yourself.
My work is my own business.
You've finished your work.
You can leave now.
Thank you.
You can go.
Mr. Ji,
are you satisfied with my service?
If the answer is yes,
please give me a good review.
Thank you.
Why should I give you a good review?
Your good review
is the greatest encouragement for my work.
Thank you.
Are you playing tricks again?
I... I haven't played any tricks.
Last time at the birthday banquet
of Nie Yucheng's mother,
my napkin fell on the floor,
and I saw you under the table.
That was a special situation.
And justifiable, right?
Mr. Ji,
after you chatted with me last time,
I thought you were absolutely right.
I should set a new goal
for my life.
So,
my current goal is to be a good attendant
and get good reviews from guests.
Isn't your goal a bit too small?
Then, do you think
setting my goal as
being the hotel general manager
is easier to achieve?
I... I just think
I was too eager to start over
and too impatient.
Now I just want to take it step by step
and do everything well at the moment.
I want to start with
getting a good review from you, Mr. Ji.
Your service is merely okay at best.
It's far from my standard
for a good review.
Then, what is your standard?
I... I sincerely want to ask you, Mr. Ji.
Can you tell me
the weakness
of my service?
You are over time.
The standard time
for cleaning a room is 20 minutes.
You can only be meticulous
within 15 minutes.
In the remaining five minutes,
you have to do the final check.
And the time you've spent in my room
has been 23 minutes.
I think there's a flaw in your standard.
What flaw?
The presidential suite upstairs
covers 308 square meters.
Cleaning it completely
requires at least 30 minutes.
Each room on the executive floor
averages 78 square meters.
It takes at least 25 minutes to clean.
I think our service
shouldn't just pursue speed.
What's more important
is the service result.
Then, let me make one thing clear to you.
You are cleaning a guest's room
but not your own home.
Ensuring both efficiency and quality
is the basic quality
of a hotel service staff.
If you can't do it,
I suggest you
go back
and improve
your professional skills first.
I can finish my work
within the specified time.
I just want to provide guests
with more meticulous
and thoughtful service.
Then, do you know
what the first principle of service is?
To provide guests with the most...
It's not to disturb.
Then,
I won't disturb you.
Good review.
Do you think I want to disturb you?
I didn't give you a good review,
so you maliciously retaliated against me,
right?
I...
I didn't mean it.
Miyu.
[Purong Hotel Staff Apartment]
I got your dorm address,
so I came to wait for you.
Why did you just get off work?
What do you want to do?
I've been cleaning up
the house these days.
There are some of your things.
When Zhenzhen was cleaning,
I saved them for you.
The things I didn't take away
are the things I don't want.
Just throw them away.
I'm here today
to visit you specifically.
Although we can't be a couple,
we've been together
for over a decade after all.
We can still be friends, right?
There's no need to be so distant.
There are some thick clothes inside.
[Purong Hotel Staff Apartment]
Winter is coming.
It's cold in the dorm.
Just keep them.
I don't want to see you
having a hard time because of me.
[Purong Hotel Staff Apartment]
Why did you throw them away?
Nie Yucheng.
Do you think a few words
can trick me back?
-No.
-I'm ready to sue you.
What did you say?
You still owe me four million yuan.
You haven't forgotten, have you?
I've made myself very clear to your lawyer
about the whereabouts of the money.
I don't have 4 million.
Don't go too far.
You know very well
whether you have 4 million or not.
We're going to court anyway.
The law will give me justice.
What justice?
Every penny in this family
was earned by me working my fingers
to the bone.
I've supported you for so many years.
I bought you everything you have.
What have you done for me?
What have you done for this family?
How dare you ask me for money?
Do you have any shame?
You're shameless!
Nie Yucheng,
you've finally stopped acting.
Have you lost your memory?
We've been married for ten years.
I did all the housework for a whole decade
and took care of you 24/7.
Even if you hire a nanny,
you have to pay her.
Also,
as your wife,
I maintained your business relationships,
curried favor with others,
and helped you sign those orders
worthy hundreds of thousands
or millions.
[Purong Hotel Staff Apartment]
Now they are all the credit of you alone,
huh?
Where is my salary?
Xu Miyu, you…
I'm going to make it clear to you today.
I will go to court,
and I will definitely win.
This money belongs to the former Xu Miyu,
and I will get it back for her.
Now that you love money so much,
why were you so eager to divorce me?
You should have known better.
If you were still Mrs. Nie,
all my money would be yours.
Even now,
do you still think I care
about your money?
Honey, you're back.
I'm back.
Did you buy this takeout?
Yes.
This is our dinner.
Look, does it look good?
I plan to wear this on my first day
of work tomorrow.
It looks good.
So beautiful.
You didn't even look.
You're so perfunctory.
Let me have a look.
Come on.
Turn around and let me see.
My wife looks good in everything.
You're so sweet-talking.
Did you throw away
what I asked you to throw?
I threw them away.
Why would I lie to you?
Not necessarily.
You never tell the truth.
My wife
is the woman who treats me best
in the world.
I swear all my money
and everything, including myself,
belong to you and the baby.
I will definitely give you happiness.
What's up?
Nothing.
I suddenly realized
that I haven't said these words to you.
Okay then.
You drop me off
at Purong for work tomorrow.
Okay.
[Purong Hotel]
Mr. Ray, this way, please.
Hello.
I'm new in the sales department.
I'm Lu Zhenzhen.
Director Lu.
Mr. Feng told me specifically this morning
that a newly transferred supervisor
from the sales department
brought a major client
to our executive floor,
and asked us to treat him well.
This is...
This is Mr. Ray.
He came from Malaysia to Shanghai
as a cultural tourism commissioner
for a special inspection.
Hello, sir.
Welcome to the executive floor
of Purong Hotel.
I will check you in now.
Please show your ID.
Ms. Zhang,
Mr. Ray
is in charge of
corporate legal conferences in Malaysia.
Throughout Southeast Asia,
he has a lot of conference resources.
Please make sure you take good care
of him this time.
If he has a good stay experience,
we will have many big orders.
This is a new batch of aromatherapy
from our sales department.
I'll give you a bottle to try.
Director Lu,
you are too kind.
Don't worry.
We will definitely use
the highest standards
to receive your VIP.
Please take good care of him then.
Call Luo Qingping over.
No need.
Let it be her.
This attendant is a newcomer.
I'm afraid her service
might not be perfect.
Newcomers need opportunities even more.
Let her serve me.
Miyu.
Ms. Zhang.
You are responsible for this guest's room.
Glad to serve you.
Mr. Ray
is a major client of our sales department.
Please take good care of him.
I'll do it myself.
The opportunity is given to you.
I hope you cherish it.
You must be tired from the journey.
Let me do it.
This way, please.
Director Lu, rest assured.
We will provide excellent service
and cooperate seamlessly
with the sales department.
Let me open the door for you.
Please come in.
Miss,
can I have your WeChat?
I'm sorry, sir.
Our hotel has a rule
that we can't add guests' contact
information without permission.
If you have any needs,
dial the phone by the bed.
I just think you are very nice.
I hope during my stay,
you will be the one serving me.
I'm sorry.
I have to follow our rule.
In other hotels,
the butlers would give me
their contact information.
Is Purong
being a bit disrespectful to
the guests?
Then I won't stay here.
I'll change to a hotel
with better service.
Sir,
let me add your contact.
Just let me know if you need anything.
Just tell me,
is the big boss of Kuanli coming?
Yeah.
Exactly.
Stop guessing.
Do you know the scale of Kuanli?
The big boss of Kuanli, Duan Longyun,
manages dozens of companies nationwide.
If he really stayed upstairs,
who would manage those companies?
But there's definitely a reason
for keeping you busy.
He's not the only Boss Duan
in Kuanli Group.
Could it be the younger Boss Duan,
Duan Aoxiang?
I never said that.
It's him.
I really like him.
Me too.
He's both a noble gentleman
and a popular star.
I really like him too.
Look at you all.
Let me tell you,
Mr. Duan Jr.
has a master's degree
in hotel management
from the University of Birmingham.
The gambling agreement
with Purong Hotel
is a project he led.
Maybe in a year,
he will be your boss.
Sir,
this place has been booked out.
this place has also been booked out.
This is a public area.
How can it be booked out?
Besides,
in the time you're stopping me,
I could have finished a cup of coffee.
Actually,
the VIP will arrive at any time.
How about you go...
I said this is a public area.
Don't you understand me?
I understand.
Do you always drive away
all the guests in the hotel
every time you receive a VIP?
Sorry.
What's up?
Mr. Wei said to clear the area,
but this gentleman insists on
having a cup of coffee here.
Go ahead.
Leave this to me.
You can't recognize me, right?
Indeed, I can't.
I grew up ugly.
Senior Xue Rui.
Long time no see.
How many years has it been?
Ten years, right?
Ten years.
Come, leader.
Xue, pour the wine.
Mr. Liu,
thank you for your bank's great support
for my work.
I toast you.
Chug!
You can drink as much as you want.
Come on.
Please.
Good.
Good drinker.
Come on.
[Young Xue Rui]
Everyone, cheers.
Thank you for coming. Come on.
Xue, come on.
Pour the drinks.
Hurry.
Come on.
Thank you all.
Let's continue to cooperate.
Come on, together.
Cheers. Come on.
Thanks to your help
back then, senior.
Or I would be kicked out as a rookie.
Thanks to you, I completed the internship.
In the blink of an eye,
the rookie has become a boss.
By the way.
I remember you've been abroad.
When did you come back?
Not long ago.
What brings you here?
First,
take a vacation and rest.
Do you want to go to my office?
Director Xue.
Coming.
Mr. Wei asked us
to gather at the VIP channel.
Hurry up.
Okay.
How about this?
I'll get back to work.
I'll find you after I'm done today.
I have a big family here.
How are we supposed to move?
We will help you pack.
You just need to move.
We can give you a discount
on the room rate,
a 50% discount. What do you think?
A 50% discount?
Can you make it a 60% discount?
I'm sorry, sir.
This price is set by our director.
Hello, room service.
Hello, Mr. Ji.
Mr. Ji.
He's dead asleep?
Who are you talking about?
Mr. Ji,
is it okay for you to
change to a new room?
The subsequent room rate will be 50% off.
Why do I need to change?
The water pipe
on the executive floor is broken.
The Engineering Department
needs to repair it.
Where is it broken?
Take me to see it.
That's the Engineering
Department's business.
We attendants are only responsible
for communication.
That's nonsense.
Then when is it convenient
for you to change to a new room?
When is it convenient for you, please?
Watch out, I'll complain about you
disturbing the guests.
What are you doing?
This is my job.
Find someone else to talk to me.
Move aside.
The renovation concept of Purong Hotel is
sharpness.
Radormok white marble
paired with black agate and pure gold
seems bright and noble,
[Lobby area]
and magnificent.
[Space Design]
As for the original crystal
lighting of Purong,
we have kept it.
But for things like
the complicated geometric splicing
on the walls,
we will consider
replacing it with large blocks
of color later.
Then, what's the difference
between this and
the Kuanli Dinghui Resort Hotel
we built in Shenzhen before?
Mr. Duan, this...
It doesn't sound very innovative.
Innovation...
The innovation lies in...
Sorry.
I didn't hear you.
The innovation lies in the difference
in internal modeling.
What I want is
very simple.
Mr. Duan,
only what hasn't been seen
before is shocking.
Tell your boss later.
Stop fooling me with ideas
from ten years ago.
Okay.
I will go back and report.
We make a new design for you.
That's your business.
Are you hungry?
Let's go.
-Mr. Duan.
-Mr. Duan Jr.
Welcome.
I specially reserved
the presidential suite for you,
is it okay?
Only you have the qualification
to stay in the suite.
Is it the suite where
the president has stayed?
I'm enjoying the honor, huh?
By the way,
hurry up with the supplementary agreement.
You haven't signed it.
I'm afraid that there will be changes.
You must be joking. How would I dare?
It's just that the details
still need to be refined.
As long as you don't change your mind,
I am absolutely loyal.
That's good.
And there is the same issue
I've mentioned.
Everything that can be solved with money
is not a big deal.
I understand. I know this.
Mr. Duan.
Just one minute of your time.
The executive floor has been cleared.
But...
But what?
Didn't I say to waive all bills?
I did so.
The other guests all happily moved out.
Only one person is left.
Then give him a large amount of money.
Everything that can be solved with money
is not a big deal.
Yes, I know.
But this person probably
doesn't want money.
Who?
Who is it?
You can't handle it?
Doesn't want money?
Interesting.
Then I'll go meet this tough nut.
Hello, Mr. Duan.
Sir,
please cooperate and change your room.
Who are you?
As for money,
you can make any demands you want.
Are you from the Engineering Department
or another department of the hotel?
If you are not hotel staff,
you have no right to talk
to me about this.
Wait.
Don't you recognize me?
Mr. Duan is here.
I thought it was some young punk
who didn't know his place
trying to mess with me.
So, it's you after all.
If you want to meet me, just contact me.
Why put on such a big show
and have so many people
play along with you?
Mr. Duan, you like a big show,
so the welcome gift should
cater to your taste.
Old classmate,
I missed you so much.
This is
my classmate and
my good buddy in Birmingham.
Call him Mr. Ji.
Hello, Mr. Ji.
Such a big show.
Are they celebrating downstairs?
What is there to celebrate?
What do you think I'm celebrating?
Kuanli Group invested in Purong Hotel
and reached a strategic partnership?
This is all trending.
It's not surprising to celebrate.
It seems
you really don't know anything.
I was never part of this to begin with.
You're no outsider.
You are my best buddy
from my time in Birmingham.
Let's go.
Join the fun with me.
Does the water pipe need to be fixed?
Still got a sharp tongue.
We're not fixing it.
Even if we did,
we'd skip your room,
okay? Let's go.
Wait.
You're in a suit.
I need to change.
It's a celebration banquet.
You've changed.
But I like it more and more.
Hurry up, I'll wait for you.
Okay.
You two will go help
in the executive lounge today.
I am a newcomer.
I'm not very familiar with
the service process
of the executive lounge yet.
It's okay.
You work carefully
and have a good attitude.
You'll definitely be fine.
But I...
Let me tell you.
All the guests on the spot today are VIPs.
If you can get
a good review from them,
your two bad reviews
might be offset.
Does he think he is Prince Charming?
Thank you.
Speak of the devil.
Come here.
This is
Ji Feng, whom I was mentioned before.
Ji Feng is my classmate,
an all-rounder in hotel management
from the University of Birmingham.
Mr. Wei,
long time no see.
You two know each other?
I used to work at Purong Hotel
and met with
Mr. Wei a few times.
You once worked at Purong?
How did I not know that?
It was before I went abroad.
I've heard Mr. Duan Jr. say
that he has someone very capable with him,
who's been managing
top-tier luxury hotels overseas for years.
So, you were talking about Ji Feng.
Yeah.
Then we go way back.
If I were not Mr. Duan's
former classmate,
I wouldn't have gotten in today.
No way, you're joking.
You don't know this, Mr. Duan Jr.
When Ji Feng worked at Purong,
he was an outstanding employee.
He is capable and popular.
I always said
he'd be a great talent
in hotel management.
Now that you've got
some overseas experience,
maybe I should be calling you Mr. Ji.
Mr. Wei, you flatter me.
Well, isn't that a coincidence?
Next year,
come be my general manager.
Of what?
Purong.
So confident.
Looks like investment
is just the appetizer,
and acquisition is the main course.
Smart.
Mr. Duan Jr.,
don't speak too soon.
Although our hotel has
some operational issues,
we still have a year
to turn things around.
Come on, Mr. Wei,
easy.
Anyway,
Ji Feng
isn't an outsider either.
What are you afraid of?
Besides,
handing Purong over to me,
you won't lose out.
Yes.
With you backing it,
what do I have to fear?
We're all friends.
Well, you guys chat.
I have things to do.
I'll get going.
Look into Ji Feng,
and see what he's really back for.
Okay.
I heard you left Siwei Group
and then swallowed sand for three years.
It's good to be back.
There's gold everywhere in our country.
Where are you working now?
I didn't make great achievements.
Just slack off for now.
You're fooling me again.
Actually, when I saw you today,
I was thinking about one thing.
Why are you here?
Just take a vacation.
No need to rack your brains over it.
Alright then.
After your vacation,
come work for me.
Just name your price.
It's the same to
work for anyone.
Mr. Duan, who is this?
Let me introduce.
This is
Ji Feng, the top manager of Siwei Group,
and my classmate
when I studied in Birmingham.
Back in school,
he was in first place,
and I was second.
We
were known as the Dual Heroes
of Birmingham.
This nickname combining East and West
isn't very credible.
Don't sabotage my efforts.
Don't just stand there.
Let's go taste today's main dish.
Let's go.
These were shipped
fresh from Europe early this morning.
Have a taste.
This taste...
It's not good.
Chef, take away all the caviar.
Change it.
Call Li Qiaoqi over here, quick.
Okay.
Qiaoqi,
the guest in the executive lounge upstairs
wants you to make a seafood feast.
I'm not going.
With those big boxes of caviar there,
they can eat anything with it and be full.
I'll just have some shrimp here.
You have to.
Qiaoqi,
the boss upstairs said he doesn't want
the caviar feast anymore,
and wants delicacies from land and sea.
What the heck?
That's such a long name.
I want to see who's causing trouble.
Let's go.
I will definitely
acquire Purong Hotel.
Since when did Mr. Duan become
so career-driven?
My father
finds fault with me every day.
He said
if I don't show him
some results this time,
he might kick me out of the house one day.
This time,
this Purong project
was single-handedly dug up by me.
I think this will work.
Why did you decide to
deal with such a troublesome case?
Purong Hotel
is a grand old hotel in Shanghai.
It just looks strong on the outside.
Go look at their financial report
from last year.
They had a loss of 47 percent.
If they want to
make a 30 percent profit within a year,
achieving an 80 percent growth,
they need a miracle.
Trust me.
Purong Hotel
will definitely be mine in a year.
No suspense.
Old classmate,
nothing is certain in this world.
But you won't lose out either way.
Even if you don't get the hotel,
you still get a high return rate
in one year.
You make a lot of money too.
Who cares about this little money?
What I want is the entire hotel,
the whole building.
Just for
that Presidential Suite,
where a few presidents have stayed,
I must get it.
When the time comes,
you can work with me,
and we will create brilliance together.
It's a deal,
no going back.
The person
in the red suit
is Mr. Duan Jr. from the Kuanli Group.
He threw today's party too.
Making last-minute changes
was his idea.
I hate these
rich kids whose brains
are soaked in alcohol.
He delayed me from getting off work.
Ya, Luo,
thank you.
It's delicious.
Awesome.
Smells good.
BBQ.
This is a good idea.
I'll go get some drinks.
Ya.
Come in and get the raw marinated food.
Okay.
Luo.
Come help.
Here, take this over.
Hurry up.
Okay.
Why is it all gone?
Chef, please make some more.
Sorry, I'm off work.
Ya, let's go.
Okay.
Master Qiaoqi.
Wait, wait.
What's wrong?
I've finished all my work.
Master Qiaoqi.
The guests are praising your cooking.
Show them a little more.
Don't leave all the work to me.
Where's Chef Jia?
He's the head chef.
Let him grill the skewers.
Master Qiaoqi.
Please don't make it difficult for me.
The guest specifically asked for you.
He's the financial backer of our hotel.
Even the boss has to treat him well.
Financial backer?
Has he paid me overtime?
Master Qiaoqi, thank you
for your hard work.
Miyu.
Thank you.
Why is it all champagne?
Is there no red wine?
There's red wine over there,
at the buffet table.
Waiter.
Hello, waiter.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Thank you, sir.
Otherwise, I would have
fallen to the ground.
Your suit must be expensive.
I'm really sorry.
Come on.
It doesn't matter, it's fine.
Mr. Ji,
did you just come back from abroad?
Do you know me?
Everyone here knows you.
You are Mr. Duan's friend,
Mr. Ji Feng,
the star manager of Siwei Group.
Just an acting one.
Mr. Ji.
We are so destined to meet.
Why don't we exchange WeChat?
I'll scan your code.
[Personal Receipt code]
What do you mean?
Adding a contact is too troublesome.
This is more direct.
No, you misunderstood.
I just wanted to add you
as my WeChat friend
to ask for your advice
on some professional matters.
Sure.
Pay me the dry-cleaning fee first.
This custom suit of mine
costs 3,280 yuan to wash once.
Just give me 3,000 yuan.
Mr. Ji, you should not let me take
all the blame for this.
It was an accident.
Besides, so many people are here.
It's so crowded.
It's her. It's her.