[The Epoch of Miyu]
[Episode 12]
Hello, Mr. Ji.
Hello.
Yin Xiang, let Ms. Xu come here.
Okay, I'll go get her.
Jia.
Luo Qingping.
Ke Wenxue.
It's your working time now.
Do the room attendants of Purong Hotel
like to chat while working?
I just wanted to provide guests
- with more attentive service.
- Then, do you know
what the first principle of service is?
It is not to disturb your guests.
Could you go to any room
on the executive floor
and get me a bottle of shampoo?
I know what you've discovered.
But it is not the time to report it yet.
I'm right here.
Always?
I'll always be here.
Miyu.
What's more,
I noticed your hair accessories.
They should be uniform.
Understood?
Ms. Xu.
Mr. Ji.
How is the check-in situation today?
Two check-ins
and three check-outs.
How did you handle the linens
in these rooms?
We used freshly laundered linens
from the new factory
and informed the guests.
Good.
No matter how many guests we have,
our service must not slack off.
Now, go back to your posts
and do your jobs well.
Dismissed.
Okay.
You are the backbone
of the executive floor.
Before the guests have left,
don't fall apart yourself.
Room service.
Hello, I am the forewoman
of the executive floor.
May I help you?
Close the door and come in.
Whatever it is, just say it here.
You are Xu Miyu,
the one trending online, right?
I wonder who you're taking the blame for.
[Xu Kai, Journalist]
Don't be afraid.
I am a journalist.
I know the corrupt upper management
will definitely use you,
lower-level staff, as scapegoats.
Speak up.
We in the media can speak out for you.
Sorry, you misunderstood.
You don't admit it
because you're afraid of
getting into trouble, right?
But you should know that
once this is exposed,
no one can stay out of it.
Just standing here, you are a story.
Do you know that?
I have no story.
Please don't make one up.
Do you know
your silence means
you are covering and indulging
for illegal discipline?
Because of people like you,
who refuse to report what you know,
upholding justice
becomes even harder.
Are you trying to frighten me?
You must be Mr. Ji,
the new general manager here, right?
Perfect. Let's sync up
on some information.
Which media outlet are you from?
Me?
I am a freelancer.
If all media were like you,
the courts would be flooded
with subpoenas.
You've already constituted a provocation.
I can call the police
on behalf of the hotel
and have your social media account banned.
Ms. Xu. Ms. Xu.
Mr. Feng wants you in his office.
Copy that.
Mr. Feng is looking for me.
I'm afraid someone has already
made up a story about
what happened to you
and told Feng Kaixin.
Go.
You can only prove yourself
by going there.
Okay.
[Purong Hotel]
I heard a reporter
interviewed you just now.
What did you say to him?
I didn't say anything.
Don't pretend with me.
So many people in the HSKP Department
saw it.
How could I wrong you?
Because of the detergent incident,
I've already been very controversial.
I know the power of the media.
In this situation,
if I talk nonsense,
wouldn't I be asking for trouble?
You talk a good game.
But who knows what bad intentions
you have in mind?
Follow me.
We're going to see Mr. Wei.
Why?
You know the reason.
It's because of what you did.
Go.
[Director's Office]
Let's see what you say to Mr. Wei.
- Stop pretending.
- Mr. Feng.
Mr. Ji.
Mr. Ji, what brings you here?
Ms. Xu is here too.
[Director's Office]
Yes, I was just about to report to you.
She
communicated privately with reporters
living on the executive floor.
It is very unfavorable for us
to carry out crisis public relations.
When Ms. Xu was being pestered,
I saw everything.
She didn't say a single word
to that journalist
that would harm
the reputation and interests of
Purong Hotel.
Ms. Xu was
deceived by the actual perpetrator,
just like us.
She's just a scapegoat.
What do you say, Mr. Feng?
What a big mistake!
You have been wronged.
I care so much
about Purong Hotel
that I was too stressed out from working.
Please forgive me.
Mr. Ji,
do you have
anything else to tell me?
Or are you here just for Ms. Xu?
I came here to remind you of
the meeting later.
I hope you will be there on time.
Don't dare to bother you.
I was just about to go.
Shall we go?
[Director's Office]
Ms. Xu,
go do your work.
After you, Mr. Feng.
After you.
Excuse me.
Hurry up! Make way.
Mr. Feng.
Take a look.
[Total Bacteria: exceeding the limit]
[E. Coli: exceeding the limit]
Mr. Wei.
[Purong Hotel]
- Mr. Wei.
[Pujiang River Flows with Eternal Glory,
as Purong Hotel Accompanies You]
Mr. Wei.
[Purong Hotel]
Sit.
Mr. Wei, shall we start?
Yes.
No need to ask me.
Some of you may not know yet.
Let me introduce.
This gentleman sitting in my seat is
Ji Feng.
[Purong Hotel]
He is
[Pujiang River Flows with Eternal Glory,
as Purong Hotel Accompanies You]
the new general manager of Purong Hotel.
Let's applaud to welcome Mr. Ji.
[Purong Hotel]
Thank you, everyone.
It's my first time meeting you all
and we run into such an emergency.
It is indeed a bit unexpected.
But the incident has already happened.
We just have to face it.
Mr. Feng,
how does the HSKP Department
plan to handle it now?
Here's the situation, Mr. Ji.
As for the outsourced laundry factory,
we terminated the contract
with it immediately.
Now we have switched
to a new laundry factory,
called Weimin Laundry Factory.
Is it your way of
solving the problem?
The hotel linens
have had excessive bleach for years.
Is it simply a washing problem?
Excessive bleach
is the laundry's fault…
How does the hotel supervise
the laundry process?
How often are the linens cleaned?
What are the cleaning standards?
Are there regular spot checks
by testing agencies?
Mr. Feng, can you
explain this to us?
Well, I'm sorry.
I have to go back and check the materials.
This is not about checking materials.
It's about the poor supervision of
the HSKP Department.
From top to bottom,
you turn a blind eye to inferior products.
When problems occur,
you let the bottom-level attendants
take the blame.
Is this what the HSKP Department of
a five-star hotel should do?
What we need to solve
is not just the problem of the laundry.
The whole linen supply chain of
the HSKP Department
should be changed.
I don't think that's necessary.
Excessive bleach
is only a laundry compliance issue.
There's nothing wrong with the linens.
The fact that there's no problem
with the linens
doesn't mean the linens are flawless.
Our bedding
does not meet the standards
of a luxury hotel in itself.
The guests on the executive floor
are like‌ burnt children dread the fire.
You don't want to get caught again, right?
No.
I mean,
changing the bedding supplier is
a big deal.
From product selection to trial,
it will take at least two to three weeks.
Not only does it waste money and manpower,
but it can't solve an urgent problem.
So you want to walk around it
when a big deal comes,
right?
Then, our concepts are really
different.
Mr. Feng believes in muddling along,
while I prefer resolving the issue
once and for all.
Everyone here is
a management elite
in the hotel industry.
Please use your resources
to find a new bedding supplier.
The quantity, price, and standard
have been sent to your corporate email.
Managers of each department
should collect all the proposals
and submit them to my office
by the end of business today.
Meeting adjourned.
Mr. Wei asks you to take the initiative
and make amends.
You guys go first.
Thank you, Mr. Ji.
About the linen supplier issue,
don't expect too much
from the subordinates.
They are just here for a free ride.
You need to understand your situation.
You are anxious,
but they are not in a hurry at all.
I know.
So I can take this opportunity to
see who is working
and who is slacking off.
Ji Feng, do you have that much time?
Feng Kaixin was right at the meeting.
If there's a major change,
the transition period
will be very painful.
Don't worry.
I've already contacted a laundry.
We'll work with them
for three months first.
We can change if it doesn't work out.
I've also found backup suppliers.
So fast?
I cooperated with them
when I was at Siwei.
We are old friends.
They will ship the goods
at this time tomorrow.
Wait.
Where did you get the money from?
I haven't heard anything
in the finance department.
That's the general manager's
emergency fund
especially approved by the board.
No one knows about it yet.
Pretend to advance along one path
while secretly attacking another.
To break the monopoly
and test
where there will be a response.
Awesome.
I'm leaving now.
Okay, this cart is ready too.
Go ahead.
In just a few days,
things have completely changed.
Yesterday, we were still repeatedly
changing these linens,
and today they all have to be cleared out.
It's so deserted.
Out with the old, in with the new.
What's so good about the new?
Let me tell you, if the new ones are good,
they're harder to serve.
Ms. Xu.
Have the linens on the executive floor
been packed yet?
Done.
The last cart is coming right up.
Do you think Miyu knew about it?
Knew about what?
About Mr. Ji becoming the general manager.
Think about it. If she knew,
could she be an undercover sent by Mr. Ji?
Madam Cailu got into trouble
and Drunkard Feng got bad luck,
while she became the forewoman.
Doesn't it all make sense now?
Could she be the big boss
behind the scenes?
Big boss?
If she were the big boss,
would Drunkard Feng be able to
bully her like that?
Drunkard Feng and Mr. Wei
are in the same boat.
But Mr. Ji pushed out Mr. Wei.
Doesn't it all add up?
If you put it that way,
she's the general manager's favorite.
If that's the case,
couldn't she even
get a little overtime pay?
Do you believe she didn't get it?
Maybe she pocketed it all.
Miyu isn't that kind of person.
[HSKP Department Management Work Group]
Notice to all managers, supervisors,
forewomen, and foremen.
We are now collecting information
on linen suppliers.
Please fill out the proposal template
and submit it to the HSKP Department
corporate email by the end of the day.
Have you finished tidying up
the linens on your floor?
Just finished.
Did you see the message in the group?
I did, but it has nothing to do with us.
How could we
have any channels for linen suppliers?
Feng's notices are getting
more and more ridiculous.
He dares to make any kind of request.
Just ignore him. I guess
he's rushing to flatter the new boss.
So, he just said it,
and we just forget it.
[Purong Hotel]
Ms. Xu.
I thought you weren't here.
I saw you hung the cleaning sign.
I intended to go out.
Just tidy up a bit.
Okay.
By the way.
Thank you
for helping me out with that reporter,
and for the media exchange meeting.
Thank you very much.
I just hope you can
pull yourself together.
We are in the same boat now.
If you don't want Purong Hotel to
decline gradually,
we have to pull together.
Understand?
Get back to work.
Okay.
Hi, Martri.
What?
The goods are stuck at customs?
Come on.
Martri,
I'm serious.
How long will it be held on?
Oh, please try something out
with the customs officials.
I need a final date
and announce it at the press conference
tomorrow.
Okay.
Is Mr. Liu there?
I'll go find him right away.
[Purong Hotel]
Please let him know.
Hello.
Asilan,
can you hear me?
I can't hear you clearly.
Please wait a moment.
Hello.
The machines inside are too loud.
Ms. Xu.
Are the guesthouse beddings
working out well?
Do you need to restock?
They're great.
I'm not restocking this time.
I'm placing a new order.
How many?
2,000 sets of
13-piece bedding set,
including slippers.
Can you supply that?
That's a lot.
Your guesthouse business must be booming.
It's not for the guesthouse this time.
It's for a five-star hotel.
If you can keep the high-quality,
we'll order even more.
Aslan,
can you hurry up
to send me a sample?
How soon can it arrive?
Tomorrow. It'll arrive tomorrow.
I'll expedite it for you.
Don't forget to send me
your product qualification certificates.
Okay, I'll send them right away.
Goodbye.
Okay, that's it. Bye.
[Aslan]
[Yunhai Cotton Mill, Brand Introduction]
[Test Report]
[Director's Office]
Ms. Xu, what's the matter?
I'm here to submit the proposal
for the linen supplier.
Just leave it to me.
Can I hand it to Mr. Feng myself?
There are some details
that I want to explain to him in person.
Mr. Feng is with a client right now.
He's not available.
Okay, please pass it on to him for me.
[Director's Office]
Thank you for your hard work, Ms. Xu.
Mr. Li.
This price cut is
just for show.
We'll make the proposal look good to
secure the contract first.
Next time,
we'll raise the price back.
Okay?
Yes.
[Supplier Proposal: Yunhai Cotton Bedding]
[Proposer: Xu Miyu]
Yes. Yes.
[Purong Hotel Supplier Registration Form]
[Supplier Introduction]
[Cooperation Plan]
For our long-lasting cooperation,
my treat tonight, okay?
We can talk while we eat.
Okay.
Book a private room
at Yuhuating Restaurant for me tonight.
Mr. Feng, as for that proposal...
Keep it here.
Don't let Ji see it.
Then, this deal won't be done.
Dare she try to compete with me?
[Supplier Proposal: Yunhai Cotton Bedding]
[Purong Hotel]
[Supplier Proposal:
Xianglong Bedding Introduction]
[Purong Hotel Supplier Registration Form]
[Supplier Proposal:
Xianglong Bedding Introduction]
[Xianglong Bedding Cotton Mill
Bedding Supply Plan]
Just one proposal?
From yesterday to today,
only Mr. Feng from the HSKP Department
submitted a proposal.
Okay. Thanks for your hard work.
No problem.
[General Manager's Office]
Come in.
Mr. Wei.
Mr. Feng from the HSKP Department
has submitted the proposal.
Here is a copy.
[Supplier Proposal:
Xianglong Bedding Introduction]
[Purong Hotel Supplier Registration Form]
Okay, go ahead.
Mr. Feng.
Mr. Qian.
[Do not block the door.
Violators will receive a written warning]
Bro, we have a deal.
I'll be the only one
submitting the proposal.
I will let Ji have no choice.
Let's make sure we don't fight
amongst ourselves.
Don't worry. I've already
made the arrangements.
I can always count on you, bro.
But
why hasn't Ji come to me?
Does he have
other proposals?
He's new to the job.
He needs to save face.
Stay calm.
He's the one who needs you.
You don't need him.
I'm leaving.
Any news from the customs negotiation?
Why is it taking so long?
We can't wait any longer.
I need an answer as soon as possible.
[Purong Hotel]
Is Mr. Tao back?
At the court? Which court?
[Purong Hotel]
Please contact him for me.
I'll head there right now.
[To Xu Miyu] [From Aslan]
Thank you.
Secretary Wu.
We're off work. Mr. Wei isn't here,
and neither is Mr. Ji.
I'm not looking for them.
I just want to ask you a question.
Did you receive
the bedding supplier proposals
for the HSKP Department today?
Why do you ask?
I delivered a proposal.
It has color pictures of the cotton fields
in the northwest.
I have no idea.
When the general manager arrives tomorrow,
you can ask him yourself.
Sorry to keep you from getting off work.
Hello, Mr. Tao.
Yes, I just arrived at the hotel.
I'll send the contract to you right away.
Add another hundred yuan for each set?
But Mr. Tao,
we just agreed on the price an hour ago.
Okay, let me think about it.
Mr. Ji.
I saw you weren't here just now,
so I changed the bedding first.
I was waiting for you to come back.
I didn't ask for new bedding.
This is a sample from the factory.
I wanted to show it to you
before the new product launch.
But your schedule is fully booked,
so I could only...
[Washing instructions]
Where is this brand from?
Yunhai is a cotton processing plant
in the Northwest region.
They also produce their own cotton,
as well as towels,
bedding, and clothes.
What about the specific parameters?
The average fiber length of the cotton
produced by their plant is 38 millimeters.
The fineness is 9000 metric count.
The single fiber strength
is around 4.9 cN.
Do you have the product test report?
I have the electronic version.
Please take a look.
[Test Report]
I've inspected many
[Shanghai Institute of Quality Inspection
and Technical Research]
[Test Report]
cotton manufacturers in the Northwest.
[Summary of Test Results
for Banned Azo Dyes]
I think this one is
the most cost-effective.
I also have some videos.
Let me show you.
Let me see.
[Test Report]
There's more if you swipe.
[March 12, 2024]
They also showed me
their cotton production base.
These are the videos I took
during my field trip.
Why did you go there?
My parents run a guesthouse back home.
I helped them purchase some furniture,
and linens.
Yunhai was the manufacturer I picked.
I felt that everything from logistics
to the after-sales experience was great.
This time I asked them to
send some samples,
and they expedited the delivery
without hesitation.
This is the set.
Besides all-season duvet inserts,
Purong Hotel usually uses summer
and winter duvet inserts
according to the seasons.
Have you taken this into consideration?
Then, the pillow inserts.
Guests with neck problems
need firm pillows.
In the past, Purong Hotel
always kept both
soft and firm ones in stock.
Then, we have to think about the quantity.
We have 368 rooms in total.
We need at least three times the amount.
That's over 1,100 sets in total
to keep things running.
Can they meet this supply volume?
I wrote all of this
in the report I submitted.
Didn't you see it?
You should have noticed.
For this linen plan,
the whole hotel is making way
for Feng Kaixin.
They want to show me who the true boss is.
You're so proactive.
Aren't you afraid that he'll target you?
They can't fire me
because I work hard, right?
And you said
we must work together as a team.
Send me that proposal again.
Sure, I'll send it to you when I get back.
Let me change the linen for you first
because the sample hasn't been washed.
It's okay.
No need to get a new one, just use my set.
♪ Life is full of ♪
♪ Countless crossroads ♪
♪ Chase joy too hard, and it slips away ♪
Hold this for me first.
♪ All those confusions ♪
♪ No answers, no reasons ♪
♪ Throwing ourselves
into the tide of the unknown ♪
Give it to me.
Come on.
♪ Knowing when to advance or retreat,
yet still asleep ♪
♪ Rushing to ripen before our time ♪
♪ Sighing at partings,
who meets whom at which crossing ♪
♪ Busy and restless ♪
♪ No turning back, no stopping ♪
♪ Our path—do you see it now ♪
What are you looking at? Help me.
♪ Just lift your head, oh ♪
♪ Don't look back ♪
♪ I've already learned ♪
♪ If it's not mine, I won't force it ♪
♪ No matter how you force it ♪
♪ It'll only turn into a long,
endless wait ♪
♪ Waiting to make peace with myself ♪
♪ And waiting to meet someone again ♪
Come on.
♪ Wave goodbye ♪
Okay.
♪ Just lift your head, oh ♪
♪ Don't look back ♪
[Supplier Proposal: Yunhai Cotton Bedding]
[Purong Hotel Supplier Registration Form]
♪ I've already learned ♪
♪ If it's not mine, I won't force it ♪
♪ No matter how you force it ♪
[Cooperation Plan]
[Return and Exchange Policy]
[Technical Support]
♪ It'll only turn into a long,
endless wait ♪
♪ Waiting to make peace with myself ♪
You're so proactive.
Aren't you afraid that he'll target you?
♪ And waiting to meet someone again ♪
They can't fire me
because I work hard, right?
♪ Wave goodbye ♪
And
you said
we must work together as a team.
[Supplier Proposal: Yunhai Cotton Bedding]
We've contacted Yunhai Cotton Mill.
The factory director will personally
lead the delivery team.
[Reception Staff List for
Cotton Mill's Guests]
They will arrive at
the hotel by 3 p.m. on the 17th.
Why isn't Xu Miyu
on the reception staff list?
Because we arranged for leaders
at the manager level and above
to receive the VIPs.
So...
Add her to the list.
She was the one
who made the connection with Yunhai.
They won't accept anyone else.
Yes, sir.
Stand straight.
Didn't I warn you
that a wise man doesn't fight
when the odds are against him?
Don't challenge Ji Feng.
He's the Old Madam's favorite right now.
He's not someone you want to mess with.
Your top priority is to sort out
the linen supply channel.
Once we have real power,
we can take our time to plan.
Haven't I said that?
Zhigang,
I did exactly what you wanted.
It's Ji
who picked on me.
Look at this proposal you made.
Everyone knows
you took a kickback.
I really didn't take much this time.
Didn't take much?
Come here and read it.
Take it.
Look at their quotes.
Then, look at yours.
Why are you being so greedy?
Who will want to work with you?
Who would dare?
You are so stupid.
[Proposer: Xu Miyu]
[Purong Hotel Supplier Registration Form]
I...
I... I clearly...
Shut up.
[Yingfeng Logistics]
Hello.
Welcome! Welcome! Welcome!
Hello!
Welcome! Welcome!
Thank you for your hard work.
Hello.
Come on, Ms. Xu, come here.
Ma'am.
Hello.
Welcome.
Thank you so much this time.
Please come in.
-Okay.
-Director.
Director, sorry I didn't come out
to meet you.
Welcome. Welcome.
Hello. Hello.
After you.
Please.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
We must stand shoulder to shoulder
for our cooperation.
Wish our cooperation to go smoothly.
That's what I hope for as well.
Cooperating with Purong Hotel,
a five-star hotel,
is a stroke of luck for our factory.
We've had more orders
than we can handle these days.
You're too kind, Aslan.
You helped Purong Hotel
go through this crisis.
We are the ones who should thank you.
Ms. Xu.
Thank you so much for this.
You are the benefactor of Yunhai.
With such high-quality products,
Yunhai should have been seen
by more people long ago.
You flatter me.
Thank you so much.
Ms. Xu,
meeting for the HSKP Department.
Please reply if you copy.
Copy that.
The banquet is ready
in the Chinese restaurant.
Someone will receive you there.
Okay, go ahead with your work.
Okay.
I'll go now.
Goodbye.
[Purong Hotel and Yunhai Cotton Mill]
Yin Xiang, time for the meeting.
Coming.
[Strategic Cooperation Signing Ceremony]
I saw you in a video, look.
The video of the contract signing
is posted.
This is you, right?
You're quite photogenic,
even prettier than in person.
Of course.
You really know how to hide.
Look how busy we've been all morning.
And you went off to show off.
It was required for work.
Miyu needed a helper, so she called me.
She is just a forewoman.
Does she really think she's a boss?
Relying on connections isn't real skill.
Mr. Feng.
Let's give a warm round of applause
to welcome Mr. Ji.
Okay, thank you.
I want to share some good news.
As of now,
Purong Hotel has completed
the replacement of linens
in all guest rooms.
Thank you all for your full cooperation.
Good job.
Great.
This was a very valuable experience.
Rather than seeing it as a crisis,
it's better to view it as an opportunity.
We eliminated unqualified laundries,
strengthened the management
of washing processes,
and initiated cooperation
with a remarkable linen supplier.
This is a breakthrough
for our HSKP Department.
Our future will only get better.
Please work together with me
to move forward.
Okay.
And this time, the linen supply channel
was spearheaded by
our executive floor forewoman, Xu Miyu,
in cooperation with Yunhai.
According to hotel management regulations,
she should receive
the Outstanding Employee Award.
The bonus will be issued
at the highest tier,
ten thousand yuan.
Oh my God.
That could buy my life.
In the future,
any initiative taken
to share the hotel's burdens
will be rewarded.
This reward will not just be verbal,
but will be reflected on your payroll.
Conversely, any behavior detrimental
to the hotel's interests
will not be tolerated.
Anyone who slacks off at their post
and just makes up the numbers
will be punished accordingly.
They will be demoted, receive pay cuts,
or even dismissed.
Mr. Feng,
do you have anything else to talk about?
No, no.
Good. We'll discuss the rest
at the directors' meeting.
Meeting adjourned.
[Transaction alert: Amount 10,000 yuan]
I wish it were given to me.
Okay.
[Transaction in progress, please wait]
[Preparing cash, please wait]
We've all worked just as hard.
Why did she just talk
and get a 10,000-yuan bonus,
while we don't even get overtime pay?
She is Mr. Ji's favorite.
If there are any perks,
she'll definitely get them.
How can we compare to her?
We all did the work.
But when it came to bonuses,
she took it all.
Why?
Exactly.
Without us bottom-level workers,
how could she claim any credit?
Listen.
We shouldn't listen to her anymore.
We won't get any benefits
no matter how well we do anyway.
Aren't you afraid she'll make things
difficult for you?
If we all present a united front,
she can't possibly wipe us all out.
Why are you two so quiet?
Don't drag me into your rebellion.
Childish.
Yin Xiang,
aren't you going to suck up to her?
Harmony brings wealth.
Why make things so tense?
Actually,
Miyu isn't
as difficult
to deal with as you think.
She can be persuaded by reason
but not cowed by force.
So,
instead of going against her,
it's better to just go along with her.
Yes. She's quite nice,
even a bit of a bleeding heart.
We can just play the pity card with her.
Just say, "Miyu, please,
help me out, I can't do it."
She'll immediately act like a cat
which is sniffed catnip,
getting all high.
Then everything will
just fall into place, won't it?
We can take time off when we want,
and slack off when we want.
Anyway, she'll take care of
all the remaining work for you.