[A Splendid Match]
[Episode 14]
If you had even a shred of sense,
you'd never
bring up divorce again.
I will never agree to it.
Gu Dezhao!
I just want to ask you.
Back then,
when you insisted on marrying me,
was it out of genuine love for me,
or
merely for the support of the Ji family?
You're acting like this again.
Ji Han.
It's been so many years.
Why are you still asking this?
My Lady.
What did
the Master say?
These gardenias smell so good.
Madam,
they haven't even bloomed yet.
That's probably magnolia.
[Misty Waters, Gentle Waves]
Madam.
Madam,
why did you come out?
I wanted to get some fresh air.
I brought you black chicken soup,
with codonopsis and goji berries added,
just right for your condition.
Okay.
Miss Gu is so filial.
No wonder last night,
Madam kept calling out for Zhao.
[Misty Waters, Gentle Waves]
You are so pretty.
You are pretty too.
You're just flattering me again.
I'm not flattering you.
If you weren't pretty,
how could I end up looking good myself?
I can never win an argument with you.
It's been a while
since I last saw Rong.
He is so playful.
I am playful?
I came yesterday afternoon,
yesterday evening,
and this morning as well.
How is it that I am playful?
You always falsely accuse me.
When he came this morning,
you were still asleep,
so we didn't wake you.
Listen.
Good thing I have a witness.
All right, all right.
My bad.
It's getting windy. Let's go back inside.
Okay.
Mother, let me help you.
Be careful.
It is said that
there was once a tofu beauty,
who was beautiful but never smiled.
Two idle men
made a bet.
The first said,
"If you can make her laugh
with just one word,
I'll give you five taels of silver."
The second agreed,
and they went
to find the tofu beauty.
They saw the woman standing at the door,
with a dog nearby.
The second man quickly stepped forward,
fell to his knees
in front of the dog,
and called out "Father."
The woman burst out laughing,
just like you.
Then the first man said,
"If you can make her curse
with one word,
I'll give you another five taels."
So the second man immediately looked up
and shouted at her,
"Mother!"
How is it?
I heard it from someone outside.
It's been a tiring day.
Go back and rest.
You should rest early too.
I'll come pay my respects tomorrow.
I'll come too.
Zhao.
You have been back for a few days.
Could you
call me "Mother"?
It's fine.
Go get some rest.
Go.
She just
wants you to call her "Mother."
Why won't you say it?
You wouldn't understand
even if I told you.
Let me ask you instead.
Have you run into something
these past few days?
What?
I'm in the manor every day
and never go out.
What trouble could I run into?
It's getting late.
Go back and rest.
Ms. Zhao.
Thank you for your hard work
all these years.
What are you talking about, Madam?
As long as I can take care of you,
I don't find it hard.
Madam, don't take
the Master's words to heart.
You have Rong
and Zhao here,
and Old Madam to support you.
As long as you can take things in stride,
you can live a good life.
Come.
My mother has come to take me home!
[Rising Clouds and Radiant Skies]
Mother!
Mother?
Mother.
My Lady.
What's wrong?
Madam... she...
Zhao.
Madam.
What did you just call me?
Did you get hurt anywhere?
I am so sorry.
In my whole life,
the person I've felt most sorry for
is my daughter—
you.
You've been back for a few days now.
Could you
call me "Mother"?
It's fine.
Miss Gu.
Madam...
After Rong and I
left last night,
did anything happen?
Madam was crying all night.
You don't know, Miss Gu.
Over the years,
Master has grown distant from Madam.
She has suffered in silence,
unable to speak her pain,
and it has worn her down
until she fell ill.
Now, with Yuping suddenly appearing,
Master refuses to
listen to any explanation
and is convinced
that Madam harmed Mrs. Yun.
Madam has nowhere to defend herself.
She even considered divorcing Master.
Divorce?
I think
instead of
enduring things here in the Gu family,
you might as well separate from Master
and go back to Tongzhou.
We could just live our own lives well.
You mean...
you want me to divorce your father?
No, no.
Absolutely not.
The divorce papers
have already been written,
but Master refuses to agree.
He even came yesterday
and had a fight with Madam.
Miss Gu.
Master must have said something
that made Madam feel
she couldn't live anymore.
Miss Gu.
Madam is truly wronged.
His courtyard
[Hall of Virtue and Splendor]
is near Baoxiang Temple.
Moreover,
it's elegant and quiet,
with beautiful scenery all around.
It's perfect for you to recover there.
Great.
Then,
let's set out in two days.
You are so pretty.
Mother!
Han.
How could this happen?
Mother.
Gu Dezhao!
I'll kill you!
My Lady!
Miss Gu!
Zhao!
You killed my mother!
Let me go!
My Lady.
I'll kill you!
Let me go!
Let me go.
[Gu Mansion] [Memorial]
[Enduring Family Legacy] [Memorial]
[The Ji family, blessed by Heaven's
Mandate, prospers through generations]
[The coffin of the Eldest Daughter,
Madam Han, of gentle and proper conduct]
[Memorial]
Mother.
Old Madam Ji,
and Mr. Ji have arrived.
Han.
I am here.
I will take you home.
Why didn't you ever tell me
what was weighing on your heart?
You were so willful,
leaving me, as a parent,
to see my child
die before me.
Mother.
Where is Gu Dezhao?
Where is he?
Mother.
How did my Han die?
Tell me.
You heartless bastard.
Get up!
Give my Han back!
Give me back her life!
Grandmother.
Song Miaohua,
come out!
Old Madam!
With Mother's passing,
our whole family is devastated.
But this matter
really has nothing to do
with my birth mother.
It has nothing to do with her?
It's true.
Like mother, like daughter.
-Get up!
-Mother!
Yun Xiang?
Yuping?
You and your daughter
schemed to
framed Han
with baseless accusations
and drove her
to her death!
Mother!
Neither my birth mother nor I
ever meant to
drive Mother to her death.
None of us expected that
she would take her own life.
Shut up!
You still dare argue back?
Do you think I can't punish you?
Guards!
Wait, Old Madam!
Lan is just young and ignorant.
She just spoke nonsense
in a moment of panic.
Please forgive her, Old Madam.
Yuping
was brought in by me.
It has nothing to do with Lan.
Today's disaster
is entirely my fault.
I know my sins are unforgivable.
Whatever punishment you choose—
beating, killing,
or selling me off—I will accept it.
It's not like that.
-Mother.
-Lan!
I beg you to see the truth, Old Madam.
This is about past grievances.
Lan is just a child.
What could she possibly know?
Whatever mistakes were made,
they are all my fault.
I beg you to punish me, Old Madam.
I will have no complaints.
Alright.
You asked for this.
Luo Yongping.
Yes, Old Madam.
Concubine Song
has served Madam Ji respectfully.
Unable to bear Madam Ji's passing,
she has requested
to keep vigil for Madam Ji.
From tomorrow,
she will be sent to
the Ji family's ancestral temple.
and shall not leave
until death.
I, Song Miaohua,
thank you, Old Madam.
Mother!
Mother.
Lan.
I'm sorry.
I won't be by your side anymore.
Take good care of yourself.
Don't throw tantrums.
Mother!
It shouldn't be like this.
Father! Father!
Father, please save my mother.
Father!
-I can't save her.
-Father.
I beg you.
It's all karma.
What are you waiting for?
Drag this wretch away!
Yes.
Lan!
Mother! Mother!
Lan.
Never be like me
and become a concubine.
-Remember what I said.
-Go.
Remember.
Better to be a poor man's wife
-Hurry up.
-Mother!
than a rich man's concubine.
Mother!
Zhao.
My poor...
-Grandmother!
Grandmother!
-Old Madam.
-Grandmother.
-Go.
Quick, get a physician.
With this modification,
it becomes easier to conceal
and harder to detect.
But the drawback is that
it can only hold a few needles
and has a short range.
This single advantage
of being hard to detect
outweighs everything else.
What are you tinkering with here?
My Lady.
Master Xiao.
Hey.
Ignoring me?
Are you holding a grudge against me?
Fine.
I was going to ask
if you wanted to go
to Madam Ji's funeral.
Since you don't care,
never mind then.
Come back.
Madam Ji?
You mean Zhao's mother?
She died yesterday morning.
She...
Although she was seriously ill,
it wasn't fatal.
How could she have suddenly passed away?
I really don't know
the exact reason.
There were no signs at all.
She was just gone all of a sudden.
Your brother-in-law and Xian
have already been to that manor.
Since I have Hui with me,
Old Madam said
my attendance is optional.
If you want to go,
I'll talk to Father
and lift your restriction,
and take you with me tomorrow.
Why are you being so nice all of a sudden?
I pity you.
Anyway, Zhao's mother has passed away,
Zhao must observe three years of mourning
and cannot marry.
Then I have nothing left to worry about.
My Lady.
It's dawn.
Why don't you rest a little longer?
Anyway,
no one will be coming
to offer condolences now.
I'm fine.
Where are the two of them?
They probably went somewhere to rest.
You stay here.
I'm going to see Grandmother.
The physician added some calming medicine
to the prescription.
Last night,
she finally slept soundly.
Otherwise, she would have woken up
several times every night.
She is getting old after all.
It is truly worrisome.
Grandmother said yesterday,
[The Fragrant Brocade Pavilion]
in accordance with Aunt's final wishes,
she will be taken back
to Tongzhou for burial.
She plans to go back the morning
the day after tomorrow to prepare.
I'm worried her body won't hold up.
Please try your best
to persuade her for me.
You know
Grandmother's temper.
She can't be persuaded at all.
Besides,
it's good for her to go back.
Staying here
will only make her even more upset.
Okay.
Then take good care of her
on the way.
Rest assured.
I've arranged everything
for Grandmother.
Moreover,
Grandmother told me
to stay and take care of you.
I'm fine.
I also want to stay here with you.
-I really…
-Be good.
[The Fragrant Brocade Pavilion]
[Chen Mansion]
Third Master.
The Gu household is in
complete chaos right now.
[Reflect constantly, stay disciplined;
cultivate virtue and the heart]
I had someone ask around.
There are all kinds of rumors.
Some say she died of illness.
Some say she was angered to death
by that concubine.
And some even say
she took her own life.
Have someone investigate carefully
what really happened.
It's best to ask
people close to her directly.
Yes.
The expenses
for the carriage and the tea
were recorded incorrectly.
Recalculate them
and come back for the money.
Yes.
Next.
Stop.
You haven't answered yet.
Why are you leaving?
My Lady.
I've come to withdraw
the donation money for the temple.
I'm worried the accounts aren't correct,
so I plan to recalculate them
before coming back to you.
Bring me your account book.
You're not miscalculating.
You've calculated it far too clearly,
even counting
your own ritual expenses.
I'm not good at calculations.
Please forgive me, My Lady.
Not good at calculations?
You are too modest.
Look at your accounts.
They are so precise.
You are obviously not a novice.
You've been with the Gu family for years.
I should
be showing you some respect.
But this isn't just any other matter.
Madam has passed away,
and the whole family is grieving.
Yet you're thinking about
siphoning money from the estate.
Guards.
Drag him out,
give him twenty strokes,
and kick him out!
Yes.
Spare my life, My Lady!
Forgive me, My Lady!
My Lady!
Miss Gu.
Guard Chen.
Third Master ordered me
to send some servants
for you to use.
They are all waiting outside.
Third Master also said
he will come see you a bit later.
Thank you.
I know.
You think
this is my first time
managing the household.
And I'm just a girl
with a thin skin
and easy to bully.
If that's what you think, you're wrong.
Anyone who isn't afraid of death
can come and try me.
And those who don't want to work here
can tell me now.
Forgive us, Miss Gu.
Thanks.
Let's go.
Third Master.
You're here.
I'll take my leave.
How is she?
She seems fine.
Everything is being handled
in an orderly way.
The more orderly she seems,
the worse she actually feels.
Lord Chen, please wait.
The Grand Secretary
requests your presence
at Wenyuan Pavilion.
Go fetch me a set of mourning clothes
and wait here.
Yes.
Master Ye, the heir of Marquis Changxing
and the Fifth Madam Gu
are here to pay their respects.
Given your status,
a bow is enough.
Did your mother really die of illness?
Why would you say that?
What do you think?
Others may not know,
but I do.
Your mother was murdered.
Who did it?
I'll help you kill them.
Good child.
I heard
you've been handling
all the funeral arrangements.
Take good care of yourself.
Your mother's spirit in heaven
would surely be comforted
to see how filial
you and Rong are.
Thank you, Mrs. Gu.
Then we shall take our leave.
-Gu Jinzhao.
-Go back first.
Do you have any idea
what you're doing?
You, the heir of a marquisate,
were kneeling before the coffin
of a commoner woman
without even an official title.
With so many eyes watching,
how improper is this conduct!
I truly regret it.
I should never have softened my heart
and brought you here.
You're not being soft-hearted.
You just wanted to use this opportunity
to remind me
to give up on Gu Jinzhao.
Even if that's true,
I'm doing this for your own good
and for the marquisate.
Do you think I want to be
the one to tear you apart?
If I were a man,
able to establish my own household
and serve the marquisate,
I wouldn't need to force you.
You could marry whoever you want.
But I am not.
I can only support my husband
and raise my children
in another household,
watching our family's future
with growing anxiety.
If I had known
you would treat yourself like this,
I should have let you
die back then.
Why did I even bother saving you?
Madam Ji didn't die of illness.
Obviously.
I asked Zhao who did it,
but she wouldn't say.
It's not that she wouldn't say.
She couldn't.
Madam Ji
was probably not murdered.
She took her own life.
How do you know?
Didn't I tell you last time?
Madam Ji
suffered from liver qi stagnation
and depression
that developed into illness.
For someone like that,
if they cannot resolve their inner knots,
it more often than
not ends in suicide.
It's just unfortunate for Miss Gu.
She lost her mother before ever marrying.
It's also troublesome.
I will take care of her.
I know what you are thinking.
You are overthinking it.
You can't take care of her.
Why don't even you believe me?
It's not that I don't believe you.
In this world,
if you can't stand on your own feet,
you can't take care of anyone.
With your health,
no matter how capable I am,
I can't heal you enough
to fight enemies on the battlefield.
If you can't stand firm,
this marquisate cannot stand either.
If the marquisate falls,
you will have no say
over your own marriage.
This is all fate.
Others may believe in fate,
but I don't.
Back then, everyone
said my heart condition was severe
and I wouldn't live past ten.
But you still saved me,
didn't you?
I don't believe
that military merit
is the only way to stand firm.
In this world,
there must be
a path other than military merit.
[Harmony Brings Blessings]
Upon hearing of Madam Ji's
sudden passing,
my mother was deeply grieved
and has specially sent me
to offer condolences on her behalf.
The Old Madam truly values old ties.
Lord Chen.
My younger brother
has been struck by sudden misfortune
and is gravely ill and bedridden.
Otherwise,
he would definitely have come
to receive you in person.
It's fine.
[A Splendid Match]