( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(Lee Na Young)
(Jung Eun Chae)
(Lee Chung Ah)
(Honour)
(Supported by the Culture Ministry and Korea's Creative Content Agency)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and animals were filmed under production guidelines.)
The defendant used a steel pipe...
and caused the death of the victim, Park Je Yeol.
While these facts are not in dispute,
the question is whether the defendant's actions...
fall under Article 21, Paragraph 1...
of the Criminal Code as an act of self-defence.
So, Seo Ji Yoon...
was your sister.
We were separated when we were kids.
It wasn't until I went to college that I came to Korea to find her.
My sister was in the hospital,
but I was too late.
Why I had to do what I did...
Surely you understand, Shin Jae?
When something happens to someone you love,
your whole world comes crashing down.
That vow, that resolve to make the world a different place.
You know that as well as I do, Shin Jae.
Verdict.
Defendant Yoon Ra Young,
not guilty.
Ultimately, we want the same thing.
A world with no more victims like my sister or Attorney Yoon.
And in the world we'll create, that's exactly what will happen.
(The late Seo Ji Yoon)
(Episode 11)
You've been through so much.
You're the ones who've been through a lot.
Thanks, Jeong Woo.
Prosecutors will appeal right away. We must prepare for the next trial.
I know. But we've bought some time, so it doesn't matter.
But where's Shin Jae?
You're here?
What's with the huge spread?
Sit down.
I felt like it's been a while since we've had a proper meal.
Go on, eat.
You look completely drained.
Shin Jae.
That video from the trial... What was it?
Right, what was it? You said we'd talk when she got out.
Let's eat first. We can talk after.
That footage...
Min Seo filmed it, didn't she?
Where did you get that footage?
You're right. Min Seo filmed it.
You met Min Seo?
You never said anything about that.
Did you find her? Where is Min Seo now?
She doesn't want to see you.
I guess a nice meal is out of the question.
LnJ is going to be dissolved.
Haeil is already processing the dissolution.
I was expecting that.
Since Haeil is representing the perpetrators,
it makes no sense for us to stay under them.
Let's leave. We'll strike out on our own and face whatever comes.
The three of us together can make anything work.
I'm not going with you all.
This is the end of LnJ.
It's time for us to go our separate ways.
What are you talking about?
- Shin Jae. - In my heart,
I think this was always going to be our final chapter.
The moment we could finally put the past behind us.
I wondered if that day would ever come,
and now here it is.
As for the Connect In case,
you'll handle it just fine without me.
You'll have to wait for the attorneys for that.
It's all right, Ye Ji. Just let them.
But, Attorney...
It's fine. There's nothing we can do.
Don't take it too hard.
When you get down to it, you brought this on yourselves.
I'll take back any employees who want to return to Haeil,
so you needn't worry about that.
And if you two want,
we can find positions for you at Haeil too.
No, thank you. We have no intention of staying with Haeil.
We'll be leaving as soon as everything is settled.
It's your choice.
Then I guess you'll have to start from scratch.
The Connect In case, without Haeil's help...
Let's see how well you wrap that up.
Hey, Kang Shin Jae!
Kang Shin Jae, open up!
Are you ignoring my calls? Are you really doing this to me?
I know you're in there! I saw your car in the parking lot.
Hey, Kang Shin Jae!
Why I had to do what I did...
Surely you understand, Shin Jae?
Hey, why does everything have to be on your terms?
You just say we're done, and that's it?
Hey, you have to at least explain yourself!
Ultimately, we want the same thing.
A world with no more victims like my sister or Attorney Yoon.
Are you really going to cut us off like this?
Open the door, Kang Shin Jae!
Hey, Kang Shin Jae!
Shin Jae!
(LnJ)
(Thank you)
Okay, I've put out the most urgent fire.
I explained to Su Eun that we have to leave Haeil,
and she said she'll let the other victims know.
What is wrong with her?
Seriously, what is up with Kang Shin Jae?
- Did you see Shin Jae? - See her?
I didn't even get a glimpse of her.
You're just like her. I was so worried about you then,
and now I'm so frustrated I could explode.
You two will be the death of me, I swear.
Something's not right.
What is?
That video.
There's no way Min Seo would've given that file to Shin Jae.
There must be a reason for it.
The way Shin Jae's suddenly acting like this,
Min Seo and that video...
We have to figure out what the reason is.
Gosh, it's finally sinking in that we're on the same team now.
So, what's the plan?
Just as you wanted,
Attorney Yoon got out safely,
so now we move on to the next stage.
This is the detonator that will blow up Haeil.
Haeil is an accomplice, and the root of this cartel.
(Submitting key evidence in the Seo Ji Yoon case)
(I'm writing to reveal the truth about the wrongful death...)
(of the late actress, Seo Ji Yoon.)
And now, for our next story.
The investigation into Seo Ji Yoon's sexual exploitation...
has been effectively concluded with no charges filed.
Prosecutors said her call logs, the key piece of evidence,
were lost during the investigation.
With insufficient evidence to prove the charges,
all the influential figures under investigation...
will not be indicted.
(Haeil Law Firm)
For the last 20 years,
the reason they kept getting away with the same crimes but new names,
is because they believed they would never be punished.
Because behind the scenes, Haeil was pulling strings for them.
Unless Haeil is gone for good, things will go back to the old ways.
So this is why I was part of your plan.
Because if I'm the one to expose this,
it'll have the biggest impact.
Can you go through with it?
It means stabbing your own mother in the back.
You once said Haeil was legacy code that needed to be deleted long ago.
You were right.
Dismantling Haeil...
is what I agreed to the moment we decided to get in the same boat.
Why did you do it?
Why bring me into this world just to abandon me in the fiery pit?
It's too late for that now.
Because I've already settled the score.
The Connect videos...
I'm the one who uploaded them.
I guess even the Almighty decided to send someone my way.
Someone to help me.
He's the one who told me...
who my birth mother was.
I've been thinking about it this whole time.
I wondered if you would recognise me.
They say blood calls to blood.
"Could she really not know, right to the end?"
(No posts)
(Send message)
Thank you for being so understanding.
Just until I find a proper office,
I'll be using the house like this for a bit.
It's fine with me. Do whatever you need to.
Any news about Min Seo?
They said there's no record she's left the country...
and no signs of activity yet.
With a warrant out for her arrest, it can't be easy for her to hide.
I can't rest easy until we find her.
A junior is keeping me updated, so try not to worry too much.
Okay.
About that conversation we had...
Our divorce.
Have you thought about the settlement terms?
Just tell me what you want.
I'll agree to whatever you want.
Hyun Jin.
Do you really think...
that's the only option...
we have left?
You have never...
asked me...
to stay, not even once.
Never mind who forgives who, or who's to blame.
Just ask me to stay with you...
and tell me you need me.
Without a second thought, just like that.
You've never once asked me to stay.
That was all I ever wanted from you.
Actually, about the divorce...
I came here hoping we could reconsider.
But...
when it comes to marriage...
You're right.
It can't work if only one person wants it to.
I'll have the papers sent over once they're ready.
I should get going.
(Haeil Law Firm)
(Full adoption consent form)
(Adoption Consent Adoptee: Lee Ji Yoon)
(Birth mother, Lee Myeong Ja: Consent given)
(Lee Tae Joo)
(Fun field day)
(CEO Seong Tae Im)
So what?
So what if Seo Ji Yoon is CEO Baek's sister?
Twenty years ago,
the people on the Seo Ji Yoon list...
were targeted again on the Connect In list.
And it all happened right as Baek Tae Joo approached us.
And that same Baek Tae Joo...
is the younger brother of the late Seo Ji Yoon.
This can't be a coincidence.
Because it isn't a coincidence. It was inevitable.
CEO Baek Tae Joo...
is the one who created Connect In.
You understand...
what his goal is now, don't you, Mom?
What, was he trying to get revenge?
How unfortunate for him.
If something that pathetic could shake me,
I never would have built all this in the first place.
This is the real issue.
I've sent the files regarding the National Assembly.
We're counting on Haeil for the lobbying on this policy.
I pulled some strings to wrap up the internal investigation.
Relax. The Yeong development case will be overturned on final appeal.
That side owes Haeil a few favours.
There are dozens more files just like these.
And that's just the ones involving Haeil.
Don't tell me...
you're not going to take down Haeil yourself, are you?
I already gave them to the Corruption Investigation Office.
You won't be able to interfere this time, Mom.
Because I also sent the files on the users' personal corruption.
Haeil, the users' shield, will fall.
And the users who protected Haeil will go down with it.
Without mutual destruction,
I realised there was no other way to end this.
And in the end, the world will discover...
that this whole connection started with the Seo Ji Yoon case.
Why on earth are you going this far?
Mom.
When I was little, I wanted to be just like you.
Your attorney's pin...
was as cool as a sheriff's badge to me.
But as I grew up, I realised...
that your badge didn't protect the powerless and the wronged,
but those who just wanted to have more.
(CEO Seong Tae Im)
Maybe...
my obsession with getting into LnJ was just a way of lying to myself.
"I'm not like my mom."
"I won't live my life like she does."
But, Mom...
I understand now.
If I don't stop you, this will never end.
You still don't get it, do you?
How long will you see the world through rose-coloured glasses?
That's not how it is, Shin Jae.
The ground beneath your feet is a minefield,
and to survive, you have to use every trick in the book...
just to take a single step forward. Just like I had to.
You're right, Mom.
Maybe the world is a minefield.
Unreasonable and absurd.
But even so,
I wanted to plant flowers in that minefield.
Using every means at my disposal.
And so, in the end,
I found no other answer than to sacrifice myself.
Because other than to jump into the fire,
I had no other path.
- Canada? - Things have been chaotic.
Here. I found this in Park Je Yeol's car.
I took a look. It'll be helpful.
It'll ensure the Connect culprits rot in prison for a long time.
Thank you.
I won't let a single one of them get away.
I promise.
(VIP Networking, VIP Risk Management)
(Complaint Handling, Expense Settlement)
So meticulously organised.
What is this?
It's interesting, I'll admit.
But what can I do with this system you've created?
It's not about what you can do.
First, think about what the people you want to get in with really want.
You mean what people with money and power want?
Using a system that's both thorough and discreet,
what do you think people who have it all want to enjoy?
If you were guaranteed to never get caught...
and could get away with anything. Think about it carefully.
He's trying to rope Park Je Yeol into something, isn't he?
Laying the groundwork for him to commit crimes...
with the app he's selling.
The Connect In developer purposely approached Park Je Yeol.
Encouraging him to misuse the app for illegal purposes.
Don't you think it could be him?
The one pulling Min Seo's strings.
First, we need to find the developer.
He must have left a trace somewhere in the app, like a fingerprint.
Why?
This is the admin app from Park Je Yeol's phone, right?
This app was built using only open-source libraries.
So that makes it hard to trace who made it.
(Lee Myeong Hyeon, Social Affairs, Donglim Daily)
The Corruption Investigation Office for High-ranking Officials...
has begun a major investigation into those on the Connect In list.
On charges of a systematic cover-up of their illegal activities,
Seong Tae Im, the CEO of Haeil, the country's largest law firm,
and its exec board were summoned.
The trigger was the tip from the CEO's daughter,
Attorney Kang at Haeil, who became a key whistleblower.
The evidence covers a major incident that shook the nation 20 years ago,
regarding the Seo Ji Yoon List incident.
It contains key proof that Haeil systematically covered it up,
which is set to send shockwaves.
I heard she's on her way out.
When is she coming out?
Are you sure?
- They say it's all clear. - She's coming.
- But the car... She's coming out! - She's coming out.
Ma'am, just a moment.
Please, just give me a minute of your time.
You know, don't you? Why Shin Jae is acting this way.
I'm sure you know Shin Jae better than I do,
but this isn't like her.
Something's happened to Shin Jae, hasn't it?
(Haeil Law Firm)
She said, aside from jumping into the flames,
there was no other path for her.
And here we are.
My daughter is a victim of Connect In.
And someone is pulling her strings.
I'm sure whatever Shin Jae is doing is connected.
Please, help me.
It's Baek Tae Joo.
He's the one who pushed my daughter into the fire.
We should have had this talk much sooner.
I feel this conversation is a bit overdue.
I never really thought of our relationship that way.
Perhaps we can be, moving forward.
As you well know,
you can't get very far when you have too many enemies.
But those who realise an enemy can become an ally tend to last longer.
So, what is it you want?
I was hoping we could let bygones be bygones...
and work for our mutual benefit.
I think it would be in both our interests.
Mutual benefit?
And what is it you want from me?
Did you turn my file over to the Corruption Investigation Office too?
And what if I didn't?
What is it that you want, CEO Baek?
Whatever I can give you, just say the word.
You seem to think you still have...
something to offer to me.
Without Haeil, what could you possibly offer me?
All you have left now is the "sex offender" label.
So, what, you want me to die?
Like your sister?
I'm sorry that Seo Ji Yoon died.
I never thought she'd do that.
But doing this...
won't bring your sister back to life.
This was an enlightening conversation.
Thank you for proving me right once again.
It's a match.
This was scraped from fragments of the Connect In app via forensics.
And this code is from a security app CEO Baek made in the past.
See? They're identical.
He reused a past vulnerability to create the attack code.
So, Baek Tae Joo created the Connect In app?
(Baek Tae Joo)
(Baek Tae Joo, Connect In App, Developer)
He did all this...
just to get his revenge?
Then Shin Jae...
knew all this and worked with him anyway.
(Attorney Kang Shin Jae)
Where's Han Min Seo?
The daughter you abandoned, Attorney Yoon?
I'm afraid you've come to the wrong person to find her.
If anything at all happens to her,
I will kill you with my bare hands.
You make it sound like I put Han Min Seo up to this.
Getting revenge on her parents...
and posting those videos on Connect In were her own choices.
Han Min Seo is an adult.
She can make her own choices and be responsible. Don't you agree?
Is that right?
Would she have done it if she knew you created the Connect In app?
All I did was create an app with a robust security system.
Park Je Yeol and the users were the ones who abused it.
But you knew it would be exploited.
No, you built it so they would.
And that's how I caught them all.
Park Je Yeol, Haeil,
and the vermin who kept getting away with these things.
If I hadn't created Connect In, you think it wouldn't have happened?
And if I hadn't, would you ever have caught them?
That's why, in ten years, you all have changed nothing.
Look. What happened to you...
ended up happening to your daughter all over again.
Right.
But what happened to me also happened to your sister.
Do you think this is...
what your sister would have wanted?
Han Min Seo will be safe.
As long as you stay out of it, Attorney Yoon.
Everything turned out just the way you wanted, Min Seo.
CEO Baek?
The people who tormented you are all going to pay the price now.
This is what you wanted, isn't it?
Where am I?
Why am I here?
The police are looking for you right now.
Things got dangerous, so you're just laying low for a bit.
Then what is this?
Latvia, wasn't it? The place you said you wanted to go?
You said you wanted a fresh start where nobody knows you.
Hello? Over here! Is anyone there?
- Help me! - Just rest until we get there.
Everything will be peaceful very soon.
Untie me, right now!
I said, untie me!
Sweet dreams.
Untie me before you go!
Hey, untie me!
Yeouido and the government district are in complete chaos.
Now the summonses have started,
everyone is busy trying to save their skin.
Statements are pouring in as they're all blaming each other.
The fallout is so huge, it's very likely...
they'll all be arrested and indicted.
Haeil is going down with them,
so they're not getting out of this one.
The only hurdle we have left now is our Technology Demonstration.
As long as we get a good score on the technical evaluation,
we should be able to win the bid without any trouble.
It's a perfect fit.
Starting with this project,
we're now sharing the same dream.
If I were you, I'd make them all pay.
You have every right to bring them to justice, Min Seo.
And I know exactly how.
I can even help you, if you want.
So, feeling better now?
The people who tormented you are all going to pay the price now.
This is what you wanted, isn't it?
(Bukgwang Hospital)
(Han Min Seo)
Where's my phone?
It's in the patient belongings room.
Take me there.
Hey, I thought your shift was over.
Yes. I was just about to head out.
- Get home safe. - Okay.
Here you go.
What about my necklace?
Your necklace?
There wasn't one in here.
(New message from Yoon Ra Young)
By the way, about your shift tomorrow...
Patient Han Min Seo has escaped her room.
He's holding Min Seo hostage.
So even if we find out who he is, there's nothing we can do.
Then how did Shin Jae get the video Min Seo shot?
Don't you think we should talk to Shin Jae?
(Han Min Seo)
Hello?
Min Seo?
Where are you right now?
Seon Kyu, Min Seo just called.
Yes, sir. We're looking for her now.
She's at the hospital, so we'll ensure she is found safely.
No. Just take care of her.
(Death certificate)
(Kim Cheol Gi, Director, Bukgwang Hospital)
(Hospital Director: Im Seo Jin)
(Record book)
(Death certificate)
(Cause of Death: Cardiopulmonary Arrest)
(Han Ji Yeon)
(Administration office)
I'm sorry, but we have no patient by that name registered here.
This is her. Are you sure you've never seen her?
I'm sorry. We have no such patient.
We traced her phone's last signal here.
Look, she made a call from this location two hours ago.
A cell tower's signal has a wide radius.
Couldn't she have made the call from somewhere else?
This was the only occupied building in this area.
Or what? Are you saying she called from a mountain with no reception?
I'm sorry, but there's nothing more I can tell you.
Fine. I get it.
(Han Ji Yeon)
Ma'am, you're not allowed to touch that.
(Death certificate: Han Ji Yeon)
(Bukgwang Hospital)
What did you find out?
They insist it's not her chart and claim they've never seen her.
That makes no sense.
Then why is Min Seo's picture on it? And we know her phone pinged here.
We can't press them any further without a warrant.
And we can't search the premises either.
Looks like the local precinct is here.
Hello.
Han Min Seo will be safe.
As long as you stay out of it, Attorney Yoon.
Baek Tae Joo.
Ra Young.
The prime suspect in a murder case, Ms. Han,
has reportedly been found hiding out at a remote psychiatric hospital,
prompting police to launch an urgent investigation.
The hospital claims it has no record...
of the patient ever being admitted...
and is flatly denying the allegations,
complicating the investigation.
The hospital was also investigated in the past...
after several patients died...
under suspicious circumstances, including medication overdoses.
This revelation increased suspicion surrounding the hospital.
Something's happened to Min Seo.
Something terrible might've happened to her.
I just saw the news.
Who do you think locked her up in there?
It's Baek Tae Joo. He's the one who created Connect In.
Don't tell me... Did you know?
I did.
Then how could you not say a single word to me?
She might be safer in there, you know.
Who knows what dangerous stunt she'd pull otherwise?
It's no coincidence that all of us, Park Je Yeol, and Min Seo,
got tangled up with Connect In.
Even before Yoo Jeong came to us, before Park Je Yeol ran Connect In,
we were already a part of his plan.
He planned everything, even selling Min Seo to Connect In.
And it's my fault he put Min Seo in that hospital.
So?
What do you mean, "So?"
Min Seo could be dead because of Baek Tae Joo.
But you said they haven't found her yet, right?
She might've just walked out on her own.
There's no proof CEO Baek was involved.
Are you serious?
I am.
I never would have imagined...
that I...
would lose you like this.
It's me. You can open up.
If you want to see for yourself, open your mother's safe.
You'll find out why Haeil has to disappear.
And one more thing.
And just in case you were worried,
I'm taking very good care of Han Min Seo.
If saving Ra Young is the price,
then fine.
I'll go to the fiery pit.
Gladly.
It wasn't until I went to college that I came to Korea to find her.
My sister was in the hospital.
Find out which hospital Seo Ji Yoon was admitted to.
You are...
I brought you some essentials.
Do I have to hide that I'm safe from Attorney Yoon too?
Yes.
Otherwise, CEO Baek will find out, and he'll come after you.
You're Ra Young's biggest weakness,
and you're his weakness too since you know everything he's done.
This will all be over in two days.
Just stay here until the day of the tech demo.
Why did you save me?
You could've just looked the other way.
You saw the newborn's jacket that Ra Young has, right?
This isn't your fault, Min Seo. I'll handle this.
Because I'm the one who bought it.
(Yoon Ra Young)
Min Seo.
There's so much I want to ask, where you are and if you're okay.
But I just need you to remember one thing.
No matter how much you may hate me or whatever you may have done,
know that I'm here for you,
and that I'm not going anywhere.
I'm very sorry, sir.
I have no idea how she just vanished from the hospital without a trace.
And the police investigation is giving me such a headache.
A complicated investigation won't do you any good, sir, so...
- can you wait till it dies down... - Wait.
(137S 5779)
So, the reason you haven't caught Han Min Seo...
was right here.
(137S 5779)
(Smart City OS Technology Demonstration)
Sign here, please.
(CCTV bypass secured. Server access granted.)
(Smart City OS Technology Demonstration)
Okay, I'm in.
Authentication successful.
I put the cameras on a 20-minute loop.
You have to be out before then.
Got it.
Authentication successful.
You're connected.
Hey, I've already taken care of the firmware for your sensor.
(Admin biometric authentication required)
There. I'm implanting the installation code now.
Now, as long as the demonstration goes off without a hitch,
the whole world will find out who Baek Tae Joo really is.
Because of the security network, it needs external authentication.
That way, if Baek Tae Joo snoops around, he'll never find it.
It will activate tomorrow when you enter the code.
All done.
(Security alert: Main server access)
(Admin biometric authentication approved)
Good. Baek Tae Joo must know by now. You need to leave right now.
But are you sure you'll be okay?
Don't worry about me. Just go.
(User: Kang Shin Jae, Legal Team)
I appreciate your help. So this is it.
(This is innovation. We design optimised IT strategies.)
This is an apartment complex in Mujin.
It appears we have an intruder.
With a conventional system, the victim or a witness...
would have to report the crime before police could be dispatched.
But in a city run by The Prime, things are different.
The Prime's OS analyses movement and behaviour patterns,
identifying them as a threat within five seconds.
This information is sent instantly to the police control center,
and the closest security team is dispatched.
Before a crime can even be committed,
the threat is eliminated first.
In the live demo that will follow shortly,
we will show you this entire process in real time.
You will see just how our algorithm perfectly protects Mujin residents,
and you will witness it with your very own eyes.
Thank you. After a short break,
we will commence the QnA...
and The Prime's Smart City Demonstration.
Here to congratulate me?
I told you, didn't I?
If anything happens to Han Min Seo, I'll kill you with my own hands.
We are one step away from a whole new world.
Why must humans ruin everything...
because they can't bear to shed the last drop of blood?
Notice how Shin Jae isn't here?
Aren't you curious where she might be right now?
(Gaseous fire suppression system)
Pressing this instantly releases a clean agent fire suppression gas.
It will remove all the oxygen from the room Shin Jae is in,
bringing it to zero percent within three minutes.
I wonder how many minutes she can last without oxygen.
If you don't want to find out,
keep your mouth shut.
(Honour)
I don't understand why I had to go through all of this.
You just left her with Baek Tae Joo?
I don't call this surveillance. I call it protection.
I'm telling you, this was the missing person's last location!
Seon Kyu, can you hear me? Seon Kyu.
- Was this your plan all along? - And you thought I'd let it slide?
If you ask me, the most dangerous person in this hall right now...
is you.