[theme music playing]
[line ringing]
WHEN THE PHONE RINGS
[elevator dings]
[indistinct chatter]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Hee-joo] I can't do this. Just let me out.
- [officer 2] We're on the road right now.
- It'll be okay if you just let me out.
It'll be okay, so let me out!
[Hee-joo gasping for air]
[Yeon-hui] I don't care.
Anyway, now that he's been moved,
I don't need to pay anymore, right?
[door opens]
[gasps] Hey, Sa-eon.
[exhales]
When did you get here?
[Sa-eon] Let's go in.
Oh my. You really are polite.
I'm curious about something.
[Yeon-hui] What?
Why won't Hee-joo speak?
What do you mean? Don't you know?
She's in shock from a
car accident as a child.
That shock…
affects her to this day?
Selective mutism
is when someone stops speaking
due to psychological factors.
Isn't it strange that she's
been like that for over 20 years?
Well, the guilt was just so overwhelming.
What guilt?
Was the car accident Hee-joo's fault?
She lost her brother,
and her sister went deaf.
How could she be okay
after that? She shouldn't be.
[sighs]
But…
why do you ask that?
It seems you keep forgetting.
Hee-joo's my wife.
Please be careful how you treat
her. Watch what you say and do.
[music ends]
What was that?
Is he looking out for Hee-joo?
[classical music playing]
Sa-eon.
It's been a while.
I almost forgot your face.
Let's meet up more often.
Yeah, you're much more handsome now.
- In-a must be treating you well.
- [woman 1] Yeah.
-[woman 2] Let's toast. -Cheers.
-Cheers. -Let's toast.
[woman 3] It's nice.
- [woman 2] I can taste apples.
- [woman 3] They're well-prepared.
- [woman 2] Such a sommelier.
- [woman 1] That's right.
Spokesperson.
Sir.
When do you plan on joining your father?
[sighs]
I guess you haven't received
a satisfactory offer yet.
Things should be clear-cut
between parents and children as well.
[phone vibrating]
Excuse me.
[intriguing music playing]
[Sa-eon] What did you say?
Supplementary pages?
[scoffs]
If you don't know, listen carefully, 406.
Hee-joo isn't supplementary pages.
She's a brand-new language.
She's repeated the same hand movements
thousands of times to become who she is.
People don't know that.
So don't talk about my wife like that.
Excuse me, where did you find that?
Oh.
In the bathroom.
You say you know her so
well. Then why did you do that?
Why did you tell her not
to think you were a couple?
[elevator dings]
[intriguing music continues playing]
[gasps]
[dramatic music playing]
[thuds]
[music ends]
Are you okay?
[Sa-eon sighs]
Why were you on the railing?
Are you trying to get yourself killed?
[hiccups]
[gripping music playing]
[Sa-eon] Were you on a call?
[scoffs]
Hong Hee-joo…
can't make calls.
Why were you on the phone?
[mouthing]
Make a sound.
Make a sound like you just
did. Hiccup or whatever.
Should I force you?
[scoffs]
Hong Hee-joo.
How could you?
[music ends]
[phone vibrating]
Go ahead.
Yes?
[Do-jae] The call went
over the ten-minute mark.
We got the location.
Where is it?
[Do-jae] Don't be surprised.
Sogong-dong. The hotel you're at right now.
I think this person is much
closer to you than we thought.
Is there anyone suspicious around you?
[suspenseful music playing]
[scoffs]
What am I thinking?
Wait.
Are you saying he's here right now?
[elevator dings]
[breathing heavily]
[suspenseful music continues playing]
[music ends]
Why aren't you going in?
[slow music playing]
[Jang-ho] Kyu-jin.
There must not be
even a single rusty spoon in my household.
Think carefully which
is more important to you.
Being a mother to your son
or maintaining your status
as my daughter-in-law?
[tense music playing]
[Sa-eon sighs]
[panting]
[line ringing]
-[exhales heavily] -[Do-jae] Yes, Mr. Paik.
Secure the guest list.
Hurry up and work on removing
the voice modulation too.
EPISODE 5
[door closes]
[Sa-eon] Hong Hee-joo.
Do you still have that scar?
[mellow music playing]
When you were a kid,
you almost got bitten by a big dog.
Even back then, you didn't
let out a single scream.
How could such a young girl
hold back a scream?
You're incredible, Hee-joo.
I wonder how long you'll
be able to hold out.
I'm curious.
[door opens, closes]
[young Hee-joo] "Our next story."
"Pope Benedict XVI resigned,
and Pope Francis was elected."
"This is the first papal
resignation in 600 years
while the pope is still alive."
[Yeon-hui] Hee-joo!
What's this?
Your dream is to be a
newscaster? A newscaster?
How can you be a newscaster?
You can't even speak! How?
[voice shaking] Didn't I make myself clear?
The moment you start
chattering in front of In-a,
you and I will be kicked out of this house.
[Yeon-hui exhales frustratingly]
[dramatic music playing]
[sobbing]
[dog growling]
[barks]
[breathing heavily]
[dog growling]
[dog barking]
[music stops]
-[thuds] -[dog whimpering]
[mellow music playing]
I'm sure it wasn't the dog that hit you.
You should fight back.
Be it your mom, sister, or whoever.
Prepare yourself to fight back.
[sighs]
Whether it's parents or family,
there's always a chance for revenge.
You scraped your knee.
[mellow music continues playing]
PAIK SA-EON
[young Sa-eon] It's red,
like your swollen cheek.
[Sa-eon] Hee-joo isn't supplementary pages.
She's a brand-new language.
[music ends]
[sighs]
[sighs softly]
Hong Hee-joo.
Come out here.
[dramatic music playing]
All this time,
you've been deceiving me, haven't you?
[Sa-eon scoffs]
Don't look at me like you
don't know. I know everything.
Why?
Why did you go that far?
You've deceived me for 20 years!
You even resorted to doing this, but why?
Yeah, let's just say
you were young back then.
But you…
You're not a kid
anymore. You're a grown-up.
At least once you started living with me,
there was no reason to hide it.
[dramatic music continues playing]
[scoffs]
Everyone has secrets.
Don't you have any? Something
you're hiding from me.
[scoffs]
[music stops]
[slow music playing]
Finalists for the sign
language interpreter interview
will be contacted individually.
They'll start work at the office tomorrow.
The main media reactions to the hiring are…
[quirky music playing]
[gulps]
"Everyone now has
acquired the right to watch
the president's speech
without discrimination."
"Korean Sign Language is on
par with the Korean language,
ensuring information access for the Deaf…"
-Excuse me, sir? -[music ends]
Yes, well…
I know I'm lacking. I do, but still…
I worked hard to prepare this.
If something is making you uncomfortable
or making you unhappy, please…
No. [clears throat]
I'm pleased with it.
Great work.
Let's take a quick break.
[amusing music playing]
MEN'S RESTROOM
[Young-woo] My liver enzyme levels
didn't just go up for no reason.
When you get anxious, your liver shrinks.
What? Because of smoking and
drinking? No, that's a misconception.
Accumulated fatigue and stress
are all causes too, you know?
Okay, honey.
Yeah, I'll make sure
to take my supplements.
One more thing.
I'm going to stand tall,
and I'm not going to…
Sir…
-Mr. Paik? -Mr. Kang?
Yes, sir.
Let's have a word.
[Sa-eon] Mr. Kang, do you…
tell your wife everything?
About that.
I definitely wasn't talking about you.
- It was about my health.
- [Sa-eon] Are there…
no secrets?
Excuse me?
In your marriage,
do you hide anything
or deceive each other?
[spluttering] I don't know. Not really.
Why do you ask?
Is your wife secretly hiding…
emergency funds from you?
[amusing music playing]
No.
What a relief.
As long as it's not about
money, right? [chuckles]
-Is that so? -Of course.
Also… [clears throat]
sometimes it's necessary to pretend
not to know and let things slide.
That's how you get some breathing room.
It'll be suffocating if you nitpick
and criticize every little thing.
Of course,
that won't be easy, given your personality.
What's wrong with it?
Like, you're the type
who strives for perfection.
But still, marriage takes
effort, don't you think?
You could try calming your temper.
Effort?
[clock ticking]
[phone vibrates]
[gentle music playing]
What? Goodness!
She passed! She passed!
-She passed! -[overlapping chatter]
Congratulations.
Congratulations!
She passed!
[music pauses]
CONGRATULATIONS ON
PASSING THE FINAL INTERVIEW.
[Jin-e] You worked hard.
[music continues playing]
Great job.
Go and tell your family the good news.
Should we get some
drinks? What should we get?
-Yeah. -[Jin-e] Let's go.
- [man] Are you buying?
- [Jin-e] Let's have cake.
[woman] Cake!
[man] It's been so long.
DAD
[gentle music continues playing]
PAIK SA-EON
[Hee-joo] I passed.
There was no special treatment, right?
Did I earn this on my own?
[sighs]
Why is this so hard?
What do I do?
[music ends]
[Young-woo] Almost forgot.
We have a welcome dinner
for the interpreters tomorrow.
We anticipate your attendance.
Normally, holding a company retreat
would be the proper thing to do.
However, many are
exhausted from the workload.
Especially since Mr. Paik
has such a tight schedule,
we'll have a dinner instead.
[amusing music playing]
Sir?
What did you just say?
A company retreat?
No, no. Since you have a busy
schedule, we'll have a dinner…
Aren't they the first sign language
interpreters in the president's office?
The media is interested as well.
Shouldn't we take a commemorative
photo for the press release?
Let's go on a retreat.
How's the weekend for everyone?
I'm free.
[Sa-eon] Sounds good.
Since we're going, let's
make it an overnight trip.
Please arrange the venue.
[employee 1] Wow, I
completely misjudged Mr. Park.
"I'm free."
[employee 2] They call him
Mr. Paik's mini-me for a reason.
No wonder Mr. Paik brought
him in when he started here.
[sighs]
He doesn't even attend the dinners, so why?
[mellow music playing]
[Sa-eon] What's this?
It came out of nowhere.
[sighs]
[Hee-joo] Should I delete it now?
That would be weirder.
My stupid finger.
[sighs]
[chuckles softly]
[Sa-eon] What does this
mean? Explain yourself.
[sighs]
"Explain yourself"?
Is that too intense?
[sighs]
[mellow music continues playing]
[phone thuds]
[sighs softly]
[Hee-joo] What do I do? I can't look.
[Sa-eon] Congrats on passing.
[music ends]
[Sa-eon sighs]
Mmm.
It's good. Just how I like it. Great pick.
I'm glad you enjoy it.
[Young-woo chuckles]
Try it, Mr. Paik.
Okay.
It's good.
[both chuckling softly]
-[phone vibrates] -[employee] It is good.
[Hee-joo] Thank you. It's thanks to you.
[chuckles softly]
[quirky music playing]
[Sa-eon] No, it's not.
Refrain from making statements
that could be misunderstood.
Let me be clear. There
was no special treatment.
[inhales sharply]
Is it too stiff?
It's fine for me. Mr. Paik!
You must have weak teeth. [laughs]
[phone vibrates]
[Hee-joo] I'll buy you a meal.
[scoffs]
You'll buy me a meal?
What's a good gift to give
someone who just got a job?
- The latest cellphone.
- It's already the latest.
A tablet? Laptop?
They have both.
What else?
Share some ideas.
Well, a wallet?
-A bag? -Not something you want.
Something practical…
-It doesn't have to be practical. -…or not.
-It doesn't have to be practical. -Yeah.
[Young-woo] Something sentimental.
Something thoughtful.
A new suit is pretty much
the go-to gift for a new job.
Come on.
A suit?
Great pick.
Yeah, not bad.
[softly] A suit.
[phone vibrates]
[Sa-eon] Come here by six.
[suspenseful music playing]
[You-ri] You want to go in there?
Yes.
-[crow caws] -[screams] Wait for me!
[metal rattling]
[You-ri] Goodness.
-[metal rattling] -No way.
We can't go over this.
What are you doing?
[Sang-woo] I think it was here.
What?
A large portrait.
I remember a huge hand with a dragon ring.
[sighs]
The room you played in every day.
Where is it?
That room.
Follow me.
[wind whistling]
[You-ri] Wow.
[inhales sharply] This is the room.
I'm sure I saw it that day.
What?
A cute…
cat.
-[thunder rumbling] -[rain pattering]
[mysterious music playing]
That child told me.
"Want to play?"
What? With what?
Let's cut open the cat's belly.
[Sang-woo] "Next, the tail."
[thunder rumbling]
"Next, the leg."
"Next, the head."
[mysterious music continues playing]
[thunderclap]
[young Sang-woo breathing heavily]
[music fades]
The way he spoke sounded so innocent.
He said it as if it was nothing.
It made it more terrifying.
Missing?
Yes, a few kids from the orphanage
went missing shortly after being adopted.
I learned that after becoming an adult.
It's still an unsolved case.
Do you remember what you
said at our first meeting?
Instead of asking what it is,
shouldn't you be asking why
I haven't revealed it yet?
[suspenseful music playing]
What's the reason?
Why are you digging up something
that happened over 20 years ago?
I was the first to discover that villa.
I suggested to the kids that we go too.
Once my channel grew big enough,
I wanted to reveal it when
people started paying attention.
Then I got the chance to be on
the show and thought, "This is it."
You've been holding
onto this for a long time.
I'm sorry.
You are?
For what?
To be honest,
Sa-eon asked me about you a few days ago.
I told him you grew up
in an orphanage by mistake.
Spokesperson Paik Sa-eon asked about me?
Like what?
You know, this and that.
[phone vibrates]
[gasps] Goodness!
What is it?
This is great for Hee-joo!
What about Hee-joo?
She's going to the presidential office.
[elevator dings]
Are you Ms. Hong Hee-joo?
Right this way.
Considering the professional setting,
I went with a neutral and simple style
without any bold patterns or decorations.
What do you think?
The spokesperson's office called.
He said that you're the sign language
interpreter for the presidential office.
I was asked to prepare
an outfit suitable for you.
Would you like to try it on?
[elevator dings]
[saleslady] Welcome.
[intriguing music playing]
[saleslady chuckles softly]
It looks great with your complexion.
But it looks a little big. I'll
get you one in a smaller size.
You look so pretty.
You have such great proportions. That
suit really flatters you. [chuckles]
[Sa-eon] It looks good on you.
We'll take it.
Okay, I'll wrap it up.
You can go ahead and
change if you're ready.
[intriguing music continues playing]
Try this one on too.
[saleslady gasps, chuckles]
[Sa-eon] Thank you. Goodbye.
[manager] Take care.
[music ends]
Why didn't you try it on?
[Hee-joo] I don't have
to try it on to know.
Know what?
I appreciate the suit. I'll wear it well.
Let's go and eat now.
[sighs]
What do you know?
I know something that
flashy doesn't really suit me.
[Sa-eon sighs]
I have nowhere to wear it to, and
it doesn't feel like it's for me.
So why bother?
Then, what about that?
[soft music playing]
[phone vibrating]
PARK DO-JAE
Yes, go ahead.
The modulated voice
analysis isn't complete yet,
but I just received a strange report.
- What strange report?
- [Do-jae] Don't be surprised.
Based on the waveform and
spectrogram analysis, 406 is…
[suspenseful music playing]
[Sa-eon] A woman?
Are you sure?
Of course, there's a
possibility of an accomplice,
-or it could be a decoy. -A decoy?
Using someone else's voice
without being the perpetrator.
You mean like a recording
or reading a script?
It's definitely not that.
The conversations weren't just
regurgitated on command like a parrot
but were more like real-time exchanges.
Rule out the possibility of recordings.
- Proceed with the analysis…
- [door opens, closes]
[pleasant music playing]
Hong Hee-joo.
Underestimating yourself is a bad habit.
I'd like to help you break that bad habit.
What do you think?
[mellow music playing]
It's expensive.
It says it's Hanwoo.
I want jjajangmyeon.
That's enough.
[sighs]
With sweet and sour pork.
[chuckles softly]
SANG-WOO
[quirky music playing]
[phone vibrates]
[Sang-woo] Hee-joo, I heard the
news. Congrats on the interpreter job.
Do you want some wine?
You-ri wants to congratulate you too.
[Hee-joo] Sang-woo, I'm
sorry, but next time…
Go now.
But with me.
[sighs]
[bottle pops]
- [You-ri] Congratulations, Hee-joo.
- [Sang-woo] Congrats.
[glasses clinking]
[exhales]
But how did you two come together?
She said she'd buy me dinner.
Interpreter Hong Hee-joo.
She did? Why?
Can she not?
[Sang-woo] Not without a reason.
There must be one.
Then why are you two together?
We're coming back from covering a site.
You know that we're doing a show together.
- You-ri told me you asked her about me.
- [You-ri gasps]
What's the story about?
Oh…
Well…
A case of missing
children from an orphanage.
[Sang-woo] We can't discuss
it due to program security.
I'm sorry I cut you off.
Will you answer me now?
Tell me.
Why are you so interested in me?
[Hee-joo] Hey, Sang-woo.
Didn't you want to congratulate me?
Yeah.
Sorry.
Hee-joo, the sign language
interpreter for the presidential office.
Yeah, it's something to congratulate,
but wasn't your dream something else?
[mellow music playing]
LEAVE NEWSCASTER APPLICATION HERE
NAME: HONG HEE-JOO
[music ends]
[upbeat song playing]
[song playing over speakers]
[song stops playing]
[mellow music playing]
[Sang-woo] After that, we listened
to music often in the broadcast room.
Oh.
Did something happen
between you two in college?
Right? I can totally sense it.
You have a bad sense.
You're known for that.
[scoffs]
Me?
What I said is based on facts.
It's crystal clear.
A college broadcast room
is perfect for flirting. [giggles]
[amusing music playing]
[inhales]
Did you two flirt?
[You-ri] Why would you
ask that? They totally did!
Why else would Hee-joo
go to the broadcast room?
It wasn't to be a newscaster.
[Sang-woo] She could be one.
Can she not?
Excuse me?
But how could she be a newscaster?
[chuckles nervously]
Of course, she can. What I meant was…
She could definitely be a newscaster.
You must have dreamed
of becoming a newscaster.
I didn't know. [chuckles nervously]
Why are you bringing that up now?
She's the sign language interpreter
for the presidential office.
Why ask about her dream now?
- Are you trying to rain on her parade?
- You think I am?
She wants us to stop.
"It's true I wanted to be
a newscaster in the past."
"Now, I'm happy to be the sign language
interpreter for the presidential office."
[Hee-joo] Got it?
[door opens]
[door closes]
[drink pouring]
[chuckles softly]
It's just…
My glass was empty. [chuckles]
[phone vibrates]
IN-A
IT'S ME. HOW ARE YOU? IT'S BEEN A WHILE.
[slow music playing]
[You-ri] Hey.
Do you think Hee-joo went to the bathroom?
I'll go check.
Who wants ice cream?
All of a sudden?
[You-ri] Me!
I want chocolate!
Get me whatever!
[panting]
Hey, sis!
Something really fun
happened at school today.
I'll tell you.
A friend sent me a note.
Do you know what was written on it?
[doorbell rings]
PAIK SA-EON
Why are you here?
[young Hee-joo] I'm going to
pass on what you say to my sister.
You?
I heard you're deaf.
Why don't you wear hearing
aids or learn to sign?
[sighs]
[slow music playing]
[young Hee-joo] He looks
forward to studying math with you!
[young Sa-eon] Solve it.
[sighs softly]
Do it again.
Another mistake and I'll
pour water on your head.
[slow music continues playing]
[young Hee-joo] In-a, solve
it again. You can do better.
[phone vibrating]
[Sa-eon] I'm glad you called.
I had a question for you.
[Hee-joo] A question for me?
What is it?
Have you heard Hee-joo's voice before?
What are you saying?
She can't speak. How could I?
Then do you know why she can't speak?
Since the accident that caused
Hong In-a to lose her hearing,
she hasn't worn hearing aids.
She didn't learn to sign.
Instead, she took Hee-joo around
and had her convey
people's words through notes.
She lost her brother,
and her sister went deaf.
How could she be okay
after that? She shouldn't be.
[mysterious music playing]
Wait.
Is it because of Hong In-a?
What do you mean?
[scoffs]
Chairman Hong's only biological
daughter became disabled,
and Hee-joo, who lived under the same roof…
was probably forced to keep quiet too.
That's the ridiculous story I had in mind.
Aside from that,
I can't find another reason.
[Hee-joo] You've mentioned before
that you have no intention
of letting Hong Hee-joo go.
If Hong In-a returns,
will you still feel the same?
Yes, I will.
Why? Why won't you let her go?
-A sense of responsibility? -No.
Then…
is it sympathy?
What did you just say?
Sympathy?
I'll say it once, so listen carefully, 406.
My true feelings for Hee-joo…
[car revving]
Paik Sa-eon!
-[Hee-joo panting] -[Sa-eon groans]
[both breathing heavily]
[slow music playing]
[groans]
[breathing heavily]
You don't need to go to the hospital?
[sighs]
You work with your hands,
so you have to be careful.
How many times have I told you?
[sighs] Have you no fear?
Where did you come from?
And how are you so strong?
You took me down.
[Hee-joo] Paik Sa-eon!
[intriguing music playing]
I…
Think I heard it.
Your voice.
Did you call my name?
I want to hear it again.
Your voice.
Hong Hee-joo.
The world won't fall apart if you speak up.
Everything you want to say,
the things you've held back…
Say whatever you want.
IT'S ME. HOW ARE YOU? IT'S BEEN A WHILE.
[intriguing music continues playing]
[Sa-eon] Hong Hee-joo.
Underestimating yourself is a bad habit.
I'd like to help you break that bad habit.
What do you think?
[phone vibrating]
UNKNOWN CALLER
[breathing heavily]
[eerie music playing]
[kidnapper] Sis!
How have you been?
Welcome and congratulations.
What's your name?
It's Jeong Won-bin.
Won-bin.
You live up to your name, don't you?
The face-off for who's more
handsome will be intense.
No way, I could never compete.
-I hear we look alike though.
[laughs] -[press secretary laughs]
What's your name?
[chuckles]
I'm sorry. I don't know
sign language. [laughs]
I see.
How can we communicate during work?
Shall we all learn sign language?
I'm thinking of learning it.
You?
Yes.
That way, I can ensure the interpreters
are conveying my words accurately.
If there's any difference in nuance,
I'll be able to correct it.
[Hee-joo] Sign language isn't difficult.
If you learn it, there won't be
issues communicating with me either.
I'm going to start learning it today.
[press secretary] Wow.
A spokesperson who can sign.
Social media will eat that
up. Think of all the likes.
-[all laughing] -You're right.
[all applauding]
- [male assistant] Welcome.
- [press secretary] Congratulations.
FINGER ALPHABET
I've already memorized this.
I've prepared in advance.
It wasn't that hard.
"A. B."
"C. D."
"A hundred questions, a hundred answers"?
"Write down one word or sentence you
want to learn in sign language every day."
Starting today?
Hmm.
Teach me.
[soft song playing]
What about this?
[song continues playing]
[Sa-eon] I look forward
to working with you.
Hong.
Hee.
Joo.
Interpreter.
What?
Did I get it wrong?
[Hee-joo] I look forward
to working with you as well.
Paik Sa-eon.
Spokesperson.
[scoffs]
[Sa-eon chuckles softly]
-[indistinct chatter] -[sizzling]
[patting]
Excuse me?
Sir?
Yes?
You don't usually come to team
dinners, so I just came to our usual spot.
What do you think? Is it okay?
Yes, it's fine.
I'm relieved to hear it.
There's no place better
than this for a team dinner.
[all chuckling nervously]
-[Sa-eon] Mr. Kang. -Yes?
What are you doing?
Excuse me? I don't…
The meat's burning.
I see!
I'll…
[playful music playing]
[Young-woo groans softly]
-[male assistant] Wow. -[Young-woo] Whoa!
[camera shutter clicking]
[exclaims]
[all exclaim]
Let's eat.
-Yes, sir. -[all] Thank you.
[Young-woo clears throat]
[Young-woo] What?
[chuckles softly]
You grilled it perfectly! It's delicious.
[employee 1] It's really good.
Eat up, everyone.
[phone vibrating]
- [Young-woo] Do you want some?
- [employee 2] Yes.
[Young-woo] It's so good.
-A big one. -[employee 2] Thanks.
-[assistant] Me too. -We don't have enough.
[Young-woo] Um,
sir, should we…
do a toast...
[Young-woo whispering]
[Sa-eon clears throat]
[interpreter] What?
We look forward to
working with you as well!
That's what that means.
-Goodness. -I see.
-Let's toast. -Everyone, enjoy!
-Enjoy! -Cheers!
[Young-woo] Welcome!
This is Mr. Paik's treat. It's on him.
Help yourselves.
[Young-woo exclaims]
[Young-woo exhales]
[employee 1] It's so good.
[Do-jae] Sir, just a moment.
- [Young-woo] Eat. Yes.
- [employee 1] Eat up. I need more alcohol.
- [Young-woo] I'll pour it.
- [employee 1] Yeah.
The call just came in.
The voice analysis was almost
complete, but malware was detected.
- The computer shut down completely.
- So what?
Most of the original files are gone,
but we were able to get results
from the recovered fragmented files.
The audio quality isn't great.
Can I listen to it?
Yes, but…
Please listen to it first.
[suspenseful music playing]
[kidnapper] Sis, are you okay?
Were you hurt anywhere?
You know, from earlier.
You ran in front of a moving car.
[car revving]
[kidnapper laughing]
You said you were getting a divorce.
[laughing]
So you changed your mind.
You won't divorce him, will you?
Why do you want me to divorce him?
[kidnapper] Because…
I want to see that bastard,
Paik Sa-eon, be ruined.
What about you, Sis?
[sniffles]
Do you know him well?
No, I bet you don't.
You probably don't know him at all.
What do you know?
How well do you know him?
[kidnapper] Me?
[scoffs]
Why would you say something so hurtful?
Listen carefully.
In this world,
the person who knows
Paik Sa-eon the best is me.
Hurry, Sis. You're running out of time.
Paik Sa-eon will find out soon.
-What? -[kidnapper] What do you think?
Your true identity, Sis!
[suspenseful music continues playing]
[Sa-eon] Everything you want
to say, things you've held back…
Say whatever you want.
[Hee-joo] What I have to say to you…
isn't what you want to hear.
[over earphones] Decide by tomorrow.
Or we can settle for two billion
won. You have until tomorrow.
Can you guess who it is?
Someone who's close to you
and knows you...
What's the age range?
The waveform analysis indicates
a woman in her twenties.
- [Young-woo] We don't do that here.
- [employee 1] No.
- We don't pressure people to drink…
- That's right.
[Sa-eon] So where did you get
your information on Hong Hee-joo?
Are you close to me?
[Do-jae] Don't be surprised.
The hotel you're at right now.
[Hee-joo] Please, let me out!
[scoffs]
I'll send you another audio file.
Analyze the sound waveform
and compare it with 406.
See how much they match in percentage.
Up to two decimal places.
Yes, sir.
[dramatic music playing]
[employee 2] I wanted to do it.
[indistinct chatter]
Let's have one more round.
-[employee 1] Come on. -Wait. No.
[Won-bin] Get in.
[engine starting]
[Young-woo] Thank you for the dinner!
Have a good night.
-Goodbye. -Take care.
[all] Goodbye.
Wow, his first team
dinner and first time drunk.
Is something going on?
Mr. Park, do you know anything?
No.
Didn't you see them leave
together? I saw you two whispering.
There's nothing.
Let's go for another round.
-No. -[Young-woo] We're friends.
-Let's go. -[employee 2] Mr. Kang, wait!
- [assistant] Let's go to karaoke! Karaoke!
- [employee 2] Let's go home.
Sir?
[Sa-eon sighs wearily]
I'm fine.
You may go.
Yes, sir.
[sighs]
[thuds]
-[phone vibrates] -[Do-jae]
I'm sorry to bother you so late.
The analysis results came in.
It's a 99.99% match.
[soft song playing]
WHEN THE PHONE RINGS
[Sa-eon groans]
[Sa-eon] Tell me if something happened.
[Hee-joo] Should I tell
you everything honestly?
[Do-jae] You have an idea
who 406 might be, don't you?
[Hee-joo] How about we each
ask a question and answer?
[Sa-eon] By any chance, does Hee-joo want…
sincerity
and affection?
Is that what she wants?
I can give her everything.
If that's what Hee-joo wants,
I'll give as much as she needs.
Hong Hee-joo!
Subtitle translation by: Sue Mounce