With this money,
we can totally turn that scrap yard
into a restaurant.
It will surely work.
Can you cook?
Just hire a chef!
Make barbecue or something.
I-I think
it's a good idea
to turn it into a bathhouse.
Later, with the bathhouse, we...
How much does water cost?
It's not a high cost.
-We can definitely make a fortune.
-You know?
Hey!
Pay me back!
♪ He is ♪
This way, this way!
Pay me back!
Stop yelling! Stop it!
♪ Too cunning but like a joke ♪
Stop shouting! Do you hear me?
That knife of yours is dangerous!
Pay me back!
♪ Ha ha ha ♪
♪ He ♪
♪ Wears his glamorous nails ♪
This way, this way...
This way works.
♪ The discord between the body and soul,
a once-in-a-century mute ♪
♪ Pride cell, soaked in the liquid;
he wants to keep sprouting ♪
Which way are we going?
Here, this way.
♪ Absurd, empty, glorious—
superior beings ♪
Go!
♪ Smug, pure, pathetic—
this gaudy human race ♪
Stop there!
Don't move!
♪ Ha ha ha ha ♪
Come on, come on.
Come up here. Come on.
Come up.
I...
What?
Come up. Come on.
Screw you!
♪ Ha ha ha ha ♪
Come up here. Come on.
What?
Will you come up or not?
Come up.
♪ Ha ha ha ha ♪
Get down!
What?
You guys...
Come down!
You come up here.
Come down if you dare!
Come up if you dare! Come on!
Then you two just
never ever come down if you can!
-Okay.
♪ He ♪
Screw you!
♪ A rusted flower etched
across his chest ♪
We were quite in sync just now.
Where is he?
♪ Oh, he ♪
What are you doing?
♪ Says your worldview's still too small ♪
Listen,
there's only one door left there.
Let's see how you two get out.
♪ A rat that steals rice—
humans call it cunning ♪
I'll outlast you two.
-You think we're scared of you?
And you think I'm scared of you?
I'm not scared of you!
♪ A human who steals honey—
calls the bees hardworking ♪
You can't scare me!
Don't try to scare me!
I'm not scared of you!
I-I'm not scared of you!
♪ Absurd, greedy—
self-proclaimed superior beings ♪
What are you doing?
♪ Hypocritical, wasteful, hollow—
this gaudy human race ♪
I'll wait until you two can't hold out.
Then wait.
Fine, wait. Come on.
♪ Ha ha ha ha ♪
What? Let me see.
Let me see how long you can wait.
Who can not sit down? I have a seat, too.
♪ Ha ha ha ha ♪
[Born with Luck]
[Episode 21]
Sir,
you haven't told me
how to get to the office.
It's on the first floor of Building 27.
There's a sign at the door.
Huo Zheng!
Who are you calling?
Huoxiang Zhengqi Pill.
We call it Huozheng for short.
[Wanted]
[Photo of the suspect, Huo Zheng]
Hurry up! I'm almost coughing to death!
Fetch me some Huo Zheng!
I... I'll get it.
You
really don't know Huo Zheng, do you?
I don't know him.
Hurry up!
Here are the Huoxiang Zhengqi Pills.
[Huoxiang Zhengqi Pill]
[Photo of the suspect, Huo Zheng]
[Wanted]
[Huoxiang Zhengqi Pill]
B-Bye.
Uncle.
We can't stay here anymore.
We need to leave now.
Immediately.
We can't stay here?
Go pack up!
Be careful.
Take it slow.
Don't let it get bumped.
I'll go check that one.
Chief!
We found an important clue.
What clue?
During the inspection on Qingchun Street,
someone called the name, "Huo Zheng."
Was it him?
The colleagues at the office said that,
during the inspection,
a man was
looking for Huoxiang Zhengqi Pill,
and they claimed
to call it Huo Zheng for short.
So he yelled, "Huo Zheng."
Are you nuts?
Well, I think we should
go verify it.
You think things are not urgent enough?
There's no other way.
Let's verify it just in case...
Yes, sir.
[Convenient Hotel]
I'll go with you.
I'm can't rest assured if he goes alone.
Let's go to that place.
Look at this!
Why were you in such a hurry?
I was just getting past,
yet you insisted on squeezing in!
I've been going straight.
If you hadn't cut me off,
you wouldn't be blocking the way.
Calm down first.
You bear full responsibility.
Don't...
Police.
Hello?
There are cops.
Be careful.
Don't go any further.
Not any further.
Stop, stop.
Are they...
Are they coming for us?
Yes, definitely.
Otherwise, why would the boss run?
Then don't look at them.
Insurance!
-File an insurance claim.
-Insurance claim.
Why did you have to squeeze in?
Everyone has insurance.
-Calm down, calm down.
-Call the police.
This area seriously
needs to be cleaned up.
It's such a mess.
Look at that car over there, too.
Is he...
Is he pointing at us?
He's pointing at us!
He's p-pointing...
I'll go take a look.
Okay.
Are you an intellectual?
I can't tell at all.
Move a bit.
I'm a cop.
Move back a bit. You...
Song Xing.
Song Xing!
Coming!
Stop there!
[Police]
You caught Huo Zheng?
Huo Zheng and Zhu Yifei got away.
We must pin them down at Sanjiangkou.
Let's keep looking for them.
What are you doing?
I fell asleep.
How could you fall asleep first?
Why is
this jerk so persistent?
How about this?
You keep snoring
and set the mood,
so he'll fall asleep faster.
What? Did I...
D-Did I snore just now?
It was nearly deafening.
Stop talking nonsense.
I'm the quietest
and stillest sleeper.
Can't you fake snoring?
I don't know how to snore.
How can I fake it?
You do it. Come on.
Y-You do it.
I-It's so hard to get you to do something.
I told you this trick would work.
Let's go now.
What are you doing?
Oh, my god.
He fell asleep?
Keep going.
Don't you feel we left something behind?
Why did we come up here?
We came up because of him.
The suitcase!
Holy.
You can't do anything right!
Just a moment.
All you do is sleep.
Hold this.
You kept falling asleep.
Don't screw things up.
You sure can sleep.
Why am I so sleepy?
I'm also sleepy!
♪ The stars twinkle, the moon curves ♪
♪ A gentle breeze
sways the willow branches ♪
♪ The two of us, working late at night,
sneak up to the base of the wall ♪
I also don't snore
when I sleep.
We're not going back?
Don't be silly.
When that guy wakes up
and finds us gone,
won't he go back and block us?
Where are we going now?
Follow me.
This is my backup plan.
A cunning rabbit has 3 burrows,
you know?
No.
This is my first home
in Sanjiangkou.
What is this place?
My home. Didn't I tell you?
Why is your home so dark
and full of water?
It'll be fine in a minute.
Oh, my.
Here it is.
Is it still dark now?
Yeah, it's a bit better.
There's a candle here, huh?
The lighting system.
Look over there.
My kitchen.
The stove.
Pretty good.
Let's go inside.
About this part...
Oh, my God.
Be careful.
My place has a high threshold.
Your place's threshold isn't high at all.
Anyone can enter.
The living room and the bedroom.
Sit, make yourself at home.
What should we do now?
Leave.
We just got here, and we're leaving?
Leave Sanjiangkou.
We can go anywhere.
Carrying a box of cash,
wanting to leave Sanjiangkou,
that'll be tough.
Let's turn to Li Penggai.
He works for Zhou Rong.
He must have connections.
He won't help us.
Did you forget
how we treated him before?
Well,
we'll just return the money to him
and give him a bit more.
Why wouldn't he help?
If you say so,
why didn't we just give the money
to Du Cong
instead of wasting time with him?
Who the hell is he?
I just won't give it to him.
That bastard.
Indeed, don't give it to him.
He even tried to hack us with a knife.
Right?
No way we give it to him!
Men have got to be tough.
Tough.
Absolutely tough.
Right?
Mao, your toughness
is right.
Keep it up.
I'll call Li Penggai
right now.
Right.
Take the money.
We have money.
Right?
Li Penggai.
Hello, boss man.
I-It's me, Mao.
Goodness.
Yes, yes.
The m-money is ready.
Yes, we have it.
I'll send you a location in a bit.
Come over and get it,
please.
Okay, okay.
Alright.
Okay, thank you.
Didn't you say you were tough?
I was just being a little polite.
That was way too fawning.
Lu Yibo went
to Zhou Qi's place after he left.
What about Lang Bowen?
He's been at the hospital
without even leaving the ward.
Yangyang brought him lunch
and dinner.
The two of them didn't contact anyone.
Who else could it be?
Who else?
Mr. Zhou,
why don't we start with those two guys
wanted by the police?
Who are they?
Why do the police think
they robbed you?
If we investigate them,
we might be able to find
the mastermind behind them.
How is that possible?
Unless you have someone inside the police.
Otherwise, how could you investigate?
What kind of dump is this?
Hello?
Here, over here,
Penggai!
Hello?
Behind you!
What are you two doing here?
Thanks for coming
all the way here, Penggai.
You guys are here?
C-Come in and sit for a while.
Penggai, this way.
Well...
It's literally cold and gloomy in here.
It's a humble abode.
Have a seat, Penggai.
Sit down.
Take... Take the seat of honor.
Here?
Seat of honor.
All right.
Given our years of relationship,
there's no need to be polite.
Where's the money?
Money.
Right.
The money... The money is here.
Penggai, here's
20,000 dollars.
Please count it.
You struck it rich?
Where did you get it from?
Well...
Selling blood.
Yes, from selling blood.
We sold blood.
You sold it to America?
We sold it to Americans.
Yes.
That's the blood-selling gift pack, huh?
Well...
No.
What?
What are you doing?
If I force my way to grab it today,
are you two any match for me?
-No.
But Penggai, you can't do this.
Look at your status.
We are just
nobodies.
We're small fry.
You can't snatch it like that,
right?
I-I definitely
won't do that.
What's my status now?
I'm a gold-collar worker.
Gold-collar.
Well, Penggai...
Why would I fight you for scraps?
Well...
Sit.
Can you be
honest with me?
Where did it really come from?
This is so much trouble! Oh, my!
Wait, we'll tell you. We will.
Penggai is our friend.
Just tell him.
Then I'll tell the whole story, Penggai.
Get lost.
I know you well.
You're the best at making things up.
Mao.
Be good.
Tell me
where on earth you got it from.
T-Then I'll tell you the story in detail,
Penggai.
That's how
we got this suitcase.
Is there a phone
in here, too?
Nope.
No.
Really... Really, there's nothing else.
I'm really not lying to you.
There's only money.
Penggai!
-Penggai.
-Wait, Penggai.
Hey, what... What are you doing?
Well...
Aren't you a gold-collar worker?
D-Didn't you say you wouldn't fight us
for scraps?
I have a gold knife, believe it or not.
No, no, Penggai.
-Penggai.
You...
Don't move.
I'll be right back.
Please l-leave us 200 dollars.
Ren,
I found Mr. Zhou's case.
The money is there,
but the phone is missing.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Search carefully for the phone.
How is it?
These two scrap dealers
robbed the two who robbed you.
The police didn't know they robbed
the two guys who robbed you
and thought they robbed you directly,
so they are wanted.
Robbed by two scrap dealers?
Wait, are you sure?
Li Penggai has already
gotten the suitcase.
He'll bring the people back soon,
and we'll figure it out.
Figure out my foot!
How can we figure it out?
Come on, give me the medicine.
The medicine!
You threw the medicine away.
I'll go get more prescribed for you.
Hurry!
Hurry, hurry.
I will hurry.
I'm hurrying.
Prescription drugs
must be prescribed at the hospital?
Who made that rule?
Do you have any compassion
as a medical practitioner?
I don't care.
Get the doctor up to work! Now!
Tomorrow morning?
Tomorrow morning won't do.
Bro!
Penggai.
He has a knife!
Where is the phone?
The phone is here.
I just got a new one
with a color screen.
I have it. I have a phone.
It can take pictures.
Wait.
Mao...
You two are totally done for, you know?
That phone and money
both belong to Mr. Zhou!
Hand over the phone now,
and I can still keep your bodies intact.
If you keep
playing tricks here,
no one can save you two, you know?
Li Penggai?
Is he dead or not?
Who cares if he's dead or not?
I didn't touch him.
I didn't do anything.
Hurry, let's get out of here.
Take the money away.
Okay.
Let's go.
Who drove it away?
I don't know.
What about the suitcase?
Was it Li Penggai's man?
Well, I don't know.
Do you even know anything?
Don't, don't...
What are you doing?
What should we do now?
Let's run away.
Let's go.
Let's run.
What could be in here?
He gave
1 million dollars to us
without blinking an eye.
There must be something
that threatens him in it.
No!
You can take all the money
in that suitcase.
Can you leave the phone behind?
What could it be?
What's usually kept on a phone?
-Videos.
-Adult videos.
What videos?
J-Just
the videos you mentioned.
It must be a sex tape
of him and a woman.
Can a sex tape with a woman
threaten him?
What makes Zhou Rong,
the richest man, stand out
from everyone else?
He looks like a gigolo?
Only a little better looking than me.
His muscles
aren't impressive as well.
I suspect he just
hooked up
with a powerful older woman.
He used his body to get where he is today.
If the phone has a sex video
of him and the older woman...
20 million.
If he doesn't pay 20 million,
we'll expose the older woman.
[A Collection of Classic Jokes]
It's not funny anymore.
[The World of Laughter]
[Infinite Foolishness and Fun]
This is not funny.
[A Collection of Classic Jokes]
Why is it not funny anymore?
Not funny.
Hello?
Hello, is it Mr. Zhou?
Who are you?
Mr. Zhou,
you forgot us so quickly.
You don't even want your phone anymore?
Hello?
Say something.
Give me my phone back.
How much money do you want?
20 million, deal or no deal?
20 million?
Final offer.
Accept it if you agree.
If you don't,
we'll secretly upload the stuff
on the phone to the internet.
Did you figure out
the password to unlock the phone?
Is it hard?
I really want to know
what's in this phone
that's worth 20 million!
Testing me?
There's a lot of stuff in the phone.
The valuable one is a video.
W-What video?
How am I supposed to describe it?
It's way too thrilling.
You still want to deny this?
Can you really deny it?
[The World's Jokes]
Do it!
Mr. Zhou! Mr. Zhou!
The medicine!
Here's the medicine!
Do it!
Don't get worked up.
I mean, I'll give you 20 million.
Let's do it.
How do we trade?
And when do we trade?
Get the money ready.
I'll contact you tomorrow.
Li Penggai just found those two.
How did these two pop up again?
What's going on?
How come?
Li Penggai should be back by now, huh?
[Ren]
Hello? Where are you?
I asked where you are. Speak!
Li Penggai!
I asked where you are!
[Ren]
Speak!
Li Peng...
Dude,
you can have the 1 million dollars.
Just don't hurt my friend, okay?
[Ren]
I know who you are.
He got taken down
by two junk collectors?
He actually got taken down
by junk collectors.
How could he get taken down
by two junk collectors?
And got robbed!
[We want to hitch a ride
to leave Sanjiangkou.]
There's a car coming.
[We want to hitch a ride
to leave Sanjiangkou.]
Pull over.
I can hold out, Chief.
I said, pull over.
[We want to hitch a ride
to leave Sanjiangkou.]
Here!
B-Bro.
Mao Hongwei?
Xia Tinggang?
Drive.
♪ Throw a toy to
that bunch of brokers in town ♪
[We want to hitch a ride
to leave Sanjiangkou.]
♪ From doubt, I forge a weapon ♪
Where to?
Anywhere out of Sanjiangkou will do.
♪ Oh, god ♪
Anywhere.
Anywhere will do.
♪ Please give me some guidance ♪
Get in.
What a nice guy!
Really... Really?
♪ Find the sleepy poet ♪
-Great!
-Thanks.
Squeeze in.
Can we fit?
Squeeze in. Come on.
Okay, nice.
♪ They are all guests ♪
Good.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
Don't bother
getting out of the car!
It's fine. Get in.
Thank you so much.
Where are you heading?
Just get in.
I...
♪ Throw a toy to
that bunch of brokers in town ♪
♪ From doubt, I forge a weapon ♪
♪ Oh, god ♪
♪ Please give me some guidance ♪
Take it slow.
♪ Find the sleepy poet ♪
Wait, uncle.
♪ They are all guests ♪
Be careful.
Over there!
It's over there.
Watch your steps.
There's space ahead.
Let's go take shelter.
♪ There's a strange, hazy feeling ♪
♪ Waiting for me to make sense of it ♪
Mind your steps.
♪ Worshippers hiding in the smoke,
just beyond reach ♪
Be careful.
Take it slow.
♪ They are all guests ♪
Go upstairs.
Let's go upstairs.
♪ Be patient and wait ♪
What are you two doing?
Don't come up!
Sir,
I have an old man with me.
It's raining outside.
We just want to go up
to take shelter from the rain.
We'll leave when the rain stops.
Cut the crap.
All my assets are up here.
I don't trust you two coming up.
I'll kill you.
How dare you?
Come on, kill me. Come on!
I...
Enough!
Uncle, I...
Come down.
-We're not going up.
-I'll kill you.
We won't bother you.
Did you eat crap?
You're so foul-mouthed.
Uncle,
why aren't we going up?
I can just kill him!
What happens if we go up?
It's fine.
What happens if we kill him?
If word gets out,
it's indecent
for the two of us
to fight a beggar for turf!
Uncle,
are we decent now?
Wasn't this a pure accident?
That... That guy surnamed Hu.
Hu.. What's he called again?
Jianren.
Scumbag! (Sounds like Jianren.)
He is the only one
who knows your identity!
If Zhou Rong didn't snitch,
why would the police want to arrest you?
I can bear with him snatching my goods!
But snitching is
a big taboo in the underworld.
It's despicable!
Call Zhou Rong
and tell him we'll trade tomorrow.
Uncle,
we don't have the bianzhong anymore.
How can we trade with him?
Tomorrow's trade isn't for money.
It's to take his life.
Mr. Zhou,
no matter what,
we must make this trade tomorrow.
You may rest now.
I'll go prepare the cash.
Wait,
where will you get the cash?
Mr. Zhou.
We can only ask the suppliers for cash.
If I contact a few more,
it should be enough.
I'll have them deliver it
to the company tomorrow morning.
Okay. Thanks for your hard work.
It's nothing.
The phone is ringing.
Can you answer it?
It's Zhu Yifei.
Mr. Zhu,
why are you still up this late?
Mr. Zhou, sorry to bother you.
What are you doing right now?
I'm taking a hot bath.
He said he's taking a hot bath.
Mr. Zhou.
We have everything ready.
Let's trade tomorrow.
Mr. Zhu, didn't you say
you were not going to sell it to me?
I was just being impulsive.
Think about it.
Who else would I sell it to
other than you?
H-How do we trade?
Tomorrow at 10 AM,
we'll meet at the abandoned building
in the western suburbs.
You bring the money here.
Be there or be square.
It's a deal.
What is Zhu Yifei up to?
Can you stop asking me
questions?
Let him do whatever he wants!
None of you should
ask me any questions today, okay?
Mr. Zhou.
M-Mr. Zhou...
Can you let me
bathe in the seawater of Gondwana
for a while longer?
Okay.
Go on.
Go ahead and bathe.
Chief Zhang.
Thank you so much.
National treasure...
It is a national treasure!
This is what we should do.
Chief Zhang,
I will compose a poem for you.
What rhyme should I use?
Curator Guo,
h-how about this?
Y-You can go to my office.
There are pens in my room,
as well as ink.
You can compose a poem anytime.
They still have to solve the case.
After the case is solved,
I will go visit you,
and we can recite a poem.
Yes, yes.
Sorry, sorry.
I'll leave you to it.
Chief.
The interrogation is over.
How are the results?
See for yourself.
[Interrogation Record]
[Details of the Interrogation Record]
Mao and Xia Tinggang
have nothing to do with Zhou Rong's case?
They have nothing to do
with Liu Bei's death either.
Nothing at all.
Then why are you so happy?
It's Li Penggai.
Li Penggai crashed
into the bianzhong himself.
But we don't know if he's dead or alive.
Then hurry up and go.
Have Li Qian go with you.
Yes, sir.
Where is the car?
Where's my car?
Are you sure this is the place?
Y-Yes.
Let's go.
He should be alive
and probably ran away.
Hello?
Who is this?
Hello, this is Gao Dong speaking.
Chief.
It's Director Gao.
Don't answer it.
Tell him I'm not here.
Director Gao, Chief Zhang said he's...
Here he comes.
Director Gao.
The interrogation's over.
These two people should have nothing
to do with Zhou Rong's case.
And they probably have nothing
to do with Liu Bei's death either.
But we did find something.
We found the bianzhong,
the complete set.
The antique trafficker is called
Zhu Yifei.
We've issued an arrest warrant.
Huo Zheng works for Zhu Yifei.
What about Fang Chao and Liu Zhi?
Still looking for them.
Can you give me a result
by noon today?
Now...
He wants us to give him a result by noon.
Then recite poetry.
Sit down.
Director Gao,
this is Li Qian.
I have something to report to you.
Go ahead.
Letting Fang Chao and Liu Zhi go
wasn't Chief Zhang's fault.
Song Xing and I acted
without authorization,
which is why they got away.
Chief Zhang said that
just so we wouldn't feel pressured.
He's taking the blame for us.
Stop it.
Everything Li Qian said is true.
If you hadn't talked nonsense,
would the Chief have been pushed
to this extent?
Director Gao,
what you're doing
is unfair to Chief Zhang.
If someone has to be punished,
it should be us first.
So, regarding the deadline
to catch Zhou Rong,
can it be extended a bit...
Hello, Director Gao.
We can catch Zhou Rong by noon today.
I'll get back to work.
Get the surveillance footage
of Lu Yibo leaving the Municipal Bureau
yesterday.
[Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau]
[Gate 2]
Pause.
Investigate this car.
[Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau]
It's Rongcheng Group's car.
Right.
That makes sense.
Lu Yibo drove his own car
when he came yesterday.
When he left,
he got into Rongcheng Group's car.
Zhou Rong wanted to know
what Lu Yibo told us.
Lu Yibo stayed at our bureau
for a day,
and we didn't see him.
If he went back
and told Zhou Rong that,
Zhou Rong definitely wouldn't believe it.
After all,
Lu Yibo has a history of betraying him.
Even the most impregnable fortress
cannot withstand an internal collapse.
So their mistrust of each other
is our breakthrough point.
Song Xing.
You're the biggest contributor
to this case.
Really?
We'll go find Lu Yibo now.
No.
We're going to visit Lang Bowen.
Everyone is going.
How unpredictable.
Look!
What happened?
So many police cars have come!
With all this fuss,
something big must have happened.
Chief Zhang,
do we need so many people?
Are there many?
No.
You keep watch here
and don't let anyone get close.
Yes, sir.