(Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
P'Fah’s pretty good at this too, huh.
Today, I actually met him.
Who was it?
The person from the letter.
Nice to meet you.
The one from the letter.
Nice to love you.
Dad, Mom.
We are dating.
It feels impossible.
But today, I got my answer.
I’m here to submit my resignation documents.
So how did it go? Was everything settled?
I thought you would burst into tears.
I'm grown up now.
Maybe it’s because
there’s something I like waiting ahead.
And if I submit my scores and get accepted here again,
I’ll get to see my friends,
and also
stay with you.
That already makes me happy enough.
You really have grown up.
Then should we head back now?
Oh right, I should tell those two first.
I submitted my resignation today.
I won’t let you leave.
Don’t be clingy. You don’t have to miss me too much,
because I’m submitting my portfolio here anyway.
Then you should call me your senior.
I order you, junior Phoon—ten push-ups! Execute!
Yeah, when the semester starts, you’ll definitely see me.
Phoon, do you want to stop anywhere?
Can we stop by the dorm first? I want to get my clothes.
Phoon, would you like to move in with me?
You mean your condo?
Yes.
Please. Even staying with you for a short while makes me really happy.
If we could stay together all the time, it would be amazing.
Please.
You won’t get bored of me, right?
No way. That way, you won’t have to go back and forth between our rooms anymore.
Then P'Fah has to help me move.
I helped you move in—why wouldn’t I help you move out?
Looks like there are way more cameras than when you moved in.
P'Fah.
Yes?
About Fun…
I didn’t tell Uncle and Auntie directly,
so I don’t really feel at ease.
Don’t overthink it.
I believe my parents will understand.
Let’s go back and tell Dad and Mom together later.
So this is the gift you think your mom sent you?
What does it say inside?
“To: Ren.”
Let me guess—Ren is your old name?
Who sent it?
Your mom?
I wish it were.
If you think your mom sent it, do you want to see her?
I do.
Why, can it transform or something?
A limited-edition robot.
Produced in early 2008 in Japan.
Whoa, how do you know that?
I used to collect them.
I think that’s it.
The name’s Ren.
Sounds Japanese. Or is your mom Japanese?
P'Fah.
You said you’d take me anywhere I want to go.
Now I know where I want to go.
P'Fah, can we head back now?
Why? You just got here.
I didn’t think it would be this cold.
How is it?
Is it warmer?
Come on.
Let’s go.
P'Fah.
Careful, little one.
Slow down, little one.
P'Fah, look over here. It’s so beautiful.
It really is.
Thank you.
You look like one of those wobble dolls.
P'Fah, want a photo? I’ll take it for you.
Right here.
Thank you.
Let's eat...right?
Yes.
Phoon.
Then let P'Fah take one of you this time.
But I think
it still feels like something’s missing.
What is it?
Like, for example…
Something like this.
Mom’s calling.
Hi, Mom.
- How was it, kids? Did you have fun on the trip?
- I did.
What about you, Fah?
If Phoon had fun, then I did too.
That’s good then. Mom and Dad won’t bother you anymore.
Yes, Mom. See you later.
Goodbye.
Phoon.
About your mom—
Honestly, I’m not really sure either.
Whether the things that were sent were really from her.
But still—
Deep down, I hope they were from her.
Coming to Japan, I already knew.
That I wouldn’t get to see her.
At least, just being able to breathe a little closer to her is enough for me.
That’s true.
How is it?
Do you usually like taking photos?
I hardly ever even touch a camera.
You don’t like it?
Just kidding.
- Really?
- Let’s go take photos over there instead.
Hey, Phoon. Phoon!
Help me with something.
What is it?
Help me look for Phoon’s mom.
His real mom.
Do you think I’m a private detective or something?
Are you going to write this term’s lab report yourself?
Fine, I’m a private detective. I’ll find her for you.
But you have to help me write the report.
Yeah, I’ll help.
Deal.
- I’ll hang up now.
- Hey, wait.
It’s—
Isn’t it strange?
It’s not strange.
It’s very cute.
Really?
Really.
Very cute.
Good boy.
At first, I thought I’d wait a little longer.
But now, I can’t wait anymore.
You’re mine, okay?
But I have already been yours for a long time, haven’t I?
I’ll take that as your answer.
Is that okay?
If it’s P'Fah, then I’m okay with anything.
I love you, Phoon.
I love you too.
You’re up early, P'Fah.
You’re the one who woke up late.
Really?
Are you okay?
Okay about what?
Well—
Last night—
I don’t know.
I’m sorry.
Forget it. I won’t say anything.
Hey, how can you not say it?
I were the one who did it.
Next time—
I’ll be gentler, I promise.
Promise.
Are you okay?
Why wouldn’t I be?
I was afraid you wouldn’t like it.
Oh.
Should I prove it to you one more time?
That I do like it?
Is it not good?
I don’t want to go back.
But earlier you said you wanted to go home.
At first, I wasn’t used to the cold weather,
but now I’m getting used to it.
Then if you don’t want to go back yet, should we stay another week?
You need to hurry back to classes.
And I need to go back and prepare for exams.
Let’s come back together next time.
Really?
Everywhere we want to go?
Of course.
Phoon.
Can I post this photo on Instagram?
There are so many nice photos. Why did you choose this one?
Because you look cute in this one.
Okay?
Do you want it?
I want to give it to my friends.
- Souvenirs from Japan.
- Hey, which one’s mine?
- This one.
- Pink's mine.
Pink's yours?
Hey, that’s cute.
- Thanks.
- Hey, there’s a cat too.
Thanks, Maew.
It’s pretty cute.
So how was going to Japan with P'Fah?
Super sweet, right?
- What the hell are you talking about?
- You’re going to hurt me again, look.
- See? You’re blushing.
- I was just curious.
It was fun, honestly. Even if it was only for a short time.
Come on, you can go more often.
Yeah, it really does sound fun. I’ve never been to Japan before—I wanna go too.
Then why are you telling us?
All you need is one call, and P'Jo will book the ticket for you.
That’s nice.
I just like it when everyone talks about partners.
I can really feel how warm the atmosphere is.
What about you? Don’t you have anyone?
Nope.
But it’d be nice if someone were there to take care of you.
- I already have someone important to take care of.
- Hey!
Who is it?
Should I tell you?
Of course, Dao. I wanna know.
Show us. What do they look like? Got a picture?
Uh…
Why are you showing me a cat?
This is my important one.
Oh.
- Cute.
- Pretty cute.
Hurry up and eat, then get to campus. You guys will be late.
I’m going back to study too.
I’m almost at the score submission exams.
Don’t forget about me once you leave.
- Don’t ditch us. Come back too.
- What nonsense are you talking about?
Fah.
- Can you check this for me? Is it right?
- Sure.
Mm, yeah, that’s correct.
Okay, thanks.
Hey, that picture you posted on IG—your real boyfriend?
Yeah. Why?
- What faculty is he in?
- He’s about to enter Photo.
Oh.
- I’ll secretly stalk him.
- Huh?
Just kidding. You’re pretty possessive, huh.
Hey Hill, did anyone ever have a crush on Phoon back when he was studying veterinary medicine?
Yeah, definitely.
Ter said there were a lot, too.
Upperclassmen and classmates alike.
That many?
Once he enters Photo, there’ll probably be even more.
Watch out.
Fah, people are crushing on your boyfriend.
Don’t you feel anything at all?
So what if they like him? Phoon only likes me, right?
I think Hill and Jo are getting annoying now.
But you’re really the most one.
You better go back to sleep.
What are you doing, my little one?
I’m studying.
Don’t forget to eat. I already sent food over.
So cute. Noted.
I’m finishing late today. Sorry about that.
Why apologize? You’re focusing on your studies. Don’t worry about me.
Alright. Good luck with your studying too.
I’ll be back soon.
You’re back already?
Phoon.
If you’re sleepy, go sleep properly on the bed.
Sleeping here will give you a headache.
I can’t get up.
Are you going to keep studying, P'Fah?
Yeah.
You’ve been pushing yourself a lot lately.
My grades weren’t great last term.
I want to make up for it this term.
You can do it.
Thanks.
Can I get some encouragement in another way?
Again.
That’s enough.
You’ve got this.
Okay.
I won’t bother you anymore.
Good night.
You little bastard—how dare you not answer my call?
Don’t think I don’t know that Phrae went to see you.
- What nonsense are you spouting?
- Uncle.
Tonfah? Why are you…
Phoon’s asleep. Is there something you’re calling about?
- Uh…
- If not, I’ll hang up.
Wait—don’t hang up yet.
What is it, Kong?
I heard there’s an investor in Chiang Mai interested in partnering with us.
They want to talk details first.
An investor?
Yeah.
A big one.
That’s good.
Then I’ll book the tickets and we’ll go right away.
Kong.
What about Phrae—the thing I told you to handle? How’s that going?
Enough already, Rit.
Just let Phrae go.
Shut up. Even if you’re my friend,
I can still kick you out of this company.
You’re the one who kept backing that kid until he get spoiled.
Did you head out early today?
I had a small errand.
Once I’m done,
I’ll hurry back to you, my little one.
I hope you have a great day today.
You too.
Please have a seat and wait for a moment.
Hello, Uncle. It’s been a long time.
Tonfah, right? I almost didn’t recognize you.
How did you end up here?
The person who contacted you about the investment—
that was me.
Don’t tell me…
the one who’s going to invest with me
is you, Tonfah?
But there’s something else I want to talk about more.
What is it?
Let me get straight to the point.
Could you stop interfering with Phoon?
What did that kid say to you?
Phoon has never once spoken badly about you.
Phoon has endured enough already.
Could you please let him go?
I never forced that kid to stay with me.
He just can’t live on his own.
That’s why he needs me.
But now Phoon can manage on his own.
He doesn’t need you anymore.
So this means
that kid has successfully fooled you, hasn’t he?
How disappointing.
In the end,
you’re not that smart after all.
If you think Typhoon owes you money,
just tell me the amount.
Money is one thing,
but that kid—
he ruined my life.
He made Phrae file for divorce from me.
Hello, Jo.
I need your help with something.
Are you trying to use this to threaten me?
Consider this a warning.
I hope you know what you should do.
I’ll make you realize how wrong you are.
You brat.
Oh, P’Fah, what are you doing here so early?
Where’s Jo?
P’Jo isn’t awake yet.
Are you heading to class now?
Yes, I have to go to class now, P’Fah. I’m off.
Jo.
- Jo.
- North?
- It’s me.
- Why are you calling yourself “me” with me?
It’s me.
Hey, how did you get here?
Where did North go?
North already went to class. He just opened the door for me.
Why didn’t you wake me up properly? If I accidentally carry you to the bed?
It’d be too awkward to even look at each other.
Good thing it’s me and not Arthit.
Yeah, he’d totally want to be my wife even more.
Come on, get up.
What’s up with you?
So how did it go? Did you talk to him?
I just warned him.
Did it work?
I don’t know.
Have you talked to him yet?
If Phoon doesn’t want us involved,
then we’re really meddling.
And
if in the end Phoon chooses his father,
and breaks up with you, what will you do?
Hey, I’m just saying hypothetically.
What you did might actually work.
Oh, by the way—
how’s the thing you asked me to look into?
Relax. I already sent someone to check it out.
No progress at all?
They’re still gathering information.
But—
what you said was
Phoon’s mother is probably Japanese, right?
Yeah.
Phoon is probably right.
You’re back already?
I’m back.
What are you doing?
I’m trying to write some Japanese.
Japanese?
Just in case I get to talk to my mom.
Oh, you’re amazing. P’Fah has a reward for a good kid.
Hm?
Phoon, do you remember telling me to ask Jo to look into your mom?
Right now, it seems your mom really is in Japan.
But we still haven’t found her yet. They’re continuing the search.
- Really?
- Really.
Thank you, P’Fah.
Phoon.
Actually…
today I met your father.
Your dad called last night.
I’m sorry I didn’t tell you beforehand, Phoon.
I just thought that
you didn’t really want to talk about your dad.
So I didn’t dare to ask you properly.
I’m worried about you, Phoon.
It’s not like that.
I just…
don’t know how to start telling you about it.
I haven’t contacted my dad for a long time.
I think…
it’s probably better to cut ties like this.
The time you distanced yourself from me…
was it because of your dad?
If…
your dad asked you to stop seeing me again,
would you agree to it?
Did my dad say that?
No.
I was just asking, just in case.
Actually…
my dad didn’t want me involved with you from the start.
But if he asks me to stop now…
I won’t do it.
That’s more than enough
for me, Phoon.
You don’t have to worry about anything anymore.
Everything will be sorted out.
Trust me, little one.
In the end, Phoon chose me.
Chose what?
He said he wouldn’t break up with me.
What?
I’m sorry. I haven’t really had much time for you lately.
You’re overthinking again, P'Fah.
It’s okay.
I’ll let Ter and North to come.
You should focus on studying too.
I’ll read and wait for you.
Okay.
Call me if anything comes up.
I’m at the café in front of the campus. Hurry over after class. I’m lonely.
I’m lonely too. You ditched me.
You’re still sulking?
Go study properly. Read your books, you dropout kid.
I’ve still got a long way to go.
Study hard, Dao.
Miss you, Maew.
I’m almost done. You have to treat me a green tea frappe.
Alright.
Yes, Aunt Phrae.
He even threatened me, saying he’d take Fai to live with him.
I’m sorry for dumping all this on you.
I don’t have anyone else to listen to me.
Other than listening, there’s not much I can do.
Don’t say that. You’ve helped me so much already.
I’ll try talking to my partner.
Maybe he can help somehow.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Just having you listen already means a lot.
I want to help. Fai is my younger sibling.
What did you tell Tonfah for him to treat me like this?
Treat you how?
How? You ungrateful bastard.
This whole thing with Phrae is because of you, isn’t it?
You already took Thorfun. Still not satisfied?
What you’re doing is making me lose my wife and kids.
You bastard. How far are you going to ruin my life?
I never should’ve let that woman give birth to you.
Then why did you let me be born?
If you never loved me or cared at all.
Did I ask to be born?
If I could choose…
do you think I’d choose you as my father?
I can’t choose that.
You’re the one who had the choice.
I’m the result of your actions.
Take some responsibility.
I told that woman to get rid of you.
I never chose you.
I never wanted you to be born.
That woman…
she was stupid and stubborn.
She chose to keep you.
And in the end, she abandoned you anyway.
No one even knows where she is now.
And you think Aunt Phrae left you because of me?
She wanted to raise Fai on her own.
Because you’re too messed up to be a father.
So messed up she didn’t even want you touching her daughter.
Big mouth.
You’re asking for it.
Hey, North!
- North, that’s enough.
- This bastard deserves it!
That’s enough!
You little shit just punched me!
I’ll remember this.
Keep an eye on your friend.
- Serves you right, asshole! Who the hell are you?
- Calm down, North.
Huh? Your dad?
That guy earlier was your dad?
Yeah.
I saw him about to hit you, so I hit him first.
Damn it, I’ve never punched a friend’s dad in my life.
It’s fine. You were just trying to help me.
What kind of father beats his kid like he’s trying to kill him?
- Does it hurt?
- Hell yes, it does.
Sorry.
What am I gonna tell P'Jo?
Say I’m allergic to chili?
Think he’ll believe it?
Or maybe I drank some wine,
and got a little dizzy.
Ow.
Will P'Jo believe me?
Hey.
North.
They said you got beaten up?
Are you okay?
Does it hurt?
Fah.
Come talk to me for a second.
Okay.
Hill, stay with them for now.
I really thought talking nicely would get through to him.
If you don’t do anything, I’ll handle it myself.
Calm down first.
How the hell am I supposed to calm down?
Then calm down for me, at least.
I’ve got to do something about this.
What do you mean, the account’s been frozen?
Are you crazy? How is that even possible? Did you check properly?
Turn yourself in, Rit.
What did you say? How dare you talk to me like that?
Tonfah.
But how could he do this?
I already cleaned everything up.
Captain, Sergeant.
What are you arresting me for, officer?
Officer, wait—let go first. Let’s sit down and talk.
You can’t just arrest me like this.
It has sent shockwaves through the business world.
A prominent businessman and former senior executive of a leading real estate company
was arrested by police in his hotel room while preparing to flee.
He is now a suspect in embezzlement and money laundering cases.
Was that you and P'Jo doing?
At first, I thought he wouldn’t bother you anymore.
But then he did this.
Honestly,
I’ve been worried about your dad for a while now.
So I asked Jo to look into it a bit.
That’s how we found evidence of embezzlement and money laundering.
At first,
I only meant to use it to scare him into leaving you alone.
But since he chose to do this,
I had to do the right thing.
Are you mad at me, Phoon?
Why would I be mad at you?
That’s exactly what he deserved.
Mr. Ritchai admitted to authorities
that he was involved in illegal money transfers,
including businesses under his management that may be linked to gray-area operations in neighboring countries.
Authorities are currently reviewing financial records spanning several years.
Back then,
he was so proud of his image.
Now he has to hide even his face.
I cared about him so much,
did everything he wanted me to be,
hoping he’d love me back.
But he never did.
In the end,
I was left all alone.
Why would you say that?
You’ve got me.
You still have me.
Don’t think you have to be alone anymore.
Or I’ll get sad, you know.
I’m sorry.
You will always have me.
Where did you go?
I went to grab something downstairs.
Jo sent it over.
Good news.
What is it?
Mom.
P'Fah.
Yeah?
Mom must’ve had me when she wasn’t ready at all.
Are you going to see her?
I think you should. She must miss you a lot.
Maybe she doesn’t want to see me.
That’s why she never replied to my letters.
Why do you think that?
Maybe I’m just not used to being happy.
I’m really sorry.
Mom loves you.