(dramatic music)
What are you doing on my laptop?
I was checking
if you had any naughty videos.
Got a problem?
Donghyeon asked me to send him
something from your laptop.
You could've asked me.
He said it was really urgent.
(sighs)
EUNSOO: I have something to ask you.
What is it?
It's about your crush.
(emotive music)
About Jennifer.
When did you start liking her?
Do I have to tell you?
(emotive music continues)
Why did you start liking her?
(emotive music)
-Are you really going to tell her?
-Eunsoo.
SUNWOO: Please stop.
Just let me handle it myself.
(emotive music continues)
(theme music)
MALE SINGER (in English): ♪ My love ♪
EPISODE 3
(in Korean) ♪ You protect me ♪
♪ You don't know that you do ♪
(in English) ♪ My love ♪
(in Korean) ♪ When I see sadness
in your eyes ♪
♪ I feel uneasy... ♪
WANT TO BE JOBLESS?
SQUEEZE IT OUT. YOU CAN DO IT.
YOUR LYRICS WILL MAKE IT COMPLETE.
RIGHT? PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER
-♪ I'm in love ♪
-(rasping)
♪ I'm searching for you ♪
-(muffled music on headphones)
-♪ Love, like the wind ♪
-♪ Caresses my ears ♪
-(sighs)
(in English) ♪ I love you ♪
♪ I need you ♪
(in Korean) ♪ I've fallen for you ♪
(music ends)
(whimsical music)
(object clatters)
Where was it...
(clatters)
EUNSOO'S LYRICS NOTEBOOK
DO NOT OPEN, ESPECIALLY SUNWOO!
(page riffling)
EUNSOO: What is this?
(chuckling)
(whimsical music continues)
IDIOT
(music stops)
WE WEAVE THE THREADS OF OUR TIME AGAIN
YELLOW FRIENDSHIP SAYS
IT CHEERS FOR GREEN DREAMS
(whimsical music)
HIGH SCHOOL
MATH
(page riffles)
(object clatters)
(Sunwoo sighs)
(whimsical music continues)
(both sigh)
(mouthing) Just once.
(paper rustles)
I'M HUNGRY
EUNSOO: When are you getting
your phone back?
I have no idea.
It's so inconvenient.
So why did you take pictures
with your phone everywhere
when you're supposed to be studying?
You weren't studying earlier, were you?
I hope you get all fat
and bloated tomorrow.
That's not going to happen.
(chuckles)
(slurps, munches)
(emotive music)
Here.
-What's this?
-My mom gave me her camera,
but I don't use it. You can have it.
Why should I?
It's an investment.
-An investment?
-EUNSOO: Yeah.
I see your potential.
When you become a famous photographer,
I'm going to mooch off of you
all the time.
I'm sowing the seeds early.
(scoffs)
(emotive music continues)
Thanks.
(chuckles)
I tried writing some lyrics
while thinking about our friendship.
EUNSOO: Give it a listen.
"We weave the threads of our time again."
Threads?
(no audible dialogue)
"Yellow friendship says..."
(camera shutter clicks)
(exhales)
(sucks teeth)
-That was me.
-No, it wasn't.
-You did.
-No, I took a photo of your notebook.
I'm sure it was me.
Let's try it again.
EUSNOO: I gave it to you for a reason.
Look. From now on,
take photos of me with that.
Now. Like this.
Take it now.
(camera clicks)
-(camera shutter clicks)
-(music stops)
What do you mean?
The Benzema Lauren?
The Benzema Lauren we know?
Benzema Lauren...
With me?
Why?
DONGHYEON: Sunwoo,
has the day finally come
for me to mooch off of you?
Will you let me?
Sunwoo, we did it!
-Wait. When did they reach out?
-DONGHYEON: Earlier!
His agent contacted the gallery directly!
Benzema Lauren!
He was really impressed with your work.
He wants to commit the next year
to collaborate with you.
(uplifting piano music)
(sighs)
Han Sunwoo.
Congratulations. I knew you had it in you.
You'll do it, right? Yes!
Of course, I don't even have to ask.
You have to, no matter what!
This is a chance
to make your name known in the world
and for me to get to the next level.
Wait a second.
To make this work, we might have
to leave Korea sooner than planned.
Let me see...
-(mouse clicking)
-We might have to leave this week.
Wait a minute.
You should get yourself ready.
(pensive music)
GRAPE JUICE
It's grape this time.
I'm really fine with anything.
If it's something
to make you smash it with your fist,
-you're not fine with it.
-(chuckles)
I'm sorry. I should have asked you first.
I just want to share the things I like
with the people I like,
and I tend to get ahead of myself.
I understand.
My mom keeps sending me mandarins
because she loves them.
(laughs)
I read your new lyrics.
(exclaims)
(Wooil sighs)
(inhales)
Why do you get so nervous every time?
Uh...
Because I'm the one getting evaluated.
The one who does the evaluating
wouldn't know.
You're doing great.
And you'll keep getting better.
(paper riffles)
WOOIL: What are you doing tomorrow?
EUNSOO: Tomorrow?
I'm supposed to meet with Jay Jun
tomorrow evening.
It'd be nice for you two to get close
before the recording.
If you're free,
join us for dinner tomorrow.
Sure.
Okay.
(Eunsoo yelping)
Gosh. What did you just smash?
-I'm so sorry about this.
-I'm sorry.
-Meeting Jay Jun? You?
-Yes.
I will be granted an audience
-with the artist of all artists!
-Oh, my gosh!
EUNSOO: I'm so nervous.
Honey, get her some braised short ribs,
-so she can calm down.
-Eunsoo, calm down and have a drink.
Hmm.
Where's your best friend
on this monumental night?
-Sunwoo?
-Yeah.
I haven't told him yet.
Why not?
(chuckles awkwardly)
(light music plays on background)
Mari.
How long were you friends with Gyeolhan?
Let's see now...
Fifteen years.
And married for eight.
Jeez, a disgustingly long time.
♪ Dashing through the snow ♪
-(chuckles)
-GYEOLHAN: ♪ In a one-horse open sleigh ♪
How did you marry someone
that's been your friend for 15 years?
You get married when you get knocked up.
I mean,
how do you get knocked up by your friend?
Eunsoo.
First, you get a room.
-Then you wash up cleaner than usual.
-Jeez.
I take that back.
You don't have time to wash up.
(Mari chuckles)
Why not?
Yesterday's enemy can be a friend today.
We can be indifferent in the morning
and in love in the evening.
Exactly.
(chuckles softly)
-I see.
-GYEOLJAN: But why do you ask?
Did Sunwoo say that he likes you?
What? So he finally told you?
How wonderful!
That's not what happened.
Huh?
What, then?
You two knew?
What? You didn't know?
(Gyeolhan gasps)
How could you not know?
(Mari gasps)
You can tell just by the way
he looks at you. We all knew.
Even these chopsticks here knew.
You're the only one who didn't know.
This is a good opportunity
for you to start thinking.
-Mr. Han is handsome.
-Right.
-He's a great catch.
-He's a rare breed.
-That's right.
You're right.
He really is a rare breed.
He feels bad all-day
for accidentally stepping on an ant.
He spends all winter worrying
about every stray cat in the world.
Every time we eat cold noodles,
he always gives me the egg, you know?
Because I love boiled eggs.
(clears throat)
-I wouldn't give you mine.
-Jeez.
I spent two-thirds of my life
with a guy like that.
And that...
(pensive music)
...makes me so upset
and scared.
I'm afraid I might hurt him.
I can't risk hurting Sunwoo...
because he means a lot to me.
(pensive music continues)
(music building)
(pensive music)
(door opens)
(gasps)
Oh, gosh!
I'm not mad anymore.
How about you?
(emotive music)
Sorry about yesterday.
(music fades)
SUNWOO: I shouldn't have reacted
like that...
(paper rustles)
(in English) Okay.
(in Korean) We're all good.
(chuckles)
I'm sorry too.
It was inconsiderate of me to pry.
(exhales sharply)
It's eight years ago.
You asked me when I started liking her.
It's been eight years.
(emotive music)
It's been that long?
Yeah.
SUNWOO: Perhaps it may have been
even longer.
It was eight years ago when I realized
that I was already in love with her.
(emotive music continues)
What was the next question?
Why did I start liking her?
Aside from my mother,
she's the only one who believes in me.
No matter what I have done or will do.
She always says I'm the best.
(emotive music)
(inhales)
The third question.
Am I really going to tell her?
Yes.
I'm going to tell her.
-(music stops)
-(birds chirping)
(breathes deeply)
(crockery clanging)
(exhales sharply)
(sizzling)
(exclaims)
(door creaks)
(sighs)
(door opens)
-SUNWOO: Heading out?
-Goodness!
-(Sunwoo grunts)
-(Eunsoo exhales sharply)
Yeah.
(scoffs)
You were still...
at home. I see.
(chuckles awkwardly)
Goodness, I can already see you
freezing later at night.
You should start wearing these.
-No. You'll be cold.
-I'm sweating now.
I can do it myself.
(sucks teeth, clears throat)
EUNSOO: What were you up to?
Fixing your bike.
(grunts)
It's so old.
Leave it, I'll throw it away later.
Throw it away?
You loved this bike.
I did, but what can I do when it's broken?
EUNSOO: I don't ride it anyway.
(emotive music)
I should get going.
-Eunsoo!
-Yeah?
When will you be home?
What?
-Today...
-Today!
I'll be home late.
Super late.
I'm having dinner with work people.
But today...
EUNSOO: I might do
some more work after that.
I'm going to be so late.
I might even see the sunrise.
So go to bed. Okay?
I'm going now!
I have something...
to tell you.
HWASIN MUSIC
JAY JUN
(scribbling)
(slurps, chuckles)
You're getting nervous again.
(chuckles)
(door opens)
-Welcome.
-WOOIL: Oh, you're here.
-Jay Jun.
-Hello.
-It's been a while. How have you been?
-Hello...
-Let me introduce you.
This is our lyricist for the new single,
Ms. Lee Eunsoo.
And this is his manager. and his CEO,
and, as you already know, Jay Jun.
Hello.
Pleased to meet you.
I heard a lot about you.
Yes.
(laughing)
-We had to grab a taxi then.
-WOOIL: I'm sorry.
(group laughing)
-Sorry about that!
-CEO: The cab fare was really high.
You know,
we were all so curious about you.
About me?
-We were all shocked to see that you...
-Hey.
(chuckles)
That you were even prettier
than Mr. Kang had described.
We all thought you were a trainee
next in line to debut as a K-pop idol.
He spoke so highly of you.
That he found an amazing lyricist.
-CEO: Right.
-Yes.
He insists that we need your lyrics
for Jay Jun's album to be a hit.
Who does he think he is, the singer?
(group laughing)
Ms. Lee, you have to do a great job.
We're all expecting a lot from you.
Stop giving her pressure.
You have to watch out for these people.
They're always scheming about
how they can get something out of us.
Don't be so harsh on us who meekly wait
to be graced with your songs.
-Hey, let's drink, just us.
-Sure.
-Cheers!
-There he goes again.
-I'm just kidding!
-Cheers!
Well, thanks a lot.
-We're in your care.
-You should watch out for him.
No way.
(pensive music)
INTERNATIONAL LANDSCAPE PHOTOGRAPHY
OF THE YEAR AWARDS WINNER
MARINE CONSERVATION PHOTO GRAND PRIZE
YOUNG ADULT PHOTOGRAPHER'S AWARD...
(tapping)
(pensive music continues)
(page riffles)
(cellphone clatters)
(exhales sharply)
(tapping)
(sighs)
-Bye.
-Dinner was great!
-Great job today.
-Jun, keep your voice in shape.
-I'll get going. I'll call you later.
-Okay.
-I was going to treat you all.
-It's okay, no worries.
Take care of her.
Ms. Lee, I entrust you with our song.
-Thank you.
-Best of luck, Ms. Lee!
Let us know
if Mr. Kang is being too hard on you.
Stop it and just leave.
Take care.
Gosh, that was hectic.
(chuckles)
Enough to sober me up.
Do you want to go for another round?
There's a really nice wine bar
on the first floor of the studio building.
Ah...
Wine?
Their carpaccio is a work of culinary art.
It pairs perfectly with wine.
Let's go.
(Wooil chuckles)
(rattling)
(brake squeaks)
(sighs)
(metal clanks)
(cellphone beeps)
(phone line ringing)
(phone line ringing continues)
FEMALE OPERATOR: The person you're calling
is unavailable...
(exhales sharply)
WOOIL: How is it? Really good, isn't it?
It is. It's my first time trying.
I've tried different places,
but this place has the best carpaccio.
(classical music plays on background)
And the best selection of pinot noir.
I'm glad you like it.
(chuckles)
By the way,
what the CEO said earlier...
Oh, I'm sorry.
WOOIL: I didn't mean to pressure you.
But...
Mm...
I told them that because
I truly believe you are a good lyricist.
And...
The day you pleaded with me
to give you two more weeks...
To be honest, you were so beautiful.
How nervous you were about changing
even a single letter of your lyrics...
It was just beautiful.
To see a beautiful person work
with a passion for what she does.
(sucks teeth)
Gosh. So this is how it feels.
Sorry?
To become the evaluated.
It really is nerve-racking.
The one who does the evaluating
wouldn't know, right?
(chuckles softly)
You don't need to say anything right now.
Let's take it slow.
Both work and getting to know each other.
Okay.
(engine rumbling)
-SUNWOO: Thank you.
-DRIVER: No problem.
VACANT
(engine revs)
There's a really unique wine bar
we should try next time.
Right by the Cheongdam Intersection...
SUNWOO: Eunsoo!
What are the chances?
What are you doing here?
I walked in to buy a bottle of wine
for Donghyeon.
SUNWOO: He has good news to celebrate.
Hello.
Oh, right. Hello.
(Sunwoo chuckles)
So you buy your bottles at a wine bar
and not a store.
How unique.
(Eunsoo chuckles awkwardly)
I wanted to pick one
that pairs well with food.
-Yeah.
-I see.
Is this good?
-(slurps)
-(clanks)
(munches)
Not bad.
(chuckles)
-Would you like me to order you some more?
-I'm fine.
(classical music playing)
(cellphone buzzing)
Mr. Kang.
-Yes?
-I need to make a phone call.
Of course.
(chair scrapes)
(retreating footsteps)
(slow, tense music)
(tense music continues)
(Wooil grunts)
She dropped this.
(classical music playing)
I wanted to thank you for last time.
About what?
Thanks to you, I was able
to learn a thing about her tastes.
Mandarins.
(scoffs)
Ah...
I see.
(groans)
(Sunwoo sighs)
I just told her that I liked her.
WOOIL: I'm not going to pressure her.
I'll take it slow and get to know her.
(emotive music)
(slurps)
(glass clanks)
Is this any good?
It's good for a gift.
WOOIL: It's a pinot noir from France.
A good amount of tannins.
Was Eunsoo enjoying this?
Yes. She seemed to like it.
(footsteps approaching)
EUNSOO (whispers): I'm sorry.
(emotive music continues)
(slurps)
Shall we call it a night?
I feel a bit dizzy.
Dizzy? Then I'll call a chauffeur for us.
Where do you live?
WOOIL: We can drop you off on the way
to take Eunsoo home.
It's okay. We'll get ourselves home.
You can go ahead.
I have another appointment to get to.
Please take her home safely.
(reflective music)
Where are you...
WOOIL: Eunsoo.
Shall we?
Okay.
EUNSOO: Thank you.
WOOIL: Take care, Eunsoo.
-Thank you. You too, Mr. Kang.
-WOOIL: Bye.
-WOOIL: See you next week.
-Thank you.
(engine revving)
(reflective music continues)
(reflective music)
SUNWOO: Am I really going to tell her?
Yes.
I'm going to tell her.
(music fades)
CONTACTS
FAVORITES, SUNWOO
(light music)
(cellphone beeps)
FEMALE OPERATOR: The phone is turned off.
You will be directed to voicemail.
Charges will apply after the tone.
(light music continues)
(cellphone clatters)
(light music)
Hey, Eunsoo. Good to see you too.
Where's Sunwoo?
He left a while ago.
He did?
Oh, right. Here you go.
Chocolate? For what?
Sunwoo told me yesterday
that you had some good news to celebrate.
EUNSOO: What's the good news?
Good news?
Yes, I have good news.
But Sunwoo is the one
who needs to celebrate, not me.
Cuba?
For how long?
At least a year in South America.
DONGHYEON: Then probably Europe
after that.
We'll go all over Europe.
Ah...
Donghyeon.
How big is this
opportunity for him?
It's an opportunity
to change the course of his entire life.
One exhibition with this guy means
getting his name known worldwide.
Sunwoo will become
a world-famous photographer.
(Donghyeon groans)
(clatters)
Did you not know at all?
Did Sunwoo not tell you?
No.
-(grunts)
-(rustles)
No way.
It can't be. No.
No. It can't be!
It cannot be it!
(blows air)
Hey.
Have you heard anything shocking
from Sunwoo?
Anything to startle you,
to make your heart skip a beat,
or to make you feel jolts of electricity
throughout your body?
Did Sunwoo make you feel
anything like that at all?
No.
Really?
-(paper rustles)
-(Donghyeon sobs)
What's wrong with you? Are you crying?
DONGHYEON: No, I'm fine.
If you do hear anything from him,
please call me right away. Okay?
-(cellphone buzzing)
-Okay.
Hello, sir.
Oh, you've heard?
Sunwoo only has good things
waiting for him now.
DONGHYEON: We'll definitely be going!
I'm so happy it's making me tear up.
-(door closes)
-(reflective music)
(reflective music continues)
(Eunsoo sighs)
What are you doing?
Ta-da.
It's all fixed up.
SUNWOO: It's your first bike.
And I taught you how to ride with this.
I couldn't throw away something
that held some of our fondest memories.
It's my gift to you.
Thanks.
It looks brand new.
I didn't paint this part.
Why not?
It's where I used to grab for you.
I just want you to remember me
every time you see it.
(reflective music)
Eunsoo.
-I...
-Sunwoo.
(music stops)
Do you remember what I said
when I first gave you your camera?
I wanted you to become
a famous photographer and thrive.
I even wrote lyrics about it.
That yellow friendship
cheers for green dreams.
I've always believed
you were better than the likes of me.
EUNSOO: My yellow friendship
will always be on your side.
Because we're friends.
That's how I feel, Sunwoo.
(birds chirping)
Can I speak now?
SUNWOO: Lee Eunsoo.
Goodbye.
(pensive music)
My schedule got moved up a bit,
so I'm leaving tomorrow.
Surprised, right?
Just as you predicted, I think I'm about
to become a totally famous photographer.
You know my favorite photographer,
Benzema Lauren?
He wants to work with me.
(chuckles softly)
Wow. Awesome!
I'm so happy for you.
Congratulations, Sunwoo.
I told you. You always had it in you.
(chuckles)
-EUNSOO: Congratulations, really.
-Thanks.
Sure.
(chuckles)
(pensive music)
(pensive music continues)
(music fades)
(car whooshing)
SUNWOO: You should go. It's cold.
EUNSOO: I should see you off.
You didn't forget anything, did you?
-You sure your passport isn't expired?
-I'm not like you.
Hey.
EUNSOO: Who am I going
to hang out with now?
You should be hanging out with that song.
If you want to make it big.
EUNSOO: Right. I'll get this song
ranked within the top 100.
No, first place on the charts.
SUNWOO: Damn, right.
(Eunsoo chuckles softly)
SUNWOO: I came to help you
with your lyrics,
but we never got to finish.
EUNSOO: Yeah, it's a shame.
Listen to the song when it comes out.
Don't skip meals and eat well.
And keep your neck covered
and warm. Please.
You'll really freeze to death
trying to be fashionable.
Gosh, all right. I heard you.
Always nagging.
Take care of yourself.
Let's hang out when I get back.
It reminds me of that day.
Eight years ago.
The day before you entered the military.
(chuckles)
Yeah.
There's my bus.
I should go.
Get home safe.
(brake squeaks)
EUNSOO: Call me when you get there.
SUNWOO: Okay.
(engine rumbles)
(engine revving)
(silence)
(footsteps)
(cellphone buzzing)
SUNWOO: I made some mandarin preserves
and left them in the kitchen cabinet.
It should be better than plain mandarins.
(somber music)
SUNWOO: Don't you feel sad at all?
Your friend of ten years
is going to the army.
(phone camera clicks)
To be accurate, 11 years.
And why should I?
I'll see you soon anyway.
Two years isn't soon.
I'm going to visit you.
I'm going to write to you.
You'll come out on leaves too.
Time will fly right by.
You're so heartless.
I'll bring lots of good food when I visit.
Good.
Worry about yourself.
Don't skip meals and eat well.
And keep your neck covered and warm.
You'll freeze to death
trying to be fashionable.
All right. Stop nagging.
See you. Now get back to work.
Okay.
Hey, Sunwoo!
Sunwoo.
Take care.
-♪ Afraid you might see my tears ♪
-Oh, my.
What is this?
♪ I cry without a sound ♪
Take care of yourself.
-♪ But these tears of mine ♪
-SUNWOO: Let's hang out when I get back.
♪ That fall now ♪
Okay, let's do that.
-♪ Are tears ♪
-EUNSOO: Don't get sick.
-♪ I can no longer hold back ♪
-You too.
♪ Afraid this loud heart of mine ♪
-SUNWOO: See you.
-Bye.
♪ Is no longer a secret ♪
-See you!
-SUNWOO: Get inside, it's cold!
♪ Embrace me a little more ♪
♪ Talk to me a little more ♪
♪ Don't push me away, not now ♪
♪ So that I can see you a little more
so that I can cry a little more ♪
♪ Before I have to let you go ♪
♪ Just a little more, just a little ♪
♪ I want to stand here
holding onto you a while longer ♪
♪ Until this night is no more ♪
♪ This cold breeze
had never brought us together ♪
♪ Afraid it will only take you
far away from me ♪
♪ Please don't leave me ♪
♪ I never imagined ♪
♪ Life without you, not even for a day ♪
♪ Please ♪
♪ Don't leave me like this ♪
(music fades)
EUNSOO: My dearly missed Sunwoo.
Maybe...
I'll be able to write
the best lyrics this time.
(reflective music)
Because I finally understand
what you meant about unrequited love.
(pouring liquid)
(slurps)
Just seeing Eunsoo smile
is enough to fill my heart.
When I put a scarf around her
on a chilly day, I feel I've done my job.
Silly, right?
(chuckles softly)
But that really is all I need.
I just want her to feel comfortable
around me.
But I almost hurt her,
just to let her know how I feel.
What was I thinking?
-(Gyeolhan slurps)
-(sighs)
When she cries...
(liquid pours)
I don't know what to do.
(rain pattering)
(wind chimes tinkle)
(romantic music)
MALE SINGER: ♪ Whenever I see you ♪
♪ It is so strange ♪
♪ My heart acts on its own ♪
♪ I no longer had the confidence to love ♪
♪ But I muster up the courage
after having met you ♪
♪ My heart flutters ♪
-♪ Whenever I see you ♪
-She was drinking wine.
♪ I never know what to do... ♪
She hates wine
because it gives her a headache.
♪ Just when I thought
I could no longer love ♪
-But if that's what she wants...
-♪ You came to me ♪
♪ My love ♪
...then I will support her
with all my heart.
♪ They say love is more than words ♪
♪ I'll pour out my heart
more than anyone else ♪
♪ I won't hurt your precious heart ♪
♪ I'll protect you now ♪
♪ I ponder how ♪
♪ How I can comfort you ♪
♪ When you are in need... ♪