(All places, organizations, characters,
incidents, and backstories...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
It's... It'll be all right.
Everyone.
There's no need to be nervous...
about the special visit.
You just have to
trust me and do your thing.
Be your usual selves, okay?
Do you understand? Act normal.
(Episode 10)
Welcome to our school.
- Hello.
- Come this way.
Yes. This way, please.
Hello.
I heard.
You almost died.
From now on,
you should be extra careful.
We meet often these days.
The school uniform suits you well.
But what a pity.
It's time you stop...
playing school games.
Vice-principal Baek.
- Yes?
- Escort the teachers inside.
Right, of course.
Teachers, shall we?
Ms. Oh!
How did you get out?
That's a secret.
I'd like my name tag back.
You can't find the gold bars
without me.
"When the one with the bead..."
"faces the red sun,"
"the gold will shine."
(3. The piano that plays alone)
(The keys play on their own.)
The one with the bead must refer
to Chairman Seo Byeong Mun.
Is there more you can tell me?
What don't I know? Give me anything.
Check again to see
if you're leaving anything behind.
Let's never cross paths again.
(Byeongmun High School)
You can't expel someone
out of the blue.
Please, sir.
It's out of my hands.
Who could possibly disobey
the chairwoman's order?
Even the chairwoman
has to follow school policy.
The school doesn't belong to her.
How could she expel my student...
- without my approval...
- Ms. Oh!
That's enough. This is a workplace.
- Mr. Baek...
- Let me be clear.
You're to follow
the order from above.
Do not mention
Jeong Hae Seong ever again.
Keep this up,
and you could suffer the same fate.
Why doesn't she get it?
Can't she tell
which way the water flows?
I still can't wrap
my head around it.
What did Hae Seong do wrong?
Won't we get to see you anymore?
We'll talk to the chairwoman.
Yes, let's do that.
We can't let Hae Seong leave.
I appreciate the gesture,
but don't barge into
Ms. Seo's office or anything.
I can't be the reason
you ruin your lives.
Are you really leaving like this?
Everything will be as it should be.
I had fun.
Hae Seong, wait.
(Byeongmun High School)
Parents in
the academic management program...
are asking to meet.
When they frantically
had their kids transferred?
Ignore them.
Those who run wild unaware
that they're no longer of use?
We'll cut all ties with them
at this time.
Jeong Hae Seong...
(Undercover High School,
Jeong Hae Seong)
(Delete file?)
Same...
for you.
I'm almost at the finish line.
I should cross it myself.
Director Kim must've helped her.
He's the only one who could've had
Seo Myeong Ju released.
I get that, but the case was solid
with witnesses and evidence.
Getting rid of evidence
is a stroll in the park for him.
The same goes for witness tampering.
What now?
Now that Hae Seong
isn't at the school,
the operation can't continue.
Things have definitely
gotten harder for us.
We should still find a way.
It was my dad's final mission.
Getting expelled
can't be the end of it.
Sure.
Our mission is to find
the gold bars,
not to have him stay at school.
Let's find a way.
- Yes, sir.
- Sure.
We're from NIS Internal Affairs.
As of this moment,
a search and seizure...
will commence on the office
of Domestic Team Four.
- What?
- Wait.
Hold on.
But...
Stay put, will you?
Wait.
On what grounds
are you conducting this search?
- What is this about?
- Found it, sir.
(Domestic Team Four)
Goodness.
(National Intelligence Service)
We won't make a big fuss,
so come with us.
Hold on a second.
This is absolute nonsense.
Let go of me!
Who gave the order?
Who ordered the darn search?
Tell me before I break your arm.
Leave it, Hae Seong.
Secure the office until I get back.
Let's go.
Make sure you get everything.
Yes, sir.
But... Hold on.
What do you think you're doing?
(Incoming call)
Yes, this is Jeong Hae Seong.
I wanted to know
if you liked your parting gift.
A gift isn't what I expected.
I'll extend my gratitude soon.
Even when Ms. Oh Su A will be next?
Your team leader
and teammates you cherish...
were only an example.
This was me showcasing
what I could do...
if you kept getting in my way.
In Japan,
at the Nikko Toshogu Shrine,
three wise monkeys have been carved.
"See no evil, hear no evil,
speak no evil."
You consider me as evil, don't you?
So don't...
look my way or hear about me.
Don't do a single thing.
Be a wise monkey.
You're giving me advice now?
You must see me as a threat.
Do you think I'll let Ms. Oh go
without making a scene?
I'm sure you get my warning.
I was passing by when I saw you.
Can I get a bowl of noodles
and a shot glass, please?
Sure.
Are you giving up?
I don't know.
Internal Affairs took
Senior Agent An.
Meanwhile, Seo Myeong Ju called.
She said you were next.
Maybe I should quit.
I'm now wondering
if I'm being greedy...
and selfish.
Get a grip on yourself.
Who are you to see me
as a damsel in distress?
Hey, don't chicken out.
Don't mind me and do what's needed.
I'll be fine, Hae Seong.
That's what scares you.
You don't want others to get hurt
because of you.
I'll help you until the very end.
So do it for my sake...
since the last thing I want
is for you to be scared.
Aren't you scared?
I am.
I'm afraid, but I'm bearing with it.
I can't sit idly by...
while the chairwoman
obtains the gold bars.
If her project is finalized,
the kids' dreams will crumble
within seconds.
You sound like the grownup here.
There's a reason I'm a teacher.
It's better now that you're smiling.
- Really?
- Yes.
Here's to tomorrow.
Cheers.
(Uncle)
How did it go?
We've been put on standby,
and the team was dismantled.
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
It's not like you
to sound weak and guilty.
If this has you dispirited...
Uncle.
I want to continue.
I...
want to correct what is wrong.
Can you help me?
That's it.
That's my boy.
Starting tomorrow,
we'll gather at my place.
- Got it, Hae Seong.
Isn't that the first time
he asked for our help?
You heard him.
Starting tomorrow,
we'll gather at his place.
(Domestic Team Four)
That was fine work you did.
Should I be thanking you
or something?
I hope this will be the end
of such requests.
No one in this room
has a squeaky-clean past.
You should
keep your head down and...
There's something
my father always used to say.
"If you serve
your servants white rice,"
"they come to think of themselves
as noblemen."
Chairwoman Seo.
That's out of line.
Mr. Kim.
I'm the one who seated you
as the director of the NIS.
Now, listen.
Don't challenge me.
Don't talk back.
Like you've been doing so far,
eat the feed I've been giving you.
No. Don't nod
and answer me in words.
Principal Park.
There you go. Good boy.
Hey, we're listed here.
- Are you saying we can't eat yet?
- What?
- Hey.
- Move, will you?
- Out of the way.
- Move!
- I'm Class B.
- Move, will you?
What's going on?
The chairwoman ordered them
to serve meals differently...
according to our grades.
I thought you knew.
I never thought
she'd stoop this low.
Why is Hae Seong
suddenly calling you?
Are you in contact with him?
Why is he calling me?
I bet he called the wrong person.
He's never called me before.
Gosh, I'm hungry.
This is me.
That reaction just now
is highly suspicious.
Chae Lin.
- Your meal's over there.
- Me?
What...
But why?
Agent Jeong Hae Seong,
this is An Yu Jeong.
I will begin my briefing.
Shoot.
The school meal.
We are served different meals
depending on our grades.
The side dishes are different,
and you have to eat later
if you have lower grades.
What about Dong Min and the others?
As if there would be any surprises.
They eat last, of course.
What else?
Only those in the special class...
can stay behind
for late-night self-study sessions.
The rest can't even if they want to.
They're only caring about those
in the special class.
Also, our grades
for midterms and finals...
will be posted
on the bulletin board.
The school has gotten weirder...
ever since the chairwoman got back.
Can't...
Can't the NIS help?
I'm hanging up.
You darn jerk.
Is there anything to place this on?
- Why you...
- What?
- Come on. Get me something.
- Over there.
Oh, right.
Did I tell you...
that Seo Myeong Ju solved
the third ghost story?
What?
I guess I didn't.
I think she saw
what was in the notebook.
Thanks for telling us this quickly.
- I'm amazed by the speed.
- I appreciate the compliment.
What's good though...
is that she hasn't solved
the fourth ghost story yet.
But we're just as clueless.
Check this out for now.
(2003 Byeongmun High School
Student Council, "Stars That Write")
A collection of writings
by the student council?
The teacher, Kim Jae Yeong.
(Advising teacher: Kim Jae Yeong)
That's my dad.
Hold on. I have something for you.
What's this?
The collection of writings
of the student council...
back when your dad
was the advising teacher.
He went by the name Kim Jae Yeong.
Was your father
also an agent at the NIS?
(2003 Byeongmun High School
Student Council, "Stars That Write")
(Advising teacher: Kim Jae Yeong)
(The Note in Red Letters)
"At midnight,
the computer turns on..."
"in an empty classroom."
"And the ghost of a dead teacher
leaves a note..."
"in red letters."
You're saying...
that this is Byeongmun High's
fourth ghost story?
That's how it seems.
Isn't it weird though?
The computer.
Seo Byeong Mun died in 1957.
At that time, computers
weren't even used in Korea.
That means the ghost story...
wasn't left behind
by Seo Byeong Mun.
Then who else...
(Advising teacher: Kim Jae Yeong)
The one who put this collection
of writings together.
There were only ever
three ghost stories,
but one was fabricated
to confuse others...
or to stop Seo Myeong Ju
from obtaining the gold bars.
If there never was
a fourth story to begin with,
that leaves us with one conclusion.
The meaning behind this phrase.
Solving it...
will point us to
where the gold bars are.
So? How did it go?
We checked from the gym
to the assembly hall,
but nothing showed up.
Anyway, Ms. Seo, has the school gym
gone under renovation before?
There are interesting tales
surrounding the school.
He even went as far
as to lie to me?
Fine. Starting tomorrow,
search the main building.
And make it fast.
Our cards are all on the table now,
so speed is of the essence.
- Okay?
- Yes, ma'am.
The one with the bead. "Hwigyeong."
The words refer to Seo Byeong Mun.
"The gold will shine."
That's where the gold bars are.
When Seo Byeong Mun
faces the red sun,
he'll point to where
the gold bars are.
What on earth is the red sun?
Seo Byeong Mun facing it
is also an issue.
It's not like a dead man
can rise from his casket.
What can he face?
Could he have...
left a copy of him at the school?
A copy of him?
To guard the gold bars
even in his death...
with those crimson eyes of his.
What is this crap you're spewing?
Go home
if you're not going to be helpful!
No, wait. Yeong Hun has a point.
See? I have my moments.
So what could be a copy of him
or something that symbolizes...
Seo Byeong Mun?
Come on.
You'd know
having been a student there.
Seo Byeong Mun's...
portrait?
His portrait?
- There are too many of them.
- I see.
Seo Byeong Mun's...
bust.
Look it up.
His bust?
"As the Minister of Finance
of the Empire of Korea,"
"he served as keeper
of the royal treasure..."
"and founded
Hwigyeong Public Academy."
"After Korea lost its sovereignty,"
"he joined
the independence movement..."
"and contributed to the development
of our nation's education..."
"by taking office
as the first chairman..."
"of Hwigyeong Academy."
He served Japan
and wasn't an independence fighter.
(3.2. The Bust
of the First Chairman)
Facing the red sun...
means to serve Japan.
Hey. Where are you off to?
The school. To confirm it.
How? You were expelled.
You're right.
(Guidelines to bring change
to Byeongmun High School)
(No longer accepting
the socially disadvantaged)
Things haven't been the same...
since Hae Seong was expelled.
Everything's a mess
and is confusing.
He came with his drama,
but things were fun
when he was around.
Anyway,
what did he do
to get on the chairwoman's bad side?
Do you know anything?
I'm just as clueless.
The recently changed guidelines
aren't making things better.
What will become of this school?
I wouldn't mind someone
turning it upside down.
- Delivery.
- Come on in.
You can leave it here.
Please enjoy.
Thank you.
You!
You?
My gosh!
My stomach hurts.
Enjoy and head home.
- What?
- My stomach's killing me!
But this is delicious.
You! Are you crazy?
Why would you come here?
You're out of your mind.
This was my best option.
My heart's still racing.
What if the chairwoman finds out?
I had something to check.
What about his bust? Why...
Did you find them?
If what I think is correct, yes.
My gosh.
So you're saying...
that he stole from the nation...
and hid the gold
in the sculpture of himself?
He sure is testing me.
What are you doing?
Do you know how long...
our independence was set back
because of him?
An independence fighter, you say?
A contributor
to our nation's education?
You shouldn't touch that.
Why you...
Who's there?
Ms. Oh?
Mr. Baek, what brings you here?
I forgot something.
Who's there behind you?
I ordered a late-night snack,
but he couldn't remember
his way out.
He should've dropped off
the food and left.
Why is he still here?
Well...
He was greatly interested
in our school's history,
- so I was explaining...
- Step aside.
Which service are you with?
What's the number?
Look at that.
You can't even answer my questions.
There's something suspicious
about you.
Take off that helmet.
Don't just stand there
and take it off!
If you don't comply,
I'll call the cops.
Good.
Guess who?
Ms. Oh, I'm sorry,
but what is the meaning of this?
What do you think you're doing?
- Ms. Oh, what...
- Guess who?
- What is this?
- My gosh!
Are you kidding me?
Let go!
What woman is this strong?
What... My eyes.
What on earth? Wait, that man.
Where did he go?
He has deliveries piled up.
Are you kidding me?
- You...
- My gosh.
- Which service did you use?
- I'm sorry.
Was it Delivery Nation
or Coming to You?
I don't know.
Hey, how did it go?
- What the...
- Hey!
Stay put, will you?
The bust is the key.
- It rotates.
- No way. And?
So?
What happened after it rotated?
I don't know.
Why not?
Because I got caught.
You were caught?
By whom?
- I wasn't caught.
- What?
I was caught, but I also wasn't.
What on earth is he saying?
Someone interpret that.
Well, I had my helmet on,
so don't worry.
Anyway, that's not important.
We need to figure out
how we'll get the gold bars.
- Okay, how will we do that?
- Let's brainstorm.
What? What is with you?
I didn't know you liked
to do things on a whim!
So, we don't have a plan.
- Seriously.
- You said you wouldn't...
Then you come up with a plan,
you punk!
- What?
- Why are you yelling?
- When did I...
- How could you...
- This fool!
- Quiet down!
I barely made it out!
Students are complaining
about the differences...
in school meals
based on their grades.
History always moves forward
even if people have complaints.
Don't mind them.
Ma'am, but if they continue
to complain about it...
The train has to depart on time
even if some dogs bark.
Don't worry about it.
- Mr. Baek, you're next.
- Oh, yes.
I wanted to talk to you
about visitor control.
- Visitor?
- Yes.
Trespassing cases at schools...
have been on the rise
for the past five years.
But we have no security issues.
Sometimes,
teachers who are working late...
would use food delivery apps.
Even last night,
Ms. Oh Su A did that.
- Ms. Oh Su A?
- Tell us more.
Sure.
The thing is, I saw Ms. Oh
talking to some delivery guy...
under the founder's sculpture
last night.
She said
he came to deliver her food.
I was like,
"Just leave the food and go."
"Why are you chatting away?"
Then she said she was explaining
the school's history...
A food delivery guy driving a van?
That's unheard of.
It's Jeong Hae Seong.
There's a chance...
he might try to sneak in again
to find the gold bars.
What should we do?
I so kindly asked him
not to do this.
Let's send him our second gift.
Yes.
Please proceed with the plan.
- I guess you're very busy.
- Yes, I am quite busy.
What is it? What now?
If it's about school management,
don't bring it up.
It's about Hae Seong.
I thought about it
all day yesterday,
and there's only one answer.
You knew, didn't you?
That he wasn't a real student.
Hae Seong is an NIS agent.
Wasn't that why he was expelled?
The recent incidents at school.
Mr. Lee, you, Principal Park.
Hae Seong's real identity
and his expulsion too.
I bet there's something
I don't know.
Ye Na, when I don't tell you
something,
it means
you don't need to know about it.
Tell me, please.
I have the right to know, Mom.
You can't get anything done
without trial and error.
The bigger the ocean is,
the more unpredictable
the waves are.
Ye Na, the important thing is...
that Edu-City will be completed.
And the owner of Edu-City is me,
Seo Myeong Ju.
You will be my successor.
That's all you need to know.
I'll take care of the rest.
Mom.
Have you ever...
thought about
what I might really want?
You see, I...
I believe there will come a day
when you can understand me.
I really believe that.
How about we go for a walk?
We haven't done it in a while.
You and me, just the two of us.
It's so cold these days.
Come on. Let's go!
(Here's the file on Jeong Hae Seong
you asked for.)
What is this?
My gosh.
That really scared me.
Hello?
I swear, I saw it move.
What are you doing?
You have a class to teach.
Yes, hello!
I'm on my way to my class. And you?
Hey, breathe.
You're out of breath.
I'm teaching Class Two.
Let's go together.
What?
(New Message)
No way.
- What is this?
- Hey, what's this?
- Did you see this?
- What is this?
- What's going on?
- A teacher dating her student?
- What's this?
- Guys, did you see this?
What is this?
What's this?
- This is huge!
- Is this real?
- What's going on?
- No way.
- Isn't this Ms. Oh?
- Is this the transfer student?
- What?
- Oh, my.
- What is this?
- For real?
My gosh.
(I'm so shocked.
Shouldn't she get fired?)
This is why...
they should've listened to me
when I warned them nicely.
Stupid Koreans.
Hey, she's here.
All right.
Let's begin.
Where did we leave off last class?
Ms. Oh, what's with those photos?
Are you really dating a student?
She's all quiet, so it must be true.
I told you
what I saw at the hospital.
They really are dating.
- How could she do this?
- That's inappropriate.
- Isn't it out of line?
- Unbelievable.
I'm so disappointed in Ms. Oh.
How could she date a student?
- How could she...
- Ms. Oh.
Chairwoman Seo wants to see you.
I'm teaching a class.
I'll speak with her later.
You don't have to...
teach here anymore.
(Korean History, Oh Su A)
Are they letting her go?
- Really?
- I think she's getting fired.
Come with me.
Who is interrupting Ms. Oh's class?
- Oh, my.
- Hae Seong is here.
The students are here now, you know.
I suggest you return to your office,
Principal Park.
I know it's only been a few days,
but it's good to see you again.
Should we applaud him?
- Applause!
- Give him a big hand!
- Thanks.
- Applause!
- Yes!
- He's so cool.
Applause!
Have you lost your mind?
What are you doing here?
I came here today...
to tell you guys the truth.
About the pictures you saw
this morning...
They're real.
- My gosh!
- So, it's true?
- It's real?
- They really are dating?
- So, it's real.
- Yes, I told you.
But you guys
shouldn't get the wrong idea.
Ms. Oh...
did not go on a date with a minor.
- "Minor?"
- What's he saying?
- What?
- He's not making any sense.
He's not a minor?
I've been serving
in the Reserve Forces for six years.
(Military Service Certificate)
I'm 31 years old.
- What?
- Now, he's even cooler.
- So, he's an old man.
- He's old enough to be my uncle.
- Who called me Uncle?
Six years in the Reserve Forces?
He's thirty-one?
Anyway,
I'm sorry for lying to you guys.
From now on,
call me your big brother.
- Brother!
Nice, I have a brother now.
- My brother, Hae Seong.
- He's older than us!
My gosh. What a relief.
(Self-study instead of PE today,
Keep quiet!)
- Hey, Jeong Hae Seong is here.
- What? Jeong Hae Seong?
- Hey, Jeong Hae Seong is here!
- Really?
- Jeong Hae Seong is here.
- For real?
Is he really here?
Did the bell ring?
Ma'am.
Jeong Hae Seong is here now.
Jeong Hae Seong is here.
Look, Jeong Hae Seong.
My gosh. I guess it's true.
- Does this mean it's true?
- Yes, I think so.
It must be true.
- Oh, my.
- I told you.
- I know.
- What did I tell you?
All right. Any questions?
Yes, Chae Lin.
Why did you lie about your age
to attend this school, sir?
Right,
I haven't explained that part.
The truth is, I'm from...
the National...
The National...
I didn't complete
my basic national education,
which left me deeply scarred.
What's he saying?
- He didn't go to high school.
- Oh, I see.
Life's been tough for me.
As a Korean citizen,
I thought I at least needed
a high school diploma.
- How inspiring.
- We understand!
- You're an inspiration!
- Yes!
- Don't cry!
- We get it!
- We understand.
- Yes!
- So...
- Don't worry!
I came here.
Then what about
the pictures of you and Ms. Oh?
What's going on between you two?
She helped me
so I could adjust well at school.
And...
I like her...
a lot.
Oh, my. They really are dating!
My gosh.
Hae Seong, you're so cool!
- Oh, no.
- How romantic!
That was so cool!
- So cool!
- Oh, my!
Kiss!
- What? Stop it.
- Kiss!
You managed to turn an ugly rumor
into romance.
You can change genres
in the middle of a story.
It all depends on the choices
that the protagonist makes.
Try to smile a little.
When you're mad, it shows.
And...
it's my turn now.
I won't let you down.
(Byeongmun High School)
Jeong Hae Seong!
Why?
Well...
Let me walk you to the gate.
Sure.
Let's go, teacher.
How could Jeong Hae Seong
get it sorted out so quickly?
I think the info got leaked...
Right, so who gave him
the information?
You and I were the only ones
who knew about those pictures...
Come on, Ye Na. What are you doing?
I'm waiting.
I'm coming.
Thanks for your help
in the morning.
Yes, hello?
I have something to tell you.
It's about you and Ms. Oh.
(Byeongmun High School)
Wait, stop!
May I help you?
Well...
He's a friend of mine.
Let's go inside.
Oh, all right.
You may go inside.
No problem.
No.
Ms. Oh means a lot to me too.
Should I use honorifics
when talking to you now?
I'll just keep talking casually.
- That's okay, right?
- Suit yourself.
By the way,
why did you give me a heads-up?
I don't know.
I just...
felt like I should tell you.
Let me ask you a question too.
Why did you come to our school?
Does it...
have something to do with my mom?
I'll tell you later...
when and if I get the chance.
I'm home.
Why did you do that?
I'm talking about Jeong Hae Seong.
Ye Na.
This is so frustrating.
I am asking you a question
right now.
My gosh.
I'm really frustrated.
Your mother is asking you
a question.
Why are you standing there,
all quiet? My goodness.
Ye Na, you...
Why do you keep acting up
these days?
It's because of you, Mom.
Hae Seong asked me
the exact same question.
To him, I just said, "I don't know."
But now, I know why.
It was because of you, Mom.
You seem to be in
a really precarious situation now.
This isn't good.
Ye Na, get ready to study abroad.
Mom.
You'll leave as soon as possible,
within one week.
No, I'm not going. I will stay here.
Don't act like a child!
Ye Na.
I call the shots.
All you need to do is obey me.
Hello, chairwoman.
The gold bars.
Find them within the day.
Search the whole main building
if you must.
I won't lose them...
to Jeong Hae Seong.
Did you read that story?
Some lunatic in his 30s...
joined a high school
pretending to be a student.
What the heck for? Is he a pervert?
If you think about it,
the world must be coming to an end.
Shouldn't a grown man
have better to do?
The darn psycho.
It's me.
- What?
- It's me.
- Eat all you want.
- Thanks.
Put that down.
Stop eating and talk first.
You mean...
the story
that's circulating the Internet...
- is about you?
- Yes.
You did a proper job
telling the truth in front of the class.
(A student is dating a teacher.)
I didn't say I was NIS.
Good for me, right?
My blood pressure's rising.
Get me some water.
But...
why did you go and do that?
Seo Myeong Ju...
threatened me with photos of me
and Su A so I had no choice.
She helped us with our mission,
so I couldn't let her suffer.
Hey. Be honest.
There's something between you.
No.
On the house.
- Thank you.
- There is.
It goes both ways.
That's not what's important.
If we don't find the gold tonight,
we might lose it to Seo Myeong Ju.
How are we to find the gold tonight?
The chairwoman is
guarding the school,
and we're on standby.
We can't apply for a warrant.
We're stuck.
And if we're to sneak in...
Security will have been upgraded.
Yes.
So today,
we'll attack in the open.
Where are you?
We completed your bust
that will be placed...
in the main building
of the new Edu-City.
There might not be an Edu-City.
What use is a bust?
The bust.
One's own representation.
The symbol of oneself.
- What?
What? Is it weird?
Forget the weirdness. Is that...
even plausible?
Let's say it is
for some miraculous reason.
We're too few.
Where will you find backup?
Director Kim can't know,
so we can't ask
the company for help.
Shall I help?
You, ma'am?
My daughter told me a bit about you.
Thanks for looking out for her,
darling Hae Seong.
"Darling..."
You need people for your mission.
How many do you need?
- Have you eaten, ma'am?
- Ma'am.
Ma'am.
What brings you out of retirement
to this rundown place?
Bongchang-dong Bloody Chicken Gang.
We have a job to do.
- Yes, ma'am.
Did you know your mother's past?
I just found out,
and I won't talk back to her.
Don't.
Why are they called
the Bloody Chicken Gang?
"Bloodbath" sounded old...
and Ms. Im
used to sell fried chicken.
Gosh.
And "Spicy Chicken Gang"
sounds weird.
Sorry.
Are you ready?
- Yes, ma'am.
Let's go!
- Okay!
I'll see you later, agents.
- Okay.
Take care, ma'am.
Make way.
My gosh.
It feels like a storm
just passed by.
We'll get ready and set off too.
- See you later.
- I'll be right there.
You're not coming?
You clueless idiot.
What...
Let's go.
After today's mission,
Jeong Hae Seong the student
will be no more.
That's a bit of a shame.
You looked good
in the school uniform.
- Did I?
- Yes.
What about you?
Do you feel sad
about leaving your friends?
I do.
I think I'll miss them.
I'm off.
- Hae Seong.
- Yes?
Once this mission is done...
- Let's grab a meal together.
- A meal?
Okay.
- Just like that?
- Yes.
I want to. Let's grab a meal.
Okay.
Let's grab a meal and a coffee too.
- Okay.
- See you.
The bust.
The founding chairman's bust.
The gold's under that bust.
I'm heading to the school now.
Bring in some heavy machinery
and start digging.
Okay.
Let's do it!
Move in! Quickly!
Let's go!
This is it.
The bust. Did you remove it?
I think you should get here fast.
Block the entrance.
- Bring that over here.
- Block the path.
Block it.
Okay.
- You can't come in here.
- Get walking.
A car's coming. Take your positions.
- Hurry up.
- Darn you.
- Let's be loud.
- Okay.
Keep your wits about you.
Do you want to be here all night?
Find it quickly!
Don't you know we must move fast!
- Get to it!
- What are you doing?
What are you doing in my school?
Speak with me...
Chairwoman Seo.
I'm from the NIS.
Mr. Agent.
What on earth is this?
I'm sorry
I couldn't inform you sooner.
We got a tip that...
a spy got into Byeongmun High.
A spy?
From North Korea, to be exact.
We believe he came in
via the west coast and Incheon.
I see.
Shall I confirm that, then?
- And spin.
- Spin.
- And swing down.
- Down.
Try again a bit more relaxed.
Let's work more slowly.
- Hello?
- It's Seo Myeong Ju.
Hyung Bae's busy right now.
Are you his wifey?
You dare take me on
with a stupid trick like this?
We'll investigate to see
if the tip-off was genuine.
For your safety, chairwoman...
Very well.
Principal Park?
Call our people immediately.
Okay.
Come this way.
Come with...
Hey.
She's calling her people.
Will it be okay?
I don't know. It could be bad.
What?
I promise to find
Emperor Gojong's gold tonight.
You must.
They're ready.
If I were Seo Byeong Mun...
If I loved riddles and treasure...
If I created the scary stories...
and allowed only those
who solved them to reach the gold.
You were a curious guy.
Even in death,
you'd have wanted to see
who solved the puzzle.
If it were your descendant...
or someone like me and my dad...
who wanted to correct all the wrong.
First, the old building.
Second, the student council room.
Third, the music studio.
When the one with the bead...
faces the red sun...
The gold will shine.
(First Chairman Seo Byeong Mun)
Senior Agent An.
How did it go? Did you find it?
The gold.
I don't think it existed.
What do you mean?
There's no gold?
Hello?
Darn it.
(Undercover High School)
Where's my gold?
Where did you hide my gold?
Chairwoman Seo's become a monster.
I think I found a way.
A way to make Jeong Hae Seong talk.
It looks like Hae Seong's father
was murdered, right?
I think Director Kim is the suspect.
Will Hae Seong...
Let's talk in person.
Try to calm down...
I'm sorry, Uncle.
This is the only way.
Why did you kill him?
Why did you kill my dad?
- Jeong Hae Seong!
- Three, two.
Su A. Thanks for everything.
Hae Seong!
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)