Officail Website : kissasia.id  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
♪ Hold me tight,
let the darkness drown me ♪
♪ Even one second of truth is enough
to lose myself in it ♪
♪ Hold me tight,
let the darkness drown me ♪
♪ Even one second of truth is enough
to lose myself in it ♪
♪ Whether you're light or a lie,
I can't pull myself away ♪
♪ In this game,
truth or lie no longer matters ♪
[Queen of Darkness]
[Episode 20]
You...
Don't recognize me?
Whatever I want,
they'll hand it over without hesitation.
I was out of line yesterday.
I'm here to apologize.
I don't accept
an after-the-fact apology.
♪ The world is bustling,
but your departure left me an island ♪
Huo Xiao.
You're getting way too bold.
You've got yourself
tangled in too much trouble.
I just don't want you to die this early.
How did you know I'd save him?
What if I failed?
There's no "what ifs".
♪ It's okay,
I'll sing my broken self to me ♪
Next time you thank me,
don't bring a knife.
Who are you,
really?
Who I am doesn't matter.
What matters is
what you think of me.
If you find out
I'm not who you think I am,
will you still treat me this way?
Who I'm willing to risk everything for
is the you right here.
Not the past.
Just focus on what's ahead.
If one day,
your memory comes back,
have you thought
how you'd handle it?
I just want a happy ending.
Whether the ending is good or not
depends on people's hearts.
♪ It's okay,
I'll sing my broken self to me ♪
♪ The rain won't stop,
just like I can't wait for you ♪
♪ The clouds share my sorrow,
eyes red from crying ♪
♪ The sky won't clear,
just like I can't reach you ♪
♪ Who said after rain comes sunshine ♪
♪ Endless rain, endless longing for you ♪
♪ I thought I could escape this downpour ♪
♪ But one look from you
pulled me right back in ♪
♪ The saddest place to be ♪
Mi...
Miss.
[Controlled Substance Code Number]
These are all internal members of
Song family's gang crime trade.
There are also
overseas trading accounts.
My dad
already had proof of their gang crime.
Could it be that the boss's death
is also linked to the Song family?
Everyone from
the Song family.
[United Nations Office on Drugs]
[and Crime] None of them are innocent.
None of them can escape.
Miss.
Just give the order.
And I'll take the guys and wipe them out!
Killing them
is too easy on them.
I'll take away what they cherish most,
then step on them under my feet
and crush them
one by one.
[Equity Transfer Agreement]
Seems you still can't let go of
the 20% shares in my hand.
You shameless woman.
I know what you really want.
As long as you hand over the shares,
I can have Ti Cha divorce you.
You guessed right this time.
I do want to kick Ti Cha out of my life.
Then why don't you just
sign the agreement?
That way, you can go
find your lover openly.
I'm not in a hurry.
Why are you?
It's dinner time.
Tonight,
I specially prepared a feast
for you and father-in-law.
What trick are you up to now?
I just want to show my filial piety.
Dad, mom.
You won't deny me this chance, right?
Serve the dishes.
That fool Jiang Meng
couldn't even kill An Ning.
I'll see what she's up to now.
An Ning.
You're playing us, huh?
(Watch on www.kisskh.ca to support Admin)
Did I get it wrong?
So you don't like vegetarian dishes.
But I heard
that when father-in-law was young,
he only ordered vegetarian dishes.
Nonsense.
Steward.
Clear these dishes away.
And make new ones.
Wait.
Mom.
I just remembered something.
I made a mistake.
Dad's first love
was your sister, Zhen.
It was Zhen
who liked vegetarian dishes.
Shut up!
You have no right to meddle in
the elders' private affairs.
No place for me to ask,
or are you scared
of what I might bring up?
Quiet.
Dad.
You don't look well.
Are you thinking of Zhen
and feeling sad?
If Zhen's spirit could know
how deeply you loved her,
I wonder if she should be touched,
or just laugh at your foolishness.
You brought up Zhen for no reason.
What exactly do you want to say?
There's a lot I want to say.
I just don't know if someone
has the courage to let me say it.
Say whatever you want.
But if you talk nonsense,
I'll never let you off.
Dad.
Have you ever thought about this?
Back then,
you and Zhen were deeply in love,
and she came from a wealthy family.
So why did she
suddenly fall into the water
and drown?
The police already looked into it.
My sister went for a walk by the river
and fell in accidentally while trying to
pick up her hat
that was blown into the water.
But I heard Zhen
was pushed into the river.
And the culprit
has something to do with you.
You shameless woman.
Dare to talk nonsense.
I'll tear your mouth apart!
If you keep making baseless claims,
I'll make you pay for this.
Are you sure she's dead?
I've already confirmed it.
I left the body at the river mouth.
The police have received the report.
Later, I'll lead the team to respond
and find the body.
Jiang Meng.
It was you.
You teamed up with Jiang Meng.
You caused Zhen's death!
Officail Website : kissasia.id  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Fake.
It's fake.
This video could've been edited.
You did this!
You're the one who tried to frame me.
Now I remember.
That ruby ring on your finger
was carefully chosen by Zhen
as your coming-of-age gift.
There's only one such ring
in the entire world.
Zhen treated mother-in-law
so kindly back then.
But right after her accident,
why did you marry her boyfriend?
Back then,
you said you'd comfort me
for your sister's sake,
but it turns out you were deliberately
plotting
to marry into the Song family!
No, it's not.
Dear, it's not like that.
Don't let that awful woman fool you.
Liar!
Zhen was your own sister.
What did she do to wrong you?
Yet you killed her so cruelly!
I knew it.
You never forgot her.
Zhen was gentle and kind.
I'll remember her forever!
I bore your children for you,
took care of everything in the family,
and we've stood by each other
for over ten years.
Does that still lose to
a fleeting crush you had
when you were young?
What makes you think
you can compare to her?
Everything you enjoy now,
the role of Mrs. Song,
was meant for Zhen.
You snatched it
with disgraceful tricks!
Snatched it away?
So what?
This happened over twenty years ago!
This video means nothing now.
Even the law can't touch me.
I'm still Mrs. Song.
I'll always be a noble lady
above everyone else!
You scheming woman.
If the law can't punish you,
I will!
Guards!
Get this vile woman
out of the Song family.
Don't let her take a single cent with her.
If she steps into here again,
beat her to death!
- I'm a billionaire's wife!
- Move!
Let me go!
I'm Mrs. Song!
I'm a billionaire's wife!
Let me go!
Let me...
Mom.
Th..this...
What happened here?
Ti Cha.
An Ning set me up.
Your father kicked me out.
Hurry, take mom back home.
No.
That's impossible.
Why would dad do that?
Mom.
I... this...
Ti Cha.
She killed your dad's first love.
And that woman was her own sister.
Do you think your dad
would ever forgive her for that?
No, no.
Ti Cha, Ti Cha.
Ti Cha!
Go.
Mom, mom!
That happened so many years ago.
How could it suddenly resurface?
Was it you?
Mother-in-law ruled
her home for half a lifetime.
But now she's a discarded woman
of a wealthy family.
So, from now on,
her life is bound to get pretty interesting.
♪ Mist coils around the sleeping forest ♪
♪ Memories scattered
through cracks of darkness ♪
♪ How to escape this real-feeling dream ♪
♪ Lies reflect in water's gleam ♪
♪ Traces of existence
can never be erased ♪
♪ How to find the self I can't reclaim ♪
♪ Fly away, hear she says ♪
♪ She'll fly out from
thorns of woven lies ♪
♪ Pierce the fog,
shatter this dream tonight ♪
♪ Burn like fire ♪
♪ Just burn like fire ♪
♪ The maze in the abyss starts to clear ♪
♪ Yet night keep on whispering ♪
♪ Surrender to fate,
no clear direction ahead ♪
♪ She will rise as the dawn
that breaks the darkness ♪
♪ Never slowing down,
for tomorrow cannot be stopped ♪
♪ Surrender to love and find the way ♪
♪ Even if fate tries to forget her ♪
♪ Never despair,
for the heart burns with endless light ♪
♪ Waiting for dawn ♪
[Copyright of this short drama
belongs to]
[Shanghai Chuqi Weishi
Culture Media Co., Ltd.]
[and Youku Information Technology (Beijing)
[Co., Ltd.]
[Youku Information Technology (Beijing)
[holds exclusive global online
and broadcast rights]