[The Epoch of Miyu]
[Episode 9]
I wanted to know what Purong Hotel
had become.
So what are your thoughts after seeing it?
Purong is a big tree
that looks glorious on the outside.
In reality,
it has been hollowed out by termites.
Okay.
Second question.
What are you exactly doing back this time?
An incognito investigation, right?
I'm not some big shot.
Tell me.
Did you come back to Purong to take over?
Yes.
Chairman Wei asked you back?
From the first time I saw you,
I knew it.
I knew I couldn't hide it from you.
Let me give you a piece of advice.
Leave immediately.
This ship of Purong
is going to sink soon.
To be honest,
what you saw today
is only the tip of the iceberg in Purong.
Do you know how much liquor
is wasted in
the Executive Lounge every day?
Do you know how many
carts of linen in the Laundry Room
are sent away every day,
and how many people take kickbacks?
Do you know how long the equipment
in the Engineering Department
hasn't been updated,
and whose pockets
the project funds went into?
I have investigated
all the problems you mentioned.
Take a look at my investigation report.
[Research Report on Operation and
Management Problems of Purong Hotel]
Rui.
I have 2 reasons
for returning to Purong.
[Front Office: Marketing Alienation
and Lack of Service Focus]
First,
I've reached the top abroad.
No matter how perfect
I make a hotel,
in the end,
it still belongs to those
blonde-haired, blue-eyed managers.
[Executive Lounge: Beverage Waste
and Uncontrolled Costs]
But Purong can give me
a place to realize my ambitions.
Second,
Purong Hotel is the start of my career,
and Chairman Wei is my first mentor.
Purong Hotel is now facing
a crucial moment.
I really can't bear
and I'm not willing to
see Purong Hotel
taken away just like that.
You are right.
But you have to be clear.
Today's Purong Hotel
is no longer the famous hotel in Shanghai
under Wei Wanjun in the past.
It's rotten to the core.
What's the use of coming back?
I plan to
reorganize Purong Hotel.
Rui, you know
what the purpose
of Purong Hotel has always been.
Making guests feel at home.
From the jasmine fragrance in the corridor
to the service specifications
of every detail,
everything should be focused
on the guests' experience.
But now?
The current managers
don't care about this at all.
They only care about
how to reach into the guests' wallets.
That's why the reputation
is getting worse.
Do you think I don't know?
Rui.
I'd like to
invite you
to cooperate with me.
Really.
Let's work together
to bring back
the traditions of Purong Hotel
and completely reform it
from the inside out.
This is the only way to save Purong Hotel.
I know.
I know it's hard.
But it's up to us.
Rui, what conditions do you want?
Just tell me,
and I'll meet them all.
Wait.
Ji Feng, are you high?
I really need you
to help me.
Ji Feng.
I'm resigning next month
to go to Yiting Siji
and work in finance.
The soup dumplings you ordered.
Enjoy.
I have no choice.
The situation forces my hand.
Within a year,
Purong Hotel changing hands to Kuanli
is almost a foregone conclusion.
For a pseudo-middle-class like me,
whether I'm ousted
or make it to the top,
I have to leave sooner or later.
For the past 10 years,
I've drifted through life
and accomplished nothing.
I am not qualified to guide you.
But I want to remind you of one thing.
Things run deep and rough
in Purong.
In the future,
take care of yourself.
Miss,
can I add you on WeChat?
Sorry, sir.
We are not allowed
to add guests on WeChat privately.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Mr. Ray.
I am an attendant from the HSKP Department
on the executive floor.
Is there anything I can help you with?
Why is it you?
I'm looking for Xu Miyu.
Whatever you need,
you can tell me just the same.
What do I have to tell you?
I already said it.
I'm looking for Xu Miyu.
Why isn't she serving me?
I'm sorry, sir.
Where is your forewoman?
Miyu.
Xu Miyu.
Ms. Zhang, what is it?
My guest requested room service from you.
Why didn't you go?
Because of your negligence,
my guest is feeling very unwell now.
Do you know that?
I have to serve many guests every day.
I couldn't handle everything at once.
I sent a more suitable colleague
who could get there faster.
Do I have to report everything to you?
What kind of working attitude is this?
Director Lu,
please don't be angry.
Miyu, stop talking.
Besides, your guest
has been harassing me.
I believe even if the hotel
follows the customer-first principle,
when this happens,
even a regular attendant
has the right to say no.
I already used a very tactful way
to save the guest's face.
I don't think I did anything wrong.
Xu Miyu.
Are you suffering from paranoia?
My guest would harass you?
What evidence do you have?
You have nothing to say, right?
Look in the mirror.
You don't have to use such dirty tricks
to flatter yourself, do you?
You call this flattering myself?
Is this how you usually
flatter yourself, Director Lu?
Your values are so advanced
that they're completely out of reach.
Say it again.
Miyu, stop it.
Director Lu, how about this?
I'll ask her to apologize to Mr. Ray
to make up for it.
Ms. Zhang,
why are you keeping an employee like this?
Director Lu.
Calm down.
You heard her.
Go apologize right now!
Well.
Why are you still standing here?
Aren't you afraid of getting a bad review?
Okay.
I'll go apologize.
Yin Xiang,
can you do me a favor?
Room service.
You're finally here.
Come in.
Sorry.
Our hotel has a rule that
during room service,
the door must remain open.
Why didn't you reply to my messages today?
I wanted to buy you dinner,
but you didn't show up.
I ordered a bottle of wine.
Have a drink with me.
I'm sorry.
I can't drink with you.
Why?
You are the guest,
and I am an attendant.
My job is to
provide you with service and help.
You might have misunderstood.
If there is nothing else,
I will leave now.
Wait.
Then help me clear the food.
Miyu,
listen to me.
You are different from
the other attendants here.
The moment I first saw you,
I fell for you.
Can I hug you?
Don't come any closer.
I know good reviews
are very important to you.
I will give you a good review.
As many as you want.
I am already recording.
What you just said has already
constituted sexual harassment.
If you don't want me to call the police,
let me out right now!
Sexual harassment?
When did I ever sexually harass you?
I haven't even touched you.
You gave me your WeChat ID yourself.
And now you say
I'm sexually harassing you?
Or is it that
you actually hope
I really do something?
The Engineering Department
received a maintenance report
for the drain in your room.
Yin Xiang!
I didn't report a repair.
Leave quickly.
Miyu.
Wait.
The guest just said
to let us leave.
What are you doing?
Let's go.
Wait, wait, wait.
Didn't you hear?
Something's going to happen.
The guest is inside now.
We don't know the situation.
Forcing the door open
will result in punishment
and complaints.
Don't screw yourself over
and drag us into it.
Open the door!
I'll take responsibility.
Open it.
What are you doing?
Who let you in?
I'm sorry, I...
I got the wrong room.
I called for a repair
and didn't bring my room card.
Sorry, my room should be next door.
[Purong Hotel Accommodation
and Conference Contract]
Mr. Qian,
if HSKP Department acts like this,
I wouldn't dare
let guests stay here anymore.
I worked so hard to get this order,
and it's ruined just like that.
What's the meaning of this?
Don't worry.
I'll settle accounts with
the HSKP Department.
How do you do things?
How am I supposed to
show my face after this?
How am I supposed to hold my head up
in front of the sales team next time?
Mr. Feng, I'm wronged.
It was that Xu Miyu who acted on her own
and made things worse.
I had no time for crisis public relations.
Why is it Xu Miyu again?
Didn't I tell you to fire her last time?
I haven't had the time yet.
You hurry up and get rid of her to
make an example of her.
I dare not, Mr. Feng.
She has the guest's leverage.
If we fire her now,
it might backfire.
Wait a couple of days
until I find the right opportunity.
Mr. Feng, someone is outside to see you.
Okay, okay. Go and handle it quickly.
He said he is a friend of Mr. Nie Yucheng,
named Ji Feng.
Ji Feng?
Hurry, invite him in.
Wait a minute.
Please invite Mr. Ji in.
Miyu,
come with me.
[Xu Miyu, 18F,
Morning Shift, Bad Review]
The sales department suffered losses
and blamed the HSKP Department.
I have no choice either.
Ms. Zhang.
I was mentally prepared
for this bad review.
But
I am also a victim.
I shouldn't bear
all the responsibility alone.
You should also reflect on yourself.
Why didn't the guest harass others
but harassed you?
Did you give the guest the wrong signal
and cause a misunderstanding?
Hello, Mr. Feng.
About your bad review decision,
I am updating Xu Miyu.
What?
Miyu,
don't let me embarrass myself here.
You clearly have Black Card Ji
as such a strong backer,
and you didn't even tell me.
You made me look like a fool.
What are you doing here?
Hello, Mr. Ji.
You came just in time.
I have some rotten fruit
in my living room.
Please come in and help me clean it up.
Okay.
How are you doing?
I'm fine.
Thank you for your help this time.
I bent the rules for you
out of my inner principles.
A dignified five-star hotel
having to cater
to a harasser
is indeed unacceptable.
But that doesn't mean
you're completely
blameless in this matter.
Do you also think
I must've done something to deserve it?
I didn't think that way.
Most of the time,
the relationship between
staff and guests is not equal.
This means
you must have a stronger
sense of self-protection and methods.
The hotel rules state that
staff and guests cannot
contact each other privately.
This rule is not only a restriction,
but also a protection for you.
Your people-pleasing mentality
leads you
to step outside
the protection of the rules,
step by step,
giving them opportunities
to push their luck.
After that, whether you
have a righteous reason or not,
no matter how cleverly you respond,
you will be the one to suffer.
Live and learn.
Next time,
I won't make the same mistake again.
You are quite adaptable.
Here.
Thanks, I'm not thirsty.
Apply an ice compress.
At least you had the sense
to call in a colleague with
the Engineering Department crew
to help you out.
In the future,
if you encounter
this kind of situation again,
you can also come to me directly.
Are you okay?
[Purong Hotel Staff Apartment]
Miyu.
Come here.
Sit.
I want to ask you a question.
I'm asking you,
how did you get so close to Black Card Ji?
Yeah, teach us
your tricks too.
Miyu,
is that guy the type who is cold
on the outside but warm on the inside?
Cold as ice on the surface,
but once he commits to you,
he will go through fire and water for you.
You read too many wish-fulfillment novels.
What's wrong with wish-fulfillment novels?
A strong, beautiful,
and tragic female lead
protected by a domineering CEO,
outsmarting a bunch
of crazy and obsessive monsters.
Dare you say your dopamine didn't spike?
Didn't it spike?
What are you all talking about?
I don't understand at all.
This is not the script of my life.
It's okay, Miyu.
We're already shipping it.
With a mysterious VIP
giving you a boost, your life
is about to take off.
Shipped it.
So sweet.
Hello, Neil.
Any updates?
Happy birthday, Mr. Ji.
Thank you.
Mr. Ji,
did you sign the contract with Landi?
Yeah, it was me.
I've signed it for a couple of weeks.
Anything wrong?
Andy is on this contract.
And it seems that Landi is suing us
for some loopholes in
the imported horses protection clause.
Happy birthday.
Okay, thank you.
Please.
Tell me more about that.
Take your time.
Tell Andy to get in touch with me.
I'll wait for him.
Happy birthday.
Hello, Mr. Ji.
Today is your birthday.
On behalf of all the service staff
on the executive floor,
I wish you a happy birthday.
Thank you.
Mr. Ji,
our executive floor
provides special
birthday services for guests.
Private dining rooms for up to 20 guests,
as well as party spaces
for up to 80 guests,
[Dear Mr. Ji, in the year ahead,]
[may your life be as
beautiful as poetry, filled with joy,]
[sunshine,]
[and surprises. Happy Birthday.]
do not require advance reservations.
Got it.
Tell the others
not to say happy birthday to me anymore.
Mr. Ji,
what would you like to eat?
The usual. Thanks.
Okay.
If you need anything,
please feel free to contact me.
Okay.
Thanks.
[Andy]
Is this Andy?
Great.
I have something to discuss with you.
The kitchen
is already preparing
the birthday fruit platter.
Should we cancel it?
Why cancel?
Free items still need
to be put on the tab.
Then who is going to deliver it?
I'll arrange it.
You guys,
just need to keep your mouths shut.
Miyu.
Make sure the service for room 1812
is spot on today.
Later,
I'll send you the birthday schedule.
Set the mood right.
Room service.
Hello, room service.
Mr. Ji.
Wish...
Just give it a quick sweep.
Andy.
Happy birthday.
Since this incident
occured in the isolated facility,
that was not under our control.
We shouldn't be held responsible for it.
We bought the horses,
but they don't officially
belong to us yet.
The seller shall be
responsible for any risks.
This was clearly
stated in the contract.
The seller didn't have third-party
disease coverage for the horses.
They then infected
all 100 high-value horses
in quarantine.
We lost over 10 million dollars.
Now they want to shift
the blame to our hotel.
Find the contract immediately.
They can't dodge their responsibility.
I'm looking for the contract here.
But, Ji Feng,
you signed the contract
before you left.
Hold on.
The group just sent a formal notice.
If this contract
causes major final losses to the hotel,
the manager who signed the contract
will be blacklisted internationally.
Do you understand?
This means that in
European and American hotel systems,
you will never be hired.
Ji Feng.
Excuse me.
You can't come in.
Who are you?
Mind your own business.
Ji Feng.
You can't come in.
Do you know who I am?
Happy birthday.
Mr. Duan,
we...
Ta-da!
-Happy birthday!
-What is this?
Happy birthday!
Thank you.
-Happy birthday.
-Thank you.
Happy birthday!
-Just a little noise.
-Happy birthday!
-To help you shake the dust off the ceiling.
Are you trying to shake the ceiling
or blow my head off?
Wait a minute.
Help me entertain the guests.
Mr. Duan, excuse me.
I need to take a call.
Excuse me for a moment.
Go.
Let's go party!
Come on.
Attendant.
Come here and build a champagne tower.
If you break it, you have to drink.
Close the curtains.
It's broad daylight.
There's no atmosphere for drinking.
I'll close the curtains.
Queue up some songs.
Queue up the songs.
[Meeting Details]
Hi, Andy.
I can't find the contract.
Are these okay?
Go find the backup copy
of your contract now.
Hurry.
I can't find the backup either.
[Meeting Details]
I suspect
Landi bribed someone in our hotel
to destroy the contract and its backup.
They're clearly out to get us.
Speaking of that,
I signed a memorandum with them.
All the necessary information
and signatures are there.
[Meeting Details]
I'll look for it right now.
You don't still have it, do you?
It's just my way of doing things.
I have to.
There are so many traps to avoid.
[Horse Purchase and Sales Contract]
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday.
Are you okay?
Who pushed me?
My buddy's cake is ruined.
Is this thing important?
Get out.
Get out!
Let's go.
Mr. Ji.
I told you to get out!
Do you people on the executive floor
not understand human speech?
I said I wasn't celebrating my birthday.
Yet you brought a bunch of people
into my room to make a mess.
I didn't bring these people in.
Then who brought them in?
Did they break down the door?
You opened the door
and let them in.
And you even made
some flower arrangement for me.
Did you think by showing off like that
I would give you a good review?
It's not like that.
Let me ask you,
how does your
HSKP Department serve guests?
Is it based on the guests' needs,
or your own preferences?
What a mess.
Do you believe I'll complain about you?
I already told you,
I didn't bring the guests in,
and this mess wasn't
caused by our executive floor.
On what grounds are you
complaining about me?
My birthday is my privacy.
Whether I celebrate it
and who I invite to celebrate with me,
is for me to decide.
You're violating my privacy right now.
That alone
is enough for me to file
a complaint against you.
You say I invaded your privacy, right?
Then as a consumer,
you didn't respect
my right to know either.
How did I not respect your right to know?
Mr. Ji,
do I need to remind you?
Just a month ago,
in the hotel where you
were the general manager,
you kept telling me
that the underwear on my bed
was left by the previous guest.
You said, "Mrs. Nie,
please rest assured.
I have looked into it.
This underwear
has absolutely nothing
to do with your husband."
Nie Yucheng is innocent.
I didn't say your husband was innocent.
Right.
You didn't use the word "innocent."
But you spun the lie so perfectly
that you made me believe he was innocent.
You made me believe
my marriage was rock solid.
I didn't lie.
I...
I just...
I just didn't tell the whole truth.
Not telling the whole truth?
You were taking things out of context,
confusing right and wrong,
misleading me with selective details,
and making sweeping generalizations.
Did your conscience
allow you to say that?
Is that how you treat your
guests and the trust
they place in you—with such hypocrisy?
You keep saying
you serve your guests
and think for them.
You speak in such high-sounding words,
but what you do is so hypocritical
and perfunctory.
Mr. Ji,
are you really thinking for your guests?
I think you're probably
just using sweet words
to build a persona
as a gold-medal manager.
Your own marriage...
Your own marriage failed,
and you don't examine yourself,
but blame me instead.
Don't you think you're ridiculous?
Yes, I am ridiculous.
I'm the laughingstock
of the whole world now.
But don't you think
you have a part in this?
If it weren't for you
helping my ex-husband lie to me,
would my life now
be reduced to this?
You say you think for your guests.
You say all you think about
are the guests' interests.
I think all you think about
are your own interests.
Your KPI.
I...
If Nie Yucheng couldn't
bring you a few clients,
would you need to suck
up to him so desperately?
The funny thing is,
I even thought after
I came to Purong Hotel
you had been helping me.
Actually, it's because of
your guilty conscience, right?
Because you are
my ex-husband's accomplice.
No matter how many masks you wear,
you're a hypocritical wretch to the bone!
If I were you,
I'd look in the mirror
and examine myself carefully.
If it weren't for your own
weakness and incompetence,
coveting wealth and glory,
blindly pleasing your ex-husband,
how could he be so fearless
and act wildly right under your nose?
You're looking for an accomplice, right?
Let me tell you, Xu Miyu,
your ex-husband's
biggest accomplice is you!
I want to file a complaint against
an attendant from the HSKP Department.
Executive floor,
Xu Miyu.
She was rude to a guest
and had a terrible service attitude.
[Album]
[Photo]
[Horse Purchase and Sales Contract]
[Horse Ownership]
[Send]
[Inbox]
Hi, Andy.
That's great.
We're gonna win it.
I can't believe we made it.
Man, you are a true hero.
How I wish I were.
I only ask to be treated like a person.
What did you say?
What I just said is...
Forget it.
I don't know how to express it.
Ji Feng.
Listen.
You should have a drink to celebrate.
Good idea.
Have a good night.
Okay, have a good night.
You say you think for your guests.
You say all you think about
is the guests' interests.
I think all you think about
are your own interests.
Your KPI!
Isn't it just that Nie Yucheng
can bring you some client resources?
Do you have to try
so hard to suck up to him?
I tell you.
You are an accomplice of my ex-husband.
No matter how many masks you wear,
you're a hypocritical wretch to the bone!
[Employee Schedule]
[Xu Miyu, 18F,
Morning Shift, Bad Review]
Miyu.
You haven't taken out
the seasoning packets yet.
We got paid.
Full bonus, 5,500.
How much did you get, Xiang?
Eight thousand?
[Minfu Bank]
Nine thousand?
[Transaction Notification:
Transaction Amount 7,350 RMB]
Ten thousand?
How much did you get?
Not that much.
You have to treat me anyway.
[Transaction Notification:
Transaction Amount 2,800 RMB]
Hello, Officer Wang.
Ms. Xu,
I'm calling to inform you
that the suspect
in the rental fraud and theft case
has been caught.
Really?
But you should be prepared.
Your financial loss
is likely unrecoverable.
I understand.
[Road closed]
Xu Miyu.
Are you Ms. Xu Miyu?
Who are you?
You don't know who we are?
Then what are you hiding for?
Not answering calls
or messages.
What?
Trying to renege?
No, my bonus got deducted recently.
I really don't have money.
Can you give me 2 more days?
I sympathize with you, Ms. Xu,
but telling me this
is useless.
Everyone who can't pay back
says the same thing.
Can you say something new?
Even if you make up a story,
make it a good one.
Don't be nervous, Ms. Xu.
We are just workers too.
I hope you can understand.
Just easily
give us the money,
so we can all go home and rest early.
Right?
I...
I really don't have a single cent.
Give me 2 more days.
I will definitely find a way, okay?
What should we do?
She said 2 more days.
How about this?
I'll treat you to some coffee,
and we can talk somewhere else.
Ms. Xu, you have more to say to us?
Not really.
How about this?
We know a place
where it's easy
to make money overnight.
How about it?
I know you're not the type
to intentionally default on a debt.
Let's go.
Let's go drink coffee.
Let me go.
You're quite strong.
Let me go!
These are my colleagues.
I'll scream!
Okay.
- Call your colleagues over then.
- Let me go!
Let her go!
I heard everything.
I'll give you the money.
If you said that earlier,
this wouldn't have happened.
Come on.
[Lu Ming; Ming]
[Loading]
[Payment to an individual]
Excuse me,
are you her colleague, sir?
Leave immediately,
or I'll call the police.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
I will pay you back as soon as possible.
[Your business loan
has been automatically repaid]
[for ¥5,000. Your payment
for this month has been settled]
Life is truly ironic.
The ones you love
and trust
betray and leave you one by one.
The one who repeatedly
saves you from trouble
is always the one
you should cross paths with the least.
I'm starting to hate my own
pitifulness and weakness.
Room service.
Hello, room service.
Mr. Ji,
you're here.
Can you sew?
Otherwise, sew it yourself.
Done.
Thank you.
By the way.
About last night,
thank you.
[IOU]
This is the IOU.
No need.
It was no trouble.
You must accept it.
I don't want to owe you.
Miyu.
Sit.
Did you
offend Madam Cailu?
No.
Why do you ask?
A couple of days ago,
I heard her
talking to someone on the phone.
She said
she wants to fire you.
What?
Why?
I don't know,
b-but I heard it with my own ears.
I'm not lying to you.
That's impossible.
I've never offended her.
When did you hear her say that?
Last...
Last Tuesday.
In the Linen Room.
I was outside and heard her talking.
She was speaking very anxiously.
It seemed like something had happened.
Last time you asked me
to get 2 bottles of shampoo
from 2 different places,
what was that about?
I can't tell you
too many details right now.
The whole story hasn't
been fully investigated yet.
Then give me a sample.
I'll help you look into it.