WHEN THE PHONE RINGS
PAIK UI-YONG AND PAIK SA-EON
DNA NOT MATCHED
Did you know already?
It doesn't matter?
If…
something happens to me,
and the Paik Sa-eon you've known
disappears from this world,
just remember this.
JUAN FISHING
The only Paik Sa-eon I want to leave
behind in this world is the one
that belongs to Hong Hee-joo.
I know I have no right to say this,
but Hee-joo,
I hope you won't be fooled anymore.
I know your mom forced you to marry him
in my place, and you had no choice,
but if the Paik family deceived us
from the start,
you don't have to stay married to him.
I'll find out the secret
that family is hiding from us.
I'll meet Paik Sa-eon if I have to.
It's my choice.
I wasn't just your stand-in.
It's not because my mom forced me.
I, Hong Hee-joo, choose Paik Sa-eon.
Hee-joo.
And he's not the only one who has secrets.
I've deceived him too.
Including about being able to speak.
So this is what your voice sounds like.
It's pretty.
I don't know how it'd sound to you,
but when we were young,
I liked how you called my name.
Though I hated your mom
and it felt weird to suddenly have
a younger sibling…
"In-a."
Your voice was so adorable.
To have a little sister
who called my name like that…
It was really nice, to be honest.
Who sent you…
this document?
I don't know.
It was sent anonymously.
And it wasn't my dad or your mom.
But I'm certain of one thing.
They knew
I wouldn't marry Paik Sa-eon
if I saw this.
So, someone hoped
the marriage wouldn't go through.
JUAN FISHING
What are you doing here?
We have to get out of here!
He's after you!
Go! Hurry!
No!
Let's go!
PAIK SA-EON
I'd like to report a missing person.
A missing person?
Yes, I can't reach my husband,
and he hasn't come home yet.
How long has it been
since you last heard from him?
About six hours.
Could it be that your husband
is just running a little late?
We can't file a missing person report
based on that alone.
What can I do then?
In fact, an adult over 18
with no history of illness
or evidence of a crime is considered
a runaway, not a missing person…
There is evidence of a crime.
My husband is being threatened.
He's being threatened?
Yes, by a complete madman.
He might've done something to him.
He set a fire and threw a bomb!
He even pushed someone off a cliff.
Threats, bombs,
and he even pushed someone off a cliff?
What's your husband's name?
Hello?
Ma'am, could I have your name
and your husband's name?
PAIK UI-YONG AND PAIK SA-EON
DNA NOT MATCHED
I wonder what his real name is.
What do you think his real name was,
and how did he end up living
as Paik Sa-eon?
When I first met Paik Sa-eon,
he was 15 years old.
I had never seen him before that.
Yes.
That was strange to me.
Paik Ui-yong had a son
who was two years older than I was.
He was living next door,
but I'd never seen him.
I think I understand now.
I see why his parents
treated him like a stranger.
There was no affection at all.
Maybe there's a biological son?
If the current Paik Sa-eon
became their son at the age of 15,
then who was Paik Sa-eon before that?
And why did they hide him?
EPISODE 9
- Why are you here at this hour?
- Did you come alone?
Where's Sa-eon?
Report it for me.
Sa-eon hasn't come home,
and I can't reach him.
How are you talking?
Mr. Min.
Chairman Paik
was known for doting on his grandson.
So, why did he keep his beloved grandson
hidden until he was 15?
There was a reason
his biological grandson
couldn't be shown to the world.
Is that why he presented
a flawless fake grandson?
Fake?
I…
have lived as Paik Sa-eon's wife
for three years,
and I only found out now.
That he's not your biological son.
Where do you get off saying that?
You must be mistaken.
You're not Sa-eon's real wife
but the stand-in.
Yeah, you're right.
Sa-eon's just a stand-in too.
Honey.
That's true, but he's different.
Isn't he
important and necessary to you both?
So find out right now
what happened to him.
Yes, I understand.
There have been no reports filed
under the spokesperson's name as of now.
Did you hear that?
Go home.
Fine.
I admit that Sa-eon
is very important and necessary to us.
So we won't just sit idly by, will we?
When did she start talking?
Did you know?
Excuse me.
How much does the spokesperson know
about the person making the threats?
What do you mean, "how much"?
Everything he told the police.
So nothing more about the heterochromia?
What…
should he know?
When Mr. Paik was young,
he had eye surgery.
It's a little-known fact.
Since then,
his eyes were no longer different colors.
What about you, Sis? Do you know him well?
Listen carefully.
In this world,
the person who knows Paik Sa-eon
the best is me.
When Paik Sa-eon first came to this house,
he was like a scared stray cat.
I've never seen him
smile comfortably in this house.
I've always
felt sorry for him.
SANG-WOO
Hello?
J&P SEOUL HOSPITAL
Where is he? Is he in surgery?
Yes, it's been two hours.
Was he hurt badly? Where and how bad…
Hee-joo, calm down.
- Take a seat.
- No, I…
What is this? What in the world happened?
JUAN FISHING
Mr. Jeong Jin-seok?
I came to ask you something.
Are you a cop?
My name's Ji Sang-woo.
I'm doing a show and covering
the missing children case
from Sinil Childcare Center.
NEWSCASTER NA YOU-RI
Hello?
I heard from one of the writers
that you found where Jeong Jin-seok lives.
Did you meet him?
I did, but it was pointless.
As soon as I mentioned the villa,
he got scared.
As if he feared the consequences.
And?
Hello?
Sang-woo?
JUAN FISHING
Mr. Paik Sa-eon?
Mr. Jeong Jin-seok?
Mr. Jeong!
This is about how the fire started,
who set it, and why Paik Sa-eon was there.
Also, your relationship with Paik Sa-eon.
I don't know any of that.
But…
I couldn't ignore the non-stop ringing
of his phone.
Thank you.
And…
I'm sorry, Sang-woo.
I've kept so many things from you.
- Is it over?
- Yeah.
For now, let's wait and see
until he wakes up.
All right, then.
It must've hurt.
It must've been scary.
You must've been lonely.
When I was hurt, scared, and lonely,
you watched over me…
and ran to me.
But that girl
had no one
to rely on, anywhere.
I wanted to help her escape.
Hoping that she could
leave that house and live freely.
And if you can, tell Hee-joo for me.
Tell her not to worry.
Tell her I'll be right there!
Tell me
how to hate you.
Tell me how to not love you.
It's my turn now.
It's my turn to protect you.
So, please wake up. Please.
DR. JI SANG-WOO
Thanks for waiting!
Eat up.
So, Crime Report. Right?
Did you receive any tip-off
about the Sinil Childcare Center?
Why are you interested in that?
What?
I'm already upset enough as it is.
Why treat me on a day
when I have no appetite, of all days?
Eat.
- Why?
- Try this too.
What is it? Just tell me.
Well…
Do you want to look into it yourself?
Me?
Sure, take your time. Eat up.
Who, what, when, where,
how, and why it happened.
I'll give you the source.
Source?
- What is it?
- Well…
- Twins?
- Come on.
UNEXPLAINED FIRE IN JEONGI-DONG
DID YOU DO THIS?
I WARNED YOU NOT TO ACT ALONE
I CAN'T CLEAN UP ALL YOUR MESS
YOU'RE LUCKY PAIK SA-EON IS ALIVE
Paik Sa-eon?
I had no idea.
How did you know?
THIS IS YOUR LAST WARNING.
DON'T CAUSE TROUBLE, JUST WAIT.
Last warning?
I think you're the one
who'll cause trouble.
Father.
That old man came again?
- Who was the kid with him?
- I told you not to call me that!
Go to bed early here tonight.
And do not come outside.
Got it?
Help…
I told you not to come out.
Go inside.
Help!
Some monsters are made,
but some are simply born.
It was bad luck.
How dare something like that
be born into my family?
At first, it was a goldfish,
and then a cat.
Next, it was children younger than him.
What kept increasing
were the black bags filled with the dead.
But it's okay now.
That bastard ended up
in one of those bags too.
And now,
I'll fill the place of my grandson…
with whomever I please.
Child,
do you know why I didn't give you a name?
It's okay.
Are you okay?
Are you feeling better?
Hee-joo.
Yeah, it's me.
Can you see me?
I'll get the doctor.
I could hear your voice.
"It's okay."
You told me that.
Yeah.
It's really okay now.
I'll go get the doctor.
Hee-joo.
He just woke up.
Is that so?
How are you feeling?
I'm fine.
I doubt that.
This is my father's hospital.
I made sure word wouldn't get out,
so you can relax
and receive proper treatment.
What about
the person who was with me?
Is he alive?
Let me ask this first.
What's your relationship
with Jeong Jin-seok?
He raised me.
His original name's Jeong Sang-hun.
I'd been looking for so long
without knowing that he had changed it.
He raised you?
It's a long story.
Complicated and personal.
Is Hee-joo involved
in this personal matter?
Hee-joo
is my only family and guardian.
It's not an inappropriate relationship.
So don't worry.
If it's not, then why do you hide it?
Why should I expose Hee-joo to the world?
My complicated personal matters
will be revealed soon.
When people start criticizing me,
do you want them to gossip
about Hee-joo too?
Thank you.
I think I've gotten you wrong.
I apologize.
Can I ask you a favor?
What is it?
Please do everything you can
to help him wake up.
He's a key witness
to the Sinil Childcare Center case.
And he provided a crucial tip-off.
A tip-off?
"He's alive."
The real culprit in that case,
the one who's blackmailing me
and sending me death threats.
It's the same person?
I thought he was dead,
but he's alive.
CANDIDATE PAIK UI-YONG'S INTRO
The cameras are ready.
But…
They're asking again
if the spokesperson still can't make it.
Filming starts soon.
What do you think?
I apologize.
Any word from Sa-eon?
No, sir.
Still, there haven't been
any incident reports.
That's good enough.
Did you check what I asked you to?
I have been keeping an eye
on the professor…
Nothing unusual so far.
TEXT MESSAGE
HEE-JOO
Are you still at work?
Will you be late?
You said you'd come early.
I can't reach you. Are you busy?
Why can't I reach you?
It's past 11 p.m. Why aren't you home yet?
And you're not picking up.
Where are you?
PAIK SA-EON
YOU HAVE A NEW VOICEMAIL
You have new messages. First message.
Where are you? Is something wrong?
This has never happened before.
You always let me know
if you're not coming home.
No matter how late,
you always slept at home.
See you at home.
I won't be late.
You said you wouldn't be late.
So, why aren't you home?
I'll check your blood pressure.
Is my guardian outside?
No, no one's outside.
PAIK SA-EON
HEE-JOO
Where did you go?
These crabs were caught
early this morning in Seosan.
My wife's favorite dish is blue crab stew,
so I make it often.
Now,
shall we see how fresh these crabs are?
Okay.
Look at this.
It's still alive.
Look!
See?
Prepping these live crabs
isn't easy, you see.
Honey!
This is what I've done for you
all this time.
Now, you make blue crab stew often
for your wife,
so what do you usually make for your son?
Well… For my son?
Yes, what does the spokesperson like?
He takes after me, so he likes seafood.
When it comes to seafood, he's not picky.
Now, my son couldn't make it today,
so to make up for it,
I invited a special guest.
You can look forward to it.
Welcome.
My daughter-in-law.
BEOMJIN DONGAN POLICE STATION
What are you doing here?
Why did you come in your state?
Why did you come here?
Give me that.
So, why did you lie to me?
I know everything now.
I know you're not Paik Sa-eon.
I even know who the real Paik Sa-eon is.
You're worse than me.
You've deceived me
more doggedly than I did,
and for much longer.
So without knowing anything,
I teamed up with the guy
who tried to ruin you.
I threatened and tormented you.
Who knows what he'll do now?
So I can't just let him be.
- Hee-joo…
- For once!
For once,
I want to protect you.
So that you never suffer…
or get hurt again.
You know what?
You could get hurt and be in danger again
if you stay with me.
But I'm asking you to stay by my side
because I can't let you go.
You still don't get it?
I lived because of you.
I endured because of you.
Hong Hee-joo.
Even if I'm not
the Paik Sa-eon you knew,
does it not matter?
It didn't matter to you either.
Whether I was the Hong Hee-joo
who couldn't speak or could speak,
and even when I was 406,
you knew, but it didn't matter.
I'm happy to finally know the real you.
No.
I'm sorry for realizing it so late.
Did you know?
I did not.
But it seems he and In-a
had been in contact beforehand.
But she is
able to talk and listen now.
I've been curious about this.
Who does Spokesperson Paik take after?
No matter how closely I look at him,
he doesn't resemble either of you.
Come on. What are you talking about?
Back in my prime,
I had big, bright eyes
and a sharp jawline, just like Sa-eon.
- Really?
- Of course.
Then show me some old photos.
Do you have an album?
Don't you want to see
what the spokesperson looked like
as a child?
I bet he was so cute.
- Show us!
- Yeah, show us!
- Show us.
- Yeah, he was cute.
- Excuse me.
- He was cute.
I have a question too.
Since the wedding,
you and the spokesperson
haven't attended
any official events together.
Can I ask you why?
The Paik Sa-eon I knew before the wedding
and the Paik Sa-eon I got to know after…
are two completely different people.
What?
What do you mean by that?
The Paik Sa-eon I knew before the wedding
is this person.
But I later found out
that their son…
Hey, In-a!
This is why daytime drinking is dangerous.
You can't even hold your liquor!
Sir.
A package came for you.
Thank you! Now!
The abalone from Wando is here!
They're fresh and very big!
Open it.
Yes, sir.
- What is that?
- What?
- What is that? That's gross!
- What is that?
Who is it?
It says Dr. Ji Sang-woo.
Sang-woo!
Be careful.
Are you okay?
What? What's that?
What happened?
I got a little hurt.
"A little"?
This isn't a little.
What?
What about there?
What about here?
Well…
- Close your eyes for a second.
- My eyes?
There. Open them.
One eye had camel-like eyelashes.
- Camel?
- Or giraffe?
Is that the only thing you can think of?
I mean, there are other things,
like a peacock.
Sure.
Let's go with peacock.
Wait.
That's not important right now.
This, this, and this.
Well?
Who did this?
It's kind of a long story.
Really?
Then follow me.
Let's go.
It was just a small accident.
There was a fire.
A fire?
That's okay.
- Sorry.
- It didn't splatter much.
Still…
I'd say I was pretty fortunate.
Who started the fire and why?
I'm sorry, but…
I can't tell you yet.
It involves someone's personal life,
and it's not my place to share.
I don't like secrets either.
Sang-woo.
Must you keep…
digging into this case?
The higher-ups are pressuring us
not to air it.
Someone's trying to cover it up.
I never gave consent,
so don't even think about showing my face.
In-a.
What are you doing?
What do you mean?
I came to ask questions
that need to be asked.
Do you need anything?
Stay by my side until I fall asleep.
I'll be right here.
I'm having trouble sleeping.
When I close my eyes,
I have nightmares about fire.
How did you find me earlier?
Give me my phone.
LOCATION SHARING
When did you…
Right after the cliff accident.
I felt anxious.
I want it on my phone too.
I'm anxious too.
Hong Hee-joo.
If…
you can't reach me again
in the future…
or don't know where I am,
don't look for me.
Promise me.
No.
Don't look for me, and just wait.
I'll come find you.
Don't worry.
I know who he is now.
I'll handle it.
What do you think he wants?
Does he want to get back
what was once his? His name?
His place?
No matter what he wants,
what I want is clear,
to leave behind the name Paik Sa-eon…
and start fresh with you.
Let's be happy together.
Go to sleep.
Don't have any bad dreams. Just sleep.
I'll be right here.
JI SANG-WOO
Jeong Jin-seok, I mean…
Jeong Sang-hun is awake.
He'd asked for you the moment he woke up.
You did great.
I'm sorry.
Back then…
I never should've saved him.
Take care of it.
Yes, sir.
I couldn't bring myself to kill…
a child who almost died.
He had lost all his memories.
His mental abilities had weakened.
So I thought it'd be okay
if I quietly looked after him.
But his natural instincts…
remained the same.
Just as you took me in
and raised me as your own,
you couldn't have cast him aside either.
Where are they?
The black bags Paik Jang-ho
asked you to take care of.
I have to find them.
I'll find them…
and expose everything he did.
He's in the hospital?
Yes. It seems he got hurt quite a bit.
But he insists on attending today's event,
so I'm worried.
I wonder what happened this time.
Was he injured badly?
I don't know.
Shouldn't we go see him?
- Where?
- At the hospital.
But would the spokesperson
be happy to see us?
We don't know which hospital.
We do.
- I don't know.
- Again?
Again?
When he says "I don't know,"
we never get what we want to know.
However, don't worry, everyone.
There's a way to find out
which hospital he's in.
But do we have to find out?
I know.
I can hear you.
Here.
Thanks.
The director of Nuri Dream Center told me…
that when we were in college,
you came to volunteer
and were holding a crying baby,
singing a lullaby to calm the baby down.
Good night, my baby
My dear baby
There are beautiful roses
Surrounding you
Good night…
That's right. I think I remember that.
I'm sorry, Sang-woo.
I had no idea.
You're sorry?
I got to hear your voice,
so it's fine.
The spokesperson and I…
Yeah, you don't have to explain.
At first, I was surprised and worried,
but there's one thing…
I'm sure of.
That he's not hiding you
but protecting you.
I face attacks from all sides.
In a way, you could say
I'm the government's official scapegoat.
So I don't want
my wife to be exposed
to indiscriminate attacks like I am.
Yes, she's my weakness.
You're ready to go already?
Yeah.
I'll do it for you.
Do you know how?
How do I do it?
Here.
Grab both ends of the tie.
Cross them over.
Next, loop it here and pull it through.
Is that good?
Great job.
Are you prepared for today's event?
Of course.
But will you really be okay?
I'll be fine.
So you come with the rest of the team.
And be careful.
Okay?
Don't worry about me.
You be careful too.
Okay.
CHIEF KANG YOUNG-WOO
Yes, Mr. Kang.
We're here.
Where?
Didn't you say you'd have it delivered?
No way! We came in person.
Sorry about that.
We've brought your commemorative speech
and your morning coffee.
What?
- The paper.
- Here you go.
And my coffee?
Are you feeling okay?
Yes, I'm fine. I'll see you all later.
Can we come in--
I was just about to go through
the discharge process.
You should all go.
Okay, we'll see you at the event then.
Sir, I'm leading the event today,
so I want to rehearse it with you
before I go.
Once you're done with the process,
we can do it inside…
- Mr. Kang.
- Yes?
Do we still need…
to rehearse it together?
No. Of course not.
You and I are like a well-oiled machine.
We're perfectly in sync, the best team.
- Mr. Park?
- Yes?
Come see me.
ENVIRONMENTAL CLIMATE DAY
Let's sit here.
- Hello.
- How pretty.
2024 ENVIRONMENTAL CLIMATE DAY
Are you ready, Ms. Hong Hee-joo?
Yes, Mr. Paik.
You look a bit nervous.
I'm confident I can do well.
I've been dreaming of this moment
for so long.
I'm looking forward to it too.
The moment I'll stand side by side
with Interpreter Hong Hee-joo.
Greetings,
esteemed citizens and honored guests.
I am Paik Sa-eon,
the Presidential spokesperson.
SPOKESPERSON SPEECH
Interpreter Hong Hee-joo is so impressive.
Of course, I knew it.
She's the best at our center.
So good!
…we often heard that
we were living in an era of extreme
climate change.
I'm so proud. My daughter.
My son-in-law.
…an era of climate "crisis,"
not just "change."
I sincerely hope that this event
will foster constructive discussions
aimed at finding solutions
to climate issues
and presenting new visions.
I believe that
if we all continue our efforts,
a better future will come.
Thank you.
- Hello?
- Are you busy?
Yeah, I'm busy.
You punk.
That Sinil Childcare Center case.
I went through everything
and found nothing.
Does that make sense?
Is that why you called?
By the way,
did you know there were twins
among the missing kids?
- Twins?
- Yeah.
So the family
of the missing person could be out there.
I mean, the other twin.
So what?
One reason this case is difficult
is that the kids are orphans,
and there are no victim families.
But if we find the twin…
We might get a testimony or statement?
That's right.
Hey, if anything comes up,
I get the exclusive interview.
Got it?
Yedong-myeon, Sinjeok Mountain.
You'll find them there.
I always thought
that someday the day would come
when I'd have to atone for my sins.
The spokesperson asked me
to take you back to the office.
Great work today.
HBC JANG HYEOK-JIN
Hello?
It's me.
The police gave me access, so I checked
the missing person's family DNA database.
I looked for "twins" from Sinil Childcare
Center in Hajeong, Gyeonggi-do in 2000.
And?
The younger twin's information
came through.
I'll send it to you.
Check it yourself.
HBC JANG HYEOK-JIN
PERSONAL RECORDS
SPOKESPERSON PAIK SA-EON
NAME: PARK DO-JAE
NAME BEFORE ADOPTION: YUN MIN-SEONG
HEE-JOO
The person you're calling is unavailable.
You'll be directed to voicemail.
Additional fees may apply after the beep.
WHEN THE PHONE RINGS
Hee-joo!
Your name? Your place?
Do you want them back?
Will you give me Hong Hee-joo too?
Where did it all go wrong?
Do-jae!
Hurry and come to the memorial service.
I've got a bad feeling.
Paik Sa-eon.
I'm really going to kill her.
- Your wife.
- Don't come.
For once,
I want to protect you.
I love you.
Subtitle translation by: Sue Mounce