Officail Website : kissasia.id  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
♪ Hold me tight,
let the darkness drown me ♪
♪ Even one second of truth is enough
to lose myself in it ♪
♪ Hold me tight,
let the darkness drown me ♪
♪ Even one second of truth is enough
to lose myself in it ♪
♪ Whether you're light or a lie,
I can't pull myself away ♪
♪ In this game,
truth or lie no longer matters ♪
[Queen of Darkness]
[Episode 9]
Yao.
Well, looks like
your luck's finally paid off.
Unlike someone
who can't even
give birth after all these years.
What a joke.
Auntie, please don't say that.
An Ning.
It's just that the timing hasn't come yet.
No need to rush.
Some people wait twenty or thirty years
to conceive.
It's common.
Sis, you're elegant and gracious.
You wouldn't pick on me out of jealousy,
would you?
You've tied your whole life to
your kid and your man.
That's your business.
Don't bother me with
your schemes of jealousy
and using a child to rise in status.
We'll be living under the same roof
from now on,
so if you can't stand me,
you can scold or punish me
however you like.
But saying things in that sarcastic tone,
it just hurts the bond between us.
Besides, I'm doing this for your sake.
With this child coming,
things will actually get easier for you.
Isn't that right?
Look at our Yao,
really.
Yao, you've really gone out of your way.
I'm so touched.
To have such a
good mother-in-law
and a good man
like Ti Cha.
Hope you enjoy your life
in this wealthy family.
So now you realize I'm a good man?
This great fortune was handed to you.
But you wasted it, didn't you?
Now that Yao's carrying my child.
You,
just live with your regret.
Ever since I got pregnant,
my feet have been swelling now and then.
I can barely walk.
- It's okay.
- Yao.
Steward, go get a basin of hot water.
A soak
will ease them.
Maybe sis could wash them for me?
Don't take it the wrong way.
I'm only trying to help.
After all, my status is special.
The servants might gossip.
This will show our deep sisterly bond.
Then the servants won't dare to gossip
or stir up trouble.
For the kid's sake,
I'll let you keep some dignity.
But don't push your luck.
I...
This... this...
What's wrong?
Don't get upset, it's bad for the baby.
An Ning.
You did that on purpose, didn't you?
You can't have a child
and now you're resentful.
Making her angry,
harming my grandchild.
Well, An Ning.
Yao is so understanding,
- always yielding to you.
- I'm fine.
What's the big deal washing her feet?
Listen,
don't take my kindness for granted!
How about I wash it for you, sis?
To show my sincere intentions.
Are you okay?
Think about the baby you're carrying.
You should do more good deeds.
Wait...
- She...
- I...
Sis, are you scalded?
I swear, I didn't mean it.
Take care of yourself and the baby.
If you lose the baby,
you'll really have nothing left.
The doctor said
the baby should hear
the father's voice more often.
This helps build a stronger bond.
Sis, how about letting me
have the master bedroom?
And let those servants
take care of me for a while too.
Live there if you want.
I don't care.
I didn't want to share a room
with Ti Cha anyway.
If I weren't trying to figure out my identity,
I'd have moved out long ago.
Why are you here?
Let me apply it.
No need.
I can do it myself.
You're so careless.
You didn't even think to block it.
I think
you're starting to care about me a little.
You're overthinking.
I'm a married woman.
How could I have improper thoughts?
It's just that
you got hurt because of me,
and I'd feel bad if I didn't do something.
Really?
It's hard to tell if
what you're saying now is real or fake.
But eyes never lie.
I have things to do.
I'm leaving.
It's okay.
I already know the answer.
What I want to tell you is
since you've lost your memory,
don't rush to define anything.
Including your identity.
Just live freely and honestly.
In my eyes,
you're a brand-new version of yourself.
Without any prefixes.
♪ Eyes still hide the night
before the dawn ♪
I get it now.
Thank you.
But
there's something more important
I need to do.
♪ Even if my palms burn, I won't give in ♪
Yao.
After I went back, I thought it over.
We're good sisters.
Why should we keep hurting each other?
Mother-in-law said
we've known each other for years,
and I know exactly what you like.
From now on, I'll take full care of you.
My dear sister.
Relax.
I will care for you
in the world's most authoritative
and most standardized way.
[Guide to A Healthy Pregnancy]
Pregnant women should
eat small meals often.
So I've arranged eight meals a day.
It's good for you and the baby.
Make sure you finish everything, okay?
Don't choke on it.
The outside environment can be messy.
If you get even a small bump,
that'd be bad.
And you haven't hit
your workout target today.
Start with a thousand jumps.
Late-night yoga
is really good for the baby's health.
Stop.
Hold it for five minutes.
Honey.
An Ning's been driving me crazy lately.
Since she's just an eyesore
in the house anyway,
and might
even harm our baby,
why don't you just divorce her?
Wouldn't it be great
if we could be together openly?
Sweetheart.
Just be patient.
She
still holds the group's shares.
My dad would never agree to it.
You're two months pregnant now.
But I was
still overseas, remember?
This
is just an estimate.
Who remembers the exact time?
Let's drop this topic.
It's been so long since we met.
Did you miss me at all?
You've taken a lot of anger
from An Ning, huh?
How about
just thinking of me as her,
and get
that anger off your chest.
Do you like what I'm wearing today?
Wait…
You're wearing An Ning's clothes?
That's so bold.
Fang...
Now, I am.
An Ning.
What's with that pride of yours?
In the end,
you still became my plaything!
Yeah.
And a useless one at that.
Can't even have a child.
Can't keep a man either.
What is this?
Role-playing?
Or just self-deception?
- Hey, don't...
- Keep going.
Officail Website : dramacool.club  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Go on.
Maybe I'll find a use for this someday.
Let more people see
the so-called love of a mistress.
No, wait.
You...
You should be the one feeling ashamed.
Being humiliated like that by me.
Shamelessness is invincible.
But when it comes to dealing with you,
I've got plenty of ways.
You two.
Mom.
What are you doing?
Get down here.
- Mom.
- You crazy kid!
She's pregnant, you know.
And you still dare to mess around?
And you.
Behave yourself.
Don't egg him on.
You little brat!
- You brat!
- Mom, don't hit me.
- I'll hit you.
- I'm sorry, Mom!
- You hit her?
- You
I'll hit you!
Hit her instead!
No, I'll hit you!
- Hit her, not me!
- I'm hitting you!
- She stirred things up.
- You brat.
That troublemaker An Ning.
She keeps getting in my way.
I thought I could use
this pregnancy to rise up.
Now I can't even share a room.
Someone, help!
Help!
An Ning pushed her mother‑in‑law down!
Mom, mom.
Mom.
- You okay?
- What happened, mom?
Mom.
- You alright?
- Mom.
Even if you don't get along with her,
you can't put her life in danger.
You've already lost your own parents,
and now you'd raise a hand
against your in‑law?
If such a jinx stays in this family,
who knows
what else might happen next.
Every word out of your mouth is a lie.
Such a low-level frame-up.
Only a fool would believe it.
I swear on the child I carry.
I saw you push your mother-in-law
down the stairs.
Fang Yao's words aren't baseless.
You've never
shown your mother-in-law respect.
Always giving sarcastic looks,
or talking back whenever she speaks.
Do you wish for her to die sooner?
Now I finally see it clearly.
You don't care about right or wrong.
You just want an excuse to trouble me.
You scoundrel!
No manners, no upbringing.
You hurt someone,
and still act this defiant?
Even your late father
would feel ashamed to
have a daughter like you!
The ashamed one should be you!
Doing anything
for my shares.
Like father, like son.
Had both parents,
and still ended up with
a scumbag like Ti Cha!
You...
Fine.
You won't yield until you see the coffin.
If you can't prove your innocence,
I'll carry out the family punishment.
Bring it.
I have
the evidence here.
My stomach hurts so much.
Anything else you want to say?
Without this video,
I'd be the one taking the blame.
Th... this video is edited.
You all teamed up to frame me.
Mom.
Please, take it slow.
I'm fine now.
The baby comes first.
Alright, forget it.
Good thing you're okay.
I'm just clumsy from pregnancy,
so I slipped and knocked into you.
I swear, I didn't mean to do it.
Officail Website : dramacool.club  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
From now on,
I'll bear more heirs
for the Song family as compensation.
Alright.
So feudal-minded you don't even
care about your own life.
You truly deserve all this suffering.
How come the missing cufflink
from father-in-law's right sleeve
fell out of my clothes?
Fang Yao wore this dress before.
Could it be that
Fang Yao and my father-in-law.
I was so scared today.
You'd better do something
to help me calm down.
My special aphrodisiac oil.
While my mom's not home,
let's enjoy ourselves, you little minx.
♪ Mist coils around the sleeping forest ♪
♪ Memories scattered
through cracks of darkness ♪
♪ How to escape this real-feeling dream ♪
♪ Lies reflect in water's gleam ♪
♪ Traces of existence
can never be erased ♪
♪ How to find the self I can't reclaim ♪
♪ Fly away, hear she says ♪
♪ She'll fly out from
thorns of woven lies ♪
♪ Pierce the fog,
shatter this dream tonight ♪
♪ Burn like fire ♪
♪ Just burn like fire ♪
♪ The maze in the abyss starts to clear ♪
♪ Yet night keep on whispering ♪
♪ Surrender to fate,
no clear direction ahead ♪
♪ She will rise as the dawn
that breaks the darkness ♪
♪ Never slowing down,
for tomorrow cannot be stopped ♪
♪ Surrender to love and find the way ♪
♪ Even if fate tries to forget her ♪
♪ Never despair,
for the heart burns with endless light ♪
♪ Waiting for dawn ♪
[Copyright of this short drama
belongs to]
[Shanghai Chuqi Weishi
Culture Media Co., Ltd.]
[and Youku Information Technology (Beijing)
[Co., Ltd.]
[Youku Information Technology (Beijing)
[holds exclusive global online
and broadcast rights]