( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
You must be cold.
Ms. Seo Mi-rae, your one-month free trial
of Boyfriend on Demand has ended.
No.
No!
Don't go.
No. You can't!
Eun-ho…
Don't let it end like this!
No!
SERVICE PERIOD EXPIRED
Eun-ho!
TRIAL ENDED
Eun-ho…
Evil bastards.
Ms. Seo Mi-rae, please give a star rating
for your second date, Seo Eun-ho.
HOW WAS YOUR DATE WITH SEO EUN-HO
IN &lt;SPRING, AND YOU&gt;?
THANK YOU FOR PARTICIPATING
No!
EPISODE 4
NO RISK, HIGH RETURN
ONE MONTH LATER
The short-lived dream came to an end,
and I returned to my life.
Awesome. TMTK and PlanC
are crushing it right now.
Just as Yun Song said, her readers indeed
loved to hate-read out of habit,
and The Man to Know did not fall easily.
A long-running webtoon like TMTK is…
But, of course,
I must never let my guard down.
The next agenda is… Yes, the contest.
It's that season again.
This time, I didn't assign the genres
based on teams.
I've personally allocated each of you.
So, first up, fantasy.
Choi Dong-min. Kim Seon-jeong.
You two are on it.
-Okay.
As for romantasy,
Seo Mi-rae and
Park Kyeong-nam. Congrats.
Next, we have action.
I let my guard down.
Why was it you and not me?
-Cheers!
I don't know either.
Does he hate you or something?
He's put you with Yun Song
and the nastiest genre.
I'm asking why I wasn't picked.
It's the most important genre.
He handed it to those in charge of
the hottest webtoons right now.
It's only natural.
Just have some of this.
Good on you for snagging us seats
far from the director.
I had to camp out to get this table.
Here.
Hey, why have you been so down lately?
Me?
-Have I?
-Yeah.
I noticed that too.
Even at lunchtime, you seemed kind of
wistful, I guess?
Maybe she's just lonely.
It's almost the end of the year.
Already?
I've got a friend who's totally awesome.
Want me to set you up?
If you start meeting up now,
you'll be dating by Christmas for sure.
Yeah, set her up.
-A blind date?
-He's younger than you.
I have a picture of him.
I'm good.
Why not? You should accept these things
when you can.
Well, I think I'm good.
-Here it is!
-Let me see.
Isn't he a catch?
-Hey, he's so fine!
-Right?
But
you're already seeing someone.
Who is?
Ms. Seo.
-Huh?
-What?
-Nah!
Wait, what are you talking about?
You told me you had a date last time,
so I thought you had a boyfriend.
Please, that was ages ago.
It was just a date, nothing serious.
I mean, I got introduced to a guy
a while back.
It was really brief.
I see. I must have misunderstood.
Ms. Seo, you wound me.
-Huh?
-Me too.
I knew you had clear boundaries,
but this one quite stings.
No, I never mentioned it
because it really was nothing.
She doesn't have to tell us
every little detail about her dates.
Still…
Anyway, does that mean
you're not seeing anyone right now?
I'm not.
How about that blind date? Go, go?
-Go, go.
No, I'm good.
That's it. Don't set her up.
I get it.
She might not be into younger guys.
Younger guys are my thing, you know.
Would you like to take it?
Well, you can show me that picture again.
Sure.
Where does he live?
He lives in Seoul.
I knew it. I live in Seoul too.
-Isn't it great?
-It is.
I've always preferred Seoul guys.
They live nearby and all.
Why, that little…
Man, aren't you cold?
Hey, let's go!
Thank you for the meal!
See you all tomorrow!
I've got to run.
Hey, I'm buying. How about round two?
-Round two, it is.
-Where…
-Where are you going?
-Good night.
Guys?
-I'll be going, then.
-All right.
Have a good night!
-Where are you headed?
-What?
Oh, I'm struggling to get a cab.
Same. I'm sure we'll catch one on the way.
Did
what I said earlier bother you?
Sorry?
You know, how I brought up
your private life in front of everyone.
It's fine. It was just a misunderstanding.
Sorry about that.
I'm a bit slow on the uptake.
You just realized that?
I see.
I look forward to
judging the submissions with you.
Did you know we would be teamed up?
No, I didn't.
If you want to change partners,
we can talk to the director together.
-You hate it that much?
-Huh?
Having to judge with me.
No, it's not like that.
Then… let's do it together.
I see taxis.
Take the first one.
Are you sure?
What do you mean?
Go ahead.
Okay, then. Have a nice weekend.
Right. You too.
Cold!
Hi. Yongsan, please.
I don't go there.
What?
This is an Incheon taxi.
You should've looked before getting in.
Sorry.
INCHEON
Are you kidding me?
You could've told me!
"I look forward to working with you"?
Could've fooled me.
1: THE MAN TO KNOW
2: PlanC
Always on our tail.
It's making me nervous.
Here to cleanse my eyes
of the rotten TMTK.
TMTK beat this? The system's rigged.
Hwany is a god. PlanC is god-tier!
JI-YEON
Hey. What's up? It's late.
Why haven't you been replying
in the group chat?
I must've missed it. What is it?
-You know it's tomorrow, right?
-Huh?
An Da-yeong's housewarming party.
Right.
I knew this would happen.
Don't forget.
See you tomorrow.
What should I buy?
-Over there.
-Look at this.
Oh my God!
-Enjoy your time.
-Thank you.
-Excuse me.
Is an idol coming here?
No, this is the line
for the Boyfriend on Demand pop-up store.
BOYFRIEND ON DEMAND
ENTRY NUMBER 454
Right this way!
-Let me show you.
-Would you like to try it on?
Ms. Seo?
-Hello.
-Hi there.
How nice of you to come.
I could have reserved you a spot.
No, I just happened to be passing by.
Is that so?
Yes. This is quite a turnout.
Yes. Isn't it amazing?
We should have the highest sales
of any pop-up here this year.
Congratulations, Mr. Min.
All thanks to your hard work
reviewing our product.
Are you enjoying it?
-Enjoying what?
-Boyfriend on Demand.
Well…
I actually haven't been playing.
I stopped playing back then.
Is that right?
You sounded very satisfied in your review.
We even gave you the device.
I was sure you'd subscribe
once it hit the market.
I appreciate the gift,
but I've just been busy with life.
Still, doesn't Boyfriend on Demand
blow real life out of the water?
I'm not sure.
I'd say real life is still better.
How heartless of you.
You can take a look while you're here.
I'll show you around.
Oh, I can't.
I'm here for some last-minute shopping,
so I should go.
I'll see you around, then.
-Thank you.
-Good luck!
That was unexpected.
Hey, what's up?
You didn't forget, did you?
Of course not. I'm not a goldfish.
I'm out buying a gift right now.
That's good to hear.
I need to tell you something.
-You do?
-Promise me you won't get mad.
What is it?
Someone else will be joining us
at Da-yeong's place today.
Who?
Just some guy Da-yeong knows.
We're setting you up.
Hello?
Come on, say something!
We didn't tell you, and that's on us.
We were gonna keep it secret
and pretend it was all organic,
but then we got super worried
that you might show up in sweats.
Hello?
Did I screw up again? Are you mad?
No.
Huh?
Well done.
Well done?
Yeah. See you later.
Okay.
What's with her?
-Is she running late?
-Don't know!
Seriously?
She's always late.
She should be here soon.
Okay.
Hey, what…
Mi-rae, you're here…
Sorry I'm late.
Hey, that outfit…
Hey, this one looks decent.
Am I wearing this a bit late?
No. It's meant to be a winter outfit.
Come in.
-Shall we have a drink?
-All right.
-Cheers!
Thanks for coming.
-Totally.
-Of course we came.
-Have some of this.
-Thank you.
Is it good?
-Delicious. So good.
-It's good.
Here.
Thank you.
-A guy with manners.
-Your glass is empty.
Thank you.
-Cheers, everyone?
-Sure.
Cheers!
APT!
Seventh floor!
One. Two. Three. Four. Five. Six. Seven!
Down the hatch it goes!
Bunny!
-Bunny!
-Carrot!
Carrot…
I'll drink that.
So sweet!
Seo Mi-rae won again.
You two are so good.
I want my boyfriend here now.
Hey, you don't mean…
Hey!
-Are you okay? Where are the napkins?
-Are you okay?
Good thing you didn't get drenched.
Thank you.
This is going well.
Happy, Mi-rae?
Cheers.
Let's drink, guys.
-Cheers!
I had a great time today.
I'm quite an introvert,
but you made me feel comfortable,
so I enjoyed it a lot too.
Really? That's nice to hear.
Da-yeong said
a lot of great things about you.
Now that I've met you,
you do seem like a really nice person.
And you're cute.
What did you think?
Sorry?
Of me.
I also had a good time.
That's good. Does that mean
we can see each other again?
Yes, I guess so.
You live near Yongsan,
so that's about two hours away
from my place.
You're busy on weekdays, aren't you?
I'm afraid so.
Would you like to meet up next weekend?
Lunch on Saturday?
I can also do dinner on Friday.
I'll check my schedule.
Can you check now?
I'd really like to set up a date.
I'll check later once I get home.
Mi-rae.
Do you not like me?
What?
Please be honest with me now
instead of turning me down tomorrow.
It's nothing like that.
We only just met today and--
Come on, we're not children.
You can just be honest with me.
Excuse me.
What exactly are you telling me
to be honest about?
Did I upset you?
Lately, I've met a lot of people
who were just testing the waters.
I must've been on edge. I'm sorry.
I know you're not one to test the waters…
You keep saying "testing the waters,"
but everyone has their own pace, you know.
Right.
I had fun today, and I'm sorry,
but I can go alone from here.
But it's so late--
I'll be fine.
Get home safe, Min-gyu.
What that guy said may have been right.
My pace wasn't the issue.
I just wasn't ready
to go out with someone.
But I just had to jump into a blind date.
I must have been crazy.
What was I thinking?
Excuse me.
Got you.
REQUESTING A DRIVER WITHIN 8 MINUTES
NO AVAILABLE TAXIS NEARBY
I'm sorry.
What the heck?
No way.
Mi-rae.
Eun-ho.
Seo Eun-ho!
Eun-ho!
It's been so long since we last met.
How have you been?
Would you be my girlfriend?
See you in Boyfriend on Demand.
"Basic."
"500,000 won a month."
500,000?
500,000?!
You're out of your damn mind!
How dare you exploit loneliness
for profit!
What a bunch of scumbags!
Forget it. Not buying.
Hang on.
When dating in real life, did you spend
less than 500,000 won a month?
No.
Dinners, gifts,
occasional trips, and clothes…
I'd spend well over 500,000 won.
No.
Could you ever meet someone
better than Seo Eun-ho in real life?
No.
Does Boyfriend on Demand involve any risks
beyond the monthly fee?
No.
Is Boyfriend on Demand
a hindrance to my career?
No.
Does Boyfriend on Demand make me happier?
Then is there a reason for me
not to use Boyfriend on Demand?
PAYMENT COMPLETE
Personalization process complete.
Place the ring on your head
and assume a comfortable position.
When you press the button,
the ring will light up
and begin connecting.
Am I in a hotel?
Who…
You scared me!
You're here? Long time no see.
So you remember me.
You weren't reset?
Do you take me for an idiot?
Where are we anyway?
Where are all the posters?
This is your house.
What?
Your house.
You'll be living here from now on
in Boyfriend on Demand.
It's a gift for your regular subscription.
Take your time and look around.
Oh my God!
That dress…
Did Choi Si-woo get you that?
Yes.
How did it end up here?
The gifts you received will remain,
and as for the rest,
they get updated with brand-new items
once every month.
Why are you so nice to me?
That's what our subscribers deserve.
You must go through a lot in real life.
I want you to be nothing but happy here.
Let me just calm down for a bit.
Let me know when you're done.
I'll show you the view.
The view?
Now you can date your boyfriend
in this house.
In here?
Why else would the house be so big?
OPERATION 0125
HEART-POUNDING ACTION ROMANCE
LOVE IN THE SKY
You've seen everything.
It's time for you to go on a date.
Wait. I have something to say.
What is it?
It's about me and Seo Eun-ho.
Things ended abruptly,
you know, at a really crucial moment.
Which is why…
I'd like to meet Seo Eun-ho again.
Picking up from that scene.
But you can't.
What? Why not?
If you want to go straight
for the guy you want,
you need to get on the premium plan,
not the basic plan.
Premium?
"Basic. 500,000 won a month."
"Premium."
One million?
Hello? That's ridiculous.
You're kidding, right?
In the basic plan, you can only date
those I match you with.
Then
does that mean
I can't meet Seo Eun-ho right now?
No.
No way.
What are you waiting for?
Go get your money's worth, girl.
Don't play it safe.
My money's worth?
What's the issue when there are 898 men
besides Seo Eun-ho and Choi Si-woo?
In here, you can bounce
between ten guys in a single day,
and no one will judge you.
Even if you got rejected ten times,
no one would mock you.
So live it up a little, okay?
She's right.
Here, I'm not expected
to be loyal to a boyfriend.
There are no talking stage rules,
and no one laughs at me
for getting rejected.
Enjoy your trip.
What?
Am I a flight attendant?
That's heavy.
That high?
Why couldn't they make me taller?
So it's a foreigner this time.
Oh my.
Just like that, without any warning?
I'm working right now, so--
It's a gun!
What's a gun doing on a plane?
What the heck?
This is what I get for paying up?
Damn it. I should get out of here.
Oh God!
You're okay now.
That was an incident
involving a terrorist group.
BAE HYEON-WOO
NIS
Congratulations, Ms. Seo Mi-rae,
on meeting your third date!
The production value
of the paid version is just…
The NIS, really?
Would you mind
calming the passengers down first?
What?
Right.
-Thank you for bearing with us.
-Excuse me.
-Are you okay?
-My head is a bit--
-It's a gun!
-Gun!
Hold on tight!
Why are you doing this to me?
Are you okay?
What was that?
I'm so scared right now.
I can't even go on the pirate ship ride.
I don't think this one's right for me.
Well, goodbye.
Doctor!
Come on!
The patient's vitals are dropping!
What?
INTERN SEO MI-RAE
-Scalpel?
-What?
Hey!
Get a grip, will you?
Move.
Did you check his rhythm?
Prepare to defibrillate. Gel.
The gel!
200 joules.
200 joules!
What? Is this a touch screen?
On the side!
Below!
One, two, three, shock.
-Can you hear me, sir?
-Yes.
Thank you so much.
Come with me.
You nearly killed him. You know that?
Answer me!
Goodness. What a total hothead.
Seo Mi-rae.
Yes?
Why won't you ever
give me an answer?
It's been over a week now.
Are you trying to leave me hanging?
I'm not sure I follow…
You're gonna pretend it didn't happen?
I'd love that!
Did you see that?
If you don't remember,
let me remind you.
I…
like you.
A fiery senior's secret crush.
It's a classic.
Would you…
give me a chance now?
You're killing me.
I think I get it now.
Why Ji-yeon keeps
putting herself out there.
The person I'd like to go
to Paradise with is
Seo Mi-rae!
Ms. Seo.
Your argument leaned too much on emotion.
The same could be said of you.
You tend to be too aloof.
Court demands a cool head.
But…
no need to be aloof right now.
Are you busy tonight?
In here, love is above the law…
What's this?
"Diyu"?
Stop.
Who goes there?
I'm a sworn enemy of this family.
Hand that over,
and I'll spare your life.
Stop right there!
If you come any closer…
…and you can even fall in love
with a sworn enemy.
BOYFRIEND ON DEMAND
REVIEW SUBMISSION
Unni, look over here!
Are you okay?
Yes.
I literally gulped down the dates
that Boyfriend on Demand spoon-fed me.
It was like I had been parched
all this time.
But why bother meeting men
in a virtual reality, you ask?
Well, there's no denying that there are
attractive men in the real world.
But Boyfriend on Demand
even lets me meet Jay Park.
WOULD YOU ACCEPT A SECRET DATE
WITH JAY PARK?
You look pretty today.
SPECIAL DATE
A SECRET RELATIONSHIP WITH JAY PARK
How can you not get a second date?
I don't know. It's so annoying.
I had a good feeling
since our date was on my birthday.
And I really liked him.
Show me the texts.
Hey, Mi-rae. Check this out.
This guy wrote, "Happy birthday, ma'am."
How old does he think she is?
He's just a really polite guy.
-He probably won't stay in touch, right?
-No, ma'am.
Try texting him first, like,
"What are you up to?"
"When should we meet up?"
That's absurd.
Hurry up and do it.
She'd never be able to do it herself.
Totally.
Here. I'll do it for you.
What are you doing?
For real? Wait!
Have you really lost it?
Don't send it. Don't!
She actually sent it.
He read it!
Oh no!
Don't hang around in the chat.
Reading messages right away isn't cool.
You're talking like a dating pro
all of a sudden.
Did you get a reply? What did he say?
-No way.
-What the hell?
-He asked her out for this weekend.
-See?
Ask first. If it works, great.
If not, move on.
That's Dating 101. Write it down.
I should take this.
Sure.
Yes, Ms. Yun.
What's gotten into her?
Do you think she's possessed?
Iced Americano, please.
That will be 4,000 won.
Thanks.
I see you're buying just a cup today.
Excuse me?
Last time, you bought another one
to drink on your way home.
Here's your iced latte.
Buying two wasn't necessary today.
Hwany must be late with his file today.
How unusual.
It looks like he's going hard this week.
Is that so?
Still, I doubt we're going to beat TMTK.
I guess it's another late submission
with Ms. Yun tonight.
No.
We are also going hard this week, you see.
Oh, is that right?
Here's your Americano.
I need a straw.
It's about time you sent it. Come on.
I'm heading out first.
Sure. Good night.
Right. Good luck.
What am I going to do?
YUN SONG
UPLOAD COMPLETE
I'm home.
Initiating home mode.
God, I'm wiped out.
Let's see now.
-Is the spelling for real?
-It has to be a joke.
The worst typo ever.
Doesn't Naemo even have an editor?
Choi Si-woo goes out in a blaze of idiocy.
God save him!
"Sorry to brother you,
but I'll be taking this woman."
"Brother"?
What am I looking at?
Are you kidding me?!
BROTHER
Excuse me, sir?
I'm sorry.
So he "brothers" to take her away,
buys her a giant diamond ring,
and proposes?
Have you
completely lost it?
I should have checked more carefully.
This is my fault.
How can I not be "brothered" right now?
I'm dying from embarrassment
because of you, seriously!
-Don't "brother" me. Just move.
-Right.
I need some sugar. Damn it.
Goodbye, sir.
Has anyone got a macaron or something?
God, I'm so freaking embarrassed!
So embarrassing.
Sorry to "brother" you,
but may I pass through?
Oh, sure.
Thank you.
Did he say "brother"?
Why did I act like such a child?
Man, I'm beat.
That hits the spot.
Ms. Yun.
From now on, please send the file
before 7 p.m. without exception.
I'm not asking.
I'm going to die of embarrassment.
For the love of…
Why is she lashing out at me so early?
What's the fuss about?
Sorry to brother you,
but I'll be taking this woman.
What's wrong with it?
-Proof that she lives on IG.
-The man to know doesn't know much.
-How are you an author?
-Airhead.
Take some Korean lessons, please.
See? You can be dumb and loaded.
Don't be so harsh. She can't help it.
Who do you think you all are, King Sejong?
If you don't want to read it,
just don't read it!
Seriously!
BOYFRIEND ON DEMAND
What's this?
Look who it is.
What are you up to? Where are you?
I'm hanging out with Da-yeong.
What? You two met up?
Without telling me about it?
You kept ignoring our messages.
We figured you were busy.
You must be free now,
calling me like this.
Are you mad?
No, I mean…
Don't be. I'm going through a lot.
Where are you? Can I join you guys?
-My boyfriend and Jun-ho will be here.
-Tell her to come.
Want to come? You're welcome to join.
So it's a double date.
Nah, I'll pass.
Okay. Stay in touch.
Yeah.
I want to get away.
Ms. Seo Mi-rae, would you like to go
and meet your new date?
I said I'll pass today.
My subscription's nearly over anyway.
What the…
What is this?
This is driving me crazy.
I said I'll pass.
An office worker?
Nice weather.
Seo Mi-rae.
Is it you?
How…
It's been so long.
Has it been ten years?
He's not a college student anymore.
SPRING, AND YOU
"To be continued"?
So what happened?
What?
I was worried when you disappeared.
Well…
Have you been well?
I knew it was just a ploy
to get me to extend my subscription,
but having seen Seo Eun-ho…
I have.
How about you?
Me too.
…I had to fall for it again.
You've changed a lot, Mi-rae.
Have I?
You too.
It's been ten years, after all.
But you are…
still as pretty as ever.
Welcome…
Oh my God, is there a fire somewhere?
Yes. Fortunately,
we managed to put out the worst of it.
That's good to hear.
There's still a fire that won't go out.
What? Where is it?
It's burning
in my heart for you.
Mi-rae, I've spent my whole life
putting out fires.
But this fire burning for you?
I never
want to put it out.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO MEET
YOUR NEXT BOYFRIEND?
YES
Subtitle translation by: Daham Yoon