I'll have an audition for my new show this
Friday, and I'll have Jib reach out to you.
You've chosen this path already.
After this, you have to be
more committed than this.
What're you doing here?
Can I stay with you for a week?
What's going on? Why did
you show up out of nowhere?
What happened?
I have a problem with my old place
and I can't go back home.
My life is quite busy lately.
I don't think I can let you stay.
Can you ask your other friends? I
They can't let me stay with them either.
I know that you don't want me here.
I really don't want to bother you.
But you're my last friend.
I don't think you should be here, sorry.
You're still mad at me about that?
I shouldn't have thought
of you in that horrible way.
I wanted to apologize to you but
you didn't want to talk to me
so I didn't know how to tell you.
I really am sorry
but can you help me out this time.
I honestly have nowhere to go.
You use the same serum as me, can I use it?
You can use this puffy blanket.
I'm fine with anything.
I don't want to hear you whine.
You don't like the feather one, do you?
How are you?
Well, I mostly
go to school,
go to cram school, do this and that.
Like what?
I'm about to be on a runway.
Wow! Is it good money?
I worked on graphic design as
my side hustle and it paid s... t.
I needed to focus on big volume instead.
Can I ask you one more question?
You know.
Diesel? I see you followed him.
I..
The brand that I will be working with
called DEVI
it is Diesel's mom's brand.
So you're close to him.
He's around our age so I just followed him.
Why did you ask?
Who is Anyone?
So what? Pick one!
Anyone is Dream, my friend from school.
Dream Danupha?
Hey!
I
I'll go to sleep now, I'll turn off the lights.
You're so bold.
Is it true that you fooled
Mhong into kissing you?
Stop asking her that. I Is it true?
And you stole his song? That DM song?
He just launched a new version, so awesome.
Did you hear it? I Did you?
You got nothing better to do?
Why don't you go and sniff some stuff?
You're close with her. I
None of your business.
Get to your classroom.
Dream is a girl who grew up with her mom's
vast collection of history and politics books.
She learned about oppression
in the past well enough
to understand the phase
everyone is equal.
She has started to fight
for it since small society
that power flows in one-way called school.
The more you cut flowers, the more
they bloom, as well as ideologies.
The more she got forbidden, the
more she thought she needed to fight.
Her online followers reached hundreds
of thousands and they're not just numbers,
but they are voices to confirm
that she's not fighting alone.
If we do nothing wrong, why do they need
to silence us? I A teacher chopped off.
This account who attacked the school / my
friend's braid in front of a whole school.
Is Danupha, your best friend, right?
Dream hesitated if
her best friend was really a snake,
or it was all made up in her head.
When trust was destroyed,
no matter what the reason was,
Dream couldn't go back to normal.
Dream's life shouldn't be this tough,
if only she was raised in a house
where everyone was allowed
to share their different
opinions. I Please come in.
Dad?
You know damn well that Mom
is inside, what are you doing?
Your mom is guilty.
What makes you think that she's guilty?
Because she has different
opinion than you have?
Dad, you're a teacher
you teach people to think differently.
You can think differently
but you can't break the laws.
Are you blind?
Or you've been brainwashed?
After that, Dream realized that
if your friends or family who were
supposed to be your safe zone
could betrayed you,
can you really trust
anyone in this world?
Mom!
This bitch?
Mhong should have known better.
Lying bitch! Song thief!
We need to turn off comments for now.
We haven't started it yet.
What did Ms.Duangtawan say about it?
We need to stop the deal.
And you need to take care of your mess.
We could work together
when there's a chance.
Why don't you invite your friend here?
Go on.
Hey! I What?
They want to get to know you.
But I don't know anyone.
I'll introduce you to them.
No, I'm shy. I Come on.
Fine, I'll go.
Mother,
this is Jay, my boyfriend. I Gay!
Gay is fantastic and cute.
I need to go out to smoke.
Are you ditching your
friends to be out here?
Nope. I have a lot of friends inside.
Mother? I Yeah?
I need to see my boyfriend.
What? But we're having fun.
Just a minute. I Fine, hurry back.
Well, well, well... are
you hitting on her? I Nope.
Take a good care of your boy.
Sure, I will. I He looks so exhausted.
Sure thing.
I need to see Ly inside.
Fine, I'll be right there. I See you.
What's wrong?
You don't like that Ly called you gay?
She said nonsense things all the time.
Don't mind her.
Maybe I just didn't get used to it yet.
Stop thinking that. We're all peers here.
They're your friends, not mine.
But…
When…
When you're inside,
you acted so differently
than when you were with me.
But you looked happier
like you can be yourself.
So mayber I didn't want to disturb you.
You look like you have something to say.
Nope, nothing.
Nothing much.
Spill it.
1…2…3... all done.
Thank you, thank you so much.
Thank you, we can finally work together.
My team is a big fan of you.
You look so cute together. I Thanks.
We're gonna do our best for this.
Should we film a TVC tomorrow?
We're always ready.
You guys are so nice,
we'll see you all year long.
I gotta go, bye.
See you later. I Bye.
This way please.
You guys did a great job this month.
There's a gathering at Siam next.
Tang is already there so
keep up your good work, okay?
Okay? I Joe,
Keep it up!
Well done. Good luck,
guys. I See you. Thank you.
What's the matter?
You're worried about Bambi?
Hey,
can you help me with something?
Someone threw rock at my
friend and invaded our house.
I moved out and I'm safe.
Are you okay?
You can tell me.
What is it?
It's nothing.
He is earning money from your missed calls.
Everyone, look!
If she did nothing wrong, why
can't she just sit still? Look?
See? I I know, what's wrong?
Not cool.
See you in game tonight.
See you.
How bad was it?
I
I made out with him.
And he gave me his song.
It's cool.
But I was wrong about this.
I think you were both wrong.
He got to make out with you and
you got his song, it's a win-win situation.
It's up to one's perspective. They
can choose to see from different side.
It's like
what happened to my parents.
Or when we
fought when we were
young something like that.
I saw it from my point of view.
You know that you did wrong,
I didn't even know back then.
I'd be like, who hurt me.
I didn't look from your point of view that
you were also in trouble.
I'm sorry.
I
I have
something to tell you.
Hello?
Can you come outside?
Is he a star?
I used to.. I Right.
Work on graphic. I Yeah?
I worked on your BL couple. I Cool.
That's right.
I'm straving.
I need to eat something. I
Go find something to eat.
I need to find something
to eat. I Bye, just go.
Watch where you're going. I See you.
Is it okay for you to be here?
Your company didn't mind?
Not at all, they're just worried.
I saw the song that just released.
Full of bulls.
I don't think you should
watch something like this.
I don't know what to do.
I think you should stay put for a while.
Don't say anything much about it.
I experienced
something like this once.
Someone posted me and
my tiring face at the event,
and they said that I disrespected the host.
Eventually, my fans protected me,
they said that I worked too much.
They spoke the truth for me.
That's good.
But it's harder in my case.
Do you know anyone
with a trustworthy account?
They can vouch for you.
What is it?
I think I can think of something.
Can you help me with something?
When Mhong goes live, can
you log into your gaming account
and bring me there to talk to him?
Let's do this.
You made up an excuse of a sick mom?
I can explain.
If I didn't worry about your mom
and went all the way to
see her with a fruit basket,
I wouldn't have known about this,
that you all fooled me. I
It's just a little gathering
it had nothing to do with the
movie. I went to all the events,
but I really couldn't go
this time. I Listen to me,
if you want to benefit from this job,
you can't make any more excuses.
How could you let Namkhang attend the
event alone? You two should be together.
Think of the people you disappointed.
This is not just about your fans.
You ditched on your work.
You had no responsibility.
No matter what your
job is, you can't do that.
Tang, you!
You said that you could control them.
Tang has nothing to do with this.
Namkhang and Tang have nothing
to do with this, it's my mistake.
Can you give me another chance? I Enough.
I must have protected you way too much.
You think you can get away with anything.
People don't get that many chances.
I can't tell you
if you deserve one more chance.
It's up to our clients, and your fans.
They have rights to call it.
Be prepared for consequences.
Where is he?
Found him.
Mhong,
can you text me back?
Why did you do it?
Who's that?
We didn't do anything.
We just made a fun song.
How did you assume that it's about you?
You got something on your back?
That's crazy? I If it's not about
me, can you delete the clip?
My life is a big mess because of your song.
Nice.
Now you know how I feel.
You know how it feels like when your life
is going down the cliff.
Do you get me now?
Are you a child? That's so stupid.
Why did you do that?
Damn it!
There're two? Your voice sound familiar.
Are you Dream?
You two are friends again?
Can I ask you something, Dream?
When you were young,
did your friend really rat you out?
Or you were just delusional?
None of your f... king business. It
got f... king nothing to do with you.
Hey, I asked you nicely.
I'm worried for you that
history would repeat itself.
Why did you say something stupid like this?
I'm here to talk to you nicely.
And I'm talking to you nicely.
Do you have any idea that you
just ruined our happy moment?
Get the hell out of here! I Go!
Get her! I That's right,
get her out of here.
Let's do this.
You son of a bitch! You can't
fight so you chose violence?
Shoot her! Let them know that
this is Mhong Muangthai!
Get her! I Get her good!
You assholes!
You son of a bitch! You're so tough in
game, why don't you shoot me in real life?
MISTER_J / Gunman: Stupid
woke feminist, I'll shoot you for real.
Damn it!
About what Mhong said earlier.
I don't think someone like them
should have a place in this society.
I recorded when they shoot us earlier.
This will create another drama.
But I think people need
to see what they did.
Why did you fold to them easily?
They ruined your life.
This is the proof.
You saw what they just did.
Fine.
I'll expose them.
It has become a hot topic
when #DickHeadMhong made
a song called 'Watch Your Back'
aiming to attack a young woman.
She tried to talk to him in the game
instead, gamers chose
violence and shoot her.
The footage of their attack
was recorded and posted
on social media channels later
by Anyone.
In the end, it seemed like people started
to agree more with Anyone than Mhong.
Mhong's song gained
higher number of dislikes.
From this story, we can see that
people who choose violence
in both real and online worlds
shouldn't have a place in society.
I will talk about this one
time and one time only.
Nowadays, when women
choose to do what they like,
they receive backlash from people.
On the other hand, when
men do what they like,
people praise them.
I just want you to ask yourself
is this the society we want to live in?
Stupid song from a stupid guy,
such a loser. #RealManKeepOnFalling.
An anthem for real men like
Andrew Tate, so disgusting.
They will blame the games, I can't
wait to see the same old excuses.
I admitted that I didn't
think it through for what I did.
I didn't think that it'd turn out like this.
I'd like to ask for another chance
from everyone.
I think we fucking got the clip.
But I just said from my perspective.
I know but I feel like
people who look sadder
seem to be on the right side.
See? Many people are on your side.
Dear members, I don't think it's fair
that Mhongmuangthai
is the only one to blame.
Anyone askes for equality.
But when there're problems,
you always blame the men.
Does it seem right to you?
If you want equality so bad, why
don't you go to war instead of us?
There's no equality since the beginning.
Which one do you prefer, rice or noodles?
I like rice more.
Why's that? Well, I prefer rice too.
I get to chew, I don't like something
soupy. I It's nothing about chewing.
You still have to chew. I That's right.
You think you said the right thing?
What're you doing?
You think you're cool? I So what?
You want a piece of me?
Thank you for helping
me out with the speech.
If you didn't help me, I
would be in so much trouble.
What? I I was just thinking about
us hanging out when we were kids
your mom bought you a
unicorn onesie and I wanted one.
I cried, then you gave me your onesie.
And all you left was your tank top.
I think that onesie looked
ugly so I gave it to you.
You still wan to wear it?
I don't want to lose you again.
I missed you.
I missed you too.
You want some Mookrata?
Where?
Khun Earn.
You don't want to go other places? I think…
Yeah? Khun Earn made all the dishes?
Well, it's good. I've been to
this place since I was a kid.
I want to help them
out. I They still do that?
Your parents aren't
home? I Did you see them?
Why don't we just go to the restaurant?
I need to change one sec.
You don't have to
change, it's just Mookrata.
Can't we go now?
One sec? I How long is it?
This uniform isn't
I don't want to waste
time. I Just a second.
You're done? I Nope.
Hey! I What?
What is it? Dream?
Bambi?
Did you tell someone
else that Anyone is Dream?
Now everyone knows her identity.
Bambi? Can you hear me?
I'm heading to your place.
Did someone call me?
Where are you going?
Do you have anything to say to me?
What's going on?
Anything to say to me?
What's wrong with you?
Did you tell Diesel that I'm Anyone?
Tell me.
You are a f... king monster.
I'm sorry. I Don't touch me.
Listen to me.
He kept on pressuring me to tell him.
If I didn't… I What pressured you?
About you walking a runway?
So you knew?
You knew that I ran away because of him?
You knew? How could you do this to me?
I'm sorry. I We shared
the same bed every night.
I'm sorry. I I was right there.
You could have just told me.
How could you sleep at
night being a monster like this?
I don't want to lose you again.
So I chose not to tell
you. I didn't dare to tell you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, please don't go.
Stay.
I'm really sorry.
When we fought back when we were kids,
did you rat me out to the teachers?
I'm sorry.
Dream.
Sorry.
You've never f... king changed.
Dream.
Dream!
Listen to me. I Dream?
Dream?
Can I talk to you?
Dream? I Diesel? What the hell?
Dream!
Diesel!
If you choose to be benefited from
this job, you can make any excuses.
You can't just ditch on your job,
- no matter what your job is.
- Joe Pastel Bay.
Take care of her.
Where are you going?
Please help her!
My people looked everywhere and.
Job did it.
I know that you're worried about Bambi.
But Tang just got fired.
If you go to the audition,
you could go further than what you said
and you could be as famous as Kimia.