[The Epoch of Miyu]
[Episode 20]
When will it open?
Very soon.
With such good news,
why didn't you inform me?
Mr. Duan.
Ms. Xu.
Mr. Xue.
Chef Li.
Mr. Ji.
This is quite a fresh combination today.
I've long heard that
Chef Li has been working on
the recipe of Yan Du Xian.
Now that I've seen this dish today,
I wonder if I have the luck to taste it.
Yes, yes, yes.
Let me do it.
Taste it now.
Okay.
Be careful. It's hot.
What do you think, Mr. Duan?
It's kind of interesting.
Mr. Ji.
When the restaurant opens,
save a few tables for me.
I'll come support
the Chinese restaurant, too.
Mr. Duan,
if you visit our Chinese restaurant,
how could a few tables be enough?
All our private rooms on the third floor
will be reserved for you.
Okay.
As for the people,
you can have as many as you want.
But when it comes to the reputation,
you have to earn it yourself.
Of course.
Mr. Duan.
Chef Jia is asking...
Um...
Tell him not to worry.
I won't
give the Purong Chinese Restaurant
any chance to turn things around.
When will their restaurant open?
On the 18th of this month.
Let's just make it shut down
on the opening day of their restaurant.
It's almost ready.
I think we can eat it now.
We are having a special meal here
without inviting Mr. Xue.
Will he be unhappy?
Who cares about him?
This is a gathering between us girls.
Here. Be careful. It's hot.
Okay.
It's hot.
Confess and you will be treated leniently.
Did something happen
between you and Mr. Ji?
Nothing happened.
No.
Why do I feel that
since we came back from our hometown,
the vibe between you two
has been different?
Vibe? What vibe?
A guilty vibe.
Tell me the truth.
What is the hidden story between you two
that you can't even tell me?
This sweet potato is so delicious.
Taste it now.
Stop changing the subject.
How about this?
Let me ask another way.
Since you're such a sensitive person,
can't you sense that
Mr. Ji treats you differently
from how he treats others?
So what?
That depends on you.
What do you think of it?
I just got out of a failed marriage.
I can't move on so soon.
Stop limiting yourself, okay?
Nowadays, it's not unusual
to date three people in a year.
Let me tell you.
A romantic relationship
is just like a baked sweet potato.
You have to enjoy it while it's still hot.
But it also depends on
the right time and place.
For example,
if you're walking in a desert,
almost dying of heat and thirst,
and someone gives you
a baked sweet potato,
wouldn't that choke you to death?
It's the same for a romantic relationship.
If the timing is wrong,
even the best person
won't be the right one.
Then, right now,
do you still want to
start a new relationship?
♪ I know at the start of every story ♪
♪ They all feel somewhat the same ♪
♪ Just never thought I would ♪
♪ Fall for you so deeply ♪
♪ Why did I have to lose myself? ♪
♪ In the virtual world ♪
♪ Unfinished dreams hurt the most ♪
♪ Like a moth drawn to the flame ♪
♪ Wandering aimlessly
through the night sky ♪
♪ Until I met you ♪
♪ Like fire that finally took my life ♪
♪ I thought my deep devotion
and sincerity ♪
♪ Would earn your eternal loyalty ♪
♪ Because you are like a cloud ♪
♪ I became a wisp of wind ♪
♪ In the end, all the promises we made ♪
That night...
♪ Turned into nothing but emptiness ♪
♪ Once, for your dream ♪
♪ I gritted my teeth
and pushed myself forward ♪
♪ Love really hurts ♪
[That night]
♪ I never thought I could be so brave ♪
Are you asleep?
♪ In the end, everything came to nothing ♪
[Are you asleep?]
[Miyu]
Mr. Wei.
Mr. Duan Jr.
Sorry to bother you.
Mr. Wei.
What brings you here?
The Chinese restaurant
will open tomorrow, won't it?
I'm up here to give you a heads-up.
We need to be on the same page.
I heard you booked a large private room.
What does that mean?
I don't quite understand it.
It's to celebrate the successful opening
of your hotel's Chinese restaurant.
What's there to be uable to understand?
Why are you putting in so much effort
for that Ji Feng?
You have everyone at your beck and call.
In the end,
he might get all the spotlight.
It's not worth it.
Mr. Wei, you're thinking too much.
[Purong Hotel]
I've merely helped you set up a stage.
As for how to perform this show tomorrow,
it still depends on
which play you want to watch.
I knew it.
You and I have the same taste.
Alright then.
Since you have no dietary restrictions,
I'll arrange it as usual.
Mr. Duan Jr., let's wait and see.
I'm leaving now.
[Purong Hotel]
[Staff Only]
Tomorrow, the private room
in the Chinese restaurant
will turn into a lion's den.
I wonder what kind of shady characters
Duan Aoxiang will bring over here.
Mr. Ji,
should we ask more people
to keep an eye on things tomorrow?
I'll be on compensatory leave tomorrow.
I can come over and help Qiaoqi.
Alright. It's settled then.
You'll be fully
in charge of the private room tomorrow.
Let me know if anything happens.
Okay.
Let's go.
-Let's go.
[Staff Only]
[Food Storage Box]
You really scared me!
What are you doing here?
I'm here to see you and the cured pork.
My foot has just healed,
and now you've hit my head.
-I'm sorry.
-Are you okay?
What's wrong? Is the meat alright?
It's perfectly fine.
What's wrong? Is there a problem?
There's something wrong with the meat.
Don't worry.
The cured pork will be there soon.
I can't believe
there's a mole in the kitchen.
When I catch this despicable scumbag,
I'll stuff this meat right into his mouth.
Wait!
Since they were so kind
to give us the meat,
wouldn't it be a waste to throw it away?
[Welcome to Purong Chinese Restaurant]
Come on, guys.
[Purong Chinese Restaurant]
Today is the first day
of Purong Chinese Restaurant's reopening.
Everyone, present a brand-new image
to welcome all the upcoming guests.
Okay?
Okay!
Mr. Yang.
Mr. Ji.
Thanks for coming.
Congratulations.
Today, I'm going to
taste the food carefully.
Yes, you have to taste it carefully today.
Stir-fried Eel with Eight Delicacies.
Eleven plates of Shanghai Smoked Fish.
Serve as many
Osmanthus Rice Cakes as we have.
Sit.
Fetch a high chair.
Ms. Xu.
I didn't expect Mr. Ji would send you here
to control the scene personally.
I'm flattered, Mr. Duan.
Today, we have so many guests here.
It's my honor to serve everyone.
Come in, please.
Welcome.
Please.
The private room is already full.
There are still six empty tables
in the main hall.
Take care.
Not a single table can be empty today.
Ask our clerks to give the guests
in the HSKP Department
some Chinese restaurant vouchers.
Okay.
Hello, Mr. Duan Jr.
Mr. Duan Jr.
-You guys are here, too.
-Mr. Duan Jr.
Have a seat. Sit.
Where is the Crab Roe Tofu?
-Is it ready?
-Almost!
The people upstairs
are pushing for Yan Du Xian.
It'll be ready soon.
Serve it.
Luo!
Come and help!
Why are we changing it, Qiaoqi?
We'll have a good show to watch soon.
Zhi.
How does this taste?
Where did you purchase
[Purong Hotel]
this salted meat?
It doesn't even taste right.
Didn't the chef taste it
before the food was served?
Is this what you call a signature dish?
[Purong Hotel]
It's so disappointing.
Today, I've even
specially invited Zhi here.
In front of so many of my friends,
how can I get out of
this awkward situation?
[Purong Hotel]
Well, my dear friends,
it's my treat today.
Now let's go to Kuanli Mingjue
across the street.
The head chef there
has prepared
the authentic Yan Du Xian for you all.
[Purong Hotel]
Oh, by the way,
our head chef in Kuanli
is Jia Shikun, who came from here.
He's the famous Chef Jia
in the Shanghai Bund.
His specialty dish
happens to be
Yan Du Xian.
Mr. Duan, please wait.
Everyone,
please give me some time
to say a few words.
Please have a seat.
Actually,
that bowl of food you just ate
wasn't our signature dish, Yan Du Xian.
It was just a small interlude.
As for the exact details
of the story behind it,
I'd like to invite you all to taste
our real signature dish,
Yan Du Xian, first.
And then I will tell you
the whole story.
Come on.
Miyu.
Be careful.
Zhi.
I'd like to invite you
to taste the Yan Du Xian
which our head chef simmered
with the ingredients
she personally selected.
Please.
This flavor...
is so fresh,
so wild
and so strong.
I like it.
So previously...
Previously, a distinguished guest
heard that we would host a dinner
for VIPs today,
so he specially brought us
a piece of salted meat last night.
Then our general manager felt
it would be ungracious
to refuse such kindness,
so he asked us to use
the best broth and the best ingredients
to simmer this salted meat.
Perhaps our capabilities are so limited
that we really couldn't
handle such a precious gift.
That's the cause
of what happened just now.
I'm sorry
to let you see this awkward situation.
Who is this distinguished guest?
It doesn't matter
who this distinguished guest is.
What's important is that
Mr. Duan
has invited you here today.
Your sharp comment just now
really gave us
enough confidence and recognition.
We are extremely grateful.
It looks like this young lady
is really good at telling stories.
I'm going to include this information
in my review.
Being able to read our hotel's own story
in your food review column
would be our greatest honor.
Zhi, I'd also like to thank you
for strongly recommending
our hotel's signature dish,
Yan Du Xian.
It looks like this Purong Hotel
is still as good as ever.
It's a time-honored brand after all.
It really deserves its reputation.
Let's eat.
Let's all eat.
Thanks. Enjoy your meal.
Are you satisfied with the dishes?
-They're good.
-Enjoy your meal.
Ma'am,
are you satisfied with the dishes today?
They're great. I'm very satisfied.
I won't disturb you then.
Please enjoy your meal.
Chef Jia is asking
when the guests will arrive.
Why are you even asking?
Can't you sense it?
I got it, Mr. Duan.
Come on, Mr. Duan Jr.
Come on, Zhi.
The food is good.
Of course.
Enjoy your meal.
Mr. Wang.
Thanks for coming.
Let me know if you need anything.
Thank you.
Enjoy your meal.
Everyone is eating, huh?
Welcome.
Zhi.
How does it taste?
The flavors of the four seasons
are all in these dishes.
Is that so?
Mr. Duan Jr.,
it looks like you're all very satisfied.
We're very satisfied. It's very good.
It's really so good.
Why don't you taste it yourself?
Let me taste it.
The flavor is indeed extraordinary.
Enjoy your meal.
Excuse me.
Mr. Duan Jr.!
Well...
I thought you would understand
my good intentions
and help me.
I didn't expect you to come here
and see how embarrassed I was.
Mr. Duan Jr., you've misunderstood.
I was also kept in the dark.
I made arrangements.
Who would have thought
it would turn out like this?
Alright.
Anyway, I've shown enough respect for you.
And I've invited the VIPs.
Then you'll have to pay for this meal.
Mr. Duan Jr.!
Let's drink to the successful opening
of the Chinese restaurant!
Cheers!
It's all thanks to your efforts today.
Otherwise,
I would have ruined our reputation.
Speaking of that guy, Guo Luda,
I definitely won't let him off.
As a dignified senior chef skilled in
both hot dishes and pastry making,
how could he play dirty tricks on me
behind my back?
It's a reasonable suspicion,
but we have no solid evidence,
so we still can't jump to conclusions.
Everyone knows about the opening
of the Chinese restaurant.
If someone is really hiding in the corner
to cause trouble for us,
it'll be hard to guard against him.
So, Qiaoqi,
I hope from now on, you can
think twice before taking action.
Impulse is the devil.
The kitchen isn't a place
just anyone can enter.
Qiaoqi.
You're the head chef
of the Chinese restaurant now.
You have a clear view
of everything in the kitchen.
No one has a broader perspective than you.
At this time, if you slowly
calm down and observe everyone,
bad guys are all afraid of being exposed.
The fox will definitely show its tail.
Now that I've heard what you said,
the swapping of the cured pork
must have something to do
with Duan Aoxiang.
I have that feeling, too.
In the private room today,
Mr. Duan almost took everyone on the spot
straight to Kuanli.
It was as if they had been
prepared for it all along.
That's consistent with the news
I've gathered.
I've heard
in terms of Duan Aoxiang's banquet,
Kuanli was also preparing for it
at the same time.
I guess if we had made ourselves
laughingstocks here,
they could just take everyone
straight to Kuanli.
So fortunately,
we found out about it in time.
Chef Jia sharpened his knife in vain.
It's getting clearer
who caused this trouble.
Duan Aoxiang, that wretched playboy.
Speaking of which,
today,
although it looked like a good start,
in fact, most of the guests
were well-connected people
or relatives and friends.
As for the rest, we just relied on
discount coupons to create a buzz.
There were still not many new guests.
I don't know how things will be tomorrow.
I've already asked the sales department
to print vouchers.
Tell them to prepare more.
If the situation is still not good
tomorrow morning,
ask the HSKP Department
to give more vouchers to the guests.
In short,
the first three days after the opening
are just like a movie's
opening weekend box office.
Success or failure is crucial.
Cheers.
Looking forward to tomorrow.
I'm starving.
Why hasn't the food arrived yet?
What's for dinner today?
White Gourd Soup with Cured Pork and Kelp,
Braised Rice with Cured Pork,
Cured Pork with Tofu
and Cured Pork with Agrocybe Mushrooms.
Alright. All the dishes are served.
Please enjoy your meal.
Wait.
What...
does this mean?
Thank you for inviting
a table full of gourmets today
to support our Chinese restaurant.
This is a luxury dinner
specially made for you.
What's this smell?
Are you trying to poison me?
Of course not.
This all-cured-pork feast
was prepared with the cured pork
our mysterious VIP
had sent to our kitchen.
These are top-notch ingredients.
How would anyone else deserve to eat them?
From now on, it'll be a special offer
for this presidential suite.
I won't disturb you then.
Please enjoy your meal.
By the way,
it's more than enough.
Just wait, you all!
There are so many people.
Are they all waiting for tables?
Yes, they are.
Li! Li!
Tell the kitchen to hurry up
and get ready.
Okay.
Come on!
The soup is ready!
Can the Yan Du Xian be served now?
Yes, it can.
Okay. Let's go.
Waiter!
I've been calling for a long time.
Where's the waiter?
Coming soon.
Waiter, we want to order more food here!
What a good meal!
Let's go.
Is there anyone else who wants to order?
I want a portion of Yan Du Xian.
To order more food,
please click on this first.
Come here!
Serve this table! Hurry!
Waiter, I want more drinks.
We still have one dish
that hasn't been served yet.
Hurry up.
Coming soon.
Go help them now.
Waiter, is our food ready?
Coming soon.
How does it taste?
It's quite good.
Enjoy your meal.
When will the Eight-Treasure Duck
be ready?
If the Braised Fish Tail
still isn't ready, the guest will leave.
Coming!
How is it today?
Is the business outside very good?
It's more than good.
It's booming. A roaring success.
Everyone!
Did you hear that?
The business is booming today.
Let's all hurry up.
The guests like our food.
Whatever skills you have,
show them all.
Did you hear that?
Yes!
At this time, if you slowly
calm down and observe everyone,
bad guys are all afraid of being exposed.
The fox will definitely show its tail.
I'll emphasize this again.
Today's Yan Du Xian is the top priority
and plays the absolute key role.
The clay pots are stewing on the stoves.
The cured pork is frozen
in the storage room.
Those who have sticky fingers
should stay away.
If anyone dares to
cause trouble for me again,
I'll teach him a lesson.
Well, what do you mean?
Who are you talking about?
Li Qiaoqi, make it clear.
Stop being sarcastic here.
Mr. Guo.
Why are you overreacting?
Have I stepped on your tail?
If I, Guo Luda,
had ever touched your cured pork,
I-I-I'd change my surname to yours, Li.
Why are you always making
sarcastic comments in this kitchen?
When can you stop?
If you don't like me,
you can just fire me.
If you want to
domineer over me and bully me,
believe it or not,
I would perform a suplex on you.
Come on!
I'll do it now!
I'll just do it!
Guys!
Calm down!
The guests outside in the restaurant
are pushing for their food.
They're about to tear the roof down.
You can fight another day.
Okay?
Heroine.
Good guy.
You only know how to smooth things over
and talk like a bureaucrat.
Calm down.
Qiaoqi. Qiaoqi.
Don't always be so emotional.
I'm the one who's being unprofessional.
Mr. Xue, I'm very busy.
Excuse me.
Everyone, work harder!
Okay!
Hello, how many tables are there
before my turn?
There are five or six tables
before your turn.
Please wait a bit longer.
There are still five or six tables?
Yes, please wait a bit longer.
This way.
This is the guest from Room 1815.
Hello.
Are you still planning to check out today?
Yes.
Isn't it fine
as long as I check out before 2:00 PM?
2:00 PM
is our deadline for late checkout.
If there were no guests,
we could definitely make exceptions.
But right now,
there are indeed guests waiting.
It's not that I don't want to check out.
The key is that
I just don't know
when my number will be called,
so I don't dare to leave
and go back to pack my things.
Do you think this is okay?
I'll wait in line for you here.
You can go back to pack your things first.
Come down after you've checked out.
Alright. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Then please come this way with me.
Sorry for the trouble, Ms. Xu.
It's my duty.
This way, please.
Luo Qingping, I'm handling something
at the Chinese restaurant.
If anything happens upstairs,
let me know anytime.
Roger that.
Mr. Ji.
Gao from the Purchasing Department
is both inarticulate and bad-tempered.
That's the reason why he loses out.
Having worked on hotel finance
for so many years,
he still doesn't understand
worldly wisdom.
[Huang Chengmin]
But he's a really good person
[Xue Rui]
and is absolutely loyal to our hotel.
Mr. Ji, you can't just listen to
the one-sided story of the whistleblowers.
[Where are you?]
Mr. Huang.
We've already handed this matter over
to the Business Management Department.
I know you quite cherish talented people.
I understand.
But let's wait
for the investigation results.
Okay?
You can look at the menu
and order your food first.
It will be quicker when you go in later.
Okay. Thank you.
You can bring two more tables
of guests up here.
Okay.
Guests over here, please follow me.
This way, please.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry, Mr. Ji.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Clean it up.
Let me wipe it for you.
Is it hot?
It's fine.
It's not very hot.
By the way,
why are there so many people
at the entrance?
Did something happen inside?
Nothing happened.
Business is just really good today.
The guests are all lining up for tables.
But don't worry.
Mr. Xue is inside,
and Qiaoqi is in the kitchen.
Everything is arranged.
It's just that the guests keep coming
one after another.
How about this?
Let's open up the coffee bar
to the waiting guests as well.
Good idea. I'll go right now.
Okay.
How is it going, guys?
Can your wrists still handle it?
Your wrists!
Tell the guests outside
there's not much Yan Du Xian left.
How much is left exactly?
Ya!
Ten portions at most.
Ten portions aren't enough, Ma'am.
There are at least 50 tables outside.
50 tables!
That's why I'm asking you
to go out and inform them now.
Tell them to come back tomorrow
if they want it.
They've been waiting for over an hour.
If I tell them to come back tomorrow,
wouldn't I get beaten up?
There's only one piece of meat left.
Once it's eaten up, it'd be useless
even if you cut off my flesh.
Do as I said
and just go out to tell them.
The earlier you tell them,
the lighter the beating would be.
My crabs.
They're overcooked.
Are you two satisfied with our dishes?
Not bad.
Please enjoy your meal.
Okay.
Are you two satisfied with our dishes?
They're good.
Thank you. Enjoy your meal.
You've seen the good news.
Do you want to hear the bad news?
Go ahead.
We're running out of the cured pork.
I called the Chunlai couple.
They promised
to deliver the meat right away.
You're just amazing.
Everyone here can testify that
both of our families
arrived at the same time
and took numbers at the same time.
It was just a matter
of who stretched out his hand first.
Just now, we let you go first
when getting the numbers,
but now you're trying to
snatch food from our mouths.
Just for a portion of Yan Du Xian,
aren't you ashamed to do this?
Then what do you mean?
Are you not ashamed?
Our number is clearly ahead of yours,
but now you're forcing us to yield to you.
Why should we agree?
Then tell me
what you mean.
Stop arguing.
Don't scare the children.
Neither of the families is wrong.
Failing to let everyone eat Yan Du Xian
is the responsibility
of our Chinese restaurant.
But there's really
nothing we can do today.
-I'm really sorry.
-Um, wait.
We...
What about us?
We've waited for so long.
You advertised this Yan Du Xian
from the beginning.
Now we're here,
but you're telling us it's sold out.
Isn't that a scam?
I'm sorry.
The key is that we...
I have an idea.
I'm so sorry, everyone.
For the sake of the kids,
please calm down.
I have an idea.
Let's see if both of your families
could share one portion of Yan Du Xian.
We can divide the large clay pot
into single-serving small bowls.
In this way, both families can eat it.
What's more, the single-serving bowls
will be a bit cheaper.
Additionally,
we can also give you
two free desserts for the two kids.
In this way,
everyone can get to eat and drink,
and the kids can even play together.
Do you think that's okay?
-Okay!
That sounds great.
Sir, please inform the kitchen.
I'm going to kitchen to take a look.
T-Then what about us?
What about us?
We want to eat Yan Du Xian, too.
I'm sorry.
The situation today is really so special.
I apologize to you all here first.
Professor Liu?
The two of us usually
can't eat up a whole portion anyway.
If anyone agrees,
we don't mind
sharing a portion of Yan Du Xian with him.
We can change to small portions, too.
Thank you, Professor Liu.
Thank you all.
How about this, everyone?
Then I'll ask this lady
to count up how many people
are willing to share Yan Du Xian.
Then I'll go back to the restaurant
and ask the guests
whose dishes haven't been served yet
to see if anyone wants to spare
more servings to share with you.
Do you think that's okay?
I think it's okay.
The manager really has a way.
Wait a moment. I'll be right back.
Mr. Xue! Mr. Xue!
The delivery truck is already on its way.
It will arrive at the hotel at 3 PM.
Just wait to receive the goods.
Then what about now?
There are less than 10 portions
of Yan Du Xian left.
A bunch of guests are waiting outside.
Give them more discounts.
Keep the guests no matter what.
Besides Yan Du Xian,
we have many other excellent dishes.
Only when the guests sit down
will they know our capabilities.
Ms. Xu.
How's it going outside?
I've already discussed it with the guests.
They're all willing to
exchange large pots for small bowls
and share Yan Du Xian with others.
I'm here to ask
how many tables in the restaurant
haven't been served Yan Du Xian yet.
If three more tables are willing to share,
all the guests outside
will be able to eat Yan Du Xian.
That's great.
Go out and help the kitchen
communicate with the guests.
I'll do it right away.
You can help me
discuss with the management department
the pricing
for a small portion of Yan Du Xian.
Okay.
Thanks for your hard work, Miyu.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Yummy!
So fresh!
Really delicious!
Very good!
Yummy!
So good.
Delicious.
Really delicious.
This feels so good!
I haven't worked this hard in years.
Really.
Delicious.
Once again, Qiaoqi's cooking has impro-
When the Chinese restaurant was closed,
I really wanted to die.
I didn't expect the business would be
so good once it opened
and everything would go so smoothly.
Mr. Ji, you've helped me
solve the cured pork problem twice.
You're truly the cured pork superman
of our hotel.
No, no, no.
Don't call me that.
It sounds weird.
Speaking of cured pork,
I haven't asked you guys yet.
When we went to Linglong Town previously,
after Qiaoqi and I left,
how did you two
spend that night on the island?
It seemed to rain quite heavily that day.
Did the ferry even stop?
Why are you so gossipy?
Just eat your meat.
I'm curious.
By the way, speaking of which,
the extent to which our restaurant
was full up today
was indeed surprising.
At first, I was worried
whether someone
was trying to cause trouble
and complain about
the dishes or something.
But later, it didn't seem to be the case.
As you said, good wine needs no bush.
But don't you think this happened
too quickly and too suddenly?
I know why.
During the daytime today,
I heard many guests
mentioning someone's name.
I guess it must be because of her.
-Who?
Dianjiangchun.
Who is Dianjiangchun?
You don't even know her?
She's
a travel and restaurant-exploring blogger,
who has been very active in recent years.
For any restaurant she visits,
if she gives it a good review,
its popularity will soar.
Dianjiangchun
really visited our Chinese restaurant.
See? I told you so.
I-Is this the blogger
you liked so much before?
Yes, it's her.
She has 23,780,000 followers.
Forget it. Don't look.
You only have over 100 followers.
Don't let it get on your nerves.
Look what she said.
The fragrance of spring
that cannot be missed
is all in the Yan Du Xian of Purong Hotel.
Such a review
has saved us so much on advertising costs.
Look.
We've really met our lucky star.
[Dianjiangchun]
[Always on the road
recording the flavors of the mortal world]
Cheers!
Let's drink a toast.
Cheers.
Let me treat you to skewers
somewhere else.
We've just eaten.
Why should we have skewers?
-Xu Miyu.
-Skewers taste differently from dinner.
Do you have time?