(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
You just got here?
Haven't seen you around before
Yeah, arrived last night
You're really beautiful
Took my breath away
You…
You're handsome too
Really
Mm
(sneeze)
Sorry about that
(blowing nose)
Wow, you came prepared
How about
let's redo it?
Sure, let's redo it
Wait, wait
This time, can you make it more… sensual?
You just got here?
Haven't seen you around
Mm… care for a taste?
Hey — what are you doing!
You're the one who said "make it sensual"
That's not what I meant
That's harassment
Harassment, my ass
Sensual is exactly this
Even if it's a fling
you don't just kiss right off the bat
Forget it, I'm done acting
I'll just go for it
Are you out of your mind?!
Out of my mind, what?
Such a hassle — fine, if you don't want to
Out of your mind
Hmph
You're the one who said it
that changing locations would bring back the spark
Now what?
What do you mean "I said"?
This is about both of us
Shouldn't you be trying too?
I've been doing my part
Playing along with the meet-cute
the first-love pretend
and—
Don't even talk about your bad acting
You even got the book wrong
Bringing an old classic
This is 21st-century Lijiang
People who don't know
would think you're acting in Plum in the Golden Vase
I really can't take you anymore
I'm done talking
Annoying
What happened to us?
Ask yourself
This isn't making love anymore
It's making hate
Making hate?
Yeah
You don't even want to do it, do you?
How long has it been?
Say something, damn it
Do you know that feeling?
Even when I'm holding you
I feel like
none of you belongs to me anymore
Do you understand that feeling?
What are you looking at?
So rude
This glass sways with a heartless light~♪
A toast to old debts of foolish love~♪
Lijiang's night, I sing alone~♪
Hoarse voice can't reach the gentle land~♪
Then you push the door, fragrance trailing~♪
A key that opens the wall of my heart~♪
Eyes meet, sparking and crackling~♪
This ruin suddenly bathed in moonlight~♪
Get drunk! Get lost! Just for tonight!~♪
Who cares about tomorrow, who's beside whom~♪
Your gaze is just a temporary painkiller~♪
My desolation is your playground~♪
Get drunk! Get lost! Just for tonight!~♪
So it really is you
Yeah
How'd you know I was at this table
Huh? This is your table?
Mm
Oh
What a coincidence
Looks like we're fated
Yeah
Hey, you sang really well
Are you the resident singer?
No, anyone drinking here can sing
600 yuan a song
Wanna sing?
I'll request one for you
No no, let's just drink
Alright
Hey, that song
the last one you sang
what was it called?
Ah, that one
"Love at the Corner"
Bullshit, what corner
There's no such song
There isn't?
Definitely not
That song hasn't even been written yet
You're making it up
Am I?
Definitely
Then you write it
Mm
That song
write it now
Come on, I can't write songs
I only sing them
Whatever, you
Mm
My drink's empty — give me yours
Hey, you—
Mine's gone too
So, want to keep drinking?
Mm
Then next round
Hm?
Hey
You keep showing up in my line of sight
Are you into me or something?
Hey
You're the one who keeps showing up in mine
And you said it yourself
it's all coincidence
I just happened to pick a song
and you walked in
And then…
Sorry — accident
You're so accident-prone
Could you be a little more accident-prone? Hm?
I think I'm sobering up
If you wait too long
my morals will sober up too
Better hurry up
That isn't your boyfriend's name, is it?
Mm
Forget him, just for now
Nick
I, um
I—
Hey
You okay?
You alright?