In the end, I chose to hurt
the person I loved the most.
All to protect another person I loved.
So, what was the very first
thing you gave P'Fah again?
- What the hell was it?
- A sandwich and chocolate milk.
Do you really think this is a good idea?
Of course it is. You've come
this far—you can't back out now.
What, do you think I'm
some kind of delivery rider?
It's not that bad. But if this is
all it amounts to, then so be it.
Please give this to
the owner of the letter.
Sure.
So… you like him, huh?
Not to the point of liking him yet.
I just want to get to know him better.
Do you even know who it is?
I don't.
Don't you want to know?
Judging by how he had someone else pass
it on, He clearly don't want me to know.
If he don't want me to know, then I won't.
But I do want to know.
Fah, I've got a question for you.
Normally, lots of people give you things.
So why does this one stand out, huh?
I don't really know how to explain it.
Reading the messages
just makes me feel at ease.
They're simple, ordinary messages.
He never ask anything or expect a reply.
The only thing he hope
for is that I'm doing well.
That's all.
It feels like I could just float away.
I get it.
Do you think P'Fah knows it's you?
That he likes you?
Or that he likes the person in the letters?
If he feels good about
the person in the letters,
that's not such a bad thing, right?
Because the real Typhoon
can't even bring himself to talk to P'Fah.
But the person in the letters can do it.
- Phoon.
- Hmm?
Can I ask you something?
Just hypothetically.
If today
your dad wasn't involved at all,
would you still try to get close to P'Fah?
I guess I would
take better care of P'Fah.
Not just writing letters, not just buying
things and telling him to take care of himself.
Good job, maew.
But honestly, I think P'Fah
would like you no matter what.
Even if he knew you were
the one behind the letters.
Because P'Fah probably likes how caring
you are and knows that you truly love him.
Hey, stop it. Phoon's about to explode.
You really mean that?
See? Proof.
Maybe he just bought things
back for everyone or something.
Come on. How could P'Fah buy things back
for everyone? So many people give him stuff.
It has to be someone special.
No matter what, P'Fah likes you.
Are you taking my side?
Yeah, maybe a little.
Why not? I'm your friend.
I'm supposed to support you all the way.
Even North supports you that
much—how could I fall behind?
By now he might've already done
some voodoo on P'Fah for you.
Well, good then. I feel like the
vibe's gotten brighter somehow.
You don't look like a sleepy cat anymore.
See? I told you the plan would
work. You guys just didn't believe me.
Huh? Your plan?
It was Dao's plan.
- Really?
- Yeah.
But I'm the one who made
the plan 80% successful.
And do you know who
found the delivery Cupid?
Me.
I'm freaking handsome.
And talented too.
And I can't help about it.
So annoying.
Enough. Get up here already—so dramatic.
This man.
But do you know what
the problem is right now?
The problem is Phoon doesn't
believe P'Fah actually likes him.
What are you talking about?
At this point, I think P'Fah's already
preparing the engagement procession.
Whoa.
But I've spoiled enough
already—you're the real spoiler master.
What are you even saying?
Does P'Fah know you're
the one who wrote the letters?
No, of course not. How would he know?
But you never know—Phoon
is someone close to him.
Does P'Tonfah know that you like him?
I think P'Fah knows that I like him.
I think
he only sees me as a little brother.
Hey.
Why do you assume P'Fah
only thinks of you as a brother?
Yeah.
Maybe because we know each other so well.
It's like he's always trying to draw a line.
And I've never crossed that line.
Wait—if P'Fah finds out you're
the one who wrote the letters…
Wouldn't he draw that line again?
That's exactly why I don't
want him to know it's me.
So you're not even thinking
of crossing that line at all?
Yeah.
I
I'm scared of losing P'Fah.
You're scared of losing P'Fah, but aren't
you scared he might fall for someone else?
Of course I am.
Just thinking about it already kills me.
So what do we do?
I think there's only one way.
There is?
And that is...
- Go for it!
- Hey! You scared me.
Just fight for it. You have to fight.
Fight or not?
Fight.
Hey, that's weak. Fight or not!!!
Fight!
I'll make P'Fah know
just how much I love him.
That's right. Good job. Fight!!!
Fight!
This one's loud, that one's all soft.
- You always ruin the mood.
- Just look at yourself.
What are you doing, P'Hill?
Does it look like me?
It's cute, but you
shouldn't be drawing it here.
So you'll think of me
while you're studying.
Come on, even if I don't
study, I still think of you.
Wow, you came so early—I thought
you were serious about studying.
Turns out you came to hang out with...
- What?
- Shut up already.
- My friends are looking for me. I'm off to class, P'.
- Mm.
- Study hard, okay?
- Yes.
Make sure you eat something too, P'Hill.
I'm going now.
- Mm, bye-bye.
- Bye-bye.
You came this early—here
to pick something up?
Yeah.
Must be really important, huh?
Really important.
"Really important, huh?"
"Yeah, really important."
That much, huh.
Which ship I am on always
sailing smooth nonstop.
Now it's your turn.
- Stop teasing me already.
- Ooh, someone's enjoying it.
Alright, alright.
You always get rough when you're shy.
Can't even tease you a little.
You're happy, huh. You're shy, huh.
Students, please sit properly.
Enjoy your meal. Have a nice day.
Wow, you walked right past
without even looking at me.
There you go—smile a lot.
Lift your head a bit. Or am I supposed
to talk to the back of your neck?
North.
Your voice is crack.
Dude, my heart's about
to jump out of my chest.
Calm down, maew.
Want some chocolate? Might help.
I don't want chocolate anymore.
Oh? Not other people's chocolate anymore?
Only P'Fah's chocolate now?
- You seriously won't stop teasing me, huh?
- It's funny when you're shy.
Dude, is this like flirting
through messages or what? Or
am I just imagining things?
Read my lips.
P'Fah is flirting with you.
Got it?
At first, I thought we'd just be pen pals.
Hey, how can it stay just talking?
I told you—you have to go for it.
Are you really going to stay
in your safe zone like this?
If you do, you'll be stuck
in that safe zone forever.
I know.
Just give me some time.
Oh please, acting like you need time.
You said you were
going to flirt with P'Fah.
Look at this—now P'Fah's
the one flirting with you.
And you made him like you first like this
what are you gonna do?
What do you mean, like me first?
Wow.
So you're really going to let
“sweet like you” slip away?
Then just tell him—“I'm sweeter
than the chocolate you gave me.”
Throw in a little compliment, maybe.
Why not try it?
I still don't even know where
our relationship is headed.
And there's my dad too.
No matter what, I can't reveal
myself as the one in the letters.
So what
you're going to make him
like you and then disappear?
That's cruel.
I never said I was disappearing anywhere.
You've already disappeared
from P'Fah once before.
You're going to do it again this time?
P'Fah would be really hurt.
I don't want it to end the same way again.
I don't want to see P'Fah hurt.
Deal with your dad first.
The only reason is he's afraid you'll tell people
you're someone else's kid and he'll lose face.
That's totally his own fault anyway.
Why the hell did he do
that in the first place?
Want me to talk to him for you?
Forget about that for now.
Yeah, and don't overthink it. Try following
your own feelings sometimes. It's your life.
Mm.
Where the hell did you
find North from, dude?
I just kicked some dirt and
he popped up out of nowhere.
What kind of creature is that?
I just feel like...
North has really positive energy.
More like positive-negative
energy, if you ask me.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
I wish I could be positive
energy for P'Fah too.
Even if I'm not as strong as North.
Why do you have to be strong?
Like I said, just being yourself is enough.
Don't try to be like North.
So, your med school exam
results are out, right? How was it?
I didn't make it.
But I'd already prepared myself for that.
I guess I wasn't ready this year.
I'll try again next year.
So why do you want to be a doctor?
I
I want to fulfill Fun's dream.
And what about your own dream?
I don't know. I've never eaten myself before. But this box of chocolate
is just the right amount of sweet. It's really good. Thank you.
Shit.
Huh?
Is it morning already?
Look over there—it's almost evening.
I finished class and came
back, and you're still asleep.
Shit—did you take attendance for me or not?
Don't worry, buddy. You're
getting expelled soon anyway.
You bastard, Fah. Asshole.
Ugh.
- Got a headache?
- Like hell I do.
There—I bought you food
and some hangover meds.
Eat up.
Thanks, man. You're a damn saint.
Why'd you get wasted like this?
Fah, what about the
person who sent the letter?
Did you open your heart to him yet?
Yeah. I think he's pretty cute.
And honestly, I really
like this kind of normalcy.
Oops.
The chocolate bill.
- How much?
- 550.
- Sounds fine. Not expensive.
- Dollars.
Dollars?
Yeah. Plus ten dollars
for the carrying fee.
- Hurry up and transfer it.
- Where the hell did you get it from?
Don't ask.
- Eighteen grand, right?
- Twenty. Transfer it.
Mm.
Transferred.
Just you opening your
heart already cost 500 dollars.
All my friends are freaking sugar daddies.
Says the guy—aren't you one too?
No way. I'm not letting
anyone leech off my money.
Love is such bullshit.
Hurry up and eat. And if you're
leaving, lock the room for me.
I'm going back to studying.
Clean up too.
Mm.
Fah, can I borrow a shirt?
Why the hell are you reading so much, Fah?
I'm summarizing what we learned today.
You skipped class—you should review too.
Of course I am. Aren't you tired?
Of course I am.
Being Tonfah is exhausting, huh?
Yeah, being Tonfah is exhausting as hell.
Then is being Arthit exhausting?
Me?
It's fucking brutal.
What's brutal?
Everything.
Hey, Fah.
Yeah?
Remember when Hill said if
he combined you and me
he'd get one perfect person?
Mm.
But honestly, I don't want
to be combined with you.
I'm just comparing, asshole.
I don't want to be
combined with you either.
Oh please.
Haven't you stopped yet?
That habit of pressuring yourself.
Yeah.
If anything's wrong, you can tell me, Fah.
Just tell me, Fah.
I want to stick my nose into your business.
I just don't want to disappoint anyone.
My dad…
He wants me to be the sky that
stands higher than everyone else.
For my mom,
she wanted me to be like
a tree others could lean on.
So I became Tonfah.
By the way, why is your name Arthit?
I was born on a Sunday.
Pretty simple, right?
Yeah, life doesn't have to
be that complicated, Fah.
Well,
both my parents are doctors.
They're kind and warm.
And they really care
about people around them.
You know, they barely ever
had to force me to do anything.
I just grew up becoming like them.
So I guess I got used to always
checking if other people are okay.
Like,
can't you just not care for once?
I've tried, you know.
But I tend to live up to
other people's expectations.
Until sometimes.
I don't even know
what kind of person I want to be.
So… are you happy now?
Yeah.
See? You right there.
Some people
don't even know what
the hell they were born for.
Like me.
When I tell you to be yourself,
I don't mean you have to be
different or live just for yourself.
For some people, just
caring about others is enough.
Damn, when you get serious,
you actually sound pretty thoughtful.
Well,
I'm the serious type—just
not very expressive.
What does that even mean?
What I'm saying is,
as long as you're living your
life happily, that's enough.
Uh…
If you're tired, take a break.
You don't always have to study.
Studying doesn't automatically
make you smarter anyway.
Or you could just not give a damn like me.
Uh
I'm off. See you.
Thanks, man.
So what's your conclusion, exactly?
Eighteen thousand baht chocolate.
If Johan bought it, I
wouldn't even be surprised.
But when it's you…
Yeah.
I just wanted to buy it.
That's all.
If he said he doesn't like
it, then he doesn't like it.
French chocolate. It's just a kind gesture.
Your “kind gesture” is
seriously over the top.
Honestly, is it really that
weird? It's just chocolate.
Not weird. Totally normal.
If it is for someone you like.
So what is it, huh, Fah?
Well
I like him. So what?
How much do you like him?
I don't know. I just do.
I don't know how to measure how much.
Is it even possible to like
someone you've never met?
I guess that part doesn't
really matter to me.
Just that he's him.
The person in the letters.
That is enough for me.
Come to think of it, nothing
about you two is really stable.
If he disappears, he could
disappear just like that.
And if one day he realizes someone close
by is more real than a person in letters,
he could disappear, and you wouldn't
even have the right to chase after him.
After all this, you're really okay
with letting things stay like this?
Fah.
I'm hungry.
- Is something wrong?
- Someone asked me to give this to you.
Who's it from?
It's from my friend. He asked me not to
say his name, but he said enjoy your meal.
I see.
I really can't accept it.
Please tell him I'm sorry.
Please take it. My friend really likes you.
I really can't. I'm sorry.
I understand.
Fah, what's wrong with you? You usually
accept stuff from people, don't you?
Didn't you say if someone gives
you something, you should accept it?
It's rude not to.
That was when I already
had someone in my heart.
How could I just accept things from anyone?
Right?
Yeah.
Fah, couldn't you take
it? What if it's food?
Where did you crawl out
from, starving like that?
I'm not asking for your
stuff. I'm asking for his.
- It's his, you know that, right?
- I'm just hungry.
Yeah, I was about to head over anyway.
Huh? What?
A car accident?
Yeah. I'm in a cast, stuck in my room. Probably
won't be going to uni for a while. Sorry.
Looks like I won't be able
to deliver it to P'Tonfah.
Then what about my gift— hey, wait.
Cupid's out of action.
He can't carry out the mission.
What are we gonna do?
Isn't there anyone else to replace him?
Why are you acting like that?
You think it's that easy to find someone?
It took forever to find someone
suitable for this huge mission.
And negotiating everything took time too.
- You think just anyone will do?
- I know, okay? I'm stressed out too.
- Phoon.
- Hmm?
What if we use this chance to test P'Fah?
If P'Fah doesn't get anything
from you and starts getting anxious,
that's actually a good thing.
Uh…
But I don't want to test P'Fah.
Then what are we supposed to
do? Wait until Bobby's leg heals?
That'll take forever.
I think we need to change the plan.
How about setting a place and
taking turns exchanging the items?
Huh? What if you accidentally
run into each other?
If P'Fah and the maew agree on the timing,
you guys probably won't meet.
But if I were P'Fah,
I'd wanna secretly check
who the other person is.
Mm.
I don't think P'Fah would
do that, one hundred percent.
If he really wanted to know,
he would've asked ages ago.
He really respects the
person in the letters.
Still, this method sounds okay.
But wouldn't that bother him?
Come on, we're already
this far. Toughen up.
Don't give up yet.
I think that Dao's plan actually works.
If you're worried about P'Fah, just
meet him in the medical building.
(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
Any coffee shop will do.
That way it's convenient for P'Fah.
Right?
But coffee shops are always crowded.
What's with you now?
I'm telling you, I've found
a new Cupid for you guys.
Who?
Yeah, who?
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Would this bother you, P'Gib?
Not at all. I'm in.
Sounds fun.
I've never done anything like this before.
North.
Do you seriously know everyone on campus?
See? I told you to trust me.
Fah comes to my café every morning anyway.
It fits our plan perfectly.
I'll tell you guys this.
P'Gib is beautiful and rich,
great at making coffee—and
most importantly, great at planning.
Wow, I can't tell if you're genuinely
praising me or just want a discount coupon.
Probably the latter.
I mean it.
- But a coupon would be nice.
- See?
I knew it—that's just like you.
Hey, North. That's my
cup. Yours is over there.
- I'm just tasting it.
- Then why didn't you order cocoa?
- I can't even taste it?
- No, I'm stingy.
What if P'Hill and P'Fah don't show up?
Are we just leaving it to fate?
Even if P'Fah doesn't come tomorrow,
he'll come another day.
I don't think P'Fah would
stop drinking coffee here.
Because P'Gib pours too little.
Maybe I shouldn't treat
you to cake anymore.
I was just about to treat you.
- I'm not involved, okay?
- I'm just joking, P'Gib.
I told you not to get too close to Arthit.
At first, you were really cute.
That's true.
This is all P'Arthit's fault.
For staining someone
pure and innocent like me.
How can you even say that, North?
You? I've only ever seen you
decent when P'Johan was around.
Other than that—you're a mess!
Let me tell you—“pure,” my
ass. More like filthy already.
I'll be the one to make you even dirtier.
Just wait till I need to take a dump first.
Whoa—are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry I couldn't contact you for several days. The
person who was supposed to pass the item on was unavailable.
So I asked P'Gib for a favor. Would it be too much
trouble to ask you to pick it up here every morning?
If it's inconvenient, that's totally fine.
The weather's been changing
lately. Please take care of your health.
I feel like I might be getting sick myself.
I already ordered hot coffee for you.
Don't order another one—one cup is enough.
- Here you go, Fah. Your hot coffee.
- Thank you.
- Uh, Mhor.
- Yes?
Do you want to look for him?
I don't think that's a good idea.
That's good. If you got curious
and started pressing me for answers,
I'd be in a really awkward position.
But
I'll give you a tiny spoiler, then.
What is it?
He is…
A really lovely person.
If about that, I already know.
What should I do next?
Guess I'll make more coffee.
Where did he disappear to? He told
me to buy it and then didn't show up.
He said he went to the drugstore.
Who's sick?
Oh—then if he's not coming, I'll
eat first. I can't wait anymore. Oops.
That's mine.
You weren't here yet. I
was afraid it'd get cold.
So I was gonna eat it for you—that's all.
So what's the conclusion—are
we gonna lie in wait?
Nope.
Don't you want to know who they are?
They clearly don't want me to know.
Shouldn't I think about his comfort first?
Then what's that?
Oh, he's not feeling well.
Oh.
You came so late—I'm about
to close the shop already.
Here you go.
Phoon.
Are you sick?
Just a little.
Don't worry about others so much
that you forget to take care of yourself.
Thank you.
Should you see a doctor?
To the patient: I'm not sure
if you're feeling better yet,
but please monitor your symptoms
and take the medicine as instructed.
P.S. Don't worry. I already asked my
aunt, who's a pharmacist, for advice.
If you're not getting
better, please see a doctor.
If there's an emergency, you
can call me at this number.
Saline for nasal rinsing - Oral rehydration salts: 1 sachet in 600 ml, sip gradually -
Cooling gel patch until body temperature goes down - Throat lozenges: 1 piece at a time.
Hello, Foam. Where are you now?
Oh wow, didn't you say you were sick? You
sound so cheerful—are you better already?
I got good medicine.
What kind of medicine?
Not telling.
Hold on a sec—there's
another call coming in.
Hello?
Sorry, is this Typhoon's number?
Yes, it is.
Who is this?
Typhoon, dear.
I'm sorry if this makes you uncomfortable.
I'm okay.
Did you come to Chiang Mai with my dad?
I heard he has clients here,
so he comes often.
No. I came here to see you, Typhoon.
Is there something you
want to talk to me about?
You've always known, right,
that your father remarried me?
Yes.
But he never told me that
he already had a family before.
I only found out recently.
You're not okay with the fact that
he had a family before, are you?
That he already had a family.
I'm okay
if he hadn't lied and
abandoned his own child like this.
P'Rit.
Did he ever take care of you?
I caught him cheating.
I'm sorry.
I ended up crying in front of you.
It's okay.
So I hired someone to investigate him,
and that's how I found out
not only did he have an affair,
he also had a family before,
and another son as well.
I'm in the middle of deciding
the most important decision of my life.
I just want to know if he can
be a good father to my child.
I don't know
whether my dad can be
a good father to your child,
but for me,
he never managed to be one.
I understand.
Her name is Fai.
Fai.
P'Phoon's little sister.
Hello.
My half-sister's name is Fun.
Really? What a coincidence.
I named her “Phafai”
to match my own name, Phaphrae.
Phafai? That's such a cute name.
Thank you.
Then where is Fun?
Fun passed away.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Even though it's sad that
I'll never see her again,
thinking about Fun
isn't a bad thing at all.
You and Fun must have
loved each other very much.
I did terrible things to
Fun before she died.
I didn't even get the chance to apologize.
So now, I atone for my mistakes by
living my life for Fun.
I believe your sister would rather
want you to live your life for yourself.
I'll get going now.
If anything happens,
you can call me anytime.
Thank you very much.
Let's go.
Living my life for myself…
what does that even mean, Fun?
I believe your sister would rather
want you to live your life for yourself.
And what about your dream?
What faculty are you studying in?
Veterinary Medicine.
P'Fah thought Phoon
wouldn't like this field.
Your peach tea is ready.
This one's on the house. Fah treated you.
He left plenty of money
too. Want anything else?
Mind if I sit here?
Oh… sure.
Phoon, do you really not want Fah to
know that you're the one from the letters?
Not really.
I don't know… I think a relationship
where one person knows everything
while the other knows nothing at all
is kind of sad.
Fah seems to like you this much.
How do you think he'd feel
not knowing anything
about the person he likes?
Sorry, I was just rambling.
Uh, I'll go get back to work then.
You can drink it now.
I just made an important
decision in my life.
I can't say what it is,
but thinking of you gave me more courage.
So I just wanted to say thank you.
Thank you so much.
I don't know what good news
you have, but congratulations.
Please consider this a
congratulatory gift from me.
Phoon, is tomorrow P'Fah's birthday?
How did you know?
P'Hill took me to pick out a gift for P'Fah.
Why don't you make use of this chance too?
I already prepared a
birthday gift for P'Fah.
From Typhoon, or from
the person in the letters?
Both.
The shirt's really nice, but
it's too loose. I can't wear it out.
Sorry. I probably should've
drunk more milk when I was a kid.
But I really like it. I'll wear it to sleep.
You're so kind. Thank you very much.
Here—happy birthday.
Thanks.
- This is from me and Ter together.
- Thank you very much.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
I'm going to the restroom.
Damn it, Fah. It's your birthday,
and instead of a bar,
you dragged me here to tutor.
Here.
Thanks.
But you don't have to next time.
Here.
Happy Birthday P'Fah.
Thank you.
Help! Help!
Someone's stuck in here!
P'Fah, help Phoon. I'm scared.
P'Fah!
Phoon.
Phoon, step back from the door first.
P'Fah, I'm sorry. I did something wrong.
Are you mad at me, P'Fah?
It's okay now.
P'Fah is right here.
I'm right here.
Are you mad at me, P'Fah?
Please don't be mad at me.
Calm down first, okay? You're safe now.
Calm down.
I'm scared.
P'Fah, I'm sorry. I did something wrong.
I used to think of Phoon
as just a younger brother.
The kid next door I wanted
to take the best care of.
But you know he doesn't
see you as just a brother, right?
With P'Fah… it probably
won't stay the same anymore.
So are you going to tell P'Fah about P'Fun?
I think P'Fah is head
over heels for you too.
Whatever you say, he'll go along with it.
Has anyone ever told
you how adorable you are?
I really like your soft lips
when I kiss you.