What is this for?
I'll unleash my dog.
I'll unleash my dog!
Come on.
All done?
An entire set of 9 pieces.
Not one missing.
Shut the doors.
[Born with Luck]
[Episode 15]
He is a bit shy.
-He is a bit shy.
Bit.
Halt.
Are you a parent?
Someone's sister?
You're here to learn English
as well, right?
I'm here to take a look.
Too embarrassed to go to an institute
for adults
and afraid of failing to catch up?
This place is great
for learning the basics.
You chose the right spot.
A-Are you listening
to English?
Could you let me hear it?
We can share our experience.
Let me hear it.
It's out of battery.
Take a listen.
What a pity.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Peter.
I'm Cici.
I took English classes with him
for 3 days.
Back in my school days,
I felt sleepy whenever I heard English.
The course lasted from 8 a.m. to 9 a.m.,
and then 8 p.m. to 9 p.m.
You're so lucky to watch Li Penggai,
since you don't need to leave home early
and come home late.
Do you know what kind of sacrifice
I made in the past 3 days?
[Mapleleaf Peninsula]
I went undercover
at the sales centers
of various new-builds.
[Mapleleaf Peninsula,
a 5A-level haven for the body and mind ]
Sir.
Sir, interested in the apartments?
How much per square meter?
-Fifteen thousand yuan.
-Thirty thousand yuan.
-Such a low price?
-That expensive?
Since when did you become so rich?
I don't have a budget.
I'll pay as much as it takes.
He took snacks
and stole an umbrella
after seeing the new-builds.
Then, he went to have Malatang.
Bro!
We just met at the sales center.
I had Malatang with him for 3 days.
This is delicious.
I got terrible diarrhea.
Don't get us started.
We had to stake out till early morning
every day.
Mr. Lang, slow down.
Careful.
[Auto focus]
-Bye!
Bye!
[Auto focus]
Team 4 has taken over. Over.
Li Qian?
She's not on our team.
Maybe it's her shift
to watch Hu Jianren.
Ask about that.
Team 1, please respond to Team 4.
There are police.
[Xinda Advertisement]
What kind of driver are you?
How could you drive like that?
I'm really sorry.
C-C-Call the police.
Team 2, get back into your car.
Do not blow your cover at this point.
Observe first.
The driver of the runaway car
takes full responsibility.
Any problem with that?
No.
Your IDs and driver's licenses.
Is this car yours?
No.
It belongs to Rongcheng Group.
It's my boss's car.
What's your boss's name?
Zhou Rong,
Mr. Zhou.
[Traffic Police Unit of Sanjiangkou
Public Security Bureau, Ping'an Province]
[Traffic Accident Ruling]
And yours?
I forgot to bring mine.
Do you or do you not have
a driver's license?
Your ID number?
Ren.
What happened?
Nothing.
Just a little fender bender.
The responsibility is all hers.
Cici?
Mr. Zhou,
I've met this girl before.
An acquaintance of yours?
Not really.
How did you meet her?
Just by chance.
Make sure you drive carefully
in the future.
Mr. Zhou,
this has nothing to do with us.
She rear-ended our car.
Gorgeous.
Did you get hurt?
No.
That's good.
The car is mine.
We'll pay for the repair.
How are you involved in this now?
You think that's a proper parking place?
Move your car now!
Don't give her a hard time.
Here, sign your name.
Does she have a driver's license?
Mind your own business.
[Zhang Yi'ang]
Come back to the station now.
One copy for each of you.
What's up
with your luck today?
Oh you...
You crashed the car so soon.
To add to it, Mr. Zhou
and Ren s-saw everything.
Bro,
I am really not to blame.
The car ahead changed lanes
over a solid line.
The one behind rear-ended mine.
None of that was my fault.
Does Ren want me to pay for the repair?
Don't talk nonsense.
Ren is not that petty.
Alright. T-The...
The responsibility is really not yours.
Look, just claim the repair
on insurance.
Alright. Don't be mad.
Calm down.
How can I not be mad?
The thing is, the car ahead ran away.
All the company cars only
have mandatory liability insurance
for traffic accidents.
The company has to pay
for any repair first.
How am I supposed
to talk about that with Ren?
No.
Just be frank with him.
That car ran away.
What's there for us to do?
Well...
When the offending driver is caught,
w-we'll be able to pay the company back,
right?
Should I also be frank with Mr. Zhou
when he asks why I used the car?
Am I going to tell him
that I let my girlfriend
borrow it
for the wedding vendor she works for?
Of course not.
Are you silly or what?
Gai,
you're much
favored by Mr. Zhou now.
You...
You're supposed to be
at the same level as Ren.
How about you put in a good word
for me with Ren?
Wait.
Is it so obvious
that I'm favored by Mr. Zhou now?
Yes, very much so.
Everyone in the company can see that.
Gai, think about it.
Mr. Zhou has a bad temper.
Many of his subordinates
have been sent to transport sand.
Has any of them come back?
Right.
You're an exception.
You're the one and only exception.
Alright, stop it.
If you're not favored by him,
then who is?
Well, I...
Ren is here.
Gai,
you must help me.
This matter involves you too.
It was you who allowed me
to borrow the car.
Fine.
I'll fix the problem for you.
Ren,
well...
Cong had a little crash
when he used the car.
I'll have it fixed
in a friend's repair shop.
Ren...
Do you know why I slapped you?
Didn't I tell you
to behave these days?
But you messed with the police.
It was the traffic police.
Gai...
Not even the traffic police!
What's wrong with you for lending
a company car to your girlfriend?
You will pay
for the car repair.
How much?
But isn't it just
fixing the dented front bumper?
How could it cost 30,000 yuan?
Bro,
this is Mr. Zhou's car.
Mr. Zhou Rong's car.
Let's negotiate it.
Yes. Calculate it again.
No.
Why are you still charging for 30,000?
Hello?
[Traffic Accident Ruling]
[Specifics of the accident]
[Signatures of the parties involved:
Du Cong, Li Qian]
Hello.
Hello?
Is it Ms. Li?
I was driving the car
that you just rear-ended.
I'm Du Cong.
What's the matter?
Do you know how traffic accidents
are processed?
No.
Just tell me why you called.
I'd like to claim damages.
Claim damages?
Shouldn't you talk
to the insurance company?
Here's the thing.
That car ahead of me
ran away, didn't it?
At that time, you didn't have your ID on.
According to
the Road Traffic Safety Law
of the People's Republic of China,
you need to pay for damaging
the front bumper of my car.
It's 30,000 yuan in total.
How would you like to make the payment?
Hello?
Hey, Ms. Li.
You can't solve a problem by avoiding it.
I-It's all clearly stated in the law.
The traffic police has records
about the incident.
I don’t have that much money.
Mr. Du,
is there any other solution?
There is indeed
a solution.
Don't give her a hard time.
Plus, I think
it could be a good opportunity
for you.
I work for Rongcheng Group.
You're aware that you damaged
Mr. Zhou Rong's car, right?
Yes, I know.
Mr. Zhou
is single.
I can arrange a meeting for you
and Mr. Zhou,
in which you can own up to your mistake.
If you manage to please
Mr. Zhou,
young lady,
you won't need to pay for the car repair,
will you?
The rest of your life
will be secured.
This is a great opportunity.
I wouldn't even offer it
to my own sister.
But I'm offering it to you now.
Aren't I kind to you?
What do you say?
Thank you so much.
When the meeting is scheduled,
call me anytime.
Okay.
Mr. Guo,
are you really urging me to pay
that mere construction fee of 7 million?
I'm a man of my word.
I'll transfer it to you in a few days.
Well...
Mr. Zhou,
our money
is saved for buying bianzhong.
What should we do now?
Do you know why geese
fly south in winter?
Yes, I know.
Because walking takes too much time.
No, it's because it is too cold
in the north
when winter comes.
Planning ahead is a must. Understood?
Half of the money has been transferred to
to the Republic of St. Marlino.
The other half has been transferred
to Tuva.
It'll travel around the south hemisphere.
By the time the money gets to Okabana,
we'll be watching
the sunset at a beach in Africa.
Nothing has happened lately, has it?
Just one small thing.
Du Cong hopes to apologize to you
for it in person.
That's unnecessary.
Mr. Zhou.
Mr. Zhou, I did wrong.
I shouldn't have used a company car
without consent.
Mr. Zhou.
Mr. Zhou...
Cut it out.
Listen,
Mr. Zhou has been busy
and grumpy lately.
I happen to have some good news
for Mr. Zhou.
Perhaps it'll help him
blow off some steam.
It's a surprise.
No way.
Surprise me first.
What's the news?
Do you remember the girl
who rear-ended our car?
What's with her?
She seems to have a crush
on Mr. Zhou.
So, she asked if I could arrange a meeting
for her and Mr. Zhou.
I'd like to know
if Mr. Zhou is interested in it.
Mr. Zhou did take a few glances at her.
Those were not just glances.
He couldn't take his eyes off her at all.
I've got it all settled with that girl.
Okay.
You did a good job in this.
I'll tell Mr. Zhou the news later.
Does that girl
eat chives?
How would I know?
Just tell her not to eat chives.
Ren.
What now?
Do I still have to...
pay for the car repair?
Yes, of course.
Are you asking me
to pay for your mistake instead?
You're out of your mind.
Go away!
How annoying.
Do not let this man in again.
How are you?
I...
A-Any injuries anywhere?
Just tell me
where you're injured.
I'm not injured.
It was just a rear-end collision.
But the car I rear-ended
belongs to Rongcheng Group.
I know.
Did you tell that driver you're a cop?
No.
It happened when I was on the way
to meet Team 3.
It was really a traffic accident.
It's true!
A situation has come up.
Today, 3 cars rear-ended each other.
The driver of the car ahead has fled.
Just now, the driver of the car
in the middle,
who works for Rongcheng Group,
called and asked me for compensation.
I said I had no money.
Then he said he could arrange
a meeting for me and Zhou Rong,
after which I won't have to
pay for the damage.
A meeting?
Yes, a meeting.
How did you answer?
I-I thought it was
a good opportunity
to approach Zhou Rong.
So, I said yes.
You thought?
Didn't we tell you
the undercover plan wouldn't work?
Why did you take action
without consent again?
I didn't take action without consent.
One thing led to another.
I just had to say yes.
If you disagree with it,
I won't go meet him.
Why are we back
to the undercover plan again?
Didn't we tell you
that it'd at least
take you 3 to 5 years to gain their trust?
Chief Zhang opposed it for your own good.
He's worried about you.
I know.
Alright. Y-You go do your job.
I won't meet with Zhou Rong.
What an upstanding girl, for knowing
that she can't cross the line.
Stop talking.
Unfathomable.
You're disheartened already?
You're so lame.
You still don't know me well.
I always have my friends' backs.
How can I not help you
when you're in trouble?
I've informed
my friends
working in repair shops.
Once this coward sends his car
for repair, I'll know it right away.
Then we can get
the repair fee back, right?
Really?
We'll even extort him and make him
pay more than repair fee.
H-He will have to compensate you.
Yes, extort him.
Let's demand compensation.
I was thinking about...
What?
It's of no use now.
Gai,
I made a right decision of following you.
Cong.
You see,
sometimes, money can buy obedience,
but not loyalty.
As long as you are loyal to me,
you'll have a bright future.
Bro,
I am really starving.
There's only one blade of grass left.
The leaves are for you,
and I'll take the stalk.
What then?
Shall we just wait to die?
Why the topic of death all of a sudden?
When someone passes here,
we'll be saved, right?
It's been 3 days.
Has anyone passed by?
Someone's up there.
Wait, bro,
he can help us out, right?
Who else other than those from the court
would come here?
Even if they help us out,
will they let us go?
What for?
Grocery delivery.
Grocery delivery?
You didn't use to serve us, did you?
No, we didn't. We're newly hired.
Our company is getting started.
So the prices are low.
Yes, low prices.
Open the trunk.
-Sure.
Show him.
Yes.
[Baoku Fresh Produce Delivery Center]
Alright.
Drive the truck in.
Okay.
Open the gate.
Uncle Yifei,
no problem. Our plan is working.
[Baoku Fresh Produce]
We can proceed anytime.
Mr. Zhou,
Zhu Yifei called and scheduled
the transaction for tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Didn't we agree to postpone it?
Why did he move it up instead?
Do people in this line
of business just act at will?
He'll do as we asked.
Tomorrow, he'll bring the bianzhong over
for us to check.
If there's no problem,
we'll make the transaction.
Is the money prepared?
Contact Fang Yong then.
Have him examine the items himself.
Got it.
As long as we land on
the East New Town project,
all the problems
will be solved.
Mr. Zhou,
you've worked really hard these days.
Li Penggai is here.
Would you like to meet him?
He's been through a lot as well,
for eating dust
at the construction site for days.
He must feel bitter.
I'm sure he needs your comfort.
Is it what a boss needs to do?
But if I do it instead,
he won't feel your care for him.
Let him in.
Li Penggai, come in!
Mr. Zhou!
D-Don't kneel.
G-Give him 10,000 yuan.
No, 20,000.
Get up.
Mr. Zhou,
I don't want money.
I hope to stay around you.
I'm done working on the construction site.
I understand why you make me go there,
but I still want to stay with you
and serve you.
Why must you stick with me?
This is a reward
for your hard work.
Mr. Zhou, I really don't want any money.
All I want is to stay by your side.
I know...
among all the people around you,
Ren is only loyal one.
I want to be a second one.
As you said, Mr. Zhou,
money can buy obedience,
but not loyalty.
It sounds quite familiar.
When did you
hear me say that?
Half a year ago,
that rainy and windy night
left a deep impression on me.
Move it a bit more.
Stop!
Let me take a look.
All of you, get out.
It's almost done, Mr. Zhou.
Get out!
Now!
Where is my phone?
Did I leave it in the study?
W-Will I be scolded
if I get in there now?
Dial my number.
Do it yourself.
Bowen.
Money can buy obedience,
but not loyalty.
Among all the people
around me now, you are
the only loyal one.
Mr. Zhou knows
what's on your mind.
Here.
Take the money.
Is it appropriate?
Scram.
Fine.
Why did he bring up
what happened that day?
All of you, get out.
It's almost done, Mr. Zhou.
Get out!
Let's go.
Now!
Bowen.
How very nice.
Mr. Zhou,
I finished the task
without anyone knowing.
It was flawless.
Why did you have to kill him?
He was chief
of the Public Security Bureau.
Deputy chief.
That is no excuse!
Lu Zheng stood in your way
several times,
and picked on Ye Jian.
You said that you wanted him dead,
so that everyone would know
who's in charge of Sanjiangkou.
I was just saying it.
How could it be taken seriously?
Find something to smash the phone!
Mr. Zhou,
I took the risk of killing him
-on your order.
-What was my order?
I already killed Lu Zheng.
You have to keep your promise, right?
Come here. Give it to me!
Give it to me.
Mr. Zhou...
Burn it.
Mr. Zhou,
Lu Zheng's death is good news
to us.
From now on, in Sanjiangkou,
nobody will dare stand in your way.
Bowen,
I’ll give you what you deserve.
Just keep this matter secret,
okay?
Don't worry.
It's all been burned into ashes now.
Thanks, Mr. Zhou.
Mr. Zhou,
what is done can't be undone.
Don't overthink it.
Money can buy obedience,
but not loyalty.
Now, among all the people
around me, you are
the only loyal one.
He heard what I said to you.
Did he also hear what Lang Bowen
did to Lu Zheng?
Li Penggai definitely
doesn't know about it.
I have a bad feeling about this.
He doesn't know, Mr. Zhou.
Just be wary of him.
Got it.
Go get prepared.
No mistake is allowed
for tomorrow's transaction.
Understood.
Hu Jianren works
in the office during the day,
and attends English classes after work.
He speaks English when he
orders food and puts gas in his car.
He even listens to English
in the bathroom.
There's nothing suspicious about him.
As for Li Penggai,
he has been to all the new-builds
and 4S stores in Sanjiangkou.
The most suspicious of all
is that Malatang place.
Chief Zhang,
I got food poisoning.
Does it count as work injury?
What about you guys?
Any findings?
Chief Zhang, Captain Wang,
we can't go on like this forever.
So chatty today, aren't you?
Don't you think Chief Zhang
also knows we can't do this forever?
But what other solutions are there
except for what we're doing now?
Everyone,
you've worked really hard these days.
But our efforts
didn't go to waste.
They've paid off.
Have you ever thought about
why Zhou Rong's gang
has been so quiet
in recent days?
Silence often falls before a great war.
I believe they will
make a big move tomorrow.
Why does it have to be tomorrow?
Why can't it be...
It must be tomorrow.
I just reported to Chief Zhang
that Hu Jianren asked for leave
from his English class tomorrow.
As the saying goes,
"Feign when the enemy is weary;
wait when the enemy is hungry;
strike when the enemy is at ease."
This is what we're thinking.
I bet Zhou Rong and his fellows also think
this is what we're thinking.
So, they'll surely make a move tomorrow.
We need to send them a message
through action
that their guess
about our guess is incorrect.
The final battle is tomorrow.
Okay.
Li Qian, you don't need to take part
in tomorrow's operation.
Why?
A more important task
awaits you.
Eat up.
Mr. Zhou needs a car tomorrow
to pick up a big shot.
Is that S600 model fixed?
Yes, Bowen.
Who's the big shot?
I'll pick him up myself.
Let someone else do it.
Mr. Zhou has an important task
for you.
Okay.
T-Then let's send Du Cong to it.
Though he often takes
advantage of everything,
he's the most reliable
among all our fellows.
You handle it then.
Why did you pull up the car here?
It's blocking the way.
I left you some space there, see?
Are you...
Mr. Fang?
Why such an eye-catching car?
Picking up a big shot like you
calls for a presentable car.
Hurry and leave.
Get a move on.
I pulled up the car here
for your convenience.
How many savory crispy crepes?
Two.
Got it.
Here you are.
Thanks.
Alright. Take care.
Don't forget your soy milk.
Here you are.
Okay, bye.
I thought it was an important task.
As it turns out,
I'm only assigned to fix the car.
[No riding, dancing, singing, or gathering
in the parking lot]
[Any consequences will be on you]
[No riding, dancing, singing, or gathering
in the parking lot]
[Any consequences will be on you]
I have to hang up now.
Place the 8 large ones in this truck.
Be gentle.
Have Liu Bei carry the small one.
[Baoku Fresh Produce]
Be careful.
Here.
Boss, here you are.
Five.
Here, six.
Seven.
Come on.
Is all the stuff loaded?
Shut the rear door.
Close that door.
After I enter that place,
I'll call you.
During the entire time,
do not contact anyone.
Got it.
Repeat it then.
I must not contact anyone.
Uncle,
we're bringing only one bianzhong piece
for the buyer to check.
Is there anything odd about this buyer?
In doing business,
I never present all the goods first.
Buyers have to pay up
before examining the goods.
I'll give you your pay
once the money arrives.
In half an hour,
the piece you're holding
and the other 8 in the truck
will be gathered as a complete set
and given to the buyer.
This is my rule.
How thoughtful of you.
This is a very big deal.
There are so many connections to grease,
and so many buddies to pay.
You promised to give me 800,000 yuan.
Then how do you make money?
You think I'm doing this for money?
I've been in this line of business
my whole life.
I just can't leave it.
Time to set out!
Okay.
[Baoku Fresh Produce Delivery Center]
Drive slower.
[Baoku Fresh Produce]