(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
(Yoo Yeon Seok)
(Esom)
(Kim Kyung Nam)
(Kim Mi Kyung, Jeon Seok
Ho, Son Yeo Eun, Lee Ah Rin)
(Choi Gwang Il, Jeong
Seung Gil, Yeon Je Hyung)
(Phantom Lawyer)
(Supported by Ministry of
Culture, Sports and KOCCA)
(All people, places, and events
in this drama are fictional.)
(Child actors filmed
safely with guardians.)
(All scenes involving
animals were staged...)
(and filmed safely by welfare standards.)
Which one should I choose?
This spot looks nice. It's like a total party.
This is so tasty!
It's really beautiful.
Na Hyun, I'm having so much fun.
Me too. Anything else you want
to do? Let's do whatever you want.
- Another roller coaster ride?
- Okay, let's do it!
If I start acting strange,
I'd appreciate it if you'd
splash some water on me.
No.
Don't go.
Na Hyun.
You'll see me again.
No.
I don't believe you.
I'll
stay by your side for a good while
before I go.
I promise.
(Phantom Lawyer)
(Episode 9)
I could've done that myself.
(Passenger Seat)
Where's my sister?
Is she in this car?
Yes. I'm right here, Na Hyun.
She's sitting right behind you.
How does the possession work?
Based on my experience so far,
it happens when they find something
they really love or really hate.
But neither I nor your sister
can make it happen at will.
So if the possession doesn't happen,
I can't talk to her or touch her?
Na Hyun...
That's right.
I see.
Yi Rang...
Can you stay with me today?
It fits you well.
Come over here.
You got an electric razor as a gift, right?
Su Jeong bought that
after saving her allowance
since that day.
The court finds the defendant
guilty on the aforementioned charge.
- Therefore, this court will now...
- So Hyun?
Sentence the defendant, Baek
Hong Seo, to 15 years in prison.
It's still me, Yi Rang.
That's weird.
While his rage over his daughter's death
is an extenuating circumstance...
Is this really the show
you wanted to watch?
Yes. I died before I
could see how it ended.
- I'm just going to step out for a minute.
- Where are you going?
To buy a board game.
My sister and I used to
play Monopoly all the time.
I'll be right back.
Monopoly?
Yes.
- Six.
- A six.
One, two, three, four.
- Seoul.
- That's mine!
- What do I do?
- Pay up.
- Just pay the 2,000-dollar toll. Yes.
- It's 2,000 dollars?
One, two...
Do you have enough?
Looks like you're bankrupt.
- Give me your hand.
- Wait, why my hand?
- You must be smacked.
Fine. As long as you
two are having fun. Alright.
Hit him hard.
Another round?
Okay... If I roll doubles, I get out of jail.
Doubles.
- Eight.
- One, two, three, four
five, six, seven, eight...
- Gosh, you landed there again.
- You're on a roll! Bankrupt again.
Gosh, this is ridiculous.
Hand.
- Are you here, So Hyun?
- I told you, no.
- Move. Go back two spaces. To Paris.
- Paris.
Bankrupt.
Na Hyun.
New York is mine. That's mine.
It's 3,100 dollars.
Don't tell me you don't have it.
Your hand.
You're not really going to hit me, are you?
Come on, don't look at me like that.
That won't work on me. Here.
Wait a second!
Han Na Hyun. I'll let you
off the hook this one time.
Hey, let me see your hand for a second.
Gosh, she didn't hit
you. She really didn't.
No, she swung and missed.
Come on. That's not how it works.
You two planned this, didn't you? Right?
Honestly...
First of all, your sister
wanted to wear a hanbok
for the Palace Tour.
That's right.
My sister's life was just
school, cram school, and home.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Then...
What should we do first?
The Palace Tour... Or camping...
Sorry.
Shall we get some sleep?
No way. Time is too precious to waste.
We'll just have to deal with it. Yes.
Next up...
A college festival.
- How about we just sleep for ten minutes?
- Ten minutes?
Just for ten minutes.
Did you have a pleasant flight, Father?
- Sit in, please.
- Don't bother.
Thank you.
(Chairman Yang Byung Il)
Father, I've gathered all the
employees in the main conference room.
I made sure everyone from the
new hires to the executives is there.
It would be great if you could go
say a few words of encouragement.
They must be busy. Why bother?
Just tell them to get back to work.
- Excuse me?
- Let's just go get something to eat.
I'm so scatterbrained.
The airline food must not have
sat well. I'll take you someplace nice.
I have a place in mind, so let's go there.
Yes, sir.
- Is this the place you wanted, Father?
- Yes.
Welcome.
Mr. Yang.
How have you been, Kyung Hwa?
My goodness.
Do Kyung, say hello. Her husband,
a prosecutor, was a good friend.
This is my son.
It's nice to meet you.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
You're still a wonderful cook.
I'm glad you like it.
If you have a moment, please sit with us.
- Should I step out, Father?
- No. You should hear this.
I collapsed one year ago.
I had heart surgery, and I'm recovering.
Goodness.
Then you shouldn't be eating
something spicy and salty like this.
No, it's fine. This actually
makes me feel alive.
Going into the operating room.
I realized I might not make it out.
As my life flashed before my eyes...
And I thought of Ki Joong.
I came here to apologize.
I wasn't there for him the way
I should have been back then.
I'm truly sorry.
No. That's not true.
You went to great lengths to defend him.
And even after he passed away,
you offered to help so many times,
and I was the one who refused.
I'm the one who should be thanking you.
I was just so overwhelmed
with trying to get by.
Not at all. If only I had known sooner...
Goodness. Please, don't.
You're just making me feel worse.
So, it seems that while I was in the US,
Yi Rang applied to my company, Taebaek.
Are you aware that our interviewers
were incredibly rude to him?
(Job application form)
I'm sorry to have worried you as well.
It's my fault for failing to
manage my staff properly.
I apologize.
No, it's all right.
Yi Rang and I don't let
things like that bother
us, so please don't worry.
As for Yi Rang...
If you don't mind my asking,
where is he working now?
Yes, he's running his own small office.
Here. Please tell him to come see me.
It's not easy running a company on his own.
I'm sure there's
something I can do to help.
Bubbles!
(So Hyun's Bucket List)
(Self Photo Studio)
Say cheese!
I'll take this one.
This one's cute.
(Photo pickup)
The breeze feels so nice.
It feels amazing. It's so beautiful.
It's so windy.
(Watching the sunset
from a hot air balloon)
Can we eat this?
Down the hatch.
Awesome!
- Cheers!
(Camping under the stars)
The stars looked amazing out there.
I know, right?
But I got eaten alive by mosquitoes.
Hey, Mister.
I want to go over there.
- Really?
- What? What's she saying?
She says she wants to go over there.
We can't. She's underage.
I heard adults say what's really
on their minds when they're drunk.
I want to know what's
truly on Na Hyun's mind.
She says she just wants
to check out the vibe.
I think it'll be fine.
- Let's drink.
- Cheers.
So Hyun?
It's me.
Right. I guess not.
Here's the chicken you ordered.
This looks so good.
The wings are all yours.
Gosh, thank you.
Then you get the drumsticks, Na Hyun.
Time to dig in.
This is so good.
How come you're not eating?
I'm happy just watching you. You eat up.
Gosh, Na Hyun, you're all grown up.
See? All my hard work raising you paid off.
But how did you end up becoming a lawyer?
What happened to being a singer?
There were just too many talented people.
Na Hyun, where did all your confidence go?
There wasn't some grand reason.
I just became a lawyer because
I thought they looked cool.
There's something else I'm curious about.
What is it?
Why are you acting that
way with Mom and Dad?
- What do you mean?
- You don't answer their calls.
That's just because I've been busy.
- Really?
- It happens. Life gets busy.
I'm sorry.
Let me use the restroom.
By the way... Where's your sister?
The restroom.
Did you get to say everything
you wanted to your sister?
Yes.
I'm glad.
I'm going to step out for a bit.
Why don't you wait? We can all
leave together when she gets back.
You really can't read the room, can you?
I'm trying to give you two some space.
- What?
- I can tell by my sister's eyes.
When she's with you,
she smiles a lot.
I'm just going to step out for a bit,
so could you please
try to cheer Na Hyun up?
I didn't know I had a knack for that, but
I'll give it a shot.
Should we get some popcorn?
Yes, let's eat it during the movie.
Wait. Where did you say you were going?
- I'm going to my academy.
- Your academy?
- To my academy.
- Get a grip!
- What do you want to eat?
- Jjajangmyeon.
- Jjajangmyeon?
- Yes.
Let's get jjajangmyeon
and sweet and sour pork.
- This place is pretty good.
- There are no other Koreans here.
She isn't back yet?
She said she'd be out for a
minute, so she'll be back soon.
Na Hyun, have you ever tried an egg shot?
All right. Take an egg...
That's literally just an egg.
Fresh eggs for sale!
Get your mood-boosting eggs right here!
Where did you learn all this?
I did my homework.
Shall we toast?
- Cheers.
It's good.
Come to think of it, I
never got to thank you.
Thanks to you, Yi Rang,
I'm getting to spend this
wonderful time with my sister.
Thank you so much, Yi Rang.
You don't have to say that.
I already know.
No.
Words like, "I'm sorry,"
"Thank you," and "I love you..."
You can never say them enough.
And as time goes on, you just
wish you had said them more,
and end up with nothing but regret.
She has to go, doesn't she?
I mean So Hyun.
Does she really have to go?
All the ghosts who've come to me
have all moved on.
The Father said that's right too.
So she has to go then.
But couldn't she stay?
- She could stay here and live with me.
- I suppose she could.
But
would staying here
really be what's best for your sister?
Even if she stays, without me,
you wouldn't be able to talk to your sister,
or even see her.
For today,
we'll try spending time together,
just the two of us, without you.
Will you be okay?
Of course. We're sisters.
All right.
I'll get going, then.
Don't you worry.
Okay.
You're here, right, So Hyun?
It feels a little awkward
not being able to see you.
But it's also kind of fun.
We should set some ground rules.
When we're at the dining
table, you sit across from me.
And when we're walking
or sitting side by side,
you're on my right.
Sound good?
Okay, it's settled then.
Please proceed to your desired location.
How about America? You
always wanted to go there.
(New York: 350 dollars)
I'm going to go wash up.
- I'm home.
- You're back.
What's all this? Did we get an order?
No, I'm just putting a gift together.
Chuck flap, strip loin,
and even brisket point.
This is our top-of-the-line
A Double Plus set.
Who's this for? This is quite a gift.
Just someone I know.
(Yang Byung Il, Chairman of Taebaek)
He was the chief prosecutor
your father served under.
He came by for lunch earlier.
He apologized for not
keeping in touch all these years.
After 20 years, why all of a sudden?
Because it's been 20 years.
When you get older, regret and
self-blame just keep piling up.
I guess that's what he must be feeling now.
He said he wants to help
now, in any way he can.
And you're sending him a gift like this
- just for a few empty words?
- He's recovering from a serious illness.
Some good quality meat will
help him regain his strength.
How are you not angry, Mom?
No one showed up to Dad's funeral.
After Dad's incident, they were
cowards who only saved their own skin.
He was the only one who fought to
the end to clear your father's name.
We owe him our thanks.
Whatever. I don't like it.
Don't you ever mention him to me again.
How long have you been sitting there?
What's wrong? Did
something happen to Na Hyun?
Nothing's wrong.
It's just that.
I feel so terrible for Na Hyun.
So Hyun, you're here, right?
Yes.
I'm right here.
It feels weird not being able to see you.
But it's kind of fun too.
Me too.
We should set some ground rules.
When we're at the dining
table, you sit across from me.
And when we're walking
or sitting side by side,
you're on my right.
How does that sound?
Sounds good.
It's a deal, then?
Okay, let's do that.
(Travel Anywhere Pass)
Move to any space you want.
How about America? You
always wanted to go there.
I'm not going to America.
I want to stay by your side.
Han So Hyun's all-time favorite ice cream.
Is it good?
I'm going to go wash up.
I can't watch TV or play Monopoly.
But even so, Na Hyun
is constantly trying to do
things, worried I'll get bored.
She doesn't have to try so hard.
Seeing Na Hyun struggle because of me...
It's just too
painful.
She's not struggling.
She's anxious.
I know.
She's worried I'm going to leave her.
And that's why I can't stay here.
You know...
Being here with Na Hyun,
I've been so
incredibly happy.
So much that I wanted
to stay by her side forever.
I really did.
But after seeing Na Hyun today,
I realized I was wrong.
A life spent with a ghost...
Na Hyun needs to go
back to living a normal life.
I'm not going to do anything
else on my bucket list.
Just one more thing.
I'll do that one last thing,
and then I'll move on.
What's all this?
- Ta-da!
Presenting Han Na Hyun's
signature seaweed soup!
- What?
- My dear...
- This soup is salty.
- Salty? But I tasted it.
It's really salty, right?
Come on, you're making it so obvious.
It really is. It's way too salty, but it's good.
- Gosh, I can't eat this.
- We'd better add some water.
I guess I should go get some hot water.
I think that's the reason I'm here.
For my whole family to make up.
Okay.
If that's what you want,
then we have to do it.
But what's the best way to go about it?
Is there any food your mom
used to make that you'd like to eat?
- There is!
- What is it?
- Mom's kimchi jjigae.
- Kimchi jjigae?
Yes. It's the pork kimchi
jjigae. It's seriously the best!
Pork kimchi jjigae?
Yes. It has way more pork neck than broth.
My mouth is watering already.
That sounds delicious.
That sounds really good.
All right then.
Let's go with that, then.
I'm so happy just thinking about it.
But about that kimchi stew...
it has to have pork in it, right?
Yes. I'm telling you, it has
way more pork neck than broth.
(Mom's Kimchi Jjigae)
Mom's kimchi jjigae?
Yes. She said she forgot
to put it on her bucket list.
You'll do this for her, won't you?
Honey.
I have to tell Na Hyun.
You know that I've
been meaning to tell her,
but I couldn't.
But now, I'm going to.
Are you sure you want to do this?
I do.
The other day, you
dropped a client at that shaman's place
in the Seocho neighborhood, right?
It started that day.
I just kept thinking that I
can't let things go on like this.
(Our Na Hyun)
It's Na Hyun.
- Quick, answer it.
- Okay.
- Hello?
- Dad, is Mom home?
Your mom? Of course she's
here. Hold on, should I put her on?
- No, I'll be home in 5 minutes.
- What? In 5 minutes?
Okay.
She said she's coming over.
She'll be here in five minutes.
I'll have her pack the kimchi
jjigae. You can wait here, Yi Rang.
- I'll be right back.
- Take your time.
No, I mean, tell her to take
her time and make it delicious.
Your sister is really looking forward to it.
Okay, I will.
You can do it, Na Hyun!
Let's go inside.
Do you think it'll be okay?
I'm worried they won't
be able to talk things out.
They might push each other
away at first, but eventually
they'll come to understand each other.
That's what family is all about.
You have to have faith.
In your mom and dad, and in your sister.
I'm so happy to hear you're
craving my kimchi jjigae.
It's been forever since
we all ate together.
Hold on. I'll set the table.
No, it's fine. Just pack
it to go. I'll eat it at home.
What? You haven't been here
in ages. Stay and eat with us.
It's almost ready. Honey,
it's just about done, right?
- It is.
- I had a late lunch.
If you pack it up, I'll just
eat it at home tomorrow.
Kimchi jjigae is always
better the next day anyway.
Na Hyun.
There's something I
really need to tell you today.
Na Hyun.
I
I'm sorry.
I completely forgot I have somewhere to be.
- I'll just go, then.
- That day
in front of So Hyun's operating room.
- Oh, So Hyun...
- It's okay. It'll be okay.
Oh, Doctor!
(Operating room)
- I'm so sorry.
- What?
Doctor...
Oh, Doctor! Oh, no. My gosh, what do we do?
Oh, no!
- No! So Hyun!
- So Hyun!
No! My goodness.
No, no, this can't be happening!
- Mom...
- Oh, my goodness.
Mom.
Why? Why did you have
to take her to the show?
You could've just been in the band alone.
Why would you bring
your sister into it? Why?
I must have been out of my mind.
That's why I said those
horrible things, Na Hyun.
What are you talking about?
I don't understand what you're saying.
I'm so sorry.
You must have been the most
devastated, but instead of comforting you,
I said such unforgivable things.
And after all that...
Even though I knew how
much it was hurting you,
- I waited, hoping time would fix things.
- No.
I killed my sister.
I'm the one who killed your daughter.
Na Hyun.
So don't you ever forgive me.
It wasn't your fault.
It was...
It was never your fault, Na Hyun.
My sweet girl.
You must have been in so
much pain, all by yourself.
I... I am so sorry.
Honey.
Let's give Na Hyun
some time to process this.
I'm so sorry that.
I don't know what to say.
You don't have to say anything.
Just...
Just keep being our daughter.
That's all we need, Na Hyun.
Our sweet girl.
Thank you. For opening up to me.
Thank you so much, Na Hyun.
The words, "I'm sorry,"
"thank you," and "I love you..."
You can never say them enough.
As time goes on, you just
wish you had said them more,
and end up with nothing but regret.
- Mom.
- Yes?
I'm sorry I got mad yesterday.
This is unlike you. What's the occasion?
Someone told me
that if you don't say you're sorry,
or thankful, or that you love someone,
you'll regret it later.
Is that right?
Thank you, then.
You're a quick study, Ms. Park.
I'm already great at
saying things like that.
By the way, where's that
meat you were going to gift?
- The meat? What for?
- I'll go give it to him.
On second thought, I
don't think it was his fault.
Goodness.
You've grown up to be such a good man.
Come on in. Have a seat.
Come on in.
My mother told me
how much you did for my father.
I know it's late, but I'm truly grateful.
Think nothing of it.
In fact, I'm the one who should
apologize, though it's long overdue.
I heard my staff was very rude to
you when you applied to Taebaek.
It's all right. Please don't
give it another thought.
How would you like to
come work at Taebaek now?
I'm making you a formal offer.
Thank you for the offer, but
I'm afraid I have to decline.
I have clients who need my help.
I see. Okay.
Then how about this?
If you ever have a case that's
too difficult to handle yourself,
I'll help you out anytime.
Frankly, I'm doing this for your father.
If something like that had happened to me,
I know he would've done the same.
I understand.
I will.
You've grown into a fine man.
Your father would be so proud.
Don't tell me you're
planning to work at Taebaek.
I just don't see any reason
why we'd need to work together.
Don't worry. I'm not
going to work at Taebaek.
Smart move.
My father's just getting
soft in his old age,
but a lawyer like you
doesn't belong at Taebaek.
You got the pen, right?
The pen?
While you're busy watching my
back I'm already racing ahead.
Why don't you stop paying
so much attention to me?
What?
Na Hyun, what are you doing here?
I was waiting for you.
For me? Why?
What are you doing Saturday evening?
It's my birthday. Want to spend it with me?
Spend it together? On
your birthday? At night?
Yes. At my parents' house.
At your parents' house?
I'm thinking of making
seaweed soup for my mom.
It's something I used to do.
That's a really nice idea.
But where do I come in?
So Hyun still haven't
gotten to try the kimchi jjigae.
The pork kimchi jjigae?
If you don't mind kimchi jjigae, I
was hoping you could give me a hand.
Is there a single person in Korea
who doesn't like kimchi jjigae?
Sure.
Okay, great. This one and...
No, not that one.
Lettuce, per ill a leaves...
- The small one.
- The small one? Are you sure?
Dried yellow croaker? No?
Here you go.
It used to feel so suffocating coming here,
but I feel more at ease now.
Hey.
- Hello, sir.
- Hello.
This is Shin Yi Rang. He's a lawyer.
We're not dating or anything.
We're just colleagues.
Right, okay. I didn't say anything.
- Let's head inside.
- Okay.
- You shouldn't have brought anything.
- It's nothing.
Hey, Han Na Hyun. Don't make it too salty.
No, please, just relax. You're our guest.
It's fine.
(Alleritin: Fast-Acting Allergy Relief)
All right, here are Na Hyun's
special braised short ribs.
Gosh, this looks amazing.
- Thank you for the meal.
- All right, let's dig in.
Thank you for the food.
This is so good.
Really?
Is it good?
It's so good.
Here you go.
This is really good.
Eat up.
But seriously, we also...
Bye.
We were all teenagers
once, but you know that thing...
That special something
with teenage boys. Right?
Right? One, two, three.
Han So Hyun.
Yes, Na Hyun?
The thing is.
I became a lawyer because of you.
Na Hyun, I had a feeling you'd say that.
There's something I've
been wanting to ask you.
In your opinion,
what makes someone the best kind of lawyer?
That's my dream.
You...
You're going to be a great lawyer.
I believe in you.
My photo is here too.
(Monopoly)
(Attorney Shin Yi Rang)
Na Hyun, that Golden Key I got last time.
I'm going to use it now.
I want to go where I'm meant to be.
I'll say my goodbyes in this text.
These last few days with you
were as wonderful and fun as a picnic.
I hope you won't be sad.
Remember.
Even though I'm gone,
I'll always be in your heart.
Until the day we meet again,
take care.
Na Hyun.
I love you.
(Okcheon Building)
(Shin Yi Rang Law Office)
Thank you so much.
Wherever I go,
I'll never forget you.
- So Hyun.
- You're really
the best lawyer there is.
Having you as my lawyer
made me so, so
happy.
But
is this really the right way to leave?
I keep thinking about it,
and leaving without your
sister knowing isn't right.
I don't want to hurt Na Hyun anymore.
I know, I understand. But
being able to say your
final goodbye in person
is a true blessing.
Saying it's for Na Hyun is just an excuse.
It's because I don't think I could bear it.
I'd tell her I don't want to go.
I'd cling to her, crying
and begging to stay,
and I'm afraid I would shatter her heart.
I'm so scared.
You're right.
That was thoughtless of me.
Please take good care
of Na Hyun for me.
Please do.
So Hyun!
Where's my sister?
She can't leave yet.
Your sister's still here.
Na Hyun.
So Hyun.
Thank you for being here with me.
I've been so happy these past few days.
With these memories,
I will live a happy life from now on.
Me too.
I was happy.
Na Hyun.
It's time for me to go now.
You go on and be happy too.
And then,
in your next life, come
back as my little sister.
It'll be my turn to protect you.
You silly girl.
Listen, Han Na Hyun.
Even in our next life,
you're still my little sister.
So don't you worry about me.
Just live a happy life,
and someday,
- We'll definitely...
- Definitely
- meet again.
- Meet again.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I think I can finally let her go now.
Thank you.
So Hyun picked this out for
you. She said you'd need it.
Thank you.
I will never forget your kindness.
Come on, that's enough.
You're going to spoil me.
I never showed you the picture, did I?
A picture?
This isn't my sister. She
wouldn't be this terrified.
That was you in there, just
toughing it out for me, right?
Toughing it out? What
are you talking about?
I love roller coasters. Goodness.
In that case, do want to go again tomorrow?
What?
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
Well...
Go on. In the mood I'm in, I'd
probably say yes to anything.
Will you
be with me?
Excuse me?
Since you don't have an office,
you should share mine
until you find a new one.
And I could help you with
your work when you're busy?
That's not a bad idea.
Okay, deal.
Before we start working together,
is there anything I should know?
Mr. Ghost-Seeing Lawyer?
Well... Let me see...
It seems like you don't remember
anything when you're possessed.
That's right. I can't remember
a thing when I'm possessed.
- So I can swear at you?
- What?
(Shin Yi Rang, Han Na Hyun)
(Legal Consultation, Civil,
Criminal, and Divorce Litigation)
(Phantom Lawyer)
- What brings you here?
- It's about my late husband.
- I'm Kang Dong Sik, a shoemaker.
- He had dementia.
Gosh, my head hurts.
What was it again?
My mother insists on
following my father's will.
Then who on earth
could have written the will?
I just can't remember.
Ms. Chae Jeong Hee has verified
that the handwriting on the will is his.
There's no reason to forge the will.
That is, if the chairman's will is genuine.
- I need to say my piece.
- You really can't right now.