( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
STILL SHINING
JULY 2014
MAEUM STUDY CENTER
5:09 A.M.
Hello.
Hui-seo, you think can you walk?
Yeah.
Hui-seo, get on my back.
Hui-seo, try to stand. You can do it.
-Don't trouble your brother.
-Ma'am, it's fine.
Hui-seo.
Okay. One, two, three.
Are you feeling okay?
Sorry.
You okay?
STILL SHINING
You think you can you walk?
Goodness.
Grandma, could you move back a bit?
I'll come down.
Come over here. He said he can manage.
-I'm pretty good, right?
-Yes, well done.
I told you I'm all better now.
You don't have to worry about me.
I'm very proud of you.
Goodness. Hi, Tae-seo.
-It's good to see you.
-Have you been well?
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR GRADUATION
My medical report?
You might not be ready for school
when classes start,
so I'll submit it for you.
I'm going to school, even if I'm hurt.
You came all the way here for my sake.
I'm not a kid. I can manage just fine.
I can just take Bus 19 at the bus stop.
Hey, the bus stop!
Grandpa!
Stop! Tae-seo's going to school.
Right, your grandfather was worried
that Hui-seo would have trouble walking.
He can walk fine on crutches,
and I'll go with him to and from school.
I saw him playing soccer last summer.
I also talked with your father.
My parents both worked,
so Hui-seo always came here
during vacation.
Right. Well, you hang in there too.
The local elementary school
closed last year,
and there's been talk
about us closing too.
But Hui-seo should be able to graduate.
We don't get any transfers.
You're the first in five years.
I see.
So…
Did my documents and transcripts arrive?
I'm looking for them now.
Yes, they're all here.
And I see
this is your second transfer this year.
Why didn't you just come straight here?
My aunt said
I had to go to college in Seoul.
Living in Seoul won't guarantee that.
You didn't cause trouble there, right?
No, of course not.
Hui-seo found it hard adjusting to Seoul.
Why?
He was being bullied.
God, those awful punks.
Doing that to someone who's hurt…
I'll keep an eye on him,
so don't worry too much.
With us, all the kids aiming for college
have transferred to schools in the city.
The rest who remain here
help out with their family businesses,
so they have no pressure to study.
Anyway, let's make sure
you get your high school diploma here.
And no need to buy a uniform.
We have some
that our graduates handed down.
You should grab Hui-seo's as well.
Okay.
This one's for winter. The summer ones
are in front of the library upstairs.
They're usually inside the library,
but there's a kid named Mo Eun-a.
She's doing independent study there,
so we moved them outside.
She's the transfer from five years ago.
LIBRARY
UNIFORM DONATION BOX (SUMMER)
Hey, what on earth is this?
It got crumpled in my bag.
They're my mock exam scores
from March and June.
I thought you may need them
for college counseling.
No, the crumpling isn't the issue.
Look at this.
Top-ranked student multiple times,
all 99s for grades,
and in the highest percentile
in all major subjects.
Geez, with these grades,
you can take your pick of med schools!
You should have this framed,
not shoved into your bag.
Gosh, you're…
Gosh…
Your desk didn't arrive.
I told them a while ago.
Goodness, what a mess.
YEON CHANG-SIK
Tae-seo's here.
Gosh, good job finding your way here!
But we have a problem.
Your desk didn't arrive.
I already told him.
We should've made sure it arrived today.
It's okay, Grandma.
Right, I'll make sure
to tell them tomorrow.
Why did you have to throw out
his father's desk?
Why are you talking about his father?
I'm just saying you could've thrown it out
after the new one came.
YEONWOO HIGH SCHOOL
CLASS 3-1
The lights didn't even come on
since it's summer break, so I made a fuss.
I heard they make you do independent study
until 10:00 p.m. in Seoul,
so the least they could do
is help me study here.
So now, just the library has power,
and I can use the fans.
Turn that one on.
Which bus did you take?
The 6:12 a.m. bus.
That's the first one.
Sit wherever you like.
You can switch into study mode right away?
I need to warm up first. Don't mind me.
Let me say one thing.
Just this. I promise.
Go on.
I suddenly have time
to spend on myself now.
I was taking care of my dad…
But I won't get into that.
I just didn't want to waste this time,
so I decided to study.
I wasn't planning on going to college,
but I think I will.
I don't know what I want to become,
but I'll figure it out as I go.
I know it won't change much,
but I'm giving it a go.
What I mean is,
I was never big on studying.
Just saying.
Right.
So my point was,
that's why I need to warm up.
I move around, so bear with me.
Okay, do as you please.
The Wi-Fi password.
I downloaded some online lectures,
so I'll lend you my USB if you need them.
I'm fine.
Blue is for seniors, green for juniors,
and sophomores are…
Maybe yellow?
YEONWOO HIGH SCHOOL
MO EUN-A
You're Yeon Tae-seo.
Hui-seo's older brother.
We call your place "Hui-seo's."
Sorry.
The men's room is to the right.
What about lunch?
That's definitely gone bad.
TEACHERS' LOUNGE
I'll restock the ramyeon I eat.
Vacation's almost over anyway.
Two a day will last us just fine.
I bought plenty in case anyone dropped by.
For you and Hui-seo.
Gym uniforms are valuable,
so upperclassmen never pass them on.
They wear them forever.
These are magic shorts.
They fit in middle school and as an adult.
They always fit perfectly.
It's amazing. They're so comfy too. Look!
Hey! Come on, don't!
You startled me.
I'm just saying I'm wearing them.
Thanks for these.
Your grandma's homemade kimchi.
This is really special.
When we were trading items,
we gave Hui-seo his soccer cleats
for your sesame oil and perilla oil.
She thanked me every time she saw me
and then gave me a tub of kimchi.
This kimchi is what my dad and I
treasure the most.
Hui-seo's soccer cleats?
Yeah, last fall.
You were the one who bought them?
I told you it was a trade.
Your grandma would never know
what to get Hui-seo whenever he visited.
The shoe bag and Park Ji-sung's jersey.
They were all my idea.
She asks me for help every year.
Just for Hui-seo's gifts.
She said you didn't want any.
Eat up.
Time to catch the bus.
If you miss this one,
the next one comes in an hour and a half.
Are you coming tomorrow?
I'm in charge of opening
and closing the library.
If you take the 6:50 bus, I'll be here--
Don't worry about me.
I don't know if I'm coming tomorrow yet,
so don't worry about me.
Fine.
Aren't you going?
I came on my bike.
I waited so I could tell you the bus time.
Run! You'll miss the bus.
You can see fireflies even in the fall!
Hui-seo, I'm cold. Let's go home.
Yeon Hui-seo, listen to your mother.
We're going on ahead.
Come on!
That bug's not around in the fall.
They all die after the summer.
Hurry up.
Hey, it's a firefly!
Where?
Hey, it really is a firefly!
There's so many! Grab them!
Dad!
-Where's Hui-seo? Isn't he coming?
-I don't know. He's catching fireflies.
We grew up eating fireflies
back in the day.
-Seriously?
-You're lying.
-You ate them?
-Eating a firefly makes you electric.
Don't be silly.
-Dad is so unfunny.
-Yeah.
Does your grandpa not know
how big you are now?
He really is clueless.
It's okay.
It's nice and sturdy.
Tae-seo can study anywhere.
As long as he can sit, it's fine.
Did you walk a bit today?
Of course.
I'm fine. Look. I'll be flying around
once the cast comes off.
Just you wait and see.
What should I pack for your lunch
to take to school tomorrow?
He's not going to school, Grandma.
He has a desk now.
I want bibim-guksu for lunch tomorrow.
-Sounds great.
-I'm craving it.
This is a bit hard to open.
-Did you see me last Chuseok?
-I saw you every year.
You stopped coming
in the summer after eighth grade.
Even during Chuseok, you only stayed
briefly because you had to study.
What happened? You acted like
you weren't coming today.
I have to study.
Since when have you known me?
I moved here five years ago, so since
your last summer visit five years ago.
Why the sudden interest?
So you were nice to me
because you knew me.
I'm just saying that I get it now.
If you pick a spot and hide the key,
I'll open up if I arrive early.
No.
The school entrusted it to me,
so I need to open and close up.
You can show up whenever and just study.
The key is my responsibility.
What?
I didn't say anything.
You don't have to know someone
to be nice to them.
We're both just country kids here.
It's going to be another hot day today.
Do you want to use this?
Yeah, thanks.
-What?
It looks good on you.
Where's your bike?
I took the bus today.
I brought my bike today.
Well, I just thought I'd ride with you
and get a little exercise.
Then, go exercise.
I'm getting off.
Sir, quickly! Hurry!
I'm not getting on.
Don't you dare try to give me a ride.
Are you serious?
What's wrong?
-The weather's nice.
-Yeah.
Are you getting tired?
No.
Are you hot?
Do you want to eat ice cream?
No.
Yeah.
Try throwing it farther.
Hey, the bus is coming.
Your bag!
Your bag.
MO EUN-A
YEON TAE-SEO
It's really hot.
Hello.
-Husik.
-Husik?
That name doesn't feel right.
Chal-oksusu.
-Chal-oksoso.
-Oksusu.
-Oksosu?
-Susu.
-Oksusu.
Oksusu.
Thanks for making dinner.
Sure thing. Eat up.
Did So-hyeon leave?
Yeah, she went to Seoul
with the guests from Hawaii.
You were drinking, weren't you?
That's why I feel great.
And then you'll feel worse tomorrow.
No, I'll be fine.
You just focus on studying.
Exactly. That's what
dads are supposed to do.
Tell their children
to just study all the time.
It feels great
that I finally get to hear that now.
"What's the point of all that?
Just take it easy."
That's what you always used to say.
Just live freely.
Try living in different countries
and search for what you want to do.
As if you're on a journey.
Dad.
I've been watching this kid who's been
through a lot but is pushing forward.
It's really moving.
-Someone your age?
-Yeah.
-What a great kid.
-You're great too.
You got all better for me.
All right,
I'll become an even greater dad.
Enough.
All right, I'll stop.
I need to be a great dad.
Mom…
Mom.
Any reservations today?
No.
I guess no energy either.
Your stomach's probably empty,
so take this with the stomach medicine.
I'm just feeling a little weak
because I threw up this morning.
Go to school. Go study.
Just give me five minutes, Dad.
Take the medicine.
Okay?
Yeon Tae-seo!
Here.
-Aren't you coming to school?
-I will. Wait for me.
Dad? Dad!
Dad?
Dad!
Nothing bad happened.
I just freaked out for no reason.
I can't hear you.
Sometimes I can't hear your voice.
Tell me what you just said.
I was acting stupid,
but now, I feel calmer after seeing you.
Seeing you makes me feel at ease.
So-hyeon, what time are you coming today?
I won't be coming today.
Look at me.
Look.
You said it helps.
I know it helps.
But I need to go home right now.
I'll only get in the way
of your studying like this.
It's not good for you.
No, don't.
Go back to studying.
-Tae-seo! Goodness.
-Grandma.
I came here to buy some mosquito coils.
Let's go home together.
Goodness, who's this handsome young man?
Hello.
-Come eat with us. Come, come.
-All right.
I'll carry that.
Go say hello to everyone.
LIBRARY
Name tags?
IM A-SOL
IM JI-SOL
What are these?
I guess it's true that kids in Seoul
say they like someone by giving name tags.
When did they put those in there?
I had no idea.
Im Ji-sol, Kim Eun-su, Im A-sol.
A lot of girls with the last name "Im."
I have no idea.
No idea about what?
Who's the prettiest?
I don't know.
I know who Im Ji-sol is,
but Hyeong-seok's the one who liked her.
So you do know.
Well, she was pretty famous.
She did well in school.
So?
I have no idea.
-This is bad.
-What is?
It's stuck in my head.
I memorized their names.
It's not like that.
I really had no idea
they put those in there.
How could you not know?
When you're always tense,
you only see and hear
what's right in front of you.
Are you still tense right now?
Just explain what happened yesterday.
I was really worried.
I told you before
that I was taking care of my dad.
He had severe depression.
He even attempted suicide.
When? Did you see it happen?
I only saw him being taken away.
He got divorced and left his job.
We came nearby here on a trip.
He fell in love with the marshes,
and we moved in five years ago.
It happened that year.
Ever since then,
I get really anxious when he's by himself.
But he got a new job
just before summer break
and also started seeing someone.
If you ask me,
dating made a big difference.
My dad told me to stop hovering around him
and go do what I want.
Before that,
I hadn't even considered college.
I was going to stay and help him out.
So for the first time ever,
I considered a different future
and started studying on my own.
And then, Yeon Tae-seo appeared.
The one Im A-sol likes.
I'll stop. Sorry.
Cut it out.
Yesterday's situation happened
because my dad had changed, but I hadn't.
My dad told me
he thought he'd live with anxiety forever,
but once he saw how trivial it really was,
the anxiety vanished.
And that's exactly
what I experienced yesterday.
I went home, and nothing had happened.
I bet you're not considering
any local universities.
And I'd never get into one in Seoul.
We'll end up apart.
-You're going to Seoul, right?
-Yeah.
My grandparents and Hui-seo
are precious to me,
so I want to help them from a distance.
When I'm too close, I burn out easily.
They're precious,
so you'll distance yourself…
I never considered distance
when thinking about the future.
It's different, right?
It was still bright
at this hour yesterday.
You'll be going to Seoul.
Where will I be
and what will I be doing next summer?
When I thought about the future
all through summer break,
I'd feel good one moment
and then overwhelmed.
Then, I'd feel excited and then down…
What thoughts made you
feel good and excited?
Working like a cool professional
while wearing an employee badge.
What kind of work?
It keeps changing.
It's a teacher one moment
and then something like a therapist
or even a regular office worker.
A place with a lot of employees
and a fancy desk.
I like being around people,
so I'll take the elevator
up to the 30th or 40th floor.
And we'll all pour out for lunch.
That sounds like
it'd be a huge, competitive company.
I'm pretty good at English, okay?
And I draw vegetables well.
Yeah, you're pretty good.
I know. I'm not saying
this will get me into art school.
But I'll keep looking.
Whatever I do, I want to give it my all.
My dad keeps telling me
to just take it easy and live freely.
But I don't want to.
I'm going to hustle and give it my all.
You?
Hui-seo would always boast
and say you'd go to med school.
That's what you aim for
if you want to study hard.
I only did it to reassure my parents
who were living paycheck to paycheck.
But now, I just feel restless.
I just want to find a job
and start making money.
I'll think about how to live my life
after that happens.
Is it really possible
to think about it afterwards?
If I focus on doing
what I can do right now,
I'm sure I'll end up somewhere.
You sound like a grown-up.
Yeah, right.
I don't even have an ID card yet.
You'll succeed no matter what you do.
You're different from the rest.
I just seem different.
This was special.
I mean our situation.
It was just the two of us
studying in this huge school.
You like people,
you're good at English,
and you draw vegetables well.
I know there's a job out there
you can give your all to.
It'll work out
in ways we never imagined.
We'll know for sure what that is
once we become adults.
Where we'll be, what we'll do,
and with who…
It feels like we've been
studying together all summer,
but it's barely been a month.
It was really nice studying with you.
I felt more motivated
having someone else with me.
I guess I like you.
I'm all packed.
It's been forever!
I want to go home!
Slow down.
Hey, Kim Ji-min. Don't run!
We don't offer physics
or a second foreign language,
so you can study on your own.
Just spend the day
studying at your own pace.
Thank you, sir.
MO EUN-A
Want to play basketball later?
-What do you say?
-For a bet?
SEPTEMBER
You're walking great.
Your Achilles is fully healed.
Grandpa's waiting outside,
so take your time.
Walking like this without a cast
makes it feel real.
I'm stuck like this for life, right?
I'm scared, Tae-seo.
My right leg's fine, so I can do it all.
The doctor also said
this is nothing to worry about.
-Right, Tae-seo?
-Yeah.
When I'm all grown,
I'll be able to drive tractors and stuff.
I might be able to get rid of
the crutches soon.
When I was walking earlier…
OCTOBER
Ladies and gentlemen.
We will shortly arrive at Cheongnyangni…
We're almost at Seoul.
Let's wait at the door.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
You didn't look back even once.
-Where are you headed?
-Where you're going.
I heard you got excused
to go to a college admissions seminar.
I told them I was going as well.
It feels like I haven't seen you in ages.
I'm taking the subway.
I'm on a tight schedule.
I'm taking the subway too. What line?
-Line 2.
-Gangbyeon Station…
Isn't that close to Children's Grand Park?
I think I went there once with my mom.
All kids do at that age.
But I don't know
if it really happened or if I imagined it.
I'm not here to have fun.
What line are you taking?
Do you know the way?
Busy Yeon Tae-seo.
Get going, then.
2015 HANGUK NATIONAL UNIVERSITY
ADMISSIONS INFORMATION SESSION
I'm Yeon Tae-seo.
So-hyeon, it's me.
I'm on the subway right now.
You live near Isu Station, right?
Can I come?
Of course.
But take your time. I'm on my way as well.
Come to Unit 610 at Space Inn
on 17 Isujungang-ro.
-You're early.
-Yeah. Did you eat?
Yeah.
You're here.
Who is he?
Let's go inside.
What's the matter?
You're dating my dad.
Eun-a.
-What in the…
-You've got it wrong.
-You said you liked my dad.
-Yes.
Liking someone doesn't always mean
you can date them.
What kind of crap is that?
Your dad won't date anyone.
He's not interested in me.
HANGUK NATIONAL UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
You're all done.
The results will be ready in an hour.
You can come out now.
MAEUM STUDY CENTER
Hurry and give it. I have to go back now.
Geez, you heartless punk.
How did our teacher know
you were in Seoul?
He booked a seminar for me.
You're always getting special treatment.
I heard your mock exam score dipped.
-He said this might cheer you up.
-What is it?
FAMILY BACKGROUND SURVEY
PARENTS' DESIRED CAREER PATH FOR CHILD
"Something safe and peaceful
where he can make a living
without struggle."
There's no damage to the eardrum.
It's a temporary impairment
caused by exam stress,
and your hearing may come and go.
It should improve after the CSAT.
When did the symptoms begin?
March 3rd…
That's right after starting
your senior year.
No.
So…
It was after Hui-seo's entrance ceremony.
They were going to buy him sneakers,
so Mom and Dad…
They got in Dad's cab…
and the three of them
got into an accident.
My parents passed away,
and Hui-seo's leg…
His leg…
Hui-seo's leg…
TAE-SEO
The safety doors are closing.
-Are you still in Seoul?
-I'm not here to have fun either.
-Where are you?
-It was a big leap for me.
I didn't come here to have fun.
I tried distancing myself.
I worked up the courage for the first time
and tried stepping away from my dad.
I thought, "I might make it
if I follow Yeon Tae-seo."
I was able to come
because I thought I was going with you.
Where are you?
The stop after Isu Station.
-I have to get to Cheongnyangni Station.
-Is it Dongjak Station?
Yeah.
Dongjak Station…
The Hangang River.
It's my first time seeing it.
The Hangang River? Where?
Over there. Look closely.
I can't see anything.
I'm seeing the Hangang River
for the first time with Yeon Tae-seo.
What's your deal?
You're completely different now.
You acted like you'd never see me again.
-Earlier, I was--
-Not just earlier.
Ever since summer break ended,
you ignored me and avoided--
The tension finally wore off.
Today, just suddenly.
I know that feeling.
How it happens all of a sudden.
I've felt sick since yesterday evening,
just thinking about leaving Yeonwoo.
But the second I saw you
on the train earlier,
all that anxiety disappeared suddenly.
It's strange.
I've been studying better because of you,
and my grades have improved a little too.
I also worked up my courage.
I wonder what you are to me.
It's the word
you memorized all summer
while sighing the whole time.
Yeah.
I know.
I know it. Don't tell me.
To make possible.
That's what I am.
We'll have to
be together forever.
Let's do that.
Starting now.
STILL SHINING
Subtitle translation by: Hyesoo Lee