[Subtitles in the making and will be available soon]
This chair...
But sir,
you've been walking on the snow
behind my back
through the dark alley,
and went through countless schemes.
and took it from me.
If you lose it,
no one
can take it back
behind my back
Ting
You've won
Relax.
Have a good sleep.
Your Highness.
His Majesty is busy reading the memorials.
He doesn't have time to see you.
You should go back first.
Sir.
Am I Father's child?
Yes.
But he has many children.
But you only have
Ting's only disciple, right?
Yes
Ting
Relax
Have a good sleep.
You're finally out.
You're awake.
How is it?
Did you see the little emperor?
You didn't slap him twice?
I don't want to talk about him.
Let's go.
He's not in a good state.
Did he play tricks with you again?
That's human nature.
100 emperors
All of them are the same.
But don't think
think
in this world.
We have to
transform our blood.
Be a mortal.
Be a good person.
It's such a big living person.
I've been looking for him for so long, but I can't find him.
My lord,
That thief is a deity.
Even if we find her,
we are no match for her.
I don't know.
You can't beat her?
That's exactly why
we need to find him.
Those cultivators
pretended to cast a spell,
There's no answer.
While they are still alive,
we must find them as soon as possible.
Take my token.
to guard the city's feather guards.
Search every household.
Sir, what's going on?
It's...
Why is there a card on the street?
Yes.
A cultivator is making trouble in the city.
If we can't catch her,
the whole city will suffer.
I heard.
Isn't Fairy Xin
for Lord Lu?
She doesn't kill good people.
Yes.
Cut the crap.
One by one.
Women leave after getting the evidence.
Hurry up.
Let's go.
Pass.
Go.
Hurry up.
Stop dawdling.
That Miss Li is really pretty.
Yes.
You have good taste.
I'm a man.
The government has ordered
no closed doors for three days.
All women in the city
need the government's evidence.
The government has ordered
no closed doors for three days.
All women in the city
must be proved by the government.
The government has ordered
no closed doors for three days.
All women in the city
need the government's evidence.
In this way,
we'll find her soon.
Let's send her out of the city.
She's badly injured.
It's inconvenient to move.
Why not?
Just carry her out.
In this situation,
whether you can
or me?
Right.
In her eyes,
you're dead now.
It's not convenient.
It's such a big deal now.
With her temper,
If she knew
you pretended to be dead to lie to her,
I'm sure she'll kill you.
Where are you going?
What if they come?
Don't let them come.
Why didn't you ask them to come?
That's your business.
How is that my business?
Isn't that your wife?
Why don't you go to the palace
to find the little emperor
and kill Liang.
If he dies,
Fairy Xin can
leave the capital.
Sister.
I'm going to use a hairpin with my brother.
to get something delicious.
I'll be back soon.
Get some rest.
Just leave the white cloth.
We'll wash it later.
Be careful.
Okay.
The Liang Mansion is at the center
in the six streets of the capital.
The left is near the Imperial Guards camp.
On the right is a bustling market.
Those disciples
must be hiding in it.
If you are not careful,
they will find out.
What should I do?
enter Liang Mansion
without anyone knowing.
Let's go.
Sister, we're back.
Sister
Here.
We have meat buns today.
We want more.
Ten is cheaper than three coins.
I even brought medicine for you.
Where did you get it
I picked it up.
When did that happen
You can't give it to her.
What if it's poison
It's not poison.
It says that it can cure all diseases.
I asked someone.
Where did you pick it up?
In front of the temple.
Sister.
Are you really going to eat it?
Your face is healed.
Where else?
Is it done?
This elixir is rare.
It's good for healing.
What are you doing there?
Today is Father's 37th day.
He's coming back to see us.
So we bought some
for the ritual.
I want to give you some paper money.
What about you?
Why did you get married?
My family is gone.
I'm dying too.
I haven't married yet.
I'm afraid after I die,
after I die.
During festivals,
I can't even receive any money.
By the way,
we bought you new clothes.
Let's get it.
When I was young,
the sorcerer said
the fate of a lonely man.
will kill three husbands.
So I thought...
In that case,
I'll find a bad guy and marry him.
But I didn't expect
I found you.
Lord Lu,
You're a good person.
You shouldn't be killed by the evil.
Maybe the sorcerer
right?
If you hadn't met me,
you wouldn't have died.
Lord Lu,
I've avenged you.
I hope you can
in the underworld.
Lord Lu,
I'll take you as my father with wine.
This is for you.
You have clothes to wear in the sky.
I told you you're not an ordinary person.
I didn't expect you to hide so well.
I almost fooled him.
You came here
to help me
or give me a hard time?
If you don't,
no one will give you a hard time.
You're heartless and rude.
It's impolite not to return.
Don't underestimate me.
I
I'm very capable.
But I can eat you in one bite.
Stop meddling in this matter.
Leave the capital now.
I can spare your life.
What are you talking about?
I'm not a bad person.
I didn't mean to give her a hard time.
I'm not interested in her.
I'm very interested in you.
Young Master, you're young and handsome.
and powerful.
unlike those righteous sects.
Who are you?
What do you want?
You always stood up for that nun.
Do you have a crush on her?
What a pity.
Duke Xiang meant it, but she didn't mean it.
She's avenging her husband.
She's taken.
You
have no chance.
Don't be angry.
Whatever.
I'm not
from the righteous sects.
don’t need to follow those rules.
But let me make it clear.
I won't interfere.
not because
the story about that nun.
but because of you.
You're handsome and unforgettable.
See you next time.
Young Master.
A bunch of people who can't take the responsibility.
Nangong Guhong is leaving too.
He said his master's strings
It's rusty.
I need to change the strings for the qin.
This is ridiculous.
He has worries.
Of course he doesn't want to do anything.
It's normal.
Are you leaving too?
There's one more thing
I don't understand.
I won't leave for the time being.
Forget it.
Just wait for three more days.
If that nun still doesn't come,
I'll leave too.
They all left.
Master Zuo has left.
Master Nangong who can play flute
is packing.
Master Jiang said
there is no progress in three days.
She left with Master Nangong.
What do they think
this capital is?
You come and go whenever you want.
Always
like a fairy.
In the end,
I couldn't even find
who practices Qi.
Useless!
A bunch of losers.
Why are you looking at me?
I have the whereabouts of that witch on my face.
Go find her.
Go to the government office.
to the Supreme Court.
to guard the camp.
Get all the soldiers
who can be deployed.
Even if we turn the capital upside down,
find her.
Yes.
Is someone really helping me?
Sachet. Sachet.
Let's go over there.
Are you looking for me?
It's her.
Go!
Stop!
Stop! Stop!
Stop! Get her! Stop!
Stop!
Get her!
Catch her!
Don't let her run away.
She's a cultivator.
Cultivation?
That's amazing.
She's leaving the city.
Keep chasing.
Yes.
Are you there?
I have something to say.
Ever since I entered the mountain gate,
Master asked me to make a vow.
He said every practitioner
to enter the sect,
I must make this oath with morality.
I, Xin Tian,
I hereby swear
I'm willing to leave the secular world
and enter the Immortal Sect.
From now on, you should devote yourself to cultivation
and learn the way of heaven.
[A good start always ends.]
[Resist objections.]
I will never
with the magic of immortals.
and disturb the order of the mortal world.
If I break this oath,
my morality will be destroyed,
It's hard to ascend.
But at such critical moment,
at such critical moment.
Master said
I'm too angry.
But to be honest,
it's not that I can't control my anger.
I just don't understand something.
The stairs are destroyed.
All practitioners
can never become a god.
Then why are we
for?
Everyone in the Immortal Sect
Everyone has the power
but live in seclusion.
I can't become a god
nor a human.
We can't help each other.
Where is the end
of our cultivation?
Where is
originated from?
Senior.
If you know the answer,
can you give me some advice?
It's going to rain.
Anyway,
thank you for taking care of me.
But in the end,
I broke my promise
and caused a disaster.
Whether it's punishment or punishment,
it's all my fault.
So,
stay out of this.
in case I get you involved.
Thank you.
Don't answer it.
Just let it slip.
Anyway,
tomorrow.
Where?
Back to the old house?
Back to the county.
There are many soldiers outside.
are after you.
So we have to split up.
You have to go first.
This is for you.
Keep it safe.
You are the elder brother.
So you keep the money.
When you go back,
you're going to Tianshui Alley
to find an old man named Sun Yao.
Tell him
I asked you to find him.
He will take good care of you.
The money...
is enough for you to go to school...
and live a good life.
Then...
When will you come back?
I have an ancestral house in the county.
You can move in.
Although it's broken,
it can cover the wind and rain.
Then you'll have a home.
But sister,
I don't want to leave you.
Will you come back to see us?
Rest early.
We have to go tomorrow.
What's going on?
This flower
contains
such powerful power.
I've advanced to the Foundation Building.
Why is this flower so effective?
It's such a treasure.
Why did Lord Lu give it to me?
Does he know
the background of this flower?
Sir.
Stop! Let us out!
We have something urgent.
Go and queue up.
Hurry up.
Let's go.
She's leaving?
Everyone in the Immortal Sect
are looking for her everywhere.
If we don't leave now,
if I don't leave now.
It's best to leave.
Fairy Xin is awake.
Wait.
Raise your head and lift the curtain.
Let's go.
By the way,
a letter from Su Taiyi.
His Immortal Pill will be ready soon.
He urges you to go back to Chong Ling Valley.
Okay.
It's indeed delayed.
You go first.
I'll come to you
in a few days.
What?
meet your old lover again?
I can't hide anything from you.
Life is short.
If you don't pay attention,
fate will slip away.
You have so many fates.
Are you afraid of running away?
Whether we succeed or not,
I have to say goodbye.
I'm just doing what I started.
Okay.
I'll wait for you on the official road.
My lord.
How is it?
Any clues?
My lord.
They said
when searching the city,
we found her place.
Since we have a clue,
tell the deities as soon as possible.
Yes.
Master.
A shabby temple in the west of the city.
We found
we found the nun's clothes
and the firewood pile that has been burnt for days.
her figure and time
match her.
But it seems that she has left.
She's gone.
There's a lot of blood on his clothes.
He must be severely injured.
I also learned that
is heavily guarded.
So I ran away.
Eat slowly.
We're still a dozen miles away.
Let's go.
Let's hurry.
Go back early.
Miss, it's done.
We can go now.
Okay.
But I don't want to leave you.
Don't worry.
I'll be fine.
Have a safe trip.
How dare you come here?
You have guts.
I haven't finished my task.
I haven't killed all the people I want to kill.
How?
Six, two.
Diagram Diagram Formation.
There's no way out.
No door to earth.
The timing and place are lost.
[It's all about harmony.]
Miss,
how can you make a living?
Heaven and earth are in order.
Everything has its way.
You violated the morality.
as a cultivator,
as a cultivator.
I should have expected this.
to deal with mortals with magic.
Are you bullying the weak?
No.
Then use power to oppress the weak
and hurt your colleagues,
is not bullying the weak.
and bullying others.
In fact,
they are worse than me.
Kill!
Avenge my husband.
You're also an infatuated man.
Unfortunately,
I can’t help you
I can't help you seek revenge.
However,
I'll send you to the underworld
to reunite with your husband.
with your husband.
A word of love.
hurt others and yourself.
How pathetic.
Are you the man from the inn?
Phoenix God
Today I will present
blood and soul.
Please bless me.
and give us divine power
to open the Heavenly Eye.
Blood draws the Heavenly Eye.
Rise
The Phoenix God has
for us
We found the murderer
who killed Mr. Ghost.
Thanks to
brought by Jin Gang.
to find the murderer.
Mr. Ghost went to the capital
to deliver goods
to those big customers.
He should have taken the benefits and left.
But he was greedy.
He insisted on meddling.
and get himself killed.
Although he was wrong,
he is
Xia Xuanzi's son.
Xia Xuan Zi
is cruel and cruel.
and vengeful.
Even the Chief has to make way.
Mr. Ghost.
He's from the Bishui branch.
in Bishui Branch.
He died in the capital.
Xia Xuanzi
won't
with you.
Tatsumu King Kong is right.
Don't worry.
I will follow
the guidance of the Phoenix God
to kill that woman
and give Master Xia an explanation.
Phoenix God
has guided me
with great prestige
and invincible
Phoenix God
with great prestige
and invincible.
What are you looking for?
I'm looking for some medicine.
Jing, have you found the medicine?
Yes.
The patient's food
Make it light.
The other porridge.
Don't add salt.
As long as there are vegetables and meat.
Boil more hot water.
Okay, got it.
Don't move. Let me do it.
Let me do it.
Sir, give it to me.
Landlady what are you doing
Deliver the medicine.
That girl is injured.
If we don't apply the medicine now,
you'll get a scar.
Give it to me.
Sir, the medicine given by Mrs. Su.
Here.
Thank you.
Thank you, sir.
You gave it to me before.
You're so generous.
Only you have legs, but you run fast.
It's obvious, isn't it?
Landlady it hurts
You know it hurts? Get back to work.
Landlady
Calm down.
Have a seat.