Hey—
I’m sorry I didn't answer
your calls earlier.
Is that Naomi with Jaron?
Do you guys know
how wild the party was?
Sam here was so hyper!
She was sexy dancing with Sevi,
and Sevi was just
standing like a statue.
It’s been a while since
we all went out together.
Yanna hasn’t been around.
Do you know
what happened to her?
- Hi, girls!
- Hi, Eva!
I hate him!
What’s your problem?
Nothing!
Go, drive Eva home.
What’s your problem?
Are you jealous?
Here.
I guess
you were looking
at the wrong hand.
And about Eva—
She's just a friend.
Oh my god.
You—
You’re really unbelievable.
Wait a minute, girls.
Hi.
What’s wrong?
I think I’m drunk.
I want to go home.
Okay, I’ll drive you home.
I haven’t had that much
to drink anyway.
Okay?
What the fuck
is wrong with me?
Cy had no business kissing me
because we’re not even dating.
I can’t take it off my mind!
Let’s go?
Um...
Raylee…
Have you ever
been kissed by a guy
you're not even dating?
Oh my god!
Who the hell kissed you?
Was it Mr. Medical Student?
I knew it!
Girl, what a catch!
He’s so handsome!
I’m not happy.
It will make things
so awkward between us.
I don’t even know why he did
that!
He obviously likes you.
I mean, why would
he kiss you if he doesn't?
No way.
Why would he even like me?
We never get along,
and we’re the total
opposites of each other.
Opposites attract.
Or do you want us
to just ask him?
Raylee, we’re not even friends.
We're just strangers who
know each other.
That’s a dumb take.
I know we’re not just strangers.
But still!
Wait,
let’s get this straight—
Do you hate that he kissed you?
You know what,
hate is such a strong word.
I’m just
taken aback, I guess.
Okay,
I think you should just let
the shock die down first.
Then, after that,
you’ll know whether
you liked the kiss or not.
And Sam,
please be honest with yourself.
I mean, you're so
honest with other people, but
you seem to keep
lying to yourself.
This is making me crazy!
I can’t face Cy. Not right now!
I need to move out
of this house tonight…
…away from Clyden.
I need to think.
Everything is so
fucking confusing.
If only Yanna was here…
Hey!
Are you insane?
Suddenly barging in here.
Good thing I was already awake.
I’m sorry.
I just missed you!
Come here, you.
The baby.
Let’s go.
You can take your
things to my room.
Perfect timing, Grandma’s cooking.
Yes.
Be careful.
What’s up?
Spill the tea,
what’s going on
with your fiancé?
You know what?
He kissed me.
What?
Just a kiss? Was it good?
- Yanna!
- I’m sorry.
This is not the right time
to ask that, okay?
I’m confused.
Why did he kiss me?
Stop acting all innocent.
This isn’t your first time.
Obviously, he kissed you
because he likes you.
You're not some
free sample, you know?
But he never told me that.
And I also don’t want to assume.
It’s just that
with Clyden,
everything is uncertain.
And you?
How do you really feel
about Clyden?
I’m really not sure.
Before, I could easily—
I could easily tell if I like the guy.
But now, with Clyden,
everything’s just different.
Here’s what I think, okay?
I feel like
it’s easier for you
to admit you like others
because you know
you’re not going
to give it your all.
But with Clyden,
you’re scared to get hurt.
You’re scared of the pain
if things don’t work out.
I got it, didn’t I?
I told you.
I know you better
than you know yourself.
Sam, Yanna, come on!
Let’s eat now.
The food’s ready.
- All right.
- Okay, Grandma.
Let’s go, let’s eat.
If you’re going
to overthink about Clyden,
at least do it
with a full stomach.
Come on.
Cy usually eats breakfast
around this time.
I wonder what time
he got home last night.
Did he look for me?
I guess not.
This champorado tastes
like heaven, Grandma!
How I wish I could eat
this every day.
Not every day, okay?
You might get diabetes.
Grandma, can you share your
champorado recipe with me?
I want to try cooking it.
Sure, sure, sweetie.
It’s really easy to cook.
I’ll write it down later
and give it to you, okay?
Why?
Are you planning to cook it
for your future husband?
Why?
Do you have a boyfriend already?
No, Grandma!
I’m super single.
Don’t believe anything Yanna says.
Why not?
You’re such a pretty girl.
No one’s courting you?
Come with me to the town
dance sometime, okay?
I’ll introduce you to the
grandson of my old classmate.
Seriously, Grandma?
Stop setting Sam up!
What do you mean?
Jaime is a decent guy!
He even studied nursing in Manila.
Looks like you attract
future hospital workers, huh?
I guess you’ll never have to worry
about getting sick anymore.
Grandma, you know what?
I’ll go with you.
Good.
Don’t worry, this is safe
for the baby.
No harmful effects.
No chemicals.
Wow, thank you.
Yes.
That’s so pretty.
You could totally be a manicurist.
Of course, you still
have to look pretty!
But wait,
have you thought of
a name for the baby yet?
Not yet,
but
the due date’s still
far off anyway.
There’s still a lot of time.
Want me to ask Hiro
for name suggestions?
So how’s that kiss
from Clyden, huh?
Come on, rate the kiss.
I won’t answer that.
Come on!
Maybe
you don’t want to
remember it ‘cause
you might realize
you actually liked it, huh?
I didn’t.
Just—
I’d probably rate it
like a five out of ten.
A five out of ten,
but you can’t forget it?
Fine! Ten out of ten.
I knew it!
Just because
it feels different, okay?
But you know what?
It’s weird that he said
he doesn’t date
but he knows how to kiss.
Right? What’s that about?
You can kiss someone even
if you’re not dating them.
- You did that!
- You too.
I did that, too!
But if he really doesn’t
have any experience,
maybe he just watches porn.
Porn, really?
Maybe he likes watching
romantic comedies.
That’s it.
So vanilla.
Was he really good?
Test it again.
Maybe you’ll get
an 11 out of 10 next time.
You’re something else.
Hey, Clyden texted!
Huh? Wait—
I knew it.
You’ve been staring at your
phone for a while now.
Why don’t you go home
so you don’t have
to keep staring at it?
I’ll go home in a while,
but I’ll go straight to the condo.
I’m still not ready
to face him. Besides—
I already moved out of our house.
Really?
What if Clyden
comes to pick you up?
Are you going to say no?
He won’t.
He’s not even messaging me.
He doesn’t even know
where I am right now.
Hey, look.
You checked it!
You’re totally busted!
He’s really not thinking of me?
I know I left suddenly,
but isn’t he
worried about me?
Isn’t he affected by the kiss?
You just can’t beat this.
I’m having coffee right now.
Look, we have books here.
They’re smart. I’m smart too,
but I’m closer to God.
You can’t beat that.
There’s Eva and Cy.
Well, I guess he’s way
too busy with Eva
to even think about me.
It’s clear she totally likes him!
Why do I feel so mad?
Why am I getting jealous?
If he’s not thinking of me,
then so will I!
I can’t just sit around
and wait for him to text!
Hey, yo! What’s up, Sam?
Hey, Adi!
Remember the time when you
said you had a friend who was
interested in meeting me?
Lewis?
Is he still interested?
Can you set us up for a date?
Aren’t you with Clyden?
We’re not together, okay?
And I’m super single.
Really now?
Yes! So, please do me a favor.
I want to meet new people.
All right, here’s the deal.
I’ll give you Lewis’ number,
and you two
can just talk it out.
I don’t want to get involved.
You’re both adults. Okay?
Okay. Thanks, Adi!
You’re the best!
You know, I’m so glad that Adi
finally set us up.
Right? Yeah.
Anyway, I’ve heard you
like documentaries?
Yes.
So, I watched this
documentary last night.
It’s about how climate change
is affecting the oceans.
Did you know that
coral reefs are dying
at an alarming rate
due to ocean acidification?
It’s so heartbreaking to think about.
It really is.
I wonder if Cy’s
had dinner already.
That’s why it made me
realize something—
He tends to forget
to eat sometimes.
Reducing plastic use,
supporting sustainable brands,
and— Sa—
Sam?
You okay?
Am I boring you?
No, no. I’m listening.
I’m just a little tired.
Anyway, have you
thought about dessert?
They serve the best
tiramisu here.
- Really?
- Yeah.
That’s a bit too sweet for me.
I think ice cream is better.
- Ice cream.
- What do you think?
You know what?
Now that I think about it,
maybe ice cream is a bit better.
What flavor
do you want? Vanilla?
Vanilla! Yes. Vanilla. Exactly.
That’s exactly what
I was going to say.
I swear, you just beat me to it.
'Cause you know,
I always go for vanilla,
whether on dates
or even with my family.
It's just this—
It’s just the memories,
At this point,
he’s just agreeing
with everything I say.
I miss Cy and our little debates.
We're just not going to get along.
I don’t like you either.
He’s not afraid to challenge
me with his opinions—
even though we end up
fighting sometimes.
Sam?
Are you okay?
You’re spacing out again.
Sorry, are you saying something?
Yes, but
I was also going
to ask if, you know,
maybe you want to
grab some drinks later or—
Sorry, Lewis.
I need to go home after this.
Yeah, okay. Yeah.
You should eat.
Why are you here?
I missed you.
What?
Did you regret kissing me?
No.
That’s the best thing I did.
Then why did you kiss me?
Say it.
I like you.
I like you, Maui.
What now?
Let’s date.
For real this time.
That makeout sesh was intense.
- Definitely an 11 out of 10.
- So,
you’re still not
coming back home?
Do you want me to?
I came here to convince you.
I want you back, Maui.
I was already planning to pack
my things when I saw you.
I also want to go back.
Everything is not
the same without you.
Shit.
That was so cheesy and corny.
Why did I even say that?
So, where were you earlier?
Huh?
I had dinner.
What about you, have you eaten?
Do you want to eat something?
Who did you have dinner with?
Have you been waiting outside
my condo for a while?
Not really.
Although I did have
a hard time coming up here,
good thing Kalix
was there to help me.
Yes, Kalix!
He lives here too.
So, who did you have
dinner with, again?
He just can’t let it pass, huh?
I was with a friend.
Who’s this friend?
Lewis.
Adi’s friend.
He’s a football player
and an environmentalist.
Wait, I’ll pack my things now.
It's getting late.
So, was it a date?
- Huh?
- Was it a date?
He still can’t let it go!
It was a date.
But I don’t like the guy, okay?
So, you just came back
from a date,
and then you
kissed me afterwards?
When you put it that way,
you’re making me
sound like a player.
I just
went out with a random guy ‘cause
I thought my feelings for you
were not that serious at all.
Feelings? What feelings?
Feelings? You already know.
No, I don’t.
Fine!
I like you.
Okay?
You know what,
it’s getting late.
The rain is pouring outside,
and I’m pretty sure
we’ll get in traffic.
Okay…
So,
I think it’s best if we just
spend the night here.
Okay, if you say so.
Oh my god.
What’s going
to happen tonight?
So I got excited for nothing!
I mean, technically,
we’re engaged.
Sam?
Are you asleep?
Yes. I’m sleeping.
Did you kiss that Ruiz guy too?
It’s Lewis.
And no,
I didn’t kiss him.
I only kiss the guys
I like, okay?
Guys?
So, how many of us are there?
One, okay? And it’s you!
God, we’re engaged!
You're not even wearing your ring.
What? I always wear it.
It’s always around your neck.
You don’t wear it like this.
I didn’t know he could be
this petty when he’s jealous!
Fine.
I’m going to wear it.
See?
That’s the last kiss
you’re going to get from me.
Huh?
Why?
Because our next kiss
should be when
we’re officially together.
Good night.
So, no kiss policy while dating?
The next kiss will be when we're
officially in a relationship?
Hey,
are you free this morning?
Yes, why?
Let’s go on a breakfast date.
Sure.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Okay.
Should I wear a dress?
This one. Pink.
Or t-shirt and jeans?
It’s just a breakfast date
after all.
- You called?
- How’s my outfit?
- I’m just heading out somewhere.
- But.
He might bring me
to a fancy restaurant!
I’m torn!
Turn around.
Nice one, bro. Great outfit.
- Is it okay?
- Where are you going?
For a job interview?
Okay, bye now.
Hey! Wait up, hold on—
You know what? It’s my
first time on a breakfast date.
It’s also my first time—
going on a date in general.
I already told you,
I don’t have time to date.
So, the kiss?
Our kiss, was that
your first time too?
No.
Are you mad?
I’m just wondering
if you’re an expert player
and if you’re playing
with me right now.
No dating experience,
but you know how to kiss?
You make me sound so bad.
I’ve only kissed three women
during college.
And during med school?
Just you.
Good.
How about we get
to know each other?
What’s your favorite color?
Blue.
I knew it.
Yours is pink. Sometimes purple.
How the hell did you know that?
Because
I pay attention.
Anyway, let’s not talk about,
like, favorite colors or
favorite anything, whatever.
Let’s talk about
something interesting.
Like,
what do you even prefer?
Soft type or—
hardcore?
What?
Are you talking about sex?
I’m talking about
personality types.
Stop talking about sex.
It’s so early in the morning.
Anyway, I’m curious.
So what’s your answer?
You.
Huh?
You’re exactly my type.
By the way,
my mom called earlier.
There’s going to be
a family dinner tomorrow night.
She said that
I should bring you with me.
But if you don’t want to,
I can make an excuse.
I know how much
you dislike my family.
I’ll go with you.
I don’t want you to go to those
dreadful family dinners
alone anymore.
Cy, I appreciate you a lot.
And I like you a lot.
Sam!
- Hey!
- Hi!
Sorry if
I’m interrupting something.
Your boyfriend?
Just someone you're dating?
No.
He’s also not my boyfriend.
He is…
He is my fiancé.
Fiancé?
Yes.
Girl, it’s a long story.
Congratulations.
Oh my god, congratulations!
Thank you.
This is Nicole, by the way.
- My college friend.
- Hi.
Nicole.
- Clyden.
- Hi.
Congratulations, both of you!
You two look good together.
I’ll just go. Sorry if
I’m interrupting you guys.
- I’ll see you.
- Enjoy.
I’ll see you. Bye!
Bye!
What did you say?
Fiancé?
Why are you smiling? Just eat.
Let’s go to the grocery?
We need to replenish
our stocks.
Sure thing.
Okay. Let’s go.
There.
Fix your collar.
I knew it.
He’s dating Raylee’s sister.
This dude better not be
playing with Naomi.
Hey!
Are you okay?
Yes, I’m fine.
OMG, OMG.
Why do I feel panicky?
It’s not my first time
to hold hands with a guy!
Remember when you asked me if
I was nervous ‘cause
my hand was wet
and you couldn't stand
holding me?
Are you nervous?
Why is your hand wet? Yuck.
Okay.
That was me. I was nervous.
But I won’t let go of you now.
I got you all giddy, huh.
You ruined it. How annoying!
I’m sorry.
Let’s go grocery shopping now.
Okay.
Let’s go!
- Make sure that’s done properly, okay?
- Yes, ma’am.
Sam and Clyden are on their way.
This one. There you go.
Hi, Sam! Hi, Clyden!
I’m so glad that
you can join us tonight.
- Good evening, Auntie.
- Hi.
What a shame, your Uncle
Stephen’s not here right now because
he has an important
business meeting.
Business?
I didn’t know Senator Vera
had any business.
It's just his side venture.
You know, outside
of his political service.
You guys go upstairs first.
I’ll just fix the food,
then I’ll call you for dinner.
- Okay.
Is the food ready?
All right.
Let’s hurry up, okay?
The kids might be hungry.
So, this is my room.
I haven’t let any other guy here.
So, you’re the first one.
And I’ll be the last.
You’re deciding for me now?
Is this your best friend?
Yanna?
Yes. She’s in Nueva Ecija now.
You remember her?
I think I was drunk
when I told you about her.
I used to have my best friend,
Yanna, you know?
And she was always there for me.
Of course, she’s your best friend.
And your sister?
Aren’t you guys close?
Hi, Naomi!
How are your studies?
Why do you even care?
I don’t need you
to buy me makeup, okay?
I can ask Dad to buy me makeup.
Stop acting like
you care about me.
You don’t know
anything about me.
It’s annoying.
Please stop giving me
your hand-me-downs
like I’m a charity case.
Don’t you know
how offensive that is?
Just leave!
Please stop acting
like you care about me.
I really care about you, Naomi.
I’m sorry.
If it’s too personal,
you don’t have to answer that.
She’s actually my half-sister.
She started living
with us a few years ago
when her mom died.
I was really happy
to have her ‘cause
I grew up as an only child. And...
I’ve always wanted
to have a younger sibling.
But you know,
I’m not sure if I’m being
a good older sister to her.
She doesn’t want to talk to me
or have anything to do with me.
But I’ll never stop reaching out
and making her feel loved.
You’re already
a great sister, Maui.
I’m sure she’ll
open up to you more,
eventually.
Thanks, Cy. That means a lot.
Who gave that to you?
- That one?
- Yes.
I can’t remember.
Maybe my ex from high school.
You like teddy bears?
I’m more of a flowers
and chocolate type of girl.
It’s so pretty!
The one who gave it
must be really sweet.
They brought a bouquet to a club.
I mean, who does that?
Does what?
Those cute and sweet things.
If that were given to me,
I wouldn’t let go of it.
I remember.
Have I mentioned that before?
Yes, when we were at the bar.
When you saw my flowers--
I mean, the…
The bouquet of flowers
that was left at the bar.
Ma’am Samantha,
dinner is ready downstairs.
All right, we’ll be right there.
Let’s go!
Hi, Naomi.
What?
I like your makeup.
Dinner’s ready.
I just want to ask you
about your birthday
since it’s coming up.
Do you have any plans?
I can help you.
I don’t want to celebrate it.
Hey, why not?
We can plan a beach
party with your friends.
We have a membership at
this exclusive island resort,
and it would be fun
to fly everyone there.
Are you for real?
Are you really suggesting
I throw a beach party?
Are you that insensitive?
Naomi, I’m sorry—
She’s a mad kid.
No.
Her anger is valid.
I was insensitive.
I suggested that she have
a beach party for her birthday
when I know that her mom
died at the beach?
What was I thinking?
It’s okay.
Sam, Clyden. Dinner’s ready!
Let’s eat.
Clyden, don’t be shy, okay?
Just eat.
Yes, Auntie.
Should we call Naomi?
We should eat together.
She always eats
around 9:00 or 10:00 at night.
I don’t know. Just let her be.
You don’t call her to eat?
I tried.
Once.
She didn’t respond, so
I guess she’d rather eat alone.
I’ll call her.
Excuse me.
Mom—
you should check up on Naomi.
Maybe there’s something wrong
with how you’re treating her
that she would rather
stay inside her room
than eat dinner with you.
I really don’t care about the kid.
It’s my fault. I ruined her night.
Hey.
Are you okay?
You don’t usually go to
the veranda to hang out.
Is something wrong?
I just need some fresh air.
Why is it always
so emotionally taxing
whenever I visit
our family’s house?
I wish I could take
Naomi out of that house.
Thank you for coming
with me today, Cy.
Having you there
made the night tolerable.
I understand how you feel.
I used to dread going home
to my parents’ house.
That's why sometimes
I stay long at coffee shops
or the library,
just so I don't have to go home.
But now, I'm starting to think that
moving in was
actually a good idea.
I look forward to going home now.
Going home to you.
You were so mean to me back then.
Did you ever feel guilty after
being mean to me back then?
Yes.
I always do.
I don’t believe you.
You know what, you’re the
most sarcastic asshole
- I’ve ever met.
- Until now?
I’m treating you nicely. Come on.
I’m kidding.
You’re a warm and kind person, Cy.
And you’re the only person
in the world who
understands exactly how I feel.
Maui?
I thought you were
going to wait for—
How do you know if you’re
already falling in love?
Because I think I am.
Naomi?
Please don’t tell Sam.
Your setup’s wrong.
Let me help you.
You have to make sure
this is level.
Your camera might fall
if it’s not stable.
And make sure this part
is always secured.
Thanks. Do you take
photography too?
Sometimes.
Well, I did back in high school,
but I haven’t really
practiced since.
I see.
Your shots look good.
You just need to
tweak your aperture a bit
when taking portrait shots.
Are you mostly shooting portraits?
I like taking photos
of people smiling
because it makes me smile too.
Well, you surely have the eye for it.
You should continue taking pictures.
Well, anyway,
we’re eating downstairs.
Come join us.
I’m still full.
Okay.
Well, if you get hungry,
just come down. We’re just there.
And
you know what?
Your sister cares deeply about you.
You should give her a chance.
It will surely make her smile, too.
All right, then.
What do you want?
I want to showcase clothes.
Redefine beauty and tell stories
through fashion on a global stage.
I want to be an international model.
Do what you actually want to do.
You cooked for me?
Sam seems to be
in a good mood today.
What is this?
It’s just food.
Wow, Samantha!
You packed your lunch
for the first time?
That’s awesome!
Hey, you’re smiling from ear to ear.
How do you know if
you’re already falling in love?
Because I think I am.
Cy said, he thinks that
he's already
falling in love with me.
That’s perfect!
You’re falling in love
with each other.
I don’t know how to answer that.
Because
I haven't fallen in love yet.