But I've...
already made up my mind.
Huh?
I'm not going to run away anymore.
Are you...
still mad?
No...
I've just been thinking
about everything you've said and done.
Wait... what?
So, basically...
it's like this.
Because of your trauma from being bullied,
you were scared to fall for me,
so you went to Kanda-san for comfort.
And then?
You hated yourself for
being weak and manipulative,
and thought you weren't
good enough for me... right?
I guess... I've always had low self-esteem.
And after things went south with that guy,
I lost what little confidence I had left.
Looking back, it was
the same with my brother.
I didn't actually feel
that inferior to him,
but I forced myself to think I did.
I didn't want to hope
for anything in the future,
just so I wouldn't get
hurt like that again.
The "Akira" I see
is just a version of you that's in my head.
Even if it's just on the surface,
I feel like that's a part of who I am.
But...
I'm starting to lose
track of who I really am.
In that case,
how about I'm the one who uncovers it?
Everything about you.
Wait, what?!
Stop it. What are you imagining?
You've got a dirty mind, Akira.
I do not! I wasn't thinking about that.
What do you mean by "that"?
I told you, it's... never mind.
It's okay.
You're fine just the way you are.
Don't force yourself to change.
It's okay if you don't
know who you are yet.
Because to me,
you've always been perfectly clear.
Just stay in my shadow forever.
Kanata...
Your name has the
character for "sun" in it, right?
So you're the one who's
supposed to light up my life.
Hey, why are you crying?
I guess I'm lucky to see a
side of you no one else does.
Idiot...
Alright.
I guess that means we've made up.
Yeah...
Come on.
How long are you going to cry for?
Your face is a total mess.
Here.
"Contrast"
(Episode 8: To Stop Wandering)
Man, this really is
the best place to relax.
The construction finished
sooner than I thought.
Oh.
By the way, practice was canceled today.
Are you busy after school?
Sorry.
I have a career counseling session.
Wait a second.
Isn't your class doing
those today too, Kanata?
Is that so?
Oh, right.
I think I remember something about that.
You really need to keep
track of these things.
So, Akira.
You said you wanted to go to college.
Do you have a specific goal in mind?
Well...
I have a few top choices.
I'm looking at schools
with strong law programs.
It'll give me more career options later on.
I see...
But with your current
grades, those schools...
A recommendation will be tough.
I know...
If you're still serious about soccer,
why not try out for the
selection match next year?
The selection match?
With my skill level...
The odds are definitely against you.
And you'll be up against
the best players in the region.
But it's still worth a
shot, don't you think?
(2027 Season Selection Match Confirmed)
Thank you, Coach.
I like you.
I already know what your answer is.
But I...
I just really wanted
you to know how I feel.
Yeah.
Thank you.
I don't have those feelings for you,
but I appreciate you letting me know.
Man, this is bad.
- These are filthy.
- They really are.
I wonder if this will even come out.
Washing shoes with you like this
takes me back to elementary school.
Yeah.
I guess it does.
Hey, Kanata.
Have you decided what
you're doing after graduation?
I haven't really given it much thought.
Oh, okay.
What's up?
I was thinking...
about studying abroad.
Wait, seriously?
Yeah.
I haven't told Mom yet, though.
I see.
The coach asked me if I wanted to
try going pro.
I'm not sure yet, though.
You're going to keep playing soccer, right?
Who knows.
By the way, Kanata.
Did someone confess to you again?
Huh?
Who told you that?
Was it those guys again?
No.
I just happened to overhear you guys
talking behind the gym.
Are you serious?
Man, you're something else.
Are you the most popular
guy in school or what?
Well... she's confessed to me before.
I just had to turn her down again.
She must really like you.
I mean, I appreciate it and all.
I've never been popular,
so I wouldn't know,
but rejecting people
seems like a lot of work.
That's why
the best I can do is say,
"I appreciate you letting me know.
I see...
Man, it's freezing out here.
Can I huddle up with you?
Is that okay? Awesome.
What are you doing?
So warm.
Hmm?
So, Akira... are you and Kanata dating?
Wait, what?!
You were totally just
thinking of an excuse.
No, I wasn't...
Actually,
I've had a feeling for a while now.
Now I'm pretty much certain.
You guys were fighting around
the time of the soccer match, right?
But ever since you made up,
Kanata spends every lunch break with you.
He used to never bring you up,
but lately, he can't
stop talking about you.
What exactly is he saying...?
So?
What's the deal?
We're not...
dating...
What? Seriously?
Yeah...
Oh... but wait,
you like him too, don't you, Akira?
Well...
Yeah...
Then it's totally mutual.
One hundred percent.
Honestly, when Kanata talks about you,
he's basically just gushing.
Why don't you guys just date already?
But...
I have to study for exams and everything.
And Kanata has his club activities.
Hmm...
Isn't that for you guys to decide?
By the way, Mizuki...
Um...
Are you really okay with this?
With what?
Me and Kanata...
both being guys...
I don't see why that matters.
If anything,
I'm more annoyed that
you aren't together yet.
But then again,
even if you aren't "dating,"
as long as you're on the same page,
that's not so bad either.
You both know how the other feels, right?
Well...
Yeah...
But
we haven't actually said it out loud.
Huh? What are you waiting for?
Just say it already.
Kanata would be so happy.
No...
I feel like I've dropped
plenty of hints already.
Well... then that's Kanata's problem.
Oh, but I'm not unhappy
with how things are.
Really, I'm fine with the way we are now.
But wanting more than what you have...
isn't that what love is?
Is it?
Yeah.
Did you hear the rumor?
- Wait, what happened?
- You haven't heard?
- They say Aoyama Senpai is leaving.
- No way, seriously?
I heard he got scouted and is dropping out.
- Then what's the point of even coming?
- Right?
- Aoyama Senpai is so cool.
- I know, he's amazing.
- Ooh, I want some.
- Sure.
Yay!
Geez, what's going on?
Do you guys know where Kanata is?
- It's a confession marathon.
- Wait... what?
The rumor about him
dropping out is everywhere.
Now there's a non-stop
line of girls confessing.
Jun!
Um... do you know where he went?
Oh, I think he left early today.
He just left, so he should still be nearby.
Thank you!
Akira!
I'm going!
Go get him!
What's the assembly for?
No idea.
Club? You mean in middle school?
Why'd you just stop like that?
Sorry, sorry, I dropped my phone.
My bad.
- Oh, okay.
- What instrument did you play?
- Trumpet.
- Trumpet?!
Pretty cool, right?
- Not really.
- It's alright, I guess.
- It's okay.
- Hey, I was the section leader!
Kanata!
- Is that a BBQ bento?
- Yeah.
- Let me have a bite! Please?
- No way.
- That Salisbury steak is huge!
- Crazy, right?
You got a haircut.
It was starting to get annoying.
I didn't go too short, though.
Nice. I should probably get mine cut too.
Even if I get hurt,
or if I end up hurting someone else,
even so...
I still feel this way about you.
Kanata!
Akira?
I...
I don't want you to accept
anyone else's feelings anymore.
I want mine to be the only ones you take.
I...
I love you.
So... will you...
Akira.
I love you so much.
Be my boyfriend.
Wait...
Sorry for cutting you off.
But I'm so crazy about
you, I couldn't wait.
I won't accept anyone's feelings but yours.
I heard you were dropping out.
Oh...
That was just a rumor.
I was just going to an info session.
You see,
I want to become an athletic trainer.
So I was just looking
at vocational schools.
I have no idea how it turned into that.
Rumors are scary, huh?
But why...?
I wanted to surprise you.
Just kidding.
Actually,
I was just trying to act cool.
I didn't want to keep
relying on you for everything.
I wanted to make a decision on my own.
I see.
Will you support me?
Of course I will.
Really?
Since you called me your "sun,"
then to me, you're the "wind."
Always running free,
and taking me along with you.
Wait.
Sorry.
I couldn't help myself.
What if someone sees us?
Didn't you just shout your confession?
Honestly...
We were once blurred and uncertain,
but now we have clear outlines.
Our different colors
are slowly blending together.
To never lose sight of what's real,
and to... stop wandering.
Kanata.
What are you listening to?
That song you recommended.
Man, this brings back memories.
Here.
Thanks.
Hey.
When did you first start liking me?
Hmm...
Probably from the moment
you made me your "sun."