♪Shrugging off past burdens♪
♪Beneath the mask, who am I?♪
♪Release and find wider shores♪
♪Love's a riddle, and rain pours heavy♪
♪Crossed paths, now downward fall♪
♪From dust arises starlight's spark♪
♪Tearing through
the night's dense blockade♪
♪Heart's flame illuminates all solitude♪
♪Let time's sails drift endlessly♪
♪Through wandering exile♪
♪Breaking free from the cocoon,
I start anew♪
♪Moon as song, life as flame♪
♪Nameless heart clings fiercely♪
♪Let me♪
♪Charge toward the next raging river♪
♪Moon darts, snow falls♪
♪We tread rugged paths to reunite♪
♪Hands held tight♪
♪We forever live for love's sake♪
♪Shadow's spear burns fiercely♪
=Legend of The Female General=
=Episode 11=
Poison first, and then assassinate.
He Rufei
hasn't changed a bit.
But his attempt to kill Xiao Jue
is because of the Mingshui Battle.
He Rufei is getting desperate.
Truly like a cornered beast lashing out.
We should question
General Feihong, who supported Mingshui.
As a firsthand witness,
he should know the truth.
General Fengyun,
I immediately dispatched troops
upon receiving the distress call,
without any delay.
He Rufei,
it was you
who delayed reinforcement
and caused my father
and the Xiao Army troops
to perish tragically!
(No.)
(Upon receiving the letter,)
(I dispatched troops.)
(Why did Xiao Jue say)
(I delayed the rescue?)
Xiao Jue would never lie.
There must be something wrong.
Even the whole Mingshui Battle
might be a conspiracy,
to eliminate
General Xiao
and the Xiao Army.
(I heard General Xiao)
(often opposed Chancellor Xu in court.)
(Though Chancellor Xu appears virtuous,)
(everyone knows)
(he's vindictive.)
(This must be his doing.)
(As for He Rufei,)
(he sent Ding Yi to kill Xiao Jue.)
(Did he get involved too)
(and fear exposure?)
(It doesn't make sense.)
(Before Mingshui Battle,)
(He Rufei was still at Yuhua Temple.)
(He couldn't have interfered)
(with military matters.)
He Rufei likely feared
his identity
being exposed by Xiao Jue,
his former classmate.
Even so,
I mustn't allow him
to keep exploiting this identity
for mischief.
Wang Ba,
next time you ambush someone,
lighten your footsteps.
It...
It wasn't an ambush!
I just wanted to check
if your skills have got rusty.
Wang,
you seem
thoughtless.
Mr. Shen warned us
that He
was injured.
Why test him now?
You're thoughtless.
By the way, He Yan,
how's your injury?
Minor wound. It's healing.
It has scabbed over.
In that case,
we're taking you somewhere
as a welcome celebration.
Right.
I'll lead.
Let's go.
Commander, since He Yan has nothing
to do with He Rufei,
why keep Mr. Shen
monitoring him?
Even if he's not He Rufei's man,
he still has
questionable aspects.
We must stay vigilant.
With enemies at our door,
the Xiao Army
can't endure
another storm.
Where's He Yan
right now?
She was dragged by his peers
to a hot spring.
Mai, I can't do it!
Listen to me.
Listen to me!
My wound hasn't healed yet.
I can't do this.
He,
don't worry.
Look.
The hot spring water
is very shallow.
Only waist-deep.
Rest assured.
Your wound
will be fine.
Don't worry, okay?
- Right.
- Exactly.
We're all men.
Come down. It'll be fine.
- Exactly.
- Yeah, come on down.
- He Yan.
- Join us.
He Yan,
soaking in hot springs
is good for you.
A short soak won't hurt.
You're not a lady.
Come down quickly.
- Hurry.
Hurry down and play with us.
Come down.
- Come soak a bit.
- Come on.
No, I can't.
It feels good.
Just come down.
Don't run. Join us.
Come on.
Stop running.
I really can't do this.
- I can't...
- Hurry.
I can't. I...
Pull him down.
I can't.
Come on.
I...
I really can't. I...
Come on.
Commander.
- Commander.
Commander,
you arrived just in time.
Get up.
Commander.
Don't take him to hot springs.
Why...
Why can't we bring him along?
Yeah, why?
Why?
He's physically weak.
Physically weak?
He seems perfectly healthy to me.
Well... Um...
I...
Won't you go?
Or
do you want to go down?
Commander,
are you telling the truth?
He...
How could he be physically weak?
Exactly.
Being weak troubles him.
I wonder in what way he's weak.
Well... What...
What does
"physically weak" really mean?
Yezhou Garrison's top one,
He Yan,
is physically weak?
Is that true?
Do you know?
He Yan is physically weak.
The top one
in Yezhou Garrison?
Right.
No way.
Seriously?
Who'd believe that?
(He,)
(we pooled)
(our money)
(to buy these dishes)
(to nourish you.)
(Don't worry.)
(Every problem)
(has its solution.)
(We'll help you).
He, are you in there?
Yes.
Miss Song,
no one else is here. Get in.
Miss Song.
Did you
not sleep well last night?
Or have you faced difficulties?
He,
don't lose heart.
Don't listen to those rumors.
I'll definitely find a way
to cure you.
He,
I... I didn't mean to
touch your sore spot.
Anyway,
what I want to say is
I won't disdain you.
In my heart,
you're the true warrior
and a real hero.
He,
you can definitely be cured.
Stay strong.
M-Miss Song.
Xiao Jue, you ruined my reputation!
You ruined
my reputation!
Now the news of my inadequacy has spread
throughout Yezhou Garrison.
They all look at me
as if mourning a death.
Xiao Jue,
you must take full responsibility
for this.
Get me a single room
to have some peace.
Blaming me now?
If not for me last night,
what identity
would you use to stay
in Yezhou Garrison?
Naturally
as your personal guard.
Or
do you want me to say
I'm your
beloved?
I said I'd consider it.
You're biting the feeding...
kicking the ladder.
I don't care.
I've decided.
I'm yours now.
Treat me nicer.
Love and protect me. Okay?
I'm not leaving.
That's the partition in my tent.
Don't you want peace?
Live there
and serve as my guard.
No one will disturb you.
Really?
Thank you.
Commander, you should eat more
to nourish yourself.
I'll take my leave.
Good morning, Mr. Feinu.
M-Morning.
Commander,
what happened to him?
He wanted a single room.
I granted it.
Perhaps he's just happy
for that.
A single room?
The new recruits' camp has that?
You put him there?
Only to keep him close
can I observe his tricks better.
(Essentials of Military Strategy)
Having prepared so thoroughly,
he must've planned long ago
to watch me fall to the trap.
Com...
Xiao Jue!
That's outrageous.
Such tight security?
Strangers would
think I'm
a rake sneaking
into boudoirs at night!
Commander?
Are you asleep?
I can't sleep.
How about
we chat for a while?
Commander,
I know you don't trust me.
That's why you placed me here.
Commander,
after all,
we've shared hardships together.
Why do you still suspect me?
Commander,
I know about the enmity between
you and He Rufei.
Since his plot failed in Yezhou City,
he's surely plotting another scheme.
Commander,
rest assured.
I'll always stand by your side
and protect you.
I'm the top one of Yezhou Garrison.
One day,
you'll trust me.
Then,
we'll fight side by side,
defending our land
and our people,
so none dare threaten Wei.
Commander,
the moon tonight is breathtaking.
Care to admire it with me?
♪Constant yearning,
still vivid as our first meeting♪
♪Endless gazing.
Step by step, falling deeper♪
♪How to untangle this love,
buried deep within dreams♪
♪My heart, unyielding as stone,
remains true♪
♪Awaiting the crescent moon's
reflection in your heart♪
♪Splendor fades from your eyes♪
♪Crimson threads entwine like rings,
binding our first vow♪
♪Time lingers as you and I share
overlapping palm lines♪
♪Zither and harp
accompany our dancing dreams♪
♪The brocade moon writes our vow,
keeping this promise♪
♪Awaiting the crescent moon's
reflection in your heart♪
♪Splendor fades from your eyes♪
♪Crimson threads entwine like rings,
binding our first vow♪
♪Time lingers as you and I share
overlapping palm lines♪
♪Zither and harp
accompany our dancing dreams♪
♪The brocade moon writes our vow,
keeping this promise♪
(Account Book)
(Records of payoffs and gifts
for Chancellor Xu and his family)
Master,
I retrieved only a few copies.
I'm not sure if they're complete.
I wanted to revisit
Sun Xiangfu's room.
But Xiao Jue's sudden move
got the Sun residence sealed.
I dared not alert them further,
so I stopped looking.
Well,
I'm not blaming you.
This trip
must have been arduous.
It's my honor
to ease your burdens.
My lord, General Feihong is here.
Take him to the reception hall.
Yes, my lord.
You have a guest.
I won't disturb you further.
Zilan,
I'm old.
I don't understand young people's ways.
Some words
are better left unspoken.
My lord,
I sent assassins to Yezhou
to kill Xiao Jue
to share your burden.
But
I never expected...
My lord,
I admit my mistake.
Master,
Ding Yi
grew up with General He since childhood
like brothers.
Surely,
he'll be as reliable
as General He
and leave no traces for Xiao Jue.
Well...
That's right.
My lord, rest assured.
Ding Yi is meticulous.
He'll never give Xiao Jue
any opportunity.
Enough.
Since this matter
left no consequences,
let it end here.
Thank you.
This world
abounds with hidden talents.
But without mentors to recognize them,
they remain buried in obscurity,
unknown to all.
(General Feihong's Mansion)
Why are you still
involved with Chancellor Xu?
Don't you know...
Rufei,
since our family
has secured wealth and status,
we should withdraw while we can.
Do you think Chancellor Xu would
ever let me withdraw unscathed?
Father,
you thought his earlier neglect
meant mercy?
He was merely preparing
to sacrifice me like a pawn.
Young Master,
wasn't the ledger
given to Chancellor Xu?
Why another copy?
(Account Book)
I transcribed some crucial records.
The amount is appalling.
I never imagined Master would embezzle
so many
military provisions and funds
behind His Majesty's back.
Aconite.
Schisandra berries.
Commander,
this is the urgent news from Litai,
(Wutuo people have been)
saying Wutuo people have been
(harassing Litai lately)
harassing them lately.
Litai's magistrate
requests your military aid
to repel them.
Go to Shen Han immediately.
Have him muster 5,000 men
to assemble at the training field
at dawn tomorrow
to depart for Litai with me.
Commander, Wutuo people are fierce.
Yezhou Garrison's new recruits
won't stand against them.
Shall the battalion join us?
Yes.
And He Yan?
No need.
Get prepared first.
Have Ma Damei
watch that person.
Yes.
Commander?
Why are you here?
Why did the wound reopen?
The wound was hard to reach
and apply medicine to.
It reopened easily.
Let me do it.
As Yezhou Garrison's top one,
you've made yourself all wounded.
And you vowed to protect me?
Commander,
so you heard
everything that night?
Why didn't you
answer me?
Duties kept me busy.
No time for your antics.
Well, Commander,
let me accompany you
to Litai tomorrow.
I promised to protect you
and I won't break that vow.
Focus on recovering properly.
Or else I might
end up protecting you instead.
Fine.
Then go with peace of mind.
Yezhou Garrison has me.
Done.
Commander,
wait a moment.
I have a gift for you.
Commander,
these are osmanthus candies.
They're sweet.
Eat them on the way.
Do accept them this time.
The moon that night
was beautiful.
Commander,
are you there?
In the past,
he always loved
eating osmanthus candies.
Never mind.
At least he accepted them this time.
(Xiao Jue,)
(you must return safely.)
(And Yezhou Garrison has me.)
Good morning, Commander.
Right.
It's late.
They should've covered
half the distance by now
and be approaching Litai soon.
This must be
from Miss Song.
Where is she?
Even if He can't swallow his pride
to take my medicine,
it's fine.
I won't give up.
I've drafted a prescription.
Once I gather the herbs,
I can develop
a medicine
that enhances physical fitness.
By then,
it'll cure all his ailments.
And that
arrogant Cheng Lisu.
This time I'll
wipe off his smug look.
Someone!
Give me a hand. Hurry up!
He is seriously injured.
Instead of fussing here,
why not tend to your own wounds?
So nosy.
Given his attire,
he is from an ethnic tribe.
We should've done 60 li daily.
But we've only managed
over 20 li after half the day.
The road is too muddy.
Mr. Liang.
Hmm.
Commander,
this man says he has urgent news.
Greetings, Commander.
What is it?
When I rushed from Litai to Yezhou,
the main road 30 li ahead
had already collapsed.
It made the journey harder.
Any alternate routes?
I know
a shortcut to Litai.
It might shorten our travel.
Okay.
You lead the way then.
We'll detour and proceed.
Yes.
You go over there.
This year's plum blossoms
bloomed earlier than before.
I suppose this winter
is colder than usual.
Chu Zhao.
Are you here to see me?
I came to pay respects to Master.
Of course, I must greet you as well.
Go.
Pick those twigs
with the finest blossoms.
Give them to Mr. Chu.
Yes.
That one.
Wretch!
Can't even handle simple work!
These were meant for you,
- but she...
- It's fine.
I'll take you to the outskirts,
where plum blossoms
bloom even better.
Deal.
Don't forget it.
Pingting
has been spoiled by me.
Master,
Miss Xu's free-spirited nature
is truly enviable.
Since your return from Yezhou City,
Xiao Jue has enjoyed
uninterrupted success.
Yezhou Garrison
needs some turbulence now.
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪I've seen the mountains♪
♪And trodden through ice♪
♪Day after day, I venture alone♪
♪Destiny is my creed♪
♪Ideals surge beneath the surface♪
♪Igniting the flame against the winds♪
♪A restless yearning in my soul♪
♪Gazing through the mire♪
♪Who cares about this boundless void♪
♪Charge ahead with blazing fervor♪
♪Stubbornly fighting with my life♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪