=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 9=
(Shuozhou)
What's going on?
Come on.
Let's go take a look.
They're opening the city gate.
It hasn't opened in ages.
Exactly.
What happened?
What could be so urgent?
Is something wrong?
Li.
They're opening the city gate?
It's open.
The gate is really open.
- The General.
- General!
I have the head of Awo'erqi,
the Hulan Force leader.
We won the battle.
Long live Great Liang!
- Long live Great Liang!
- General!
General, you're amazing!
You're amazing!
General!
General, you're amazing!
You're amazing!
Long live Great Liang!
Long live our nation!
(I had always wondered)
(why the Deliverance)
(chose Duan Xu as its master.)
(At this moment,)
(I know the answer at last.)
(He has no spirit power.)
(His strong fate,)
(heaven-blessed talent,)
(and unordinary resolve)
(aren't why)
(the Deliverance chose him.)
(This sword, born of mercy,)
(can take lives and save them.)
(It came into his hands)
(because it wished to redeem him.)
(That is why it made him its master:)
(It's to cleanse the blood on his hands)
(and the hardships etched on him.)
Great news from Shuozhou.
Awo'erqi is dead.
The Chong Army has been routed.
Tabai
has successfully held Shuozhou City.
Great news for the New Year.
Great Liang prospers.
Heaven bless Great Liang.
Your Majesty, congratulations.
Your Majesty,
now that Awo'erqi is dead,
the one he strongly backed,
the 13th Prince, rose up.
The 6th Prince recalled
the Fenglai Force as well,
claiming to rescue the throne,
but truly to seize power.
Chong Court is now
in complete turmoil,
with no mind for anything else.
Once Fenglai pulls back,
Qin Huanda can soon
reclaim Yuzhou.
In the battle of Shuozhou,
Duan Xu's merit
was beyond measure.
Your Majesty,
Shuozhou is stable for now.
But the food shortage remains.
Sending provisions is urgent.
Your Majesty,
the provisions are all prepared.
The enemy has withdrawn.
Now is the best time to send them.
Very good.
Fang, handle this matter.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Physician, you...
Dress the wounds.
The General has many wounds.
His robes must be removed
before he can be treated.
That's easy. I'll do it.
You're a girl.
Move aside.
I'll do it.
- General.
- He…
Miss He, please
dress my wound.
I know a little medicine.
Let me bandage the General.
My thanks, Miss.
Why can she do it, but not me?
You may hurt him.
- The General fears pain.
- I...
Let's step outside.
Let the General rest.
Yes, you should go.
I'll stay with the General.
Your voice is too loud.
The General needs quiet.
Come on.
Since when am I loud? I...
What do you know? This...
Enough, enough.
Don't pull me.
If it hurts, just cry out.
If your throat aches,
you may forget the pain you bear.
You're quite careless.
So, you truly feel nothing.
Shall I ask Captain Meng
to take my place?
Perfect.
Then you can explain to her
how the other wounds on you
came to be.
To have you bandage my wounds
is a great honor for me.
Since you are my spell bearer,
I will not let you perish
so easily.
Aside from the stab
in Rib Fifteen,
the other wounds aren't too deep.
Thank you for your care.
Then recover as soon as you can.
Fulfill our pact with me.
Then please,
be a little gentler with me.
You asked me
to dress your wound.
And you're so picky.
Do you take me for a servant?
How would I be picky with you?
I'm begging you.
Since you know it hurts,
why risk yourself like that?
Back then,
Tabai was not yet mine.
But now,
the Tabai Army
is finally yours.
(Yueran Fragrance)
Miss Duan,
your sachet.
It has agarwood,
amber,
storax, mint leaves,
Bletilla, and benzoin in it.
The finest-grade scents.
Very nice.
In all of Nandu,
none surpasses your craft.
You flatter me, Miss Duan.
By the way, Miss Duan,
I recall you once told me
this was for Young Master Xu.
Could he have returned to Nandu?
Not yet.
It's for the Spring Festival.
If I forget him,
he'll be upset with me.
I only pray he turns peril to peace
and fulfills his long-held wish,
so he can come back soon
to reunite with us.
(Yueran Fragrance)
I have an umbrella.
Let's go home.
Move, move!
Quick, quick!
Sorry, coming through.
Make way, make way!
Go, go!
Milady, wait here for me.
I'll fetch the carriage driver.
Be careful.
Wipe over there.
Come here to avoid the rain.
Come here.
This rain came out of nowhere.
Excuse me.
(Tabai Army, Duan Xu)
The Censorial Counselor,
Fang Xianye?
After Nandu got the news,
it sent provisions to Shuozhou at once.
I just did not expect
Mr. Fang to lead the convoy.
One report for Marshal Qin,
one letter for my family.
Please send them out for me.
Yes.
No matter who brings the grain,
it eases the army and the people.
Why do you look so troubled?
I don't think Fang Xianye comes
with good intent.
Is everything ready
for the provisions?
Everything is set.
Good.
Pass the order down.
We leave tonight.
Young Master,
we're delivering grain
to Duan Xu
under Chancellor Du.
Must we rush so hard?
There's a clear order.
The grain delivery
must not be delayed.
We're already here.
Let's wait and see.
Yes.
Captain Han, what's wrong?
General,
word has just come.
Marshal Qin will be here soon.
Marshal Qin is coming.
I'm feeling unwell.
Have Commandant Wu
receive him.
Yes.
Captain Han,
any more questions?
No.
I only know
that I'm now Han Lingqiu,
Captain of Tabai Army.
I do not wish to pursue
what happened before.
You've recovered well.
You even made the trip to camp.
Even if the commander is badly hurt,
they should still visit the camp
to steady the troops.
Thanks for checking on me.
I only came to see
when you can begin
honoring our agreement.
If it's okay with you,
any time.
You're back rather late today.
I once made a promise to someone.
After Shuozhou was relieved,
I would grant him one question.
Today, he came to see me.
I was prepared to answer
all his questions.
But he seemed not to care.
Han Lingqiu?
We were in the same grade.
We barely talked.
We crossed paths most
during the Blindfolded Trial.
(Trial)
The contest was cruel.
Only one would be given
a codename to graduate.
At that time,
only Han and I were left.
He'd be defeated,
only later than the others.
I left that long scar
across his face.
When you'd kill him?
No.
I never meant to kill him.
I wanted to save him.
When I looked into his eyes,
I saw my own reflection there.
So, I used a small ruse
to make him seem dead.
I made him drink a decoction
to erase his memory,
swapped him with a corpse
bearing the same wound,
and sent him out.
Do you want to hear my story?
Last time, when I had my hand
around your throat to end you,
you would not say a word.
And now you are willing to speak?
When you meant
to end me,
of course, I'd say nothing.
But when I reached out to you,
you took my hand.
Then I knew I could say it.
In this vast world,
life in the All-Knowing
was far better than begging.
We never lacked food or clothes,
and the Priest would read
from the Aphorisms of Cangshen.
Mentor favored me greatly.
He taught me martial arts
and guided me in strategy.
For the first few months,
I was happy.
But after a few months,
our real training finally began.
Or rather,
our game of survival began.
Chong laws were strict.
My mentor oversaw the code.
The People of Liang
were punished at will.
And our training
was their chance to be free again.
At first, we were all afraid.
But soon we understood.
There,
one's kindness was
the cruelest thing to themselves.
Don't end me.
Please, don't end me.
Please.
Don't end me.
This went on
for who knows how long.
Until one day, as always,
I went on a mission.
The sunlight was harsh.
That day,
the weather was fair.
The weather today
is truly fine.
Please show
some mercy.
This is someone alive
in this world, like me.
He, too, loves fair weather.
That was when I realized
I was becoming a monster.
Again and again, I told myself:
Stay awake.
Do not kill me.
Do not become a monster.
One day, you will return to the light
and reclaim your true name,
living openly as an upright man.
When I left the All-Knowing,
I swore that one day
I would end this madness.
Then did you succeed?
You're human,
instead of a monster?
I suppose.
Just not quite a normal one.
You've been
treating yourself like an object,
hammering and mending,
patching yourself as you grew up.
All these years,
mired in such wretched muck,
you did not turn crooked.
What is normal?
What is not?
General,
little fox,
my spell bearer,
live your life,
finish your days in this world,
fulfill your wishes,
and die without worries.
This is the most normal life.
Yan,
what brings you here?
The Chong Army was routed,
with heavy losses.
Something's off with the Fusang Tree,
so I came.
You made the trip just for that?
What did you bring this time?
As expected, nothing gets past you.
I had this painted by a mortal master.
Through winter and spring,
the steadfast spirit
of pine and cypress
never changes.
As expected of a master.
Do you like it?
But lately,
I prefer plum blossom.
It braves the frost and snow,
never yielding.
Is it because
of that mortal general?
He was only a passing amusement
on my rest day.
Plum blossoms fade with ease.
They're fleeting delight.
But pine and cypress stay evergreen.
I'll keep this painting for you.
I won't disturb you any longer today.
Get some proper rest first.
I'm Duan Xu, the General!
General, welcome back!
Charge!
(Shuozhou)
Tabai is fierce as tigers!
Here, you are the General.
Xiaoxiao, you're finally here.
It is just one victory.
Is it worth all this joy?
This time is different.
We beat the Chong people
and drove them away.
Shuozhou is safe now.
How could we not be glad?
You sound like an expert
when it comes to war.
Xiaoxiao, come with me.
We can't be late.
(Victory Cake)
There is still some left.
Two Victory Cakes, please.
Coming right up.
We've had it before, right?
You want
more again?
No need, Xiaoxiao.
I have money now. I'll pay.
Where did you get it?
I earned this myself.
While you were with the General,
I ran errands
for Commandant Xia.
You used to look after me.
Now that I have money,
I'll look after you.
Here.
You eat it.
It's so sweet. Really tasty.
Put it
into your pouch.
- Thanks.
- Food!
Food from the court!
Hurry! Go look!
The General must be distributing
grain again.
Take this basket.
General,
Censorial Counselor Fang
has arrived.
Have the officers and soldiers
welcome him.
Mr. Fang's grain convoy
went around us
and distributed grain.
Everyone,
I am Fang Xianye,
Grain Commissioner.
His Majesty
ordered me to bring grain.
Shuozhou has long been at war;
provisions are running low.
His Majesty cares for the people,
so he procured grain.
Now,
the Tabai Army,
under Marshal Qin Huanda's command,
has returned in great victory.
From this day on,
with the soldiers here,
you will have grain to eat
and clothes to wear.
Distribute the grain!
It's grain!
Real grain!
Just days after the victory,
grain from Nandu arrived.
Thank you, my lord!
Thank you!
Thanks, my lord!
Thank you, my lord!
No need to rush.
There's enough for all.
Enough for everyone!
Don't crowd. Easy now.
Line up, everyone.
Don't crowd.
Easy now.
Enough for everyone!
You don't want some?
He's so annoying.
Why do you say that?
It was the General
who won the battle,
so the grain could get through.
But now,
he won't mention the General
and acts like he was the one
who saved the whole city.
General Duan,
your prize has been claimed
by someone else.
Thank you, thank you.
Line up over there.
Hold it steady.
When will it be my turn?
I...
We won the war,
and now he wins hearts.
Food for the people
matters more than anything.
Everyone gets a share.
General Duan,
I trust you've been well.
Censorial Counselor,
you came far to bring grain here.
Thank you on behalf
of Shuozhou's people.
(Clear-sighted and Astute)
You took Shuozhou by surprise
and held the city.
You're amazing.
I came to ease your burden.
So, you have another charge.
(Upright and Incorruptible)
The Ministry of Personnel
has appointed me
to take over all civil affairs.
In that case,
I will comply.
If you take over here,
what are we to do?
Report!
Marshal Qin has ordered
Tabai to withdraw
outside the city
and await further orders
once he arrives.
Outside the city?
The spring chill still lingers.
Making the soldiers camp outside now
is too harsh.
Are you behind this?
How could it be such a coincidence?
You just arrived,
and Marshal Qin's order followed.
How dare you!
You struck without orders.
That broke orders.
Marshal Qin remembers
the service you rendered
and spares you punishment.
Spares us?
I...
As Marshal Qin commanded.
Mr. Fang,
if we withdraw,
and the Chong remnants rush in,
we may not return in time.
If chaos breaks out,
it'd trouble you as well.
You're right.
The city's defenses
are indeed vital.
In that case,
before Marshal Qin arrives,
you should handle
the city's defense duty.
Then please,
govern Shuozhou for Tabai.
(Shuozhou Yamen)
General,
we just handed
Shuozhou to Fang Xianye?
General,
what a mess.
I mean, him...
I just can't accept it.
Should I let you
govern Shuozhou?
I...
Forget it.
That lad got off easy.
Hurry up.
Though that man is annoying,
we still need to eat.
Don't rush.
Make way.
Make way, thank you.
Thank you.
Give me more.
Two in my family.
Give me some.
Thank you, thank you.
Don't shove. Don't shove.
Enough for everyone.
Next.
(Lin Mansion)
This is wonderful.
We can't be late.
Yes, hurry.
Xiaoxiao...
That person
looks like Xiaoxiao.
Good thing we brought a big basket.
We can get plenty.
General!
Xiaoxiao!
Chenying,
come tonight with your sister.
We have grain now.
The victory banquet will be a feast.
For trifles like a victory banquet,
is it worth having you
handle it in person?
Not me.
Censorial Counselor Fang Xianye
came to bestow imperial rewards.
Why not?
Fair enough.
You can eat a little more.
You sound like I'm a pet you raise,
asking every day if I'm well
or fat enough,
so you can butcher and eat me.
If you think you're ready,
I could carve you up right now.
Then,
tonight,
are we having pork
or the General?
General,
does it mean that every time
we win a battle,
we get a victory banquet?
He truly adores you now.
He keeps saying
he'll be a hero like you.
You want to go to war with me?
General,
I want to fight on the field
and defend our nation
like you.
Good.
If you want to join the army,
you can drill and train with me daily.
Alright.
But...
General,
if I go there,
does that mean
I won't see Xiaoxiao again?
It doesn't matter.
We'll part ways someday anyway.
So,
Xiaoxiao,
you still don't want me,
do you?
Yes.
Chenying.
Chenying!
Aren't you going to comfort him?
Children cry for a while,
and then they're fine.
That day had to come.
Why are you pushing Chenying away?
No one can stay
with someone forever.
I care for Chenying
only for a deal
with his father.
Once the deal is done,
I will leave.
It is the same with you.
After I trade for your five senses,
I'll return to where I came from.
Can you bear it?
Mortals' lives are short.
General, mind your own path
and recover soon to honor our pact.
In a moment,
if Fang Xianye dares come,
I will send him out
on a stretcher.
- Your words?
- My words.
We all heard it,
Commandant Wu.
General Duan,
the Censorial Counselor
is tied up with state affairs,
so he could not come.
He sent me with Nandu wine
to honor the soldiers.
He truly dared not come.
Thank him for me.
- Come on.
- Come on, brothers.
We are in for a treat today.
Enjoy!
Fang Xianye knows his place.
Listen up, brothers.
This time,
the General
killed the Chong leader
by his own strength alone.
What an achievement!
Today,
it is
Tabai's victory banquet;
it's also the General's.
Everyone,
this cup of wine
is to the General.
To the General!
May Great Liang
soon reclaim the lost land
and rise anew!
May Great Liang soon reclaim
the lost land and rise anew!
Cheers!
♪Beneath war-lit walls, axes break♪
♪Gongs sound, spears rest,
and bones remain♪
♪Homes lie like tombs, bare and still♪
♪Graves guard the borderlands♪
♪Heroic souls depart♪
♪Willing to sleep through the ages♪
♪I shall return with you♪
♪With liquor on the far road♪
♪Heroic souls depart♪
♪Willing to sleep through the ages♪
♪I shall return with you♪
♪With liquor on the far road♪
♪Heroic souls depart♪
♪Willing to sleep through the ages♪
♪I shall return with you♪
♪With liquor on the far road♪
Captain Meng.
Come on. Have a drink with us.
Come on, bottoms up.
Come on, come on.
Here.
Come, come. Fill it up.
Drink it all.
Well done.
Meng Wan,
I want...
To drink with me?
You should've said so.
Fill it up.
Bottoms up.
Xia Qingsheng?
Xia Qingsheng!
Wake up, Xia Qingsheng.
Wake up.
That's all you can drink?
Captain Meng,
Commandant Xia can't hold his liquor.
- Let's drink.
- Sure.
Come on.
- Drink.
- Cheers.
Come on.
If you're free,
could you change
my dressing again?
I've sat for hours.
My wound is bleeding again.
It hurts so much.
Take my sense of touch now.
Pain is a mortal's way
of protecting themselves.
If you felt no pain,
the danger would only grow.
When cutting through foes
and facing Fifteen,
you were like a spirit with no feeling.
And now you're crying out.
I like it very much.
Like what?
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪