(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 26=
Milady, it's raining.
Wait here and take shelter.
I'll go get the carriage.
It's you.
(Yueran Fragrance)
It's another rainy day.
And I've met you again.
I'm Duan Jingyuan.
Mister,
who are you?
Greetings, Miss Duan.
I'm from a humble family
and I'm just a nobody.
My name is Fang Ji,
courtesy name Xianye.
Fang Xianye?
You...
You're the one who goes
against my father and my third brother?
I...
I've heard you are
the top scholar of Nandu.
Most of the finest essays of this era
are authored by you.
I've long heard of you.
You flatter me, Miss Duan.
My essays may shake the world...
But that's just empty talk.
(Be worthy of the world...)
(Bravery is the bone of heroism.)
Your essay
has always been the best.
(That's the spirit of heroism.)
You'll be the top scholar.
Why do you talk like my brother?
General Duan is of noble birth.
I can't compare to him.
How hypocritical.
Why is it still raining?
You don't need...
Why is there
such a deep scar on your hand?
On my way to the Capital,
I encountered bandits
and nearly lost my life.
Luckily, Duke Pei saved me
and took me in.
I got this scar
at that time.
Oh, I see.
It's not safe around here.
My third brother
encountered bandits too.
(No wonder he works for Duke Pei.)
(So this is the reason.)
(After all, Duke Pei)
(is the most terrible man.)
Miss Duan,
are you going to hold me forever?
I've heard
you have a feud with my family.
Is that true?
I'm an ordinary man.
Before my success,
I hadn't even met
your father or brother.
(This man)
(isn't as annoying)
(as I imagined.)
(Lotusborn Pavilion)
Everything's ready.
I'll just wait
for Great Ancestor's last material.
You look too old in this outfit.
Don't wear it again.
I'm the Prophet.
A prophet wears this.
This is what you asked for.
Great Ancestor,
this isn't enough.
Why did you get so little?
Oh, Great Ancestor.
Finding this stuff isn't easy.
No rush.
Great Ancestor,
I've got you a room
with a wonderful view.
You can overlook the entire city
and enjoy all the breathtaking views.
Make yourself at home
until the artifact is done.
No need.
I have somewhere to stay.
Your Lordship,
we've searched the Void,
but haven't found Bai Sanxing.
Keep searching.
Yes.
One day,
you will die
by the hand of your beloved.
(Hide in the Mortal World)
(and collect spirit aura.)
Assassin!
Protect Mr. Fang!
Catch the assassin!
- Yes!
No need to pursue.
On Duke Pei's orders,
we've come to get you.
Sorry for all that.
Please forgive us.
That was unexpected.
Let's head back now.
Don't hold up our plans.
- Yes.
(Yuzao Pleasure House)
Nice.
Hi, Ying.
The new dish today tastes good.
Then enjoy your meal.
Take your time.
Young Master Xu, it's been so long
since you returned.
Have you forgotten us?
Whatever happens,
I'll never forget you, Luoxian.
Come with me, please.
Let's go to the private room.
All right.
I'll have a good drink with you.
(Luoxian, Yuzao Pleasure House)
This floor is taken.
Keep people away.
Yes, Young Master Xu.
Your zither skills
still need improvement.
If you can't appreciate my music,
I happen to have
some martial arts.
There's no point.
You can't beat me.
Any damage in here
has to be fixed.
Your father will pay, anyway.
This is a place of business.
Is this what you wear?
Young Master,
I'm just back from a mission.
I was almost exhausted.
And it's past midnight.
If I weren't waiting for you,
I would have gone to bed.
You worked hard.
How did it go?
You may doubt my zither skills,
but you can't doubt my capability.
My assassination was successful.
But I don't understand.
You sent me to assassinate him,
but not to kill him.
Why?
Mr. Fang, in you go.
Mentor.
How did you get injured?
Go get the medicine kit.
- Yes.
- It's nothing.
How did you get injured so badly?
How could I trouble you, Mentor?
In the future,
I'll give you more guards.
You must not travel alone again
like you did today.
Oh.
Is there any lead on the assassin?
Some people want me dead
simply because
I'm in their way.
It seems Chancellor Du
has been too impatient.
He's being impatient
just because our military power
completely rests with you.
Imperial Guard Commander Meng Qiaoyan,
involved in the Southwest rebellion,
was Du's strongest force
in the army.
Later, Meng Qiaoyan
chose to step back from court disputes.
Then Chancellor Du started
to cultivate Duan Xu.
This time,
Duan Xu repelled the Chong Army.
Chancellor Du wanted
to divide the military power.
Unexpectedly, His Majesty
turned Duan Xu into a civil official.
Chancellor Du's only hope
failed as well.
So he won't just wait for his doom.
The assassination today
is also a warning.
He must have further schemes.
Put it back.
You're right.
Ever since Duan Xu returned,
Duan Chengzhang has been
secretly arranging a marriage for him.
Wang Suyi, the 3rd child
of Minister Wang of Revenue,
Lu Changling, the 5th child
of Academician Lu,
and Xie Qiuyan, the 4th child
of Prince Xie,
are all on the list.
Minister Wang holds real power
in the Minister of Revenue.
Academician Lu is the Imperial Tutor,
deeply trusted by His Majesty.
Prince Xie is an aristocrat.
These men
have always been righteous.
The support from any one of them
will have huge influence.
Chancellor Du still backs Duan Xu.
Your Lordship,
shall we press our advantage?
The fish has bitten.
I specially had my men
build a fish pond here.
So I can enjoy
the joy of fishing without leaving home.
Now I've got the first carp.
It's a sign for action.
Then please go
to the 5th Prince's Mansion.
After all,
he's old enough to get married.
Yes.
Here's what you want,
information about Wang Suyi.
Also,
a tip just came in.
After Fang Xianye was attacked,
he headed straight to the 5th Prince's.
As you expected,
Duke Pei wants the 5th Prince,
who is of marriageable age,
to steal your bride.
But I'm confused.
Why do you get yourself
a rival in love?
The 5th Prince is the right age.
He'll get married.
I'm not getting myself
a rival in love,
but eliminating a real rival.
Through contrast,
my value will be clearer,
won't it?
Fine.
Oh,
a rumor is going around in Nandu
that Young Master Xu loafs
and fools around.
Are you really getting married?
Soon, you'll know
what I'm going to do.
Aren't you going downstairs?
Many people are waiting.
Why would I need to play music myself?
Even if my fingers
were swollen,
they wouldn't understand.
A new top beauty is here today.
Otherwise,
I wouldn't have time for you.
I'd have been asleep.
Then go to sleep.
When can I go back?
Soon.
You said the same thing last time.
I'll keep my word this time.
Is this the new top beauty?
Quite impressive.
Exactly.
This top beauty is quite special.
She loves to hear stories.
(5th Prince's Mansion)
Your Highness,
Mr. Fang is here to see you.
Your Highness?
Mr. Fang is here.
Come in.
Your Highness,
Mr. Fang is here to see you.
Your Highness.
Come over.
Your Highness?
(Consort Yu)
Stop playing.
Get up now.
You won't miss out on the treasures.
Why aren't you up yet?
You don't let me out, do you?
Why can't I just play?
Fang Xianye is here.
(Han Mingxuan, 5th Prince)
Who's that?
Why is he here?
Fang Xianye
is Duke Pei's close confidant.
He came in person so late.
He must have something important to say.
That's your business.
None of my business.
Don't forget.
Your cooperation
with every move we make
is the only way
to keep things as they are.
If you no longer want a great life,
try to refuse me.
Fine.
I'll just go
and see that man.
Greetings,
Your Highness
and Your Grace.
No need for such formality, Mr. Fang.
Take a seat.
How many times have I told you?
I can't eat this thing
and it's ugly too.
Just display
the Seven Seas Dragon Pearl.
What is your purpose?
Duke Pei has a message.
Your Highness
is old enough to get married.
Did he send you
because he had
candidates for my son?
(Wang Suyi)
(Changling, Qiuyan)
Son.
So Duke Pei wants me
to marry the three of them.
Then get prepared.
I'm getting married tomorrow.
Their fathers are important officials
who have been neutral.
Marrying a prince will get them involved
in the fight for the throne.
How would they agree easily?
Your Grace,
you just follow Duke Pei's instructions.
Then he'll spare no effort
to support your son.
Since the message is delivered,
I'll take my leave.
Mr. Fang.
Please tell Duke Pei.
Hope he won't forget
his promise to my son and me.
I'll tell him.
(Yuzao Pleasure House)
Wine.
I want wine.
Come here.
The new top beauty
wants to hear stories, doesn't she?
What...
What are they doing here?
Sir,
you have no idea.
Way too many men want
to see the top beauty.
So we have this new rule.
No one can go up unless he finishes
three jars of strong wine
within about half an hour.
That much?
When someone's drunk,
how can he tell a story?
I don't know.
This is her request.
Then tell me.
What kind of stories
does she love to hear?
She loves
to hear stories
about separated couples,
mismatched sweethearts,
and unattainable love.
Anyway,
it's about love and hatred.
Waiter, another jar of wine!
Be right there!
Gentlemen, help yourselves.
Let's go.
Let's go up there.
Come on.
Wait. Wait for me.
I'm not finished yet.
My Lady,
let me continue.
My Lady!
Go away.
Get lost.
Get out of my way.
My turn.
Don't jump the queue!
My turn!
It's my turn.
He cut in line.
He...
- I'll go.
- How come?
Miss He,
I am...
Welcome, sir.
Take a seat.
All right.
Sir,
please tell your story.
Miss He,
I'm Chen.
I'm 28 years old.
I live...
I live in the three-sided courtyard
near the city gate.
Do you know that?
Next.
When will it be my turn?
There he is.
Look at him.
Next!
Pick me! Pick me!
Welcome, sir.
Take a seat.
Go away.
Sir,
please tell your story.
Here I am.
Greetings, Mentor.
Fang Ji,
your recent essays
have impressed those
in the Censorate.
They must have spoken favorably
just for your sake.
Don't be so modest.
Consort Yu
wants to hold a palace banquet.
During that,
she'll request His Majesty
for her son's marriage.
So you want him
to seize the advantage
and steal Duan Xu's candidates,
leaving him with no one to marry.
You'll also go to the banquet.
The 5th Prince is unpredictable.
Only when you're there
will I feel truly reassured.
I understand.
(Yuzao Pleasure House)
Great Ancestor.
Where are you?
Your outfit looks great.
I'm so bored
that I act as a top beauty.
This place is interesting.
But people here
have very few obsessions.
I've just collected so little.
Mortals' obsessions are the most vivid.
You need strong obsessions to make
the magical artifact you want.
This amount
is far from enough.
If it goes on like this,
who knows how long
I'll have to wait.
People in the royal palace
have deep obsessions, don't they?
Oh, that's right.
Consort Yu will hold a banquet.
We can go check out the palace.
Banquet?
Consort Yu will hold a banquet.
Marriageable royal relatives
and nobles were invited.
If they fall for each other,
the marriage will be settled.
It's actually
a wife selection for the 5th Prince.
Great Ancestor,
why don't we go check there?
Perhaps,
you'll meet the mortal you want.
Good idea.
(Erudite and Determined)
Xu, I'm coming in.
Consort Yu will hold a banquet.
Father asked you to go.
He also said
the girls he chose for you
would also be there.
You should make a good impression.
Father didn't tell you?
Maybe he was too forgetful
to bring that up.
Xu,
do you
not like to stay in this city?
I always feel
something's bothering you.
Don't worry about me.
I have things to do here.
Father may get you blind dates too.
I'm having bad luck today.
I can't shoot straight.
You're right.
Watch this. Two arrows at a time.
I hit it.
- Impressive.
- So steady.
(Lu Changling)
I heard the Duan clan also sent you
a visit request.
Yeah.
(Xie Qiuyan)
They not only sent it to me,
but also Miss Wang.
(Wang Suyi)
Young Master Xu is good.
He's a handsome scholar and warrior.
How could anyone not like him?
Sadly, he has fallen from power.
Now he only has a fifth-rank sinecure
and a bleak future.
Now he probably needs a wife
to regain power
with her family's influence.
I don't want to take that risk.
That's Duan Xu
who retook three northern cities.
What a pity.
He was demoted.
Chancellor Du's camp
has lost its influence in the army.
Duan Xu's family
can hardly regain power.
(Wang Qi, legitimate son
of the Minister of Revenue)
That's difficult.
I wondered which gossipmonger
was spreading rumors here.
Turns out it's Minister Wang's son.
Meng!
He...
Why did he run away?
Wan?
Xu,
ignore those dandies.
It's my father's fault.
Ever since I came back here,
he has been urging me
to have blind dates.
He also said,
"Fighting in battle is useless.
You'll get married anyway."
I nearly slapped him.
Don't listen to him, Meng.
If you want to fight, then go.
Maybe
you'll be the first lady general
of our nation.
Right?
I haven't thought about that yet.
There's never been a lady general.
Wan,
maybe you'll be the first.
Mr. Fang is here.
He's Duke Pei's pupil.
Look.
So that is Mr. Fang.
Mr. Fang.
- Yeah.
- Mr. Fang.
Xu,
it's Fang Xianye again.
Mr. Fang.
- Mr. Fang.
Consort Yu is here.
Greetings, Your Grace.
- Prophet.
How I wish I could take off your mask.
You have no taste, Great Ancestor.
My peerless face
has fascinated countless women.
Spiritual energy.
A spirit is here.
It's coming this way, I think.
Great Ancestor,
my body reacts badly
to all spirits but you.
You go first.
I'll look around.
Your Highness,
come with me, please.
There's quite a crowd here today.
Young ladies and gentlemen in town
are gathering here.
Even the Prophet has come.
I'm so delighted.
Make yourselves at home.
If you find it boring,
you can walk around
in the garden of Linhua Palace.
- Yes.
Your Grace.
Cheers, General Duan.
How come he shielded my detection?
Come on, ladies.
Here you are.
It tastes great.
I'm too weak to sit for long.
I want to take a walk.
Please forgive me.
As you wish, Prophet.
Great Ancestor.
Shortly after you left,
the red spots on me
all faded away.
Have you caught him?
What's he look like?
He escaped.
Escaped?
He did that
right under your nose?
When I got there,
he had escaped.
I used my power to detect,
but didn't find any trace.
How did that happen?
It doesn't make sense.
He managed to shield your detection.
Could it be...?
It's Song Xingyu.
Only the Glazed Pagoda
he has been holding
can shield your detection.
It seems you aren't
a very powerful prophet.
He's been in the palace,
but you haven't noticed.
Even you can't find him.
Don't give me a hard time.
Take out your magical artifact
to track spirits.
I've set a formation here.
Once he appears,
I'll know.
Then...
You go on to search for obsessions.
I'll take my leave.
Sadly, my son
is too busy to come today.
Why don't the three of you stay here
and have dinner with me?
By then, Mingxuan will be back.
I believe he also wants
to meet you.
It's my honor
to have dinner with you
and His Highness.
The honor is mine too.
I was away for too long.
Since I came back,
I haven't greeted you privately.
Young Master Xu,
you're a man of charm.
It's so kind of you
to say that.
You flatter me, Your Grace.
I've heard
the garden in your palace
was exquisitely crafted
by folk craftsmen.
Miss Wang.
Would you like to go
and appreciate it with me?
Your Grace,
I'm also curious.
Please approve.
I won't force you to stay then.
You may leave.
Thank you, Your Grace.
This banquet
is so boring.
I'll sneak out soon
and leave you alone.
Go find the person
with the strongest obsession.
Thank you.
No, no.
How are your parents?
They're very well.
Thank you for caring.
Come on, let's have a toast.
Yes, Your Grace.
Your art is impressive.
I can't compare.
Don't be so modest.
Your needlework
is far beyond my reach.
Come to my home someday
and we can practice.
All right.
Thank you
for helping me out.
After all,
your awkward situation
was my fault.
I'm the one
who should apologize.
Born in this kind of family,
you and I have no choice.
We're both pawns.
Let's not apologize for that.
Miss Wang,
don't be too pessimistic.
Life is a chessboard.
We're either a pawn
or a player.
I believe
when we control the game,
success or failure
will lie in a decision we make.
Miss Wang.
- Watch out!
- Look out!
Are you all right?
Yes.
Thank you, Mr. Fang.
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪