(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
To make Bloody Week more exciting
look inside your lockers.
You'll find the names you have to kill
before the time runs out.
If you don't get a name
you are chosen to die.
Mia!
- Mia?
- Mia!
Mia!
Jerome, I know you.
You're not capable of killing anyone.
You just defended yourself.
You didn't do anything wrong.
This is an emergency.
Open the door!
I'm sorry but
this is an order from
the headmistress.
Open the clinic!
If I were you
I'll use my courage elsewhere.
Not for this menial reason.
I hope
she was worth it.
It's Mia's life.
Just tell me my punishment.
Death.
Tonight.
I will introduce to all of you
the new co-leader of the
Black Blood Gang...
Raise your voices
for Matthew!
Well, well, well...
We have a visitor, boss.
He said he won't leave
until he talks with you.
Wait.
Did you really give this
arrogant ass a chance?
And you allowed him
to enter our hideout?
Show him out.
What do you need?
I'm here to talk to you.
I want to join your gang.
Do you think it's easy to join our gang?
That you'll just sign an attendance
and you’re magically a member?
I hope you can forgive my
boys for greeting you harshly.
Why are you here again?
I want to join the Black Blood Gang.
Why not?
We need as many
members as we can get.
I say...
let's give him a chance.
Matthew Hart.
I commend your courage
coming here on your own.
Specially during Bloody Night.
I want to know your reason.
Oh?
Why did you become so quiet?
Fine
let's make it more simple.
In one word
what do you want
that we can offer?
Power.
But power is not given.
It should be earned.
Well, well, well...
you know
all of us did our own
fair share of bloodshed
before we got accepted here.
What I want to say is
you need to defeat me
but of course
don't cry if you lose, alright?
You need to defeat Luke
before you get the chance to be
a member of this brotherhood.
Luke will not go easy on you.
What now?
Are you scared already?
Do you want to go back to your dorm?
One more word from you
and your hair will not be the
only thing that'll be red tonight.
- Ooh.
- Okay.
Move, guys.
Luke, don't embarrass us.
Show him how it's done, Luke.
Alright.
That's it?
Why? Why did you have to do this?
I hate you!
You're too noisy.
Mind your own business!
Raze...
Don't you know
it's not safe for a lady
to be out here at night.
The way you look at me...
are you afraid of me?
You shouldn't be afraid of me
because he's scarier.
He is the man you would
never want to challenge.
Who are you talking about?
I know what's bothering you.
Fuck this.
Did they really think
a newbie can kill me?
Don’t you dare touch Matt.
Why do you still trust him?
He betrayed you
and your friends
by joining the enemy.
He must have a reason...
A reason?
What could it be?
Or maybe you can
give me a reason?
What?
Give me a reason
not to kill him.
Well...
if you can’t give
me a reason then...
Me!
Because of me!
Because of you?
Maybe you are a valid reason.
You know why?
Because you are giving us something.
Something?
It's possible that you'll be
the reason why I won't kill him.
It's possible that you
are still an asset to us.
Or maybe you're deadweight?
So whatever your reason is.
I'll accept it for now.
I don’t get it
but please
don’t touch my friend.
I can't promise you anything.
But as long as he
stays out of my way
he will be safe.
You should go now.
Zein!
Dave?
Zein...
let's go.
Come on.
Why were you there?
Ah, I get it now.
For Matt.
But you shouldn't be
outside during that time.
I should be the one saying that.
Is that what friends do?
Lie?
Pretend?
Keep secrets?
That's not friendship.
That's bullshit.
You don't know anything!
Because you don't
talk about anything!
We didn't tell you because
we didn't want you to be involved.
Dave...
We're all dragged into
this situation already.
That's not and will never
be a good enough reason.
Don't tell them yet.
In the right time.
Matthew, how could you do this?
I can't look at him like
I don't know anything.
I can't pretend like nothing is wrong.
Hoy.
Hoy, hoy!
Come here.
You're too cute.
Were you following me?
Do you have fun scaring me?
What could your name be?
Do you have a name?
I know!
Hoy...
it suits you, right?
Now you know how it
feels to be surprised, huh?
Seriously, you always startle me.
Look at you, you're so dirty!
Insanity.
Are you done talking to your cat?
You know
he has a name.
Hoy.
You're a lot of things, Ms. Shion.
But I didn't think corny
was gonna be one of them.
What do you mean corny?
Why?
Wouldn't it be funny if
everyone called him...
“Hoy”.
Hoy.
Hoy!
Right?
You look like you're not eating.
I see...
this place is starting
to take a toll on you.
But you know what?
Sometimes
there are days when you won't
be able to do anything.
What?
Did you comb your hair?
I really don’t know what
you're talking about, Ms. Shion.
Maybe.
Maybe your eyesight is
getting bad from starvation.
No, it's not.
It's like
you made an effort
today with your looks.
I think it's your hair.
Did you comb it?
I really don’t know what
you're talking about, Ms. Shion.
What's that, Hoy?
Are you saying something?
What is it?
Are you still not done
talking to your cat?
Ah!
Hoy said
you look handsome.
Really?
More handsome than Matt?
Nevermind.
Let's go, Hoy.
You okay?
Hoy!
Hoy?
Where did he go?
I saw him run here.
Hoy!
Where did he run off to?
Supremo...
please help me.
I'm begging you
save my mother, please.
I can't live without her.
Please!
Help me, Supremo!
Save my mom, please.
Supremo, please.
Please!
- Please!
- Lyka!
Lyka, stand up!
Get up from there.
I said get up!
I don't want to, mom.
I don't want to.
You need to do this, my child.
Please...
I can't do it.
You need to kill me.
I don't want to.
No, I don't want to!
You have to kill me!
Ma, please.
You need to kill me!
Supremo...
Get me away from here.
Kill me now!
You have to!
You need to kill me now!
I'm begging you, my child.
There's not much time left!
I don't want to!
You're the only one I have left.
Can we try to do someting.
Can you try to save them?
Please kill me!
Please.
Just this once.
Zein...
Please.
Kill me!
No!
- Kill me now!
- I can't!
No!
I don't want to.
Please...
just this once, please.
Fine.
Just this once.
Hoy!
Where are we going, Supremo?
Thank you, Supremo.
Thank you for
granting my wish.
Supremo?
I am still Supremo of this school.
I can choose who I protect.
That's enough for now.
But I also know
that I can't protect everyone
that I want to protect.
I can take care of myself.
Really?
You don't believe me?
That's not the Zein Shion I know.
You ignored Matt.
You looked away from him.
That wasn't Zein.
That wasn't my secretary.
I'm still the same Zein Shion.
The weak have no place here.
They're nothing but garbage.
The Zein Shion that I know
loves her friends.
That's why I looked up to her.
If you really know me
you should know
that I do taekwondo.
So again, Supremo.
I can take care of myself.
I’ll be the judge of that.
You have to show
me your moves first.
Any time.
SSG office.
Anytime you're
free after last period.
Brace yourself.
Now that my secretary is back,
she's ready to join me.
To where, Supremo?
To the admin.
So we can truly save
Lyka and Ms. Aya.
I'll handle Violet and Mr. Francisco.
What a rare occurence,
Mr. President.
What brings you here?
I'll speak plainly
exemption for Ms. Aya.
Exemption?
Mr. President, there are
rules and precedents to respect.
But who am I to turn down a favor
for my Supreme Student
Government President?
But I'm just wondering
what's the cause of this weakness?
There are still limits, Madam.
Even in a hell hole
like this university.
I know that you're aware of the
consequences of this exemption.
Mr. President, you must never
forget the only rule of your position.
That you must never
get involved with anyone.
You are not allowed
to make friends.
Never let your emotions
hinder your path.
You don't have to worry about me.
I know what I'm doing.
I really do hope so.
Okay then.
I will give them the exemption.
Tell them
that they can breathe
for now.
You remind me of Lux.
I'm nothing like him.
The mother and child
is safe for now.
But you
you're safe too.
Impressive.
Me?
The one who picked
your name is dead.
I guess you have a
guardian angel, Ms. Shion.
Where did you
pick up that stray?
He followed me, ma'am.
I'll set him free later.
Make sure to do it soon.
Are we done here?
For now, Madam.
Attention, students.
The locker game is now concluded.
Any pending business is void.
Carry on with your remaining classes.
It's done for now.
This isn't peace.
Do you have any
suggestions, Ms. Shion?
Huh?
Are you with us, Ms. Shion?
You're supposed to be
the one planning this.
You're the secretary.
We are just here to
approve your suggestions.
I guess leisure activities
and games should be fun.
That's your idea?
Then write it.
I must say.
This is a brilliant idea.
If there are no objections to this list...
then I approve.
I keep telling you all
she's more than
qualified for this position.
If there isn't anything else
may I ask to take my leave?
I think we have what
we need, Ms. Shion.
You may go.
A penny for your thoughts?
Everything is so complicated.
And we tend to overcomplicate it more.
What the fuck do you want?
I'm busy.
Whoa, harsh!
Well, I was just...
wondering about a few things and
maybe you can help me out.
Why do feelings suddenly change?
What are you trying to say?
I'm sorry
what I mean is
why do people change?
Because there's nothing
permanent in this world.
If you're done asking
nonsensical questions
you can leave.
Even with friends?
Nothing is permanent.
I'll take note of that.
By the way
thank you for your answers, Zein.
Ms. Shion.
Damn it!
Ms. Shion
get this little shit off of me!
Are you... afraid of cats?
You are afraid of cats!
Ms. Shion!
Are you not afraid of cats?
I'm not afraid of them.
I just...
hate cats.
There's nothing to hate about cats.
You're just afraid of them.
Ms. Shion,
get him away from me.
You know just admit it
you're just afraid of him.
I am Ace Craige.
I am afraid of no one.
Especially not a
cat.
Really?
Daddy Ace.
Baby Hoy wants to be carried.
Carry me.
Okay. I get it.
You're not afraid of cats.
Really?
But
are you afraid of me?
What are you.
Ouch!
Ouch?
Stop pinching, Zein!
Dammit, that hurts!
What the fuck is it now?
You know... just a little more.
It's not bad to smile
from time to time.
You're not worth smiling about.
Because I'm worth more
than you can imagine.
Right?
Smile!
Never.
Smile...
He's telling you to smile.
Smile!
Never!
You don't want to?
Wasn’t I clear?
Smile!
You really won't do it?
Are you content?
Look at you, oh!
You're smiling!
I'm going to count.
One...
Sorry...
Two...
I was just... you knew
I was just kidding!
Three.
Ouch!
Are you ready?
If you're talking about my death.
Always.
You sure?
You still got a couple days left.
Aren't you...
Aren't you going to
ask for my help again?
You can't do anything about it.
Is that really how you see me?
You must know.
I am not named Ace
without one.
Think about it.
Ew!
Van!
Get out!
OMG Van!
What?
What are you doing!?
Stop it, that's animal abuse!
You poor baby.
- What animal abuse?
- Zein!
Stay away from it, Zein.
Are you okay, Hoy?
You poor thing.
Poor baby.
Zein!
What are you doing?
Stay away from that!
That's a ghost!
A ghost?
This cute cat?
His name is Hoy.
Poor baby.
Hoy?
Were you scared?
He's traumatized because
of the two of you.
Hey!
You were the one who hit it.
Poor baby.
You're too naughty.
That's just a friendly pat!
You're such a naughty baby.
Look where it got you.
Here you go.
Have you seen Matt?
Did you guys fight?
Why did it get weird
between the two of you?
It's nothing.
Really?
Nothing happened?
Why are you guys
avoiding each other?
Because.
We need to talk.
We have nothing to talk about.
My body is suddenly aching, Mia.
Can you give me a massage?
Come on, let's go.
Sorry.
I'm too good at this.
- I made you believe I was upset with you.
- Sorry if I...
seemed cold towards you
these past days.
My mind has been
overloaded with things.
You don't need to say sorry, Zein.
I wouldn't care even if
you were avoiding me.
I'll always try to understand you.
You don't need to
apologize for anything.
You didn't do anything bad.
Apologies are for those
who did something bad.
I hate myself.
I'm so frustrated with myself.
A lot has happened
and then-
Shhh.
It's nothing.
I'm sorry if I made you feel that way.
That hurts.
I hate you!
I hate you because.
I can't trust you the way
you obviously trust me.
I know you have a reason, Zein.
I won't force you to tell me
the reason why you became
cold towards me...
why you started avoiding me.
Because I don't care
about that anyway.
What's important to me is
my belief that in the end
I'll still be the one
you'll embrace.
Come here.
Maybe, I was wrong
but it is never too late.
Whatever your reason may be.
I’ll trust you, Matthew Hart.
Ladies and gentlemen
welcome to.
Hell University's
Mr. and Ms. Face of the Year!
See? We didn't make a
mistake by choosing Matt
as our class representative.
Matt! Go, Matt!
Let's go, bro!
Let's go, Matt!
I'm watching here
get out of the way!
Move!
Look at me as long as you want.
What's your relationship
with Ms. Shion, Supremo?
She's my secretary.
I need to protect her.