ADAPTED FROM THE NOVEL HIDDEN LOVE BY ZHU YI
But I can't resist temptation.
What kind of temptation?
If someone is dating in front of me,
I'll also want to date.
Who is dating? You watch too many idol dramas.
The people close to me.
Those around me.
Are you talking about me?
Kiddo.
Why are you so petty?
You can't stop others from dating just because you can't date.
Isn't it a provocation
to date in front of me?
Fine, let's say you're right.
I won't talk about the future for now.
But we're going to talk
about your old boyfriend
who told you to go to Yihe to meet him.
It's quite a coincidence
because I'm from Yihe.
So if I ever find out
that you went to see him while you're still a minor,
then I'm afraid
you won't live to become an adult.
Let's begin the lesson.
How was the last exam?
Take point M as the intersection on side AB.
I explained it before. Like this problem.
Then try to recall the formula.
I'll explain static electricity first.
You got this problem correct.
This problem.
I was originally going to choose C.
C, you say?
I meant D.
D is the answer to this problem.
Pay more attention next time.
One incorrect multiple-choice problem.
You got 97 points.
Not bad.
You've improved a lot.
So,
you have no problem with physics now.
I won't come to tutor you anymore.
If there is anything you don't understand,
you can ask your brother
or your teacher.
You can ask me too.
Just send me a picture of what you don't understand.
I'll reply after I go through it.
My phone was confiscated.
Your brother will talk to your parents.
Don't worry.
Cheer up.
You've improved so much now.
So did I teach well?
All right then.
So will you have more exams after school starts?
Yes.
Then send me each exam's result.
You had better get high scores.
As long as there's an improvement,
I'll give you a gift.
Let's stop here for today.
HAPPY LUNAR NEW YEAR
Are you doing housework?
Is the lesson over?
-Yes. -Come and have some fruit.
-Thank you, Mrs. Sang. -Have some fruit.
I was just talking to my husband.
Let's celebrate Lunar New Year's Eve together.
Come and join us.
Thank you for inviting me.
But I think I'll stay on campus.
It's amazing at school now.
They host a holiday dinner
and give us red packets.
Don't go back.
It will be boring being alone.
In that case,
all right then.
Let me help you, Mr. Sang.
Okay. Sang Zhi, pass that to me.
This one.
Let's stick it here.
This one needs to be upside down.
Is this one good, dear?
Should it be bigger?
If I give him a red packet,
it will seem a bit strange.
He definitely won't accept it.
Jiaxu,
Happy Lunar New Year.
PROSPERITY
Sang Yan said
you'll stay in Nanwu after graduation.
Have you found a job?
Yes, I plan to work at the game company
where I interned.
That's great.
Keep it up.
Okay, let's put it up.
Allow me.
Having it up there will be good.
At the top.
-A bit higher. -Higher.
-Zhizhi. -Perfect. All right.
Help me clear the table.
Right here.
Stop sweeping already.
Wash the rag and wipe the table.
Okay.
-It's all done. -Okay, thank you.
Of course.
GOOD FORTUNE
How does it look?
Okay.
-That's enough. -So little?
That's enough for me. Thank you.
Okay. It's time to toast.
Happy Lunar New Year!
-Happy Lunar New Year! -Happy Lunar New Year!
-Dear, Happy Lunar New Year. -Cheers.
I dare you to finish all of this.
-Cheers. -Go away!
-He won't clink glasses. -It's such a big bottle.
The most exciting part
is yet to come.
Dear, you'll be the first to get this.
Do I get a red packet too?
Perfect.
Thank you, dear.
I love you.
-Dad and Mom, Happy New Year! -Dad and Mom, Happy New Year!
-May your wishes come true! -May your wishes come true!
-Be happy… -Stay healthy…
"Be happy" comes first.
It's "stay healthy".
No, it's "be happy"!
Fine.
-Be happy every day! -Be happy every day!
-Stay healthy! -Stay healthy!
-I like it. -Good. Here you go, Sang Yan.
Thank you, Dad.
Sang Zhi, this is yours.
-Dad. -Thank you, Mom.
You're being so unfair.
You're almost a university graduate.
You're lucky to even receive one.
Sang Zhi.
What should you do after getting your phone?
I'll uninstall the games.
What else?
What about your online dating prospect?
I already deleted it long ago.
What about his phone number?
I don't have his number.
Online dating doesn't use phone numbers.
I'm telling the truth.
Really?
You can see for yourself.
You don't even have enough money
to afford game currency.
-Why are you dating online? -Stop talking already.
-All right. -Cut it out. Stop arguing.
-Let's eat. -Eat up.
I have something to say before we eat.
I hope
my two lovely children will grow up
and behave a bit more
in this new year.
And you.
-Be more mature. -He means you.
-All right, let's eat. -Okay, let's dig in.
By the way, Zhizhi.
Didn't you want
to buy a set of anime merchandise?
Now that your brother has money,
ask him to buy it for you.
Why should I? No way.
Thank you, Sang Yan. Thank you.
Sang Yan is the most generous.
Sang Yan, have some of this.
A toast to Sang Yan.
-Happy New Year. -Happy New Year.
This is for you.
At least you have a conscience.
-But it's not much. -You like eating this.
-It's delicious. -Really?
I want this one.
JIAXU
It's from Jiaxu.
Sang Yan, you did well. Have more.
-Thank you, Mom. -Should we go on a trip?
Sang Zhi, I wish you happiness every day
and find your dreams soon.
Happy Lunar New Year.
-Sure. -Zhizhi.
How about going skiing in a few days?
Skiing? Sure.
Okay, then make up an itinerary for us.
-Okay. -It's busy during the holidays.
-So book early. -That's right.
-Next to number three. -Forget about numbers.
How about salt with vinegar?
-Footsteps. -Listen to my upper couplet.
It starts with "Perfectly."
-Damn. -"Perfectly matched."
-What matched? -Behind the bridge.
Perfectly matched, matched as in paired.
That's a good start.
I follow that with Minister.
-Move. -Minister against Cannon.
Why is it Minister against Cannon?
You move the Minister, and I counter with the Cannon.
It's Chinese chess. Get it?
I'll put it this way.
I structured these five characters together.
Thank you, Jiaxu.
Happy Lunar New Year.
YIHE CITY NURSING HOME
ANSWER
Hello?
Hello. Are you Mr. Duan Jiaxu?
Yes.
Your dad has severe pulmonary edema caused by a lung infection
and must be transferred immediately for drainage.
The current condition is quite urgent.
Please come as soon as possible to sign the consent form.
Okay, I understand. Thank you.
CHAPTER SIX, DISTANCE
WHEN YOU ARE IN ANOTHER CITY
Mr. Sang, your package.
Okay, thank you.
Hey, silly dog.
It has a name. It's Winner.
Silly dog, come here.
Come here. Let me tell you.
Come here.
Listen. Look.
You look so similar to him.
You two look exactly alike.
Wait right there.
Duan Jiaxu sent this to you.
It's your reward for ranking 20th
in the placement test
and scoring 95 on the physics exam.
Why didn't he give it to me himself?
Didn't he tell you?
He went back to his hometown.
He's back in Yihe.
He said something came up at home.
Why don't you ask him yourself?
Wait.
Then will he come back for the graduation ceremony?
Of course he will.
Why did he leave without saying goodbye?
XURI MIDDLE-HIGH SCHOOL TO NANWU UNIVERSITY
2 HOURS AND 33 MINUTES
Sang Yan, are you coming home today?
SILLY DOG
What does this mean?
Why are you taking your time when class is over?
My sister is probably in trouble again.
She asked if I'm going home.
Is she in trouble again?
It was awesome just now,
tossing the basketball with this pose.
I was off my game today.
Hello?
Sang Yan, it's already Friday.
Why aren't you coming home?
There's a BOGO promotion on candy
at the convenience store today.
I bought an extra pack. I can share it with you.
If I want candy, I can buy it myself.
Just tell me what you want.
Nothing. I'm just asking.
Well, I can just not go home.
-Right? -It was cheap.
-You can invite friends over. -Duan Jiaxu!
Where are you going?
Where are you guys going?
I'm going home for a bit.
I happen to be going to your area.
Let's go together.
Sure. Come over for dinner if you're free.
Okay.
I'm not joining you.
I'm going back to the dorm.
-Okay. -Bye.
Bye.
-Hello, little demon. -Suspicious.
What's wrong?
She hung up on me.
Let's go.
Why don't I call Sang Yan
and ask where they are?
Forget it.
They should be here soon.
Don't worry. What's the situation?
-Again, Chen Junwen? -He's finally home!
How many times have you forgotten your keys?
I can't bring it to you.
You come to get it yourself.
Did you forget to bring your brain too?
I'm already home. How can I open it for you?
Why is he alone?
Little demon!
Why didn't you close the door?
There are mosquitoes!
Duan Jiaxu was supposed to come with me,
but the library gave him a call,
so he had to go back to work.
As you know, he's crazy about making money.
All right, that's all.
I'm hanging up now.
Bye.
Little demon.
Why did you want me home?
Dad and Mom wanted
to have dinner together this weekend.
Have dinner together?
Couldn't you tell me over the phone?
Dad! Mom!
Sang Yan? Sang Yan is back.
I thought you were coming home tomorrow.
Let's have dinner together this weekend.
You're getting more thoughtful.
We're sweaty from a day of work.
We'll shower first.
-Okay. -Okay.
Afterward, I'll make dinner.
Okay.
Mom, why not let Sang Yan make dinner?
Let him make dinner?
That would work too.
Cook the rice first.
Wash the vegetables too.
Cooking rice is too simple.
It's okay. Let him cook the rice.
I'll cook the rest.
Sang Yan.
Which library is Jiaxu working at?
Is it the university's library?
Why are you asking me this?
Nothing. I'm just curious.
Are all university students so busy?
What are you usually busy with?
I'm busy trying to get away from a little demon like you.
Busy sleeping in class.
Isn't that the same as middle school students?
How can it be the same?
University students have one more thing to do,
which is dating.
Dating?
Well, I should've known.
A kid like you wouldn't understand this.
How is that possible?
Why would any girl like you?
Listen, plenty of girls chase after me.
Not even a high-speed train can fit them all.
What's wrong with you?
It has been so long
since I've heard anyone
tell such a tall tale.
You don't believe me?
Okay, listen.
Do you know why
none of my roommates have girlfriends?
None of them have girlfriends?
It's because those girls
are lining up to pursue me.
Who would believe that nonsense?
SENDER, DUAN JIAXU
Another reward from Jiaxu for my exam scores.
Hello?
Hello, Jiaxu.
I received the package you sent.
It's a black dog plushie.
So? Do you like it?
It looks a bit familiar to me.
Is that so?
Does it look like Sang Yan?
You still remember my essay.
Of course I do.
I was walking on the street one day
and saw this dog.
It reminded me of your drawing back then.
So I thought
it would be a perfect gift for you.
Congratulations on scoring 95 points
on the physics exam this time.
By the way, Jiaxu.
Give me your address.
I want to send you something.
Do you want to send me something?
I'm just exchanging favors.
No need.
Why? It's important.
What is your monthly allowance?
Keep the money
and spend it on yourself, okay?
No need to send me any gifts.
Let me send you something.
You really don't have to.
The fact that you want to
already makes me happy.
So Sang Yan said
you will come back for your graduation ceremony.
Is that true?
Yes.
Will you be going?
That's great.
We'll see each other then.
I have to go now.
Bye.
Then consider it your graduation gift.
Who's there?
It has been a long time.
Why are you here?
Aren't you inviting me in?
It's not a good time.
Sorry about that.
Here.
Isn't that person in a bad condition?
Don't worry
about returning the money this month.
It's fine.
I can figure it out myself.
I just don't want you to have a hard time.
It's really not necessary. Thank you.
By the way,
has the time for your graduation ceremony been set yet?
Can I go too?
No need.
It's all right.
Since you're returning to Yihe,
we'll get a chance to meet up.
Then
I wish you an early happy graduation.
Thank you.
I'll be in touch.
-Three, two, one! -Three, two, one!
-Cheese! -Cheese!
Smile a little.
A bit lower.
Okay, smile.
-Three, two, one. -Hi, Sang Yan.
Your classmate?
Actually, I don't know him.
-Sang Yan! -Sang Yan, come here!
Over there.
-Hello, Mr. Sang. -Hello, Mr. Sang.
Congratulations on graduating.
Thank you, Mr. Sang.
Mr. Sang, where is Mrs. Sang?
She's sick with a cold and fever.
I told her to rest at home.
-Many people have fallen sick lately. -Yes.
Sang Yan, you're late.
We need to take a picture together.
Okay, come on.
-Let me help you take it. -Thank you, Mr. Sang.
No problem.
Look this way.
One, two, three.
Make a different pose.
Ready? One, two, three.
It's all done. Take a look.
-Thank you, Mr. Sang. -Qian Fei!
-Take pictures with us! -Come, Qian Fei!
-Come on! -Let's go.
-Come! -Dad, I'm going over there.
Jiaxu, come and join us.
-Come! -I'm coming!
I heard you'll work in your hometown.
Yes. I've already found a job.
That's not a bad idea either.
After all, you're familiar with the area.
If you ever visit Nanwu,
come to my house for a meal.
Okay, that's for sure.
Good.
Let's go take a photo with your brother.
-Let's take it together. -Okay.
It has been a long time, Sang Zhi.
This is for you.
For me?
I thought it was for your brother.
He already has one.
This one is for my physics tutor.
I wish you
a happy graduation
and happiness every day.
Thank you.
I like it very much.
Then I wish my student
a bright future
and smooth academic progress.
The graduation ceremony is about to begin.
All graduating students,
please gather in the auditorium.
Jiaxu, you should go ahead.
I'll go and find my brother by myself.
It's okay. I'll take you there.
I'll text your brother.
Come on.
-Jiaxu. -Jiaxu.
-Hey, Jiaxu. -Come and join us.
-Come take a picture. -Okay.
I'll take a picture with them.
Jiaxu, who is this?
My sister.
Hi. Can you help us take a photo?
Sure.
-Thank you. Just press this. -Okay.
Come on, everyone.
-Come on. -Picture time.
-Okay. -This is it.
-Stand there. -Okay.
Okay.
Three.
Two.
One.
Good.
Okay, thank you.
-Jiaxu. -It's a great picture.
Professor Zhang, thank you for your help.
I hope to see you shine and excel
in the gaming industry.
-I'll do my best. -I believe in you.
Thank you.
Okay, I'm going inside first.
-Okay. -Okay, Professor.
Jiaxu.
Participating in competitions and research projects with you
was the most painful and happiest thing for me
in these four years.
Both painful and happy?
-Yes. -It sounds complicated.
Do you remember
when we stayed up late every night?
-Seriously. -We could only eat instant noodles.
Those were hard times.
But it will all pay off.
I'll be returning to my hometown tomorrow.
Are you leaving tomorrow?
-What about you two? -I'll probably leave tomorrow too.
I wonder if we'll see each other again.
It's okay.
We will get a chance to meet again.
I'm heading inside.
-Okay. -Okay, I'll see you later.
Jiaxu.
Does that mean it'll be difficult
to see your classmates after graduation?
Two, one.
I guess so.
How do I explain this to you?
We majored in the same discipline,
but after we enter society,
everyone will make their own choice.
Gradually, we'll take different paths.
It could be
that it will be really hard to meet again.
Then what about me?
You?
You're not the same as them.
They won't be like my dear sister
who snuck me a red packet
during Lunar New Year
and even came to give me flowers
on my graduation day.
Don't worry.
After I leave,
I'll come back to see you whenever I'm free.
When will you be free?
I'll let you know in advance
before I come back.
Okay?
Xiaozhou, can you do me a favor?
Sure.
Help me take a photo with my sister.
Okay.
Hold this.
Come on.
Both of you look at the camera.
Okay, smile a bit more.
-Happy graduation! -Happy graduation!
Enough. Don't drink too much.
You can't hold your alcohol,
so don't drink too much.
We're celebrating today.
You two are inseparable again.
I have to get to the bottom of this today.
You two always stick together
and never find a girlfriend.
I understand if it's Sang Yan.
With his temper,
who would like him?
Shut up.
Jiaxu, what about you?
Yes. Why don't you have a girlfriend?
What do we say?
See?
That's why we're best buds.
What? Is there a problem?
Duan Jiaxu!
I thought I was your best friend!
How could you have a change of heart?
You are. Of course you are.
Let him be. He's such a crybaby.
-He's ignoring me. -It's okay.
I'll take care of you. Come.
Are you really crying?
How can you cry for real?
You're a grown-up!
Can someone open a bottle for me?
Give it to me.
Thank you.
Jiaxu, come and have a drink.
-Cheers! -Cheers, guys.
Happy graduation.
We've graduated, and you're drinking cola?
-Drink beer. -I can't drink alcohol.
No way.
You're spoiling the fun. Come on.
Give it to me.
Okay, cheers!
Come on, guys.
There they go again.
Are you drinking on his behalf?
Stop wasting time and drink up.
-Drink up! -Cheers!
-Cheers! -Cheers!
Jiaxu, drink up.
Don't stop drinking. Finish it.
Is it for the whales or the sharks?
I can finish it. I'll drink first.
Listen. Wait a moment.
I want to ask you something.
-I'll ask you first. -No, I'll ask you.
-Do you have a crush on her? -Me?
Do you have a crush on her?
Do you?
Let me finish this drink first.
Today is the last day.
It's the last day, right?
It's the last day.
If you don't tell the truth, you won't get another chance.
JIANG YING
I'm happy you're coming back to Yihe.
Happy graduation.
CALL CANCELED
I'M HAPPY YOU'RE COMING BACK TO YIHE. HAPPY GRADUATION.
-What's wrong? -Jiaxu.
I can't bear to part with you.
Are you drunk?
No.
Why are you alone?
He's drunk.
I'm not.
You are. Stop denying it.
Come. Let's drink.
-Who turned Qian Fei into this? -Come on, drink.
Come and drink. Qian Fei, here.
-Don't drink with him. -This is our last time.
-Here. -Happy graduation, guys!
-Cheers. -Drink up.
You drank too much.
Jiaxu, I want to ask you something.
When I'm no longer around,
who will watch over you?
Don't worry.
Many people are eyeing me.
Duan Jiaxu.
You and Chen Junwen are going back home.
Only Sang Yan and I will be in Nanwu.
I don't know what is good about Yihe.
Why do you have to go back?
Enough. Let's keep drinking.
You were so loud earlier.
Look at you now.
You're right.
You're home.
Jiaxu.
Will you be okay in Yihe?
Promise me you'll live well in Yihe.
Of course, I'll be fine.
Sit.
Jiaxu.
You must come and visit us regularly.
I'll come back often.
Sang Yan.
Are you home?
-Mr. and Mrs. Sang. -Xiaoduan, you're here too.
What's wrong? Did he drink too much?
We celebrated our graduation.
-Why did he drink so much? -Thank you for bringing him home.
Give him some water.
-Okay. -I'll make hangover soup for him.
Okay.
Why did he push himself to drink so much?
Sang Yan, have some water.
-Move slowly. -I'm going to go, Mrs. Sang.
Wait. Where are you spending the night?
There's an inn nearby.
Don't waste money. Just sleep in Sang Yan's room.
Don't go to the trouble.
Not at all.
Zhizhi, you're here too.
Xiaoduan will spend the night.
Get him a new towel and toothbrush.
It's really okay, Mrs. Sang. I can manage.
Stop turning me down. Go upstairs now.
It's all right.
Are you feeling better now?
-Thank you for having me. -It's no problem.
Bring him upstairs.
Are you feeling better now?
Little rascal. Go on now.
Okay, it's fine.
Don't worry about it. I've got it.
-Okay. -Zhizhi, bring him upstairs.
Why did you drink so much?
Dear, is the soup ready?
Just wait a little longer.
Give him some more water.
Is this okay?
Yes.
Thank you.
Jiaxu, do you want some hangover soup?
I don't drink alcohol.
I don't need it.
It's late. You should go to bed.
I'll sleep after taking a shower.
Right, Jiaxu.
You need a towel
and other things.
Attention, ladies and gentlemen.
Passengers traveling to Yihe
on Nanwu Airlines Flight NW413,
please proceed to Gate Eightfor boarding.
Passengers traveling to Yihe
on Nanwu Airlines Flight NW413,
please proceed to Gate Eightfor boarding.
PROSPERITY
Jiaxu,
Happy Lunar New Year.
JIAXU, HAPPY LUNAR NEW YEAR