What's up?
- What's up?
- Hey, Suer.
You’re making a move on day one of joining the club?
What about you guys? You joining or what?
We’ve gone this far already.
Of course we’re joining.
- That’s the kindergarten friendship spirit.
- What about you?
You gonna be captain again this year?
- Nah, too lazy.
- Huh? Why?
- If you’re not doing it, then who will?
- Yeah.
Anyone around here, I guess.
Who could possibly be better than my friend?
Here. Your other friend.
Nah, I’ll give it to you.
This position belongs to you.
Let’s go.
As for this year’s captain selection,
it’ll be based on points earned from daily training.
Whoever gets the highest score will become captain.
Today’s scoring activity is running laps around the field.
The person with the fastest time gets the most points, and so on.
Today’s scoring activity:
ball juggling.
My shoulder hurts.
Who got second place? They were neck and neck with Suer.
The twin from Class 9.
Twin?
Yeah.
But I’m not sure if this one’s Dannue or Duennao.
Don’t really see them around much.
This guy?
Yeah.
I think that’s Duennao.
He’s kinda well-known.
Dannue’s more soft-spoken.
But I don’t know why people call him Maew too.
Maew?
Why Maew?
No idea.
People in Class 9 call him that.
And he seems okay with it.
So the name just stuck.
If you ever talk to him, try calling him Maew.
Maybe you’ll get closer.
Maew, huh?
Mm.
One-on-one ball control.
Whoever gets matching numbers
will pair up together.
However many times you keep the ball up,
that’s how many points you get.
- What number did you get?
- Check your numbers and find your partner, okay?
Go find your partner.
- What number did you get?
- Pair up and stay with your partner.
Who’s this?
Find them.
Come on, find them.
What number did you get?
- What number?
- Mick, come on! Mick!
Find your partner.
Same number.
Duennue?
Duennao.
Your name is seriously
hard to remember.
I’ll just call you Maew.
Huh?
Maew, obviously.
- Asshole.
- Hey! What the hell? Why’d you curse at me?
Let’s go.
Just so you know,
I seriously don’t care about the captain position at all.
Same here.
But I’ll probably become captain because I’m gonna beat you.
That’s it?
Just kidding.
Hey.
Alright, everyone.
It’s time to announce the results.
And this year’s football club captain
is...
Tiger.
Of course it’s him. That’s my friend.
That’s my buddy.
See? I told you you’d end up becoming captain anyway.
Who could ever take my friend down?
An entire team of eleven
still couldn’t beat my friend.
Wait a second.
Actually, there might be one person.
Maew.
Come here for a sec.
I just wanna give you some feedback about today.
It feels like you’re still
hesitating when you shoot.
From now on, decide faster.
Okay?
I asked if that’s okay.
Yeah.
Good boy.
Here.
Maew, I got you a reward.
Hey, what? You don’t like it?
Hello? Maew?
You don’t like it? Hello?
Maew.
Shut the hell up, asshole.
He's here.
Yeah. I’ll take Field home today.
See you tomorrow.
Mm.
Go get your bike and head straight home, okay?
Don’t go looking for trouble again.
Your lips are still red.
Get going.
Yeah, see you.
See ya.
- Which table is this for, Mom?
- This table, sweetie.
Dan, one glass of water for this table.
Okay.
What the hell are you looking at? I’ll poke your eyes out.
Dannue, can we get the bill?
100 baht.
- Here you go, Mom.
- Just leave it there, sweetie.
Okay.
You two should get going to school now, or you’ll be late.
Let me serve this table first.
Okay.
Alright, go on now.
Dan, let’s go to class.
Mom, I’m heading to school now.
Alright. Study hard, okay?
- I always do.
- Hurry up or you’ll be late.
Nao.
- Hey, Nao.
- Huh?
Class is over.
Why am I this sleepy?
Because you stayed up gaming instead of sleeping.
- Yeah.
- Let’s hurry.
Apo’s been whining about being hungry since last period.
He’s already waiting downstairs.
He’s gonna bite our heads off if we’re late.
Okay.
- Wait for me.
- Just follow us.
Hey, Nao. I heard you got into a fight yesterday?
How’d you know?
People have been talking about it all over class.
Who’d you fight with?
Some asshole.
- He kept calling me “meow meow.”
- Meow meow.
Go meow at your mom, asshole.
Damn. Harsh.
I just wanted to give you some feedback today.
Yeah.
Good boy.
Here.
Maew, I got you a reward.
Hey, what? You don’t like it?
Hello? Maew.
You don’t like it? Hello?
Maew.
Hey, hey!
- What the hell is wrong with you?
- Hey, calm down.
There’s no need to start punching.
What the hell is your problem?
I should be the one asking you that.
Why’d you get so pissed over a little teasing, huh?
- Huh?
- I’ve had enough of your shit.
And what exactly can’t you stand? Just the word “Maew”?
Maew is my mom’s name, asshole.
Let go of me.
Shit.
What are you laughing at, Dan?
He was making fun of our mom’s name.
You overreacted, Duen.
Mom wouldn’t care about that.
See?
It’s because you’re so hot-headed.
That’s why people think you’re some delinquent leader.
Like you beat up kids from other schools since middle school.
Back then, I punched a guy for flirting with Dan.
And just only guy.
So what are you gonna do now?
You punched their team captain like that.
And you still have the nerve to keep playing with them?
Then what do you want me to do?
Quit the club?
And leave you there alone?
No way. I’d get lonely.
Then maybe you should apologize to him.
Explain to him that you didn’t mean it.
Maybe he didn’t even realize he was making fun of Mom’s name.
Just looking at his face, you can tell he did it on purpose.
But you guys still have to play together for a long time.
Wouldn’t it be better to make peace?
You need to calm down sometimes, Duen.
See? Listen to your big brother.
Just go talk to him nicely.
Duen.
Alright, alright. I’ll talk to him.
You little puppy.
Your dad’s the puppy.
- Puppy this, puppy that.
- Hey, my meatball!
Don’t eat it.
- I’m taking it back.
- Well, I’m taking it back too.
Hey.
When’s he gonna go talk to Tiger already?
You didn't even talk during practice. Tiger’s gonna head home soon.
Yeah, I’ll go talk to him.
Hey, it’s Micky. Tiger’s friend is here.
He’s definitely here for you. What do we do?
You think he’s here to start shit, or should we strike first?
Apo, calm down. Don’t panic.
Nao, I want to talk to you.
About what?
I came to talk about Suer.
Did he send you?
What does he want?
If this negotiation isn’t fair,
then the deal is off.
Ten of my men are on their way.
Ten more minutes.
Are you guys seriously some delinquent gang leaders?
Yeah. You’re screwed.
Shit. So the rumors were true.
So what exactly do you want?
I came to confess something.
Actually, I was the one who told Suer to call you Maew.
He really didn’t mean anything by it.
So?
I already punched him.
Then go talk to him.
We’re on the same team now.
I don’t want things staying like this.
Suer just wanted to get closer to his teammates.
What should we do?
Go ahead. Talk to him.
Alright. Where is he?
I’ll go talk to him myself.
Over there.
- What should I do?
- Just go talk to him yourself.
I’m heading home.
- Asshole, you’re just leaving me like this?
- I’m going home.
I still have stuff to do.
Hey.
I need to talk to you.
About what?
Why were you making fun of my mom’s name?
I really didn’t mean to.
Mick told me it was your nickname.
Yeah.
Then I’m sorry for punching you.
I lost my temper.
You can punch me back if you want.
Really?
Yeah.
Just kidding.
Why’d you squeeze your eyes shut so hard?
You looked like you punch hard.
You scared the hell out of me.
I wasn’t really gonna punch you.
You’d die.
Your punch wasn’t even that hard.
Sorry for making fun of your mom’s name.
Wait, so...
what’s your name again?
Dannao?
Duennao.
If it’s too hard,
you can just call me Nao.
Okay, Nao.
So we’re good now, right?
Then I’ll head home first.
(That guy.)
Dan, we have homework today too?
For math. You slept through class.
Then let me copy yours.
Mm. It’s okay. I’ll do yours too.
Do what? Our handwriting doesn’t even match.
So, did you clear things up with Tiger yet?
All settled. No problems. Don’t worry.
Good job, Duennao.
Yes!
See? I told you that from the start.
- Hey.
- I told him to go get the stuff...
You guys are loud as hell.
And why the hell do you care?
- People are trying to sleep, asshole.
- You wanna fight or what?
Hey.
You.
Hey! Cops!
Shit! Run!
Hey!
What the hell?
Patch me up.
Fuck, asshole.
You’re always picking fights and dragging me into it.
I was bored.
Bored of what?
Everyone else gets bored too.
But you’re the only one who gets bored and still goes looking to get hurt.
Maybe there are others. Who knows?
Nope. It’s just you.
- Look at this shit.
- Hurry up.
Seriously, you think this makes you look cool, huh?
So? How does it feel?
Mr. Dark Knight.
Pretty good, actually.
Pretty good? And yet you came back with a busted arm for me to patch up?
Stay still.
- This asshole...
- It’s not busted. Can’t you see?
Men...
getting hurt and dying is normal.
I seriously don’t even know what to say to you anymore.
Hey.
Suer.
Wake up.
Wake the fuck up.
Come on.
Six o’clock.
Yeah.
What, are you rushing to open the school gate?
Come on, hurry up.
Let’s go eat.
Wake up.
What the hell is this?
Put it on first.
Cover the wound.
Just say you fell down.
Oh, just wear it already.
It’s cold today anyway.
No.
Your shirt...
isn’t cool.
If you want to wear cool clothes,
bring your own next time.
Perfect then.
Can I just move in with you?
Shit. If you move in with me,
your brother’s gonna rip your chest open.
Go shower already.
Why the hell are you bringing him up?
Look who’s talking. Taking forever and shit.
What would you like?
Sure.
- Cut carefully. Watch your hand, dear.
- Yes, Mom.
20 baht.
Thank you.
Maew.
What is it, sweetheart?
- Hello, Auntie Maew.
- Hello.
Wow, calling my mom that casually already?
When did you get so close?
My bad.
Why are you just standing there?
My shop doesn’t need a mascot.
Come on. Let’s eat.
Speak nicely to your friend, dear.
What the hell should you eat this morning?
Damn, the staff at this place are savage as hell.
Then I’ll have garlic pork rice with a fried egg.
Extra rice too.
What about you?
I’ll have the same as Field.
Okay.
Please wait a moment.
With this many customers,
he must be exhausted.
Do you think...
he’s cute?
Huh?
Nue.
Do you think he’s cute?
He’s alright.
Damn.
Yeah, I shouldn’t have asked you.
You’re not into everyone.
Why?
Does he get hit on a lot?
A ton.
He’s cute and nice too.
Even I think he’s really charming.
Oh.
But Nao’s cute too.
The only problem is...
his mouth is kinda foul.
“Kinda” is an understatement.
He’s feisty as hell.
What shit are you talking about behind my back?
Nothing.
Let’s just eat.
Let me see.
Mm.
This is so good.
Maybe I should hire Auntie Maew as my home chef.
Mm, but if she became your home chef,
your brother would get to eat it too.
Why the fuck do you keep bringing him up?
Do you secretly like him or something?
Hmph.
No thanks.
I’m keeping this place all to myself.
I’m not letting him eat anything this good.
Why do you hate each other that much?
You’re real brothers.
Nao.
Go take a break.
I’m fine.
Go rest.
That’s an order.
You’re making the team lose.
And send Ball in too.
Yeah.
Ball’s playing striker with me.
What happened to you?
How’d you know?
I just know.
I’m the captain, remember?
Give me your leg.
What are you doing?
- Treating it.
- Hey, no need.
Hey, seriously, you don’t have to.
Here.
You’re an athlete.
Try taking care of your body for once.
Take a break for now, alright?
And you? You’re an athlete too.
Picking fights just to get hurt?
Does that make any sense?
You saw that?
I’ve got my reasons.
Damn, all mysterious and shit.
Whatever though.
Thanks anyway.
Those asshole gang kids
keep causing trouble in front of my house.
Some nights I barely get any sleep.
Having you deal with them makes things peaceful.
That’s enough.
Keep icing it when you get home too.
- Mm.
- Here.
Thanks a lot, man.
Seriously, thanks.
Having you handle things like this keeps the peace.
Field.
- Hey, Field.
- What?
I just...
got thanked.
Someone thanked you?
You actually do good things now?
For the stuff I do at night.
Who thanked you?
So I can go yell at them.
Asshole.
Why would you yell at them?
They actually saw the good in what I do.
Mm. “Good.”
More like asking for trouble.
I’m tired of stopping you anyway.
Do whatever the hell you want.
Just not right now.
I’m sleeping.
- Keep it down.
- Field.
I’m sleeeeping.
Damn, your bike’s so loud I heard it from the alley entrance.
Got no food at home or what?
Whoa.
I came to support your shop. Or should I go somewhere else?
Kidding. Welcome, valued customer.
- Hi, Aunt Maew.
- Hello.
Hi, Nue.
What would you like, dear?
Chu Chee with a fried egg, please.
Sure thing. Give me a sec.
Alright.
Nice bike. Where’ve you been?
Mind your business.
Asshole.
Duen.
Don’t throw spoons.
Yeah, yeah.
Nue, he flipped me off.
Dan wouldn’t scold me over something that small. I’m rude all the time anyway.
Oh my.
Oops.
How’s your leg?
Feeling better?
Yeah. It’s getting better.
I’ll probably be back at practice on Monday.
- Good.
- Here it comes.
Thank you.
How is it, dear?
Just as delicious as always.
Then finish it all.
Aunt Maew.
- Here.
- Thanks.
I’m heading out now. Bye.
Alright, get home safe, dear.
Will do.
- See you.
- Later.
He seems like a nice boy.
That new friend of yours.
Isn’t he
the captain of the football club?
Yeah.
But he’s not a good person at all.
Still, it’s good to stay close with him.
You’ll be together for a long time.
What family is he from anyway?
Have you ever asked?
No idea, Mom. But I know his family’s probably rich.
Otherwise they wouldn’t buy their kid a big bike just for fun.
Though honestly, it’s dangerous too.
Tiger likes speeding around.
Feels like he could get into an accident any day.
Yeah.
That’s just how it is, Dan. The ones rushing through life rush to death too.
Who would wanna rush to their death?
Such a sharp tongue.
Where's he?
Mr. Leo has gone to the company, sir.
When will he be back?
Probably sometime tonight.
Tell them not to disturb me.
What?
Dad wants you downstairs for dinner.
I’m not hungry.
What, avoiding him now?
Such a kid.
Still haven’t stopped doing stupid shit?
Mind your own business.
Always acting out for attention.
It was just some pathetic gang.
And you still came back hurt.
Yet you still act all tough.
Want me to help next time?
Try begging me first.
Singha.
Why don’t you just go die?
Ten minutes.
Put your foot down.
No.
You really love acting stupid.
Oh yeah?
Like you’re so smart.
At least when I was a kid, I didn’t act like a problem child who hated the world like you.
Well, you were always Dad’s perfect son.
He pulled the strings and you followed wherever he led.
You’ve got no mind of your own.
You really think what you’re doing is right?
You really proud of causing trouble for the family?
You’re getting older, but not any smarter.
No matter what, you’ll always just be a child.
P’Suer, P’Singha, stop fighting.
We’re eating right now.
Serve some rice for P’Suer.
Suer.
I heard you got hurt because you got into a fight.
Don’t you think that’s pathetic?
You’re my son,
yet you act so disgracefully.
Whatever.
I gave up hoping for anything from you a long time ago.
Did you hear what I said?
If it’s not worth hearing,
then I don’t hear it.
You need to be stronger than this.
With skills like yours, you can’t do anything to anyone.
I don’t need weak people.
It’s pathetic.
You think I even wanna stay here?
Suer, where are you going? Suer!
Where to next?
What the fuck are you doing?
The hell’s your problem?
You wanna start shit?
Motherfucker!
Fuck!
You carrying sugar around to eat too?
Fuck, if my boss finds out—
- You’re dead.
- Then go tell your boss.
My name’s Tiger.
Remember my face and my name too.
Fuck.
- Rawr.
- Fuck!
What kind of greeting is that? Can’t you say hi normally?
Why’d you get so damn startled?
What’re you doing around here?
Just riding around.
You?
Looking for something to eat.
Want some?
Did you walk here?
It’s not exactly close, you know.
What about you? You live around here?
I told you, I was just riding around.
And
taking care of a few things.
You seriously
don’t understand my superhero path.
While everyone else is asleep,
I’m the only one
- keeping the peace around here.
- So you’re the Dark Knight now?
What kind of knight steals other people’s food?
You handed it to me yourself. Here, take it back.
Just keep it.
Here.
At least pay me for the buns.
Nice view.
Never been here before?
Then take a good look.
This place is romantic as hell.
You bring your girlfriend here a lot?
My girlfriend?
Yeah.
Nope.
Seriously?
Why would I lie?
A guy like you doesn't have a girlfriend?
But it's probably for the best.
I'd feel bad for your girlfriend.
The hell, asshole?
What about you? You don't have one either?
Not yet.
- Figures, asshole.
- Hey!
You're such an asshole.
Come on, let's head back.
Head back? We just got here.
Let's stay a bit longer then.
What are we even doing, staring at the moon?
Save this spot for when you bring your wife next time.
Damn.
This is so romantic I don't even know how to act.
Want some?
Nah.
Dan doesn't like it.
Your brother, right? Dan.
Yeah. My brother.
You really love your brother, huh?
What's weird about that?
I don't know.
What's it like having a twin?
I don't really know either.
I've had him since I was born.
So it just feels normal to me.
If one day he wasn't there,
I'd probably feel weird.
You've never been apart?
Mm.
Nope.
At most, we stay in separate rooms.
Other than that, we're always together.
It's like...
if there's me, there has to be Dan too.
I'm just used to it.
I can't even imagine it.
What about you?
You don't have siblings?
No.
Let's go back.
Mm.
What the hell? Pushing your bike isn't cool at all.
Your bike's loud as hell.
You'll wake Mom and Dan up.
Just keep pushing it.
You see me riding?
So?
Want me to clean your wound?
Nah. Too lazy.
I'm gonna find somewhere to sleep instead.
Come on, do it for me.
- Nah.
- Help me use up the Betadine.
It's about to expire.
You're this nice of a person?
I'm not nice. I'm just your friend.
Me?
- Your friend?
- Yeah.
You know I don't have any friends.
Be my friend, okay?
Oh.
Can I park here?
Right here.
Easy there.
Or I'll start the engine.
Smartass.
Wait here first.
Aren't my hands too rough?
They are.
Then why didn't you even flinch?
Field's hands are rough too.
I'm used to it.
Mm. Done.
Thank you.
Can you really ride back like this?
Yeah.
Actually, you could stay here tonight.
- Wouldn't I be bothering you?
- No.
Your mom and Nue upstairs won't mind?
They won't. It's just like having a friend sleep over.
It's no big deal.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
But can you sleep on the couch?
Then...
Can I get a blanket too?
Easy.
Wait a sec.
You keep blankets in a drawer?
Yeah.
Here.
Thanks.
If I didn't met you,
I don't know where I'd be sleeping tonight.
Field already went home,
and Mick's house is packed with people.
I’d feel bad to stay.
Mm.
Alright, I’m going to bed then.
Night, Ger.
Suer.
Uh...
You can call me Suer.
That’s what my other friends call me too.
Mm. Then good night, Suer.
Good night, Nao.
You asked if I could stay over at your place.
Can I really do that?
My mom said it’s fine.
The question is whether you want to come or not.
- Like permanently?
- Yeah.
Do whatever the hell you want.
You said your brother’s cute?
Guess that makes you cute too then.
Don’t you feel bad for those people?
Having trouble because of you.
No matter what, you can’t run from the truth.
You’re a mafia’s son.
- Fuck, Tiger! I remember you!
- Go, go!
Where are you going?
Come here!
Where the hell’d they go?
Damn, they're fast.