Astrological fortune-telling.
A fortune-telling activity
held by our Astronomy Club.
You two will be our fortune tellers
on Club Fair Day.
-For our Astronomy Club, keep fighting.
-Where are you going?
-Fighting.
-"Borrowing power from the stars
to foretell someone's fortune
requires you to sell the power
of your own soul."
Let's say I like someone.
How likely is it that the person
will reciprocate my feelings?
Very likely.
That person must like you very much.
A universe that needs
no prophecy from the stars.
A universe where
you already know how you feel.
Are these for me?
Sun.
I…
I don't know.
The delivery guy left them with me.
Yeah?
Thank you.
Sure. You're welcome.
In the end, I chickened out.
I need to get back to the club.
I haven't grabbed my stuff yet.
Bye.
Did you send me flowers?
How did you do it?
Yes, I did.
Do you like them?
Well…
I do.
That's great.
That you like them.
That makes me happy.
It's true that the Sun should be
with the Earth,
not with you, Ongsa.
Alien, please let us join your club.
We love your club so much.
It's true. Please recruit us, Alien.
Talk to the club leader.
Come on. Can't you talk to her for us?
Please.
Speak with us.
Say something.
Please.
I might have made history
by defeating Ton's club.
Luna? What are those girls doing
at your club?
Please accept us, Alien.
Alien, will you talk to her for us?
Please.
Where are you going?
Guys, stop it right now.
Why are you cornering her like that?
If you want to switch clubs,
wait until next semester.
Apply again next semester, guys.
Aylin, are you okay?
Alien has no reason to talk to humans.
Aylin.
Aylin, wait.
Sun, you've known Aylin
since junior high, right?
Yes.
I've known her since Grade 7,
but we weren't close then.
Has she always been like this?
What do you mean, Alpha?
Well, she has no friends,
she doesn't talk to people,
she doesn't care about anyone,
and
she's been nicknamed "Alien."
Aylin is different from other people.
She's quiet.
She doesn't talk much to people.
She's interested in space,
UFOs, and alien stuff.
Her classmates thought she was strange
and started calling her Alien.
After that, she distanced herself
from people even more.
Hearing that makes me feel guilty.
I knew she was obsessed with aliens,
I just didn't know that it had caused
social problems like that for her.
Aylin is my cousin,
but I can't help her with anything.
Come on now.
At least you know her problem now.
Let's find a way to help her.
We don't know what Aylin's been through
like you do,
but we really want to help her.
From now on, if you see her struggling
with any kind of problem,
can you let us know?
Of course.
Aylin is my friend too.
I'll let you know if I notice anything.
Thank you so much, Sun.
Why are you smiling? Can I see?
It's nothing.
Every time you say that, it's something.
It really is nothing.
Keep on working.
Hey. Your birthday is coming up.
What will you do this year?
Planning to meet up with someone?
Meet up?
I'm not.
We thought you'd be going on a date
with Mr. Earth or something.
What date?
There's no meeting.
No date.
No nothing.
Earth and I are just friends.
Girl, this is not what friends do.
Friends don't make you smile like that.
So, have you ever seen his face?
I haven't.
I think it's weird.
-He could be a crim.
-A criminal?
What?
No way.
I've just never asked for his photo.
I don't want him to feel uncomfortable.
But you might want to.
You've been talking for a while now.
Don't you want to see each other's faces?
Earth has never made me feel uneasy
and I don't want him
to feel uneasy either.
If he wants to show his face,
he eventually will.
How about this?
I have a way to find out
if this guy Earth is serious with you.
A way?
What way?
Your birthday. Invite him to come.
It describes how often something happens
in the simple present tense.
Give me some examples.
There are more. What adverbs do we use
if something doesn't happen very often?
It's my birthday in a few days.
If I ask you a favor, will you grant it?
What is it?
Can we meet up?
Sit back down.
"Never" in the present simple tense
means "not ever,"
as in a habit that is always negative.
But "never" in the present perfect tense
implies "not ever," as in,
"You haven't done it."
I want to go.
But no promises.
I know you live far away.
But if you can, I'd love you to come.
If someone says, "I have never loved you,"
what do they mean, Tinh?
They mean they don't love you,
not because they never had the chance to,
but because they never did
in the first place.
Ouch.
That hurts.
Correct.
You can tell by the adverb of frequency
that's used in the sentence.
It indicates how often something happens.
Guys, are you free this Saturday?
We are.
Why do you ask, Sun?
I'm throwing a birthday party
this Saturday.
That's why.
Do you have time?
-We do.
What about you, Ongsa? Are you free?
I am. I'll be there.
Great. Please tell Aylin
she's invited as well.
Thanks a lot for inviting us.
I'll be going now.
-Bye.
-See you.
Come on.
Aylin.
What, human?
Sun has invited us
to her birthday party this Saturday.
You're invited too, Alien.
Right. She asked us to ask you.
I never thought someone like Sun
would invite people like us.
I thought she would only
invite you, Ongsa.
Why are you looking at me like that?
We saw it.
You gave Sun the flowers.
Me?
No way.
Don't lie.
We saw with our own eyes
that you visited the Floral Design Club,
got the bouquet, and gave it to Sun.
You're wrong.
You saw it wrong.
I didn't. You want proof?
Wanna see it?
Fine.
I gave Sun the flowers.
But…
Sun doesn't know they're from me.
What?
Well…
Here's the story.
What? Sun thinks you're a guy?
I didn't think it was a big deal at first.
I didn't know it would escalate.
I think you'd better tell her soon
that you're Earth.
I'm scared.
I'm afraid that if she learns the truth,
I will…
But keeping on lying is a sin.
But I have no clue what to do.
What do we do?
Are you waiting for global warming
to strike first?
Humans always blame it on other things
when they're the ones responsible
for global warming.
Keep lying, and one day,
you might drift away from her orbit.
Latte,
do you think she'll still want
to be my friend
if she knows I'm Earth?
What should I get Sun for her birthday?
Should we chip in
and buy something for her?
Can I chip in too?
No.
Why not?
Ongsa, "Attā hi attanō nāthō."
Oneself is a refuge of oneself.
You must find the present yourself.
That's right.
A gift for someone you like must be
more special than other people's gifts.
Special how?
It should be something meaningful
and have sentimental value.
Sentimental value?
I was up all night thinking about
what gift to get Sun.
A meaningful gift.
What gift would be suitable
for someone like Sun?
There's none unless you box up the Sun
and give it to her, Ongsa.
Hello?
Student?
Uh, can I get a box of Kanom Sun, please?
What?
A box of Kanom Sun.
Kanom Sun?
Oops! I mean a box of Kanom Krok, please.
I'm sorry.
Did you just say
a box of Kanom Sun, Ongsa?
I…
Why would you say that?
Were you thinking of me?
Well,
I was thinking of
what I should get you for your birthday.
Is there anything you want?
No.
Nothing at all?
For me, spending time
with someone special is enough.
Someone special?
My family, my friends,
and you, Ongsa.
You must come, all right?
So…
what about Earth?
I invited him too.
He's also special to me.
ALIENS AND UFOS
That's Alien.
Over there?
-Are you about to finish?
-I am.
Give her this.
Go on.
Alien, someone asked me to give you this.
AYLIN = ALIEN
She's in shock.
Alien is angry now. That's new.
-We'd better bounce.
-Let's go.
Alien, can you return
these books to their shelves?
We don't know how to arrange them.
What are you guys doing?
You're too old to be this childish.
You think it's cool
to harass other people?
Huh? You think you're so cool?
What a loser. I'm gonna punch…
Human senior, stop.
It's the library. Keep your voice down.
Why should I?
Everyone should know
that this bunch of youngsters
think they're so cool
that they can mock and harass
other people.
Just because she doesn't respond
doesn't mean you can do that.
Never let me catch you doing this again
or you'll be talked about all over S-Tar.
We're sorry, Alien.
-What did you say?!
-We're sorry, Aylin.
Why were you being so loud?
Those guys were harassing you.
I saw it and yelled at them.
-It was the right thing to do, yeah?
-Next time, don't.
Humans can't harm aliens.
It isn't something you should put up with.
You're not a joke.
You're not causing trouble to anyone,
so don't let anyone cause you trouble.
I don't put up with them.
I just don't care.
Okay. How about this?
If you don't care,
then I'll be the one that does.
We're friends after all, right?
Don't you remember?
Here.
You know there are lots of holes
on the moon's surface, right?
Maybe, they are shelters
for aliens to hide from danger.
-Aylin.
-Human.
You go first, human.
It's fine.
You go first, Aylin.
No. You first.
I don't know what to do
with the Sun situation.
She has such high hopes about Earth.
I still don't know if I should attend
her birthday party
as Ongsa or Earth.
But whatever I choose,
I'm going to let her down.
It's a choice
you have to make yourself, human.
But I don't know what to choose, Aylin.
If your brain can't think,
let your heart think.
Human.
Do you think aliens have hearts?
Can aliens fall in love like humans do?
How are human hearts different
from alien hearts?
Human hearts have limits.
That's why they get emotional so easily.
Their hearts are weak.
Yeah. That's true.
My heart is weak right now, Aylin.
Can I get a box of Kanom Sun, please?
What? Kanom Sun?
Oops! I mean a box of Kanom Krok!
Sorry, it came out wrong.
Did you just say
a box of Kanom Sun, Ongsa?
Why would you say that?
Were you thinking of me?
Well…
Kanom Krok-Sun?
SSSUNSHINE SENT YOU A PHOTO
Kanom Krok-Sun.
Crap!
What is it, human?
Sun.
Sun sent me a message.
So?
She sent the message to me, not Earth.
Aylin.
She's so cute eating her snack.
Who on earth looks this cute
when eating snacks?
Cute, huh?
Get it together, human.
Aren't you gonna reply?
Right.
ONGSA SENT YOU A MESSAGE
Looks yummy.
I invited Aylin on your behalf.
Thank you, Ongsa.
Aylin, Sun replied to my messages.
How cute.
She's so cute, I can't.
It's the first time
Sun's ever reached out to me.
Hey! Don't go yet, Aylin.
Hold on.
Hey!
How can someone be so lovely?
She's just the cutest.
I KNOW YOU LIVE FAR AWAY…
If you can't come
to my birthday party, it's okay.
I know you live far away.
Traveling to Bangkok might be troublesome.
I understand.
I'm sorry, Sun.
See you, Sun.
I still can't decide whether the one
who will give her this gift
will be Earth or Ongsa,
but I'll try my best to make it.
Hand out the plates.
-Oh.
-Hold on.
Sun.
Sun, like the Sun,
is burning you once again, Ongsa.
All the worries
I've been carrying for days
are chased away by Sun's smile.
How can someone be this lovely?
Come on in.
Thank you for coming, guys.
-No. Thank you for inviting us.
-Right.
H-B-D.
Thank you, Aylin.
This is from me.
Thank you, Tinh.
Happy birthday, Sun.
This gift was enchanted by
Luangpu Sek himself.
May Buddha be with you.
Sadhu.
Let's have some snacks.
We have a lot.
Have a seat.
Vi, do you want this too?
-I want the one at the bottom.
-This?
-You want a refill, Tinh?
-No.
Sun, is Mr. Earth coming?
He said he was.
Did he say what time?
We want to see your Earth so bad.
Shut up. He isn't my Earth.
Look at you.
Your cheeks are red.
Stop it. No more teasing.
I want to know how he does it.
Sun is head over heels for him.
He must be hot.
Do you think he's hot, Sun?
Enough. You want some drinks?
Changing the subject, I see.
-Sun is blushing.
-No teasing.
Don't.
It's tough, human.
But you must keep going.
How's the orange juice?
Earth, where are you?
Can you find the way here okay?
Sun.
What's up, Ongsa?
Are you…
waiting for Earth?
I'm afraid he might get lost.
What if…
he doesn't come?
I would be sad, I guess.
But no.
I think he's coming.
He told me he would.
Sun…
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
I…
Yeah!
Thank you, guys.
Let's eat the cake.
Should we bring it outside?
-Yeah.
-Let's go.
Aylin, come on.
-Yum!
-The cake is so good.
Have you tried this?
Eat some fruit too.
Sun.
Are you okay?
What do you mean?
About Earth.
It's late. He hasn't shown up yet.
What did he say?
He read
but didn't reply.
I don't think it's gonna work.
It's your birthday, for goodness' sake.
Your special day.
That guy can't do this to you.
Right. Why the heck didn't he reply?
If he wasn't going to come,
why didn't he say so?
He shouldn't have led you on like this.
He might have his reasons.
Don't you take his side.
Your relationship status is vague.
You haven't seen his face.
There's never been one phone call.
Guys, stop it.
It's Sun's birthday.
I've made up my mind.
I'll give Earth one last chance.
I'll ask him to meet me this evening
and we'll go from there.
If he doesn't show up,
I'll stop talking to him.
I'm waiting for you right here.
What should I do, Latte?
You all right, human?
I don't know what to do.
If I go see her and tell her I'm Earth,
she'll be disappointed that
I'm not a guy like she thought I was,
but if I don't go,
she will be sad
because Earth broke his promise.
I know for sure
she will be broken-hearted.
She might cry.
I don't want her to cry on her birthday.
But I'm scared.
Do you really like Sun, human?
If you do, you have to make it right.
Otherwise…
you might drift away from her orbit.
But I still want Sun in my life.
Human hearts have limits.
That's why they get emotional so easily.
Humans get angry,
but they'll come around eventually
if you don't quit trying.
Human hearts have limits.
That's why they get emotional so easily.
Humans get angry,
but they'll come around eventually
if you don't quit trying.
Hey, Ongsa.
What are you doing here?
I came to see you.
Are you worried about me?
Thank you, Ongsa.
It's good to have company while waiting.
You know,
I've never thought birthdays
were that big a deal.
I always felt like
they were just another ordinary day.
Nothing special.
But once I knew Earth was coming,
my birthday suddenly became special.
It might be silly
to wait for someone I haven't even met.
Someone who reads my messages
but doesn't reply.
But do you know what's sillier?
Deep down, I still believe…
Earth will come to see me
because the Earth I know,
the one I talk to every day,
would never let me down on my birthday.
It's good you're here, Ongsa.
I think you and Earth
can become good friends.
I'm selfish.
I'm cowardly and hesitant.
But I really can't, Aylin.
I really can't ruin Sun's birthday.
Earth, the one Sun has faith in…
I really can't tell her
that he doesn't exist.
Sun, we've been waiting a while.
Should we go?
Let's go, Sun.
Sun.
You can leave me here, Ongsa.
But I don't think Earth will come.
I want to be alone.
Please give me some alone time.
Earth, you really can't come?
You can just tell me honestly.
I won't be mad.
Just don't disappear like this.
Did something happen?
Though she's been hurt,
she still trusts
and has faith in Earth.
Sun!
I know you're upset,
but there must be a reason
why Earth can't come.
Please don't cry.
Let's wipe your tears.
Thank you.
Sun, please don't cry.
Excuse me.
Which one of you is Miss Sun?
I've got a package for you.
It's me.
Here you go.
Who sent this?
The sender's name is Earth.
It was sent from Phuket.
All right then. Please excuse me.
Why don't you open it, Sun?
I'm sorry I couldn't go see you,
but I've sent you all the planets
in the universe instead, Sun.
Happy birthday.
Ongsa!
Earth sent me a present!
You should put it on.
Let me hold this.
Thank you.
Happy birthday, my Sun.
And…
sorry.
Ongsa, look.
I've got the whole universe.
There's the Sun at the center.
Pretty?
-He isn't being honest with Sun.
-I trust Earth.
Even though we've never met,
I feel like he's always by my side.
Didn't Aylin tell you that your friends
would be sleeping over tonight?
This is your chance to tell Sun
that you're Earth.
If it turns out he isn't who you think
he is, will you be able to take it?
@S_SSUNSHINE: MORNING
Ongsa, are you Earth?