Kee, as your mom, I'm
asking you to listen to me.
"Mom"?
How dare you call yourself my mom?
You tricked me into believing you had died,
and you still have the nerve
to call yourself my mom?!
I know you're very angry with me,
but I want you to listen
to what I have to say.
I have my own reasons.
That's not true!
You left me to struggle all by myself.
I've lived in confusion!
I've lived for revenge. How
could you do this to me?!
How could you?!
I thought it was for the best,
for everyone's sake!
I wanted to protect you!
Protect me?
Out of all the ways you
could have protected me,
you chose to disappear
and call it protection?!
You know what?
Seeing you standing right here
is even more painful than
thinking you were dead!!
I'm sorry.
But I want you to know
that Weiling isn't who you thought she was.
What lies are you going to tell me now?
What lies?!
You want to lie to me so much, huh?
Go on.
You've been lying to
me all this time anyway.
Say it!
Say it now!
I'm here to tell you the truth.
I want you to know that Weiling
wasn't the one who hurt our family.
She was the one who helped us.
If you just give me a chance to explain,
you'll realize
and understand who was behind everything.
Your chance was there 20 years ago.
You missed it.
Are you okay?
Are you satisfied now,
seeing me like this?
Are you satisfied now?!
It's not about satisfaction.
Even though I'm still angry at you,
I understand you better
after listening to your story.
Want to curse at me?
Go ahead, curse at me.
Curse me out as much as I
deserve for what I've done to you!
I'm despicable!
I destroyed your life!
Curse at me, Lalin. Why
are you just standing there?!
Say it! Just say anything! Say it!
I'm not gonna say anything,
but I'll be right here
next to you.
I won't go anywhere.
Just tell me when you're ready.
I can wait. It'll be fine.
I can wait.
It's over, Lalin.
It's over for us.
It's over.
Stop being so good to me.
Stop it.
You need to be where you belong.
I don't deserve you!
This is bad enough as it is.
No.
I won't accept this.
You know too well I'm not
the type to give up easily.
We're both hurt,
but we're supposed to
get through this together!
Give yourself a chance.
I'll wait for you to come back.
Auntie, please wait right here.
I'll go get my mom for you.
Excuse me, then.
You haven't changed one bit.
Of course, I have.
A lot, actually.
I still remember so vividly
the last day we met.
I know
it would mean nothing if I apologized now.
No one would forgive me.
Aren't you going to try?
I've been waiting for an
explanation for 20 years.
I saw that you were happy.
I saw that you had a family,
a child,
and a good reputation in society.
You have everything I could never give you.
If I came back...
If you chose me,
everything would fall apart.
- So you decided for me…
- Couldn't you just let me fall apart on my own?
Why would you decide for me?!
What about our promise
to fight it all together?!
Just the two of us.
Why did you just decide it all on your own?
For 20 years, you left
someone who loved you waiting.
I never even knew if
you were dead or alive.
Isn't that too much?!
I have no excuse
except for an apology.
I used to think that my happiness
was seeing you and Kee happy,
and that if I...
If I watched you two
from far away, I'd be okay.
But I never thought that
everything would turn out this way...
That's because you assumed everything.
We've known each other for so long.
Have I ever once left you behind?
I miss you so much.
♫ Never a second could I forget you ♫
♫ You're still here when
night comes through ♫
♫ I don't wish to wake up sometimes, ♫
♫ Afraid that you'd say goodbye ♫
Just seeing you again is
beyond my wildest dreams.
♫ To say that I'll never stop missing you ♫
Don't ever leave me again.
That way, we won't have to miss each other.
♫ Do you know I miss you? ♫
How are you doing, Uncle Kengkad?
Are you better now?
I'm sorry I didn't visit you.
Any updates on the matter?
I can assure you that it
wasn't one of Weiling's people.
Actually, I've been keeping an
eye on this situation for a while.
I looked into it, and I
think I know who it was.
I was going to tell you, Ms. King,
but he got to me first.
Who was he?
This is the man who works for Arisa.
That's right.
From what I've learned about
what happened to your father, Chet,
it might've been this man's doing too.
Hey.
Hey...
- Ugh...
Why did you sigh like that?
Going through a rough time?
It's pretty rough.
And why did you sigh like that?
I've
been through a difficult situation.
Hey,
wanna grab a bite together?
To cheer us up.
Got anything you want
to get off your chest?
Let's share.
It's nothing.
It's just that I found out
who caused my dad's death.
I'll see this through to the end.
Part of me is relieved,
but I also feel uneasy for the victim.
Anything I can help you with?
It's fine.
I'll handle it.
Thanks.
What about you?
I
Just feel bad for my boss.
With everything she's been through,
she must have been so confused.
Out of nowhere,
her mom, who she thought
was dead, just showed up.
Not to mention the
situation with Ms. Weiling,
which seems to have turned into
an even bigger misunderstanding.
Worst of all
is probably what's going on with Ms. Lalin.
Gosh.
I don't think
my boss can handle all of this.
She's really fragile on
the inside, you know.
I think this kind of thing takes time.
I agree.
But
if time doesn't help,
I'll tell you right now
I'll be the one helping her.
You seem to enjoy sticking your
nose in other people's business.
But you've gotta help me, too.
We're a team.
Cheers.
By the way
how did you find my boss's mom?
Tell me everything.
Uh...
So, Ms. Lalin came to see me at home,
and she asked me to look into Ms. Arisa.
I want this bracelet
to be a reminder
of the days we have each other.
But ever since we crossed paths,
there was never a
glimpse of darkness again.
I promise
I will treasure this light
for as long as I shall live.
Boss!
Boss, it's fine.
I'll have the maid take care of it.
It's been days,
and you still don't feel better?
Boss,
we're gonna have a meeting off-site.
What meeting? I didn't know about it.
Since the case became messy earlier,
you'll have to sort it out
with your partners now.
Have someone handle it.
That won't do.
It's just
I've already scheduled it, Boss.
Please go
before things get worse.
Oh, hey.
What are you doing here?
At first, I was gonna come
here to talk to you about the intel,
but seeing the state you're in,
I don't think it's a good time.
I'm sorry.
I'm not in the mood for guests today.
What do you mean by
that? I'm here as a friend.
It can feel pretty cramped
just staying indoors.
How about we go outside?
I don't have the energy to.
Being in the same place
will bring all the memories
flooding back.
Trust me, let's go do something outside.
Wanna see the menu?
The food here is really good.
I'm gonna use the restroom.
Want me to order anything for you
so the food comes on time?
Anything. You decide.
Uh, Boss.
Please go in first.
I forgot some documents.
You're holding them.
Uh, they're in another envelope.
Go on in.
I'll be right with you.
Hey, wait!
How long are you gonna
keep pushing me away?
Stop avoiding me.
I'm not pushing you away
or avoiding you.
I'm just not ready.
Hey,
maybe it's time we face the truth,
even though it's painful.
Maybe it could be the start of healing.
And I'm
tired of acting like I don't care about you.
Don't you see me in a bad light?
Don't you feel even a little
anger or hatred toward me?
After I found out the truth,
you can say I'm stupid
or too generous,
but I can't bring myself to hate you.
Please go see your mom.
She probably wants to
explain everything to you.
I'm ready for the truth.
Weiling and I have been
friends since university.
She was my best friend
and closet person
until I had to marry your dad
for the sake of our family's business.
It seemed like a happy ending,
but no one knew
it was the start of a nightmare.
Still using that pen?
It's been 10 years.
Want me to buy you a new one?
So what if it's old?
It just has sentimental value.
I could never throw it away.
Today,
I have a gift for you.
Whoa...
Where did you find this?
I'm not telling you,
but let's just say it was
hard to get my hands on.
- Do you like it?
- Of course, I do.
It happened again?
It's on your neck, too.
This has gone way too far.
What if he kills you one day?
It won't happen.
I'm the mother of his child.
He wouldn't be that cruel.
I can still handle it.
When Kee gets older,
I'll find a way out.
But I have you,
so nothing can ever scare me.
Seeing this happen right in
front of me, I can't accept it.
Saitharn,
if it ever becomes too much to handle,
promise you'll tell me.
Please?
Back then, Weiling was my only safe space.
Right?
Does it hurt?
I'll take care of it.
As for you, take good care of Kee.
Don't let Weiling come
anywhere near my daughter.
Yes, Boss.
Listen carefully.
If I'm ever gone,
you'll take care of Kee for me,
and tell her I love her
more than anything.
You came home so late
that your child asked for you.
Aren't you worried about her?
How come you're the only
one who gets to live your life?
I work so hard.
You don't even think about easing
my burden by looking after your child?
Huh?
It hurts.
Does it?
Does it?!
- Let go...
- Does it hurt?
Huh?
- Let go...
- Does it?
I can't take this anymore.
I'm gonna run away with my child.
I'm coming with you.
You shouldn't have to stay anymore.
What are you talking about?
You're not alone. You
can't just do as you please.
What about Lalin?
I don't want you to be caught up in this.
Well
once everything's over,
I'll bring Lalin to be with me.
I'll have a word with Thana.
We only got married because
of the business, anyway.
We never loved each other.
Anyhow
your situation is much more critical here.
What if he goes crazy and just kills you?
How would Kee live?
But he's a good father.
But he's a sh♪tty husband.
You shouldn't have to stay with
this kind of person, you know that?
I don't want you to get in trouble.
I don't want you to get in
trouble because of me...
II'm scared...
It's fine.
Maybe...
It's the right time for everything.
I know everything's gonna be okay.
Saitharn, you b♪tch!
Come here!
Ow!
Where do you think you're going?!
You're gonna run away with Weiling?
Huh?
Do you think you can abandon
your child and me to run with Weiling?
Are you gonna run with your mistress?!
She's not a mistress!
We've loved each other even
before I f♪cking married you!
Ow!!
Ow...
Come here.
Ow!
Are you gonna take our child with you?
Huh?!
I won't leave my child
with someone like you!
B♪tch!
You b♪tch!
You f♪cking b♪tch!
Huh?!
You really think you could run from me?!
- Help!
- You...
Stop!
Oh, Weiling.
Weiling!
Good thing you f♪cking showed up!
Huh?!
- Weiling!
- About f♪cking time I get to see you!
- Weiling...
- Good thing you f♪cking showed up!
- Weiling!!
- Good thing you f♪cking showed up, Weiling!
Huh?!
Are you gonna fight me?!
You dare attack me?
Huh?
You dare attack me?!
I killed.
I killed him...
Saitharn...
Take a deep breath.
Saitharn.
Saitharn, you did not kill him.
It was self-defense.
You helped us. Do you understand?
- Do you?
- What do I do...
What do I do now?!
What do I do now...
Run.
Run away for now.
I'll take care of everything here.
Run away and get in touch with me
once you're safe. Do you understand?
Do you?
Go.
Come on, come on.
I knew Mekhin was trying to find me, too.
That's why I had to lay low.
I didn't want you and Weiling
to be in trouble because of me.
Mekhin
was probably just a pawn
in Thinnakorn's game,
instilled with vengeance
to be passed on to you, Arisa.
Maybe he did it out of loyalty to his boss.
Dad really did it, Mom?
Say it, Mom!
You were just a little girl.
I didn't want you to find
out about any of this stuff.
I only wanted you to
remember the good side of him.
At least, he was a great dad.
I'm sorry I've never told you this,
but everything I've just said is the truth.
You know?
Ever since I could remember,
I always looked up to my dad as a hero.
He was such a good person in my eyes.
He was my role model in every way possible,
whether it was about
life or on a spiritual level.
Everything.
I never thought that he could hurt someone,
especially Mom
especially me!
He hurt everyone!
Hey, take it easy.
Just take it easy.
I know you've been through so much pain,
but your dad loved you so, so much.
How about
you only treasure the good memories of him?
If I have to keep good memories of him,
then there is probably just one.
The one where I'm thankful
that he brought me into this world.
You're amazing for getting
through everything, Arisa.
But there's one more thing
that I have to get through.
Hello, Ms. Arisa.
Just call me Kee like usual.
Lalin already found out about everything,
and so did I.
Found out about what, Miss?
The truth, of course.
About how, all this time,
what you've been telling
me was nothing but a lie.
You're the reason I misunderstood Weiling,
thinking she would hurt our family.
You never once told me
who he hurt all this time.
That included Mom.
More importantly,
why haven't you told
me that Mom's still alive?
Why would you do this?
Ms. Kee.
I did it all
because of your dad's final
words before he passed away
to take good care of you.
Take care of me?
To make it so that I lived
with misunderstanding
and resentment?!
I only did what was right.
Weiling and Saitharn were having an affair!
They killed my boss!
Your dad!
After killing him,
they were going to go
enjoy themselves together!
- Ms. Kee...
- But Uncle...
Dad hurt Mom.
He assaulted her.
She was in so much
pain that she almost died!
She was barely surviving!
I don't even know
how I should think of my hero anymore.
Do you know?
Ever since I lost my parents,
you were the only one I had,
the only one I loved and respected!
You were my only respected elder!
I'm begging you,
from this moment on,
to please get out of my life.
I did what I did because I was
loyal to your family, Ms. Kee!
But killing someone is wrong!
You killed someone innocent!
How could you do that?!
If this was out of love and good intention,
please don't ever do this again, Uncle.
Get out of my life.
Consider this my last request for you.
I've never even thought
of meaning you any harm, Ms. Kee.
But since you asked,
I will oblige.
Please excuse me, Ms. Kee.
Hey, it's gonna be okay.
I'm right here.
You've done your best, Arisa.
You've taken care of everything now.
Good job.
Where are Lalin and Kee?
They went outside.
It seems like they're still
not over it with Mekhin.
I know you're still blaming yourself,
but we have to move on.
Live in the present.
So what's your plan going forward?
I don't know.
I've never imagined
that this day would come,
the day when you and I
get to listen to music again.
Do you still want to be with me?
We can go somewhere far.
Just the two of us.
How about Canada?
Isn't that too cold?
How about the UK?
It rains too often.
You pick, then.
Wherever you want to
be, I'm coming with you.
What's wrong?
What's wrong...
What's wrong, Weiling?
Weiling, what's wrong?
Come take a seat.
What's wrong?
I understand how
uncomfortable you must have felt.
Let it out through what you love.
Step on that gas pedal
until you're satisfied.
Do it so hard you forget about your past.
Come on, let me put this on for you.
- Does it fit?
- Mm.
I promise I will be right
here to support you.
I'm not going anywhere.
Go on.
Go on!
Bye-bye!
Go get it!
Pedal to the metal!
Hello?
What did you say?
Weiling, it's gonna be okay.
The doctor will be with you soon.
Dear.
Dear!
Lalin?
Lalin!
Where are you? Who did this to you?!
If you don't bring Pin to me by tonight,
there's no reason
for me to let Ms. Lalin live.
It all started with me,
so it has to end with me.
Arisa!
Ow!
How could you do this to Lalin?
How could you?!
Arisa!
Help!
You tricked me!
It's all over now, sweetheart.
♫ Never a second could I forget you ♫
♫ You're still here when
night comes through ♫
♫ I don't wish to wake up sometimes, ♫
♫ Afraid that you'd say goodbye ♫
♫ I dream of another rendezvous ♫
♫ To say that I'll never stop missing you ♫
♫ Since you're my whole heart ♫
♫ Do you know I miss you? ♫