The perpetrator becomes the victim,
and you lose the upper hand.
That's all fabricated!
A sloppy investigation has turned
a living person into a dead one.
And then she vanished,
like she never existed in the first place.
WANTED: FUGITIVE FOR FRAUD
What do you think made her so sure?
The visible evidence?
SUSPECT
The word on the street?
It's the pattern.
The suspect's crimes follow a pattern.
She cons a large sum of money,
fakes her own death,
assumes a new identity,
and sets up an even bigger con.
Did the search warrant include
Boudoir's bank account?
- No, I'll apply now.
- It'll be too late.
There's a way to check without it.
Follow me.
Why did the money come in?
Didn't anyone check?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Call Violent Crimes.
What the hell are they trying to pull?
What's going on?
"What's going on?"
You said Boudoir was all a scam.
Then how the hell is money coming in?
What money are you talking about?
The 15 billion won
Jeong Yeo-jin embezzled!
The full amount was just paid back.
WITHDRAWAL
I know this is a bullshit ploy
to cover up the case.
Why didn't you even freeze the account?
You were so smug raiding that place.
What, did you take a payoff or something?
- You fucking shit!
- Ma'am, no.
- Let go of me!
- Hold on.
- You!
- No, stop.
Is that how you got promoted, asshole?
We can still catch her.
"Catch"? The suspect is dead.
The suspect is still alive!
What?
Hey.
Looks like our cases are really connected.
I'm about to lose it, too,
so just hand over Boudoir's bank records.
I'm sure you went over them
while tracking Nox's accounts.
Give it to me.
We have less than three days
to hold Jeong in custody.
Get this solved by then, no matter what.
Please authorize a wanted notice.
At this rate, we're practically aiding
the suspect's crime ourselves.
Please help us bring her in responsibly.
Say we issue a public notice. Then what?
The suspect has been meticulously erasing
her tracks up until now.
But she can't erase one thing.
People's memories of her.
There must be someone who remembers her
before she took a new identity.
If we find them…
we can identify the suspect.
That's not enough.
A no-name con artist managed to dupe
high-society figures everyone knows.
If this gets out, the public will track
the suspect down on their own.
It's only a matter of time
before we locate her escape route.
And if we lose her?
She won't last.
In the end,
she'll lose her cool and reveal herself.
That will be our only chance
to question her
about the Jane Doe sewer murder case.
But you just said
you want to do a public search for her
as the Boudoir fraud suspect.
Up to this point,
we were pawns in the suspect's setup.
This time, I'll lure her into mine.
You want to con the con artist?
And the evidence?
All we have so far is circumstantial.
You have nothing?
And you're asking me
to authorize a public search?
The suspect's statement,
no, her presence alone
will be the most conclusive evidence.
I'm positive I can get a confession.
Mark my words.
This could make you or break you.
Thank you, sir.
SEOUL METROPOLITAN POLICE AGENCY
REGIONAL INVESTIGATION DIVISION
This is Park Mu-gyeong
of the Seoul Violent Crimes Unit.
Over the years, the suspect has changed
her name, age,
nationality, job, and education,
living under
at least three false identities.
Due to the crime's severity,
a public wanted notice has been issued.
Effective immediately.
If anyone knows
or has recently seen the suspect,
please contact
the Seoul Violent Crimes Unit.
What's going on?
We apologize. We retract the notice.
We'll have a press conference
immediately after our investigation…
What are you doing?
Well, you see…
Sarah Kim is here voluntarily.
Why did it have to be
now, of all times?
Did you gather all the evidence
on the list?
- Yes, I got everything here.
- Okay.
Make sure you gather everything.
Don't leave anything out.
Yes, sir.
Do you think she'll confess?
The suspect came voluntarily.
- Everyone focus, okay?
- Yes, sir.
JANE DOE SEWER MURDER REPORT
INTERVIEW RECORDING ROOM 1
Do you know when we find people
who vanish voluntarily?
When they decide to return.
RECORD OF STATEMENT (SUSPECT)
Are you turning yourself in?
No. I voluntarily presented myself.
Let me change the question.
What is your name?
It's Sarah Kim.
There's no record of a Sarah Kim anywhere.
No name, birthplace, age, or education.
Let me ask you again.
What is your name?
I already told you. Sarah Kim.
Would you rather not reveal who you are?
It means who I am is not important.
If you see me as a con artist,
I'm a con artist.
If you see me as a businesswoman,
I am one.
But if you see me just as a person,
then you'd be able to understand me.
What if I can't understand you?
Then you will never know me.
THE ART OF SARAH
BOUDOIR
Feel free to say anything you want.
You can tell me a convincing lie,
as you did to others until now.
You think you know me
when all you've seen is my ankle.
You're the person who created Boudoir.
I am.
I won't deny that.
Are you admitting to the fraud charge?
It wasn't fraud.
I did plan and produce Boudoir completely.
Anyone can make a bag,
but not everyone can build a luxury brand.
I accomplished that.
So why would I deny that?
Everyone's the same
once they're in that seat.
They end up resorting to pathos.
I want to be wealthy for a day
before I die.
A reduced sentence
is her only way to survive.
To me, it wasn't a con.
It was a matter of survival.
The world is kind yet indifferent.
On one side,
a lavish party can be underway
while someone freezes to death
on the other.
Is that why you used other people's money
to buy luxury goods and live lavishly?
CHEONGDAM GODDESS RESALE SCAM
INVESTIGATION REPORT
Oh, this case.
Yes, I've heard of it before.
But I remember hearing
that the suspect committed suicide.
So that's not you?
I'm alive, aren't I?
Then I wonder how this person
wrote a Boudoir product review
before the brand even existed?
Who knows?
The dead tell no tales.
But wasn't this case already closed
due to lack of prosecutorial authority?
The suspect can't even be punished
unless she comes back to life.
This isn't what's important, Detective.
You haven't even come remotely close
to what I'm about to say.
Luxury brands became luxury brands
because they discarded what mattered most.
Clients.
The more you ignore them,
the more they want you.
That attitude is what makes you
a luxury brand.
Which is why I discarded myself.
So that I could start over from scratch…
in a place where no one asked my name.
Fuck, this is why
I didn't want to be the first pick.
He wouldn't keep
his fucking hands to himself.
Hey, move.
What are you glaring at?
Well…
I'm a follower of yours.
I took your advice
and tried the eyelash extension place.
- Really?
- Yes.
I'll follow back.
Here.
How long have you been doing this job?
This is just a temp gig for me.
I'm quitting once I save enough
to start my business.
"A temp gig"?
It's temporary for you,
but it's a lifetime for me?
So?
How much have you saved up?
Not that much.
You didn't take
an upfront payment, did you?
Idiot.
Don't just look at how they spend money
but at how they earn it.
Like school, regional, and blood ties?
But you can't have those things
even if you try.
Of course you can.
Just find yourself a sucker,
and he'll get you a new identity.
Is this a real diamond?
Not a chance.
But everyone will think it is
if I put it on you.
I even sold my soul
just to get into that world.
- I didn't realize the look until today.
- That's what I mean.
I'm all dressed up too.
Look at Eun-jae. She's dressed so nicely.
Honey, you're…
The moment I entered that world,
I suddenly had some serious pull.
Aren't you being too rash?
The world was on my side.
I just realized
everyone here went to Oxbridge.
Oh, really?
They say drinking makgeolli
on the campus lawn
is a fond pastime of a Korean college.
But for us,
it was gulping down muddy water
when our punts capsized.
These days, I do miss
the taste of that muddy water.
I wondered when he'd bring that up.
Seriously.
Eun-jae, I take it
you've never gotten a failing grade?
Oh, I guess I haven't--
So, regarding the thing
you mentioned last time…
He's no fun, is he?
No, it's just that…
I actually graduated
thanks to a ghostwritten thesis.
My attendance was appalling too.
You seem genuinely nice. No sneaky side.
Let's meet up
without the husbands next time.
I'll take you somewhere fun.
Where?
Somewhere with guys in a hot pool,
not those who gulp down muddy water.
Isn't life ironic?
I tried so hard to look like them…
Shall we say…
…but they make an effort
to look like who I used to be.
It's like a web made strictly
by introductions between associates.
- Is this your first?
- Yes.
Being so young,
you must feel cooped up at home.
Actually, I've been working
on a business idea
to bring in a luxury brand here.
But I don't know
the geography of Seoul well,
so I'm not sure where to open the store.
I have a building in Cheongdam.
The location is good. Want to take a look?
Yes, Chairwoman Jeong,
you should help her.
I'll rent it to you cheap,
and you can raise
the building's value for me, Eun-jae.
For some reason,
every tenant goes bust and leaves.
I know, right?
It's right in the main area too.
145, CHEONGDAM-DONG, GANGNAM-GU, SEOUL
It's in the luxury district.
Hi.
It's been a while.
I'm not saying I'm entirely innocent here.
But people pay money for fake degrees.
I just made up credentials I never had.
Who's more at fault?
You never put in fair effort either.
What about you, Detective?
Are you being justly rewarded
for your fair efforts?
Your watch doesn't suit today.
Don't you have money?
Or do you not care how others see you?
If it's not that either,
are you pretending not to care
what people think
just to hide the fact
you can't afford an expensive watch?
You've just admitted
to posing as a Korean American
and falsifying academic credentials.
Am I correct?
Yes, I admit it.
While I can be morally criticized
for impersonation,
there's no actual law against it,
is there?
And falsifying academic credentials
is just a fine
unless I'm a high-ranking official.
A fine of 80,000 won, right?
If committed for financial gain,
the two charges constitute fraud.
A 50 billion won fraud is punishable
by severe penalties.
That's a bit of a stretch.
Who cares about a seller's education
and background when buying a bag?
You swindled 15 billion won from Jeong
for investment.
Jeong handed over the funds
before Boudoir had officially launched.
The timing suggests
it wasn't the brand she invested in
but you, with your fake background
and education. Is that a stretch?
When Jeong Yeo-jin was arrested
for embezzlement,
it seems
you wanted to cover it up somehow.
You rushed to repay the full amount.
I think you have it wrong.
All transactions have been confirmed.
No, those were dividends,
not repayment of the investment.
If you recover your principal
in less than a year,
don't you think
that's a decent investment?
It may begin with a bluff,
but if it ends with success,
it's business, not a con.
I'll say this again.
I didn't create Boudoir to deceive anyone.
I built Boudoir
so I wouldn't have to do that.
The Boudoir appraisal report
has arrived, sir.
I'm sure you know
exactly what it says, right?
You sold bags worth just 180,000 won
for millions,
tens of millions,
even hundreds of millions of won.
Production costs do not determine
the value of luxury goods.
People chase the status that comes
with the brand, not the product itself.
"I like the brand's heritage."
"I like its identity."
That's all bullshit.
I sold the added value of superiority
and set a reasonable price accordingly.
She's admitting to the charges
while dodging punishment.
It's flawed logic,
but it makes sense.
How is this possible?
Tell me about it.
He has been outmaneuvered too.
No, he's waiting
for the contradiction to peak.
Let's get Financial Crimes.
JEONG YEO-JIN
Would people still have bought them
if they had known the production cost?
Everyone knows that luxury goods
are expensive because of the brand value.
What if they knew
the bags were made in Korea?
This is the import declaration document
seized from the Boudoir store.
With this one forged document,
you turned bags made in Sinwol-dong
into "Made in the UK."
Yes, the bags were manufactured
in Sinwol-dong.
But that document is not forged.
The bags were produced
with the top handles detached
then sent to the UK.
Once there, they were reassembled,
then reimported to Korea
to get the document.
Legally.
That can't be called legal.
You used a loophole.
You could say I did,
but it's also not illegal.
Do you know how far I went
to make Boudoir a luxury brand?
I deliberately made
and distributed counterfeits.
No counterfeits exist
without luxury goods.
On the flip side, if counterfeits exist,
it must be a luxury brand.
So if I'm a fraud,
then every other brand is too.
And as long as they're not frauds,
I'm not one either.
Do you understand
what Boudoir means to me…
and what it is you're messing with?
Do you get it now?
I will do anything to protect Boudoir.
Damn.
Proving trademark infringement
won't be easy either.
I know.
Is that why you stole the heritage
of a luxury brand?
"Crafted for European royalty
for 100 years."
"A British Royal Warrant Holder."
How do you justify promoting the brand
with a history that doesn't exist?
It wasn't exactly promotion.
It was just word of mouth, I think.
Pass them down.
God is in the details.
- "Bu-do-ire"?
- What's this?
"Bu-do-ire."
First time seeing this, right?
Hey, open it carefully.
And this money here…
This one's mine.
This is for promoting. Get on it.
Thank you.
Details amass to build credibility.
Hey.
You should get a new bag.
Why? Does it look weird?
No, it's just that
all the ministers' wives in the next room
couldn't stop talking about Boudoir.
They say these days, owning a Boudoir bag
is a sign of true wealth.
Hey.
Yes.
Credibility builds into trust.
And when trust grows, it becomes faith.
But I played absolutely no part in that.
So if I'm a con artist,
that would make them accomplices,
not victims.
Would you be able to stand
in front of the victims
and call them accomplices?
There's no reason I can't.
But…
has even a single victim come forward
to formally accuse me of fraud?
Have you met the purchasers?
Were they willing to make statements?
They spend hundreds of millions of won
on a bag for social status.
I wonder if they'd come forward
as fraud victims.
What I'm saying is…
there are no victims.
So how is this a con?
This case
can't even be established
in the first place.
Let's take a short break.
Now.
Goodness.
You should've just died.
Why are you still alive? Why?
What do you think you're doing?
Hurry up and go inside.
What the hell did you do?
Hey!
INTERROGATION IN PROGRESS
Jeong Yeo-jin said
nothing about being defrauded
because she believed Sarah Kim was dead.
Now that she's seen Kim alive,
she might decide
to take her down with her.
Her resentment runs deep enough
to spit at a corpse.
Let's hope we can count on that.
I'm sure I don't need to explain
why we're having this confrontation.
Ms. Jeong, you're undergoing
a custodial investigation,
suspected of embezzling 15 billion won.
I did not embezzle.
I was making an investment.
It doesn't matter.
We're not here
to interrogate you, Ms. Jeong,
but to prove the crimes of this suspect.
Ms. Jeong, in your previous interview,
you said you invested 15 billion won
with Sarah Kim
after she told you about Hotel Boudoir.
Is that correct?
I don't recall.
I was not in my right mind then,
having lost a close friend.
Ms. Jeong Yeo-jin.
Did you say "a close friend"?
Do you know her real name?
Her age? Where she went to school?
Anything?
"A close friend"?
Will you fall for it again?
Think carefully.
Everything about her was a lie.
Do you think she was ever honest with you,
even for a moment?
The suspect is denying
all charges against her,
as no one has filed a formal complaint.
No one?
Yes. At this rate,
proving the allegations,
let alone punishment, may be difficult.
I have suffered no damages.
Don't you realize the consequences
of the statement you've just made?
Would you be okay
with the suspect's crimes being dismissed?
If Boudoir turns out not to be a scam,
then what Jeong did
isn't embezzlement either, right?
That's right.
Do you know what you're throwing away
and what you're protecting?
I have not thrown anything away.
I have no objections.
Are we done?
Am I free to go?
Go and get Jeong Yeo-jin out.
I was considering suing you
for defamation…
but I won't do that.
You seem to be suffering enough already.
Seriously…
You stupid bastard.
I'm sorry, sir.
I wasn't talking to you.
I was talking to myself.
Chances should be given
to people who know how to use them.
I made a mistake.
SEOUL METROPOLITAN POLICE AGENCY
REGIONAL INVESTIGATION DIVISION
It was wrong of me
to even want to become rich.
You don't become rich.
You're born that way.
It was wrong of me
to have been born this way.
I was born the wrong way.
Let me help you sign up
for membership first.
May I have your name, please?
Sarah.
Sarah Kim.
Please help those in need.
SALVATION ARMY
Let us share our warmth.
We have set up a collection kettle
to help those around us in need.
RED KETTLE
Please help those in need.
What the… She's giving all that?
Thank you.
Yes, over here.
We have it in red.
How do you like this model?
The sexy vibe suits you very well.
Are you looking for a long-term rental?
No, just one day.
Then how about this one?
If you roll down the window, the side is…
Just insanely beautiful.
Do you have a specific car in mind?
A Rolls-Royce.
This one.
This is a Rolls-Royce.
Here.
- Just leave it, please.
- Yes, ma'am.
We wish you a pleasant day.
Just a moment.
Thank you.
APOLOGY
CHEONGDAM GODDESS HERE
I CAN'T SHIP ITEMS
DUE TO UNFORESEEN CIRCUMSTANCES
I'M SORRY
I wish I could be born again.
I'm here to stay for good.
You know, I have a dream now.
I want to become a person
who suits this bag.
EDIT
I GOT THE LUXURY BOUDOIR BAG LOVED
BY EUROPEAN ROYALS FOR 100 YEARS
The world is kind yet indifferent.
On one side,
a lavish party can be underway
while someone freezes to death
on the other.
Stop there!
- Play it back.
- Sir?
- I said play it back.
- Yes, sir.
The world is kind yet indifferent.
On one side,
a lavish party can be underway
while someone freezes to death
on the other.
Get her.
Yes, sir.
Do we still have something to discuss?
You are under arrest without a warrant
for the Jane Doe sewer murder.
You have the right to an attorney
and the right not to incriminate yourself.
You will have the chance
to explain yourself
and the right to request
a detention review from the court.
Why are you so set on arresting me?
On what grounds are you accusing me
of being a murderer this time?
The Jane Doe sewer murder case.
As it happens, the murder occurred
on the same night as your Boudoir party.
Then you must already know.
My alibi for that day is overwhelming.
The world is kind yet indifferent.
On one side,
a lavish party can be underway
while someone freezes to death
on the other.
You let something only the suspect
and the police know slip.
It was never made public
that the victim froze to death.
And based on that statement,
you have become the last person
to see the victim alive
and the only suspect
who knows the cause of death.
If you had taken the entire 50 billion won
and disappeared,
I would've thought
it was a meticulously planned murder.
But you didn't do that.
Something happened that day, didn't it?
Accidental killings
can be a mitigating factor.
Was it premeditated?
Or were you
acting on impulse?
Could I have a cigarette?
We've got her.
Whether she calls it
premeditated or impulsive,
she's finally admitting
she committed the murder.
God, I tried so hard to quit these things.
Did you know?
Every single wealthy person I met
quit smoking
so they could live longer.
Detective, have you ever thought,
"I want to live just a day longer"?
No matter how desperately
I tried to be like them,
I couldn't even bring myself
to think something like that.
Have I become like this
because I lived tirelessly?
Or did I live tirelessly
to become like this?
Detective.
The reason people trusted me
isn't because I had some special skill.
I just knew
what they desperately wanted.
And it appears
you want something from me too.
You're desperate for my confession.
Detective.
I did some research before coming here.
"The arrest warrant must be requested
within 48 hours of arresting the suspect."
"If the warrant is not requested
or is not issued within 48 hours,
the suspect must be immediately released."
What comes next?
That's right.
"A person released under this regulation
cannot be rearrested for the same crime
without a warrant."
If I run, I'm a con artist.
Arrested, I'm a murderer.
But if I get released from here,
what would people call me?
You have 47 hours left now.
WARRANT REQUEST DEADLINE
Subtitle translation by: Yung Un Choi