(Lee Jae In, Kim Woo Seok, Choi Ye Bin)
(Cha Woo Min, An Ji Ho, Jung So Ri)
(Scriptwriter: Kang Min Ji)
(Director: Im Dae Woong)
(Night Has Come)
(All people, organizations, locations, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
Ju Won. Let me give this a shot.
Stand right there.
Here it goes.
(Jin Da Bum)
(Jin Da Bum, your identity is the Mafia.)
Darn it. Die!
Die!
Let's kill him.
Are you sure?
If he dies too, they might be onto you.
So say that we don't.
Do you think he won't come after us?
Besides, this jerk...
knows that I'm the Mafia.
What?
So everyone agrees that we kill Ko Kyung Jun, right?
We just need to catch the Police now.
It'll be over soon.
Are you okay?
Yes.
During the night, Ko Kyung Jun was executed by the Mafia.
Ko Kyung Jun was a Citizen.
All participants, identify the Mafia and begin to vote.
They were at each other's throats yesterday.
Yet, they both died on the same day.
Exactly.
I know that the Mafia had to execute someone.
But did they have to be this cruel?
(Jin Da Bum)
We should...
move the guys first.
No.
I won't do it.
If you want to do it, you do it.
Hey, where are you going?
Let's go.
We were supposed to stay together until the vote.
We can reassemble at night.
We don't even know which one of us are Mafia.
Staying together sounds riskier.
Come on.
We must identify the Mafia today.
If another Citizen dies, we'll be doomed.
Who could it be?
I thought about it.
Then I realized something weird.
Kyung Jun and Jin Ha...
They both died on the day Yoon Seo suspected them.
What?
Are you saying Yoon Seo is the Mafia?
Well, I might be wrong.
But it's odd that she's always hurrying to move the bodies.
I just thought that was weird.
It'd be nice if the Police would step up at times like this.
Who are you going to vote out?
I told you Yoon Seo seemed off from the get-go.
Think about the security cameras and the ghost she rambled about.
I think she's trying to distract us from playing the game on purpose.
But...
Yoon Seo didn't seem like the type to lie.
How could you possibly know that?
Kyung Jun also said she was the Mafia.
Besides, he was right about Woo Ram.
So naturally, Kyung Jun must be right again.
Don't you agree?
Mi Na.
- What? - Don't you agree?
I don't know.
Can we talk?
Talk about what?
Come out for a second.
(Ahn Na Hee, Lee Yoon Seo, Oh Jung Won, Jin Da Bum,)
(Kim Jun Hee, Choi Mi Na, Kim So Mi, Nam Yeon Woo, Im Eun Chan)
There are only nine of us left.
We must identify the Mafia tonight by all means.
What should we do?
Even if we were to make it through the night,
someone would end up dead by tomorrow anyway.
If this is truly the mission of this game,
we might be able to get out of here as long as we find the host.
Let's find the host first.
We must do whatever we can.
Yes.
But if we can't find the host before the sun goes down,
we must try to identify the Mafia.
We can't afford to vote out another Citizen.
Yes.
If we don't identify the Mafia, we'll be in danger too.
Okay.
There might be another clue other than the picture.
- Right. - Let's search this room first.
What is it?
I think Jin Da Bum is the Mafia.
- Jin Da Bum? - Yes.
Why?
Only the three of us know...
that we locked Kyung Jun up in the storage room.
To be honest, among the three of us,
he's the only one who must want to get revenge on Kyung Jun.
But it was us who wanted to steal the keys first.
What if he tells the others and we end up being suspected?
What will you do then?
I'm serious. There's something off about his gaze.
It's creepy. It's the same gaze I saw from Woo Ram.
What's going on?
What are you doing here?
What?
Aren't those Ko Kyung Jun's keys?
Yes. So...
I saw him hiding them behind the indoor fire hydrant.
What?
How come you didn't tell us that?
No way.
You guys...
wanted all the food to yourselves, didn't you?
You guys are unbelievable.
Hey, not everyone is a glutton like you.
Kyung Jun is dead.
We were hungry.
We didn't tell anyone because we were scared too.
Yeon Woo.
Aren't you hungry?
I'm not hungry.
Yoon Seo, can we open this up with that key you found?
This isn't it.
What?
Wait.
It won't open.
Let's open this up just in case.
We can just break it.
Yes. There must be tools in the storage room. We'll get them.
You'll get it back at voting time.
This is our class.
(Check the name of the game host.)
(Park Se Eun)
"Park Se Eun?"
(Swimming Pool Cafeteria)
(Oh Jung Won)
(Check the name of the game host.)
(Park Se Eun)
Park Se Eun?
"Park Se Eun?"
Hey, Park Se Eun!
(Park Se Eun)
"Park Se Eun?"
The girl who committed suicide?
What's this?
Is this real?
Se Eun was the host.
But she's dead.
How?
Yes.
How can a dead girl be the host?
I bet it's all because of the game too.
Anyway, thanks to Yoon Seo who figured out the host,
our memories came back too.
But still.
How could our memories disappear and come back?
This is crazy.
Wait.
Yoon Seo, you said you had seen a ghost before.
Was it Park Se Eun?
(Im Eun Chan)
Whatever.
So this is happening because of Park Se Eun, right?
Hey.
You were the one who found the picture.
Is it possible that you know more,
but you're not telling us?
You and Park Se Eun were close!
We were just her classmates. We had nothing to do with her.
Why are we playing this game?
Come on.
Yes.
I've barely talked to her.
- Me too. - What's wrong with Park Se Eun?
Why is she trying to kill us after committing suicide?
Park Se Eun didn't commit suicide.
The rumor says she was killed.
Someone killed her?
I heard that too.
I heard someone pushed her.
Isn't that just a rumor?
Yes.
The police said she committed suicide.
What does that have to do with this?
Mafia Game is what we have to worry about.
Wait.
Why did Se Eun start this game?
If...
she didn't commit suicide like the rumor says,
and she was trying to tell us that she died because of one of us...
Are you saying...
that one of us killed her?
One of us?
What are you looking at?
How does that make sense?
What could it be?
Does it have something to do with the Mafia?
Hey.
Who were the Mafias?
Woo Ram.
Ju Won. Ye Won.
The rest are unknown.
Hey, Park Woo Ram killed Ju Young.
He said he wanted to kill him...
because Ju Young always disregarded him.
Did he...
kill Park Se Eun too?
Between the two,
did anything happen?
Do you know anything?
We wouldn't know.
Park Woo Ram wasn't committed.
Maybe he flirted at Park Se Eun too.
Then...
did all this happen because of Park Woo Ram?
But...
if Woo Ram killed Se Eun,
what about the other Mafias?
What did they do?
What?
What do you want to say?
About Se Eun.
She died because of us, didn't she?
Are you crazy?
Why would you bring that up now?
She wouldn't have died unless that happened.
We should tell everyone...
and beg Se Eun for forgiveness.
Then she might save us.
Tell everyone about what?
It was just a joke. It wasn't a big deal.
We did nothing wrong. Why...
would we beg for forgiveness?
So Mi, let's just confess.
I'm scared.
Please...
keep your mouth closed, will you?
If you tell everyone, they'll all vote us out.
We'll die today even before we get to apologize.
So,
don't say anything stupid and get a grip.
Okay.
Na Hee.
Wipe your tears before you go in.
What are you doing?
What if someone sees us?
Ahn Na Hee's going to cause trouble.
What do we do?
- What trouble? - About Park Se Eun!
She's going to tell everyone about what happened.
What if other kids find out?
So what?
Hey.
You shouldn't have crossed the line.
Why did you have to bully her so much?
- Hey! - Ahn Na Hee!
You're in charge of that wench.
So you should've paid attention to her.
You neglected her for too long while hanging out with Choi Mi Na.
You're the one who threatened her.
Now you make it sound like it's none of your business?
Who else knows other than you?
Too bad I already killed everyone who knows.
It has nothing to do with me now.
Do you really want to die, loser?
If she talks about Park Se Eun,
we can't protect you anymore.
Better take care of it.
Dang it.
This is Kyung Jun's.
I found it here.
I thought you needed to see it too.
What was that doing here?
I went to see Jin Ha,
and Da Bum went to give the phone to Kyung Jun.
I think the door was slammed with a chair.
It wasn't like this yesterday.
No.
Was it Ko Kyung Jun?
Something's strange.
Jin Ha and Kyung Jun suspected each other of killing Seung Bin,
and they both ended up dying.
What if...
the Mafia planned to kill both from the start?
We fell for it too.
Dang it.
What took you so long!
I was petrified to see a ghost.
Hey.
Park Se Eun is forcing us to play a game after becoming a ghost.
Aren't you scared?
Stop talking about a ghost!
Why are you yelling?
Hey.
We don't even know what's going to happen after voting tonight.
Who cares about the ghost?
What now?
Who are you going to vote out?
After listening to you, I thought about it.
And Jin Da Bum...
looks suspicious.
On top of Kyung Jun and the other kids being dead,
even when Park Se Eun treated him like he was invisible,
do you remember how he kept talking to her?
- Stop it. - Wait.
Right.
So other kids thought he had a crush on her.
Then what?
Vote Jin Da Bum out?
No.
If we vote him out now,
other kids will suspect us because of the keys.
What do you want to do then?
There is...
one more suspicious person apart from him.
Who?
Did you go to the storage room...
on the second floor last night?
No. Why?
Kyung Jun's phone was there.
You were the last person who saw Kyung Jun yesterday.
We were wondering if you knew anything.
No, I don't.
I didn't go see Kyung Jun alone.
So Mi and Mi Na came along too.
Yes?
Did you see where Ko Kyung Jun went last night?
I knew it.
Hey.
You were lying when you said you found the keys, weren't you?
Aren't those Ko Kyung Jun's keys?
Yes. So...
No, it's true.
What keys?
They have Kyung Jun's keys.
I saw them in the cafeteria earlier.
It's a misunderstanding.
I already explained everything yesterday.
Tell us what happened.
Kyung Jun wouldn't have given you the keys for no reason.
I saw him hiding them behind the indoor fire hydrant. That's all.
Hey.
You didn't get along with Se Eun.
What do you mean?
You never talked to Se Eun, and you always ignored her.
When did we?
I never did that.
Stop lying.
You always gossiped about her with other girls.
Eun Ha told me.
What kind of nonsense is that?
The more I think about it, the stranger it is.
Are you...
the Mafias?
Wait.
To be honest,
I know...
who started the rumor about Se Eun's video.
What?
Kim So Mi voted...
for Ahn Na Hee.
Choi Mi Na...
voted for Choi Mi Na.
(Voting announcement)
What are you doing?
She said...
Woo Ram showed her the video.
I should've stopped them.
She's the one who spread the rumor.
Na Hee, did you?
Hey, is there really a video?
Yes.
Ahn Na Hee spread the rumor and the video.
When did I?
You created the video.
You hated Se Eun because of Jun Hee.
You started the rumor. Why are you framing me?
Stop it for goodness' sake!
Do we all have to die...
because of you?
It wasn't me.
I'm the Mafia?
Are you...
going to take responsibility for what you said?
You're the one who needs to take responsibility.
Sure.
We'd know who's telling the truth if we checked.
Can I check your identity now?
How are you going to check that?
I'll show you.
I'm the Police.
What are you talking about?
Stop lying!
(Kim So Mi is the Mafia.)
Take responsibility for what you said now.
(Night Has Come)
(Gwangju Information and Content Agency)
(This content was produced through Gwangju Information and...)
(Content Agency's 2022 OTT Platform Content Production Business.)