No, you can do it.
- I told you, I can't.
- Why not?
When was the first time...
I really noticed him?
In that ordinary, crowded place...
he was the only one...
who stood out so clearly.
"Contrast"
(Episode 2: He always stood out so clearly)
Senkawa...
Senkawa-kun...
Akira-kun...
Hmm?
Hey, Aki-chin...
Just call me Akira.
Oh, really?
Akira, you're not getting bullied, are you?
Why do you ask?
Because you're always alone.
You don't really have a
group you hang out with.
I'm not.
I just don't have anyone
I'm particularly close to.
I'm not being bullied.
My relationship with my
classmates is... normal, I guess.
I see. How about sports?
Sports?
I'm not good at them. No talent.
I'm usually last in the marathon.
We're kind of an interesting pair.
How so?
Hmm?
Just us.
But I think it's nice.
Is it?
Don't you think?
We're pretty rare. Total opposites.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Hey, so...
If we went on a trip, where would you go?
The beach or the mountains?
Let's say it at the same time.
Ready, set...
- The beach.
Wait, we actually matched.
Hey, so what are you going to call me?
Huh? Why?
Oh, I know.
Call me Kana-chin.
Why that?
Kana-chin is good.
I'll just call you Kanata.
Kana-chin.
Try saying it once. Just once.
Um...
What's up?
We're in the same cram school.
I'm Nakano Mizuki.
Same high school, too.
And...
I'm a friend of Aoyama Kanata's.
Huh?
Sorry for being so sudden.
I saw you and Kanata together today.
You two seem really close.
Akira.
Sorry I'm late.
Huh?
A friend of yours?
Oh, we're in the same cram school.
I see.
I'm...
Senkawa-kun's tutor.
Oh, I see.
Um...
Please don't tell Kanata about this.
Sorry.
Let's talk later.
Let's go.
Okay.
Alright, that's 200 yen.
Stop pushing.
Line up properly like always.
Hurry up, 200 yen.
Okay, okay.
How many times do I
have to say no large bills?
Hey, you're short 100 yen.
Come on, give me a break.
Here, 200, 200.
Man, math class went on forever.
How about you, Jun?
- Got the curry bread.
- Me too.
Mizuki's worried about you.
About what?
The soccer thing.
You know...
You went to see the
game the other day, right?
Yeah.
So she found out.
There's no reason to hide it.
Mizuki and I...
have known you since middle school.
But isn't your injury all healed up?
What injury?
Nothing.
Then get back out there and play.
You quit soccer because of that injury...
It's fine.
Sorry.
No, it's okay.
Forget it. Let's not talk about soccer.
My bad.
You two are totally different types.
I was thinking the same thing.
What do you guys even talk about?
- Nothing special, just normal stuff.
- Yeah.
Seriously?
Even your grades are on different levels.
How are you guys so close?
Shut up.
It doesn't matter.
Ah.
Wait, actually it does.
If I keep this up...
I won't get into the same
high school as Akira.
What should I do?
Then you have to study.
Just study?
Then teach me, Akira!
Are you asleep?
No.
You're earlier than usual today.
Yeah.
I thought I'd eat here.
Don't you want to be with your friends?
Nah.
It's fine.
Akira, have you decided yet?
- Huh?
- What you're doing after this.
Yeah.
Just a normal university.
One with a high rank?
Yeah.
Wow, I can't do that.
Why not?
I'm not smart enough.
Do you want to go to the
same university as me?
Well, it'd be fun if we could go together.
Even if the schools are different...
as long as they're close by, it's fine.
I guess so.
Besides...
there's no guarantee
we'll still be friends then.
That's...
You mean we'll be best friends?
You're getting ahead of yourself.
Let's eat.
Thanks for the food.
It's already cold.
Senkawa-kun.
Right?
Oh...
Kanata's...
Yeah, can we talk for a bit?
Senkawa-kun...
When did you and Kanata get so close?
Oh.
We only started talking recently.
Really?
You guys seem so close.
I thought you'd known
each other for a long time.
I see.
He's been disappearing during lunch lately.
I guess it's because he's with you.
Pretty much.
Kanata...
always has a crowd around him in class.
He looks like he's having fun.
But that's not really the case.
Did you hear about the soccer thing?
A little bit.
Then...
do you know why he stopped playing?
Yeah, sort of.
About Kanata's injury...
That...
was my fault.
Huh?
I...
I've known Kanata since middle school.
Back then...
he was completely devoted to soccer.
I should have stopped him.
Did you hear about Kanata's brother?
The one who got scouted, right?
What? Is he a celebrity?
No, he's a youth team player.
But Kanata's really good too, isn't he?
Yeah, but he's just in a school club.
Kanata.
Can you grab those handouts for me?
Why me?
Just do it, stop complaining.
Watch out!
Kanata?
Your leg...
I'm fine.
I just twisted it a bit.
I'm so sorry, I...
You have a game the day after tomorrow.
I told you, I'm fine.
But...
This won't affect the game at all.
Besides...
I don't have time to be resting.
But...
He ended up playing in that game anyway.
He tried to protect his
ankle and got seriously hurt.
That's...
That wasn't your fault.
Yeah.
Kanata told me the same thing.
He said playing was his own decision.
But...
I'm the reason it happened.
I...
I want Kanata to keep playing soccer.
I don't want him to give
up on what he loves.
But... that's just me being selfish.
I can tell you really care about Kanata.
So...
Don't be so hard on yourself.
Thank you.
But, um...
I have a favor to ask.
A favor?
Crap, I haven't thought about it at all.
Seriously, what am I gonna do?
We're already second-years, this is bad.
Huh?
You're in the same cram school as Mizuki?
Yeah.
I asked her what class she was in...
and found out she's in yours.
She never mentioned it to me.
So she knows I know you?
Yeah.
She said she saw us together.
Did Mizuki say anything to you?
Like what?
Nothing.
Never mind.
She said you're popular.
Huh?
That you're always surrounded by people.
Oh.
So that's what she meant.
What?
Well...
How should I put it?
I just manage things well.
Manage things?
I talk about what everyone
wants to talk about.
I do what everyone wants to do.
When things get serious...
I just laugh it off.
Peacefully.
Like it's nothing.
I see.
Actually...
Actually?
Is it emptiness...
or just feeling unsettled?
People around me...
keep asking why I don't go back.
To soccer?
I'm actually scared.
It's embarrassing to say...
but going back after
such a long break...
I'll probably just end up in pain again.
If I keep going like this...
I'm afraid I'll end up hating it.
But...
I also wonder if this is really okay.
I just feel...
constantly anxious.
Of course, I support my brother.
With him...
I think becoming a pro isn't just a dream.
But...
When I look at him...
For some reason...
I just feel pathetic.
I don't even know what
I'm thinking anymore.
In your heart...
right now...
what are you sure of?
In my heart?
Yeah.
I want to play soccer.
Seriously.
One more time.
Because...
I still love soccer.
Then...
That feeling...
protect it for yourself.
People find their own paths
in many different places.
You don't need to compare yourself.
If you're serious about it...
you'll feel the
hardship and frustration.
But you'll also feel real joy...
and happiness, won't you?
Right?
Akira...
Thank you.
For what?
For everything...
(Akira: I'm counting on you) (Kanata:
Akira, what do you usually do after school?)
Huh?
Kanata, why aren't you back in the room?
Just taking a break.
Mizuki.
Yeah?
Why didn't you tell me about Akira?
Oh, Senkawa-kun.
No, it's just...
I thought you might not like it.
What?
Because...
Kanata...
you don't really talk about
serious stuff with us, right?
But...
I thought you might be able to talk
to Senkawa-kun about those things.
It felt like a special place for you.
Oh, no.
I'm not saying you
have to tell us everything.
I just felt like if I stepped into...
somewhere so important to
you, it might be uncomfortable.
I just...
wanted you to be able to relax.
Hey.
I'm thinking...
about playing soccer again.
Huh?
But you know...
Our school is weak.
I don't think we'll get any good results.
That's not true.
You can do it.
If it's you, Kanata, I know you can.
Thanks.
Mizuki.
Let's go back.
Oh.
I should tell Jun and
Makki I'm playing again.
They'll be annoying if I don't.
We'll give you all our support.
I'll do my best.
Wow, today was so much fun.
- Seriously.
- So much fun.
You're a great singer.
Me?
- You were really good.
- Thanks.
- Makki was terrible, though.
- No I wasn't!
- Didn't you hear him?
- I was great! I killed it from the start!
(Akira: Either at cram school or at home)
(Kanata: So you're at home today?)(Akira: Yeah)
What are you doing?
Don't look.
I'm just texting a friend.
You found a good friend, huh?
Yeah.
Come to think of it...
I don't really have any
friends I keep in touch with.
What?
Is it someone you like?
Well...
I don't know.
Maybe... something like that.
Oh?
I'm jealous.
You don't mean that at all.
Oh, right.
Did I interrupt you the other day?
The other day?
At the cram school entrance.
Weren't you talking to a friend?
No.
It's fine.
True... nothing to be suspicious of.
It's not like I'm lying
about being a tutor.
A 'former' tutor, anyway.
True.
But, um...
I have a favor to ask.
A favor?
The person I was with...
Um...
Oh, you mean the tutor?
Yeah.
About him...
Could you please not tell Kanata?
Yeah.
I understand.
Let's go.
The 'me' that Kanata sees...
is definitely...
not who I really am.
(Next Episode)
We've never met outside of school.
Then, want to go somewhere?
Wow, amazing!
Is it an accessory?
Thanks for the food.
Crap, crap, crap!
Kanata?