Really? Are you sure?
They broke up?
How did that happen?
I swear, bestie!
I was just as shocked!
Weren’t they a power couple?
They’re so perfect
for each other!
Football team captain,
and the president of
the student council.
And he’s running
for class salutatorian…
…while she’s the cheer captain
and title holder of Miss St. Collete High!
They were literally
the perfect couple.
Such a good match.
- What a waste.
- Why’d they break up though?
Wow! News really travels fast.
Sheen is such a weakling.
Right? He let Kei
go just like that.
The whole school found
out about the breakup first?
But I’m his best friend!
I heard they broke up
because of the transferee.
Drake Palma!
Drake Palma?!
- Drake Palma?!
Drake Palma?
The cute guy who suddenly
appeared at St. Collete?
Yes! That Drake Palma!
- Drake Palma?
- Exactly.
And because of
that rumor, here I am.
Running and running and running.
Checking every corner of the school
just to find the “Man of the Hour.”
The center of all the
gossip at St. Collete High.
By the way, I’m Alys.
Senior student.
I believe in the saying…
If you love someone, go all out!
Give it everything.
And of course,
I’m giving all my time to help
heal the broken heart of My Loves…
…my best friend--
Sheen.
Sheen!
I knew you’d be here!
Kei and I broke up.
I know.
How did you know?
We just broke up earlier.
Kei is the worst.
She found someone cuter
and dropped Sheen just like that.
Drake Palma?
Pfft!
Sheen’s way cuter than that guy.
Just be glad they’re done.
You’ve been waiting
for this forever, bestie!
Fine, I’ll go check on Sheen.
For sure, he’s already sulking.
Of course!
I’m good at this!
Don’t get all emo!
That’s so not you!
I’m just not used
to seeing you sad.
That’s why you
became my best friend…
because you’re always smiling.
Your good vibes are contagious.
I want to sulk, okay.
Here.
What am I supposed
to do with that?
Eyeliner!
You want to be an emo, right?
Go all in!
You’re the worst!
No, I’m helping you--
- There!
- Use it--
Please!
See? You’re not even using it.
What’s up with you?
Psst...
What?
Seriously.
- What is it?
- I want her back!
Boogsh!
That hurts!
Help me out.
Ugh.
Why is it like this when
you're the best friend?
Always the one helping.
Always the one sacrificing.
Always the one secretly in love!
Make Drake Palma your boyfriend.
Huh?
What?
Make Drake Palma your boyfriend!
Sheen!
Hey!
Alys!
Wow.
Are you even hearing what
you’re asking me to do?
You’ve got some nerve!
You’ve already had,
like, three boyfriends!
It’s easy for you!
Unbelievable!
As easy as one, two, three? Really?
I can’t even go near that guy!
His vibe is super scary!
Totally intimidating!
Come on.
Come on, please.
If a face this handsome
begged you like this…
Could you really say no?
Fine! You’re so
annoying! I’m in!
Girl, wait!
Did you really say yes?!
Maybe you
could still take it back--
Thanks, Alys!
You’re the best!
Thank you!
Yeah, yeah, thanks my butt!
There’s a fee for
that, you know!
Okay, okay!
I’ll treat you to lunch
the whole week. Deal?
Not enough! All meals!
Even snacks!
You’re such a freeloader!
I’m telling your mom!
As if you’d dare!
I know you love me!
What?
- Try me!
- What?
What? Come on!
See?
We’re only sweet and romantic
when it’s just the two of us.
If I trip--
Wait!
Oh, life.
Things would have been
so simple and happy.
But of course…
I know Kei’s the
one he really likes.
Wait! Wait!
Hold up! Hold up!
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
You’re all talk!
Come on, just admit it…
Are you really heartbroken?
You’re chasing like you
drank a full energy drink!
I am broken, okay!
It just doesn’t show.
And why would I worry…
You’re gonna help
me get Kei back, right?
What if I can’t?
I know you can.
Why are you so sure I can?
Because… you’re Alys Perez!
And when you want something,
you get it by hook or by crook!
What? Where did that come from?
For me, I like you,
but I just can’t have you.
Whatever, Sheen!
You talk too much!
You know, I wonder…
- Alys.
- Hmm?
Most best friends end up
falling for each other, right?
So?
Why didn’t that ever happen with us?
Because ours is unrequited love.
You talk about
nothing else but Kei!
Darn it!
Makes sense. I’m not into you either.
You talk too much!
And you’re clumsy!
You know that?
And you always flunk
your exams… always--
Ouch!
What? Do you want help or not?
I’m not done yet.
If you weren’t like that,
you wouldn’t be Alys Perez.
And if you weren’t Alys Perez…
What would happen
to Sheen Mendoza?
K-Drama you say? Ugh!
You’re being too sweet, Sheen!
Lord, why does it have to be like this?
How am I supposed to stay
mad when my best friend who I like…
…is hugging me like this?
And we both know…
that between me and Kei…
he’ll still end up running
back to Kei in the end.
Fine, Sheen! Fine!
I’m heading out.
I’ve got a mission to do…
all because of you.
Love you, Alys!
Bye!
I might not be smart
in academics but
I know the difference between
friends and more-than-friends.
That “love you”?
We’re not taking that seriously!
That’s how real pain
and heartbreak starts.
We’re only allowed
to fake sulk, okay?
Where’s my notebook?
Damn you, Kei!
I really like this guy,
and you’re just making him cry?!
Don’t worry, Sheen, My Loves…
Drake Palma, you
better watch out!
I’m going to get you by hook…
…or by crook!
I love you, Drake Palma!
- Thank you.
What? Seriously?
Do I look like I'd joke
about something like this?
You always believe Sheen
the moment he says anything…
…you're just all go.
You don’t even think!
Then again, when have
you ever used your brain?
Uhm!
You're just as bad!
Are you even really my friend?
You’re so mean!
- Oh, come on…
- What?
I was just kidding!
You can’t take a joke?
But seriously though…
Your mission is challenging.
You know that guy's kind of weird.
Well actually,
Drake is really weird.
He’s always sleeping in class but always
getting perfect scores on quizzes?
While I’m wide
awake and still failing!
I really don’t get it.
I have no idea.
Bestie, please help me!
I don’t even have
a boyfriend!
How am I supposed
to help you?
Ugh!
Life, why are you so hard on me?
I just want Sheen to be
my boyfriend, that’s all!
Ouch!
You’re so dramatic,
you know that?
You’re ruining my day!
Fight me.
Sometimes I really
wonder why Aya's my friend.
There are so many people better than her.
She’s always hitting and hurting me!
Sometimes she even
teases me when I fail my exams.
Well, she fails, too!
I don’t know anymore.
But seriously, you really
don’t have any suggestions?
Tips? Or advice?
Bestie.
How exactly are
you going to pull off
“Mission Impossible:
Seducing Drake Palma”?
Hi, Drake!
Oh, hi, Drake!
I didn't see you there.
Hi, Drake!
Hi, Drake.
How am I even supposed to
introduce myself to that snob?
Hi, Sheen, My Loves.
Alys?
Yes, Mom?
Hi, what's up?
Oh, nothing.
I'm just here because I've made
a few sketches for the gowns.
It’s for the acquaintance ball.
So we can prepare early.
- Oh. Okay, Mom. I'll check it out.
- Here.
Oh, my god, Mom. All
of these are so pretty.
You're so good at this, Mom.
You're the best!
Hmmm…
- You're the best!
- My daughter is such a flatterer.
Anyway, Manang
already prepared dinner…
…so just come down so
we can eat together, okay?
And then check that one out later.
Okay, Mom. I’ll
be right behind you.
Okay. Don't take too long.
Yes, Mom.
Hi, Drake.
Alys!
Yes, Mom. Coming.
So, Manang, just bring that
over there, okay?
Oh, Dad!
You’re here! I thought you
were on a business trip?
Yeah, I was. But…
I missed you and your mom.
So I decided to come
home, even just for a bit.
- Ahh.
- Oh, before I forget.
Just take care of this, Manang.
Surprise!
Oh, my gosh! Dad!
- Oh my--
- This is a lot, Dad!
You deserve it.
You know, Alys,
you’re getting spoiled.
Why are you getting gifts when…
we haven’t even seen
her report card yet.
Alys, do your grades
deserve these gifts?
I think my grades are fine.
- Hmmm…
- I think.
Just make sure that
“fine” and “I think”…
…can actually get you into a
good college—if not the best!
You know St. Collete Academy
is still the best in the country.
Of course, if the
princess gets a gift…
…the queen should get one, too.
What's that?
You didn't have to.
- Dad’s so sweet.
- I wanted to.
My god.
Let’s try it on.
It’s so pretty.
- Look.
- Wow, Mom, it really suits you.
- So pretty, Mom!
- See? It’s beautiful, right?
- Thank you.
- It suits you!
Thank you, hon.
It looks good, Mom.
Alright, well.
Eat your dinner now.
Thank you.
They’re having a concert
here this November.
Hmm?
Too bad, my bias still hasn’t
finished military service.
But you’re still going?
Hey! I’m asking you! Hey!
Hello?
What are you even looking at?
Banana.
Let’s follow him,
quick. Let’s go!
Wait, my pizza! My pizza!
I might drop it!
Girl, I’ll just leave it
here for now, okay?
Hurry!
Where do you think he’s going?
That’s why we’re following him.
Calm down, bestie! Relax!
We’re following him so we’ll know!
Come on! You go first.
Wait—do we have
homework for tomorrow?
Did you guys know
we have an exam later?
- Did you study?
- For Filipino?
You studied?
Nice. Nice. Nice.
Thank you! Thank you!
Who were those?
Do you know them?
Looks like our classmates.
Hurry, before Drake disappears.
Huh?
Nap is life?
Let’s go.
He’s just sleeping!
Bestie, wait, wait!
Ouch, bestie!
There’s a girl, look.
Drake!
In fairness, she’s pretty.
Hmm.
- Drake Palma!
- What did she say?
Come on.
Bestie, you’re too loud!
Ouch!
I like you, Drake.
Can you be my…
…boyfriend?
That girl is brave.
Go, sis!
We salute your fighting spirit.
Okay.
What the--
That’s it?
Really?
We’re done.
That’s really it?
What do you mean?
Drake, we just became
a thing and now…
…it’s over? We’re
breaking up already?
You want bragging rights, right?
There.
Poor girl.
Hmp!
What just happened, bestie?
Drake Palma, you’re the worst.
Karma’s going to get you.
Karma’s coming.
Well, there you go, bestie.
It’s actually easy to make
Drake your boyfriend.
He’s really easy to talk to.
I don’t get his logic at all.
What just happened?
A two-second relationship?
Yup! And that’s exactly
what you need. Come on!
Huh?
Listen to me.
Hmm.
Talk to Drake
like what that girl did.
Then tell Sheen, Your Loves,
that you already broke up.
See? Problem solved!
Oh--
But that’s embarrassing!
He’s our classmate!
Come on! That’s fine!
For all you know, he
doesn’t even know you exist.
So, don’t worry, bestie!
Actually, you have a point there, bestie.
But it’s annoying,
he doesn’t even mingle with
our classmates…
That jerk, Drake Palma!
It really makes me wonder…
…why did he even
transfer to St. Collete?
I don’t know.
So annoying!
But I really felt
bad for that girl earlier.
- Yeah, same.
- I hope she’s okay.
Right!
So, are you going to do it?
For all the girls who were hurt by Drake!
There you go! That’s the spirit!
Game!
I’ll tell him later.
For that girl.
But most of all…
…for Sheen, My Loves!
That’s my bestie!
Letting love make her a fool!
You better watch out, Drake Palma!
Good luck with your
mission impossible, bestie.
Aja!
As always, perfect score…
…for Mr. Palma!
A round of applause, please!
- How?
- I don’t know!
Maybe that’s just how weirdos are?
I know.
Ms. Perez? Ms. Pineda?
I said Ms. Perez and Ms. Pineda!
Are you with us?
Yes, Ma'am!
Good! Get your papers.
Ms. Perez, failed.
Pineda, failed.
Hey. Let’s go.
Let’s just eat out our feelings.
Let’s go to a karaoke.
Go ahead, you go first.
Sad much?
Come on, you act like you’ve
never had a low score before.
What was that again earlier?
Idiot! I still have a mission, remember?
What? You’re going to beg our teacher?
It’s the promise I made to Sheen!
Oh, I got it.
You want me to pray for you to St. Collete?
Forget it. Just go. Go!
- Okay, fine! Good luck!
- Do your best!
Please don't leave me.
Please.
Please come back.
Psst.
- Psst.
- What?
What do you want?
Uhm…
I’m just tying my shoelace.
Seriously?
Is it wrong to tie shoelaces now?
That was close!
Good thing I got away with it!
Thank you, St. Collete!
Thank you, shoe...
...lace.
I don’t have a shoelace!
Yes, Alys! You got this!
You can do it!
Let’s go, Alys! You got this!
Yes, Alys! You got this!
Get back at him for that girl earlier.
…for everyone he’s hurt—
For Sheen!
Let’s go! You can do this!
Come on. You’re not gonna
let him win. You got this.
You got this. For all the—
Oh, crap!
What?
- Oh, my god.
- What?
It's now or never.
Drake Palma!
You’re my boyfriend now!
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
Onee...
We’re done!
Okay. Bye!
From now on,
you’re my idol, bestie!
Damn, you were so cool!
Five, four, three, two, one!
We’re done!
Bye!
Hey! Would you stay quiet?!
Oh, my god.
Picture, please!
As if he’d even remember
you with all the exes he’s had.
It’s fine!
At least I’ve already done the request of
Sheen My Loves.
Oh, Alys.
My ever-martyr best friend.
You’re really so into Sheen!
When are you going to tell him
you’ve completed the mission?
Wait. Let me check if he’s on the rooftop.
Bye!
Alright. Congrats, bestie!
Kei.
Why’d you ask me to come here!?
I love you and I want you back.
Don't you get it, Sheen?
We're over!
Why are you acting like this?
Is this because of that Drake Palma guy?
What do you care?
Come on, Kei.
You know he’s a player.
He always has a new girlfriend.
Kei, please!
I know!
But he always dumps them anyway.
Then why do you want to chase him?
Do you really think
he’ll take you seriously?
I'll show you that he
will take me seriously.
Kei...
I’m taking Drake back.
Damn, this life!
I’m the one who broke up with him,
and now I’m the one trying to get him back.
But anything for you, Sheen.
I got you.
Wow! Kei really said that?
Yeah!
So basically, she wants to be
the first girl Drake will take seriously.
That’s why she’s acting like that.
So, she’s just feeling challenged by Drake?
Pretty much.
So what’s your plan,
Ms. Alys Zyril Perez?
I don’t know.
Looks like I have to get back with Drake.
The way you say it—
Like you two were even officially together?
Why, weren’t we?
Technically, we were.
And take note!
I’m the one who dumped him.
M-E. Me!
And you’re also the one
trying to get back with him!
Y-O-U. You!
Aya, can you be supportive just once?
Try it!
Just try!
It’s hard when you look like that.
Come on!
I’m just kidding! Fine.
I’ll be serious now.
So what are you gonna do now?
I don’t know!
Does this face look
like it knows what to do?
Huh?
An entrepreneur needs
to have an innovative
mindset if you want to
stand out in the market.
You also have to have or
recognize potential markets.
Ms. Perez?
Oh, shocks! Here we go again.
Ms. Perez!
Oh! Yes, ma’am?
Are you even listening?
Yes, Ma'am.
Then what did I just say?
Okay, ma’am. Let me
just ask for a detention slip.
Go to the admin of the Student Affairs.
Ma'am…
Ms. Perez, I really don't know
what I can do with you anymore.
Same, Ma'am. Same.
Oh, Alys!
All you do is collect problems.
Ms. Perez, what brings you here?
Let me guess.
Detention again?
Let’s see where you’re assigned today.
Lord, please let it be the library.
Not the cafeteria.
Not the bathroom either, gross!
Please, Lord?
Just a little bit of joy, please.
There!
You’re assigned to the computer lab.
Thank you, Lord.
You will be detained
together with Sheen Mendoza.
Seriously!?
Sheen!?
Yes, Ms. Perez!
He got caught cutting class.
What’s going on? This is a first!
Sheen’s not a regular in
detention like me.
But thank you, Lord.
You’re really easy to talk to!
Alright then, go on.
Head to the computer lab
so you don’t stay too late.
I’d even stay all night!
What was that, Ms. Perez?
Nothing, Ma’am. Thank you.
Bye.
Jeez, kids these days…
Where is he?
Sheen.
Oops!
Sorry.
So, Drake, are you dating anyone now?
Huh?
What the hell?
What time is it?
Uhm…
It’s 4:30.
What’s this?
Uhm… a watch?
What do you take me for?
Of course, I know it’s a watch.
But why’d you put it on me?
Alys, you’re a senior.
And you still can’t read analog?
You rely too much on digital.
It’s the same time either way.
Fine! I’ll learn, okay? Geez.
Fine, okay! I’ll practice.
Remember that, okay?
Come on.
Let’s start shutting down the computers.
Hey, Alys.
Let’s go.
This is my favorite moment.
Just the two of us.
You…
Me...
No Kei.
Just me.
I agree.
You and Drake look good together.
Like a perfect girl like me?
For a perfect boy like Drake.
Speaking of…
Aren’t you gonna follow Drake, Kei?
No need.
I'll make him mine tomorrow.
You sure, girl?
Yeah!
What Kei wants…
…Kei gets.
Right?
Let's go, guys.
Alys, I’ll go ahead, okay?
Can’t walk you home today, sorry.
Sheen!
Huhu. What do I do?
Even though I love Sheen so much,
I’d still rather he gets
back together with Kei…
…than see him crying like this every day.
Being in love is such
an inconvenience!
Where the heck is Drake, anyway?
I need to follow him
and get back together with him.
All for Sheen My Loves!
Where are you going, weirdo?
This guy’s house is so far!
Are we even still in the Philippines?
Huh?
A house this big?
It’s impossible they don’t have a car.
Why does he have to walk this far?
Who’s that?
Drake has a live-in partner!
Okay. False alarm.
I was really shocked by that.
Me?
Me?!
Oh no.
Hey, let me go, Drake.
Drake!
Hey, let me go.
Drake, who is she?
I’m his girlfriend.
I’m Alys.
Alys Zyril Perez...
...soon to be Palma. Hello!
Tss. What does she want now?
Yes, Alys! You can do it! You got this!
Let’s go, Alys! You weren’t born a coward!
You got this!
You can do it.
Oh, crap!
It's now or never.
Drake Palma!
You’re my boyfriend now!
Five...
Four…
Three...
Two...
One...
We’re done!
Okay! Bye!
Well, that's a first.
Did that girl just really break up with me?
Yes!
On the next episode of
Seducing Drake Palma.
Are you stalking me now?
Sheen’s here because I’m
introducing him to my boyfriend.
You? Drake’s girlfriend?
Why are you taking my cake?
It’s mine now. Just make a new one.
No way! This is mine!
- It’s mine now!
- This is mine!
My cake!
Hey, Drake! You’re my
boyfriend in front of Sheen and Kei!
You seriously think I like you?
Keep dreaming.
You’re ugly.