(Uilhan Brewery)
(1. Malting, 2. Malt milling, 3. Mash tun, 4. Hopping)
(Kim Se Jeong)
(Highly passionate, highly sensitive)
(Lee Jong Won)
(Shin Do Hyun)
(Baek Sung Chul)
(Uilhan Brewery)
(Naro Beer)
(Brewing Love)
(This is a work of fiction.)
(Scenes with child actors and animals were filmed...)
(under production guidelines along with experts.)
Didn't you just say you liked me?
Me? When? I wouldn't say that.
Then was it a mistake?
A mis... A mistake is...
No.
At least...
what happened just now was...
I really meant that.
It's fine, then.
- But... - I get it.
You're not yet sure how you feel.
Take the time you need to think.
I'm pretty good at waiting.
And...
There's something I really wanted to say.
Thank you for saving my life.
And...
I'm sorry you had to save my life.
I'll stick close to you and make up for the guilt.
So keep me close...
and let me wait.
Well, do whatever you want.
Stay close or not, it's up to you.
Let's get back before it gets dark.
I brought a tent.
What on earth are you...
I packed a tent.
- A ten... - A tent.
What exactly are you imagining?
Me?
I'm incapable of imagining anything.
My MBTI says I'm extremely intuitive.
No, am I sensory?
This looks tasty.
Yes. There's a lot to eat.
Here you go.
- What? - You're taking the leg?
- What the... - Thank you.
- Hey. - You all did great today.
You're so cheeky.
That's a no thanks from me. Darn you.
Is the person who called for help all right?
It was a young man in his 30s.
He sprained his ankle a bit.
That's fortunate. Why did he come all the way here and get hurt?
It was quite an eventful day.
- Good job, everyone. - Let's drink.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
What's the matter?
We have some tasty chicken so why won't any of you eat?
Ms. Chae went looking for CEO Yoon...
and she's not back yet.
- I'm dead worried. - Darn it.
No. Why worry?
I vote that wherever CEO Yoon goes,
Chae Yong Ju will find him and bring him back.
Is that your vote? I vote ten times that she'll do it.
Will you wait?
Wait up.
Hey. I was really hungry.
- Hey. - They're back.
She found him.
You found him.
- Come and sit down. - Yes, join us.
- You're back. - Take a seat.
- Were you eating? - Yes.
This looks good.
- It's really good. - Yes.
- What is this? - It's a famous place.
I just love the portions too.
- It's good. - Jot down their number.
- Here. - Let's eat.
Yes, sure.
- Go on. - Eat up.
No, I have a top.
You don't have to give me yours.
- You might catch a cold. - You don't have to...
What a dreadful sight.
Hey.
Oh, dear.
There's a mosquito.
Are you saying you don't care if we get bitten?
- It got me already. - Oh, dear.
I donated enough blood to save a life just now.
- Spit on it for me. - Shall I put this here?
Here you go.
Well...
Since when did the boss...
join us to eat as if he didn't mind?
Why don't you switch to beekeeping?
Honey drips from your eyes when you look at a certain someone.
You seem to have the wrong idea. There's nothing...
We're nothing at all.
Why are you overreacting?
We're just colleagues. That's all.
Yes. That's what she says we are.
I see.
Let's say that's what you are.
Not you too, Jjuan.
Say something.
There really isn't anything... We're nothing at all.
How about we just drink?
- Yes. - Sure. Congratulations.
You can't be so sweet and kind in the open.
Now you gave everyone the wrong idea.
- You said you'd wait. - Yes. I am waiting.
We wait under each other's noses.
That look. It's banned.
Right now, I feel... So confused.
I have no choice but to do that.
You're blocked.
Okay. Then... It can't be helped.
Are you sure you won't regret blocking me?
Yes. I don't regret.
- Are you sure? - Yes.
You're blocked!
(Brewing Love)
What the heck is this?
It's just me.
Oh Chan Hwi.
Why are you... Did you sleep here?
You don't remember?
Darn it.
Go.
Don't go?
Don't go.
Go.
Don't go?
I shouldn't go.
Wait.
Don't wait.
Wait. Don't wait.
Wait.
I should wait.
I'm pretty sure I saw...
Ah Reum receive a guy's profile from a matchmaking company.
She has a date tomorrow.
What would you think of a guy who showed up to mess it up?
Would I be a loser?
I told Yong Ju clearly that I'd wait.
She needed time to think.
But...
what would you think of a guy who can't wait?
- Would I be a loser? - Should I just go?
Should I just not wait?
I shouldn't go, should I?
I should wait, shouldn't I?
What if the guy she meets is a real catch...
and they fall for each other and things go really well?
What then?
What if she keeps me waiting?
What if she needs forever to think?
What if she tells me to wait for 1, 2, 3, 4 months?
What if she says no then?
What then?
I hate Bang Ah Reum.
I hate Chae Yong Ju.
Yes. Chae Yong Ju's worse.
Hey. That's not true.
Will you wait?
I should wait.
- Will you go? - I shouldn't go.
You liar.
What am I doing here?
She looks even more beautiful today.
We saw each other's profiles and details.
We shouldn't waste time.
I heard you're a practical and reasonable person.
To someone whose goal is marriage,
timing and conditions are more important than love.
I love you.
Right.
The couple manager said you and I were quite similar...
and that we'd suit each other and I think so too.
You seem to fit all the conditions I require in a woman.
How do you like me?
I'm a man with many secrets.
I found...
I ripped it up.
Make a wish and blow it out.
Let me date Oh Chan Hwi.
Fine, then.
What's your favorite food?
I heard you had a strict diet.
- Toasties. - What?
Toasties. They're my favorite.
Shall we wrap this up? I have another date.
Another date?
You scheduled two dates in one day?
- Well... - You're rejecting me?
Hey. You're an A minus and I'm an A plus.
I agreed to go below my grade because I couldn't stand girls...
who bragged about their families and you have zero manners.
I apologize for that.
I'll settle the bill.
Hey!
"Hey?"
Shall we go see the ocean?
Yes.
Where's the ocean?
Ocean. Where are you?
Give me your hand.
I think you're a grade A with many pluses.
How dare he call you an A minus?
Will this come off?
Hey. Ms. Beautiful.
It's not the time to say things like that.
Things were so romantic.
What if it doesn't come off?
Shall we date?
Why won't you respond?
- You don't want to? - No. I do want to.
I was shocked. That's why.
I'm all about logical judgments,
so to me, this decision is pretty impulsive.
But I don't want to have regrets.
Yes!
Ocean! We're a couple!
Chae Yong Ju!
Focus.
No, I have a top.
- You might catch a cold. - You don't have to...
Goodness.
Well, I'm worried, that's all.
If we meet again today, he'll be excessively kind.
If he were to give me his shirt in front of everyone again,
that would make me feel too uncomfortable.
No. Chae Yong Ju, focus on your job.
Draw the line and keep him blocked.
"I'd rather you not get too close."
Say that. That's it.
I look too much like a black marker.
What?
You don't like any of your clothes?
It's not that. I was looking for something new.
Yes. You should buy some clothes.
I wanted to say that long ago.
- Buy something bright. - Should I?
My hair's boring too, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Go to a hair salon and a department store this weekend.
For once, you're saying just what I like to hear.
You wanted me to say that? Why?
I don't know why, but it's oddly pleasing to hear.
What?
- I'm off. - Don't be intimidated.
Let's go.
- See you. - Bye.
Don't come outside.
(Fate)
Rao, thanks for driving.
It's my job.
Is it?
Why isn't Ah Reum here yet?
Neither is Chan Hwi.
There's Chan Hwi.
(Hwi's Toast)
Hi.
- Hey. - Hey.
Why would he drive you?
Sweetie.
- The... - Crazy...
Punk.
Ah Reum and I are together!
(The Crazy Punk)
He's at it again.
Why say that? Ms. Bang will feel uncomfortable.
I'd be sick of him already.
He shouldn't take his jokes too far.
It's true. We're dating.
What?
If you're being threatened, blink twice.
You need to rethink this.
Did you get drunk and...
It so happened.
What?
Ms. Beautiful Bang asked me out.
Why?
(Uilhan Brewery)
Mr. Yoon.
Did you hear the shocking news?
About Chan Hwi and Ms. Bang?
I don't get it.
But how do you know already when we just found out?
I'm quick to notice stuff.
I can tell right away who likes whom.
Hello.
- Oh, so how is your father? - Right.
I should've started with that.
Thank you so much for your help.
The surgery went well and he was moved to the general ward.
After my father fainted like that,
I wondered why bad things kept happening to me.
I blamed myself as if...
it were because I was useless.
Rao.
Once we move the beer to the fermentation chamber,
our job is done.
The fermenting process is left to the beer.
That's why sometimes, even though we did...
the exact same thing, we must throw out a whole batch of products.
That's because...
it's a process we can't control.
It didn't go wrong due to anyone's fault.
So try not to blame yourself too much.
Mr. Yoon.
Can we be sworn brothers?
- Let's get the samples. - I'll help you set up.
I think we can do without you.
Can't I come...
(Uilhan Brewery)
Why does it feel like he's blocking me?
Because of the price point, to make the second sample,
I took out the premium ingredients and focused on a light taste.
The second sample definitely tastes more like a mass-produced beer.
I would be widely accepted and the aroma's not too strong.
It's a good thing that everyone could like it,
but that could be a weakness too.
It doesn't have a distinct feature.
It's good from a cost point of view.
Cost is the most important to me.
But taste-wise, I like the first one.
The second one is better to mix soju with.
Koreans love somaek...
that's easy to drink.
Youngsters these days...
don't drink that much somaek like in the past.
They want to drink something premium even if it's just one glass.
I like the first one more.
First one and second one. It's a 50-50.
Honestly, it's a fact that both...
the first and second ones don't taste new.
The critical point is to find if it's in any way better...
than the classic beers already on the market.
But nothing comes to mind.
We're running out of time.
Keep your style, will you?
Aren't you a director?
Being so neat...
makes you look cold.
Is the new product development going as planned?
Yes.
Of course. It's sailing smoothly.
Ms. Chae isn't just doing her best.
She's risking her life on it.
Come to think of it, I'm blessed with good people.
My senior guides me forward.
My junior supports my back.
Maybe you wouldn't know since you've got no connections.
Sorry.
That little...
He's no match for me.
Chae Yong Ju.
What progress have you made with the new product development?
Forget it. Come to the office at once.
What? I've got no connections?
As if he has a lot of connections!
Seriously. He only got promoted...
by pouring drinks and currying favors!
How dare you...
Calm down.
(Planning Team Director Yeom Jang Goon)
Right. How's the new product development going?
Did you get any news from Bang Ah Reum?
Ever since Ms. Chae stormed in,
Bang Ah Reum stopped giving reports.
You should've still checked in with her.
Must I even give you such orders?
I'm sorry.
I can't let the Marketing Team run wild any longer.
I will cut off all of their luck and connections.
How...
I'd rather see the new production development fail...
than let the Marketing Team Director succeed.
That'll play more favorably to me.
What do you think? Is this good enough?
I'll try harder.
No.
Trying harder isn't enough.
Show them what you've got.
The chairman is waiting for it night and day.
Bringing you here must be worth something.
You Marketing Team Manager.
Listen. At this rate,
saving the guys in Busan will be hard.
Don't you agree?
We'll settle on a concept fast and report it to you.
I'm back.
Did you have dinner?
Teach me how to record audio on this phone.
Right now? But why?
Don't ask. I just need to know how to do it.
If you're tired, I'll ask the caregiver.
No. Take a seat.
- Look. - Okay.
- Go into this app. - Okay.
See this red button? Give it a touch.
- Say "hi." - Hi.
After that, touch the button next to do it.
Save, and that's it.
Got it.
Grandma.
I'm so busy that we can't spend much time together.
- You get bored, right? - No way.
Life is really fun right now.
What is it? What fun are you having?
Watching you.
Watching you is the most entertaining.
Me? What's there to watch about me?
- I'm the same every day. - You've changed.
You've changed a lot.
Really?
I need a story.
A story.
At this rate,
saving the guys in Busan will be hard.
(CEO Yoon Min Ju)
No.
Stop relying on him.
Bear it alone. Chae Yong Ju.
You were the best at bearing it alone.
No! Hang up!
(CEO Yoon Min Ju)
- Hello? - Hi.
I called the wrong number.
You went to the office in such a rush.
Is something going on?
No. Everything is fine.
The higher-ups are extremely interested in our beer development.
It was like giving them a report. Don't worry too much.
Is that so?
I'll think about the concept more.
All right. I'll see you at our next meeting.
Isn't she acting tougher than usual?
Did the higher-ups scold you?
(Did the higher-ups scold you?)
As the manager, you have to hide it from your teammates.
I hope you're not enduring it by yourself.
I would run to you to comfort you if you were close by.
Should I head over...
right now?
Right?
I'm overdoing it, right?
I know, okay? I know.
But these are my honest feelings.
So what?
Yes. I know I'm waiting.
I shouldn't pressure her either.
But how much longer do I have to wait?
Cheer up!
(CEO Yoon Min Ju: Cheer up!)
Don't laugh.
Seriously.
How did Oh Chan Hwi and Bang Ah Reum hook up so fast?
How did they figure out their feelings that easily?
Yoon Min Ju? Yes, he's a nice person.
I want to protect him.
And yes, he gives me butterflies.
But love? I'm not sure if I love him.
Isn't love like that?
Like the heart pounding like thunder?
Or like make my hair stand on end?
My feelings don't go that far.
As if I had ever thought about these things.
This and that.
All of them give me a headache.
(3rd Sample)
Beer developers are incredible.
They must've drank tons of beer.
You now realize how hard it is to create a new beer, right?
What shocks me is the lack of decisions...
we've made despite all of our meetings.
Will we make it in time?
- My head hurts. - We have to.
One way or another.
All right.
- Here you go. - What are those?
Here.
Are you giving us coffee in a bowl?
You wanted a bowlful of coffee for your hangover.
Why are you complaining?
I love the size of it.
Guess what the villagers here say when they drink Americano.
This is what killed Royal Noble Consort Hui.
What? I make my coffee with a pod machine.
Are you looking down on us, Toast?
I only drink Yirgacheffe coffee.
What you're drinking is hand-drip coffee.
To think I'd drink hand-drip coffee in the countryside.
It's all thanks to our boss.
We were offered different kinds of coffee.
To find our coffee taste,
he brewed us new coffee every day.
Finding our old ladies' tastes seemed ridiculous at first.
But we understood after drinking different coffees.
It was quite nice.
Right?
It's a lifetime of homework to find my own taste.
Isn't the iced Americano right up Chae Yong Ju's alley?
Yes, it suits my taste.
Taste?
Let's meet up at the brewery.
(Respecting...)
(Respecting One's Style Era)
The era of drinking until you drop dead is over.
The get-together culture has changed.
The alcohol consumption pattern has completely changed too.
Here comes respecting one's style era.
(Select Your Beer)
- "Select?" - This era...
does not need a beer solely to get drunk.
"Select."
It needs a beer one can select.
I love it.
How did she come up with it?
You little... I'm Yong Ju's biggest fan, okay?
Yong Ju. I have a good feeling about this.
Respecting one's style era. Select your beer.
I like the direction it's going. But newly released beers...
are also emphasizing personal style as their central concept.
Objectively speaking, it's nothing new.
You're right. That's the current beer trend.
But despite focusing on people's style,
why do brands release only one type of beer?
We will...
release beers with different ABVs all at the same time.
We will produce beers one can actually select.
I see. I like the idea.
It's hard to differentiate visually if only the ABVs are different.
Let's add some colors so that people can easily select their beer.
- How? - With taste.
How about using fruits to add taste and color?
The original ingredients' essence...
will be extracted with only pressure...
and no chemical additives to avoid artificial flavors.
Hold on.
Liquor companies have released single types...
because the factory needs different machine lines for each beer type.
But to install different lines?
It'll cost us too much.
The cost.
It may be costly, but it's not impossible.
I'll take responsibility and negotiate it with our company.
- Super cool. - Super cool.
Yes! We've finally got the concept down.
How about a cheer?
Respecting one's style era. Select your beer.
- Come on! - Finally!
Let's do this!
All right.
Yes, Director. We have our concept.
I'll present the project proposal to you as soon as possible.
Okay. Yes. Got it. Bye.
- Hi. - Hi.
Have you seen CEO Yoon Min Ju around?
I'm Baekmok Liquor Marketing Team Manager Lim Ju Hee.
I see.
I'm Jisang Liquor Marketing Team Manager Chae Yong Ju.
Oh, my.
Nice to meet you.
How may we help you?
I'm sure you heard Mr. Yoon signed the contract with our company.
But for Baekmok Liquor to come all the way here.
He's working with Jisang Liquor this time, but who knows?
He might work with us next time.
It's best to make myself known to him in advance.
Right. I see.
Lim Ju Hee?
- Oh, she's from Baekmok Liquor. - Ju Hee?
- How did you know where to find me? - "Ju Hee?"
It's been ages.
My ex-boyfriend.
"Ex-boyfriend?"
By the way, why is she sitting next to us?
- You see... - You see.
As the general manager...
for the new product development with Mr. Yoon,
I wanted to stay informed about the discussions with Baekmok Liquor.
You're fine with me being here, yes?
- But you're already here. - Be quiet.
I'm actually using my position as Baekmok Liquor's employee...
as an excuse to see how my ex-boyfriend is doing.
You're as good-looking as ever.
So when, where, and how did you two meet again?
Oh, we were classmates during high school.
I kept chasing after him.
You see, he was extremely popular.
You had girlfriends throughout high school, didn't you?
I see. Mr. Yoon had relationships nonstop.
Right.
Why are you bringing up the past?
He was such a nice guy.
He had a hard time turning down a girl's confessions.
But he and I ended up dating.
Because our names both had "Ju..."
from Ju Hee and Min Ju, we were called the Ju-Ju couple.
Is that so?
"Ju-Ju couple."
Isn't it adorable?
- It sure is. - Do you see her?
She's a beauty.
But why is Yong Ju shooting lasers from her eyes?
Even if she's from Baekmok Liquor, Yong Ju isn't rude to a stranger.
You still don't know her, Beom.
Listen. We must keep our eyes on Chae Yong Ju.
If her hand goes up,
- we must run and stop her. Got it? - Okay.
We can't let a person die.
Stop overreacting.
I'm not.
Yong Ju rips people apart.
Do you remember this, Min Ju?
I used to do ballet.
Goodness, ballet of all things?
On cold winter nights when my practice ended late,
he kept this can of coffee warm in his pocket,
even as he shivered,
just to hand it to me.
- I'm going home first. - Okay. Bye.
Strangely enough, on days work gives me a hard time,
I recall this canned coffee.
When did you get here?
- It reminds me how loved I was. - Hey.
That's why,
- It's warm. - even if I become a granny,
- Thanks. - looking at this canned coffee...
will remind me of you.
Min Ju's kindness leaves a very long impression.
Is that so?
In high school, he always tied up my hair.
Your hair? He tied it up for you?
No wonder he's good at it.
So he's a habitual offender. I had no idea.
I see. Okay.
My gosh.
I left the project proposal for you in my car.
- Excuse me for a bit. - Go ahead.
- Goodness. - Oh, no.
I'm guessing your ankle is still weak.
I even quit ballet because of my ankle. But it still hurts.
Can you help me get to my car?
Why not? She's in pain.
But...
- Hurry up. - Yes, hurry up.
Okay. Here.
Be careful.
- Here. - It hurts too much.
Isn't love like that?
Like the heart pounding...
like thunder?
Or like make my hair stand on end?
Right now. Come on.
Stop!
What? Left foot.
Left foot.
Can't you smile at me like that too?
Did I not?
Goodness. Whose hair are you going to tie up with that hair tie?
Didn't I have to beg you to tie mine up?
Well, that's true. But...
she won't catch that.
Excuse me first. You can leave the project proposal there.
But my ankle hurts.
I know it's bearable.
Go back.
Come on.
Ju-Ju couple?
As if she's the only one.
I've got "Ju" in my name too. It's Yong Ju.
As if I had never dated in high school.
I didn't. So what? You've got a problem with it?
It's so hot!
He talked to her so casually like second nature.
Aren't we also the same age?
He's always formal with me.
"I'm guessing your ankle isn't all better."
He was all happy, wasn't he?
I'm going to become a soldier.
Help me prepare for the physical fitness test.
- Is that what you truly want to do? - Yes.
It doesn't seem like it.
I need to earn money.
I want my granny to stop selling hotteok.
If that's what you've decided,
I'll root for you.
You should still learn to write music.
You've got to keep something you like. Don't you agree?
I'll try.
Good.
Hot, isn't it?
Would I have been able...
to relax a bit more...
if I had had a friend like him in high school?
How did I end up daydreaming like that?
How did you end up like this?
What were you daydreaming about when your mind rarely wanders off?
Don't tell me you regret it...
- when you're not one to regret. - What are you talking about?
I looked for you everywhere.
Look for me, my foot.
Keep reminiscing with your ex-girlfriend...
about how the chemistry was off the charts.
- Are you jealous? - Of course not.
- You are. - As if.
- How about we go on a date then? - Forget it.
We'll do what?
Go on a date.
Our nickname as a couple is also Ju-Ju.
What are you saying? How are we a couple?
We're colleagues.
Think of me as a colleague. I'll think of it as a date.
You said you'd wait for my answer.
Yes, and I will.
I wanted to take you out for a meal,
but what can I do when you're not into it?
When did you suggest we go out?
Should I clear my schedule for this weekend?
This weekend would be best.
But I could be busy.
Mr. Yoon.
You look exceptionally pretty today.
What? Well...
It's just...
You're here as a colleague, not someone on a romantic date.
Of course. Anyone could tell we're here as colleagues.
Are you free this evening?
What's this about? Am I being summoned again?
Yes, but it's for something intimate and personal.
Who likes flowers that much?
As if they're special.
When was the last time you received flowers?
I don't know. Let me think.
Are those for me?
But...
Why did you invite him? He is a busy man.
Just get some water for him.
Water?
(Middle School Diploma)
(Citation, High School Diploma)
(Citation)
They're all the same kind of flowers.
Grandma.
I thought that buying flowers was a waste of money.
They're pretty.
It turns out I never knew their value...
because I had never received them before.
Flowers are something you like, Yong Ju.
I'll help you discover...
everything that you like.
To make up for the time you spent not being yourself,
I'm going...
to find everythingyou like.
Thanks for today. The date and...
That and the flowers.
Get home safely.
Sure. You get home safely too.
- Head in first. - Sure.
- Good night. - Sure.
Grandma, I'm home.
I received flowers today.
Where is she?
Grandma, are you in the bathroom?
Grandma?
Hello?
Hardships and sufferings.
They always wait for you to be in a better place...
before they stab you in the back...
bringing you to your knees...
in the most miserable way.
The cost for the mortuary and casket...
will be about this much...
while the catering service has a minimum order of 30 portions.
You have three options for flowers on the altar...
which differ in size.
This is how much each option costs.
I'll go with this option.
Do you have a photo of your grandmother?
Surprisingly enough,
families of the deceased don't tend to have one.
There's one on my grandma's phone.
I took one this morning.
(Audio recordings)
What's this?
(Condolences, Jisang Liquor)
(Jisang Liquor Planning Team)
(Jisang Liquor Mutual Aid Team)
(Jisang Liquor Sales Team Manager)
(Condolences, Jisang Liquor)
(Mungang Elementary School Graduates' Association)
(Audio recordings)
Yong Ju, it's your grandma.
Just like you've been nagging me,
I called for an ambulance, so don't worry.
It'll arrive soon,
so...
don't blame yourself.
I...
I'm getting that feeling.
It seems like my time to go.
Is it too much? Maybe it is.
Has my granddaughter always been this pretty?
How do I look?
You look beautiful.
- Really? - Do you have some time to spare?
Do me a favor before you go.
Why do you suddenly want to take a photo?
I don't have one with just me in it.
Make sure I look good.
I wanted my funeral portrait...
to be taken in my happiest moment.
Smile, will you?
That's why...
I thought of when I'm the happiest.
You look pretty.
Grandma, I'm impressed.
It turns out that I'm happy when you are.
You look stunning right now.
Today,
you looked incredibly happy.
Yong Ju,
smile and laugh to your heart's content...
and cry your eyes out when needed.
Don't keep everything in or hold back your emotions.
Let your heart guide the way.
It was...
an honor...
to have been your grandma.
(Condolences, Jisang Liquor)
(Jisang Liquor Employee Association)
(Mungang Elementary School Graduates' Association)
I appreciate you making the long trip.
- Have you eaten? - Yes, of course.
Yong Ju, it must be tough.
I'm all right.
Gosh, you look gaunt.
Hardly. Anyway, does the food suit your palates?
- Absolutely. - Everything's tasty.
More guests have arrived.
Sir, thank you for coming.
- Sorry for your loss. - I appreciate that.
This way, please.
Goodness.
(Wholesale Association)
Sir, I didn't expect you to be here.
Of course, I should come.
May she rest in peace.
Thank you.
- Shall we? - This way, sir.
My goodness.
What's all this?
- Are you all right? - Of course.
We got as much as we could from the company storage.
An employee of a liquor company...
can't run out of booze at her grandmother's funeral.
Yong Ju,
I'm an expert at managing funerals. Leave this to me.
Thank you.
- Shall we head up? - That way?
- It's the second floor. - Got it.
Goodness.
Yong Ju...
- You poor thing. - I'm all right.
- Goodness. - My gosh.
You're suffocating me.
- Are you okay? - I'm all right.
Shall we head inside, then?
Goodness.
- Have you had dinner? - Of course.
(Condolences, Jisang Liquor)
(Jisang Liquor Mutual Aid Team)
Good grief.
My gosh.
- Ladies... - It's all right. I'm fine.
Right, of course.
- Goodness me. - Right.
- Let's give her some space. - Sure.
- Hang in there. - Thanks.
Let's sit there.
Mother.
We decided to go our separate ways.
Gyeong Cheol.
Mother, I'm really sorry,
but can you raise Yong Ju?
Grandma, look at my bear.
I'm ashamed as your father.
You're ashamed?
As my...
Why would you even say that...
when that won't excuse you?
I had no other options.
I was...
only 21 at the time.
I was practically a kid myself,
so how could I raise one?
My only option...
was to run.
Mr. Chae Gyeong Cheol.
Did you see the flowers that were lined up outside?
What about the guests that came to express their condolences?
As you can see,
I built a good life for myself.
And I owe it all to my grandma.
Don't cry over something like this. It's all right.
You're okay. This isn't something to cry about.
I'm all right.
Gosh. I'm fine.
I'm...
Grandma.
He...
is hurting more over my ordeal than me.
(We thank Lee Jong Hyuk, Ko Sang Ho, and Pyo Ye Jin...)
(for their special appearances.)
(Brewing Love)
Grandma, I thought...
I'd never be able to manage a life without you alone.
But it turns out, I'm not alone.
Come with me.
Oh Chan Hwi, I keep seeing you in my future.
But I don't even know what my own future holds.
Bang Ah Reum, that's your job!
I can hamper the launch of the new beer without you.
You did great work, Ms. Chae.
You too, Mr. Yoon.
Today, we'll make it or break it, so let's stay strong.
Let us begin.