=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 17=
Good thing I didn't go astray
and make a grave mistake.
Sir,
you must help me out
before Her Grace.
Put in a good word for me.
Sir.
Hey.
These are the decrees
issued by the former Sovereign.
That's right.
Also the second thing
spirits hate the most.
But I quite like it.
So golden and shiny.
Building this wall
cost quite a bit of gold.
Issuing decrees
to bring fortune to the world
is called the Way.
How wise of you.
But most spirits
dislike
these restrictive laws.
When Her Grace
enforced the decrees,
it caused quite a stir.
But she's so powerful.
With a wave of her hand
and a single glance,
she silenced those rebels
forever.
As long as she is the Sovereign,
the Void will be stable
and the Mortal World safe.
(Even if no one knows)
(or remembers.)
I heard that to spirits,
mortals are just prey.
Why aren't these spirits
interested in me?
You carry Her Grace's aura now.
In their eyes,
you're one of them.
You said the Golden Wall
is the second most hated place
for spirits.
So, what's the first
most hated place?
Sir,
why are you so curious
about everything?
The place spirits hate most
is the Nine-Square Maze Prison.
Let's go.
Quick, hurry up.
He...
The Execution Platform
is a sacred place of the Void.
For a mortal like you to go there,
can you withstand it?
It's filled with righteous energy,
and Simu guards it.
Why shouldn't I?
You're not a Starhaven sorcerer.
How can you wield this spirit weapon?
You seem interested in my affairs.
Looking for another way to kill me?
You think I'd do such a thing?
I doubt you'd do
such a reckless thing again.
Simu's patience
has always been limited.
Even the most novel things
quickly lose their appeal.
Your hostility toward me
is all because of Simu.
She's known you for 300 years,
and she still doesn't like you.
You think too highly of yourself.
Farewell, Your Lordship.
What's wrong?
I'm feeling cold again.
Hey!
Maizi,
I'm still cold.
Bring me a few more braziers.
Alright.
Your Grace.
Why did you end up like this
in such a short time?
I just caught some wind
and got a bit of a chill.
Didn't I suppress
the cold poison?
How did it relapse so quickly?
It really isn't easy for a mortal
to stay in the Void.
Why is it suddenly getting warm?
In this Zone,
you can be free from the cold poison.
But you can't leave me.
So, that means
I can stay
by your side openly.
If you dare offend me again,
I'll remove this Zone immediately
and let the cold poison consume you.
Thank you for your great mercy.
You saved my life.
You just need to stay
within ten steps of me.
No need to follow so closely.
Now that you've become spirits
and newly arrived in the Void,
you must strictly obey
the Golden-wall Decrees.
The decrees were established
to govern all spirits in the Void.
From Her Grace above
to ordinary spirits below,
all must comply.
All spirits of the Void
can't enter the Mortal World
without cause,
can't harm or kill mortals
without reason,
can't meddle in Mortal World affairs,
can't incite unrest or rebellion,
and can't commit treason.
During curfew, those without a token
may not venture outside.
Remember the pain you just felt.
If you violate the Golden-wall Decrees,
the punishment you'll receive
will be a thousand times worse.
You enforce the law
with unwavering dedication,
never once slacking in 300 years.
The decrees
have endured in the Void to this day
thanks to your efforts.
Her Grace enforces the decrees
to honor the previous Sovereign's will.
You're always consistent
and swift in action.
We're pale in comparison.
Whatever Simu wants,
I will make it happen for her.
(Xu)
Xuling Temple.
Good.
Next.
Jiling Temple.
Excavating North Abyss.
The Right Hand wants to recruit spirits
to excavate North Abyss.
Since we're all here in the Void…
30,000 spirit stones.
So many.
I should give it a try.
There's no such easy fortune.
What about your life?
Look at what's written there.
(Notice)
This won't be easy.
I still have to go.
Come in.
I have urgent matters for Her Grace.
Others
should leave.
My apologies.
I can't leave even if I want to.
Go ahead.
All new spirits
have been registered.
Recruitment for the excavation
is proceeding as planned.
Yet all temples have failed
in spirit ascension.
What a loyal
and diligent subordinate.
Your Lordship…
Spirits are born from obsession.
Having them
willingly let go and enter the pool
won't be easy.
We'll need more time
to plan this carefully.
Spirit ascension is the righteous path.
We can't give up just because it's hard.
This can't be rushed.
Discuss it more with Jiang Ai.
Yan,
you've worked hard lately.
Go back and get some rest.
Then,
I'll take him with me as well.
As for the rest,
I'll oversee it.
Yes.
Speak.
What were you about to say?
♪Touched memories linger like shadows♪
♪Scattered reflections
sink into my heart♪
♪If I could softly call you like this♪
♪As gentle as a fleeting embrace♪
♪Though apart, my thoughts still swirl♪
♪A lifetime is given
for a name to be remembered♪
♪There are passions and pains♪
♪Hope we'll experience them together♪
♪Before we forget or grow apart♪
♪Even if the day gives way to night♪
♪Grows dim and fades away♪
♪What would come of it?♪
♪I care for no one but you♪
♪I'll come near and run to you♪
♪To heal the deepest wounds♪
♪Miracles, eternity, and radiance♪
♪Worth more than any barren land♪
♪I might as well
spend the rest of my life♪
♪Walking with you through eternity♪
(Sovereign's Hall)
I knew him.
Her Grace favors him now.
Let me in,
and I won't hold this against you.
I'm a generous person.
I'll let you off this time.
I'll just wait for him outside.
I won't go in anymore.
Put me down!
A mortal.
He's following Her Grace.
He smells so good.
A mortal.
(His obsession)
(is probably to live a warm life.)
(This person)
(must be afraid of water.)
(The Lords of the 24 Temples)
(truly are)
(unique.)
I never expected Her Grace
to choose such a pretty boy.
He's so scrawny.
I could crush several with one hand.
I think he looks fine.
His appearance
only falls a bit short of mine.
Young man.
Young man,
Her Grace brought you here.
The former Sovereign's wife
never even came here.
You flatter me.
Her Grace and I had no choice.
What are you saying?
If Her Grace didn't want to,
who could force her?
I feel sorry for the Right Hand.
This pretty boy was brought here.
Are we going to have
a wedding feast?
Then I must dress up nicely.
Lords present today,
what matters do you wish to report?
I dare not deceive you.
That mortal's cold poison
has indeed flared up.
I heard Her Grace used a Zone
to protect him from it.
But
he must stay close to Her Grace.
Keep a close watch on him.
Keep me updated anytime.
Yes, yes.
You'd protect
an ordinary mortal to this extent?
Who has angered you
to such an extent?
What brings you here?
You always tend to Her Grace's needs.
I heard the mortal young man
she brought back
is suffering from cold poison,
causing her great distress.
I happen to have a Cloud Tripod
forged with the South Blaze.
It can temporarily suppress cold poison.
Why not take it to Her Grace?
You're being this generous?
My generosity
naturally comes at a price.
Go on.
On what terms?
Simu wants us to excavate.
Your temple will send Spirit Officials.
Agreed.
After the excavation,
I'll oversee the mining
of spirit stones.
Also agreed.
Deal.
I have one more question.
Do you know of any way
to turn a person into a spirit
or a spirit into a person?
You don't want
to become a mortal, do you?
Seeing Simu likes mortals,
you want to turn back to win her heart?
Mortals are fragile.
How can they compare to spirits?
Who knows?
Perhaps there might be records
in the Starhaven ancient texts.
Back to business.
I agree to the deal we just discussed.
Sign and seal it.
(Yan Ke)
You're paying
such a heavy price.
Are you really removing
the mortal's cold poison?
Once that mortal uses this Cloud Tripod
to dispel the cold poison,
the spirit power attached to the tripod
will enter his organs.
No one will be able to save him.
Thanks, Lady Jiang Ai.
You're so thoughtful.
Simu.
I found a magical artifact
forged with the South Blaze.
Its pure yang and scorching energy
can temporarily dispel cold poison
and help you
avoid trouble from that mortal.
Yan,
how kind of you.
However,
Lady Jiang Ai just gave me
a method to cure cold poison.
Keep the tripod
for yourself.
I sold you the treasure you want.
You never asked me how to cure it.
Simu,
I helped as promised.
Don't forget the spirit stones
you owe me.
Come with me somewhere.
Jiang Ai,
I underestimated you.
The Void's greediest spirit
naturally knows how to scheme.
Your Lordship,
the Left Hand's Spirit Officials
are here for excavation experts.
Their attitude was aggressive.
Should we cooperate?
Of course.
I personally promised Jiang Ai.
Don't let these matters
delay the important business.
Yes.
They say mortals and animals
can't stay long in the Void.
I didn't expect plants here.
The Void is rich in spiritual energy.
There are always blessed things
born from that energy
for spirits to use.
The Crystal Orchid can cure
your cold poison.
It grows right here.
A flower that grows on bones?
Spiritual energy sometimes forms bones.
What grows on those bones
is the Crystal Orchid.
But this one
is far too young.
You need one
that's at least 300 years old.
Even the plants here
live this long?
- Xu.
- Young Master.
- You're finally back.
We've been waiting for you.
I think I saw
the scenery of Nandu.
This Crystal Orchid can read memories
and trap people in an illusion.
Best not to touch it.
Simu,
all these Crystal Orchids
won't work?
Father.
It's been 300 years.
Why is Father's spirit sense here?
Did he also come here
to cure your mother's
cold poison?
Probably.
It seems that any mortal body,
even Starhaven sorcerers,
can't withstand the Void's cold.
You've asked around
quite a bit about me.
Rather than hearing it from others,
I'd prefer to hear it
from you directly.
Simu.
Simu?
We've searched for so long
with nothing to show for it.
It's all right.
I believe there's always a way out.
We'll find it.
Siwei,
your cold poison attacks
are getting more frequent.
We must find
a cure as soon as possible.
We mustn't let Simu find out.
She'll worry.
Father, Mother, the food is ready.
Coming.
I never knew
Mother once suffered
from cold poison too.
Here.
This is your favorite.
Prying into my past so easily.
I might punish you again.
A little punishment is worth it.
I got to see
your different side.
Simu, did you
make all these dishes?
Do you think they're good?
Let me try.
Delicious.
So good.
- Here.
- Father.
All right.
Mother.
Thank you, Simu.
Why do you keep going out lately?
Since you've already noticed,
let's tell you
the truth.
Open it and see.
Do you like it?
I do.
Good.
Put the gift aside
and eat first.
The dishes Simu made
- Here.
- are delicious.
Here.
- Alright.
- Your parents loved you.
Thank you, Simu.
They lived with you in the Mortal World.
Have some more food.
Alright.
They hoped you'd live like a mortal,
a real, genuine person.
So what?
It's been too long. Let's go.
Since you won't tell me,
I'll stay in this illusion
and see everything.
Do you know why the Crystal Orchid
dragged us into this illusion?
From the moment we entered here,
it's been feeding on my spirit power
and your soul.
This place is becoming unstable.
It knows we want to leave
and is trying to hide the exit.
I could easily destroy
this illusion.
It holds your father's memories.
Let's keep it
and find another way out.
I can use my five senses
to feel your father's
spirit sense outside.
Perhaps he can help us.
Father,
you helped me, right?
Simu,
have you found the gift I left you?
If you've met someone
very important to you
and brought him here,
this gift is yours.
Follow my spirit sense.
I'll lead you to it.
Father.
I almost forgot.
It's just the spirit sense
Father left behind.
Take a sip.
It needs
to be consumed in small doses
to merge with your meridian
and eradicate the cold poison.
Now,
you can leave my side
without suffering for now.
Simu!
Simu,
are you all right?
I'm fine.
You call this fine?
I've never seen you this weak.
I used some spirit power
to restore the Fusang Tree.
When I formed the array,
I couldn't hold it steady.
No need to worry.
What are you waiting for?
Take him here.
Go.
No!
No, I don't want ascension.
I don't want ascension.
It didn't work.
I told you my obsession runs deep.
While the obsession lingers,
the spirit won't sink.
The obsession must be let go of
willingly.
I don't believe it.
One more.
Who are you
to trespass here?
A formidable spirit here.
What a surprise.
Sir,
who are you?
How dare you ask my name?
This place is forbidden.
You're just a wild spirit.
How dare you speak to me like that?
I know not who you are,
but your vulgarity
is no different from a beast's.
Speak like a normal person.
Lei Qi.
What? Looking for a fight?
Are you stupid?
These spirits
have no way to ascend.
We're not getting
any spirit stones anyway.
No need to stir up trouble
and alert Her Grace.
This is my home.
You shall not trespass.
Where are you going?
Curfew is in effect.
The moonlight is beautiful.
I thought
I'd take a walk.
Let me come with you.
I'd be delighted.
(Sovereign's Hall)
Who knew General Duan
was afraid of heights?
Thanks to you,
I've discovered
another weakness of mine.
Last time I took you flying,
you seemed quite calm.
Last time, you held onto me,
so I wasn't as scared.
♪All things wake, with the east wind♪
From this angle, the Void
looks like an ink painting.
♪In the season at its fullest♪
♪Light the lamps
to pierce the old night♪
Cobblestone paths,
ancient architecture,
weathered walls,
and…
♪Warm winds bring fragrant blooms♪
♪Savoring wine and graceful dances♪
♪Let me love with all my heart♪
And what?
And Simu.
♪With light, carefree words,
still shining bright♪
If I were to throw you
off from here,
what would happen to you?
Didn't you say
you liked my skull?
If I fall from here,
my head would split open,
and my skull would shatter.
Then you should thank your skull
for saving your life.
♪Through this life♪
♪In the netherworld♪
♪I see a ray♪
♪To what home shall I return♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪