( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
ALL FIGURES,
INCIDENTS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS,
AND OTHERS ARE FICTITIOUS.
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
WERE FILMED SAFELY
IN ACCORDANCE WITH GUIDELINES.
No matter how beautiful and grand
their lives may have been,
the dead tell no tales.
Thus, murderers believe
that they can keep
their crimes hidden for good.
But the problem is,
they're wrong.
Some things do exist
even if they're invisible.
They're always around us.
Actually…
He came into the office…
They're around me.
And unexpectedly,
they're talkative.
What about it? Hear me out, Mr. Attorney!
Well, I understand why.
- They have no power to take revenge.
- Tell them something!
Nor do they know how.
WITNESS STAND
This is exactly why they need
someone to hear their resentful stories
and convict those who deserve punishment,
which is me,
Shin I-rang.
Your Honor.
I have an objection.
The culprit…
is someone else.
However,
I wasn't a ghost-seeing attorney
from the start.
ONE YEAR AGO
Attorney Shin I-rang.
Why don't you tell us
about your strengths?
EPISODE 1
I have two hearts.
A strong heart that allows me
to race until I win a case,
and a warm heart that motivates me
to create a righteous society.
INTERVIEW ADMISSION TICKET
NAME: SHIN I-RANG
You can just walk away.
I was meaning
to walk past you today anyway.
That's good, then.
Go on.
It's okay. Just go on.
PITTER-PATTER BUTCHER-STYLE BBQ
Hi, Mom.
Hey.
You must be tired from work today.
Not at all.
I do this because I like it.
Oh, this?
The vegetable lady was coughing.
The flu is going around these days.
You're such a softie.
Your older sister's shop
has tons of vegetables,
and you bought extra.
It's nice to have a lot of vegetables.
Koreans eat too much meat. It's not good.
Says someone whose mom is a butcher.
What I'm trying to say is--
Shut it, and just bring this over.
Okay.
Sir, don't get drunk like last time.
- Please enjoy.
- Oh, thank you.
Welcome back, my dear brother-in-law.
Is it a periodic drama this time?
I have as many as two lines for this role.
Congratulations, my lord.
Thank you.
Honey.
I'm on my way, my lady.
Da-bong, your uncle is here.
Put me down, Uncle.
Look at you, brat.
Choose between Carbot and me.
I choose you. Happy now?
Yes, happy.
Why are you here again?
I told you to stop coming.
I might not be able to come for real soon.
I want to help out while I can.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
Oh, right. How was the interview?
How did it go?
Everyone seemed worried.
Worried? Why?
Isn't it obvious?
Words spread fast in this field.
They were worried they might lose me.
That means they'll hire you.
I didn't get an official offer yet,
but I must say it's most likely.
An attorney at K and L Law Firm!
What a great honor for our family!
Hold on.
Attention, please!
Each table will have
a bottle of soju on the house today!
- Oh, my.
- Really?
The owner's insane.
Drink up!
One serving of pork belly
on the house too.
- Oh, goodness.
- My mother-in-law never disappoints.
Just one serving, not two.
- A bottle of beer, please.
- Here too.
Coming right away.
WE REGRET TO INFORM YOU THAT
WE WON'T MOVE FORWARD WITH YOU
This can't be.
Okay.
I was too naive.
There.
WE REGRET TO INFORM YOU
OF UNFORTUNATE NEWS
Are you serious?
YOUR APPLICATION
WAS NOT SELECTED
What on earth is the problem?
LAWSUIT FOR DAMAGES
PLAINTIFF: SEONGHO ELECTRONICS
- This is about Haeseong Trading.
- Thank you.
This is the petition
for Myeongjin Construction.
- I placed the materials on your desk too.
- Okay.
TAEBAEK LAW FIRM
PARTNER HAN NA-HYUN
Hello.
Seongho Electronics' chairman
was greatly satisfied.
He wants to sign a partnership with us.
That's good.
You seem busy. Do you want me
to interview the applicants?
It's about my future associate.
I'll do it myself.
I have about 20 minutes.
Then, just refer to this.
What is it?
THE 2025 ENTRY-LEVEL
ASSOCIATE INTERVIEW
INTERVIEW ADMISSION TICKET
NAME: SHIN I-RANG
Next applicant, please come in.
Okay.
INTERVIEW ROOM
Hello, my name is Shin I-rang.
Hello, please have a seat.
Attorney Han, ask questions first.
I don't have any questions
for Mr. Shin.
I'm sure he knows why.
Let's move on.
He's the last applicant.
What are you doing?
Let me ask the same question.
A scarlet letter…
As expected.
Were you aware
of your husband's corruption?
What do you think you're doing?
Have you no manners at all?
- Do you admit to his crimes?
- Get out.
My dad wasn't a criminal.
He was a prosecutor
who punished bad people!
I'm turning you down.
I am…
turning you down first.
You should've at least asked
routine questions.
He needs to know how the world sees him.
Only then, he'll stop biting on granite.
I'll be off since we're done.
A father's actions from 20 years ago
is causing harm to his son.
How cruel.
Is it because the judge and prosecutor
related to it haven't retired yet?
Maybe.
This won't do. Just change your name.
Put all the past behind you
and make a new start with a new--
No.
Now that I know how the world sees me,
I won't stay still.
You know what?
I'm going to make the best law firm ever
under my own name.
And then,
I'm going to have all those
who mistreated me line up in two rows.
I'll take good revenge on them.
Wait and see.
What?
Are you pleased
to have ruined your son's future?
Fine.
Let's see who wins.
Bring it on!
EMERGENCY MEDICAL SERVICES
MR. KIM'S REAL ESTATE OFFICE
4,305,100 WON
Would this be enough?
What brings you here, I-rang?
The thing is…
Your mother must've sent you.
What?
After all,
an attorney should
take charge of a contract.
Please do the rest, okay?
Where's Mr. Kim, though?
Oh.
Someone passed out or something.
He'll be back soon.
I'm a detective this time.
See you.
This must be Mom's lease contract.
COMMERCIAL LEASE AGREEMENT
The deposit's 200 million won?
I didn't know Mom was this rich.
Hold on.
Two hundred million won?
Why be a shaman
if you can't even tell your own future?
Hello.
Oh, my.
What brings you here, Mr. Attorney?
- Have a seat.
- Okay.
Are you here to renew
the butcher shop contract?
The thing is,
were you the landlord of my mom's shop?
You didn't know?
Mr. Kim, I need your help.
You need my help?
I need to open a law office,
so please let me use 30 million won
from her deposit.
What?
That's out of the question.
I'll pay 10% more of the commission.
- And I'll provide you with legal services.
- Indefinitely?
- Deal.
- What's the condition?
I'd like a courthouse view.
A close-up courthouse view.
You can't rent out an office like that
with a 30-million-won deposit.
Is that so?
I-rang.
There may be one.
Really?
Yes.
OPEN
Come on. You're young enough for this.
It's a quiet neighborhood.
Over there.
This is the one right here.
OKCHEON BUILDING
I didn't know this neighborhood
had a building like this.
Oh, perfect.
The wallpapering must be over.
- Mr. Park!
- Hello.
I appreciate the hard work.
We're all done. Thank you.
Come along.
All of this will get moved out.
- It's here.
- Here?
FOR LEASE
The interior is quite unique.
The landlord has elegant taste.
Oh, these.
The former tenant left them behind.
I'll throw them out, so don't bother.
You can leave them here.
It takes work to throw them out.
Let's save the Earth.
Anyway, what was this place?
- A Chinese restaurant?
- What?
Oh, what's the word?
You know,
something about foreseeing the future…
An AI company? Big data?
What?
Yeah, I think it was something like that.
Don't you smell something weird?
It's coming from the wallpaper.
It will go away soon. Don't bother it.
There's no place like this
in the neighborhood.
The heavens really helped you out here.
You may trick a ghost, but not me.
I know there are
many empty offices these days.
Wait, I-rang.
You wanted a view, didn't you?
Come here.
Isn't it nice?
Breathtaking, right?
There's no other place with a
courthouse view like this at your budget.
Think wisely.
I'll take it.
I like it.
Good thinking.
Yahoo.
Please place it all the way
at the top of the building
so that it's visible from the courthouse.
SHIN I-RANG LAW OFFICE
ATTORNEY SHIN I-RANG
It sure is in my blood to run a business.
What was that?
What is this?
Is this incense?
Nice. The air was musty anyway.
I like it.
Huh?
Was it a dream?
Hi.
Hi, I-rang.
Remember the man you mentioned?
Man?
Who?
You asked me to set you up
with a paralegal.
He's already here.
Let me call you later.
What… Hello?
No, he's already hired.
That's why I called.
He came? Who is he talking about?
You're here early.
You must've waited long.
I don't usually sleep in like that
but I've been stressed out lately.
You can see me?
Pardon?
Yes, that's why I'm talking to you.
I'm quite tall myself,
but you're really tall.
Are you 190 cm tall?
Maybe 2 m?
Y-You…
W-What is it?
G-Ghost…
Ghost!
- It's a ghost!
- Oh, dear.
Dear God, Jesus Christ, and Virgin Mary,
please forgive me.
I'll pay off Mom's deposit
and turn over a new leaf.
Please don't let me die.
What are you doing?
Do you want to play hide-and-seek?
Oh, my. That must be painful.
Go away! Go!
Go away…
An AI company?
Big data?
He lied to me.
I can't believe this.
Look.
Ghosts don't exist,
especially in this day and age.
A shaman must've summoned him.
What shaman?
Fine, here.
This is the evidence.
You deceived me into signing this lease,
so call it off.
Nowhere in real estate law
is there an obligation to notify
who the former tenant was.
There's more.
Article 4, Paragraph 5
of the contract says,
"The tenant may cancel the contract
if they have not been notified
of any undesirable facility."
A haunted place is clearly
an undesirable facility.
So, you'll go by the book?
Then, prove that there are ghosts here.
Unbelievable.
There he is. He's here.
Over there.
Where?
There!
There. He's there!
Where?
Do you really not see him?
See what?
Snap out of it, I-rang.
What a shame.
This is driving me nuts!
Maybe that's it.
ATTORNEY SHIN I-RANG
There's this tale
called the Legend of Arang.
Every time a new district magistrate
is appointed,
a resentful virgin ghost visits him.
And it kills all the feeble magistrates.
This is killing me.
Wake up.
It's a dream.
But then,
- a brave magistrate survives…
- Hear me out!
…and helps her
resolve her resentment at last
in this beautiful tale.
Beautiful, my foot.
What are you looking at?
You're not even a virgin ghost.
I'm sorry.
He spoke.
Mr. Kim, did you hear him?
He spoke just now.
Wow.
You're good at acting.
Still, no. I won't back down.
Neither will I.
I absolutely will not use this office.
If you refuse, I'll take you to court.
That leaves me no choice,
but to discuss this with Ms. Park.
I wonder if she's done butchering.
I hope she has some energy left.
Who scares you more? Ghosts or your mom?
I'll give you a few days
until rent is due, okay?
Wait for me, Mr. Kim!
You have until tomorrow to leave.
Otherwise,
I'll come with a cross and a Bible.
PITTER-PATTER BUTCHER-STYLE BBQ
Eat up.
Uncle!
Hi, Da-bong.
You always come
every time we're having something yummy.
Da-bong.
Were you eating a lot?
I expected you'd have dinner outside
and didn't prepare your share.
It's okay.
I'll just have what's on the table.
- Hold on.
- Well…
You must be tired.
- Let me go make some stew.
- Thanks.
Have some of this first.
Goodness.
Uncle, why aren't you having pork belly?
It's delicious.
I'm allergic to pork.
If I have pork belly…
Then, what?
Goodness, it's…
It's needless to say.
This is to die for.
You…
What?
What are you looking at?
Have you never seen
someone eat meat or what?
That's right.
I've never seen Shin I-rang have meat!
Uncle.
Your cheeks are red.
Just like a monkey's butt.
What?
What about my cheeks?
Hey! Hey, you brat.
You shouldn't be eating pork!
Or you'll get rashes.
Look at your face. It's already red.
- I-rang.
- Unbelievable.
Just why are you doing this to me?!
Why do you have to give me a hard time?
Please leave me be!
"He was with the wild animals,
and angels…
attended him."
"After John was put"--
What do you want from me?
Who are you in the first place?
I don't know myself.
This is insane.
Look. Since you're an attorney,
can't you look into who I am?
Why should I do that?
I have to pay rent starting next month.
Otherwise, my mom will kill me.
Bring me money or…
get me winning lottery numbers.
If I had such power,
I would've bought a building
in the other world.
Is all you can do startling me, then?
How pathetic.
A ghost?
I think I got possessed
at a shaman's house.
That shaman had been taken to a hospital,
but he was nowhere to be found.
He ran off
without paying the hospital fee.
How did you come to see that ghost?
There was a desk that used to be his.
I found an old incense burner
in the drawer.
It's cold.
That's cold.
How strange.
In most cases, the body twists
or the holy water makes smoke.
This is not an ordinary ghost.
He reads the Bible,
and he enjoys eating pork belly with soju…
He even drinks coffee.
Maybe he used to like having those.
Being possessed
manifests when their desires reach a peak.
When something triggers a rush of joy,
like their favorite food or song,
or oppositely,
when they're faced with someone they hate
or something that causes rage,
the possibility of possession increases.
Once you're possessed,
you'd make absurd behaviors
while you don't even remember
what you've even done.
That means I'm in a dangerous situation.
Whether you are or not,
let's go to Okcheon Building and check.
Seriously!
This is as expected.
These talismans are summoning ghosts.
If I burn the talismans,
will the ghost disappear?
Probably.
No.
Never, not until I find out who I am!
You don't have a say here.
Is he here right now? What did he say?
What is he claiming?
He's been grilling me
to find out who he is.
Then, why don't you
look into who this ghost is?
It's easy to help a spirit pass on
if you know their story.
Do it for me. Do it!
Do it…
Even if I'm to help him,
I don't know how.
With his name and date of birth,
he'll regain his memory.
Are you serious?
How do you know that?
Oh, I was…
once a shaman.
And God's embrace has changed me
like this.
Come to think of it,
it won't be hard to find out who he is.
You just need to check it
with whoever visited the shaman.
That person must've wanted
to summon the ghost.
I see.
I saw there was
a security camera in the hallway.
Is this all?
There aren't enough materials.
We don't need materials.
The bereaved want to settle.
I just want you to follow up on it.
Well, a peaceful settlement is
the best option,
but just in case it goes south,
I'll make sure
to get the bereaved's signature.
That sounds better.
SARANG VOLUNTEERS
This woman was the last visitor.
Look here.
She visited several times.
Sir, when was this captured?
Oh, that?
That's a live feed.
What?
I'm saying that the woman is standing
in front of Unit 501 right now.
How may I help you?
Well…
It was a male shaman's place
until recently…
The shaman left due to illness.
Yes, I know.
I was with him when he passed out.
I called an ambulance too.
I came out of concern
and decided to enter because it was
changed to an attorney's office.
Did you perhaps visit the shaman
regarding your husband?
How did you know?
Go ahead and tell me what happened.
Both attorneys and shamans are there
to hear stories of those who were wronged.
A few months…
A few months ago,
my husband had surgery
at Cheongil Hospital.
He went into shock
during the surgery.
Is that why you visited the shaman?
To say your last goodbye?
No.
Since then,
my daughter won't come out of her room.
Open the door.
- Her healthy dad died out of the blue.
- Open up.
It must've shocked her badly.
Come on, say something.
Ji-woo!
I won't do it again, so please…
She's locked herself in her room
for five months.
I've tried to persuade her
softly, with anger, and in tears.
But none of it worked.
At least,
it feels a little better
to open up to you like this.
Thank you.
M-My name. My name and date of birth.
Could you tell me
your husband's name and date of birth?
His name is Lee Gang-pung.
He was born
on April 25, 1980.
My dear puppy is awake.
You're pretty just like your mom.
I'm a dad now.
Thank you.
Look. You're like a newlywed.
Careful.
SARANG VOLUNTEERS
Bingo!
What do you think?
Min-ju!
You must've
struggled so much alone.
Are you out of your mind?
Why did she slap me?
What happened all of a sudden?
I…
remembered.
Really?
My death…
Please administer anesthesia.
He's going under.
His airway is blocked.
We must perform emergency surgery now!
- Damn it!
- Should we prepare for a tracheostomy?
- Doctor!
- Shut up!
I'll handle it, okay?
Keep this a secret.
We'll just say he died from shock
due to cardiac arrest.
I clearly heard a voice…
urging to frame it as death from shock.
He never puts his clothes
in the washing machine.
JOB APPLICATION
NAME: SHIN I-RANG
Why aren't you asleep?
Oh, I couldn't sleep.
I should go to bed now.
I'm going to have a drink.
Care to join me?
There's no drinking snack.
Soju is best when you drink it neat.
Cheers.
Son.
Is life hard these days?
When was it ever not tough?
It took me five years
to barely get a law license.
And I barely got a job.
Still, you've pulled it all through.
You're right, but…
How much does it cost
to open a law office?
That senior of yours named Jeong-su
or whatever even bought a building.
What are you saying?
You said I was too soft
to run a legal office.
That was to prevent you
from getting ahead of yourself
in the beginning.
We don't have the money.
I can take some out of the deposit.
The deposit is 200 million won.
Hold on.
Wait. No.
Mom.
I love my job right now.
I-rang.
Yes?
You know I believe in you, right?
Yes, I do.
I'm not sure what's concerning you,
but do what you want.
I've got your back.
Goodness, Mom.
You're drunk after one glass of soju.
Okay. Go to sleep now.
I will.
You should go to bed soon too.
Okay.
TAEBAEK LAW FIRM
That's not very satisfying.
Do you realize how much
I'm paying you guys?
The bereaved must be
signing the agreement by now.
SETTLEMENT AGREEMENT
Ms. Kim, you're very lucky.
The doctor didn't even kill your husband,
but to take moral responsibility,
he's offering as much as 30 million won.
The police investigation isn't over yet.
And if it is over?
Take it to court?
- Yes, if needed.
- Goodness.
Why would you want to complicate things?
It's easier said than done.
You don't know how tricky it is
to prove medical malpractice.
If a single thing goes wrong,
you may even lose your house.
I hear your daughter is sick.
What if you end up on the street
with your sick daughter?
Goodness.
Attorney Han, tell me if I'm wrong.
Your late husband's life
can't be measured by money,
but please consider it
as a token of sincerity.
Of course, the decision is up to you.
Can I take a look at it?
You may read it through
if you can't trust me,
but would you be able to understand it?
It's only natural for a settling party
to read through an agreement.
Keep your manners.
Actually, it's okay.
I'm sure the attorney reviewed it well.
Good thinking. Please sign there.
KIM MIN…
Excuse me for a moment.
What are you doing here, Mr. Shin?
You remember me.
Are you Mr. Lee Jeong-seok's attorney?
I hope I'm not too late.
Excuse me.
Oh, thank goodness.
Wait.
Do you know him?
Who are you to--
You can take time to learn about me
because I'll say a few things
about you first.
Attorney Byeon Seung-jun.
Since graduating from the Judicial
Research and Training Institute in 2017,
you worked at Taebaek
for five years and three months
until July of 2022.
Yes, what about it? Is there a problem?
Taebaek is the dream law firm
that every attorney wants to work for.
Yes, you're right.
And this field is so small
that you may be acquaintances
with the other party's attorney.
That's honestly a little leery.
So,
what is your point?
It turns out that Attorney Byeon
and Managing Partner Yang Do-gyeong
played golf together last weekend
and had a private talk afterward.
Hey, are you snooping on me?
Me?
Of course not.
Oh, my goodness!
Mr. Lee, congratulations.
You won free legal service
at my office's grand opening event.
Mr. Attorney.
I'm quite smart, so you can count on me.
Thank you.
But what do we do?
My wife already has an attorney.
I looked into it
and her attorney has many issues.
He will definitely not defend your wife.
Then, what do we do?
Isn't it obvious?
We'll have him fired.
Like a ghost without letting anyone know.
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
Wait just a moment.
The real deal is about to begin.
Here it is.
Hello, Mr. Yang. It's me.
Attorneys always want
to leave advantageous evidence.
You'll wire the money
to my borrowed-name account, right?
Did you convince Kim Min-ju?
It was extremely hard
to minimize the settlement money.
I mean…
…if not for me
your client would've had to pay up
like a billion won.
How could you!
How…
This is bad enough
to lose your law license.
It's not good at all.
Wait.
I can explain. I can explain it all.
Attorney Han, where are you going?
Attorney Han.
Do I have any reason left to stay here?
We don't need your explanation.
Pull out of this case immediately.
And wire twice the commission
you've received
to Ms. Kim's account.
Understand?
Attorney Shin.
Thank you.
What are you going to do now?
You will file a suit, right?
If I file a suit and things go wrong…
Why do you think your daughter is
locking herself up in her room?
Excuse me?
Maybe she's mad at the current situation.
It's already devastating
that her dad died of a simple operation,
but her mom is about to give up
even without taking it to court.
I…
felt the same.
She knows that
her mom is suffering the most
from her dad's sudden death.
How did the interview go?
Well, I think I did a good job.
She can't bring herself
to say such a thing.
If I were you,
I'd ask Ji-woo what she thinks.
JI-WOO
Look, Ji-woo.
What happened to your dad…
wasn't an accident.
His doctor made a mistake
during the operation,
and it killed your dad.
I want
to punish the doctor
for what he did to your dad.
What do you think?
Win.
Ji-woo.
What did you say?
Win the trial.
Okay.
I'll make sure to win
and punish all those
who caused your dad's death.
KIM MIN-JU
Shin I-rang speaking.
I'll do it.
I will fight for Gang-pung and Ji-woo.
You made a good decision.
I will
do my best to help you.
I was taken here,
said goodbye to my family,
and entered the ER.
There were about five people inside…
- Hello.
- How may I help you?
May I take a quick look inside?
- It won't take long.
- No.
- Please leave.
- Wait.
- Come on.
- Leave.
- Wait, I…
- We'll walk you out.
I'm not a weird person!
CHEONGIL HOSPITAL
This won't do.
No.
Hello.
I'm an inspector
from the Korean Hospital Association.
I'm here to conduct a status survey
for better working conditions
of hospital workers.
I see. Please come this way.
Sure.
We've received a report that labor rights
aren't protected at this hospital
due to the recent lack of resources.
I need a list of hiring and termination
for the last six months.
Well, that's…
From 2019 to 2024…
DREAM PRIVATE DETECTIVE AGENCY
ALARM
PETITION
- Congratulations on your first trial!
Congrats!
You'll win for sure today. You can do it!
Uncle, crush them all.
Da-bong, watch your language.
You look amazing, my son.
Good luck.
And watch your manners in court.
Don't you worry. I'll do well.
I'm running late. See you.
- Gosh, okay. We should hurry too.
- Oh, okay.
Where are you all going?
Isn't it obvious?
We're going
to watch your first trial live.
How exciting!
Not you, Da-bong.
You have to go to kindergarten.
Go on. We'll drop her off and follow you.
- Shall we?
- Good luck, Uncle.
Watch it live?
This isn't the Premier League.
COURT OF KOREA
PLAINTIFF'S TABLE
Don't worry. It will go well.
Okay.
I-rang.
I already have enough to worry about.
COURT OF KOREA
You better wait here, Gang-pung.
I can't afford to have you get worked up
during the trial.
I move to examine the defendant,
Lee Jeong-seok, himself.
Accepted.
Defendant, come forward
to the witness stand.
Oh, my goodness.
Why did you come?
I told you to wait outside.
Attorney Shin, are you okay?
I solemnly swear…
- My neck was itchy.
- …to speak the truth
the whole truth and nothing but the truth,
- and if I tell a lie…
- I remembered something I didn't tell you.
Save it. I'm busy right now.
I think it's important.
That punk…
That piece of trash.
Don't get worked up.
Defendant, you performed surgery
on Mr. Lee Gang-pung
on October 13 last year, correct?
Yes.
Will you elaborate
on the situation at that time?
Surgery for snoring is an easy operation.
There was nothing unusual.
According to the materials
from the hospital,
Mr. Lee's case required a change
in the structure of his airway.
Thus, general anesthesia was mandatory.
That's right.
But the problem was
the patient's heart.
That little…
He's lying. It's all a lie!
Calm down. No one else can hear you.
I got this.
That's all.
Your cross, Counsel.
Mr. Lee.
How many nurses were present
during the operation?
Two.
Come on. You're lying.
There were about five people inside.
And three nurses.
Aside from Kim Mi-yeong and Choi Ji-a
whom you reported to court,
there was Oh Jin-suk.
Pardon?
Oh Jin-suk?
Well… I don't know who that is.
She was with you in the ER
until the very end.
Good work, everyone.
- Good work.
She is the witness
who watched what happened
at the closest.
Sir, can you hear me?
Sir? Sir.
Darn, what's going on?
His airway is blocked.
You must perform emergency surgery now!
Should we prepare for a tracheostomy?
- Doctor!
- Shut up!
I'll handle it, okay?
In case your crime got exposed,
you hid the only witness,
Oh Jin-suk, out of fear.
I object, Your Honor.
Let us hear more first.
Counsel, you made
a crucial remark just now.
Can we hear from Oh Jin-suk,
whom you claim to be a witness?
It is
not possible at the moment.
The plaintiff's counsel is straying
from the point with unverified claims.
Please consider
that his statement is inappropriate.
Objection sustained.
Counsel, speak your words carefully.
Yes, Your Honor.
Then today,
I'd like to submit
just his facial expression as evidence.
A facial expression cannot be evidence.
That is all.
Defendant.
Does this kind of accident happen often?
No, it's a rare case.
Then, you must've wondered
what caused the accident.
The thing is…
If it's hard to speak,
should I talk on your behalf?
Sure.
The truth is, Lee Gang-pung was…
a gangster.
- What?
- A gangster?
No way!
- Really?
- Oh, my goodness.
What is she saying?
Gang-pung was a taxi driver.
Your Honor.
The defendant's counsel is
making up a story in this sacred court.
I doubt that.
Lee Gang-pung was part of the Oseong Gang
- in Daejeon 20 years ago.
- Hello, sir!
He has a prior assault conviction.
And please look at his surgery scar here.
He got stabbed in the right chest
at that time.
A patient with the record
of a cardiac operation
died of a cardiac attack
during his surgery.
Is it really irrelevant?
We're screwed.
Your Honor.
The defendant's counsel is
insulting the deceased
as well as inciting hatred
by showing unnecessary pictures
and overly bringing up his past.
Sustained.
Defendant's counsel, please watch it.
I wouldn't have brought up his past
if his behavior had only been in the past.
But he caused a stir with violent words
and uncooperative actions
during his hospitalization.
That's a lie.
Please tell us how he behaved
at the hospital.
Patient Lee Gang-pung…
spoke profanity all the time.
He often scared the nurses
with intimidating behavior.
I heard he did the same to his family.
No.
It's not true.
This can't happen here.
Oh, there's one more thing.
I heard he abused
his middle school daughter.
It caused her to have anorexia
and she's cooping herself up in her room.
Being possessed
manifests when their desires reach a peak.
When they're faced with someone they hate
or something that causes rage,
the possibility of possession increases.
Hey, punk.
Are you out of your goddamn mind?
You're running your mouth
because you see nothing, aren't you?
Are those eyes for show?
Then, give 'em to me instead.
Goodness, this reminds me of the ol' days.
I have quite a lot of experience
in prison.
What is he saying?
And what's wrong with his cheeks?
Mom, I'm getting a feeling
that something bad will happen.
Plaintiff's counsel, go back to your seat.
Dang it, why should I sit down?
That man should be the one sitting
in his coffin.
Punk, how dare you mess around
with your pathetic lies?
You and that little mouth of yours.
I should just…
I truly hate
being a ghost-seeing attorney.
This happened because I was such a softie.
No! Not now!
Don't try to get in the way,
or I'll make you pay.
They submitted
a fabricated record to court.
Search through the EMR.
Consider yourself blessed
to have Attorney Han defend you.
Han Na-hyun would even risk her life
to win a trial.
I'm from the Prosecutors' Office.
I don't care if she's a prosecutor.
Get her.
- Who are you?
- Me?
I'm a gangster attorney, Lee Gang-pung!
Subtitle translation by:
Eunjin Erica Kim