(All places, organizations, characters,
incidents, and backstories...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(Episode 3)
Let me...
Let me first call the cops.
Don't.
These aren't human remains.
It's plastic.
Who's there?
I was wondering
why the door was open.
What are students doing in here?
Principal Park.
It's a skeleton model.
We came to see
if the ghost story was true...
and stumbled upon it.
- What ghost story?
- They say this place is haunted.
The ballet studio, to be exact.
Who would do such a thing?
Actually, when we got here...
We don't know.
I apologize for trespassing.
It won't happen again.
You'd better behave yourselves.
Yes, sir.
(Keep Out)
(Byeongmun High School)
Why did you stop me
from telling him?
About that person
who was here before us.
We don't know for sure who it was.
I thought telling him
would only make things worse.
Who do you think it was?
Time will tell.
Byeongmun High's school uniform
from the 1950s,
the ballet studio,
a skeleton model missing legs,
and a tutu.
The scene was staged...
to perfectly fit the ghost story
of the old building.
Why though?
And who?
This is a key I found
next to the skeleton.
Look at the seal on it.
It's a perfect match
with Seo Byeong Mun's.
What we should especially focus on
is the phrase on its side.
It translates
to "The beginning of the gold bar."
The character itself
doesn't mean "bar" though.
Doesn't that mean odd or bizarre?
It's used to make up the word
for "ghost story."
Are you saying...
there's a connection
between the ghost story...
and the gold bars?
As of now, yes.
The ghost story itself
is the key to finding the gold bars?
Seo Byeong Mun
who hid the gold bars...
set up the ghost story as a riddle.
One must solve the ghost story...
to gain access to the gold bars.
As of now, there are more questions
than answers.
However, I'm certain of two things.
A...
We must find the gold bars
before Chairwoman Seo Myeong Ju does.
B...
Now that we know that the gold bars
and the ghost story are related,
we must focus on that story.
Including the one
of the old building,
Byeongmun High
has four ghost stories in total.
Please approve
of my investigation into them.
Get on it.
Find out about
the other stories first.
Yes, sir.
(The beginning of the gold bar)
The ballet studio?
Why there?
They were there to see
if it was really haunted,
and in the process,
they stumbled upon
a model of human remains.
A ghost story?
Oh, dear. My gosh.
That thought never
even crossed my mind.
A ghost...
How amusing!
I can't believe that man.
He's an odd one. I give you that.
Ghost stories
related to this school?
How should I wrap up
this transgression?
For now,
we'll let them be.
No one knows the school
better than the students.
An unexpected solution
might present itself.
Why do you want to know
about the school ghost stories?
What happened last night
has me intrigued.
Spill, will you?
You really must like
this kind of thing.
I thought that was only
for people like me.
And what kind of person
would that be?
Someone with no connections
and no friends.
A loner and loser
who writes weird web novels.
Hey.
As if there's anything
wrong with you.
Besides, friends are overrated.
Once you graduate,
it's you against the world.
We're all by ourselves.
As if you'd know.
That's just how it is.
Anyway, what's the next ghost story?
Are you trying to make
the ground give way?
What are you thinking
so deeply about?
It's nothing.
What's your take on me?
Do I seem clueless to you?
I can't say
you're quick to notice things.
Why? Did something happen?
Wouldn't you like to know?
Hello, Ms. Choi. Have you been well?
Yes, I have.
I'm sorry to bother you,
but I called about my ID
that the school needed.
I was wondering
when I'd get it back.
The school asked for your ID?
Dong Min's friend said so yesterday.
Dong Min was receiving a scholarship
and my ID was needed.
His friend as in who?
Jeong Hae Seong.
Jeong Hae Seong?
Apart from the story
about the old building,
there are three others.
And one of them is about this.
The grandfather clock.
People think it's broken
because it doesn't chime,
but it does so now and again.
When you're the only one left...
in the school building.
It's the story
everyone's most terrified about.
(Donated by Seo Byeong Mun)
"Never be alone
in the school building..."
"because when the clock chimes,"
"crimson eyes will come for you."
Crimson eyes?
There were
these top two students in school...
You're busted.
Are you conning people now?
Get over here.
Hey, that hurts.
That's "Ms. Oh" to you!
Ms. Oh, please. That hurts.
Give it to me straight.
Why did you take
Dong Min's grandmother's ID?
Her ID?
Is it over if you don't bring it?
Why do you want my grandma's ID?
You almost had me fooled.
This is a serious issue.
Be at the counseling office
after school.
Me?
But it wasn't me.
I'm busy today!
Damn, the stress...
Park Tae Soo, you piece of trash.
Tae Soo...
What will become of that boy?
What am I going to do
with you, Jeong Hae Seong?
Jeong Hae Seong...
(Byeongmun High School)
(Oh Su A)
Hi, starting today,
I'll be your homeroom teacher.
The name is Oh Su A.
I hope we get along.
- Sure.
- Got it.
Come in.
Director.
I have the analysis report
from the Korea Heritage Service.
It is most definitely a forgery.
Agent Jeong's already
carrying out the mission,
so I'm baffled as to
how this should be handled.
(Analysis Report)
(Forgery,
Has no value as a cultural heritage)
You're dismissed.
(Director Kim Hyung Bae)
(Analysis Report)
Hey, Hae Seong.
The analysis report came in.
First, the pointe shoes.
They were buried there
sometime in the 1950s.
As you suspected,
they were probably placed there
by Seo Byeong Mun.
What about the guy
who ran from the building?
I also have
the blood analysis report.
It'd be faster for you
to see it yourself,
so I'll send his info and photo.
Okay, thanks.
(Go Yeong Hun: Hae Seong,
here's his info and photo.)
(Personal and suspect information)
(Student Counseling Office)
What's taking him so long?
Ms. Oh, I'm sorry,
but I left the stove on at home.
I need a drink.
Here you go. You seem exhausted.
Goodness, how sweet of you.
I'll enjoy this.
You must not have gotten
a lot of sleep last night.
Maybe it's because
you were at the old building.
You're the one who threw...
the hammer at me.
That is one wild accusation.
Why would I go there...
when I could piss off the principal.
The tracksuit you wore last night...
How about a wager?
Did you or did you not
scrape your leg on a nail?
The unused sealed entrance
at the back of the old building.
That's how you got in and out.
I only have one question.
What were you doing in there?
You probably knew
about the fake human remains.
- They're fake?
- So you didn't know.
Goodness me.
I thought it was real.
Do you have any idea
how shocked I was at first?
What kind of psycho...
Goodness.
The first time
I discovered the remains,
I mean, the fake skeleton,
was when I was feeding the cat.
You must've been hungry.
Tasty, isn't it?
Nabi.
Nabi?
I was aware of the ghost story
regarding the old building...
and went to check it out
out of boredom.
(Byeongmun High School)
Kids?
What could I do?
I was terrified...
and couldn't say anything
for fear of losing my job.
Last night, I went back
to hammer the floorboards back in...
when you scared the life out of me.
That's why I swirled
the hammer at you.
That's all.
Did you see anything suspicious
the first time you saw the skeleton?
I'll take any minor details.
I'm not sure.
I don't remember anything else.
By the way,
who made you a detective?
Why are you asking me this?
(Mister)
We're good, then.
Don't forget your tetanus shot.
Or you could be in trouble.
(Byeongmun High School)
You won't tell the school, will you?
You have to keep it between us.
Why was the security guard...
in the old building?
I didn't find anything suspicious
about him.
Then why did he run?
He didn't want to be seen
in a restricted area.
I have to ask though.
Why are we here?
Isn't it obvious?
We're here for a meeting.
I get it, but why a sandwich place?
Welcome.
I'll take a sandwich and coke.
Got it. Please have a seat.
- You heard her.
- One sandwich and coke.
What on earth...
I'll cut right to the chase.
This will be...
the headquarters
for Domestic Team Four.
- What?
- Since we're supporting you,
we figured it'd be better...
to be closer to the scene.
I get that,
but this isn't like the movies.
What about the person
who ran this place?
He'll be vacationing in the US
until we're done.
I paid for it with my pension.
You've got to be kidding me.
Does Yu Jeong know?
I agreed to raise her allowance
by 100 dollars.
What about the ghost stories?
Has it been quiet at school?
I'm looking into them.
Meanwhile, at school...
This is a serious issue.
Be at the counseling office
after school.
Nothing's going on.
If you're going
to give me an excuse,
at least let it be decent.
You left your stove on?
Your stove?
That's something I didn't expect.
Just wait till I see you
in school tomorrow.
You'll be begging for mercy!
You've finally lost your mind.
What do you want back?
Give back my grandma's ID.
Unbelievable.
I know you took it,
so before I call the cops...
Shut up.
Hey, get up.
Get up.
Hey.
You've got some balls.
Why have you been
challenging me lately?
Dong Min,
let's stick to how things were.
Give it back.
Just target me, okay?
Leave my grandma out of this.
Damn it.
Fine. Whatever.
I don't need it. Take it.
It'd be no fun
to give it back for free.
Our aspiring writer
is right-handed, is he not?
From now on, you'll be a lefty.
What are you doing?
Hello, Ms. Oh.
I asked you a question.
What are you doing here?
I just got here myself.
Dong Min, are you all right?
What's wrong?
I saw it all.
Park Tae Soo,
wait for me
at the counseling office.
I told you to go.
Should I call your parents?
Goodness.
What a joke.
Ms. Oh.
Just look the other way.
You're only a temp, so act like it.
Damn it.
Ms. Oh, I'll leave it at this
since you look pretty today.
Don't let this be a habit.
Dong Min.
Has this been going on for a while?
Your grandmother called.
- Was it Tae Soo who...
- No, Ms. Oh.
Tae Soo and I
were only messing around,
and I'm fine.
I'm sorry for putting you
in this spot.
I'm sorry.
Shoot.
Give it to me straight.
Why did you take
Dong Min's grandmother's ID?
Hey, Hae Seong.
Are you alone?
Is there something
you need me to do?
Look into something for me.
Park Tae Soo, Class 1 of Grade 11...
If anything like this happens again,
the mission will be called off.
You joined the NIS to follow
in your father's footsteps.
What will you say to him
when you finally locate him?
That you got fired
for botching a mission?
Hello?
It's nothing.
Forget I said anything.
Old lady, get out of my way!
Goodness me. I'm terribly sorry.
I don't appreciate the racket,
so keep it down.
Sorry.
I didn't want you to be late
for your study group.
Come on. Move out of the way.
Goodness.
My gosh.
I'm sorry about that.
Thank you for this.
He sure is an oddball.
It's dangerous out here,
so let's get out of the street.
Let's go that way.
Thank you, young man.
You made the trip home easy for me.
Can I get you something to drink?
It's fine, ma'am. I'll be on my way.
Grandma!
Dong Min, you're home.
- Goodness.
- What's going on?
Why are you two together?
Is he your friend?
A friend of yours?
Hold on a second.
I'm giving you this in the hopes
of you being a good friend to him.
Grab something delicious to eat.
Grandma, come on.
Two dollars gets you nowhere.
You can't even buy a bag of chips.
Is that so?
Oh, dear.
But that's all I have.
This is more than enough, ma'am.
I'll spend it wisely.
- Goodness.
- I'll get going, then.
See you tomorrow.
Good night.
Hae Seong.
Thanks for helping out my grandma.
I considered it a workout.
Besides, it's no big deal.
I overheard what happened
earlier today...
when Ms. Oh approached you.
I should've told her...
that it wasn't you
who took my grandma's ID,
but I didn't know how to say it.
I'm sorry.
There's no need to apologize.
It was Tae Soo, wasn't it?
Yes.
But I'm done worrying about him.
I got the ID back anyway.
If that's what you want.
Head on in.
Your grandma must be waiting.
- Your phone.
- My phone?
Give it here already.
It's my number. Save it.
Call me if anything happens.
I can't believe
I'm saying this to a guy.
I'm really off now.
(Hae Seong)
So, it was Tae Soo
who did that to Dong Min.
We should tell
the vice-principal, right?
Hey, don't even.
As if he'd listen to us.
He's trying so hard
to build connections...
to get the principal title.
Then what do we do about Dong Min?
Just turn a blind eye to it.
What?
Tae Soo's father is
a three-term assemblyman,
and he's on the parent board.
Besides, you know
how things are done at this school.
They're categorized
based on what their parents do.
The school only cares about
important people's kids.
Then let's submit a petition
to the Office of Education.
You're so naive.
And shouldn't you worry
about yourself first?
Ms. Oh, don't you want
a permanent position?
Let's just turn a blind eye to it
this time.
Make a wise decision.
Seriously, what am I supposed to do?
(Start)
It's me, Dong Min.
To tell you the truth,
I didn't have anyone's number,
except for Tae Soo's.
So, thanks.
Hello.
I grabbed this first.
No, I beat you by a split second.
I guess you live around here.
Yes, I guess
you live around here too.
I don't really want it to be known.
As if I wanted to know.
Are you going to
keep talking back to me?
Hey, Jeong Hae Seong.
Get it together.
You're a student,
and I'm your teacher!
You took your hand off,
so it's mine.
Darn it!
(Corn Silk Tea)
The owner stocked the shelf again.
It's buy-1-get-1-free.
Thanks for this.
You knew about Tae Soo
and Dong Min, didn't you?
You knew about it
but couldn't tell me...
because you couldn't trust me, right?
Dong Min asked me not to tell anyone.
About his grandma's ID
and everything else,
I'm sorry
for getting the wrong idea.
About your situation too.
Sorry for not catching on sooner.
So, what's next?
Now that you know everything,
what do you plan to do?
What's this?
Dong Min's grandma gave it to me,
hoping I'd stay friends
with Dong Min.
I don't deserve this.
You can work on it.
You kind of look like him.
- Who?
- Just someone.
Someone who's like my sworn enemy.
What did he do
to become your sworn enemy?
Eat up.
I sure will.
Who is it?
We're from Gangnam Police.
Ms. Choi Bok Sun lives here, right?
What is this about?
Is she inside?
I am Choi Bok Sun.
You're police officers?
We were investigating
an illegal gambling website,
and your name came up.
They said you were running the site.
Take her.
- Wait, but...
- Hold on!
There must have been
some misunderstanding.
Take her.
What? Why are you doing this to me?
Dong Min.
- Grandma!
- Come on.
Dong Min!
Why on earth
are they doing this to me?
- Grandma!
- Seriously!
That's enough. Go back inside, okay?
Grandma!
It's getting late.
Where's your place?
Near those houses over there...
You live in a rooftop room
near the school.
Do you live in a house?
No, in a rooftop room
across the street.
It's close.
Hey, Dong Min.
What?
(Civil Affairs)
Dong Min, what happened?
Ms. Oh.
(Park Tae Soo)
(Bet Amount: 8,000 dollars)
This is why gambling is
so dangerous.
Why do people think
they can win this money?
(Ladder Game, Round 59)
(You've lost.)
Damn it!
Hey, you.
Can I borrow
20,000 dollars from you?
Spare me a moment, Ms. Oh. This way.
I'll be right back, Dong Min.
She was running a gambling site?
What is going on?
I bet this is connected
to Park Tae Soo.
Ms. Choi's ID.
At this rate, Ms. Choi
might end up getting arrested.
That's crazy.
The police must know
she's not the one.
But all the evidence says
it was her.
This is no longer
a school bullying issue.
This is a serious crime,
and someone should step in.
Me?
This isn't right.
What should I do now?
Damn it. This isn't right.
This is wrong!
What do I do?
I should take sick leave.
Yes, I'm going to take sick leave.
That's it.
Ms. Kim mentioned that
she had a positive COVID-19 test.
(1 Dollar)
(Seo Myeong Ju,
Chairwoman of Byeongmun High School)
Ma'am.
You need to see the discussion board
on the school's website.
(Im Yoon Chul)
This crazy punk.
Why is he calling
at this important moment?
(Im Yoon Chul)
What is it?
What?
Hey, guys!
Did you see the discussion board?
It's nuts.
- Someone ratted on Tae Soo.
- What?
- What is it?
- Look at this. Come here.
Look, the discussion board.
- My, Tae Soo is doomed now.
- Amazing.
- Goodbye, Tae Soo.
- Oh, my.
- He was so mean.
- He's done for.
- Honestly, this is all true.
- I know, seriously.
- Who wrote this?
- You reap what you sow.
As they say,
"Reward good and punish evil."
- Totally.
- Tae Soo is doomed now.
Who did this?
Who posted something like this
on the discussion board?
Look, what is this?
Tae Soo bullied Dong Min?
And what? Illegal gambling?
Are these punks trying
to shut the school down?
This is...
Hold on.
Was it perhaps...
one of the teachers?
Ms. Oh?
Did you write this, by any chance?
Who did this?
Who dared...
to disgrace the great Byeongmun High
like this? What a traitor!
- Was it you?
- No, it wasn't me.
- I bet it was you.
- No.
- It was you, Mr. Baek.
- No, it was not me.
- Ms. Oh, please calm down.
- No.
I cannot let this slide.
If it concerns you,
then I'm concerned too.
If it involves the school,
then it's my problem too!
Who dared to upset
our vice-principal like this?
Mark my words.
I will be sure to find out
who did this.
I promise I will bring
the traitor's head to you.
No, you don't need to do that.
Please calm down. Come here.
- How can I calm down right now?
- Well, get back here.
This way. Yes.
- For you, I'll calm down and...
- Yes, it's okay.
Good. Thank you.
Anyway, we'll need
Tae Soo and Dong Min's parents...
to come in tomorrow for a meeting.
Chairwoman Seo will meet with them.
Ms. Oh, please calm down
and contact the parents.
- So, that's what we're doing?
- Yes, that's right.
Got it, sir.
- I'll sit down.
- Yes, please sit.
(Byeongmun High School)
When we catch this person,
we'll teach them a serious lesson.
All right, then.
Get back to work, all of you.
It was you, wasn't it?
Was it that obvious?
A little bit? About 51 percent?
Fifty-one percent?
What will you do if you get caught?
Honestly, I don't know anymore.
I will worry about tomorrow
when tomorrow comes.
Go back to your desk.
"The traitor's head!"
- I shall behead the traitor!
- Goodness.
Oh Su A.
Thank you.
Who knew the situation
would unfold like this?
Isn't it the first time Chairwoman Seo
is meeting with parents?
I knew Park Tae Soo
would end up like this.
He brought it upon himself,
so let him figure out what to do.
What will we do
about Jeong Hae Seong?
Right, at the cafeteria.
I know Tae Soo is a jerk,
but he is a member
of the student council.
He humiliated Tae Soo
in front of everyone.
We can't let him get away with it.
Why not? I liked it.
It was so manly of him.
Are you jealous
because he's good-looking?
Why should we waste time
worrying about that punk?
He seemed a little crazy.
Let's just ignore him...
For now, let's just wait and see.
It's entertaining to have
someone like that at school.
Besides, he piques my curiosity.
This is too bitter.
I don't like this.
Oh, one moment.
Sorry, Yu Jeong. We have to go.
We forgot we had to meet
with our study group.
Oh, okay.
What about you, Yu Jeong?
Well, I'll leave in a bit.
All right, then. See you at school.
Don't worry too much.
Everything will be all right.
You did nothing wrong, Grandma.
They'll let you go as soon as
the misunderstanding is cleared up.
Did you have dinner?
Yes, of course.
You should never skip a meal either.
Eat well, okay?
I'll get you out of here
no matter what, so hang in there.
You can do it, right?
You, over there.
What are you doing here
at this hour?
You can't go in there.
Oh, I'm sorry.
- I was just...
- Hello.
Oh, my.
We haven't met before, right?
I'm Chairwoman Seo Myeong Ju.
- I'm Jeong Hae Seong.
- I know.
Well, Principal Park told me.
Was it a skeleton model?
I heard you and Dong Min
were the ones who found that thing.
Yes.
You must be very interested
in the ghost stories.
You broke the rules...
to enter the old building
and even came in here.
I'm sorry.
I'm just a curious person.
You're a curious person?
Oh, my. That's great.
I mean, I just...
Well, being curious...
is a great thing, as a person.
But you know what?
The students these days
aren't curious.
Well, good for you.
If you ever need my help...
or want a counseling session,
come to my office.
I'm always on the students' side.
Thank you for your advice.
I'll be off, then.
Dong Min.
Thanks for coming
despite your busy schedule.
Dong Min.
Where's your grandmother?
She's still being investigated
by the police.
I'm here instead as his guardian.
Why are we in this mess
because of a stupid post...
anyone could've made?
Did you identify who posted it?
We didn't bother to check.
Whether it's a rumor or a fact,
it will be sorted out today.
Even so, this isn't right.
Ma'am, why don't you calm down?
Let's hear what the kids say.
Yes, honey. Let's wait.
The chairwoman
will handle it just fine.
Why worry?
Lee Dong Min, was it?
I read the online post too.
The assault and stolen ID.
It was full of lies.
Will you explain?
Don't mind us at all. Be honest.
Yes.
Tell your side of the story,
Dong Min.
This isn't fair at all.
We have been good friends so far.
Why would such a post
suddenly appear...
Will you explain the truth?
Dong Min?
The online post.
It's a lie.
Dong Min.
Tae Soo...
didn't hit me.
The one who hit me...
was Jeong Hae Seong.
Dong Min.
Why didn't you
tell the truth earlier?
Will you tell me at least?
Why did you
suddenly mention Hae Seong?
Say anything tomorrow...
and I'll slit your cheeks open.
One more thing.
Who bullied you so far?
Jeong Hae Seong.
That's not true.
It's not? Too bad, then.
Your grandma will die in prison.
I want to help you.
Dong Min?
No.
I don't need your help.
Just keep quiet.
Please...
don't do anything.
I didn't think this would happen.
Tae Soo framed Hae Seong, right?
What will happen to Hae Seong, then?
Will he really be expelled?
And I thought
school had gotten better.
He will be disciplined, I guess?
What's the current score?
Even though it's up to my mom.
Why are you staring at
Hae Seong's seat?
It's nothing.
(Vroom Vroom)
I'm off.
Why did you lie?
Sorry. I have to go.
Were you threatened?
Yes.
I was threatened.
He said if I didn't
put the blame on you,
my grandma would stay in prison.
What else could I do
in that situation?
I can't fight,
my grades are at rock bottom,
and I'm an outcast and a moron.
What should I do?
I tried to think of a way, you know.
Should I call the police...
or tell our homeroom teacher or...
Should I really...
just stab him to death?
I imagined murdering him
dozens of times a day.
I thought prison...
would be nicer than school.
But if I were to do that,
my grandma...
Do you know what the worst part is?
That reality isn't a fairy tale.
The wounds and trauma he left me...
will ensure I stay a loser forever.
But he'll forget that he bullied me
and live happily.
Life isn't fair.
I hope you get through it.
You've never suffered.
Don't talk like that.
You'll never know...
how I feel.
I might not.
I heard your part. Bye.
Jeong Hae Seong.
Why won't you chew me out?
It wasn't your fault.
Whatever happens.
The name I gave you.
Look into him and everyone he knows.
(Anti-School Bullying
Committee Session)
(Grade 11 Class 1 Jeong Hae Seong)
- What?
- Hey.
- Jeong Hae Seong?
- The transfer student?
- What's this?
- He'll be punished?
- For what?
- Look.
- Is this real?
- The transfer student?
- Yes.
- Hae Seong?
- Look.
What did he do?
(Jeong Hae Seong)
- Gu Sang Tae?
- Yes.
He buys innocent people's IDs...
and runs an illegal gambling site
with their names.
He's the one guy...
I think is relevant
to this and Park Tae Soo.
The police recently arrested someone
for being a ringleader.
Her name is Choi Bok Sun.
There's a Lee Dong Min
at the school, right?
She's his grandmother.
(Personnel Information)
Shall I send you
Gu Sang Tae's location?
Right away.
Hello? Where are you?
Has it begun?
You sound like you don't care.
Get here right away.
Ms. Oh. Is Hae Seong not here yet?
He's on his way.
Goodness.
Did you hear that?
You have ten seconds.
Get here now.
Stall for me. I'll be a bit late.
You talk like you're in the right.
You'll be expelled
if you don't come...
I trust you.
What?
What the heck? This is insane.
(Anti-School Bullying
Committee Session)
(Jeong Hae Seong)
(Oh Su A)
(Seo Myeong Ju)
I apologize.
This is quite a long delay.
Ms. Oh?
Well...
Hae Seong will be here soon.
We can't wait forever.
- Let's begin.
- Mr. Park?
We can't proceed
without the student.
Don't you think he's not here
because he has a guilty conscience?
If he's not here,
let's get Tae Soo and...
Who was that kid? The poor one.
Let's talk to them.
Let's do that.
Chairwoman.
I have a joint session later.
(Seo Myeong Ju)
Ms. Oh?
Park Tae Soo and Lee Dong Min.
Get them both.
Okay.
(Jeong Hae Seong)
That was a close call.
What...
There's a famous line
that suits you, Yeong Hun.
"Confess your crimes."
Where's Hae Seong?
Everything Dong Min said is true.
Hae Seong assaulted me...
for no reason in the cafeteria.
Thanks, Dong Min.
For being so brave.
Lee Dong Min.
I'll ask you one last time.
What you just said
about Jeong Hae Seong.
It's all true, right?
Lee Dong Min.
Your statement is true, correct?
It's all...
Hae Seong's doing.
Let's wrap this up.
Chairwoman?
Sure.
Let's wrap it up.
Regarding the school bullying issue,
this school will discipline
Jeong Hae Seong...
by expelling him for his actions
that brought shame...
Wait.
What for?
Do you have something to say?
Well...
What are you doing?
Mt. Geumgang
should be seen after a meal.
Yes.
What I mean is...
So...
They are serving pork cutlets
for lunch today.
I just love pork cutlets.
We eat to live,
and it's almost lunchtime.
- Hae Seong will be here soon...
- Ms. Oh.
Sit down. What are you doing?
Mt. Geumgang and pork
are irrelevant.
Stop it and sit down.
But pork cutlet...
I apologize.
Regarding the school bullying issue,
this school will discipline
Jeong Hae Seong...
by expelling him for his actions
that brought shame...
What is it this time?
Someone rode a motorcycle to school.
A motorcycle? That's madness.
- What's madness?
- What is it?
Kids.
Sit back down.
Let's have a look.
Sit down!
- Look.
- It's for real.
No way.
- Who is it?
Who is it?
Whoever it is he's dead cool.
Hey, look.
Isn't that Jeong Hae Seong?
Hae Seong!
- It's Hae Seong.
- You're awesome!
Hey!
Hae Seong!
It's Hae Seong!
That lunatic.
Move. What is it?
A motorcycle...
He's here. Jeong Hae Seong.
It's Jeong Hae Seong.
You look awesome!
- Look over here!
- What?
Hae Seong!
That crazy...
Will you give me a ride?
Hae Seong!
Our school is a mess.
- Hae Seong!
- Look at him.
- Jeong Hae Seong!
You crazy...
I'm sorry I'm late.
Shall we begin?
(Undercover High School)
I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry.
If you show some mercy...
How can you say that
to my son's messed-up face?
This is why kids without parents
are troublemakers.
From what my son said,
you're not related to him.
You're just a patron.
I didn't teach him properly.
Please show some forgiveness.
No. I won't let this go.
Si Hyun.
Say you're sorry.
Why should I?
- Jeong Si Hyun.
- They teased me...
for being an orphan
and picked on me.
Why should I apologize?
Do you hear what he's saying?
He's proving
how poorly you taught him!
Sir.
I want that punk expelled.
I'll drop out.
Hey, you. Come back here.
Will you really quit school?
Will you quit school?
Quit if you want to.
School isn't the only way
to get a high school diploma.
Study at home...
and get a GED.
Can I do that?
Why not?
I'm on your side.
And...
I'm sorry.
I'm doing my best
to fill in for your dad,
but it's not easy.
You're doing enough.
I'm grateful.
Damn it.
Hey, I'm hungry.
Let's get some ramyeon.
Let's go.
(Undercover High School)
If you're asking
if I was violent against Dong Min...
No.
I didn't do that.
I just feel like
my heart is skipping.
I'll be careful.
No one knows the fourth story.
The twin clocks?
There were always two.
"Student Council recruitment?"
Don't join.
I'll tell everyone who you are.
He's a loose cannon.
He could stir up more ruckus,
so keep an eye on him.
Hae Seong, there's a problem.
What?
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)