ظآزShrugging off past burdensظآز
ظآزBeneath the mask, who am I?ظآز
ظآزRelease and find wider shoresظآز
ظآزLove's a riddle, and rain pours heavyظآز
ظآزCrossed paths, now downward fallظآز
ظآزFrom dust arises starlight's sparkظآز
ظآزTearing through
the night's dense blockadeظآز
ظآزHeart's flame illuminates all solitudeظآز
ظآزLet time's sails drift endlesslyظآز
ظآزThrough wandering exileظآز
ظآزBreaking free from the cocoon,
I start anewظآز
ظآزMoon as song, life as flameظآز
ظآزNameless heart clings fiercelyظآز
ظآزLet meظآز
ظآزCharge toward the next raging riverظآز
ظآزMoon darts, snow fallsظآز
ظآزWe tread rugged paths to reuniteظآز
ظآزHands held tightظآز
ظآزWe forever live for love's sakeظآز
ظآزShadow's spear burns fiercelyظآز
=Legend of The Female General=
=Episode 35=
(Xiao Zhongwu, Song Wan)
Father, Mother.
I cannot abandon the Xiao Army.
Nor can I be her obstacle.
If we're not destined to be a couple,
then I'd rather be
single and alone.
(Virtues' Enduring Legacy)
Your Majesty.
Shall I
change it with fresh flowers?
I ruined Xiao Jue and He Yan's marriage.
They
must hold resentment toward me.
I suppose
you have your reasons, Your Majesty.
The imperial court requires
a balance.
But now,
two powerful generals
seek to unite.
How could I
rest easy with this?
Their grievances were predictable.
Since that's the case,
I shall
make their division
more absolute.
Your Majesty,
General Fengyun requests an audience.
(Xiao Mansion)
Your wedding gown
was rushed to completion.
It just arrived.
Quickly try it on.
If it doesn't fit,
we'll alter it.
Come on.
Come.
The embroidery and fabric
are truly first-rate.
Huaijin is thoughtful.
But this dress looks so complicated.
How do I wear it?
Don't worry.
We'll help you.
Go try it.
Miss He looks stunning.
Huaijin chose well.
In Yaojing, these past years,
no bride's gown
could compare to
what you're wearing now.
Truly magnificent.
Rongwei.
Miss He.
Huaijin has returned.
Let him try his attire alone.
Right now,
he shouldn't see
the bride's full ensemble.
He's returned with an imperial edict.
Xiao Jue.
Is anything wrong?
He Yan, heed the decree.
His Majesty
decrees that
He Yan,
a scholar and warrior,
has done great feats,
protecting Jiyang,
defending Rundu,
and repelling Wutuo.
For her contributions,
she is granted
the Mansion of General Feihong.
May she continue
exceeding my expectations
with tireless dedication
and loyalty.
- Thank...
- Another edict.
General Feihong,
He Yan,
has noble character
and dual expertise.
Lord Shijin's son,
Chu Zhao, Vice Director
of the Secretariat,
has honorable bearing
and exceptional talent.
They are
a most fitting match.
By imperial decree,
the two shall wed
(Imperial Edict)
on a day
of good fortune.
That's all.
He Yan narrowly escaped death
to reclaim the General Feihong title.
Forcing her to abandon it
would erase
her very essence.
The Xiao Army
is my father's life's work
and remains my duty.
Let me let go.
Then I
cannot remain myself.
It seems
you've made your choice.
You left me no other choice.
I shall have you perform another task.
This marriage decree.
You shall personally deliver.
No,
I won't.
You are defying my order?
Please
punish me.
You...
Aren't you afraid of
dragging down your family?
If that's your order,
I obey.
What did you say?
Repeat that.
You broke plum branches
and made bridal attire for me.
In the end,
you want me to marry someone else.
ظآزWalking through the crowd,
without asking about the futureظآز
ظآزWandering half a lifetime,
solitary as the moonظآز
If that's the case,
I...
accept...
and give thanks.
ظآزJust to see you turn,
a fleeting blush in your glanceظآز
ظآزJust to tread the snow you describedظآز
ظآزThe more fate intertwines intenselyظآز
ظآزThe further we drift apartظآز
ظآزIt's hard to sever love or hatredظآز
ظآزBefore destiny is sealedظآز
ظآزAgain and againظآز
ظآزMy love rests between your fingersظآز
ظآزFarewell tears blur my visionظآز
ظآزIndescribable yearningsظآز
General Fengyun,
why won't you let go?
How else should I
accept this decree gratefully?
ظآزBefore destiny is sealedظآز
ظآزAgain and againظآز
ظآزMy love for you burns fiercelyظآز
ظآزLifelong devotion turns into a vowظآز
ظآزThat's my last wishظآز
ظآزAwaiting the spread of moonlightظآز
(As the General Feihong,)
you must soar freely
in the sky.
The Emperor
summons General Feihong to the palace.
(Devoted to Duty, Open to Counsel)
This is He Yan.
Your Majesty.
At ease.
Miss He,
I know you and Mr. Xiao
share mutual affection.
But
Mr. Chu is also an outstanding talent.
He'll soon rise
to first-rank official status.
Your Majesty,
however great he is,
it is irrelevant to me.
I come today
to request you to revoke that decree.
Your Majesty.
At ease.
Perfect timing.
She wants me to retract my decree,
but it's inappropriate.
Your Majesty,
I will cherish He Yan wholeheartedly
and make her understand my sincerity.
Given time...
This is unnecessary.
Your Majesty,
I know
you just want to prevent
a marriage between two military leaders.
I won't marry Xiao Jue.
But
I won't marry Chu Zhao either.
Outrageous!
Please calm your anger.
I
won't defy the decree,
but I refuse to settle.
If I can't spend my life
with the one I love,
I would rather
remain alone forever.
Please grant me.
Your Majesty,
if He Yan
refuses to marry Chu Zhao,
I implore you
to grant her
a choice.
Fine.
Have it your way.
I shall
take my leave.
(Have I)
(truly erred?)
Were you involved in
this arranged marriage?
Yes.
I requested it.
But Xiao Jue still dumped you.
You're an intelligent man.
You should understand
that decree cannot constrain me.
We were never
in the cards.
There's no future
for you two.
Why not turn your eyes to me?
Can you not tell
my heart is as true as his?
That's not love.
It was all a calculated game.
Should I cut open my heart?
Is a calculated heart any less worthy?
Tell me!
You're insane!
How much ambition is hidden
behind the love you speak of?
Was every single thing you did
truly only for me?
Stop deluding yourself, Chu Zhao.
I'm just
a pretty excuse for your ambition.
You know what?
You're becoming another Xu Jingfu.
(Chu Mansion)
Miss Xu, your meal is served.
Chu Zhao had you send these
for me to eat?
You're overthinking, Miss Xu.
Our young master
is extremely busy.
He has no time to care about it.
You wretched maid.
You!
Still acting high and mighty?
Listen up.
His Majesty has decreed
a marriage between our young master
and General Feihong.
Abandon your foolish hopes.
What did you say?
Chu Zhao is marrying He Yan?
Y-Yes.
The news has spread everywhere.
No way.
Chu Zhao,
you won't get your way.
Have you met with Miss He?
How about
your marriage?
There will be no marriage.
Don't bring it up.
I heard about
your imperial marriage decree
and came specially to congratulate you.
Why the haste, Mr. Chu?
I once thought
only fools like me
would cling to unrequited feelings,
be used by others
and then discarded like trash.
I never imagined
that a shrewd man
like you could also
experience unrequited desires.
Miss Xu,
if you continue this outburst,
I'll have to ask you to leave.
If you're done venting,
I'll arrange your return.
Return?
Return where?
You killed my father.
My family home is sealed.
I have neither a home nor a father.
Even the lowest servants
look down on me.
You tell me to return.
Tell me where I should go.
Where should I go? Tell me.
Tell me!
Miss Xu.
What?
You think yourself the greatest victim?
What of those sold into slavery
and forced to grovel?
Or those displaced
and begging on the streets?
Your father's death
was nothing but his deserved punishment.
You still live in luxury.
Only deprived of your former status.
And you're whining now?
You deceived me,
betrayed me,
and dumped me.
But I'd let it all slide.
How could you betray my father?
He may have been a monster to the world,
but he never did you any harm.
In this situation,
you still act superior.
I don't know if this is pitiful
or laughable.
Chu Zhao.
Yingxiang.
Ying...
Guards!
Go fetch a physician. Hurry!
Yes.
Yingxiang.
It's okay, Yingxiang.
It's okay. Don't worry, Yingxiang.
You will be okay.
I
don't fear.
I only fear
in the world,
you'll end up alone.
From now on,
stop pushing yourself so hard.
Spare...
Spare yourself.
Chu Zilan.
This is your karma.
Those you love
remain unattainable.
Those who love you
abandon you.
ظآزYet I yearn to stand opposed to youظآز
This is your karma.
Karma!
This is your karma!
ظآزUpon towering fortress wallsظآز
ظآزBrooding over lamented pastsظآز
ظآزWhere shall light be foundظآز
ظآزOnceظآز
ظآزI had an unbreakable faithظآز
Get out!
Listen.
No customers,
no coming back today!
Stop putting on airs like noble ladies!
Did your father even accept you?
I'll teach you a lesson!
Stop!
ظآزHeartacheظآز
ظآزResenting the lonely yearsظآز
Leave with me.
ظآزNot let it goظآز
ظآزTears crystallize to frostظآز
ظآزClutching stubborn obsessionsظآز
ظآزYet falling into follyظآز
ظآزFading into oblivionظآز
ظآزYet memories surge everywhereظآز
ظآزAfter the separationظآز
ظآزMy heart feels adriftظآز
(Virtues' Enduring Legacy)
(Ancestral Tablets of the Xiao Clan)
Huaijin,
yesterday, you read the decree
not just under imperial pressure,
but also to shield me and my wife,
and to protect the Xiao Army.
Since childhood, you've shouldered
too much for our family
and me.
Always walking on thin ice
and bearing heavy burdens.
But since Miss He arrived,
you've been a lot brighter
and more open.
As your brother,
I'm deeply grateful to Miss He.
But Huaijin,
you've already given too much.
Don't sacrifice your marriage.
This is unfair to both of you.
Don't overthink it.
No matter what,
we will
always support you.
Why are you still here?
Are you just going
to wait until Miss He marries others?
Can you bear that?
(General Feihong's Mansion)
ظآزConstant yearningظآز
ظآزStill vivid as our first meetingظآز
ظآزEndless gazingظآز
ظآزStep by step, falling deeperظآز
ظآزHow to untangle this loveظآز
ظآزBuried deep within dreamsظآز
ظآزMy heart, unyielding as stone,
remains trueظآز
Why have you come?
I can't let you go.
I can't get past it.
I can't give you up.
ظآزTime lingers as you and I share
overlapping palm linesظآز
ظآزZither and harp
accompany our dancing dreamsظآز
Then why did you
come to see me only now?
Is it still possible?
ظآزIn the vast world,
I searched for yearsظآز
ظآزShadows hustle. Scenes reappearظآز
ظآزWhat is there to fearظآز
ظآزWe'll weather storms togetherظآز
Of course it's not too late.
No one can force me to do
what I refuse to do
or marry whom I refuse to marry.
ظآزSplendor fades from your eyesظآز
I'm done with overthinking
and hesitation.
Now,
I'm doing what I want.
ظآزZither and harp
accompany our dancing dreamsظآز
I understand your struggles.
You care for me,
but how can you abandon your army?
I've convinced His Majesty.
I won't marry you
or anyone else.
With or without a marriage contract,
He Yan,
you're my chosen wife.
And I choose you too.
ظآزThe brocade moon writes our vow,
keeping this promiseظآز
(Happiness, Groom's Procession)
I keep thinking
you're still
that naive young girl.
But now,
you're a bride.
Yan,
I'm suddenly scared.
What should I do?
After today,
you'll have a new identity.
It's natural
to feel nervous.
But Taotao,
remember.
Whether you are
someone's wife
or a mother,
never forget
that above all, you are yourself.
Don't let any single identity
confine you.
I won't forget.
I have my aspirations to pursue
and books I want to write.
Whether Cheng Lisu is with me or not,
I'll see them through.
Why the sudden tears?
If you keep crying,
your makeup will smudge.
It just occurred to me
that if you wore bridal attire,
you'd outshine everyone in Yaojing.
Even more radiant than me.
But now...
Who cares about marriage?
I'll still be a general,
live my life,
and enjoy my freedom.
Alright, stop crying.
Save those tears
for the wedding procession later.
The bride alights from her sedan!
Blessings descend!
The couple enters the gate!
Fortunes arrive!
The star of fortune clears all paths!
Step over the saddle for good omens!
The bride crosses the saddle!
May peace and wishes be granted!
Come on.
Step over the saddle!
Cheng Lisu.
Don't be angry.
I just wanted to surprise you.
See.
Turning the felt like a scroll,
joy yearns to be whole.
Husband and wife turn the felt,
may your house brim with descendants!
Good fortune hides in the fans!
Open them with a smile!
Fans open!
Flowers bloom with prosperity!
First bow to heaven and earth!
Second bow to the parents!
Peace throughout the year!
The couple bows to each other!
A century of devotion!
The ceremony is complete!
- Congrats.
Congrats.
Who told you to wear this?
I think this pouch looks great.
Just don't tell anyone
that I embroidered it.
Get up.
Send the newlyweds
to the bridal chamber!
Having such a lively wedding
is truly wonderful.
Sorry.
No.
Many lovers in this world
never get together.
At least, we, here and now,
can hold hands.
Even without marriage,
we'll grow old together.
Why aren't you eating?
In this freezing weather,
we should have lamb hotpot.
General Feihong, eat a lot.
Get stronger.
Put on some weight.
The world thinks slimness
makes women attractive.
Why do you think differently?
Others' opinions
mean nothing to me.
I only want you
to be vigorous and healthy,
so you can triumph on battlefields.
That's what I like to hear.
Here's to you, General Fengyun.
General Feihong.
They're sounding
the drums at the beacon tower.
Commander.
Border alert.
Wutuo attacks Mingshui
and Huayuan simultaneously.
No time to waste. Go to the palace now.
ظآزLight shines upon my heartظآز
ظآزUnveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstreamظآز
ظآزThe resonance of courage
rings loud and clearظآز
ظآزIt's the boldness
that defines existenceظآز
ظآزI've seen the mountainsظآز
ظآزAnd trodden through iceظآز
ظآزDay after day, I venture aloneظآز
ظآزDestiny is my creedظآز
ظآزIdeals surge beneath the surfaceظآز
ظآزIgniting the flame against the windsظآز
ظآزA restless yearning in my soulظآز
ظآزGazing through the mireظآز
ظآزWho cares about this boundless voidظآز
ظآزCharge ahead with blazing fervorظآز
ظآزStubbornly fighting with my lifeظآز
ظآزSoaring across the world's expanseظآز
ظآزThere must always be a longingظآز
ظآزDisregard the wounds to seek the lightظآز
ظآزLight shines upon my heartظآز
ظآزUnveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstreamظآز
ظآزThe resonance of courage
rings loud and clearظآز
ظآزIt's the boldness
that defines existenceظآز
ظآزChasing the light within my heartظآز
ظآزBurying frailty,
embracing life through deathظآز
ظآزYou'll meet gazes where storms brewظآز
ظآزWith our unwavering true love,
brave the world with meظآز
ظآزSoaring across the world's expanseظآز
ظآزThere must always be a longingظآز
ظآزDisregard the wounds to seek the lightظآز
ظآزLight shines upon my heartظآز
ظآزUnveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstreamظآز
ظآزThe resonance of courage
rings loud and clearظآز
ظآزIt's the boldness
that defines existenceظآز
ظآزChasing the light within my heartظآز
ظآزBurying frailty,
embracing life through deathظآز
ظآزYou'll meet gazes where storms brewظآز
ظآزWith our unwavering true love,
brave the world with meظآز