(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
(Press Conference)
Good afternoon.
I am Xu Wanxin.
Today,
in my capacity
as Interim Chairwoman of Minghui Group,
I am here to announce
important decisions of the Group.
First,
the remains of Mr. Xu Zhaoming,
former President of Minghui Group,
have been safely returned to Gang City.
The funeral will be held tomorrow.
We ask that members of the media
refrain from disturbance.
Second,
Chairman Xu Qianmo
is currently in stable condition.
We appreciate the attention
and concern from all sectors.
Although Minghui
is presently facing
significant turbulence and challenges,
up to this point,
our cooperation with Junlin Group
continues to progress
steadily and intensively.
Now, please welcome my fiance,
Mr. Shen Gu, shareholder
of Junlin Group, to speak.
Ladies and gentlemen, good afternoon.
I am Shen Gu.
It is a great honor
to stand here
as Miss Xu Wanxin's fiance.
I am truly grateful to Miss Xu Wanxin
for choosing me in this partnership
between Junlin and Minghui.
From this day forward,
I will uphold Minghui Group's
century-long founding vision.
(Junlin Group)
Creating value for the people,
contributing to the prosperity
of the nation.
Finally,
as the largest shareholder
of Junlin Group,
I will commit thirty-five percent
of my shares
to ensure the stability of cooperation
between the two companies.
Quite an honor?
You really played the part well.
Anyone watching would think
you were the one
engaged to Xu Wanxin for eight years.
Can you keep your composure?
At this rate, how will you
ever achieve anything big?
Dump all the Minghui shares
in your hands.
I want Minghui stock
to drop below 120 today.
Yes.
=Echoes of Gang City=
=Episode 4=
(Very convincing)
(Minghui Holdings)
Shen Tingyuan's people
have already begun to act.
No need to rush.
What Shen Tingyuan is doing
is sending a signal to the market.
Shen Gu does not represent Junlin Group.
Could it be that in the end
we will really be pushed by Datong Bank
into early loan repayment?
Miss Xu,
Minghui Group's stock is dropping.
Do you have any measures
to stabilize the share price?
Thank you to all members of the media
for your attention and support for our Group.
As for this...
Minghui!
Watch out!
(Minghui Group Press Conference)
Minghui,
return our hard-earned money!
Take him away!
What was that just thrown?
It smells awful.
Dear members of the press,
it is ammonia.
The concentration is low.
Please remain calm.
Are you alright?
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Miss Xu,
if Mr. Xu Qianmo does not
regain consciousness this time,
how do you plan to handle
the issues Minghui is currently facing?
How will you respond to the public
(Minghui Group Press Conference)
about the sharp drop in share price?
Miss Xu, you suddenly changed
your marriage partner.
Were the two of you
already involved before this?
Yes, ask it like that.
Strip away all their dignity for me.
Continue clearing out
all Minghui shares.
(Minghui Holdings)
Everyone,
you are not on
our invited media list at all.
How did you get in?
At a press conference, you are actually
blocking us from covering it.
That only shows
you have something to hide.
You entered
under the guise of reporters.
What are your intentions?
We are here to uncover the truth.
Do you even realize
impersonating a reporter is illegal?
Sir,
my father has just passed away.
I have lost the person
who loved me most in this world.
My grandfather
collapsed from the shock
and was rushed to the hospital.
Minghui has fallen into
an unprecedented crisis.
And what am I facing?
It is my former
most trusted fiance Shen Hao
and his father Shen Tingyuan
using Minghui's future as leverage
to force me into marriage
and give up my shares,
trying to take everything my father
left behind through marriage.
This is the life's work
they devoted everything to.
All I want
is to protect what they built.
My mind is filled with Minghui,
and the livelihoods of our employees
and the interests of our shareholders.
I simply have no time
to think about the shameful
insinuations you are making.
As for Shen Gu and me...
As for my marriage to Shen Gu,
I know everyone finds it sudden.
But to me,
from the moment
he chose to stand by Minghui,
he is the one I can rely on,
my strongest partner
in both my marriage and my career.
Tonight,
all those reporters
who maliciously smeared my wife
and those behind them,
I will make sure you pay
the harshest price the law allows.
(Minghui Holdings)
Now.
Time to move, brothers.
- Okay.
Everyone,
please leave now.
In ten minutes, announce the partnership
between Qingniao and Minghui.
Spread it as fast as possible.
Also,
find the person who caused trouble
at the press conference.
I apologize
for the disturbance just now.
What I was about to announce is
that our Minghui Group
has entered into a strategic partnership
with a globally renowned company.
Minghui's key projects
will continue to move forward.
Funding is currently sufficient
with no concerns ahead.
This is my response to all of you
and the confidence of Minghui Group.
Miss Xu,
can you disclose which company
you are partnering with?
(Confidentiality Obligation)
Minghui Group will issue
an official statement
to inform the public.
Ms. Xi, Qingniao Group
has just officially announced
their partnership with Minghui Group.
It is a formal statement
on their official website.
Qingniao?
Miss Xu,
are you referring to Qingniao Group?
(Official Statement)
Thank you all for your
attention and concern.
And we also thank Qingniao Group
for their strong support
of Minghui Group.
Thank you.
(Minghui Holdings)
It is rising.
Good.
♪It is a night filled
with a soft fragrance♪
♪Forgot again
to prepare dinner for myself♪
♪Arguing playfully
with a friend on the phone♪
♪Seeing each other often
has made things feel ordinary♪
What is going on?
We signed a confidentiality
agreement with Qingniao.
Without their approval, we were not
supposed to announce the partnership.
It was Qingniao's official website
that released the partnership
statement with Minghui.
People from Qingniao.
Hello, Ms. Xu Wanxin.
We have discovered
that someone has been maliciously
manipulating Minghui Group's stock price.
To protect our partner company,
without prior notice to you,
our Group decided to announce
the partnership with Minghui.
This means a great deal
of support for us.
Thank you for your decision.
We appreciate your understanding.
Alright then.
Wait.
If possible,
I would like to meet the person
in charge of Qingniao Group.
I want to thank them in person.
(START)
About what happened today,
thank you.
If you want to thank me,
go home tonight and get a good rest.
Wanxin.
Look at this news.
Arizona News Agency has issued a notice,
announcing its shutdown
as an apology for its improper remarks
about Minghui Group.
The reporter involved
has had their press credentials revoked.
Did you do this?
Me?
Even Ms. Song could not pull this off.
Either way,
it is a good thing.
Tomorrow is Uncle Xu's funeral.
Go back early tonight and rest.
I will stay here with Grandpa for you.
I want
him to see me first when he wakes up.
Alright.
Boss,
after Miss Xu took the call,
she wants to meet you.
Understood.
♪Tonight the rain falls soft and slow♪
♪Blending with letters left unread
drifting through the air♪
♪You turn and look back at me♪
♪In those same eyes
familiar tears quietly appear♪
♪It feels like we have carried so much♪
♪So many questions time itself
could not make clear♪
♪The moment you walked into my life♪
♪Every dream I had became
something I want with you near♪
♪How many letters
have I written just for you♪
♪If only you could truly hear
what my heart is trying to say♪
♪From this life on no distance
could keep us apart♪
♪The promise we made♪
♪Will find its way
to be fulfilled one day♪
♪But I want more
than just that fleeting gaze♪
♪Still I have not heard your answer♪
♪Can we still rewrite
the ending we face♪
♪When regrets begin to turn around
you will hear it all♪
♪Everything that leads me back to you♪