(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
9 YEARS AGO
This is hilarious.
Hwal-sung.
Yes?
What?
For real?
Wait, Hwal-sung.
- Oh, sorry.
- Be careful.
I don't believe it.
Oh, my goodness!
Good job, Yi-gyeong.
You too.
My gosh...
It's for real.
Two lines.
It's unbelievable.
Hey, should you be out this late
with Yi-gyeong at home?
How far along is she?
Sixteen weeks.
It's just the beginning.
I can't believe you'll be a dad.
I'm so worried about you.
Drink first, noodles later?
I'll accept but not drink.
I have an early start tomorrow.
Yi-gyeong wants me to take
the civil servant exam.
I've never studied in my life,
so how am I going to do that now?
Forget it. You'd be more of a patriot
doing something else.
I agree.
For my country's sake,
I won't become a civil servant.
Why did you want to see me
all of a sudden?
Friend.
Do you want to be a landlord?
What?
Now bring your arms forward
and stretch them out.
I'm home, Mrs. Jeon.
One, two, three, four.
Relax and breathe.
Seven, eight, nine, ten.
Two, two, three, four
five, six, seven, eight, nine...
Arms up, one, two...
Whether the baby's a boy or a girl
it's a Jeon with my blood,
so remember that.
Yes, Mrs. Jeon. Of course.
Carry yourself appropriately.
I will.
Mrs. Jeon.
I'm actually working on something.
It's for Yi-gyeong and our child.
Do you think
you could help me out?
Let's talk after the baby is born.
Okay.
SELLER: KIM YEONG-HWA, LEE GYU-HAK
BUYER: GI SU-JONG
I think it's done.
- The transfer went through.
- Okay.
- Please give me a moment.
- Sure.
- I'll write you a receipt.
- Okay.
Gosh.
Hello, Mr. Landlord.
You psycho.
If I'd known you would buy
I'd have gone somewhere expensive.
You drank a bit too much.
We should get together one day
with Seon and Yi-gyeong.
Yes, sure.
Thanks for the food and drink,
Mr. Landlord.
Get home safely, Mr. Landlord.
- Gosh, thanks.
- Thank you.
- Thanks so very much.
- You're the best.
It's mine.
- Thank you.
- Goodbye.
Bye.
Hello, Mrs. Jeon.
What?
INTENSIVE CARE UNIT
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
Yi-gyeong.
The mother will pull through.
And the baby?
THE PASSCODE IS INCORRECT
PLEASE TRY AGAIN
How dare you set foot in here?
Mrs. Jeon. Did you...
Did you change the passcode?
Don't even think of coming home
until Yi-gyeong fully recovers.
What do you mean by that?
I must look after her.
It's the second miscarriage already.
Listen carefully.
I do know one thing.
A couple can never overcome
the loss of a child.
Prepare to split up.
Mrs. Jeon!
Yi-gyeong!
Yi-gyeong.
SU-JONG
What do you want?
What's up with you?
What do you mean?
What happened
to the remaining balance?
I'm sorry, man.
I don't think I can help.
What's the matter with you?
Is that all you can say?
Mom was harsh this time, wasn't she?
It wasn't your fault.
I talked to her for you.
Let's lie low for a while.
She's distraught, too.
Okay.
- No.
- What?
I haven't fully recovered yet.
Can you take that away for me?
I can't stand to look at it.
Why did you bring the urn?
It must've been so hard on Yi-gyeong.
I thought she'd want to see it
one last time.
You don't know anything at all.
Let's go inside.
Hwal-sung.
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
EPISODE 10
Wait, who are you?
Hwal-sung.
I need you to die today.
What?
I'll see you in hell, friend.
4 MINUTES
So...
We want to say he fell to his death
when he came to check out
a property up for auction.
Can you help me carry him over there?
Darn it.
I'm doing all sorts of things now.
What's up?
What are you up to?
Don't come closer.
Or what?
Stay there.
Don't come closer.
What are you even doing?
You're cute.
You'll hit me with that?
Go ahead.
How about you all go down today?
I followed you
because I had a bad feeling.
Darn you...
Go to sleep.
Ae-su.
Let's handle that first.
- How long has it been?
- About five minutes.
Darn it.
- Step away from the patient.
- Step back.
Calibrating machine.
Administered electric shock.
- Step away from the patient.
- Step back.
Press the orange button.
Administering electric shock.
Administered electric shock.
Begin CPR.
Ae-su.
Min Hwal-sung.
Wake up, Hwal-sung.
It worked.
He's awake. Hwal-sung.
Are you all right?
He's okay.
- It worked.
- Yes.
Su-jong?
Wake up, Su-jong.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Are you all right?
- Yes, what about you?
- Yes.
What about Hwal-sung?
He's awake.
DO NOT ENTER
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
PERSONAL DETAILS
OF CONTRACTING PARTIES
NAME: MIN HWAL-SUNG
- You got it?
- Yes, let's go.
Take care of the rest for us.
Wait, what about him?
Will we get out of there safely?
Yes, of course.
JONAH, REAL CAPITAL
Call me whenever you need help.
(Are you okay?)
How do you feel?
To have murderers for parents.
(You have no right to say that.)
Are you saying I'm in the wrong?
(I think there are lines
that shouldn't be crossed.)
Your parents crossed the line first.
(Just because someone did wrong
doesn't mean I can, too.)
We made it look like
he fell from a height.
It's over now. Can we take Da-rae?
Turn yourself in.
I will after the body's found.
Da-rae.
(Is Hwal-sung really dead?)
We'll explain everything later.
Let's get out of here.
- Come along.
- Let's go.
Wait.
- Take your time.
- Okay.
JEON YI-GYEONG
Hello, Yi-gyeong.
Why would you call at this hour?
Detective.
Come to Se-yoon Building right away.
Is something wrong, Yi-gyeong?
Your voice sounds a bit off.
The culprit you're after is here.
You'll recognize them
when you see them.
What is it?
Let's go.
Where to?
Keep still over there
or I might have to zap you again.
Why would you do that?
You're no electric eel.
Here's the key.
People will come in the morning
to check out the property.
Okay, fine.
In return
- will you do me a favor?
- What is it?
I'm about to wet myself.
What do you want me to do about it?
Will you undo my pants for me?
You've lost your mind.
Come on.
You won't let me
go to the toilet anyway.
What the...
Help me out here.
Undo them from behind.
I have some pride
and rights, you know.
Come on.
I can't hold it in much longer.
Hey, stop it.
Hey!
Darn you!
Hey.
What the heck?
Is that him?
Darn it.
SE-YOON STUDY ROOM
Seon, you take Da-rae
and leave.
You go ahead.
Go, it's okay.
We'll chat a bit first.
Did he say anything when he died?
I can't say.
Before Hwal-sung died
did he leave any last words?
He said he was sorry.
And he asked me
to speak well of him to his child.
Hwal-sung knew
I was pregnant?
Yes.
LOAN HEAVEN
Keep them all there.
They faked it.
They duped us!
To the very end...
Hey, Gi Su-jong!
Get him!
Seon, get out of here!
Get in here!
Get him!
What's going on?
- Hey.
- Yes?
Am I in paradise?
- You're in Korea.
- What?
What are you doing here?
Where's Su-jong?
At Se-yoon Building.
To save Da-rae.
Da-rae?
Oh, gosh.
You don't know?
Your wife kidnapped Da-rae.
Hey.
Thanks for saving my life.
HANMAEUM BADUK CLUBHOUSE
M&amp;A REALTORS
They cleaned up pretty well.
They did not.
You bastard.
- Get him!
- You punk!
JONAH, REAL CAPITAL
Get out of there!
Will you pick up?
We're on the third floor.
Save us.
JONAH, REAL CAPITAL
SAVE US, SE-YOON BUILDING
Save us, Se-yoon Building.
MISSED CALL: SE-YOON BUILDING
Shall we go?
Yes, let's go.
M&amp;A REALTORS
DO NOT ENTER
That's enough.
Go upstairs and find the girls.
Okay.
Hurry up and open it!
You're here.
Move aside.
- Get him.
- Let go of me.
Darn it.
HANMAEUM BADUK CLUBHOUSE
How will you escape this time?
Keep talking nonsense, you idiot.
Who the heck are you?
Hey, there.
What the heck is going on?
Darn it.
What is this?
What's this fire?
You bastard.
What? What's going on?
Min Hwal-sung?
Do not come! Don't!
It's 52 Sejeong-ro,
in front of Se-yoon Building.
Min Hwal-sung?
No, there's a fire.
The building is on fire.
Min Hwal-sung!
LOAN HEAVEN
Wait!
Yi-gyeong!
Seon.
Seon, Da-rae.
Please.
Please stop.
You need to calm down, Yi-gyeong.
Don't do it.
Don't do this, Yi-gyeong.
Don't come closer.
Stay there! Don't come closer!
Calm down, Yi-gyeong.
We can go back to how things were.
Let Da-rae go.
Please.
But I lost everything. So how?
I lost everything! So how?
How can things go back to before?
It can, Yi-gyeong.
You have your baby.
Think of your baby.
Please.
It's time to stop.
- Please?
- Yes.
Please stop.
Yi-gyeong.
What is this?
What's going on?
I can explain.
All of you...
All of you were on the same side.
No, Yi-gyeong. That isn't the case.
You were all on the same side.
Let's not do this here.
We can talk alone.
No.
Say everything here.
This wasn't what I wanted.
I didn't want
to put you in this spot.
I just...
wanted to escape from your mother.
My mom?
You abducted me because of my mom?
Yes.
I wanted to live a good life
with you and you alone.
I only thought of you.
I'm sorry.
Is that all you have to say?
Let's talk after you let her go.
I can explain everything in detail.
Okay?
Why didn't you just die?
You should've just died.
Why did you come back alive?
Even death was something
I couldn't decide on my own.
Let's go home, Yi-gyeong.
We have to meet our baby.
This time,
I want to protect our child.
Wait, Hwal-sung.
- Oh, sorry.
- Be careful.
I don't believe it.
What about me?
Yes.
Let's start over.
Okay?
Yi-gyeong!
It's the police.
Freeze.
Hands in the air.
Hands in the air!
Detective.
It wasn't me.
- Aim higher.
- Aim.
Keep going!
We need backup!
- The whole building is on fire.
- Keep shooting up!
Are you okay, Da-rae?
What about you, Seon?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Su-jong.
What are we going to do now?
I don't know.
Da-rae.
I love you, Da-rae.
Seon, let's go downstairs.
Let's go down. Go, Da-rae.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
She lived, thanks to the man.
BADUK CLUBHOUSE
Over here!
We're here!
Are you all right?
- Get things under control.
- Hey!
We need to go!
The ambulance is on its way!
Ma'am, there's a fire here!
Hey!
Hey, what's going on here?
- Hey, who's the suspect?
- Yes, sir.
Are the reporters here?
- Keep an eye on him.
- Yes, ma'am.
- You're here.
- Hey.
What's going on?
This is driving me insane.
Seon, you still have to get examined
once you get there.
Are you all right?
Yes, but I should go to the hospital.
All right.
About that fire.
A few days ago
a repairman came by and inspected it
but I didn't want to waste money,
so I sent him back.
But he had said
it was clearly compromised.
That's classic Gi Su-jong.
I have something to say to you.
What is it?
Promise me that
you'll never lie again.
I will never lie to you,
even if I'm born again.
There's no such thing as rebirth.
Death is the end of everything.
You should've been good
while you had someone in your life.
You're right.
What the heck?
You're doing this again,
falling asleep while drinking.
Hwal-sung, when are we?
When are we?
We're here now. What do you mean?
Your wife's birthday.
Come quickly.
We still have lots of drinks left.
- What's with him?
- I had a nightmare.
It was terrible.
What was it about?
Well, I don't even know
where to begin.
Anyway, it was an awful dream.
Did your building's value plummet?
No, it wasn't that.
You abducted Yi-gyeong.
You did it to get money
from your mother-in-law.
But...
Were you truly not at fault?
Gi Su-jong.
Wake up.
You're up.
Get a good rest today,
and then you can leave.
- Okay.
- Good.
Thank you.
Don't worry.
Your wife and daughter are fine.
I see.
What time is it?
How long has it been?
It's been about ten hours.
You do not have to do it now
but you must show up
for a questioning.
Many of the victims were deceased.
Deceased?
Min Hwal-sung has died.
Let me ask you one thing.
Why were you all there
at Se-yoon Building last night?
No reason.
We got together for no reason.
I heard Jeon Yi-gyeong
had Jang Dong-chul
abduct your daughter. Is that true?
There's security footage
of them abducting her
at Hyeyun Temple.
No, I think...
I think that's a misunderstanding.
What misunderstanding?
It's because
Jeon Yi-gyeong is like family to us.
There's no problem with us.
Yi-gyeong has woken up.
Gi Su-jong did everything.
My abduction, Oh Dong-ki's case,
and what happened to my mom
were all Gi Su-jong's doing!
Yi-gyeong.
There's evidence you abducted Da-rae.
It's true.
But I wasn't going to do anything.
You abducted a minor!
I know.
And I'll pay the price.
But you have to arrest Gi Su-jong.
I told you that I found the culprit
and it was him!
I need evidence.
It's in my phone...
My phone.
Where's my phone?
Or you can ask Da-rae.
She knows everything. No, wait.
You can ask Hwal-sung.
He'll tell you everything.
What did your husband say?
Gi Su-jong said he killed my husband.
But he suddenly showed up
at Se-yoon Building.
He showed up,
saying everything was his fault
and asking for forgiveness.
If you can ask him,
he'll tell you everything.
Hold on.
Are you saying
Gi Su-jong killed your husband
but he showed up at Se-yoon Building?
Yes.
Well...
He had died.
I saw it with my own two eyes.
But he came to save me.
Min Hwal-sung fell
from the rooftop, right?
Yes, sir.
Why?
Is there a problem?
Your husband has passed away.
What do you mean?
I just told you.
He came to Se-yoon Building.
I thought he had died,
but he came back to save me!
It's...
We should stop here today.
So Yi-gyeong did get
Jang Dong-chul of Loan Heaven
to abduct Da-rae.
Are you done examining
the footage from Hyeyun Temple?
We're almost done.
Dig into what's going on
between Jang Dong-chul and her.
And get Mr. Gi's daughter
to testify as well.
What about Gi Su-jong?
Hey.
What about Mr. Gi?
Are you going to dig with no proof?
Enough is enough.
Goodness.
- Hello?
- Hey, Su-jong.
Da-rae has been called in
as a witness.
Yi-gyeong must've mentioned her.
Then we should talk to her
and make her understand.
Is this right?
We must tell the same story
to avoid suspicion
and Yi-gyeong will be freed as well.
Da-rae's out of her room. Bye.
Bye.
Da-rae.
I got a call from the police station.
They want you to testify
as a witness.
(When are you going?)
It's not me.
It's you, Da-rae.
Will you be okay?
If it's too hard for you
then you don't have to do it.
(No, it's all right.
It's something I have to do.)
(I must do it for Yi-gyeong.)
All right.
Let's eat for now.
Eat up.
RECENTS
My name is Kim Seon.
I admit to helping
my husband, Gi Su-jong
by aiding and abetting
Jeon Yi-gyeong's kidnapping
and obstructing
the police investigation.
Jeon Yi-gyeong's abduction
was planned and carried out
by Min Hwal-sung and me.
WOULD YOU LIKE
TO MOVE THE VIDEO TO TRASH?
SEND TO TRASH
OFFICIAL DUTY
- Hello.
Hello.
ARCHAEOLOGICAL EXCAVATION TEAM
This is killing me.
Anyway, why are things
moving so slowly at this site?
It's because you're way too detailed.
It's true. I'm quite exquisite.
- Goodness.
- Hey, man.
Why did you leave this out here?
- What if it got wet in the rain?
- I left it there?
Why did you leave
the garden hoe here?
What's this?
Call the police! It's a human hand!
Phone. Your phone. Now!
Call the police now!
- What's wrong?
- What's going on?
There's a hand!
It's a human hand.
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
Jang Hee-ju was found dead.
You were with her at her office
all through the night.
Let's make 30 billion won.
We can easily obtain Pyeongbukgwan
without that woman.
I'm here to meet Yi-gyeong
and it looks like those jerks
will do something to her as well.
Wait, what about Gyun?
Did she kill him?
And you knew that?
It worked.
How would you feel
if your friend betrays you, sir?
Don't you think I can just kill them?
Subtitles by Eunsook Youn
and Jennifer Lim