It's so fine.
You like it, dude?
What?
Is it good?
Huh?
Oh!
He's crying.
BLOODHOUNDS 2
He had his annual physical
at our clinic one month ago.
We compared that data to today.
His liver function
is now 30 times worse than before.
-That's horrible.
-Indeed. He's in bad shape.
It's not just because of drinking.
In my medical opinion,
there's a possibility
he might have some drugs in his blood.
Drugs? What type?
We won't know
until the lab results come in.
There's one thing we can do.
Get a sample of the exact beverage
Min-beom was consuming.
Do you know
how long it will take him to recover?
I'm not sure.
He may not recover at all from this.
Worst-case scenario,
he'll need to get a liver transplant.
WILL WEE EVR MEET?
HOW ARE THE BOYS?
DU-YEONG, IT'S BEEN A WHILE
SINCE WE LAST TALKED
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN TO THE BOYS?
THEY'RE OKAY FOR NOW
LET ME KNOW RIGHT AWAY
IF ANYTHING HAPPENS
-Mr. Min, how are you.
-Oh, you're here.
How's Mr. Hong doing right now?
-His situation is not very good.
-Oh, that's awful.
-I'm praying for a quick recovery.
-That's much appreciated.
-Let's go inside.
-Sure.
Sh!
-Do you know her?
-I've never seen her in my life.
Oh my God.
-Uh…
-You don't know her at all?
Like I told you,
I've never seen her before.
-Not now.
-Oh, sure. I'm sorry.
So when she kissed me,
this weird kind of plastic film
came right out of her mouth. So strange.
And then I suddenly got dizzy
and my legs gave out. Then I fell down.
After that, the bitch dropped this liquid
right here in my mouth.
Then she asked me some questions.
Like what?
You know, I… I can't recall.
So it made you talk without
your ability to control anything, right?
That's it. Just like that.
Oh my.
You're familiar with it?
Oh yeah. So this drug
can make the user tell the truth.
This drug is very powerful.
It lowers inhibitions and forces you
to say whatever is on your mind.
You know what else?
I heard that some people use it
to get information from dates.
-It must be illegal then?
-Yeah, that's right.
So would it be used
for getting confessions?
I think so.
Shit.
She's a smart one.
Did Min-beom schedule in advance?
He did. Reserved it last week.
By who?
His assistant.
Go to the hospital and get a blood test.
Then call me when you have the results.
I'll get a blood test right away.
Great. We need to have a talk.
Only Secretary Cho and him knew
that Min-beom was coming here.
That said, I'm not convinced he did it.
So, Gun-woo,
you and I will go see Mr. Cho, okay?
Gwang-mu, see what you can learn
about this woman.
I'd guess she'd be active
in areas where younger folks hang out.
-That's more your scene than mine.
-Yeah, okay.
-She's a professional. So watch out.
-Mr. Min, I'm a pro as well.
-One thing, sir.
-Hmm?
Would you mind if I tag along?
Why?
If Woo-jin goes with Mr. Moon,
I'm worried he'll use his hand.
-Gwang-mu, does that work for you?
-Sure, Gun-woo can tag along!
Okay then. Let's go.
-Yeah guys, let's move.
-Yeah.
Mr. Min?
I think this is the president's jacket.
-You ready for this?
-Yes.
Well I'm glad you're ready.
-Sir.
-Yeah?
You can count on me.
I'm much safer now!
Looks like there are benefits
of hanging out with a champion. Hmm?
Oh.
Well, I guess now it's our time.
NO CALLER ID
You can answer it,
but you can't speak first.
How's the president?
Hey.
What did you put in his drink?
You're a fucking idiot.
You still don't get it, do you?
Want to know what else will happen
if you don't fight me?
I will remove your coach's hand.
I'll rip out your mom's tongue
and whore her out in Southeast Asia.
Oh fuck.
The president's cousin… I'll wash
that pig's face with hydrochloric acid.
Go on, make me your enemy.
Then I'll make every poor bastard
who needs money your enemy.
That cop who got stabbed to death
right in front of you? Who did that?
Just a coworker at his police station
who we paid 50 million won.
Listen to me carefully.
Everyone in this, world,
and I mean everyone, has a price.
You'll get all the money I discussed.
Just fight me one time.
Shit.
KIM GUN-WOO
So that's it, you fucker.
In a few days,
your coach's hand will be the first to go.
Then your mother.
Fun.
I know his type.
These people are horrible fucking vampires
who suck the blood from others
and would even sell off their organs.
If you want to take down a beast,
then you need to be
a bigger, stronger beast.
If you show the tiniest bit of weakness,
those bastards will attack.
Get what I'm saying?
What should I do?
You want to beat the beast?
Be ready to do anything.
Like I told you, you must
make your heart as tough as steel.
When your heart is steel,
then your fist is the sharpest knife.
Then stab him.
You have to take them down.
Otherwise…
your family goes down.
Hmm.
Hello. How are you?
Won-yeong,
Min-beom was attacked. He's badly hurt.
Let's talk.
Have a reservation?
-We're here to see the owner.
-Okay, just a minute.
-Party of two coming in. Go in, gentlemen.
-Thanks.
Ah! Let's go, bitches!
You're out of your mind.
I'm staying right here.
Oh my! Daddy!
-Hi, Daddy!
-Oh!
Well, look who came
to show his gorgeous face.
Wait, are you wearing
your mother's necklace?
You like? It's super pretty.
-Yeah.
-What's up, gorgeous?
Ah, well, I'm looking for someone.
What's your type?
It's a woman.
You've come to the wrong place.
What? Oh no. I'll pass, but thanks anyway.
Because you know
a lot of people around here.
How about, if I find her,
can you lower my interest just a smidge?
You're crafty.
-Oh, Daddy.
-Yeah, but can you handle it?
Oh, you know I can.
Who's the lucky girl?
Can we have privacy?
Come, come.
-Oh, hey, Gun-woo.
-Yes?
-Don't go anywhere alone.
-Yes.
You know what's strange?
When I said that Min-beom was injured,
you didn't even ask how bad it was.
So why did you sell Min-beom out
to those guys?
He took care of you.
He even set up your university scholarship
with the Iil Group Foundation. Full ride.
Min-beom handled every decision.
He handpicked you as his assistant.
He's done everything
for you, Won-yeong. Right?
And you turn on him. For what? More money?
Hey!
Look. He's fucked up right now.
He's unable to even open his eyes.
He took care of you,
and you stab him in the back.
Hey, Cho Won-yeong!
Are you really this much of a lowlife?
-Not now!
-Don't speak to him like that! Stop it!
-Get back in your room!
-You didn't do anything wrong!
Look at this.
Those bastards did this with a knife.
Enough. Go back now.
Wait.
Tell me what happened.
I need the truth now. Yeah?
I'll handle it.
It's okay.
I got it.
Just tell me everything.
So who is she?
Ew. The resolution is terrible,
and her look's so basic.
Hey. Can you try a little harder for me?
No, it's impossible.
Maybe if you lower the interest for me?
Give me something good before you start
bargaining with me, idiot.
And give me something to go on.
I have no clues.
Oh yeah!
What's that drug that makes people say
whatever's on their mind?
Oh, Truth Game?
That's the name of it?
Yeah, Truth Game.
This girl gave the waiter something,
and I think it was that drug.
Hmm. Oh my. You'll definitely
have to lower the interest now.
Ah, so there is info
in that head of yours!
I know a guy who imports it
into the country, and distributes it too.
Okay. So where's that punk now?
-Uh, will you lower your rate by 5%?
-No way. You're a thief.
-Come on, Daddy, do it one time for me.
-Uh-uh.
-Just one time, for me?
-Let go of me.
-Stop it right now!
-Please? Just this one time.
Fine, 5%. Good enough?
Oh!
-So make the call.
-Yeah.
-Give me a minute, sir.
-He's a good friend, you see.
Yes.
-No, really.
-Yes.
I was on my way home, after
buying some beer at the convenience store.
I was closing the door,
but a hand suddenly came in.
Mm-hmm.
Those bastards kicked me
in the stomach.
And they tied me to a chair.
They said if I screamed…
…they would melt off my face
with hydrochloric acid.
Wow.
-Do you remember what they--
-Uh, Mr. Min?
Do you mind if I tell you
the rest of what happened?
Is it okay if my sister leaves?
I appreciate it.
You can go inside.
So what happened with your sister's hand?
First, they applied an ointment.
Then they took a knife and cut her.
It was an anesthetic cream.
She didn't feel it.
So what did they look like?
There were three of them.
So the largest of the guys
had big eyes with these heavy eyelids.
He was strong.
The second guy did almost all the talking.
His eyebrows were thick.
He was really good
at playing a psychological game.
Go on.
The guy who cut my sister's hand
was very skinny.
He also had a receding hairline.
Something odd with his eyes.
Like he was high or something.
Okay. Did they seem close?
They weren't speaking with each other
very much.
But they worked together like a team.
Good.
They asked me if you
were the president's relative.
It's clear they researched me.
Also, uh…
It's okay. Yeah?
I said something I shouldn't have.
I mentioned where Gun-woo and Woo-jin are.
-Should we alert them now?
-No, no, no.
If they move first,
we'll expose Won-yeong.
We need to protect him
for a number of reasons.
I'll have more guards assigned.
This could be helpful.
If they arrive there,
we'll stop those assholes.
The guys in Team 3 are all elite.
I can't go to the police.
-They said they'd kill my family.
-Don't sweat it.
Listen to me.
More undercover cops will be assigned.
For both your sister and this house.
Tell her to act normally.
This is the safest approach.
I'm so sorry.
If they did that to my family,
I'd respond just how you did.
It's not your fault, okay?
They are doing this to your family.
How's my boss?
Will he survive?
So you do care?
I'm sorry.
LEE WOO-JEONG
CLASS 39
Pray for him, okay?
Hello, Woo-jeong.
He's here!
Oh.
What's wrong?
You're Kim Gun-woo, right?
Yes.
Holy shit! I'm a big fan.
You and I… met once, remember?
After the Hong Jong-min fight.
After you crushed him. Then you gave me
your autograph, right here!
TO JANG JUN
THANK YOU, KIM GUN-WOO
Oh! Sure. Yes, I remember you.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah. That was a great time!
-Oh sure. Well, hello again.
It's so nice to meet you.
For sure. It's such an honor.
Wow.
Wow, I can't believe this!
Well, I'm thrilled for you.
So, um… So how may I help you today?
So Kim Gun-woo is seeking
this woman here.
Do you know her? Have you seen her?
For sure. It's Gi-na. We're super tight.
We have a thing going on.
Did you sell this lady
Truth Game recently?
Yeah. For sure.
Where could she be right now?
Ah, yeah. Have a good evening.
Yes, Mr. Min? It's Moon Gwang-mu.
Any updates?
Yes, I found her! Her name is Gi-na.
I'm heading out to the gambling den now
where she works.
You're serious? You're fantastic.
Well, you believed in me sir, so I really
didn't want to disappoint you, you know.
So let's talk later. Maybe you can help me
with this investigation.
It'd be my honor.
You know, I've actually
always dreamed of being a detective.
Let's meet up to discuss
strategy before making our move together.
Sure, of course. Where should we meet?
Uh, the hotel
where Gun-woo and Woo-jin are staying.
One of my guys has found a lead
off of the picture you sent me.
Oh, wow.
Okay, fine, I'll see you soon.
I'm on my way.
Great. See you later.
Oh. Perfect timing.
Everyone, this is
my colleague, Lee Woo-jeong.
-Hello.
-New investigator on my team.
Hello, everyone. It's a pleasure.
Hmm. At school, we were
in the Green Pine Tree Club together.
It's a group founded by seniors.
We are encouraged to stay evergreen
like pine trees,
and uphold justice and equality
in our society.
It's a secret club which consists
of the best students from each class.
And we met there.
You two haven't met? This is Tae-yeong.
She was in our Cyber Investigation Unit.
It's my pleasure.
I finally get to meet
the Cyber Investigation Unit star.
What an honor.
I know very little about boxing,
but I enjoy watching your matches.
I've been a fan since the Rookie
of the Year Tournament during COVID-19.
Uh, that's very kind of you.
-I'm Moon Gwang-mu. It's a real honor.
-Oh, the honor is mine.
I've never met a top student before.
Uh, I'm a top student.
Well, then it's my second time.
Oh.
Can you tell me your name please?
Hong Woo-jin. Yeah.
Aha.
I also competed in that match,
Rookie of the Year tournament.
Oh, forgive me, I didn't… Uh…
Uh…
So, Woo-jeong,
the character "Woo," does it mean "help?"
My character "Woo" means "outstanding."
The "Woo" character, for me,
it means "help," you see.
I propose we get to know each other
so we can help each other out.
Yeah. I'm gonna make sure
to greet you first next time.
Wait. In your name,
does "Woo" mean "help" as well?
-No, it means "friend."
-Ah.
Oh, I think we should make a new club too.
Like you guys.
Three different "Woos" join forces
and fight the enemy,
How about the "Three Woo Club?"
Oh, wow, that's a fantastic idea.
Great, great,
I hope your new club lasts forever,
but I think it's time to get to work now.
-Yes, of course.
-Great.
OCTO ROMA NATURALIA CASE FILE
Let's begin with the investigation report.
The watch in the photo you sent us
is a limited edition model.
In Korea, it's been purchased
by only two people.
One, a pro soccer player
who currently plays in Europe,
and the other,
former Special Forces Officer
Yun Tae-Geom.
Wait. That's the guy.
-Him? You sure?
-Oh yeah. He fought us.
Yun Tae-geom. He was born in 1990.
In 2009, he enlisted as an NCO
in Army Special Warfare Command.
He served with
the 17th Airborne Special Forces.
And his specialty? Explosives.
According to fellow soldiers,
he was highly intelligent,
and excelled at making
improvised explosive devices.
He was dishonorably discharged
in April 2020.
The reason for that is classified.
I'm looking into it.
I researched his family
and personal history.
SPOUSE: HAN EUN-JI, DECEASED
CHILD: YUN MIN-A
He has a young daughter.
-And where is she?
-Lives with her grandmother in Daejeon.
I still haven't figured out
his wife's death.
Where's our former officer now?
He went to Thailand in March last year
and hasn't come back officially.
I think he's here.
With forged identification and a visa.
Okay, everyone, gather around.
Of course.
This is the head.
This is Yun Tae-geom.
Our special forces guy. He's the fixer,
the muscle. You follow me?
Kang In-beom.
Not sure yet
what this bastard's role is in all this.
But according to Mr. Cho…
The voice?
Exactly. That's what I'm thinking.
First, we should go over
what we know for sure.
This here is the junkie doctor.
Maybe this asshole is responsible
for that drug on Min-beom.
The one with the thick eyebrows
works logistics.
Like gathering intel, sizing things up,
and bringing in the hired guys.
He probably handled everything
for Kang In-beom's escape from prison,
making sure everyone had
everything they need.
Don't forget their computer expert.
-So he's number six, right?
-Okay.
Wow, that's a pretty big crew.
Just their monthly salaries are a fortune.
Um, sir, there's something
I wanted to share with you directly.
When were at Golden Slumber before,
I got a call.
-On your phone?
-Yes.
-What did he say?
-He directly threatened him.
If he didn't take part in their league,
everyone around him is in danger.
Did you get his number, by chance?
I guess not.
-He say anything else to you?
-Gun-woo.
The detective who died
right in front of us.
One of his fellow officers sold him out.
He was paid off
with a massive amount of cash.
Wow.
For right now, I want only the people here
to work on this.
-Yeah.
-Okay.
Now, in a way,
this is a way more intelligent,
better-run organization
than when we fought Kim Myeong-gil.
No need to be worried. Justice is with us.
There are quite a few things we need
to do, and they all must be done at once.
Mr. Moon and Gun-woo, find that woman now.
-Okay.
-Yes.
Woo-jeong, check the footage and see where
the guy who stabbed Detective Choi went.
Okay.
Woo-jin, come with me
to meet Yun Tae-geom's mother.
Got it.
Okay. I want you watching the website.
If you learn anything about this asshole,
contact me right away.
This lowlife got money to the police.
I don't know what he did before,
but he's got connections everywhere.
I think… I think he was likely police.
Yes.
And we all must be safe. Bring it in.
Yeah.
-One, two, three.
-Let's go!
Which camera shows the best view
of where he goes next?
-Give me a second.
-Okay.
This one should be the best angle.
I'll give you a sedative.
-It'll definitely help ease your pain.
-No!
I can do this.
I can do this on my own.
It's very possible
that you'll need a liver transplant.
The sedative will help.
I said I can do this on my own!
Keep this up, you'll be in serious danger.
I can do this. I can do this!
Hey.
-Hmm?
-What are you doing?
Woo-jin. You know how much this costs?
Not really sure. Thirty thousand?
Are you serious?
So, how much is it?
This costs about ten times that.
Huh?
It's a limited edition.
There's a waiting list for it.
Oh.
Wait.
Hmm?
Now I know
why you wanted me here with you.
-Why?
-To see Yun Tae-geom's mother.
And then butter her up.
Then we can meet
Yun Tae-geom in person, right?
I'll try. I'll do my best.
Okay. You're overestimating
yourself here, Woo-jin.
You handle the little kid.
I'll handle the mother.
-Uh, of course.
-Good.
Who is it?
-Oh yes, hello there.
-Yes?
Would you mind
if I… speak to you for a few minutes?
Oh.
Okay.
He left us two years ago.
He said he got some job in Thailand.
And he was going to guard
this rich person.
He hasn't been back since.
Does he return for holidays?
No.
Oh.
Min-a must miss her dad so much.
Do you both keep in touch?
No.
Hmm. Wow.
He must miss her a lot.
I couldn't do that.
I have a young daughter like Min-a too.
Yes.
I don't know what that boy is thinking.
I… I don't wanna know.
Mm.
That's a great drawing.
I see that uncle's stuffing his face
with all of Min-a's snacks.
Uh… Uh…
Min-a, listen. How about
we do something else?
What else do you like?
Do you like stickers?
There's plenty of stickers in my room.
Oh yeah! Let's go!
She's so pretty.
Tell me. Why'd he leave the military?
Mina's mom. The hospital.
Those costs weren't covered
by military income.
She was sick?
Mm.
She had cancer.
Pancreatic. It was bad.
Oh.
That's really hard.
Wow, Min-a.
This is a lot of stickers you're using.
Are you positive it's not too many?
Yeah.
I bet you also like to stick these on your
dad too. I'm sure he enjoys that, right?
Last time, I stuck a hundred on his face.
When was that?
This past Monday.
Oh.
Oh, then I bet your dad
bought you that scooter three nights ago.
So it's this past Monday night.
Is that right?
Yeah.
Oh. Having fun with it? Is it cool?
Well, I'm a little scared of it.
How about… if I gave you a private lesson?
Yeah!
Oh yeah!
Here we go.
Hi, Grandma! I'm gonna ride my scooter
with my new friend.
I'll make sure
she rides safely and carefully.
-See you later, Grandma!
-Be safe.
Sure.
Here we go!
So, ma'am…
actually, we know about your son.
Ah, okay, uh… Well…
If you can help me out today,
I can help your son safely return home.
I promise that.
Uh, okay, okay…
So how am I, uh, supposed to help?
It's simple. You just have to call me
when he calls you.
-Okay, show me what's next.
-Sure.
Now zoom in on this camera angle.
-Okay, pause it there, please.
-Yes.
-Ah. Excuse me. Give me a minute.
-Take your time.
Hi, Woo-jeong.
What's up?
I reviewed the CCTV footage
and found the fourth suspect.
Oh yeah?
-Can you text me that picture?
-Yeah, I'll send it now.
And we just talked
to Yun Tae-geom's mother
and we learned that his wife
had pancreatic cancer.
It seems he borrowed cash from loan sharks
for her treatment.
When he couldn't pay the interest,
the sharks caused trouble at his base,
so he was discharged.
Must have been tough.
Yeah, right?
I feel for the guy a little bit.
Give me his number
and I'll see if I'm able to track it.
I think he's using a burner phone.
She says his number changes.
What should we do?
Well, yeah, we could notify the police,
but in all likelihood
there are cops out there
who were bribed by them too.
If we put out a wanted notice,
Yun Tae-geom will disappear.
Ah.
Why don't we leave Yun Tae-geom
and Mr. Cho alone for now.
So we can stay under the radar.
And Yun Tae-geom and I must meet.
He's clearly a tough guy,
but he does this for his family.
It's possible we could
bring him to our side.
Yes, that works for me.
So for now,
send me that bastard's picture.
Sure.
Okay, it's time to see his face.
HONG MIN-BEOM
Oh!
-Hello, sir! How are you?
-Where are you?
Investigating in Daejeon. I'm with Woo-jin
right now. How are you feeling?
It's painful.
But it's getting better.
That's so good to hear.
You know everyone was worried.
Just a few more days.
Then I'm back.
Yes, of course. Take your time.
We'll talk soon.
Yes, yes, for sure.
Oh wait, here it is.
Hmm. So this is what it's like
to be a detective.
Uh, yeah, sort of.
-Uh, Jun.
-Yeah?
Be honest. Is she gonna be here?
She goes to work right around this time.
This is where I dropped her off once.
Oh, look!
Is that her? Yeah, that's her for sure.
Okay. Okay, so you take the elevator
to the seventh floor.
When you get out, you take a left.
Then walk down that long hallway.
Finally, you'll come to a door.
-You'll see a bunch of playing cards--
-What happens there?
Uh, high stakes games
of blackjack, poker, mah-jongg.
A lot of the regular players
are criminals,
so many of them are armed.
Guns, knives, and even axes.
You have to be extremely careful.
Yes. Thank you for your advice.
Let's do this!
Or whatever you say.
Let's do this.
-Ah.
-Mr. Min, we found the girl.
-Her name's Gi-na.
-Great.
She works here, on the seventh floor.
-Great work, you guys.
-Thanks.
Oh right. I had a case once
in this building.
There was a serial killer
hiding here years ago.
So this building was built
back in the '70s.
Things were different then.
See the fire escape?
Oh. So my guess,
she'll either use that stairway,
or take the elevator
directly to the parking lot underground.
So here's the plan.
Two of us flush her out.
One of us watches the fire escape,
and the other covers the garage.
Uh, sir?
Can I join Mr. Moon
going in the main entrance?
Mm.
-You sure?
-Yes.
Then, sir, I'll take the fire escape.
Okay. Everyone, be careful.
Let's, not get hurt.
Okay, guys, bring it in.
-One, two, three…
-Let's do it!
Yeah.
You have gloves?
Ah, shit.
-Yeah?
-I'm President Moon from Dream On Capital.
I'd like to play.
This fucking guy.
What?
Jang Jun mentioned this joint. He said
it's a great place for some gambling.
This is getting on my nerves.
Over here.
Okay.
-I would like more chips, please.
-Hmm?
You keep dealing me the same crappy hand.
First time playing mah-jongg.
Oh, come on!
You're on a cold streak.
I've never seen it this bad.
Last bets, gentlemen.
-These guys are cops!
-Wait, who?
Cops. Let's move!
Hey, Gun-woo, stop her!
She's getting away!
Bastard!
Gun-woo!
Huh?
Shit!
Hey!
Let go of me, asshole!
-Come here, fucker. I got you.
-Wait a minute!
Wait. Listen, I'm not a cop.
I'm not! I'm a small business owner!
You think we give a shit?
[indistinct yelling in distance]
I will kill you!
Gwang-mu!
Hey!
-What? No!
-Sir! Sir!
-No, stop it! No, no, wait!
-It's me. It's me.
-You okay?
-Yeah. I'm fine.
Are you sure you're okay?
Oh yeah. As long as I'm with you,
I'll live, okay?
She must be close. Let's go.
-Right.
-Okay.
Shit.
Ah, shit.
-You coming?
-You go ahead.
Let's go quietly.
[Gi-na sighs]
[knife slices]
Put the knife down. Let's go.
Ah, shit.
Someone help! He's attacking--
[music fades]
-[sighs]
-[cell phone buzzing]
Yes, hello?
-Tae-yeong, hey.
-Yes?
I took her phone from her. What's next?
What's the model?
It's an iPhone 14 or 15. Not sure.
iPhone cameras can be opened
without a password.
I'm going to send you a message
with a QR code.
Use her phone to scan it.
Okay.
[tense music playing]
Got it. Hang on a minute.
GI-NA
MONEY
[sighs]
HOW MUCH
HOW MUCH?
MANJI
GROUP CHAT? WHY NOT DM ME?
Whoa!
IS THE JOB JUICY?
YOUR PRICE PLUS BONUS
LEAVING IT TO YOU
JUST SPIKE A DRINK
USE MY OWN DRUG?
-LET'S TALK IN PERSON.
-WHERE?
I'LL CALL YOU. MEET ME THERE
OKAY
Oh, shit.
I found this, sir.
Yeah?
She's the one
who spiked President Hong's drink.
She met with the guy
who arranged the job today.
Where?
The Entra Hotel.
There's a bar on the second floor.
At 11:00 this morning.
Tae-yeong, call the hotel
and see if Yun Tae-geom is booked there.
Yes, sir.
Good evening, Entra Hotel lobby.
This is Kang Tae-yeong,
Cyber Unit, Seoul Metro Police.
Can you provide the room number
for Yun Tae-geom, please?
So be aware that if you do not cooperate,
you may be charged
with obstruction of justice.
He's staying in the penthouse
as a long-term guest.
Thanks for your cooperation.
HE'S A LONG-TERM GUEST IN THE PENTHOUSE
-It's him. We got him.
-Oh!
Now take this young lady
and go somewhere safe.
-Yes, of course.
-I'll stick with Mr. Moon right now
-Sure.
-I'll stay with you, sir.
Let's go.
[music fades]
[tense music playing]
[telephone ringing]
You were right. Bringing a mainstream
fighter into IKFC was a huge success.
So you see the profit.
We made more money
than we have ever made previously.
I told you
it was gonna be immensely helpful.
Okay. So now, we will bring in another
mainstream fighter. His name is Gun-woo.
He just destroyed Adik and is the current
super-middleweight champion of the world,
and we convinced him to join our IKFC37.
Our numbers will be bigger than ever.
Hey.
He's an infighter.
There will be a lot of blood.
They're gonna love it.
And we will market Gun-woo
to Korea, Japan, Taiwan, Thailand.
All our Asian markets.
The bets will be higher than ever.
All because he's an Asian fighter
who they can cheer for.
Look, gentlemen. Like I mentioned before,
I'm still divided between your IKFC…
Let's be honest, needs a major overhaul.
…and an established moneymaking
Dutch soccer gambling site empire,
called Hatricks.
But…
[sighs]
…if you continue to make steady profits,
I guess I can pour in
up to 400 million dollars
for 51% of the shares
of your little up-and-coming startup.
Sound good?
Okay, we will continue
to make arrangements.
Great. Ciao.
Hold on. You said he'd buy it.
Did that fucking sound
like he was interested?
Oh, he's only bluffing.
As long as we land Gun-woo, we'll be fine.
You better be right, you motherfucker.
[telephone ringing]
-What?
-This is the front desk.
Man-bae mentioned that I should call
if anything suspicious happened.
Well, the police
just called the front desk.
[phone clatters]
-[dramatic music playing]
-[sirens wailing]
SPECIAL OPERATIONS UNIT
We'll take over from here. Stay inside.
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
Clear.
All clear.
[music fades]
[sighs]
Get out!
[cell phone buzzes]
[car alarms blaring in distance]
[dramatic music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[Gun-woo gasping]
Somebody help!
NO CALLER ID
[somber music playing]
This is your fault.
How's that feel?
-[indistinct chatter]
-[breathes deeply]
I told you this would happen.
I said if only you'd fight me
just one time… Just once, you asshole!
But you don't listen.
Your coach's hand will be next.
What do you say?
[exhales]
Huh? What do you say?
[suspenseful music playing]
Where do I meet you?
That's right. That's the right attitude.
Wait for my next call.
[music swells]
[music fades]
[dramatic music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[music stops]