=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 25=
Yan Zhang, it was you.
Actually,
I was never going to tell.
One day,
Yan Ke,
you too will die
in the hands of the one you love.
Bai Sanxing.
Did I tell you to kill him?
Bai Sanxing is not yours
to deal with.
Yan Zhang, Vice Lord of Xuling Temple,
harmed spirits and forged puppets,
bringing ruin to the Void,
and trespassed into the Prison,
colluding with felon Bai Sanxing
to plot against Her Grace.
After investigation,
the evidence is conclusive.
The chief culprit, Yan Zhang,
has been annihilated by Her Grace.
Bai Sanxing has also been seized.
From this day on,
search all of the Void,
and hunt down Yan's accomplices.
Wipe out the remaining puppets
as soon as possible.
Any spirits who stir up trouble
must also be punished by the law.
Yes, Your Grace.
Your Grace,
how will you deal with Bai Sanxing?
He swallowed so many brothers
in my temple.
He must die for this.
Her Grace has a plan.
But...
If there's nothing else,
you may leave for now.
Yes.
Go on, go on. Move.
Who knew Yan Zhang was so cruel?
Indeed.
Your Grace, I seek audience.
Enter.
Yan,
what brings you to me?
Simu,
Yan's rebellion is no small matter.
She could never
have done it alone.
Though Jiang Ai worked with us
in the ambush on Bai Sanxing,
she still has ties to Bai Sanxing.
Besides,
her Vice Lord plotted against you.
Could she truly know nothing of it?
If you suspect Jiang Ai,
go find proof.
If you can find proof,
I will judge it fairly.
Pity, though, Yan Zhang
has met annihilation.
Otherwise,
I could have learned much more.
The situation was urgent then.
In my haste, I killed her.
It's okay.
For 300 years,
those who sought to kill me
have been many.
I'm used to it.
Luckily, by my side
are you and Jiang Ai.
Otherwise,
we wouldn't have taken them so easily.
Thanks to your sound planning, Simu.
I only followed the plan.
There's one more thing.
How will you deal with Bai Sanxing?
Even the Prison
could not destroy him in 300 years.
I've found another place
to hold him.
But he's stirred rebellion
time and again.
We must root him out.
You need not remind me of that.
The chaos is not yet settled.
Jiang Ai is badly hurt and bedridden.
You must have a lot to deal with.
Go attend to it first.
Yes.
Your Grace,
the Left Hand is stable now.
She still needs time to recover.
Your Grace.
How are you?
My Vice Lord tried to kill you.
I failed to see it
and control her.
Please punish me.
Rather than that,
I'm more curious
about why you saved Bai Sanxing.
Back then, Bai Sanxing
locked me up and controlled me
like a caged possession.
I was never one
to be manipulated.
I hated him to the bone.
For these 300 years,
every time I thought of him,
I wished I could
hack him to pieces
and be done with him for good.
But at that very moment,
I just couldn't stand by and watch him
die before my very eyes.
Deep down, you still care for him.
You just will not admit it.
Do not dwell on it.
You've been badly hurt.
Get some proper rest.
Your Grace,
how
is he now?
Still alive.
Grand Ancestor.
Grand Ancestor, long time no see.
I thought you had forgotten me.
In a few days,
I will go to Nandu.
Grand Ancestor,
you are coming to Nandu?
(Chamber of Buddha's Grace)
We are going to visit
my mother.
She likes it quiet.
Who is it?
Xu.
Mother,
I'm back.
You had a tiring journey yesterday.
I only...
Sit down.
Go on, sit.
This is...
I took him in on the battlefield
as my brother.
He's Xue Chenying.
He lost his parents.
His sister earned great merit in battle.
I promised her I'd look after him.
Chenying,
greet Mother.
Greetings, Mrs. Duan.
Child,
no need for such a grand bow.
That you came here
is fate in itself.
The Buddha is merciful.
This place
will be your home.
Here, have some pastries.
Thank you.
Chenying,
go on, eat.
Mother, whenever you see me,
you're always so reserved.
Jingyuan may start to suspect
there is discord between us.
I only feel
that all these years,
I've done nothing for you.
After all, when you needed me most,
I could not stay by your side.
You're overthinking it.
As for this matter,
I've never blamed you.
That's exactly why
I feel even worse inside.
I can't face you.
Perhaps my parents
had something
they truly sought.
Even blood kin,
in their eyes,
meant very little.
I do not think that is right,
yet I understand them.
If only Xiaoxiao
were here now.
Why?
Because she'd surely comfort you,
and ease your sorrow.
It is all right.
I am not too upset.
But I still hope for her
to come here,
Simu.
Why must we come here?
Simu,
you grew up in the Mortal World.
You have always liked
its bustling liveliness,
instead of the cold silence of the Void.
If you like,
we can make the Void
vivid and lively
like the Mortal World.
Yan,
you're just trying to cheer me up.
The Void is at the bottom of the sea,
without daylight.
How could it ever be lively?
If you want,
I will do everything I can
to make it happen.
Simu,
I have a gift for you.
I know
that you never wanted to be
the Sovereign of Spirits,
bound by the Void's endless affairs.
I will guard the Void for you.
Those who stand above all
often walk alone.
But you have me.
I'll always stay by your side.
I've bound my vital gate
to this hairpin.
Now, I give it to you.
This is my heart's vow.
If you are willing,
I will be yours forever.
I'll forever love you,
be your friend,
your lover,
and your Yan.
Simu.
I'm sorry, Yan.
I can't say yes.
You're the partner I trust most.
That is all.
Simu, you...
Are you truly turning me down?
If you don't want it now,
that's all right.
I can keep it for you.
Yan,
Jiang Ai's wound is nearly healed.
She can resume duty tomorrow.
I'll leave the Void's daily affairs
to you both.
I need to go to Nandu.
Simu,
I don't want you to go.
Whatever it is, I'll go for you.
Yan Ke,
you have overstepped.
Overstepped?
I kept too strictly
to the proper code between us,
so you neglected me.
I never neglected you.
You are my most trusted Right Hand.
When I am away,
the Void relies on you and Jiang Ai.
As for what you said just now,
I will pretend I never heard it.
Greetings, Grand Ancestor.
Grand Ancestor.
To welcome me,
you even dressed up.
Grand Ancestor,
may I
shake your hand just once?
It is not as if we have never met.
No need to be so formal.
That was in my childhood.
I only remember
you holding me back then.
It still feels the same.
You've rarely had the chance
to come to Nandu.
Would you like
to go check on Duan Xu?
I have no time.
General Duan hasn't been
having an easy time lately.
I heard his family is choosing
a bride for him these days.
Perhaps before long,
he will be married.
What is that to me?
Grand Ancestor,
if he truly takes a wife,
you will lose him.
Doesn't this sadden you?
Duan Xu is a mortal.
Starting a family
is the most natural thing for him.
Why should I feel sad?
Isn't he your spell bearer?
Don't you find it a pity?
If he's still willing
to trade his senses with me,
the arrangement between us
will continue as before.
What is there to regret?
- But…
- Enough.
I came for serious matters.
Spare me nonsense.
Last time, you asked me
to make a magical artifact.
I was...
It is late. You should sleep now.
Grand Ancestor is here tonight.
We're having a meeting.
Leave it to tomorrow.
(Ziji, Hejia Fengyi's maid)
Considering your health,
you should be asleep now.
Your Grand Ancestor
also wishes you a longer life.
It's all right.
Let's talk tomorrow.
Don't you wish to know
which young ladies the Duan clan chose?
I do not.
Your Grace, I'll arrange your rest.
Please come with me.
Fragrance pouch! Trinkets!
Xu,
I don't think
the girls Father picked for you
are very pretty.
You're too brilliant.
How about this?
You stroll the streets,
seeking romance.
What do you say?
Stop talking nonsense.
How is that nonsense?
Fang Xianye
is only good at studying.
It's nothing special.
But you can write essays
to steady the realm
and fight on the battlefield.
How about I
seek a fine match
for you today?
What do you think?
What kind of lady do you like?
I like...
I like
a lady not found in this world.
Fine.
Then I'll go make a wish.
I'll wish for Goddess Chang'e
to come down and find you.
All right.
With your sincere heart,
your prayer may come true.
Xu, be serious, will you?
(Lotusborn Pavilion)
Xu,
you're really not coming in with me?
Go in by yourself.
All right then.
Everyone, please wait a moment.
The Prophet will soon arrive
to burn prayer paper for you all
and present blessed flowers.
This is
the soul candle from the Prison.
Grand Ancestor,
you came for this matter?
That's right.
Could the magical artifact
you asked for…
300 years have passed.
It's time to end this.
Only those in the Mortal World
can grasp its affairs.
♪Touched memories linger like shadows♪
(Lotusborn Pavilion)
♪If I could softly call you like this♪
♪As gentle as a fleeting embrace♪
So, this is what mortals call
the bustle of mortal life.
It really is a mix of scents.
I can smell everything.
Foxy,
just let me have a taste.
♪A lifetime is given
for a name to be remembered♪
♪There are passions and pains♪
♪Hope we'll experience them together♪
♪Before we forget or grow apart♪
Simu.
What are you doing?
♪Grows dim and fades away♪
♪What would come of it?♪
Sorry
for my rudeness.
♪I'll come near and run to you♪
♪To heal the deepest wounds♪
♪Miracles, eternity, and radiance♪
♪Worth more than any barren land♪
♪I might as well
spend the rest of my life♪
♪Walking with you through eternity♪
It's the smell of rain.
Rain carries the scent of the sky
and draws out the earth's scent
and the vitality
of all living things.
♪I'd bear your feelings♪
How wonderful.
♪I'm blessed to have met you♪
♪Then I won't let you go♪
♪I wish I could be a firework♪
♪To burn out for the moment you turn♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪