LOVE NEXT DOOR
Ah! The weather is so lovely!
Yes, it's a good day to go hiking.
Take off your sunglasses
before you fall on your face.
Okay.
- Hey, In-sook.
- Yeah?
Your skin looks flawless today.
- You think so? Oh!
- Yes.
I guess my Botox injections
are finally working their magic.
Wait, you had Botox? Where?
- On my frown lines, my smile lines…
- And?
and pretty much everywhere.
- I don't approve of it.
- Why not?
It just seems too artificial to me.
What's most beautiful
is getting old naturally.
Says the woman who uses
the most expensive cosmetics.
I'm just respecting my skin.
Sure, since our country
is all about respect.
- Hey, Jae-sook.
- Yes?
Did you do something to your face too?
You're glowing.
I did a prune juice cleanse yesterday.
I guess it was effective, though.
- It was.
- My goodness.
I can't control my sphincter.
What did you eat yesterday?
- Prune juice.
- Prune juice!
I can relate.
I was looking at myself in the mirror
and saw that my buttocks
looked like squashed tofu.
They used to look like peaches, you know?
- They were.
- I'm so upset.
That's why we have to work out at our age.
That's why we're going hiking, right?
I'm not talking about hiking.
- What then?
- Squeeze and release.
- I can't do it well.
- What are you doing?
Kegel exercises.
- I'm off.
- Kegel exercises.
- Squeeze and release.
- The air is so clean.
Oh, no!
Hey!
That smells!
Hey, wait for me!
Wait up!
Hey!
Don't come near me!
My goodness. I can't believe you.
Oh my, Mi-sook.
Did you buy a new hiking outfit?
- Wow.
The color is so pretty!
Yes, I guess my taste changed with age.
I love red clothes now.
It's not a matter of taste but science.
As we age,
changes in the retinal microvasculature
make it harder for us to perceive
colors with short wavelengths like blue,
as opposed to colors with long wavelengths
such as the color red.
It must be nice to be so knowledgeable.
This is made out of functional fabric.
You know "Core-Tex"?
You mean "Gore-Tex," right?
Not "Core-Tex."
That's right.
It was just a slip of the tongue.
My daughter sent it to me from the U.S.
It's really expensive.
- It looks expensive.
- It really does.
Seok-ryu is a wonderful daughter.
She's right.
Mm-hm.
I don't feel comfortable
receiving gifts that my son bought
with his hard-earned money.
As if he ever gave you anything.
I don't place much value
on such material things.
The fact that my son, Seung-hyo, exists
is a gift in itself.
Are you saying my daughter isn't?
I didn't want to mention it
to avoid bragging,
but Seung-hyo
recently met with the president.
He designed a library that won an award
at an architecture competition,
so the president personally came to visit
and praised it as a superb model
of a public facility.
Seung-hyo is so impressive.
Of course.
Listen, guys.
Do you know who the second richest person
in the world is?
- I do. It's Jaden Becker.
- Right.
The CEO of Greip?
Not everyone in the world will know
who the president of South Korea is,
but everyone knows Jaden Becker.
Every Friday night,
he and Seok-ryu
shoot the breeze over some beer.
It's all because she works in
the most prestigious company in the world
after graduating from a top university
in the U.S.
As you know, Seung-hyo was at the top
of his class at Hanguk University.
Seok-ryu not only graduated early
but also got offers
from all the top companies.
Greip didn't pick Seok-ryu.
She was the one who chose them.
Seung-hyo helped design
the New York Art Center,
which won an international
architecture award.
He was the first Korean to do so!
Seok-ryu is the best employee
in that global company full of geniuses!
You wouldn't believe
how much she earns just in incentives!
You have to remember
that Seung-hyo
was on the national swim team too.
It's not easy for people
to excel in multiple areas,
but my son does exactly that.
Hey, Seok-ryu is a gift from heaven.
You know what I dreamed about
when I became pregnant with her?
- I was--
- You were in a rainbow-colored paradise
- and found a huge tree there.
- Yes.
You were entranced by it
and saw a juicy pomegranate.
So you picked it
and got pregnant with Seok-ryu.
- I memorized it all.
- Thanks.
That sounds like some fairytale.
As for Seung-hyo--
As for Seung-hyo,
you got assigned to work in France
without knowing you were pregnant.
And you dreamed about a blue dragon
rising out of the Seine.
You remember all that?
That's some extravagant founding myth
you have there.
- Let me tell you…
- Unbelievable.
Those two won't stop
talking about the same things.
It's driving me crazy.
They just want to brag
about their successful children.
Who do you think will win today?
- Hye-sook.
- Why her?
Because she's a diplomat
and can be persuasive?
No, because Seung-hyo
is receiving another award today.
CHOI SEUNG-HYO
Seung-hyo!
Oh. It's you, sir.
You're here.
I thought only top celebrities
got to come to parties like this.
Seung-hyo is such a star!
Where is he?
Seung-hyo? I don't know.
What?
Hmm?
CHOI SEUNG-HYO
CEO, REGISTERED ARCHITECT
You want to design a memorial park?
Yes.
But why did you ask me to see me?
I have visited
many funeral homes for research,
but I don't think I've interviewed
any of the workers.
I heard that you've worked
as a funeral director for 20 years.
Has it been that long?
In all my years doing this job,
I've never had anyone
ask to interview me before.
I see.
I want to do a good job.
A proper job
with sincerity.
I don't know how much help I'd be.
Just tell me what you honestly felt
while working on this job.
To tell you the truth,
my mother passed away not long ago.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Everyone has to go through it
sooner or later.
But it was a comfort to me
that I could send her off beautifully
with my own two hands.
I'm sure your mother was glad to know
that her daughter
was there to see her off.
I agree.
That is why
I want people to visit
with a sense of gladness as well.
Memorial parks don't always have to be
so solemn and sad.
The people resting here were once alive.
They are all beloved friends
and family members.
What if we build
a Shelter for Memories in the lobby?
It would look like
a small library or a café.
We'd fill it up with things
that the departed used to love,
like books and music.
So the people who are visiting
their loved ones can reminisce.
Of course they'd be sad,
but I want their tears to be
interspersed with warm smiles too.
I love it.
How did you come up with such an idea?
I'm sorry.
I have to take this.
Hello.
I can't really talk right now, Myung-woo.
Where the heck are you?
The awards ceremony is starting soon!
I'll be right there.
Through a design that harmonizes
with the environment…
Aw, it's almost Seung-hyo's turn
to go up on stage.
Did he say he'll make it in time?
What are you doing?
I mean, I'm the co-CEO
of Architectural Firm Atelier In,
so I should accept the award in his stead.
Next, we will announce
the winner of the Creative Award.
Oh, no.
The Creative Award
for the 2024 Magazine Awards
- goes to…
- No.
architect and co-CEO
of the architectural firm, Atelier In,
Choi Seung-hyo.
- I'll be back.
- Wait, no.
- What?
- Hey, Myung-woo.
- Seung-hyo!
- I'm not late, right?
- Right.
Ah, look who's finally here.
The star got here just in time.
With a face like that,
he has to be a star.
MAGAZINE DESIGN AWARDS
CREATIVE AWARD
Let's hear Mr. Choi Seung-hyo's
acceptance speech.
Thank you.
I told him to prepare
an acceptance speech beforehand.
He should've spoken longer
for the cameras to capture his beauty
from all angles.
Hey! Our name!
You forgot to mention our name!
I'm from the architectural firm,
Atelier In.
Please give him a round of applause.
Yahoo!
Yelling "yahoo" at the top
of a mountain is so old-fashioned.
Who cares if it's old-fashioned?
I'm respecting the mountain.
You'll get reported to the police.
Who's going to report me? You?
Those two are still going at it.
They're wasting energy
fighting and making up all the time.
I know, right?
Hey.
I have something for you guys.
- What?
- What is it?
Seok-ryu's wedding invitation?
Wow, look at this.
I held off giving them to you
because I wanted to present them
in a special place.
Why did you print the invitations
when the wedding will be held in the U.S.?
I didn't want to miss out on anything.
Look at this. It's so beautiful.
You must be so happy
that your daughter's getting married.
You now have a weight off your shoulders!
That's right.
When will I get my loser daughter
out of my house?
- Mo-eum will find someone soon.
- She will.
Oh, right. Is Seung-hyo
going out with anyone these days?
- No, he's way too busy.
- I see.
That's just an excuse.
Even busy people can find time to date.
Seok-ryu managed to find someone
even though she was so busy.
I told you that my son-in-law
is an international lawyer, right?
- Hey.
- It's so pretty.
Women are lining up to meet my son.
Is that so?
The minister and the director
of my husband's hospital
both keep begging me
to introduce their daughters to him.
Say that again when you have
your own wedding invitations to give out.
Gosh. My legs fell asleep.
And victory goes to Na Mi-sook.
The wedding is only a month away.
I know.
It's so soon.
Yahoo!
We're about to land, ma'am.
Could you open your window shade
and straighten your seat, please?
Excuse me.
Ma'am…
Oh, I'm sorry.
I should be the one to apologize.
I startled you.
No, it's just that I was dreaming
about getting beaten up.
My goodness. What a nightmare.
Or it could be an omen.
I've arrived.
EPISODE 1:
COMEBACK
Where is she?
What the…
Bae Seok-ryu!
Wow.
Seeing your face makes me feel like
I'm really back, Mo-eum.
You.
Do you know how startled I was
when you said you were at the airport?
I didn't even get to wash up!
I can see that.
Did you miss me so much
to rush over with soot on your face?
Good grief.
You've become so slimy
after all those years in the U.S.
I know.
I felt it was over the top
even as I was saying it.
Still, it's been years
since we've seen each other.
Don't pretend you're not happy to see me.
Give me a hug.
Come on.
A thief.
She stole my luggage!
What the…
Warn me before you roll up the window.
I almost hurt myself.
I'm teaching you
to be cautious at all times.
Sticking your head out like that
is dangerous.
Aw. You sounded like
a real paramedic just now.
That's because I really am.
Exactly.
Where's the girl I used to know
who'd jump off fences wearing a cape?
I liked that girl.
It's thanks to kids like that
that I get a paycheck.
What was I thinking back then?
Were you near a fire?
Yes. Paramedics accompany
firefighters to the site.
No one died, at least.
That's good.
By the way,
why are you so skinny?
Are you losing weight
for your wedding day?
I'm killing it, right?
This jawline could cut you.
Could you avoid using
dangerous words like "kill" or "cut"?
It's making me antsy.
Sorry.
Did you call your mom?
My mom didn't tell me
you were coming back home.
Sure I did.
Of course you did. What about Seung-hyo?
He must be busy anyway.
How is he anyway?
He's doing good.
You forgot to say my name
in your acceptance speech.
I did.
No, you just mentioned the company's name
and not mine!
I can tell from the color of your suit
that you visited another memorial park.
Yes.
- Did you take a compass?
- No.
Yeah, right. You can't deceive me.
You're an architect,
not a feng-shui master!
It's part of an architect's job
to learn about the cultural
and historical context of a space.
- Ah.
- Don't you know about gravesite feng shui,
a long-standing traditional practice?
You're absolutely right.
Put that camera away.
I can visit a hundred memorial parks
as long as I'm with you.
If you want, I can get buried with you.
No, thank you.
Come on, don't be shy.
I'm scared. I think she means it.
Yes, me too.
Hey, it's Roh Yoon-seo!
Do you know her?
- How do you know her?
- I don't really know her.
We met briefly
at Oblique's launching ceremony.
Amazing! Let's go say hello to her!
I have to go now. I'm busy.
Hey, where do you think you're going?
She's Roh Yoon-seo,
the woman whom every young man
considers perfect!
You can't leave!
My idea of perfection isn't a person,
but a well-made structure.
- You're going there again, aren't you?
- Of course.
No, I won't let you leave
until you help me get her autograph
and take a photo with her!
Just go. Go on!
- Hey!
- Bye.
Hold on.
Hello.
Oh! Oh.
BAE SEOK-RYU
"Heungbu Sausage Stew."
"Sanshin Ox Bone Soup."
"Grandma Kwon's Pork Wraps."
Did you forget Korean or something?
Why are you reading those shop signs?
The restaurant signs keep catching my eye.
Oh, I see.
I guess I'm hungry.
Right.
It's past lunchtime.
Everything looks so good.
"The In-Law's Fried Chicken."
That one doesn't sound so appetizing.
Don't be greedy and just pick one place.
One place? Ah.
Then…
- Enjoy your meal.
- Thank you.
Hey.
I bet the blood of Korean people
is redder than that of others
because it's actually chili paste.
Ooh. What a scientific theory
you have there.
But I thought
we'd go to your family's place.
We came here all the time
during high school.
All right, let's eat these rice cakes
and talk about the good old days.
Wait.
We should have some sundae too.
Get ready.
Begin the battle.
Let's eat!
It's good.
It's so good.
It's spicy though.
Really spicy.
Why is it so spicy?
Jeez, it looks like
I can't handle spicy food now.
Drink some water. Are you okay?
Wow. I guess your blood
isn't as red as it used to be.
You're losing your identity as a Korean.
- It's too spicy.
- All right, I know what to do.
Let's wash them in water first.
- What are you doing?
- Say "ah."
It's okay.
Come on. That's sinking too low.
- Hide!
- What?
- Hello.
- Hi, what can I get you?
One portion
of tteokbokki, assorted fries,
and sundae
with lots of steamed offals, please.
- All right.
- It's Dong-jin.
- Exactly.
- Looks delicious.
What's the deal with them?
Are they feeling sick?
Your food is ready.
Thank you.
You can pay here.
Okay.
Thanks.
- Goodbye.
- Enjoy your food.
It looks good.
Ow! Oh. Oh.
- Sir!
- What's in that bag?
Let go of my ear first, please. Ah!
- Open it.
- Okay.
This tteokbokki has 500 calories.
You also have sundae,
fried seaweed rolls, and fried squid?
That's 1,350 calories in total.
How do you know that?
Listen up.
This is your exercise regimen for today.
A hundred pull-ups, a hundred push-ups,
two hundred lunges and burpees, each.
Then 500 squats, okay?
That's so unfair.
I haven't even eaten them yet!
You ate all these in your mind.
Don't you want your trainer certification?
What about the upcoming contest?
Just the fact that
you considered eating these things
is a crime, all right?
Hand them over.
Come on, hand them over.
I'm confiscating them for your own good.
The offals have protein, though.
Be at the gym in five minutes. Go!
That dimwit.
- I told him squid has more protein.
- Is he gone?
It's delicious, ma'am.
- Have a good day.
- You too.
- He's gone, right?
- Yes.
He should be eating at Dad's diner,
not here.
Hey.
That's the pot calling the kettle black.
Anyway, what was that?
Why did you hide from your brother?
You might not know
since you only have sisters,
but this is what having a brother is like.
Mm…
Does your family not know
that you're back?
Surprise.
I mean,
it's been a while since I came home.
So I thought it would be more fun
to surprise them like this
than just to walk through the front door.
Right.
You're nuts. So you're making
a whole production out of…
Wait, "a whole production"?
We might as well go all-out.
Come on, let's go.
We need to decorate the house
until our moms come back from hiking.
Wait, Mo-eum…
- What?
- Please promise me one thing.
Stay with me until the end of the day,
no matter what happens.
What do you mean?
Even if Mount Baekdu explodes
or the Han River overflows, okay?
Even if the world ends
or the dinosaurs come back!
Hold on.
- What I mean is--
- Hello?
Yes, captain?
Jae-gyeong did what?
Right now?
- All right. I'll be right there.
- You're leaving?
- Where are you going?
- I have to go. It's an emergency.
I have an emergency too.
I'm going to need you later on!
Then call 911 later! Bye!
Hey, wait! I'm being serious!
Jung Mo-eum!
Hey!
Bye.
But…
That traitor.
There used to be a sauna here.
CORNERSTONE
THIS BUILDING WAS FUNDED BY THE GOVERNMENT
FOR THE RESIDENTS OF HYEREUNG-DONG
TO COMMEMORATE THE HOSTING
OF THE OLYMPIC GAMES
HYEREUNG SAUNA
No!
You really have to take a bath today.
See? You're so grimy with dirt,
I can hardly tell you're a human brat.
Well, I'm your grimy brat!
You're not doing this on purpose, are you?
No! I don't want to take a bath!
Come on!
I don't want to go inside
with Bae Seok-ryu.
It's okay, Seung-hyo.
HYEREUNG SAUNA
- Oh, come on.
- No!
SAUNA OPEN
WOMEN'S BATH
Our mothers were so cruel.
How could they make us share a bath?
It was a violation of our rights.
I used to hate going to the sauna,
but it's a shame it's gone.
What is this place anyway?
There's no sign.
No front door either.
Who are you?
Bae Seok-ryu?
Choisseung?
What are you doing here?
That's my line.
What's up with you?
None of your business.
You're stepping on my land.
Don't make me laugh. This is your land?
Wait, is it?
It is, so go away.
- I do dancesport.
- Your old age is showing.
What the heck?
- What are you doing?
I can't talk right now.
Just help me out, okay?
What are you going on about?
Help me out just this once.
Just pretend I'm a discarded box, okay?
Don't tell anyone you saw me.
Got it?
Whatever. Get out.
- I said, get out.
I don't believe you.
You want proof?
- Look at her.
- Hey.
Hey, stop that!
- That's enough!
- Gosh, how embarrassing.
One, two!
What's this luggage doing here
in the middle of the road?
- Seung-hyo.
- Mom.
Give me a hug.
Oh, my.
- It's been a while, Seung-hyo.
- You're here.
- You're as handsome as always.
- He is.
I'm In-sook. Do you remember me?
Of course. How have you been?
My goodness!
- Hello.
- What are you doing here?
- Hi.
Why aren't you at the diner?
Where are you sneaking off to?
Why would I be sneaking?
Is that any way to talk
to your beloved husband?
Wanna try that again?
I just went to the market.
Hey, Seung-hyo! Here, have one.
- Thank you.
- It's good to see you.
Thank you.
You should've called ahead
to say you were coming home.
Uh, I came to receive
some furniture today.
- I apologize for not letting you know.
- I see.
I understand.
Your firm opens next week,
so you must be busy.
I invited a lot of guests
for the opening party.
- About that--
- So you're saying that this building
is your new office?
- Yes.
- That's impressive.
- Thank you.
- Seung-hyo.
- Is this your luggage?
- What? No.
- Really?
- This was just here?
- We should take it to the police.
- We should.
- Let's do it.
- Let me see.
It says something here.
It's in English.
Hold on. It is mine.
It's definitely mine.
Seung-hyo
has the same taste as me.
- I suppose.
- Pink is a man's color, you know.
- Right.
- You should take better care of it.
What if you lost it? Here you go.
I'll do it.
Seung-hyo.
Did you eat the beans I sent you?
- Did you eat everything?
- Uh, actually, not yet.
I've been too busy to eat at home.
You need to have healthier eating habits!
You want me to come over
and check your fridge?
I'm sorry. I'll give you an apple
as an apology.
An apology?
I'm only eating beans from today onward.
What are you guarding this box for anyway?
What's in it?
I don't know.
I mean, it can't be a person, can it?
Are you hiding something precious?
Of course not.
It has nothing of value.
I should throw it out.
Really? Then we'll throw it out for you.
- Honey.
- Yes, I can carry it.
You can sell a box like this for money.
Hold on.
Now that I think about it,
I still need it to put all my trash in.
I'll throw it out after that.
Maybe there is
something of value after all.
- Really?
- Okay.
Tell me when you plan to throw it out.
Okay.
Seung-hyo.
Don't forget the beans.
Yes, ma'am.
You should cook it better.
Let's go.
- Bye!
- Goodbye!
- Goodbye.
- Have a good day!
I'll be going too, Seung-hyo.
All right. Goodbye.
- See you later.
- Yes.
Bye.
Are they all gone?
I'm coming out.
Let me out.
Why are you hiding from your mom?
Let me out! It's stuffy in here!
It's just very strange.
I thought you were
supposed to be in the U.S.
Did you get into trouble?
I have other ways of getting out.
Jeez.
You tore the box?
I can tear you apart too.
Aunt Mi-sook!
Just kidding.
I'm going to end you!
Is that any way to talk to your savior?
So this is your new office?
It kind of sucks.
- It's full of bucks though.
- Whatever.
Then why don't you save me one more time?
What?
Let me use your bathroom.
Don't mark it as your territory.
You can't go in there!
Jeez.
Go straight and turn left there.
That's the front door.
Goodbye.
It's actually not that bad.
Just follow the recommended route.
Hey, what are these?
Millstones?
They're stepping stones.
Keep your dirty hands off of them!
Are you doing this on purpose?
Does this place
have bad feng shui?
Or are you my bad luck?
You know you're kind of mean, don't you?
You don't know you're immature, do you?
I don't like this at all.
At least you were cute
when you were little.
You weren't cute
even when you were little.
You little…
Look at this.
You immediately start throwing punches.
I tell you, you're closer to a beast
than a human being.
Your fiancé must be a saint.
What?
Aunt Mi-sook gave me
your wedding invitation.
She offered to buy my plane ticket,
but I think I'll be too busy to make it.
Congratulations on your marriage.
Thanks.
By the way, where's your office?
Aren't you going to leave?
It's over there, isn't it?
Please just leave!
Just go, please.
Why are you going upstairs?
Hey, come on! Get out of there.
Why would you come in here?
Your office is huge.
Just go home, okay?
Ooh.
That's an impressive ceiling.
I guess you have eyes, after all.
I referred to the ceiling designs
of the Goguryeo mural tombs.
You mean like the Twin Column Tomb
or the Tomb of the Dancers?
Exactly.
It's a ceiling
with triangles in each corner,
the most common type of the era.
It holds the principles of
"the sky is round
and the earth is square."
In other words,
you designed your office like a tomb.
What a weirdo.
What? A "weirdo"?
Whatever.
Of course, someone as crude as you
wouldn't understand my art,
which reinterprets
our ancestors' timeless wisdom
with modern sensibilities--
For crying out loud.
Are you okay?
Do I look okay to you?
I can't believe you crawled out alone.
I have a very strong attachment to life.
What was it that fell anyway?
Ow.
This thing is heavy!
Did you think it'd be
as light as a feather?
Did you hurt yourself?
Let me see.
What are you doing?
Do you have eyes in the back of your head?
If you don't, just stay still.
I knew this would happen.
I always end up getting hurt
when I'm with you.
Be quiet and stay still.
You're completely fine.
Nothing to worry about.
But it might leave a bruise…
What did you just say? Say it again!
Stop it!
Don't!
Let me go!
You still have this scar.
I told you, didn't I?
My body is bruised and battered
from everything you put me through.
You're exaggerating.
I don't expect you to apologize.
I just want you to leave now. Please.
Hey, I didn't want to spend
my first day back with you either.
- But something unexpected came up--
- Hey, Seok-ryu.
I couldn't care less
about what you did or didn't do.
I see.
Sorry for inconveniencing you.
But I know one thing.
Knowing Aunt Mi-sook, putting it off
wouldn't do you any favors.
Things are going to escalate
the longer you put it off.
You could face a 24-hour silent treatment
for what could've been resolved
in 30 minutes.
So stop dawdling
and just get it over with.
You're so annoying when you're right.
You're so pathetic
when you get in trouble.
That's it.
Let me hit you just once.
I think
this cost 17 million won.
Not 1,700 won?
A designer friend of mine gave it to me.
If it's broken,
I should claim for damages--
Let me see.
It's not broken. It's fine.
What an expensive chunk of metal.
Look. I gave it a rub so it shines better.
It's so shiny now.
It's totally fine, right?
It's as good as new.
I'll just carefully put it back here.
Don't bother.
There, all done!
It looks even better than before.
- Just go.
- It looks so perfect.
HYEREUNG 911 SAFETY CENTER
Hey.
How could you call me back
after I'd gone home for the day?
I'm not even on this team.
I had no choice.
The newbie got seriously carsick.
I told you
Captain Song should drive slower.
You're the only one
who can bear to be in the car with him.
Who would've guessed
that a good paramedic
is one who doesn't get carsick?
I'm leaving.
Emergency dispatch.
911 AMBULANCE
Sir.
I'm a paramedic.
Are you okay?
Can you hear me?
What? Who called 911?
Who was it?
Jeez.
We got a call that you collapsed
with a cut on your forehead.
We'll take you to the hospital.
How did you get hurt?
I just fell from a chair.
It's fine. I don't need a doctor.
Yes, you do.
It could be superficial,
but we can't rule out concussion.
You should get checked out.
Get lost.
I said get lost.
Jeez, I'm hungry.
When is my mother getting here?
- For crying out loud.
- Sir.
Sir.
Do you have diabetes?
You shouldn't have drunk this much.
I told you to get lost.
Careful.
Come on, Captain Jung.
Let's just call the police.
- Let me check your blood sugar level.
- Why you…
I said no!
I'm not going to the hospital!
Stop bothering me and get lost!
Don't curse at me.
Do you see this camera I'm wearing?
I have no choice but to film your face
if you keep acting like this.
I told you to get lost
and stop bothering me.
Why would you film me?
Who do you think you are to do that?
- Get back, Mo-eum.
- Sir.
Put down that bottle, please.
And who the hell are you?
I'm just a civilian.
Everyone, please stay out of this.
We'll deal with it.
I wanted to help out
because the situation looked dangerous.
Why? Because I'm a woman?
No,
because I'm a red belt in taekwondo.
- What?
- I'm sorry, sir!
Hold on!
What's the deal with him?
What the…
I'm a black belt.
Can you treat him, please?
Are you okay, sir?
Good grief.
What?
Let me just check your blood.
Oh, all right.
It's going to sting.
- Okay.
- Give me your hand.
Why did you drink so much?
It's so noisy. Don't walk so close to me.
You're the one who's following me.
Do you think I'm following you?
You might have forgotten,
but our parents live
right next to each other.
I'm just going home.
Just take another road. Go on.
This is the quickest.
For crying out loud.
Are you craving fried chicken right now?
THE IN-LAW'S FRIED CHICKEN
I feel sorry for you. I really do.
Do you think I could ask
to borrow that helmet right there?
You think they'd lend it to me?
What?
I need something
to protect me from my mom.
She'll crack my melon.
You could've picked a more normal word
like "head" or even "skull."
There aren't any helmet shops nearby,
are there?
This lunatic is actually being serious.
What are you doing?
What are you doing
in the middle of the street?
Hold this.
Hey.
You're driving me nuts.
I guess I underestimated you.
You're insane.
You look like a blowfish.
It's only natural to puff up one's body
when faced with incredible danger.
Come on, hit me.
What are you saying?
Just hit me. I need to see
if I'm protected enough.
Why didn't you just buy
a bulletproof vest in the U.S.?
I really should've.
Should I go back and buy one?
Considering the time and money
you'd have to spend,
just get it over with right now.
Mm. Mm.
Hey, do you want to
spend the night with me?
- What the hell are you on about?
- Stay with me.
Stop fooling around.
I'm not asking for much.
Just stay by my side, okay?
Go away! You're scaring me.
I'm the one who's scared.
I really screwed up, Seung-hyo.
I came home to just tell my mom
and get it over with,
but now I can't bear to face her.
What is it? What did you do?
I have to know what it is
if I'm going to help you
decide what to do about it.
Well…
The thing is…
I…
called it off.
What?
I said…
I'm not getting married.
Speak up, will you?
I said I broke off my engagement!
Uh, Aunt Mi-sook.
Hey, you can't fool me twice
with that trick.
What did you just say?
Seok-ryu.
What did you say? Say it again.
Mom.
I must have heard it wrong, right?
Right.
Mom!
- Oh, my.
- How have you been?
You must be surprised to see me
out of the blue.
You're still so beautiful.
I'm actually kind of confused
because of jet lag, you know?
The reason I'm back in Korea is…
Yes?
It's…
to tell you
that I broke off my engagement.
Oh, my God!
- Dad!
- Geun-sik!
- Move out of the way.
He must have had a shock.
Goodness!
Are you all right, Geun-sik?
I just had a bad dream.
- I thought Seok-ryu said…
- Are you okay, Dad?
Seok-ryu!
It wasn't a dream?
No, this has to be a dream!
Just a bad dream!
Seok-ryu.
What did you say? You did what?
I broke off my engagement.
I canceled everything.
Everyone in the U.S. knows already.
You're out of your mind.
You're completely nuts.
I'm totally fine.
How could you call your own daughter nuts?
I'm calling it as I see it!
Only a nutjob would pull a stunt like this
a month before the wedding!
Come here.
Aunt Mi-sook!
Use your words, please.
- No violence.
- That's right, Mom. Hear me out.
There's a saying in the U.S.
"There are three types of people
who get married."
"The dumb, the poor, and the masochist."
Why you… Get over here.
Wait, I have more.
I have one more thing to say.
There's another saying that goes,
"Marriage is leaving a festival
before it begins."
Are you nuts?
What in the world happened?
You sounded so happy
- the last time we talked!
- Stop it.
Don't tell me that my son…
No, he's not my son-in-law anymore.
Did that jerk Song Hyeon-jun call it off?
That dirtbag!
Honey, buy us
two plane tickets right away.
- Okay.
- I'll tear him to pieces!
It's not his fault.
Do you have no pride?
Are you seriously defending him?
It wasn't his fault. It was mine.
That makes no sense.
What could you have possibly…
Did you…
cheat on him?
Goodness.
Dear me.
Be careful.
Now, breathe in deeply.
You might start hyperventilating.
I need CPR.
You crazy brat!
I can't believe you!
- Even I never cheated on anyone,
- Mi-sook!
with a pathetic husband like that!
So how could you do
such an unthinkable thing?
I've had it up to here with you!
I'll end you!
- Aunt Mi-sook!
- You don't have to talk to me like that.
Do you want me to be an unfilial daughter
who dies before her parents?
- Hey.
- What about now?
As if you're a filial daughter now!
- Mi-sook! Stop!
- Auntie! Hold on!
- Let's talk it out like civilized people.
- That's right!
Let's be civilized.
You're being too violent.
Also, I'm a grownup.
You can't just
discipline me like that anymore!
I'll treat you like a grownup
when you act like one!
Come over here, you brat!
- Aunt Mi-sook!
- What are you doing?
Stop hitting me and hit her instead!
That's right!
Why are you hitting my son?
He's taking all the blows
for your daughter!
He's so cruel and ruthless.
He really made me do all the push-ups.
- Come here, you brat!
- Hey!
What's with the ruckus?
- You should go.
- Is someone fighting?
Why do you keep calling me "brat"
instead of the name you gave me?
That's your issue?
How about I call you "bastard" instead?
- I think I prefer "brat."
- Hey, you…
Are you making fun of me?
Aunt Mi-sook! Stop!
Don't hit me there!
Hey!
Are you trying to castrate my son?
I've had enough.
Let me go! Stop it!
- Honey.
- Out of my way!
Don't do this.
Uncle Geun-sik.
Honey, please!
Stop hitting her, okay?
You haven't even heard
Seok-ryu's side of the story yet.
She wouldn't do something like that
for no reason!
Dad.
Oh, my daughter.
It's okay.
She basically raised herself
without our help!
So she must have had a reason
for doing whatever she did!
Fine, tell me.
Let's hear it.
Will you stop hitting me if I tell you?
Fine.
Will you really listen to
everything I have to say?
Yes.
I'll listen.
Are you sure?
- I said yes.
- She said yes.
Mom.
I also quit my work.
I'm unemployed now.
No way.
So you're… what?
- Dad!
- Geun-sik!
Is he okay?
Dong-jin!
- What is it?
- I'm just so…
You little…
You hopeless brat!
You quit your job
on top of all that?
You're insane!
- Goodness, Mi-sook!
- Come here!
Seok-ryu!
- You said you'd hear me out!
- You're hitting Seung-hyo!
- You're hitting my son!
- This is too ridiculous!
- You worked so hard to get there!
- Stop it!
- You had such a good job.
- Stop!
- Why would you quit?
- Hey!
- You little brat!
- Stop it.
- I can't believe…
- It hurts!
Are you in your right mind?
- We have to run!
- Hold it right there!
- Hey!
- I'm not done with you!
Why did you have to bring me along?
I have no reason to run!
I saved you from being beaten to a pulp.
You're the only reason I got beaten
with a bunch of leeks!
What's your plan now?
Just think of it as playing tag.
- Stop right there!
- We're dead if we get caught.
Hey!
I'm counting to ten!
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight,
nine, ten!
We're dead if we get caught, okay?
Hey, get back here!
Stop right there, Bae Seok-ryu!
Hey!
That little brat. Get back here!
Hey.
She wouldn't follow us here, right?
We shook her off a long time ago.
Then why didn't you tell me?
We could've stopped running.
Why did we come all the way here?
I'm totally wiped!
Don't slap me away like that.
You're the one who grabbed my hand first.
Hey.
Buy me something to drink.
Are you nuts?
The store is down there!
I'm so thirsty right now
that I might puke.
Swallow your spit.
You heartless jerk.
I'm exhausted.
You should work out more
if you're exhausted from that.
You try sitting in front of a computer
for ten years
and see if your body comes out unscathed.
That's still just an excuse.
You could've worked out more.
It's so hot.
Why isn't there any wind?
Come here for a second.
What now? What are you doing?
Stand right here.
Are you seriously going to use me
as your human shield again?
You're my changing room this time.
Hide me while I take these off.
Why are you doing this to me?
Jeez.
How many layers did you wear?
Are you a nesting doll or something?
What's that?
You know, the Russian toy
that has dolls inside dolls.
Oh.
Are you saying I look like a doll?
More like a dolt.
I will end you.
Just finish your shedding.
I'm letting you off
for so many things today.
Can I turn around?
Hey, I'm turning around.
Why didn't you answer me?
I should've listened to you.
Now Mom won't talk to me for a whole day.
I'd say two days.
That sucks.
I should've looked more closely
at my mom's face then.
I missed her.
You should've been honest.
Why did you tell her that you cheated?
You don't believe
that I cheated?
Why not?
Maybe I'm an irresistible femme fatale.
- You?
- Hey.
You shouldn't judge a book by its cover.
The truth is…
I'm hiding something huge.
Just keep hiding it then.
Ha! You're so annoying.
Fine, I don't care.
You won't guess in a million years anyway.
It doesn't affect me at all.
I'm completely fine.
You don't seem fine.
You made two huge life decisions at once.
Only a doll would be undamaged by that.
Ooh.
So you really think I'm a doll, don't you?
Maybe a satanic doll.
Shut up.
I just…
felt like my life was getting overheated.
You know how hard I've worked.
I was studying in Korea,
then I suddenly went to the U.S.
and had to adapt to that life.
Then I got a job
and got engaged too.
Going at full throttle
all the time like that…
overloaded my CPU.
The screen went blank,
and the keys stopped working.
So I had no choice
but to reboot myself.
That was my excuse for quitting my job
and calling off my engagement.
That was brave of you.
It was.
So I had to come back
before my courage expired
and my resolve crumbled into nothing.
Excuse me. Could you take a photo of us?
- Sure.
- Thank you.
Over there.
- On three.
- Okay.
One, two, three.
Take a horizontal one too.
Okay.
One, two, three.
- Here.
- Thanks.
Thank you.
Do you want a photo too?
- No.
- No, thank you.
- Ooh.
- It was as if on cue.
You guys are totally in sync.
You must have dated a long time
to get that way.
- No, we're not…
- No.
Ah.
Then how do you know each other?
- He's the son of my mom's friend.
- She's the daughter of my mom's friend.
Ah.
- Goodbye, then.
- Thank you.
It's Dong-jin.
Hey, wait!
Hello?
Mom wants Seok-ryu to come home.
She says she won't hit her anymore.
She's out of energy.
Is that so? All right.
What did he say?
Your mother calmed down
and wants you back home.
- You're lying.
- I'm not.
She's not going to be violent anymore
and wants to resolve this peacefully.
And I'm saying I don't believe her.
You saw how she broke her promise
to hear me out.
She's only going to smack me again.
She wouldn't.
She has bad shoulders and wrists.
She looked healthy enough earlier
when she was going at it.
I can come with you if you want.
Why are you suddenly being nice?
It's just that Aunt Mi-sook
likes me better than you.
It's so annoying that I can't deny that.
Wait up!
Jeez.
Good work today.
Can you give this to the patient
who came in with me earlier?
Thank you. See you tomorrow.
Excuse me.
Oh, hello.
How is your hand?
It's fine.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have interfered like that.
It's okay.
You looked a little foolish,
but I have a soft spot for kindness.
Goodbye then.
- Excuse me.
- What is it now?
Is it okay for me to ask your name?
Listen. I've been a paramedic
for six years.
Of all the people who have asked
for my name and number to thank me,
no one actually got in touch with me.
I will, though.
But I'm not telling you.
- Goodbye!
- Wait!
JESEUNG UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
Here you go.
What's this?
The paramedic who brought you in
told me to give you this.
They're glucose candies.
Take them if you get dizzy
from low blood sugar.
Don't drink alcohol anymore, okay?
Call 911 right away if you need help.
THE CHUNGWOO DAILY
As for me…
I have a soft spot for touching stories.
Wait a second.
Give me a minute.
I'm not prepared yet.
You'll never be.
Hey, wait!
Who is it?
It's me, Aunt Mi-sook. I brought Seok-ryu.
Okay. Come in.
See?
You go in first.
I think she's crying.
Mom.
Are you crying?
I'm sorry, Mom.
Don't cry.
Come here.
Let's see this out to the end.
Run!
What are you doing?
I brought her to you,
so do whatever you want with her.
Hey! That little… Open up!
Open up!
Come on, open the door.
I should've known you'd betray me!
You're dead meat tomorrow!
Tomorrow?
Do you think you'll be alive tomorrow?
Mom.
Just hear me out.
- Come inside.
- Getting mad is bad for your health.
Okay, fine! Mom!
- Come here.
- Mom!
Just tell it to me straight!
What happened?
Just tell me!
Is it true
that you can't speak Korean?
It's because he was born abroad.
Then say something in a foreign language.
Come on!
Looks like he can't do anything.
Are you dumb?
Hey!
It's Bae Seok-ryu.
She'll kill you
if you make fun of this idiot.
What did you just say?
Say it again.
I'll kill you if you bother my baby again!
Now that she's back,
it's going to get chaotic again.
You already hit me there, Mom!
Hit me somewhere else!
Does it hurt?
Then you know how I feel!
You're about
to reach your 60th birthday.
Shouldn't that make you more lenient?
Just hear me out, please!
It hurts!
COMEBACK
COME BACK HOME
LOVE NEXT DOOR
I basically raised Seung-hyo.
Don't trust her.
Every word she says is a lie.
This girl was
the first lunatic I met in my life.
I can't believe that picky little kid
grew up to be such a successful man.
I'm proud of you.
Seok-ryu.
What are you doing here?
You don't want me here, do you?
You never wanted me to come back.
That's why you got rid of my room.
I turned back time.
I recreated your embarrassing past.