ADAPTED FROM THE NOVEL
HIDDEN LOVE BY ZHU YI
- I couldn't stand it.
- Wait.
- What were you doing?
- Let me eat first.
What?
The three of us were in a ranked match.
Then I got a call.
You even scolded me.
- The day we almost won?
- Yes, that day.
I told you before, didn't I?
Her again?
Valentine's Day was around the corner,
so I bought her roses.
That's so tacky.
Is buying roses tacky?
Yes, it's so tacky.
Man, you have no game. Seriously.
- All right. Eat.
- You don't get it.
No amount of flowers will work.
- Listen.
- What flowers did you give?
- Don't you know?
- And it's extremely tacky.
Do you know that he gave her red roses?
You still don't remember.
Can you pay more attention to me?
Let me tell you.
She posted on Weibo
that it would be nice
to receive red roses on Valentine's Day.
I liked the post.
Then I immediately went out
to get her red roses.
I ate too much.
We shouldn't have ordered so much food.
We had already ordered before you came.
Did he do all that
because he didn't want me
to be embarrassed?
One wanted your number.
Another wanted your number.
No one wanted mine.
Am I not your backup?
Just change your name to Sang Yan.
Wouldn't you be yourself then?
Or you can change it to Duan Jiaxu.
Okay, I'll get the car.
You two can wait for me at the entrance.
Follow them.
- Hurry.
- Let's go.
Sang Zhi.
Shall I take you to the claw machine?
Let's play.
No, thank you, Qian Fei.
It's fine. I promised you. Come on.
Listen, I'm the best.
I'll teach you step by step.
Sang Zhi.
Take a handful.
Thank you.
Take it.
This is enough.
Okay, come on. I'll teach you.
Here, let me help you.
The white one?
Give me two more.
I got you a plushie.
Don't cry anymore.
Thank you, Jiaxu.
Have some candy.
What do you think?
Wasn't I brave earlier?
Thank you, Jiaxu.
Come on. I'll see you home.
I can lecture you along the way.
Wait a second.
When Sang Yan met the teacher,
he didn't lecture me afterward.
- Really?
- Really.
I'll call your brother and ask him.
No! Wait a minute!
Won't he find out if you ask him?
Then you will have come here for nothing!
Kiddo.
You called me all the way here.
And now you're lying to me.
Won't that make me a sucker?
That again?
Fine, I won't tell your brother.
Kiddo.
Goodbye then.
Where are you going?
It's getting late.
If I'm not home yet,
my mom will worry about me.
I'll see you home.
Wait!
The bus station is nearby.
Besides, it's a short walk
after I get off the bus.
Jiaxu, you must be very busy right now.
I've kept you long enough.
I'll get out of your hair.
You didn't care so much about me before.
I'll see you home no matter how busy I am.
Walk faster.
Jiaxu, it's getting dark.
Are you not returning to campus yet?
Don't worry, kiddo.
I will keep today's incident a secret.
Really?
Pinky promise?
You must also promise me
you'll pay attention in class
and not break the school rules.
- Okay?
- Okay.
I'm not joking.
If your teacher wants
to meet your parents again,
what happened today will be exposed.
I'll be in trouble.
You can come again next time.
Will there be a next time?
No.
I just think you're very nice to me.
You're nicer to me than my brother is.
So…
If something like this happens again,
can I ask you to pretend to be my brother?
Got it.
Go home.
There had better not be a next time.
Here.
By the way,
the light bulb in your kitchen burnt out.
After you get inside,
give this to your dad.
Okay. Thank you, Jiaxu.
Don't mention it.
Hurry inside.
- Goodbye, Jiaxu.
- Be good.
Bye.
Difficult kiddo.
Let's go.
CHAPTER THREE, CONSIDERATE
GET A LITTLE CLOSER
Why did you lie to me again?
I don't want to go. I really don't.
We're already here. Let's go together.
Besides, I already bought a gift.
That's right. I didn't buy a gift.
It doesn't matter.
We'll say it's from both of us.
It's no big deal. Come on.
Just say it's from you.
I hardly know him anyway.
It's fine. Let's go together.
We agreed to meet here.
Welcome.
Sang Zhi?
Jiaxu.
Are you hanging out with your friend?
Hello.
Do you work here?
Here.
See what you would like to eat.
You can order here later.
Find a table first.
He's so handsome.
Who is he?
That doesn't look like your brother.
He's my brother's friend.
Your brother's friend?
He's handsome.
Your brother is handsome too.
Sang Zhi, you're so lucky.
See what you would like to eat.
I want…
Red beans
or milk custard with mango.
I think I'll get
the milk custard with red beans.
Saigon milk custard.
I don't think I can eat this.
I'll get the milk custard with red beans.
Milk custard with red beans then.
Have a look.
I will have
pearl sago with coconut milk.
- Is that all?
- Yes.
I'll go order.
Keep an eye on my phone.
Sure.
What do you want to order?
I want
one milk custard with red beans
and one pearl sago with coconut milk.
Okay.
Which one is yours?
The pearl sago with coconut milk.
You're one yuan short.
No, I'm not.
You stole so many glances at me.
I can't let you do that for free.
No wonder you have no customers.
It's because you're running a shady shop.
Only because I charged you an extra yuan?
I didn't steal glances at you.
Okay, I'm the one making stuff up.
Would I really charge you?
Keep it to buy yourself candy.
No way.
Don't you work here to make money?
If I don't pay you,
how will you make money?
Take back the money.
Treating you to dessert
won't put me in the red.
Your friend is waiting.
Sang Zhi, is your brother's friend
treating us to desserts?
- Yes.
- That's great.
I'm low on money after buying the gift.
I'll ask the others.
Where are you now?
Where are you guys?
We've been waiting for a long time.
Fu Zhengchu, hurry up.
All right.
Your milk custard.
Thank you.
Thank you, Jiaxu.
Yours is hot.
Try it.
It smells so good.
Do you want to try mine?
Xiaoduan.
Mr. Gao.
I have to run to the second store.
By the way,
how about I give you
half a month of your advance first?
- Thank you, Mr. Gao.
- Okay, get back to work.
- I'll take care of it.
- Okay.
Does he keep working
because he is short on cash?
Fu Zhengchu!
- Sang Zhi, sorry for being late.
- Hello.
Hello!
Hello.
Sang Zhi.
Does your brother work here?
But isn't your family rich?
Will you mind your own business?
It's late.
Let's go have fun.
Let's go.
We're not done yet.
Stop eating, Sang Zhi.
Let's go.
Everyone is waiting for us.
There is plenty of food there.
Let's go.
Sangsang, let's go.
What are you thinking?
Get ready. Hide.
Are you going out with your friends?
Be careful.
Make sure to go home before dark.
Leave her to us.
- Have fun.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
Let's go.
Sangsang.
Why does your brother's friend
sound like my dad?
My dad said the same thing before I left.
We haven't hung out in a long while.
Just the thought of it makes me happy.
Wait, Zhenru.
Give me a minute.
Sangsang, where are you going?
They're already waiting for us.
Why did you come back?
Jiaxu, are you short on cash?
I heard from Sang Yan that you work.
Then I see you working today.
I wanted to say
that you don't have to treat me
if you're short on cash.
I can afford to buy you dessert.
Why are you worrying so much?
This kid.
- Happy birthday to you
We wish you…
- Health!
- Good luck!
Great fortune,
and a happy family!
Enough.
- Come on.
- Let's have cake.
- Make a wish!
Make a wish.
Here. Make a wish.
This is my wish.
Sang Zhi--
Wait.
Do you have something to say to me?
I have something to tell you.
Is it okay
if I go home first?
I already spent your birthday with you
and sang the birthday song.
I really want to go home.
- Bye.
- Wait.
Carry on. Have fun!
Sang Zhi!
Fu Zhengchu, go after her.
Quick.
You guys can eat first. I'll be back.
- We'll cut the cake when you're back.
- Go.
Fu Zhengchu!
It's Fu Zhengchu's birthday,
but Sang Zhi left early.
He won't be happy.
Yin Zhenru, Sang Zhi is a lousy friend.
Sang Zhi!
Why did you follow me outside?
Aren't you partying?
I came out for some air.
You get your air.
I'm going home.
Let me see you off.
We know each other so well.
You don't need to do that.
Sang Zhi.
I don't believe you can't tell.
Can't tell what?
I studied so hard
to get into the same high school as you.
Don't you know?
I know.
That's why I think you should
focus on your studies.
Why do you keep telling me to study?
If, on the off chance,
I have a crush on you,
what would you think?
I can't imagine it.
No, what I mean is
that you should think about
how to study hard.
Don't make jokes like this.
I'm not joking with you.
Have you forgotten that you knocked out
one of my teeth when we were kids?
That was years ago.
Didn't I break my hand too?
You're right.
Well…
Sang Zhi--
No.
Let's not talk about it.
Sang Zhi!
It's my birthday today.
I chose today to tell you this.
You're always doing this to me.
- Couldn't you reject me another day?
- Why are you always like this?
You start crying before even saying much.
- You're always like this.
- I'm not.
You're crying!
What are you doing? Stop crying!
Fu Zhengchu, why are you always--
Am I interrupting?
Sang Zhi's brother, hello.
Goodbye.
Jiaxu, were you eavesdropping?
Yes.
You sound so righteous.
You're in high school.
You can't date so early.
I'm not.
I'm not dating.
Really.
Weren't you eavesdropping?
Didn't you hear me tell him
to study hard
and not think about other things?
Come to think of it,
it's normal to have these ideas
during adolescence.
But your task now
is to study hard and not get distracted.
I told you I didn't.
I really didn't.
I trust you.
But Sang Zhi,
it's nice to have people who like you.
You can thank him for liking you
before gently rejecting him.
But you can't hurt him.
I didn't hurt him.
I saw him crying.
He was crying
because he has always been a crybaby.
He and I grew up fighting.
He's always the first to cry.
Fighting?
No wonder your parents
got called to school every day.
It didn't happen every day.
It was just a couple of times…
Put out your hand.
Take it back.
Otherwise, people will say
I extorted a high school student.
It's not extortion.
I had dessert. I should pay for it.
What dessert costs this much?
Do you really think this is a shady shop?
Jiaxu.
I just think it's a little hard for you
to work multiple jobs
because you're short on cash.
If I can help you…
But don't overthink it.
If it were my brother,
I would help him too.
I swear.
So do you feel bad
for me?
No.
Sorry.
Are you mad?
I'm not.
Thank you, Sang Zhi.
You know you need to be nice to me now.
I'm touched that you did this
and the thought behind it.
But I'm not that broke.
How about this?
When I'm so broke
that I can't afford to feed myself,
I'll borrow money from you.
Okay?
All right, I need to get back to work.
Do you know how to get
to the nearest bus stop?
Yes.
Can you go home by yourself?
Goodbye then.
Zhenru.
What's the teacher's main focus?
It's this one.
15th century BC.
This question type.
Zhenru.
For Sports Day,
what event did you sign up for?
The name list is ready.
Look over here.
The annual Sports Day
is about to begin.
This year, we have a lot of events.
The school decided to hold it
at Nanwu University as usual.
Is everyone participating?
- Yes.
Sang Zhi.
Why don't I see your name?
Sir, I'll be the record clerk this year.
That's not a sport.
You can do the high jump.
I can't jump.
I have bad knees.
You're 17 years old,
not 70!
Knee problems at such a young age
prove that you lack exercise.
You're doing this.
I'm scared I'll drag everyone down
with this flaw.
It doesn't matter.
Participate and show what you can do.
It doesn't matter whether you win.
What matters is participation,
not prizes.
What do I want?
I want you to be involved.
It's you then.
Also,
go to the class monitor
and report your clothing sizes.
I'm going to order class uniforms.
Sir, what is the style of the uniform?
It's a secret.
It will look very good.
It carries the vitality
of 17-year-old students like you.
- Really?
- Is that so?
The 100 m race.
Chen Liqiang.
Train hard with your three classmates.
Zhenru.
Zhenru, where are you going?
I'm going to the store.
I'll go with you.
What do you want to eat? It's my treat.
No, thank you.
Grade 11.
Men's 100 m sprint.
Ready.
Get set.
- Go!
Fu Zhengchu, go! Fu Zhengchu!
Grade 11 students participating
in the women's high jump,
please report
to the registration area immediately.
Sang Zhi, it's your turn.
- Let's go.
- Zhenru, it's Sang Zhi's turn.
- Let's go together.
I'm not going. You girls go ahead. Bye.
We'll leave first.
Yes, right over there.
Thank you.
It's so good-looking.
It looks nice.
Sang Zhi.
Good luck.
I'm going to accept my award.
REGISTRATION AREA,
WOMEN'S HIGH JUMP QUALIFIER
Number 26.
Xie Jialu, okay.
You're disqualified from the competition.
- Go home.
- You're really annoying.
You're not tall enough, 120 cm won't do.
I'm already 155 cm. Here.
Class 1, Sang…
- Here.
- Sang Zhi.
Here. Turn around. Let me see.
- No.
- Turn around and show me.
No.
Turn around.
Turn around. Let me see.
- What are you doing?
- It's a match!
0155!
Are you worried nobody knows
that you're 155 cm?
- Seriously. Go.
- Sang Zhi.
What event are you participating in?
High jump.
155 cm, participating in the high jump.
The sunflower is cute.
I didn't choose it.
Do your best.
Good luck, little demon!
- It's hilarious!
- You're so loud.
I was napping.
- Go!
Wear a hat.
Don't get sunburned.
How is your warmup?
Move more
so you don't get a sprain later.
GO
What are you doing?
Mom and Dad told me to take photos.
Can't you take it when I look good?
Why do you have to do it when I'm…
You have to tell me when you look good
or I won't know.
- Look at 155 cm here.
- Delete it.
- Give it to me.
Don't touch it.
Stop bullying my sister all the time.
What do you mean?
Did you hear that?
My brother told you to stop bullying me.
Who is your brother?
What about it?
Fine, you can have her.
- Let me take some photos.
- Go away.
Take a few photos. You're handsome.
Fine, you can have her.
- Give me back my camera.
- Look.
Don't I look handsome?
- Grade 11.
- Do you really think so?
The women's high jump will begin soon.
Okay, competition time.
Do your best. You can do it.
Good.
Next, 0845.
Mr. Chen,
the middle school isn't involved.
Why are you here?
I'm here to watch and learn.
The middle school's Sports Day
is next month.
Mr. Ling.
The high school is different this year.
How is it different?
Look at your class uniform.
What a great scene.
It's trendy and stylish.
Most importantly,
it's full of vitality.
Look at who chose it.
Next, number 0155,
Sang Zhi.
Starting height, 1.05 m.
- Go!
- Sang Zhi, good luck!
Go, Sang Zhi!
Go!
- Go, 0155!
- Good luck!
- Go!
- Sang Zhi, good luck!
- Go, Sang Zhi!
- Go!
If she had just jumped,
she would've gotten over.
What the heck?
- Sang Zhi, go!
- Sang Zhi, lift your legs.
- Do your best, Sang Zhi.
- Work on it.
- Go!
- Go, Sang Zhi!
Jump. Don't grab the rod, little demon.
- Sang Zhi, go!
- Go!
- Sang Zhi!
- Good luck!
- Go, Sang Zhi.
- Do your best, Sang Zhi!
Go!
- Go, Sang Zhi!
- Good luck, little demon!
- Go!
Good luck. Do your best.
- Sang Zhi, go!
- Go!
Go, Sang Zhi.
Are you okay?
- Here. Make way.
- Are you okay?
Get up first. Come on.
- Be careful.
- Three, two, one, go.
- It hurts.
- What's wrong?
- This hurts.
- It's likely sprained.
Take Sang Zhi to the medical station.
- Yes.
- Sure.
I'll carry you. Get on.
- Be careful.
Don't touch that leg.
I don't…
Let's go.
Aren't you Sang Zhi's brother?
Hello, sir.
- This is…
- My dad.
Let's go.
- Go.
- Hurry.
Is this your…
- It's all your fault.
- My dad.
I'm so sorry, sir.
Seriously.
Did you hurt your head or your leg?
Am I that old to be your dad?
Can you stop scolding me?
- You've nagged me all day.
- You're so bad at jumping.
You still insist on it. Gosh.
- Okay, stop it.
- I'll tell Dad.
Are you going to rat me out again?
- Stop moving!
- Watch out for her leg.
- I don't want you to carry me.
- How will you walk with a sprain?
Put me down.
- Stop moving.
- Let me carry her.
Sure. You can carry her.
Stop arguing. Watch out.
- Okay.
- Be careful.
- Here.
- Her leg.
Are you okay?
Why is the medical station empty?
Take her there first.
- I'll get someone.
- Okay.
You still talk so much when you're hurt.
XURI MIDDLE-HIGH SCHOOL,
TEMPORARY MEDICAL STATION
Sit down first.
Be careful.
Don't touch that leg yet.
Let me disinfect it for you first.
It might hurt a little.
Bear with it for a bit.
Does it hurt?
Hang in there. It will be over soon.
You're so badly hurt.
What about this hand?
Does it hurt?
Why are you looking at me like that?
What's the matter?
You're nice to me.
Unlike my brother.
All he does is yell at me.
Do you think he isn't nice to you?
He doesn't love me at all.
He doesn't love you?
Didn't you see
how panicked he was when you fell?
He rushed over and carried you in no time.
He doesn't love you?
What's going on in your little head?
But he's always yelling at me.
I'm already hurt,
but he is still yelling at me.
It's an impossible task
to make him stop yelling.
It's all done.
Be careful
with these wounds.
Don't touch them.
Don't get water on them.
How are the wounds?
I've treated the abrasions.
But you had best take her to the hospital
to check the sprain.
Sure. Have a drink first.
Here.
Drink up. We'll go to the hospital.
By the way, hold onto the camera.
Here. Get on.
Your brother has a class in the afternoon.
Only your dad can take you
to the hospital.
I beg of you.
I'll also have to drop you off at school.
How troublesome.
It's fine.
If your dad can't take you to school,
I'll do it.
Listen to your brother.
Get on.
Be careful.
Don't strangle me.
I'll leave you to it.
Let's go.
Wait.
- Why?
- Wait.
Wait.
I can't see.
Help her up first. Be careful.
Proceed with the competition.
- Be careful.
- What are you doing?
Be careful.
XURI MIDDLE-HIGH SCHOOL,
TEMPORARY MEDICAL STATION
He's nice.
He's very nice to me.
But he seems to be nice to everyone.
I'm not the most special one.
Well, that's all for my class today.
Class dismissed.
Sang Zhi, bye.
Bye.
Hello?
Hello, little demon.
Duan Jiaxu will pick you up today.
He will be there in about 20 minutes.
Wait for him.
Got it.
Also, be good.
Don't cause him trouble.
When have I caused him trouble?
All right, I'm just saying.
I have to go. Bye.
Why would I cause him trouble?
Sang Zhi.
Can you come with me to buy something?
I'm not going to tell Mom and Dad.
They're at work.
Coming here would be a hassle.
I already helped you take the day off.
Don't worry.
Here. Hold on tight.
Look at what this is.
I'll unwrap one for you.
Here.
So
did you purposely leave
to buy me some candy?
You wish.
I went to buy water for Duan Jiaxu.
I got one for you in passing.
It was all your fault today.
You call me ugly every day
- and I don't complain.
- That's different.
How so?
I'm speaking the truth.
Go!
I'm not a horse!