[Fated Hearts – Suige's Fitness Results Revealed]
[On-set of "Fated Hearts"] [Working out during breaks]
[Arm strength training]
[A wide variety of workouts]
[Dripping with sweat]
[Drenched in sweat] [Checking training stats]
[Satisfied]
What kind of partnership?
[Running lines]
Looks to me like you're trying to humiliate me.
Push him away.
[And down she goes—gracefully and dramatically]
It wasn't me!
[Frantically proving innocence]
That wasn't me!
I'm being framed!
[Pure survival instinct]
Oh my god—
Slow down!
[Fails to get up]
Touch it.
Go on, touch it.
[Tentative poke]
Qin,
what do you think of Zheyuan's muscles?
I thought they were fake just now.
[Bursts out laughing]
Now Zheyuan's upset.
He's worked hard for years,
sticking to his fitness meals.
So basically, you're complimenting me in disguise.
Actually, that makes me pretty happy.
They look unreal though!
Oh my god.
[Thumbs up for you]
We should add a bathing scene.
[Making a wish]
Let him show off properly.
We've got one, we've got one!
Bathing—
and wiping—
getting a little scrape.
That could work.
That could definitely work.
You've got to see it for yourself.
[Stay tuned!]