ظآزJust To Meet You, you fell for meظآز
ظآزJust to meet me, into my trap you fellظآز
ظآزWanna try a breathless love?ظآز
ظآزEvery move hits the heart, close and sureظآز
ظآزJust To Meet You, you love my playful charmظآز
ظآزJust to meet me,
my romantic little schemes for youظآز
ظآزWanna play another brand-new game?ظآز
ظآزLayer by layer, we close the gapظآز
=Just To Meet You=
=Episode 9=
=Crisis &amp; Proposal=
What's on your mind now?
Jiang Niannian asked about Jiang Xiaodi.
You didn't tell her, did you?
You owe me one.
When you have time,
let me run a few tests.
Haven't you studied me enough?
Now I'm your lab rat too?
If you say no,
I'll dissect her instead.
Her bone structure is excellent.
She's worth my time.
I'm warning you one last time.
Don't you touch her.
If you love her so much,
why did you kidnap her brother?
That wasn't kidnapping.
Someone's after Jiang Xiaodi.
Jiang Xiaodi is safest with me.
And his whereabouts can't leak out.
Jiang Niannian can't see him either.
Only then
will the two of them be safe.
Right now,
I feel like sawing open your skull.
I've never seen
someone this hopelessly in love.
(Renxin Hospital Outpatient Hall)
(Zhong Minghui is already detained.)
(Liu Yexi can't do much now.)
(As long as Xiaodi's surgery succeeds...)
You
were waiting for me?
Hey, handsome,
mind giving me a ride?
My honor.
- Ye Lang.
- Mm.
Are you close with Dr. Zheng?
Renxin Hospital belongs to me.
Dr. Zheng
is our best neurosurgeon.
That's all.
Oh, right.
I remember
you have a brother with brain cancer?
Which hospital is he in now?
Dr. Zheng
is the best neurosurgeon in Manlong.
Wanna transfer him here?
He's with relatives,
doing pretty well.
No need to bother you.
(As if you have any relatives you can trust.)
(Jiang Niannian.)
(When will you really trust me?)
Okay.
If he comes back,
call me anytime if you need anything.
Ye Lang,
is there anything else
you haven't told me?
Niannian.
I need you to trust me.
I'll keep you safe.
(Ye Lang.)
(Can I really trust you?)
You were brave today,
but don't put yourself at risk again.
Alright.
It's just a tiny cut.
Maybe it'll heal by tomorrow.
Even a slight wound
pains me to see it.
Niannian.
You must have
had a really hard time.
When I was little, living with my mom,
I was always bullied at school.
Later,
my mom had me learn taekwondo.
You've had it hard too, right?
I know it's hard for you to trust me,
but I'll do my best.
Ye Lang.
I'm not a good woman.
I can't give you what you want.
ظآزJust To Meet You, you fell for meظآز
ظآزJust to meet me, into my trap you fellظآز
ظآزAre you real, or just a dream?ظآز
ظآزHow did I fall so deep into this?ظآز
ظآزLike a chance encounter in plain sightظآز
Let's not talk about that,
okay?
ظآزYou're as beautiful as the moonlightظآز
ظآزI won't miss you or choose anyone elseظآز
(Li &amp; Murong)
(Could the one who grabbed Xiaodi)
(to threaten me be among them?)
That's Ye Lang.
Just an illegitimate son,
yet he holds the position.
Looks like you
have had a hard time in the Li family.
Even now,
he still goes by Ye.
Feel bad for me?
Feeling bad for a guy
will bring me trouble.
What's this?
This is...
This is Water Lilies.
Monet's Water Lilies.
Is it real?
Sure, it's the Li family.
You even have an authentic Monet?
This painting
was a gift to my fianc├رe Xue.
It was given to me
by my brother's mom,
the renowned artist,
Ms. Ye Mei.
This painting is fake.
- It...
- Fake?
Impossible.
Auntie Ye is such a great artist.
Why would she give me a fake?
The texture of the canvas
is smooth, with no visible grain.
But during Monet's period,
the canvas was coarse,
with visible texture.
This is clearly
a modern fake.
Li Hong.
Don't take this the wrong way,
you're just too kind.
You're the true heir.
Ye Mei was just a mistress.
Would she give you this good thing?
Why not save it for her own son?
You're overthinking it.
Auntie Ye is very kind.
No matter what others say,
my brother and I are real brothers.
A woman willing to be "the other one"
will never be respected.
She's nothing special.
Ye Lang,
calm down.
Don't let them use you.
Reporters are here.
(Brother, after all these years,)
(It's your turn to be looked down on.)
It looks like
she really knows her stuff.
(Copy made at age 12.)
(A copy made at age 12.)
My future mother-in-law
was truly a genius.
At only twelve,
she could replicate Monet so convincingly.
No wonder
one original painting of hers is prized.
I didn't expect
you know art this well.
There's a lot I can do.
Father.
Why don't you go
see if Xue is ready?
Don't mess this up again.
Got it, I'll go now.
I'm Li Zhongtian.
Thank you all for attending
my son Li Hong and Murong Xue's
engagement ceremony.
Here we'll also announce Ye Lang's marriage.
Jiang Niannian is like his mom.
A woman who brings no gain to the family
won't enter the Li family alive,
and won't be buried with them when dead.
Shut up!
Fine.
I'll make an announcement.
Jiang Niannian and I
are officially engaged.
Niannian.
I have a gift for you.
This is
Ye Mei's final painting?
I heard
it's already been valued
at 30 billion on the art market.
30 billion?
Before my mom passed,
she told me
this painting was for my wife.
She wanted me to find someone
I could entrust my life to,
not for profit,
but for happiness.
Niannian.
Will you accept it?
I'm not forcing you today.
I just need your answer.
I only want the world to know my love.
If I do this,
will you be a little more moved?
So romantic.
Hong.
You're hurting me.
Sorry, Xue.
It was meant to be our engagement party.
It's okay.
Even if no one supports us,
as long as I have you, that's enough.
Mm.
(Ye Lang.)
(Why do you always show up)
(at the biggest moments and take all I have?)
ظآزStitched-up lips
tear open a blood-red duskظآز
ظآزYou return reborn,
seeing through all my cracksظآز
ظآزThis tenderness, a trap or a gift?ظآز
ظآزStill, I'd wager my next life on itظآز
ظآزJust for a moment to recognize you againظآز
ظآزYou are the blazing light in my despairظآز
ظآزLighting the edges of my frozen wingsظآز
ظآزI burn myself,
leaping into an illusion of fireظآز
ظآزBreaking free
from dead vines in the ashesظآز
ظآزYou are the brightest star in the nightظآز
ظآزAwakening my dormant fateظآز
ظآزFreeing me from this half-life prisonظآز
ظآزAs the bells shatter the pastظآز
ظآزLife finds its way againظآز