[The Epoch of Miyu]
[Episode 11]
How could it be the towels' fault?
Our hotel has been working with that
towel brand and laundry for over 10 years.
Never once has a guest
had an allergic reaction.
Then maybe the guest
just has sensitive skin.
So she-
Then it's even less our problem.
She's the one with sensitive skin.
What's that got to do with us?
Trying to scam the hotel?
Don't even bother with people like that.
The guests in that room
are a few ladies
from a senior modeling team.
They've stayed here for a long time.
And they're quite easy to get along with.
I really don't think they would-
They stayed a long time, spent a lot,
then right before checkout,
find an excuse
to get their room comped.
Trying to pull a fast one on me?
No way.
Go reply to them.
And be firm when you do.
Tell them there's absolutely
nothing wrong with our towels.
Mr. Feng, shouldn't we
check our towels first
to make sure there's no problem?
Check what?
Didn't I just tell you?
There's no problem with the hotel!
Get this straight, Xu Miyu.
You are a forewoman now.
You need to see things
from the hotel's perspective.
Otherwise, what do I need you for?
But I think I...
Why are you still standing here?
Get to work!
You're just so dense!
Hello?
Yes, it's me.
Yes.
Okay.
Hello, is this Xingkang Testing Center?
Yes. How can I help you?
I have some towels and sheets here.
I'd like to get them tested
for detergent residue.
We're really sorry.
The hotel will definitely
look into this.
Once we get the results,
we'll give you a satisfactory answer.
When will the results come out?
-Yeah.
Don't try to drag this out.
Once this hits the news,
your hotel will suffer the consequences.
Don't play tricks.
Go reply to them.
And be firm when you do.
Tell them there's absolutely
nothing wrong with our towels.
We won't. Rest assured.
Our hotel isn't just any hotel.
We will never brush it off.
We just need some time
to find the root of the problem.
After all, nothing like this
has ever happened before.
Guess I'm just unlucky.
Let's go home.
Fang.
Ms. Xu, you're a nice person,
and you've taken good care of us.
But you can't keep dodging
the towel issue.
[Recording]
Yes.
Fang was fine
before she used your towels
as a pillow for a few days,
and ended up like this.
Yes.
If it's not your hotel's responsibility,
what else is?
I get it.
Please rest assured.
We will investigate this thoroughly.
We're really sorry
for the trouble.
[Recording]
What good is sorry?
Exactly.
Driver, follow that car.
[Test Report]
Mr. Ji, how can I help you?
Take a look at this.
[Test Report]
[Total bacteria count: Failed]
[E. coli: Failed]
This is...
The test results of the hotel bath towels.
So our hotel towels
really are the problem.
That's why the guest
had an allergic reaction.
I'll go find Mr. Feng.
Miyu.
Take a look.
You're in the video.
Someone in the room
had an allergic reaction.
Her neck is all swollen.
A towel allergy?
You must give us
an explanation today.
Our hotel isn't just any hotel.
Nothing like this
has ever happened before.
Guess I'm just unlucky.
Ms. Xu.
Rooms 1806 and 1817 are checking out.
Got it.
Go get Yin Xiang,
and you two go clean up
Rooms 1806 and 1817 together.
She went back to the dorm.
She forgot her phone and went to get it.
What are you still standing here for?
Ms. Xu.
Rooms 1811 and 1816 are checking out.
Got it.
The number of guests checking out
will only increase.
You need to be prepared.
Ke,
go call Luo Qingping back
from her vacation.
Everyone, gather at the Linen Room now.
That won't work.
No one replies
to mass messages.
You have to send
voice messages one by one.
Stay calm.
This is exactly when
you can't act impulsively.
Got it.
Let's get out of here quickly.
I'm never coming back again.
Seriously.
What kind of hotel is this?
It's so disgusting!
Exactly. How can anyone stay here?
I'm so mad!
I'll never stay here again!
[Minhang Road]
Hello everyone. My name is Peng Jie.
I'm here to report serious hygiene issues
with the linen at Purong Hotel.
Last week, my team and I
stayed at Purong Hotel.
[Name: Peng Jie]
Our lead model unexpectedly
had an allergic reaction from the towels.
This is my test report.
[Test Report]
The towels contain excessive bleach.
All three bacteria tests failed.
The excessive bleach incident
at Purong Hotel
has drawn widespread attention today.
According to reports,
a guest developed an allergic reaction
after using hotel towels
during their stay.
A single spark
can start a fire these days, huh?
It's just a towel.
Is it necessary
to make such a big deal out of it?
Go on! Move!
Just shift over a little. Problem solved.
Psycho!
[Wei Siyuan]
[Answer][Decline]
Are you sober yet?
Well, I...
I'm already on my way.
I'll be there soon.
Um,
let me handle this.
Mr. Wei,
I already have a solution.
You better have.
[Wei Siyuan
Call Ended]
How many have you got?
Five already.
That whole row over there—all checked out.
Same here.
I heard the Laundry Room is full,
and the linen carts can't get through.
All stuck in traffic.
-Really?
-At a time like this,
you two are still chatting?
Make way.
Why? What's your problem?
We've been busy since early morning.
And we can't even say a word?
It's not like I made the guests check out.
Step back, Xiaoxue.
Is no one in charge here?
Sorry, my bad.
Come on, this way.
Sorry.
Move forward.
Miyu.
Is there more after this load?
I don't know either.
Room 1808 checking out.
Room 1807 checking out.
Got it.
Alright.
If anyone's gonna break down,
it's not you.
Stop being so whiny.
I refunded my ticket home.
And they charged a 20% cancellation fee.
Then don't come.
It's not like the executive floor
can't do without you.
Go be a college student.
Enough. Stop arguing.
Move this cart out,
then everyone head back
to the Linen Room to rest.
Good work.
Sorry
to call you back while you're on leave.
You already called me.
Save the sweet talk.
Well, when I came up just now,
I saw that the other floors
were a total mess.
Ours is at least... somewhat organized.
You guys are taking a break here?
There's been a lot of drama
on your executive floor lately.
First, Black Card Ji came
and terrified everyone.
Then right after that,
Mr. Duan Jr. arrived
in all his glory,
clearing out
he executive floor in a flash.
And now look,
the whole hotel is having a mass checkout.
All of us other departments
are stuck cleaning up your mess.
Such bad luck.
Well, Xiaoyan,
you can't blame me for that.
I'm exhausted too.
Look at me,
my hands are swollen.
Look at my legs, will you?
I've been standing all morning.
They're like two logs by now.
The bell desk is also complaining.
You executive floor staff
better keep a low profile now,
or you might get jumped.
I actually wish
someone would knock me out,
so I could comfortably
rest in the dorm.
You have no idea—
the executive floor
is covered in linens now.
It's a nightmare.
I don't even dare to go up.
Ke? Ke, are you there?
Please reply if you copy.
They're calling you.
Hurry up and get to work.
It's fine. I'll just pretend
I didn't get it.
I'll hang out with you guys a bit longer.
Aren't you afraid
your forewoman will yell at you?
Miyu wouldn't do that.
We just give her
all the work we don't want to do,
and she'll do it for us.
Your forewoman's that much of a pushover?
Of course.
She didn't earn her position.
So what right does she have to manage you?
True.
Ms. Xu,
the new laundry's
finished linens are here.
Mr. Feng wants them replaced immediately.
Got it.
Four.
Everyone, the new linens are here.
Please do another round of replacements.
Here, let me help you.
Thank you.
Careful.
Okay.
Sir,
how did you get in here?
This is the Laundry Room,
a major work area.
Outsiders are not allowed in.
I'm sorry.
I just want to wash some clothes.
I'm in a hurry to wear them.
Can you do me a favor?
No, no.
You have to follow the process.
Register at the HSKP Department first.
I know the process.
I've worked at Purong Hotel for years.
I'm a veteran employee.
Doesn't matter if you're a veteran.
Our linens haven't even been
sent out to wash yet.
They've been piling up for half a day.
I remember this place
used to be quite efficient.
Why are there so many piling up now?
You know how it was.
Everything used to be well-organized.
But now,
it's a mess everywhere.
It's a wonder nothing's gone wrong sooner.
Didn't the director of the HSKP Department
switch to a new laundry vendor?
So why is it still like this?
It's the same.
It still follows Feng's order.
The director of the HSKP Department
named Feng.
Feng Kaixin.
Look, these linens
haven't been replaced for years.
Just bleached white over and over.
How greedy is that?
Treating guests like fools.
It's criminal.
Just thinking about it
makes me itch all over.
Everyone,
it's okay to take a break.
Later,
let's hurry up and work harder,
sort these linens out,
and put the new linens on first.
Alright?
I really can't do it anymore, Miyu.
I can't even lift my arms.
These are all clean linens.
Who can even tell if we swap them or not?
We might not,
but the guests can feel the difference.
Those from the new laundry factory
are still safer.
Ms. Xu,
can you even tell which towel
came from the new laundry
and which from the old?
The colors are the same.
They feel the same.
What's the difference?
Jia, didn't I just tell you?
We can't just focus
on the surface in service.
Spare us the lectures.
I just want to ask one thing.
This is clearly the higher-ups' fault.
Why do we have to take the fall?
Is it just because we attendants
at the bottom have no voice?
We've been working over 10 hours already.
Is this overtime
or some kind of punishment?
I'm sorry.
I didn't think it through.
Everyone, let's push a little longer.
I'll go fight for overtime pay right now.
Overtime pay?
How can you even ask for that?
You caused this huge mess,
[Purong Hotel]
and you still have the nerve
to ask for money?
Are you out of your mind?
Mr. Feng,
it's clearly stated
in the employee handbook
that exceeding regular work hours
must be compensated by the hour.
Wh-What compensation?
You drove the guests away.
I should be the one
asking for compensation!
The guests left
because of the linen issue,
not because of us attendants.
How is it not the attendants' fault?
It's because you gave them bad service
that they started nitpicking the hardware.
If you had swapped them out more often,
how could there
have been an allergy issue at all?
The guest's allergic to bleach.
The more often we swap,
the worse the allergy gets.
And regarding the linen issue,
I've been keeping you updated.
Stop right there.
Let me tell you, Xu Miyu,
don't give me that.
I made you forewoman.
It's not for you to manage upward on me,
but to manage the people below you
and manage yourself!
What about our overtime pay?
Still on overtime pay, huh?
Do you want to quit?
Anything else?
Nothing.
Everyone.
Let's call it a day.
Go back and rest.
Ms. Xu,
did we get our overtime pay?
Clearly no chance.
I knew it. Empty promises as always.
Ms. Xu, I can't take the night shift.
Don't. I'll take it.
Earlier today,
the famous Shanghai Purong Hotel
was exposed by self-media
for excessive bleach in its linens,
causing severe allergies to guests.
The incident is currently
under investigation.
[Imperial Court 28, Pujiang]
Relevant departments
may be involved in the investigation.
Hello.
Please come in.
This way, please.
Chairman Wei.
I knew you'd come.
If not tonight,
then tomorrow.
Purong Hotel
is currently
facing a critical PR crisis.
I know you won't stand by and do nothing.
It is indeed very difficult
to achieve the condition of
turning losses into profits of over 30%
within a year.
But securing Kuanli's investment
is a turning point for Purong.
You don't want to just
give Purong Hotel away.
Purong
can't lose this bet.
I'm prepared to take drastic measures.
Based on my observations recently,
drastic measures might not be enough
for the current Purong Hotel.
We might need to make severe sacrifices.
First, we must reform the system
to change the hotel's mindset
from top to bottom.
Then cut off corrupt collusion.
By rectifying internal corruption,
we must break the profit chains
that severely drain the hotel's wealth.
The first to go
if the HSKP Department.
Beyond the linen issue
making headlines these days,
the toiletries in the HSKP Department
also have
channel and management loopholes.
Of course, these are just
the surface symptoms.
Once the profit chains are cut,
their mutual protection network
will start to crumble.
Then we sever the interpersonal collusion.
Corruption is ultimately about
managers stealing from their own posts.
The root of the problem
lies with the people.
If management itself isn't solid,
Purong Hotel's disease can never be cured.
My nephew
just doesn't know how to run a hotel.
I invited you here this time
to help him pull up the weeds
and clean up the backyard.
We can't ruin Purong Hotel's reputation.
[Total Attrition Rate]
[Analysis of Attrition Reasons]
The attrition rate is so high.
It's all the reporters
stirring up trouble.
It wasn't a big deal at first,
but some meddlers hyped it up.
Since that's the case,
we might as well
let nature take its course.
Arrange a media briefing
to appease all parties.
That's a good idea.
But we should plan in advance what to say
and how to say it at the meeting.
We can't have any more trouble.
I'm here.
Everything is sorted out.
Zhigang.
Mr. Wei, I've changed
the laundry supplier.
You can trust me to handle things...
What's the use of
changing the laundry supplier?
I told you a long time ago
to focus more on your work.
And what did you do?
All you know is drinking every day.
Now look what you've done,
causing such a huge mess.
How am I supposed to
explain this to the Old Madam,
and to the old folks on the board?
Tell me!
Well,
how about this?
I'll find a few guys
to warn the troublemaker
and make him withdraw the complaint.
You watch too many movies!
Purong Hotel is such a big hotel,
and you want to play gangster?
Alcohol must have ruined your brain.
Kaixin, just drop it.
An allergic reaction
like this has never happened before.
[Home] [Recommend]
At this point,
there's no putting it out.
All we can do is steer public opinion
so it doesn't blow back on us.
Shift all the media attention
[Home] [Recommend]
onto her.
After all, she is the one on camera.
And the words came out of her mouth.
We might as well
turn this bleach incident
into her personal behavior.
Like being careless at work
and irresponsible to the guests.
Then,
we will deal with her internally.
Play it down and smooth it over.
Too...
Forewoman of the executive floor?
Just promoted.
Why?
Does she have someone backing her?
She...
She works for Old Madam.
You don't know my aunt.
She looks kind,
but she is an absolute businesswoman.
She is very ruthless.
The trouble is at her doorstep now.
As long as you handle this matter well,
she won't say anything about it.
[Monday, January 6th,
7th of the 12th Lunar Month]
Ji Feng went to see the chairwoman.
It's just that you took
on this role in a crisis
without even a proper ceremony.
You flatter me, Ms. Wei.
It's my honor
to help Purong Hotel
at such a critical moment.
Your current achievements and abilities
prove that I wasn't wrong about you.
Being able to repay your kindness
in recognizing my talent
is my opportunity and glory.
Do you need me to escort you
to your new post tomorrow?
The hotel is currently
at the center of public opinion.
If you go, you'll just give
the reporters more to talk about.
It's better if you direct things remotely.
The time for the press conference is set.
9 a.m. tomorrow.
I'll personally oversee the venue setup.
As for the Communications Department,
I told them to draft
a press release first,
find some influencers to post it,
and stir up some buzz.
[Aunt]
Aunt.
Siyuan.
A new general manager
will take office tomorrow,
to deal with this crisis.
I invited him back from abroad.
He is very experienced.
You should know him.
His name is Ji Feng.
Do you remember him?
[Ten years ago]
Aunt,
why?
You promised me.
You said you'd give me
the recommendation letter.
Why did you go back on your word
and give it to someone else?
What I told you
was that I would think about it.
I was almost on my knees.
What else do you want me to do?
Some nobody foreman
just shows up out of nowhere
and takes what's mine?
Why is that, Aunt?
You'd rather support someone
who has nothing to do with you
than help your own nephew!
Wei Siyuan!
Over the years,
I have been carefully cultivating
useful talents.
Ji Feng is capable and ambitious.
He came to me himself
for a recommendation letter.
Of course I am willing to build
this good relationship for Purong.
Then why couldn't that person be me?
Am I that useless to you?
Do you really want
to learn something by going abroad?
You fool around outside all day.
How can I feel at ease
letting you go abroad?
Hello, Siyuan?
Aunt.
Okay, I got it.
Welcome, friends from the media.
Please get your press badges first,
then ahead,
you will see our sign-in area.
Just sign in there.
If you need anything,
you can come to me anytime.
Yes, get your press badges here.
Thank you.
[Purong Hotel Cloth Safety
Media Exchange Meeting]
Hello, hello, hello.
[Sign-in Desk]
[Purong Hotel Cloth Safety
Media Exchange Meeting]
[Sign-in Desk]
Hello, everyone.
Welcome to today's program.
[Boyuan TV]
Right now, I am inside the Purong Hotel.
As you can see,
we're at the sign-in desk
for Purong Hotel's
linen safety media briefing.
[Tuesday, January 7th,
8th Day of the 12th Lunar Month]
[Welcome to Purong Hotel]
Mr. Wei.
The press conference is about to begin.
As for the speech,
are you sure you don't need one prepared?
No need.
I know what to say.
Okay.
I'll go keep an eye on the venue.
[Purong Hotel]
[General Manager's Office]
Ji Feng? You're here.
Come.
Please, have a seat.
You came just in time.
I got a call from Aunt last night.
You have no idea—it felt like
a huge weight was lifted off my shoulders.
It was such a relief.
Ji Feng.
We were in a hurry last time we met,
and there were things I didn't get to say.
In the past,
we had some misunderstandings.
Let this cup of tea be my apology to you.
I hope you can let bygones be bygones
and help Purong.
Mr. Wei, you're too polite.
I've long forgotten about the past.
I came back to learn from my seniors.
What seniors?
How can I compare to returnees like you?
What happened these past few days
is a real headache.
My subordinates and I
can't manage it at all.
Then how do you plan
to deal with it, Mr. Wei?
We...
Come in.
Mr. Wei, the press conference is ready.
Okay, I got it. You can go.
Did I come at a bad time?
Not at all.
You came at the perfect time.
How about we walk together
and talk on the way?
Okay.
Come on.
After you.
Please.
This press conference
is making such a big scene.
Everyone from the grassroots
to the leaders has to attend.
What exactly is going on?
I don't know.
Mr. Qian spent the whole day yesterday
in Mr. Wei's office.
I guess the matter
is not small.
Why do you care if it's big or small?
It's not our place to worry.
Just go in and listen.
[Purong Hotel Cloth Safety
Media Exchange Meeting]
Let's take our seats first.
Mr. Wei.
Mr. Ji?
Mr. Ji helped rescue
a heart attack patient
on the executive floor.
Really?
Mr. Wei.
The media is here.
The reporters from Weekend Times
are also here,
and they want to arrange
an exclusive interview with you.
Ji Feng.
I forgot my phone.
How about this?
You take Mr. Ji over there first
and let him sit in my seat.
Is that appropriate?
That's the general manager's seat.
Mr. Ji is the future general manager
of our hotel.
You still think it's inappropriate?
Don't just stand there, go.
Understood.
Mr. Ji, please follow me.
Okay.
I'll be there in a bit.
This way.
This way, please.
What's he doing sitting there?
Purong Hotel's media meeting
is about to begin.
Friends from the press,
please take your seats.
Here to watch the show?
You got a good seat.
Why are you here?
I am the future chairman
of Purong Hotel.
How could I not come
when something this big happens?
Respected leaders, guests,
and friends from the media,
good morning.
It's a great honor
to have this opportunity
to gather with you all
at Purong Hotel's media exchange meeting.
Today,
we will
give a sincere response
regarding the bleach incident
at Purong Hotel a few days ago.
A sincere response?
That old fox Wei Siyuan is absent again.
I wonder which fearless person
will be brought out to do
the damage control this time.
Now, let's welcome
the new general manager of Purong Hotel,
Mr. Ji Feng, to answer your questions.
Who is Ji Feng?
When did our hotel get
a new general manager?
Yeah.
Mr. Ji.
Please.
Good morning, everyone.
I'm the new general manager
of Purong Hotel,
Ji Feng.
I'll keep this brief.
Regarding the incident
where excess bleach in the linens
of the HSKP Department
caused skin allergies in our guests,
after investigations by various parties,
it has been determined to be
a major internal error of the hotel.
Purong Hotel will
take full responsibility.
Please rest assured.
Bring Xu Miyu here.
Hurry up.
Why did the new
general manager admit to it?
What is he trying to do?
Ms. Xu.
Mr. Wu.
Come with me for a moment.
What is it?
I'm sorry
to meet you for the first time
in this way today.
[Purong Hotel Cloth Safety
Media Exchange Meeting]
Regarding Purong's
internal issues this time,
I will never tolerate them.
Here,
I promise to all of you
and the consumers in front of the camera
Purong Hotel
will definitely replace
the problematic linen as soon as possible,
thoroughly investigate
the cause of the accident,
and welcome everyone's stay
with a brand new look
in the shortest possible time.
Go in.
It's her.
She is the person in the video.
That's her.
Yes, it's her.
She's that attendant.
Hello, hello.
Hello.
Excuse me.
Did you run any tests
before claiming there was no problem...
-with the towels?
- What was the situation when the guest fell ill?
Do you ever feel any guilt
when you brushed off the guests?
What's your relationship with
the linen service company?
-Did you profit from it?
-Who asked you to do this?
Did someone else support you?
Did the hotel support you?
Please tell us.
Miss.
You don't have to answer any questions.
[Purong Hotel Cloth Safety
Media Exchange Meeting]
Friends from the media,
I'm the only spokesperson
appointed by Purong Hotel
regarding this incident.
I will answer
all your questions.
Please return to your seats. Thank you.
Thank you for your time.
Excessive bleach
is essentially not a service issue,
but an oversight in executive management.
As for how we will handle this matter,
within 48 hours,
I will give you a proper answer.
Mr. Ji, may I ask
if the excessive use of bleach
is already a tacitly accepted fact
within Purong Hotel?
How long has this been
tacitly accepted internally?
That is a very good question.
What you're asking is exactly
what we'll investigate next.
Well played, Mr. Ji.
You kept it from me for so long.
You clearly didn't see me as a friend.
You misunderstood, Mr. Duan.
It was an emergency.
I was forced into it.
You saw it just now.
I had no choice.
I offered you an olive branch,
but you refused.
And now you're standing against me.
Whatever Wei Wanjun is paying you,
I'll double it.
I'm flattered you think
so highly of me, Mr. Duan.
Then all the more reason
for me to prove myself first
before I discuss my worth with you.
Thanks.
You just want to beat me.
In your dreams.
Ji Feng.
I should address you
as General Manager now.
Why are you standing here?
I...
I forgot to tell you,
I vacated my office for you.
Wait a moment.
Wu.
Mr. Wei.
Mr. Ji is here.
Get the keys and open the door.
Okay.
Mr. Ji,
you're the person Purong Hotel
needs most right now.
To be honest, I thought this would
take a long time, but you're
planning to move fast.
Solving such a thorny crisis in 48 hours,
it's like a miracle.
We're all waiting to see.
Do you have any ideas, Mr. Wei?
What ideas could I have?
I'm completely overwhelmed.
It's a huge mess.
My brain isn't working properly.
But look,
[General Manager's Office]
whatever resources you need,
feel free to use them.
Okay.
Also,
I'm your soldier now.
I'm at your disposal anytime.
Mr. Ji, please.
Mr. Wei, this is...
Secretary Wu.
From now on, he's your secretary.
Feel free to use him.
Okay.
Then please inform everyone, Secretary Wu,
that there will be a full
management team meeting in an hour.
Why are you looking at me?
Mr. Ji told you to inform them, so go.
Okay, Mr. Ji.
Thank you for your support, Mr. Wei.
[General Manager's Office]
Of course.
Do you want me to show you around?
No need.
I'll go change.
See you later
in the meeting room.
Okay.
[General Manager's Office]
Ungrateful.