♪Just To Meet You, you fell for me♪
♪Just to meet me, into my trap you fell♪
♪Wanna try a breathless love?♪
♪Every move hits the heart, close and sure♪
♪Just To Meet You, you love my playful charm♪
♪Just to meet me,
my romantic little schemes for you♪
♪Wanna play another brand-new game?♪
♪Layer by layer, we close the gap♪
=Just To Meet You=
=Episode 13=
=Niannian's Fury & Lang's Confession=
Ye Lang.
Finally!
(If you want to see Jiang Xiaodi,
come here.)
(Renxin Hospital)
Renxin Hospital.
Ye Lang's car.
No.
No way.
Jiang Niannian.
Calm down.
When you find Xiaodi,
the truth will come out.
(In Surgery)
How is it?
Don't worry.
Let me wash my hands first.
(Ye Lang.)
(Really him.)
(Xiaodi.)
(Where is Xiaodi?)
(No.)
(That's impossible.)
The blood bank got units here in time.
Luckily you arrived in time.
(Blood bank?)
(Luckily?)
Being a match for Xiaodi
is incredibly rare.
The surgery went well.
(A successful match?)
After hiding it from Niannian for so long,
we can finally give her a healthy brother.
(Hiding it from me...)
You did a lot.
We need to monitor his post-op condition.
(You did a lot...)
(Post-op condition.)
Alas.
Finally, no more lies to Jiang Niannian.
You okay?
I feel dizzy and nauseous.
Maybe you gave too much blood.
(Lies.)
(Nauseous.)
(It really was him.)
(He's the one who hid Xiaodi.)
(Those sweet words,)
(that true love,)
(all lies.)
(All of it was for today.)
(I was stupid enough to believe)
(that in this world,)
(someone could love me completely.)
(I even sent my own brother)
(straight into hell myself.)
Who are you?
Why are you here?
Jiang Niannian.
Are you insane?
I am.
I'll kill you right now.
Go join Xiaodi!
(This moment)
(has finally come.)
If Xiaodi is dead,
then go to hell too.
(Why?)
(Why has nothing changed?)
(Is this always how we end?)
Niannian.
Listen to me.
Someone, get blood!
Prepare the OR!
Ventricular fibrillation!
Push lidocaine, now!
No blood pressure!
Defibrillation!
Stay calm, 1mg epinephrine IV!
Another shock!
Why?
Why did the blade go in,
and I still couldn't end him?
Why can't I bring myself to do it?
(Nurses' Station)
Move!
Out of the way!
Wait.
Go check on Jiang Niannian.
Don't let her do anything rash.
Bro, at a time like this?
If he dies,
send the body to me for dissection.
Xiaodi.
This is all my fault.
I'm coming to be with you now.
Jiang Niannian!
Snap out of it!
Xiaodi isn't dead.
Look.
His brain tumor pressed a vessel
and caused bleeding.
We got no enough O-type RH-negative blood.
Even with emergency transfers,
it wasn't enough.
That's why I called
Ye Lang here.
He drew blood himself,
and hold on till your brother's safe.
Really silly.
If anything happens to him,
you owe me a new heart.
(Admission Time, Treating Doctor)
(Zheng Lu)
(Jiang Xiaodi, Admission Time)
After my brother disappeared,
he's been in this hospital?
So from the very start,
my brother was under your watch.
That's right.
That idiot
said someone wanted
to kill Xiaodi,
but he didn't know who it was.
He said he'd be safe here,
and couldn't leave.
And you two couldn't meet.
Can you give me Ye Lang's phone?
I need his key
to confirm something.
Okay.
(Nurses' Station)
(Behave and Jiang Xiaodi will be fine.)
It turns out he sent those emails.
And I stupidly thought
someone was using me to hurt him.
How ridiculous.
Three million.
You have to follow the rules.
Marry the dead?
What's the issue?
No, no issue.
I'll go now.
Jiang Niannian was born tough.
Your family picked her,
that's her good luck.
Yes.
Niannian's been smart since little.
She is sensible,
and won't go back on it.
(Renxin Hospital, Outpatient Hall)
(One Week Later)
Niannian.
How did you get hurt?
Three months ago,
you went to Jiang Feng and Liu Qin
and had them sign the contract to marry me.
And that same day,
you secretly moved my brother
and checked his blood type thoroughly.
This was all your setup!
Ye Lang.
You plotted this whole thing.
No!
I...
Actually,
I was reborn.
In the past, Zheng Lu died in a crash.
Later, Xiaodi died on the operating table.
And I...
I died at our wedding too.
♪For your return♪
Ye Lang,
you're making things up again.
Why not say you're an alien?
I know this is hard to explain.
But hear me out.
I was only in a coma for a week,
but you can ask me
everything that happened
during that one week.
Ye Lang,
you're lying to me again.
♪I can't stand♪
♪So, I'll give in♪
I know you won't believe me now.
But I'm begging you...
♪Why can't you stay?♪
Please, just wait till tomorrow.
It'll snow tomorrow.
If it doesn't,
I swear,
I'll never show up again.
♪I cannot hear you♪
It's June right now.
Check the forecast before lying.
I'm grateful you saved Xiaodi,
but right now,
I don't believe a word you say.
♪Where did you go?♪
♪Stitched-up lips
tear open a blood-red dusk♪
♪You return reborn,
seeing through all my cracks♪
♪This tenderness, a trap or a gift?♪
♪Still, I'd wager my next life on it♪
♪Just for a moment to recognize you again♪
♪You are the blazing light in my despair♪
♪Lighting the edges of my frozen wings♪
♪I burn myself,
leaping into an illusion of fire♪
♪Breaking free
from dead vines in the ashes♪
♪You are the brightest star in the night♪
♪Awakening my dormant fate♪
♪Freeing me from this half-life prison♪
♪As the bells shatter the past♪
♪Life finds its way again♪