May I be like the stars
and you like the moon.
As long as the world remains,
so shall we.
I only wish to stay with the one I love,
watching every sunrise and sunset.
I want to be with you forever.
Eternals and demons walk different paths.
You and she are ultimately different.
Have you ever
truly cared for me?
No.
Never.
In this life and the next, through all lifetimes…
May we live and die together,
and share life and death as one.
[Moonlight Mystique]
[Episode 10]
Oh, right.
You're a Kunlun disciple.
Tell us.
What happened
1000 years ago?
A thousand years ago...
It was a tragedy.
Get to the point.
Back then,
Ling Long, the Saintess of the Fox Clan, entered Kunlun
and fell in love with Rong Xian, the Saint.
But their love was not accepted by either clan.
Eventually, they lived in seclusion, away from the world.
Yet, for some unknown reason,
one day,
Ling Long suddenly attacked Kunlun
and slaughtered the entire clan.
Mr. Rong Xian, upon hearing the news, rushed back.
Not only did he kill Ling Long,
but he also went on a killing spree in Jingyou Mountain
and avenged
Kunlun.
But Ling Long
doesn't seem to be such a cruel person.
Why did she slaughter Kunlun?
I don't know either.
But there's one thing I've heard about.
When Ling Long entered Kunlun back then,
she brought three people with her.
One was her younger sister,
and the other two were her attendants.
Isn't that us three?
Stop stating the obvious.
Since this place
is formed from Rong Xian's resentment,
if we kill him in this illusion,
will the resentment disappear?
No.
Kunlun Illusion is tied to the caster's life.
If you kill him,
you'll only kill the version of him in the illusion.
The illusion won't be destroyed,
and instead, we'll be trapped here forever.
There might be a way out.
If the illusion is formed from Rong Xian's resentment,
then if we can stop Ling Long from slaughtering Kunlun,
we might be able to quell his resentment
and break the illusion.
That makes sense.
So, what...
should we do now?
All we need to do is one thing:
stop Ling Long and Rong Xian from falling in love with each other.
Wu.
Why are you two acting so strange today?
Aren't you usually inseparable?
What happened?
Have you two suddenly become distant?
How is that possible?
They are very close.
-Right?
-Yes.
You three
must protect each other
and prioritize the overall picture.
Now Rong Xian wants to see us.
Remember,
he is the guardian of the Snow Lotus.
We must follow the plan and gain his trust.
What exactly is the Fox Clan's plan?
The beauty trap.
Who will be the beauty?
You?
Me?
Saintess,
please.
Please.
This young lady
is quite different.
Saint, please excuse us.
This is my younger sister, Wu.
It's our fault for spoiling her so much
that she lacks proper manners.
Let me toast to you on her behalf.
Saintess, you are unconventional and poised.
You're quite different from what I imagined
a Fox Clan girl to be like.
How?
The world believes the Fox Clan to be petty,
always haggling over every penny.
But seeing you today,
I feel the world has misunderstood the Fox Clan.
Both of you
are truly generous people.
Kunlun is a righteous sect,
open-minded and inclusive.
You have a sharp eye,
unlike those shallow and ignorant people.
I toast to you
in admiration of your noble character
and trust in my clan.
Oh no.
As the toasts keep coming,
it feels like they really hit it off.
Saint!
Saint,
my apologies for earlier.
I like divination.
How about I offer you a reading
as a greeting today?
That sounds wonderful.
Please, Miss Wu.
This divination technique is quite accurate.
It's called Grain Divination.
If there's anything you want to know,
feel free to ask.
I'll make sure to give you a clear
and correct answer.
Really?
Of course.
In that case,
I'd like to ask you to see
if we are destined to be together.
What?
Are you saying we're in that Rong Xian's
resentment illusion?
Keep your voice down.
Let go of me!
I didn't expect you to be sucked into this realm of resentment too.
Why did you, the Young Master of the Fox Clan,
act so sneaky in participating in the Wutong Martial Arts Contest?
I didn't!
If it weren't for my aunt forbidding me from coming to Outlanders' City,
I wouldn't have had to be so sneaky.
Look what happened now.
I ended up in this stupid illusion
and became a stupid Eternal.
What did you say?
Our Kunlun Sect
is the leader of the...
sword sects,
shining in glory. We're not some stupid Eternals.
Shut up.
Aren't they...
hosting the foxes?
Why didn't you go in?
Master and I are just attendants right now.
We can't sit at the same table as the Saint.
I didn't expect
Master of Bright Moon
to ever be in a position where he couldn't sit at the table.
My aunt is Chang Mei, the Master of Jingyou.
She is one of the three kings.
You can't hit me.
You think
I'm afraid of her?
It's the realm of resentment.
You...
You are Saintess Ling Long?
I've heard a lot about you.
You really are
gorgeous in person.
You are quite interesting.
The Divinity of Kunlun
has heard a lot about the Fox Clan Saintess?
Aren't you afraid of being punished by your sect?
Anyway, I've heard a lot about you.
Where is she?
How are you speaking to the Saintess?
Watch your attitude.
Don't disturb them.
The atmosphere inside is quite harmonious.
It seems Rong Xian has fallen for Wu at first sight.
How about this?
Tonight, let Wu hold off Rong Xian,
and I'll steal the Snow Lotus.
What are you doing?
According to your divination,
I find that we share similar interests.
It's fate.
I'd like
to ask you to read my fortune again.
Would you
like it?
What else do you want to know?
My fate with a girl.
A girl?
Who is it?
Someone...
Someone I've known for a long time.
Known for a long time?
Then it shouldn't be Ling Long.
This Rong Xian.
First, he wanted to know his fate with me,
then his fate with another woman,
and later, he'll fall in love with Ling Long.
He seems to be a weak-willed,
easily enamored playboy.
But that's good.
The more he behaves like this,
the easier it will be for us to break him and Ling Long up
and prevent the future tragedy.
Then tell me,
when is her birthday?
Her birthday is...
Wu!
Where did this rude servant
come from?
I, the Master...
Is this how people from Kunlun behave,
showing such a lack of courtesy to someone they've just met?
Qi,
don't be rude.
Saint, please forgive us.
This servant of Wu
is...
a bit slow-witted.
He only knows to protect his master,
which is why he offended you.
I'll take him back now and teach him proper manners.
It doesn't matter.
Let's go.
After all these years,
she's still the same.
The Master of Bright Moon fell into the illusion
to save Ms. Bai.
Although the Saint is a true gentleman,
their being alone together
would inevitably make Master suspicious
that Ms. Bai is in danger.
With his temper,
he might cause trouble.
Get it straight.
You are a servant from the Fox Clan now.
If you go in there and stop Fan Yue,
aren't you helping the outsiders?
All you do is make trouble.
Me?
f it weren't for you causing trouble at the Yi Clan Tomb,
we wouldn't have entered this realm of resentment.
Are Kunlun disciples really this vengeful?
Does the Fox Clan
never admit their mistakes?
Rong Xian almost wiped out the Fox Clan.
How is it wrong for me to kill him for revenge?
It was your Saintess who almost wiped out Kunlun.
-Don't make a move.
-I'm going to punch you.
It's the realm of resentment.
-What are you doing? Let me go!
-Let's go.
-Let go of me!
-What are you doing?
The Elder wants to interrogate him.
Follow up.
Interrogate him?
I've already figured it out.
Stop pretending.
Could it be that…
she has figured out we're impostors?
Qi,
you little brat.
You and Wu have been keeping this well from me.
Tell me.
When did you two
start liking each other?
Sister,
it's not what you think.
Wu,
stop explaining.
I've lived for more than 100 years. How could I not see this?
Just now, when Qi heard that Rong Xian was interested in you,
he rushed right in without a second thought.
Even a fool can tell
he cares about you a lot.
He even dared to challenge the Kunlun Saint for you.
Such a fiery spirit.
I've underestimated you all this time.
Young Chief,
you misunderstood.
Why are you so shy?
I think Wu quite likes you too.
You almost ruined our plan just now.
But during this whole time,
she didn't criticize you for your reckless actions.
What does it mean?
It means favoritism.
Only someone who likes you
would protect you like that.
Am I right?
Come on.
Sister,
you really misunderstood.
We're not what you think.
Misunderstood?
Then let me ask you,
when you're in danger,
who do you most want to protect?
When you're bored,
who is the first person you think of?
When you're happy,
who do you want to share it with the most?
When you're sad,
who do you want to talk to?
When you truly like someone,
you think of this person all the time.
Aren't you like that for each other?
Of course,
sometimes the person involved might be too confused
to realize it,
but others can see it clearly.
Qi,
although you're just a servant,
our Fox Clan has always been open-minded
when it comes to love.
Since you two are already in love,
I'm happy to support you.
How about this?
I'll carry out the beauty trap myself.
You two go to the back mountain and steal the Snow Lotus.
If she goes,
it'll be terrible.
No!
Sister,
I like Rong Xian.
I'll go.
Alright.
Stop saying things against your will.
I can't sacrifice your happiness
just to complete the mission
and send you to another man.
It's decided.
Tonight, I'll hold off Rong Xian
while you two go to the back mountain and steal the Snow Lotus.
If you manage to get the Snow Lotus
and make a great contribution,
when we return to the Fox Clan, I'll make sure to speak to the Chief
and appoint you as an Elder.
That way,
you'll be worthy of Wu.
Although Rong Xian already has someone he likes,
the Fox Clan's seduction techniques are unmatched.
How can Rong Xian resist?
So, we need to hurry.
The sooner we get the Snow Lotus and complete the mission,
the sooner we can take Ling Long back to the Fox Clan.
The shorter the time Ling Long spends with Rong Xian,
the less likely they are to fall in love.
I'm still here.
Stop being so lovey-dovey.
Let me remind you,
don't let love
ruin our big plan.
Qi and I will go to the back mountain now.
We'll definitely bring the Snow Lotus back.
The conflict between
the Eternals and demons has been ongoing for all this time,
and Kunlun and the Fox Clans have also been at war endlessly.
Your proposal of peace talks this time
is quite strange and suspicious.
Do you really think Kunlun will believe you?
Tell me.
What is your purpose
in entering Kunlun?
El...
We are truly here for peace talks.
You're full of lies!
You,
beat him up!
Yes!
How dare you!
How dare you, fox demon,
play tricks in front of our Elder?
Speak up!
Let me tell you,
don't do anything reckless.
If we can't break the illusion,
none of us will be able to leave.
Just wait.
When I get out...
Then you should wait until we get out first.
I haven't tasted the sweet dew,
but I've already smelled the sacred fragrance.
Saint, you arrived on time.
This is your invitation,
so I naturally couldn't be late.
If I'm not mistaken,
this tea smells like
the Fox Clan's Nine-Color Flower Tea.
You sure know a lot about the Fox Clan.
That's right.
Nine-Color Flower Tea
has a delicate and refreshing fragrance,
best brewed with water derived from thousand-year-old ice.
I specially brought some
to share with you.
The thousand-year-old ice
can be sourced endlessly from Kunlun.
The purest part
lies beneath the Snow Lotus.
Saintess,
would you like to see it?
If you hadn't mentioned it,
I wouldn't have known.
Kunlun and the Fox Clan have never been on good terms.
Are you really so at ease drinking tea
that I brewed?
You came from afar for peace talks
to bring
tranquility to the countless lives
of both the Fox Clan and Kunlun.
You're such a noble person,
so you would never
engage in despicable deeds.
I've misjudged you with a narrow mind.
Your doubt
is quite understandable.
Just as I too want to ask you—
did you really come here
with no other intention?
Isn't my intention to seek peace
for countless Fox Clan members enough?
I've heard of Saintess Ling Long's heroic qualities for many years,
and seeing you today
I can confirm those words are true.
I have long admired you
and have always wanted to come to Kunlun to see
what Saint Rong Xian of Kunlun
truly looks like.
Now that you've seen me,
what do you think?
Even the stars in the sky
cannot hide your brilliance.
By the way,
I heard that
the old Chief of the Fox Clan is seriously ill.
How is he doing recently?
The old Chief is blessed
and has strong spiritual power.
With the treatment of the Fox Clan's holy healer,
he has fully recovered.
Thank you for your concern.
That's good.
Kunlun is full of suspicions.
The Fox Clan entered the mountain,
but the elders are all avoiding us.
Bei Chen and Mu Jiu also seemed to have disappeared.
But the longer we wait, the more complicated it will become.
We can only give them this one night
to spend together.
Once we get the Snow Lotus,
let's take Ling Long and leave Kunlun as quickly as possible.
The Snow Lotus!
Wait.
Is there a trap?
Let's go!
The Fox Clan is indeed crafty.
They used the peace talks as a cover to steal our treasure.
Fortunately, the Elders have already made preparations.
Today,
you won't be able to go back.
Capture them!
Yes!
Oh no.
Wu and Qi were discovered.
The Elders had already made arrangements around the Snow Lotus.
You won't be able
to save them now.
You knew our plan all along?
Did you come tonight
just to watch me fail?
Ling Long,
you really don't remember me?
Hurry!
Someone is coming.
Come with me.
The old Chief of the Fox Clan is seriously ill.
I know you're here for the Snow Lotus.
Take it.
Leave Kunlun now.
No.
Wu and the others are still inside.
I can't leave.
Leave Wu and those two attendants to me.
I will send them back to the Fox Clan safely.
But since you knew I was lying to you,
why are you still helping me?
Ling Long,
Kunlun is not where we first met.
I've known you
for a long time.
Do you remember
ten years ago,
in Qingling Mountain,
when you saved a severely wounded Eternal?
Ten years ago?
It was you?
At that time, I was ambushed by demons,
severely injured, and fell off a cliff.
My face was covered in wounds.
It's normal that you didn't recognize me.
If you hadn't taken care of me for three days,
I might have died at the bottom of the cliff.
The reason I didn't tell you
when we met again today
wasn't that I wanted to deceive you intentionally.
I just...
just wanted to spend more time with you.
Although Kunlun and the Fox Clan have been enemies for years,
I have always hoped the two clans could reconcile.
The two clans have a deep grudge;
someone has to take the first step.
So,
take the Snow Lotus
to save the old Chief.
But if Kunlun finds out
you helped me,
how will they deal with you?
Don't worry.
I am the Saint after all.
At most,
I'll just get scolded by my master.
I won't die.
I won't forget
your kindness today.
If there's an opportunity in the future,
I'll repay it.
What happened?
Why are we suddenly here?
They...
We were still a step too late.
Emotions in this world are truly unpredictable.
Some feelings may take a thousand or ten thousand years to develop,
while others
might arise in the blink of an eye.
Why is it changing again?
It's Rong Xian's obsession leading us.
Everything in this illusion
changes according to his key memories.
Where will we go?
I don't know.
Qi.
What's wrong with you today?
You've lost five rounds already.
It's...
Sister, don't misunderstand.
He was just too tired last night and didn't rest well,
so he spaced out.
I see.
It's not what you think.
It is.
Last night...
I was too tired, so today I feel a bit weary.
I understand.
You're young,
full of energy.
I can understand.
Here.
You took back your card again.
What do you mean "again"?
Haven't you done it before?
I haven't.
Not taking back cards
is a noble act.
Yes.
You are noble.
Then why don't you cook?
For the past month,
I've been the one cooking at home.
That's because you refused to wash the dishes first.
So now you want to bring up old grievances?
I've been the one doing the laundry.
That was me.
You always forget to collect them.
How can you lie?
Even if I did collect them,
you'd still throw them all over the place,
and I wouldn't be able to find anything!
You, the Saint of Kunlun,
are lazy and don't know life at all.
That's because I have order in my chaos.
When have I ever failed to find something
when you asked me to?
You always forget our anniversaries.
Who has hundreds of anniversaries in a year?
You have secret money.
With a fierce wife,
this is my last line of defense and dignity.
Actually, these are not important.
Shut up!
You don't love me anymore.
What I saw just now
was the Saintess of Fox Clan and the Saint of Kunlun?
You saw an ordinary couple.
They say that marriage is like a tomb.
That makes sense. They didn't deceive me.
This should be the place where Rong Xian and Ling Long
lived in seclusion, which Bei Chen mentioned before—
Carefree Valley.
They've grown so tired of each other already.
It shouldn't be hard to break them up.
Sister,
I really feel for you.
You gave up your position as Saintess for him,
enduring public criticism.
But what about him?
It hasn't been long,
and he's already speaking to you harshly,
with no patience at all.
The Saint of Kunlun,
pure and untainted, the best of his time?
I think men are all bad.
He's not that bad.
Wu,
you're still young.
What you see now is just romance.
But when two people live together for a long time,
it's never just about romance and passion.
In the end, it all comes to a simple life.
Although he's not good at cooking,
he knows I always sleep in,
so he always gets up early to prepare breakfast.
He always puts things everywhere,
but whenever I can't find something,
he always manages to find it for me.
Although he can't remember
all our little anniversaries,
he always prepares
a thoughtful gift for me,
never repeating.
Even if he forgets,
he always makes it up to me.
When you think about it,
all these little things
are the happiness in our ordinary life.
Marriage
should be like this.
Besides,
I've already...
Qi,
did you see that?
Married women
are really scary.
Who has
100 anniversaries in a year?
And after using
any ornament in the house,
it must be put back in its exact place.
If I get it wrong, she scolds me.
She doesn't even let me save any secret money.
Isn't that terrifying?
Terrifying, right?
Yes.
So my advice is,
you should return to Kunlun
and continue to be the Saint.
How can I do that?
For me,
Ling Long left her clan,
abandoned her position as Saintess,
and came with me to live in this secluded place.
How can I abandon her?
Besides,
she often breaks bowls
because she thinks I'm too tired from cooking,
and she breaks them
while fighting with me to do the dishes.
Remembering every single one of our anniversaries
shows how much she cares about me.
Not letting me save secret money
is because she's afraid I'll sneak out to buy alcohol
and get spotted by Kunlun and the Fox Clan.
With such a wife,
I have nothing more to ask for.
No.
I have to coax her now.
I didn't manage to persuade Ling Long.
How about you?
No.
Bei Chen said that
not long after Rong Xian and Ling Long lived in seclusion,
the Fox Clan and Kunlun encountered problems.
Fan Yue,
we don't have much time left.
What do you think of Rong Xian?
He became too talkative after getting married,
but he is also kind,
righteous,
and noble.
And he is deeply devoted to Ling Long.
As you can see,
Ling Long gave up her position
as the Chief of the Fox Clan for Rong Xian.
But why did she suddenly go to wipe out Kunlun?
What happened a thousand years ago
that led them to this point, where one of them must die?
I was wrong.
It's always like this.
You have to argue with me,
and then I have to apologize to you.
Yes, yes.
It's all my fault.
There's something
I want to tell you.
What is it?
It's a letter from Kunlun.
Open it.
Actually,
if Kunlun really wanted to stop us from being together,
they would have found us
long ago during these three years.
[Master is seriously ill and on the verge of death. Return quickly]
What happened?
The letter says
that my master is seriously ill
and nearing the end of his life.
I have to go back to Kunlun.
Don't worry.
I'm just going back to see my master.
The Kunlun Sect Leader has treated you like a master and a father.
You should go back.
By the way,
what did you
want to tell me just now?
I'll tell you when you come back.
Just go.
I'll take care of things at home.
Three years?
Why is it already three years later?
I still haven't finished beating that Bei Chen.
In this realm of resentment,
time changes without any logic at all.
I wonder where those three were sent.
Am I
going to stay in this stupid illusion
for the rest of my life?
Why is he back?
Master.
You've been gone for three years,
and you're finally back.
I'm sorry.
During these three years,
the Eternals and Demons have been fighting incessantly.
[In Harmony with Heaven and Earth]
Kunlun has been guarding the boundary between the two races,
and the responsibility is immense.
Rong Xian,
I don't have much time left,
but Kunlun now has no one capable of bearing such a heavy responsibility.
You are my only disciple
and the Saint of Kunlun.
Only you
can inherit the position of Kunlun Sect Leader.
Master,
the dangers and evil of the world
do not have just one source.
Not all demons are evil and should be eradicated.
Nonsense!
Demons are wreaking havoc in the world.
They should be eradicated.
The Eternals and the demons have been fighting for over a thousand years.
The casualties include not only demons
but also Eternals and Kunlun disciples.
Why don't we stop the war
to prevent the world from being flooded with blood?
Eradicating the demons
and protecting the people is Kunlun's duty.
Rong Xian,
don't forget,
you are the Saint of Kunlun.
I've left Kunlun for a long time,
and I no longer want to get involved in the conflicts between the two races.
As for inheriting the position of the Sect Leader,
I can only let you down.
-Rong Xian!
You don't want to take on the position of the Sect Leader
because you can't let go of that Fox Clan Saintess, right?
It's true that I don't want the slaughter between the Eternals and the demons to continue,
but it's also true that I can't let go of Ling Long.
Ling Long and I
swore to be together for life.
I will never break that promise
and betray her.
Since you can't let go,
I'll make the decision for you.
[In Harmony with Heaven and Earth]
Master,
what are you doing?
Eternals and demons are destined to fight each other to the death.
Rong Xian,
you are the hope of all Kunlun.
I cannot allow you
to abandon your sect
and the Eternal Race
for a Fox Clan demoness.
In order to preserve Kunlun's reputation
[In Harmony with Heaven and Earth]
and thousand-year legacy,
I will transfer all my spiritual power to you
and change all of your memories with that demoness.
Rong Xian,
remember,
your parents and closest kin
were all killed by the Fox Clan.
Three years ago, it was you
who deceived Ling Long into going into seclusion,
all to make
the Fox Clan lose their strongest heir.
[In Harmony with Heaven and Earth]
You have never loved Ling Long.
You only have hatred
and murderous intent toward her.
My parents and closest kin
were all killed by the Fox Clan.
I have never loved Ling Long.
The Demon Race deserves to die.
The Fox Clan deserves to die!
Is this
the true reason Rong Xian slaughtered the Fox Clan?
I must hurry back to the Fox Clan
and tell them everything.
Stop!
You were spying outside the Sect Leader's room.
Take him away!
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
Move!
Sister.
I haven't seen Rong Xian all afternoon.
Where did he go?
He went back to Kunlun.
Why did Rong Xian suddenly go back to Kunlun?
Did you two have a fight,
and he
went back to Kunlun out of anger?
Of course not.
The Sect Leader of Kunlun is seriously ill
and summoned him back.
What's wrong?
Wu,
over the past three years,
you've been living in seclusion with me in Carefree Valley.
I know
that you and Qi are in love with each other.
Why did you suddenly bring this up?
I just feel that Qi is gentle,
kind, and upright.
If you choose him,
I will be at ease.
You've always been a free spirit,
not interested in practicing magic.
Now that
you've left the Fox Clan,
just don't go back.
From now on,
stay in Carefree Valley with Qi
and live as a simple, carefree couple.
Sister,
what happened exactly?
I just suddenly feel
that my little Wu has grown up.
Let's take a look!
What happened?
-Get up.
-What happened?
What happened?
Rong Xian?
Aren't you living in seclusion with the Saintess in Carefree Valley?
Why did you suddenly barge into the Fox Clan?
Did something happen to the Saintess?
Saint,
stop!
Why?
After all this,
haven't you understood?
From the start,
he got close to you intentionally.
You are the Fox Clan's most powerful Saintess.
You were supposed to inherit the position of Chief
and strengthen our Fox Clan,
but he
deceived you into living in seclusion,
keeping you away from the clan.
And while you were gone, he came to Jingyou Mountain
and slaughtered us.
All of this
is a conspiracy of Kunlun!
That's not true.
It's not true, right?
Who would use three years to set up a trap,
spending thousands of days and nights together?
No one would do that.
If I had known you were this stupid,
I wouldn't have gone to all the trouble to scheme for three years.
For the past three years,
every moment I pretended to love you,
I felt
utterly disgusted!
But it's also thanks to you.
If you hadn't trusted me completely,
how would I have known everything about the Fox Clan?
When I was charging up the mountain,
it felt like walking into an unprotected territory.
Miss Ling Long!
Saintess!
Even if these three years were all a lie.
Even if you never loved me.
Rong Xian,
they are all living beings.
How could you bring yourself to do that?
They are just a group of vile demons.
And you.
You're the same.
Vile,
and disgusting.
I am the Saint of an Eternal Sect.
How could I ever fall in love with a demon?
Ridiculous.
There should be an end
between us!
Miss Ling Long!
Saintess!
♫No matter if I'm drunk or not, I just want to be reckless once♫
♫Because love is thrilling♫
Miss Ling Long!
Saintess!
♫If you tear open my heart♫
I have long admired you
and have always wanted to come to Kunlun to see
♫I can hold you a little tighter♫
what Saint Rong Xian of Kunlun
truly looks like.
♫This pain will gradually fade♫
♫Time withers the moonlight♫
But since you knew I was lying to you,
why are you still helping me?
♫All that's left is pitch darkness♫
I won't forget
your kindness today.
If there's an opportunity in the future,
♫I want to tear apart♫
I'll repay it.
♫This sky for you♫
You always forget our anniversaries.
Who has hundreds of anniversaries in a year?
♫A lifetime of guarding everything with you♫
You have secret money.
♫Crossing the abyss to fulfill our vow♫
I'll tell you when you come back.
Just go.
♫I'll leap without a thought for tomorrow♫
I'll take care of things at home.
♫This moment feels like forever♫
♫I've missed too much time in my life♫
♫I'll throw myself into this flame for you♫
♫Even if I'll perish♫
♫At least I can still kiss your face♫
♫Burn out my waning moon♫
♫In exchange for a lifetime of passion♫
Eternals and demons are destined to fight each other to the death.
Why?
All of this is a conspiracy of Kunlun!
You fox demoness!
Long!
♫What kind of flower would never bear fruit?♫
Ling Long!
♫What kind of fruit never sees a flower?♫
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
♫Withstanding the stillness, you are a broken piece of me♫
Our...
child...
♫I am the fruit to your flowers♫
♫Across thousands of miles♫
♫The pain of parting lingers♫
Child?
♫ I light a lamp with no wick to carry me through the rest of my days♫
What child?
♫Flowers in the wind, sand in the water♫
Can't you see
that she's already pregnant with your child?
Children conceived
♫What kind of tree never takes root?♫
by an Eternal and a demon
are naturally flawed and hard to carry to term.
♫What kind of roots never turn into trees♫
She has expended a great deal of her own spiritual power to sustain the baby.
Otherwise,
she wouldn't have so easily died under your sword!
♫ To break the roots of love, to look at the past and seal one's heart ♫
Rong Xian,
what you've done
is unforgivable!
♫I'm your wanderer♫
It was me.
♫The flowers flew away♫
It was me
who killed our child.
It was me who killed Ling Long.
♫My tears are streaming down like rain♫
Why?
Why did you do this to me?
♫Light my heart's lamp, cast away attachments, and ask the world♫
Why?
♫On the vast sea, you and I♫