I'm really anxious
that something might happen to our child
if he accepts that job.
Can we talk?
You probably heard
Mom and Dad's conversation last night.
It's because Betchay saw you.
You know how it is in our house.
No secret stays hidden.
Everyone there is such a gossip.
They're so into gossip.
They're so annoying.
But your mom and dad are right.
Dad's offer for you to work for him
wasn't really in good taste.
You know what?
That's what I felt at first.
Should I feel flattered or insulted?
Doesn't he want his daughter
to date a waiter?
Did he offer me the job
so I could look good in front of you?
-Of course not.
-Exactly!
Why would I think badly of your dad?
But of course, I also wanted to refuse.
But you said it yourself,
it's difficult to be a waiter.
Especially in Prague.
Especially during winter.
It's really cold there.
And I really don't like the food there.
No offense, okay?
But that goulash?
It's like a stew
that lacks attention and love.
The Czechs might attack you
on social media.
You're right.
But between the two of us,
I'm not a fan of goulash either.
But if you think about it,
your dad's okay.
The truth is, his offer is actually good.
First, it's a decent job.
Second, it's based here
in the Philippines.
I'm closer to my family.
Right?
But Mikoy…
You said it yourself,
that our worlds are completely different.
Are you sure this is what you want?
Are you sure about the complications
you're getting into?
There's only one thing
that's certain in this world.
Every decision you make in life
comes with no guarantee.
That, I'm sure of.
But you're right.
We absolutely have different worlds.
We grew up with different lives.
But…
Do you know what gives me courage?
What?
You.
Even if I don't know
what will happen tomorrow,
or the day after,
or in the coming years or months,
I just know
that I will regret it
if the one knocking
on the door of my life,
I wouldn't open my heart to them.
I know that…
everything happens so fast.
I hope you'll give me the chance to…
love you.
It's not actually fast for me.
Honestly…
It's slow for me.
Your moves are so slow.
Oh my goodness!
Kids these days are different!
You're kissing in front of the church?
Get married first!
Wow, pretty girl!
Yes? What's the problem?
Uhm, Kian here…
He is stable, but not out of danger yet.
The doctor said that
the next 48 hours will be critical.
They are on their way here
from the province.
How did this happen?
Do you have any idea who did this?
This is my fault.
Bok.
Agent Kian knows
how dangerous our mission is.
Just like you.
All of us at the agency.
We will do everything
to bring down the Moravianos.
Okay?
Bok!
Alex! Where are you going?
we still don't have
a breakthrough on the Moravianos.
It's very difficult
to build a case against them.
It's as if they are always a step ahead.
And they already know our every move.
I disagreed with what you did in Prague.
But…
what you did paid off.
I believe
you now have eyes and ears
inside their organization.
I don't even know
if having a spy in the syndicate
will be useful.
This Mikoy could prove to be very critical
in your mission against the Moravianos.
But right now, the Moravianos
are being very careful.
They don't make mistakes,
so they're hard to break.
His name is Jethro Salamangkero,
also known as Jepoy.
I don't care if he has a whole battalion.
Especially if we are right.
And most especially
when the one they wronged
is one of our own!
Move now.
Hello. Hi!
Oh yes?
But…
did you think about that
when you killed a police agent?
I thought he was a nobody,
just a pawn of a rival syndicate.
My problem is that
you did not finish the job.
I made sure when I shot him,
I went back to him,
I checked,
he was really dead.
Le Morte Bianca,
But all our plans will be ruined
Our plans will not be ruined.
So, my suggestion is,
let it be.
Yes.
What do you think happened here?
So before he could confess,
they silenced him.
You know, this would have been
a big breakthrough for us.
Especially if they found out
that one of their consiglieri
was already in our custody.
That's why they had to silence him.
They don't want noise.
They don't want trouble.
That's why they don't want attention.
Is that why the Valtrovis
are here in the Philippines?
Do you think Viktor did that?
I wouldn't be surprised
if he were also the one
who killed Mr. Salamangkero.
He is probably
the most dangerous criminal we will face.
He's heartless. He's soulless.
His core is evil.
Hold on. There's my sweetheart!
Wait a minute. First of all,
I would like to say sorry to you, Chiara.
I hope I didn't hurt
your feelings too much.
That's okay, Auntie.
Mikoy and I have already talked.
We've cleared things up.
But, in-law, your concern is very valid.
That's why, Mikoy, you know…
we're not that different
in terms of background.
Back then, I had nothing, too.
I was just a simple caregiver,
until I met my Viktor.
And then life got better.
Wow, sweetheart. I'm so proud of you.
You don't even know.
But I'm sure you will be very,
very successful in your new job!
Thank you.
Also, he will not only be
hardworking in his job.
I'm sure he will do everything
to make your company a success!
And I feel like I'm seeing
someone blessed
who will stand up and represent
the Pinagpala family.
Here it is.
Give us a speech, Mikoy.
Thank you for this opportunity.
And I promise
I won't let you down.
Anyone else want to say something?
I need to report to Agent Alex.
Mikoy?
Of course.
I'm completely fine.
I'm very happy.
Come on. Let's celebrate.
Don't lie anymore.
Just by looking at you,
I know you're not telling the truth.
What are you hiding, Mikoy?
Because I can't help you
if you won't tell me.
As soon as you talk to Viktor,
let me know immediately.
And if you get new information
that you think we need to know,
call me right away.
It's because…
I really can't do it.
What? You can do it.
Mikoy, you can be the COO
of Dad's company.
That's what you're scared of, right?
That's what you're unsure of?
If you think
this is a huge responsibility,
that you don't have enough experience
to run a company…
Darling…
You think Papa hasn't done
research about you?
You think he will appoint you as COO
without knowing your background?
What do you mean?
I heard Uncle and Auntie.
But it's hard for them to believe.
How can a waiter run
an international company all of a sudden?
Usually, it's not believable.
But in Mikoy's case, he's very capable.
However, the school closed.
So, he wasn't able to finish studies.
That cake business
used to be under a lot of debt.
But since Mikoy started running it,
he managed to turn it around
and make it profitable.
That's why I don't think you should worry
about becoming a COO.
You just have to believe in yourself.
Thank you for the vote of confidence.
It's actually hard.
It feels like yesterday
I was just a waiter.
And then, now,
I suddenly became a COO.
You know what I mean?
Look at me.
Will I qualify as a COO?
You know what? You think
too little of yourself.
Isn't this over the top?
And is the private jet necessary?
I'm scared.
It suits you.
You look cute.
Where are you going?
Huh?!
What are you doing here?