[Episode 1]
[Yumi's Missing Cells]
Hello, sir.
What are you doing?
Looks like you just came from the bathhouse.
Your skin's glowing.
Man Sik, you got a new car?
Never seen this one before.
My daughter bought it for me.
- Yumi?
- Yeah.
I told her I didn't need it,
but she bought it anyway.
Man, I heard Yumi makes serious money.
So what, one page of writing
equals the price of this car?
What? That's what people are saying?
Yeah.
It's not that much.
But yeah, she does pretty well.
Having a successful daughter, that's the best.
That's not my money, though.
Come on.
Same thing.
- Oh, right.
- Yeah?
Did you see the article yesterday?
No, why?
Yumi did a newspaper interview.
[The Queen of Romance,
Author Kim Yumi Interview]
See? The Queen of Romance,
Author Kim Yumi Interview.
- She looks great.
- Right?
[We'll be cheering on your future books too!]
[Keep it up!]
Hello.
Hey, Su Jin! What's up?
- Off to class?
- Yes.
When's Yumi's new book coming out?
She's working on it.
She said that months ago,
but it's been over three months.
She's probably super busy.
Lots of interviews and stuff.
Plus, they're making
another drama based on her book.
So there's like a press conference
she has to attend, too.
Anyway, it'll be out soon.
Please ask her when it's starting.
My whole class is waiting.
Alright, alright. I'll give her a nudge.
- Go on.
- Bye.
Okay, see you.
Take care.
Man, seriously...
They can't even wait a few nights, huh?
Writers are people too.
They need a break sometimes.
Good grief...
Let's see.
[Love you, Dad]
[My daughter]
Is she busy?
- Hello?
- Oh! Yumi?
Dad!
Hey, where are you? Why can't I hear you?
Dad, I'm on a plane!
- A plane?
- Yeah!
I'm on a plane!
Why are you on a plane? Where are you going?
I'm going skydiving.
What?
S-k-y-d-i-v-i-n-g.
"Sky..." What?
Wait, what about your writing?
I'm here for research.
The main character
falls in love with her instructor
while skydiving.
That doesn't mean you have to go skydiving!
We're about to take off. Please hang up.
- Okay.
- Yes.
Dad, I'm here with the producer. Don't worry.
I'll call you later, okay?
Oh no.
Writer Kim!
Yes?
Do you really have to do this yourself?
You could totally write
the "falling for your instructor" part
without actually jumping.
He's already holding onto you like this...
See, right?
- Sorry?
- I mean...
Just get a feel for it
and maybe head back down?
Right now?
What is it?
- Oh no.
- Oh my.
No way!
Right now!
How about canceling?
You're the one who told me to do this!
You said I'd get the feel if I tried it!
No, no, I...
Can we cancel now?
- I can't do this!
- Let's go!
- No, no!
No, no, seriously, I can't!
- Please!
- Sir! Sir!
Wait, wait!
- Writer Kim, please save me!
- Three, two...
One!
- Let's go!
- What?
Wait, I can't! Hold on!
Wait, my helmet! Tighten my helmet!
Wait a second!
Let's go!
Ready, set, go!
What is happening?
What is this?
We survived.
Everyone okay?
Hey, Writer Cell!
What the hell was that?
Do you have to go this extreme to write?
This was it.
So this is what it feels like.
I was wondering
if you could actually fall in love
while skydiving.
So?
Did you get what you needed?
Can you write it now?
No.
What?
There's no way you'd fall in love
in that kind of chaos.
[I don't know]
I need a different setup.
Hey! Just to figure that out,
Yumi had to risk her life?
You used to write just fine without this.
I don't know.
Now I can't write unless I go this far.
Beats me.
Hey!
Hello!
- That's so cool.
- Fresh and tasty today...
- Hi!
- Oh, welcome!
Dae Yong!
Come on, hurry!
- Honey.
- Yeah.
You've got the car key, right?
- The key? I don't have it.
- Yes, you do.
- You used it earlier.
- Did I?
Oh, here it is. Sorry.
- I'll open it.
- Let's go.
- Look at you, so cute.
- Alright, hop in.
Let's go.
- You packed everything, huh?
- Yeah.
Did you cry that much?
Where do we go first?
My mom's.
We drop Ran off there first,
then take me to Yumi's studio.
Got it.
And you're stopping by the hospital,
then the publisher, right?
Okay, perfect.
Mornings are a battlefield.
Don't overdo it.
You mean don't have too much fun?
- I'll call you.
- Okay.
Hello.
Who is it?
Writer Kim, it's me.
You're here?
Oh my.
Look at you.
So dedicated to your craft.
I just made coffee. I'll pour you some.
Yes, please.
This is nice.
Hey.
I heard Hemingway once said,
"If you want to write about life,
you've got to live it first."
You even know Hemingway?
Come on.
I've been married to
a publishing editor for three years.
The sparrow near a school sings the primer.
You know?
So...
you know how Hemingway,
the guy who chased "real life," ended up?
He shot himself.
Hey, don't worry.
I'm no Hemingway. Not even close to that level.
I just couldn't write, and PD Yoon said,
"Maybe you'll get a feel for it
if you try skydiving?"
So I did.
That PD's the problem.
Why would they send a writer to do that?
How's PD Yoon doing?
Broken toe. That's not healing anytime soon.
By the way,
why can't you write?
I don't know.
You've already had four hits.
You're a legit hit writer.
Just relax and write.
Even if one flops, who cares?
You're just feeling pressure.
I don't think it's pressure.
Then what is it?
You're not worried about money,
and you're not tied down with a kid like me.
You can sleep whenever,
go wherever you want...
You've got this amazing studio view,
fans waiting for your work...
What's the problem?
Maybe it's because I have no worries.
Are you kidding me?
Sorry, but it kind of feels like that.
Having no problems...
is the problem.
How do I put it...
Life just feels...
kind of dull.
Then go on a trip.
Like Europe or something.
I already did that.
And?
It was nice.
"Wow, this is great."
And that was it.
Like skydiving.
I was moved.
For a moment.
It was incredible.
But...
once that moment passed,
I just wanted to come down.
There was no...
real impact.
Like your trip?
Like that.
Honestly...
it's because
you haven't dated in forever.
- Dating?
- Yeah.
Hey, you're a romance writer who doesn't date.
Of course you're stuck.
You need to start dating.
You know, Dae Yong said
there's a whole line of guys
he could set you up with.
Yeah, but...
It just feels like a hassle.
I've seen the guys, they're all great.
Still, it's a hassle.
Why though?
If someone asked me
to go on a blind date right now,
I'd say yes a hundred times.
I don't know.
Everything just feels kind of boring.
Why?
Here's why...
Because a lot of cells
in the village disappeared.
As the Prime Cell and Writer Cell
grew stronger...
Little by little,
cells started vanishing.
Where'd they go?
Hey, Emotion Cell.
Wake up.
Why?
Where's Love Cell?
I can't find it.
Love Cell?
Is it gone too?
Two disappeared just last week
and now Love Cell's gone too.
Where is everyone going?
Actually...
Love Cell has been really bored lately.
Every day is so boring.
Yumi hasn't dated in three years.
No wonder it's got nothing to do.
So where did it go?
Did it run away?
Love Cell!
True Heart Cell!
No-Way Cell!
- Where are you guys?
- Pride Cell!
- Love Cell!
- Please, come out!
Love Cell, True Heart Cell!
Where are you?
Careful.
Love Cell, True Heart Cell.
Where are you?
What is that?
What is it?
I don't know.
There's something in our village
even I don't know about.
What is this? Why is it so cold?
Is this... a cancer cell base?
Wait, does Yumi have cancer cells now?
No.
That doesn't seem right.
Love Cell?
Hey, Love Cell!
It's a freezer facility.
What does that mean?
Cells that aren't needed anymore
get dragged here and frozen.
It feels flat.
If I had to sum it up,
it just feels flat.
No matter what I see or go through,
nothing really hits me.
Nothing really makes me mad.
Exactly.
That's why you need to date.
But here's my problem.
I actually like it this way.
- What?
- I don't really have those anymore.
Getting mad, getting excited, nervous...
all those emotional ups and downs.
It's so comfortable.
Like before,
when my emotions would go crazy
that kind of thing,
it just feels like too much now.
Hey.
You've got a serious problem.
Your body's in your 30s,
but your heart's 80.
That might be true.
Wait, that's it.
You're totally dried-up.
Maybe I am.
You've just got it too easy.
I'm seriously jealous of you.
Hey,
when do I get to stop worrying about money
and raising a kid?
About 19 more years?
- 19 years.
- Oh my...
I've got to go.
- Okay.
- Going down.
First floor.
I wish I could feel that "flat" life
just for one day.
Take care.
I'll call you.
Yes, Editor.
I Da just left.
Oh, okay.
How's PD Yoon doing?
I'm dying over here.
Ms. Seulgi, hold on a second.
Yes.
- That silly guy?
- Are you okay?
He's got a cast on, so he'll be better.
But it'll take about a month.
I hope he gets better soon.
You know, I told him to help you,
not jump out of a plane with you. That's silly.
Oh, hey.
Thanks.
So I told her...
"Writer Kim,
I'll go first."
Then I jumped,
and right behind me, she was screaming.
Anyway,
I definitely got the full skydiving experience.
Well...
PD Yoon will need some time off,
so we're assigning a new PD for you.
Someone very calm and rational.
Oh, okay.
He's new, but extremely calm and level-headed.
Honestly, you won't find anyone more composed.
Well...
he doesn't have to be that calm though...
Anyway, got it.
Okay.
Now I get it.
The ones who disappeared
they were all tied to emotions.
Love Cell.
I didn't expect to find you here.
You were incredible.
Guys!
The day is finally here!
Go get True Heart Cell.
- Hooray! Go Yumi!
- Guys, I'm getting dizzy.
Naughty Cell...
You fell asleep too.
No chance for Yumi to feel that way lately.
Let it all loose!
All Yumi needs is a bed!
Yes!
Kiss!
Tongue Cell, you too.
You used to be on fire.
Nice to meet you. I'm Yumi's tongue.
We used to listen to music
and dance together.
Yeah.
Now that Yumi's life is stable,
even Hysteria is gone.
Hysterical Cell!
All that stuff we held in,
let's blow it all up, Yumi!
Burn it all down!
- Everyone!
- Run!
Yumi hates this kind of thing.
It's too much for her. No way, no way.
Right now...
Yumi doesn't really hate anything,
but she doesn't really love anything either.
- ♪ Call out to me ♪
- ♪ Let it out loud ♪
♪ Through the pain and sorrow... ♪
Five o'clock!
Target spotted, totally Yumi's type!
She doesn't even look for someone
to date anymore,
or even guard against it.
- I might end up here soon too.
- What?
I've got nothing to do these days,
and I keep getting sleepy.
Before Love Cell disappeared,
it kept saying it was tired too.
No!
If you fall asleep too,
what am I supposed to do?
But I'm sleepy.
Emotion Cell!
How do we wake them up?
Wouldn't they wake up if Yumi feels more?
Is that even possible?
Even jumping out of a plane didn't work.
And now,
a super calm, hyper-rational PD is coming?
Then Yumi's just going to get even more numb.
I'm coming.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Yumi's assistant writer, Baek Na Hui.
Welcome. Please come in.
Writer Kim! The PD's here!
- Oh, he's here?
- You know what?
The new PD.
He is super young, super tall, super handsome.
Oh my.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kim Yumi.
I'm assistant writer Baek Na Hui.
Yes, I was told earlier.
Come in.
Thank you.
Dae Yong was right.
He literally looks like
"calm" is written on his face.
With this ultra-calm PD,
will even more cells disappear?
[Producer Shin Soon Rok]
PD Shin Soon Rok.
Yeah, I look forward to working with you.
That's a unique name.
Yes.
I bet people called you Rudolph in school.
They did.
Or maybe...
[Strawberry Cream Custard Bungeoppang]
[Episode 2]
I'll head out first.
Good job. See you next week.
See you.
Okay, bye.
Handsome, handsome, we got a handsome PD.
This is going to make work way more fun.
The writing's just going to flow now.
Once Na Hui, the chatty extrovert, left...
Suddenly,
everything went quiet.
My assistant writer...
She's very upbeat.
A little scattered,
but fun to be around.
Yeah.
Right?
Would you like to review the contract?
Oh, sure.
I've already looked it over,
and I'll point out anything
you should pay close attention to.
Okay.
[Producer Shin Soon Rok]
By the way,
have we met before?
Your name sounds familiar.
How long have you been with...
About a year.
Oh, really?
But I feel like we met...
I did introduce myself once,
when I was assigned to you.
Right?
Yeah, that's right.
About three years ago, huh?
Yes.
Oh, but then...
I left the company shortly after.
You're that PD Shin from back then.
We were supposed to meet,
but I heard you'd left.
So you worked somewhere else
and then came back?
Yes.
And now you're assigned to me again.
I guess we're meant to be connected.
Here.
Okay.
They said he's the calmest person ever,
but this is too calm.
Why doesn't he react to anything?
This is so boring.
I'm going to sleep.
Emotion Cell, you're sleeping again?
Everything looks fine.
Okay, then could you sign here?
Sure.
Just sign on the last page.
Thank you.
Would you like something else to drink?
No, I'm good.
Oh, I actually have some chocolate
I got as a gift...
I should get going.
Oh, okay.
- Thank you for the coffee.
- My pleasure.
Did you drive here?
If you need parking validation...
No, I took the bus.
I see.
You said you live in Ilsan, right? Madu-dong?
Yes.
Oh, we live in the same neighborhood.
- You take the 545, right?
- Yes.
Oh, I knew it.
Then I'll see you next week.
Okay, have a good weekend.
- See you.
- Okay, bye.
I'll get going then.
Bye.
He barely talks.
Like, seriously short answers.
Well... I guess that's better than
someone who talks too much.
Short is better than long.
He said he's taking the bus...
Let's wait ten minutes
so we don't run into him.
Ten minutes, right?
You're still here?
I thought you left a while ago.
I did.
- I was on a call.
- Oh, okay.
You take the 545, right?
Yes.
You too, right?
- Oh, yeah.
- I see.
Same bus...
Yeah.
This is so awkward.
I should've said I'm taking a different bus.
Let's put the earbuds back in.
Listening to music would feel more natural...
Absolutely not!
Manners Cell, come on.
The conversation keeps dying.
He only gives short answers.
No way.
You cannot put in earbuds
when you're with someone.
That is extremely rude.
Okay, fair point.
Oh, there it is.
Our bus is here.
How long have you lived around here?
As for me,
it's been over seven years.
About three months.
Oh, not long then.
Right.
What made you move?
Closer to the publishing company?
Yes.
Oh, because it's close.
As for me,
I moved here back when
I was at a noodle company.
The rent was cheap, so I picked this place.
Then I became a writer
and realized the publisher's nearby.
I never thought I'd end up a writer back then.
Oh, I see.
You don't talk much, do you?
Not really.
Being "calm" can be exhausting in its own way.
This PD has a problem too.
Talking too little is also rude.
See? Wearing earbuds would've been better.
I said that's rude!
Listening to music when you're with someone?
How could you be so impolite!
No way!
I can't sleep now, seriously!
Did you see that?
What was that?
Earbuds while walking with someone?
When did you wake up?
Seriously, what is his deal?
That's just bad manners.
Maybe he's just not much of a talker,
so he's awkward too, huh?
Still, that's not okay.
Beats me.
No. I can't keep walking with him like this.
Okay.
First, ask which way he's going,
then we go the opposite way.
- Well...
- Which way...
are you headed?
Me?
Yes.
What? He beat us to it.
What do we do?
Which way
do you think I'm going?
- Sorry?
- Want to guess?
Just kidding.
Which way are you going?
This way...
Oh, then we're going opposite directions.
I'm going that way.
Oh, okay.
- Alright then...
- Bye.
Bye.
That was exhausting.
Weirdly exhausting.
Hello?
Hey, Na Hui.
Our next meeting is at six, right?
Yes.
Can you get there by 5:50?
Yes, of course.
But why?
I think PD Shin might get there early.
- Huh?
- It's kind of awkward talking to him.
I need you there.
I know. He is pretty quiet.
I don't mind, though.
Exactly, that's why I need you.
- Don't be late. Okay?
- Got it.
Okay, see you next week.
That drained me.
I didn't even do anything, and I'm exhausted.
You tired?
If you're tired,
let's get Strawberry Cream Custard Bungeoppang.
When your blood sugar drops, that's the answer.
Let's go.
What? That's PD Shin.
He's not home yet?
Don't say hi. It'll get awkward again.
Let's just keep it low-key.
Guess he's heading somewhere.
Same direction.
[Long way around]
Should we go another way?
No!
[Adds 7 minutes. Store will close]
If we want to make it before closing,
[Fastest route]
we have to go this way.
- Hello.
What?
Is he getting bungeoppang too?
I thought this was my hidden spot.
Guess it got popular.
He'll probably just get Red Bean Bungeoppang.
The real hidden gem is
the Strawberry Cream Custard Bungeoppang.
Ten Strawberry Cream Custard Bungeoppang,
please.
Sorry, but
we're out of
Strawberry Cream Custard Bungeoppang.
These eight are all we have left.
Then I'll take all of them.
Sure.
He bought them all?
Why eight?
Isn't three or four enough?
What about me?
What is happening?
Hi, again.
I saw you from behind.
Oh, Writer Kim.
I didn't know you knew this place.
I thought it was my little secret.
It's really good.
Right?
I've been coming here for years.
Especially,
the Strawberry Cream Custard Bungeoppang.
That's all I get.
I see.
Here you go.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
Okay, done.
- Thank you.
- All right.
Then...
Bye.
That's not just being brief.
That's ignoring her.
My bungeoppang, my bungeoppang!
No manners at all.
Seriously, none.
- Give me my bungeoppang!
- He's not just quiet.
- He's a jerk.
- My Strawberry Cream Custard Bungeoppang...
Maybe he didn't hear Yumi.
He probably missed it.
Excuse me.
They're sold out. Right?
What?
The Strawberry Cream Custard Bungeoppang.
I came for those too.
That was the last batch.
No way...
Even after all that hinting...
They sell out fast.
Right.
So...
No way...
Even with a hint that obvious?
Anyway, I'll get going.
See you next week.
He just ignored me?
My bungeoppang...
He's a tough one.
The day she lost all eight
Strawberry Cream Custard Bungeoppang,
one dormant cell
woke up.
I hate
Shin Soon Rok.
I really hate him!
[Episode 3]
[On the Intelligence of Maltese Dogs]
The only gate into Yumi's Village.
As you all know,
getting into Yumi's heart is not easy.
- Yeah, not easy.
- Not easy.
The password
is super long and complicated.
But that doesn't mean no one can get in.
Right.
Cute ones can get in without a password.
For example...
Like that frog a long time ago.
And today...
Oh my gosh.
Hi, I'm here.
If you don't like dogs...
No, not at all.
Come in, come in.
Oh my gosh.
Come here, come here.
[Open the door]
- Got it. 3-7-2-8-2-0...
- Got it.
You know...
- A Maltese. So cute.
- Oh my.
A Maltese has entered Yumi's heart.
Hi, I'm Yumi.
What's your name?
"My name is Coco."
Coco.
Nice to meet you.
Isn't she cute?
She's even prettier in person.
So cute.
She really is.
Hold on.
Coco, your fur is so soft.
Hi, hi.
What's that?
It's our two-year anniversary today,
and the dog daycare is closed.
Coco's super friendly and fully house-trained.
She's no trouble at all.
Just give her some love
and a treat now and then.
If you're busy, I can ask someone else...
No, I'll watch her. Go have fun.
- I'm off.
- All right, bye.
Mom's leaving, Coco.
Bye-bye.
Okay, secured one dog sitter.
[Spring]
My whole family's out of town, so...
Yeah, go enjoy yourself.
Hey.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
[Summer]
Hey.
I'm on summer vacation starting tomorrow.
Yeah, have fun.
Coco, come here.
[Fall]
We're going to Gangneung.
Have fun.
- Bye.
- Safe trip!
Just as Ruby planned,
Yumi became Coco's sitter.
[Winter]
Coco, look at this.
It's a little jacket.
Writer Kim, how about this one?
I'm going with bunny.
Pick the one you like.
See that?
So cute.
Coco.
Look at this.
Lovely.
"Mom, I'm doing great."
[Spring again]
That was a big one. Yeah?
And so,
on days the Maltese comes by...
Did you sleep well? Here you go.
Your fur looks a bit rough.
I'll brush it nice and pretty.
Oh, that scent.
So golden and thick.
The whole village is buzzing again.
Hey, your paws are so tiny.
Why isn't she here yet?
I told her to come early.
Right, Coco?
Oh, that must be her.
The only problem with dog mom Yumi is...
this person.
Hello, it's Shin Soon Rok.
Hold on.
- Hello?
- Na Hui.
I told you to come early.
PD Shin's here. Where are you?
I got a taxi, but the tire blew out.
- What?
- They're changing it now.
I'll be a bit late. Sorry.
Okay. Be careful.
This is bad, Coco.
You think you can turn on the charm?
- Hello.
Sorry I'm a bit late...
Coco, no barking.
Oh, do you have a dog?
No.
She belongs to a close friend.
I watch her sometimes.
They're on vacation right now.
- Come in.
- Okay.
Coco, quiet.
She's gentle,
just a little timid.
Come in.
Sure.
By any chance...
Do you not like dogs?
Or are you scared of them?
Or allergies or anything...
No, not really.
Oh, that's a relief.
Then could you pet her?
You want me to?
Yeah, she warms up faster if you do.
She might keep barking.
Okay.
See? She likes you.
Does she?
Of course.
You like him, right?
What would you like to drink?
I have coffee, or orange juice.
I'll take juice, please.
Sure.
Stay still.
That's a relief.
At least it started naturally
thanks to the Maltese.
Why does Yumi have to try this hard?
What's his deal?
Exactly!
What a jerk.
The weather's nice, right?
It is.
Did you have a good weekend?
Yeah.
Why don't you ask her too?
If she had a good weekend?
That's basic social skills, Shin Soon Rok!
This isn't your first time
interacting with people, is it?
Let go!
Did you
have a good weekend too?
Yeah.
That's better.
That's how you do it.
I spent the weekend with Coco.
I watch her about once a month,
and we go to this dog cafe.
I meet a friend there who has a dog too.
I see.
When I let her run on the grass,
she runs like crazy.
She's not even mine,
but she's just so cute.
I swear she was born just to be cute.
Isn't she just a Maltese?
What?
She looks like a typical Maltese.
Right. Just a typical Maltese.
I mean, Maltese are cute.
Oh, yeah.
I hate him.
I really hate Shin Soon Rok.
Seriously.
It's been a while
since I've hated someone this much.
Thank you.
Another silence.
We're back in silence again.
Hey, stop trying so hard.
Yumi did her best.
The problem is that jerk.
Oh, she's here.
- Hello.
- Oh, PD Jang.
I ran into her right outside. Sorry I'm late.
Come in. PD Shin is already here.
Hello.
Oh my gosh, what is this?
Is that a Maltese?
Oh, so cute!
Her name is Coco. Isn't she adorable?
She's so cute. Oh my goodness.
- Coco, Coco.
- PD Jang,
what would you like to drink?
I was just about to make coffee.
Coffee for me, of course.
What kind of coffee do you have?
I've got three capsules. Come pick one.
Thank god. The mood finally loosened up.
That's a relief.
This isn't something to celebrate.
Why are we grateful for this?
Hey, aren't you sleepy?
We're about to start the meeting.
You can go sleep if you want.
I'm not sleeping.
I'm watching this till the end.
I really liked this part.
It feels very... stylish.
This is definitely going to hit.
Really?
I liked it too. That part gave me butterflies.
Right? Same here.
It really got my heart racing.
I thought it might not work,
so that's a relief.
PD Shin,
any thoughts?
It's good.
Oh, really?
Yeah, I enjoyed it.
There's just one thing, though.
What is it?
About the Maltese the male lead has...
I think we should change the breed.
Why?
The dog is supposed to be very intelligent.
Yes?
But Maltese
aren't that smart.
Maltese aren't smart?
I thought they were.
Not particularly.
Isn't the smart one a Border Collie?
Maltese
are smart.
When I'm feeling down,
she stays quietly by my side,
and when I'm happy,
she somehow knows and brings me a ball.
She even recognizes her owner
on video calls and barks.
She's really smart.
Don't all dogs do that?
Unless it's a lizard.
Well, that's true.
Even my grandma's mixed-breed dog
does all that.
That's not the same.
I don't raise one myself,
but I do know a thing or two about dogs.
Have you read this, by any chance?
According to Stanley Coren's
dog intelligence rankings,
out of 79 breeds, Maltese rank 59th.
[Maltese: 59th]
59th?
Seriously?
Why are Maltese so dumb?
If it's officially ranked, it must be true.
That's just statistics.
It's different when you actually raise one.
She understands human emotions.
Emotional response
and intelligence are different.
Here's another reference.
"Intelligence is measured by
problem-solving ability and trainability."
So what you mentioned, empathy,
has nothing to do with it.
So...
what you're saying is...
The dog in your story
is basically at genius level.
For that level of performance,
it should be a smarter breed.
That makes sense.
Shin Soon Rok.
You're pretty thorough.
Okay, then maybe we should change it
to a Border Collie...
Hey, stop!
Hey, Writer Cell!
You're really going to accept that
without any pride?
Fact-checking matters.
If it's a fact that Maltese are dumb,
- then it's better to...
- What "fact" are you talking about?
Even if it were a fact,
you can't just agree to that.
He's saying that right in front of a Maltese.
That's straight-up discrimination.
Breed discrimination, technically.
- You don't even know...
- Whatever!
Coco's feelings are hurt.
How would a dog even understand that?
She understands everything.
Dogs can tell just from your tone
whether it's praise or an insult.
That jerk
has the nerve to insult
Maltese owners everywhere?
But...
Border Collies are kind of big.
I think a small dog fits the male lead better.
Then how about a poodle?
Right, poodles are supposed to
be really smart too.
PD Shin,
you know what?
At the 2022 World Dog Master Classic in Brazil,
second place went to
a Maltese named Lucas.
Oh, for real?
"Dog Master Classic?"
Out of 300 purebred dogs,
it took second place.
Which means intelligence can vary
depending on training.
So the idea of fixed,
innate intelligence is flawed.
So Maltese can be smart.
There's no such thing as a dumb dog.
It depends on the owner.
Do you still think
it's common knowledge that Maltese are dumb?
I don't think so.
That was just my opinion.
It's not a major issue for the story.
Then let's just keep it as a Maltese.
Maltese is good. Cute and smart.
Okay.
Look at him back down.
Facts shut him right up.
But was that actually real?
That Dog Master Classic?
I've never heard of it.
Whatever.
He shut up, that's what matters.
Wait, you made that up?
Going down.
Good work.
- Good job today.
- Let's keep it up.
- Bye, Coco.
- See you, Coco.
Take care.
Coco, paw.
Good girl.
You're smart.
See how smart she is?
And he wants to replace her
because she's "not smart?"
Is that even supposed to make sense?
You agree, right?
[PD Shin Soon Rok]
Huh?
Coco, hold on.
Hello?
Writer Kim,
I think I left my document envelope there.
The envelope? One second.
Yes, it's here.
That's a relief.
Would it be okay if I stop by tomorrow?
I can come around five.
Sure, anytime. I'll be here.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Oh, right.
Also...
That Brazil Dog Master Classic
you mentioned earlier.
What exactly is that?
I couldn't find the results anywhere.
[2022 Brazil Dog Master Classic]
Oh, you couldn't find it?
I read about it in an English article.
Could you send me the link?
So he's calm and rational, huh...
Guess that's true.
Annoyingly calm. Annoyingly rational.
Why does he nitpick everything?
That's why you shouldn't lie.
The link?
Yes, I'm just curious.
A Maltese placed second
in a world competition that's interesting.
What's so surprising about that?
Maltese can be smart too.
The Maltese I know...
What do you even know about Maltese?
Maltese...
Don't they eat poop?
[Poop]
At that moment,
another cell
awoke from a long slumber.
Did you just say
a poop-eating dog?
This is just my personal opinion,
but Maltese...
Oh, taxi's here. Sorry.
I'll come by tomorrow.
Hello? Hello?
Coco, don't listen.
Just forget it.
Damn, I feel wide awake
for the first time in a while.
These stairs are brutal. Shit.
What was that? Our Maltese eats poop?
What kind of bullshit is that?
How about you shut that damn mouth of yours?
Why don't you eat it yourself, you asshole?
How does he take all eight
for himself like that?
This place never gets a moment of peace!
I'll take everything you've got.
Shin Soon Rok.
I've got you completely figured out.
PD Shin.
Shin Soon Rok? What now?
Watch out!
How long have you been driving?
She's totally lost it!
Don't come. please.
Writer Kim?