RTNNJ
GLORY
The left side should be lowered.
Mr. Jeong, a little more to the left.
Maybe a little to the right.
JOO YEO-JEONG - PLASTIC SURGEON
Maybe I can touch you with my hand.
Don't be afraid.
I was at the mechanic
and the button fell off my sleeve.
I crawled
like I'm crazy.
They are ugly, aren't they?
My scars.
These are traumas.
If you stumble again,
call me so you don't get worse.
I was at the bottom too. I understand you.
I understand your anger.
Wait, I'll sew your button on.
Come.
Trust me.
I sew better than most mechanics.
Because of what kind of person you are
wanted to learn it?
The device is turned off. Leave a message.
Are you here?
I thought you didn't come home.
I'm going to work.
What is this? Do you remember the past?
I didn't think you'd dig this up yourself.
- Are these your friends from school?
Hye-jeong then
she hasn't fixed her nose and breasts yet.
I could get a breast augmentation too. Do I need it?
Son Myeong-o is not in this photo?
I wonder where he was.
How do you know Myeong-o?
Do you see them often?
Jae-jun and Myeong-o?
Sometimes.
I try on clothes at Jae-jun's.
But Myeong-o doesn't call me anymore.
I'm so embarrassed.
Sometimes he does strange things.
Did he threaten you with something?
With what?
This is not normal.
When I mentioned Myeong-o,
you and Jae-jun asked if he threatened me.
Have a good trip.
RECENT DESTINATIONS:
GOLF CLUB PLATINUM
He met with Jae-jun?
Ha Do-yeong.
Director of Jaepyeong Construction.
Yeon-jin's husband.
Why are you interested in him?
When my revenge one day ends,
I want Yeon-jin to stay
without any allies.
He won't have friends,
parents, daughter or husband.
No one.
No one will love her anymore.
Did you beat him at go?
I am.
Thanks to the teacher.
The code for the front door is 3742.
Maybe the party will be long,
but i want to play go with you.
I'll make a move,
you will come another day and withdraw yours.
I'll know you were here.
You don't have to call me or answer me.
That's how we'll stay in touch.
I don't need more than that.
And I will obey your every command.
Whatever she was looking for.
I will gladly be your executioner.
YEONHWADANG
- Write your name here.
-Good.
- They say this shamanica is good.
-That?
Sorry.
Are there always so many young women here?
Shamanica is obviously great.
I don't know. First time here.
But my friends say that shamanica
offers a solution to the underlying problem.
Fundamental?
Following!
Kang Hyeon?
It's me!
I'm here.
Oil stain. Can you remove it?
No problem.
Want a new button here?
I…
Let it stay that way.
I sent Dr. Jo the potted plant
as a greeting card for the clinic.
And these are letters addressed to the hospital.
Okay, thanks.
One brat.
Maybe he sent me the bills.
CHEONGSONG PRISON
KANG YEONG-CHEON
A PATIENT KILLED THE DIRECTOR OF THE HOSPITAL
SERIAL KILLER ARRESTED
DR. YOO, I'M KANG YEONG-CHEON.
GOOD FATHER
THE SMELL OF HIS BLOOD
VEINS BURST IN HIS EYES
Rotten bastard.
That rotten bastard!
He is 182 centimeters tall
and weighs 75 kilograms.
Let's keep at least a shred of morals, Dong-eun.
Why are you robbing me in a holy place?
I like it here.
Your Heavenly Father can be our witness.
I don't have to count?
Shit, you used to be nobody and nothing.
Now you are educated
and became a fucking badass.
I'll go then.
This fucking scumbag has work to do.
You can't go to heaven anymore.
But I can.
I repented for everything
and now I am saved.
You had a relationship.
Good.
And you should go to heaven when you die
because your life will be real hell.
What do you mean? Aren't we done?
Let me go
or I'll call your father
for him to be our witness.
You little…
Answer me. Do you hear?
Do you hear?!
Hell!
Will we have a class here?
Today you will write a test.
It will be easy, don't worry.
Exit when you're done. I will wait for you.
What kind of test?
I will send you to study in the USA.
I'm going abroad?
Something came up.
I won't be able to teach you anymore.
That's why I want to find you a better teacher.
You're going!
Isn't that too big of a lie?
How will you send me to study in the USA?
Are you rich?
I am. I got a lot of money.
Come in.
STALKING: DO YOU HAVE MONEY?
You were excellent today, Ye-sol.
Like Sonny.
But the one in the pink socks
he doesn't know what fair game is.
He's going to hurt someone.
The one with number two?
Yes, she always brings others down.
Seriously?
Oh, yes!
Dad, next Friday is Open House.
Only for fathers.
It doesn't matter if you can't come.
It's good when dad works.
Oh, no.
I will come
regardless of how much work he had.
Ye-sol, I have a question about your teacher.
Mom doesn't like her.
And you? Do you like it?
She is a friend.
Girlfriend?
Whose?
The teacher is my mother's friend.
From school. Why wouldn't you love her?
Ha Do-yeong?
Why are you asking about Yeon-jin's husband?
I wonder if he's a jerk.
I don't know anything about him.
He's nice, but he's also a badass.
In first grade
there are always assholes like him.
Flight attendants are considered maids
who speak English.
Do you know how many people I beat up?
for that job?
Vera Wang's new dress.
It is cut for a mermaid.
It is perfect for a bride of your build.
What do you think? Is she beautiful?
He's just my type.
explain to me
how can a bastard be nice?
How is he different from me?
It is immediately clear to you that you are a bastard.
But Ha Do-yeong… How can I say this?
You have to take a good look at it to understand it.
No bad intentions.
He is used to commanding others.
That's why he looked at me like that.
You found Yeon-jin's husband? Why?
He found out about you and Yeon-jin?
Hye-jeong.
That?
And if it was, you wouldn't have a chance.
She should know that.
The dress fits you beautifully.
She should get married.
You're too old to find someone else
who will buy you Vera Wang.
Ask your guy
where he had a wedding last time.
He might get a discount as a regular guest.
That's not him?
Want to try on a different dress?
You said this one is the most expensive.
Cut it out. It tightens around my chest!
Rotten bastard.
He is bigger than Yeon-jin.
It's bigger. So what's the problem?
Snow White lived with seven men.
Why?
Because they were extracting gold from the mine!
WHERE DOES THAT FOOL MYEONG-O LIVE?
-The person you called…
- Damn it!
Where are you? You are not at home.
Have you met Do-yeong?
He had the address of your club in his GPS.
JAE-JUN SENT A NEW MESSAGE
Look for my watch if you go there.
He lives in Eulseo Street, no. 34-9.
I don't know the code.
INVITATION
JAE-JUN
Why don't you answer? Where are you?!
You didn't answer me.
I had work to do. Did you see the messages?
Let's meet. Where are you?
I'll hear from you later.
I went to a family gathering.
Ye-sol!
Sorry.
Nice to see you.
I know how to cross the road too.
It doesn't matter. Where's mom?
I'm alone. I came to see you.
What would you like?
Game console? Dolls?
I love stocks.
Samsung Electronics or Kakao.
Please?
I'm kidding.
Mom said to say that
if anyone asks me that.
An eight-year-old understands a joke like that?
You're so fucking...
You are very smart.
You're a genius, Ye-sol. I wonder who.
Who the hell is blowing the horn in front of the school?
I'll cut your hands off!
Can't you see the child?
I decided.
Right now.
I will protect you from now on.
I love you, Ye-sol.
God, it stinks.
What the hell is this?
Did he run away or stop packing?
What a fool.
He stole Jae-jun's stuff?
Fuck!
You should have been in church!
You can pray anywhere and anytime.
I wondered who would come.
Reverend Hye-jeong came.
Crazy bastard! Why are you interested in that?
The perpetrator always returns
to the crime scene.
You didn't know that?
Shut up. Myeong-o isn't here?
- You made this mess?
- I did.
"Knock and it shall be opened unto you."
I knocked and it opened.
Answer to my prayers.
You're going to stink me up.
Damn, I really need it.
If he comes to my wedding
with weird photos, they will screw me!
Why would you want to do that?
Because he couldn't have me.
You know what he said over the phone?
I don't know.
He went on a trip.
On a trip?
Vladivostok?
Why are you going to Russia?
You decided to become a dog?
Will you pull the sled?
What?
Was he serious?
Why didn't he go?
Fuck it! He really didn't leave for me?
- He didn't leave?
- You have his passport.
Why are you always screaming?
I see the light is burning!
Open it!
Didn't you say you were in a hurry?
I have new tenants. Why don't you answer?
What was so important?
- We were at Myeong-o's!
- He might be dead.
Slowly. What did you say?
Myeong-o has disappeared. We were at his place.
Even the landlady doesn't know where she is.
He wanted to move out.
He packed and bought a ticket.
- It's strange.
- Report it to the police.
Why did you call me?
Shall we report? What do you mean?
You can't call the police
because something is strange.
Sa-ra is right.
I'm getting married soon. I can't go to the police.
Then why did you call me?
I have to leave with the report car!
I have a question.
Myeong-o didn't call you
before he stopped answering?
I called him often.
He is Jae-jun's driver.
What day do you mean?
On August 19 or 20.
Why do you ask?
I got a terribly strange call from him.
I was wondering if he called you too.
What was strange?
He called me too.
And you? What did he tell you?
I don't know. He mentioned some kind of gift.
I ended the call.
I was not sober.
Did you get a gift?
Shit, he asked me out!
The asshole told me he loved me
and invited me to Russia!
Did he think I was crazy?
I get angry as soon as I think about it.
Who let him like me?
Think he's up to me?
You obviously messed him up badly
when he did such a thing!
- Punished you!
- Very funny.
I'm leaving.
I'll be in the car. Don't call me.
Well, clearly.
That's how you knew his code was 696969.
And you? How did you know her?
I've been there a few times,
but I wasn't quite myself.
I'm rooting for you two.
Shit, there is no "two of us"!
Saturday, 3 p.m. Cabinet number C7.
Pin: 4885
STORAGE AND DELIVERY
BIOGRAPHY
AN JEONG-MI
Miss An Jeong-mi?
That. I'm glad.
I've heard a lot about you.
I look forward to our cooperation.
Also.
I'm looking forward too.
How do you feel?
Very good.
I sleep well. I started working out.
I hear you opened a practice
in Semyeong. Congratulations.
Thanks.
I regret not listening to you sooner
when you told me to change my environment.
It's good. How do you eat?
There are excellent restaurants in Semyeong.
Does it still calm you down when you hear the rustling?
effervescent vitamin tablets?
I came to say goodbye.
I won't be back.
You are far away, but we meet
once a month.
Is that too hard for you?
Distance is not a problem.
You failed to help me.
What kind of shit have you gotten yourself into?
Watch your tongue, asshole.
They're not shit this time.
It is about something small and precious.
- I want to take it away from someone.
-Small and precious?
A gem?
Are you stealing now?
Damn it, I got robbed!
friend,
listen to me well
Let's cut to the chase.
It's impossible.
- You can't get a small one.
- I can't?
Why? I am her father.
You're just her biological father.
A child born out of wedlock
legally belongs to the married couple.
Her father is Ha Do-yeong.
That's nonsense! I analyzed the DNA.
The match is 99%. It's science!
Why are you wasting your time with that?
The match can be as high as 990%.
If the legal father does not renounce the child,
you will forever be second.
Hell! Can't you file a lawsuit?
You can't file a lawsuit
because you are not a parent.
How come I didn't? I am her father!
Shit.
What the hell kind of law is that?
You can file a lawsuit only if the parents
then they could not make a child,
if one of them was in prison
or on a business trip.
Was it like that?
It's not. They are doves in love.
The father does not abuse the child?
If he was abusing her, why would I call you?
I would call the police.
In that case,
the best move would not be to sue,
but the mother's divorce.
Custody is another matter entirely.
Divorce?
I was with a shaman,
but I didn't discover anything.
I'll go a few more times, so I'll know more.
Anything else.
You're not taking out any more eggs, are you?
Whatever! I'm working!
What is it?
Remember the guys in the rental car?
This time I discovered something.
STORAGE AND DELIVERY
I followed them from the cabinet.
They drove for a while
Bukbu highway.
They went to a motel in Namyangju.
Just when I thought
that I should return,
guess who came.
That! A policeman visiting a shaman
with Yeon-jin's mother.
They are on the same page!
Crazy, right?
I'm not even afraid anymore.
I was thinking something.
If I reincarnate,
I want to be a spy.
Then I'll put on red lipstick
and wear a cool leather jacket.
You can wear red lipstick in this life too.
I think Son Myeong-o
he didn't just disappear.
Bass! Me with red lipstick?
He didn't disappear?
You think it's Son Myeong-o
actually dead?
I think these people
they run errands for Yeon-jin
which are outside the law.
In fact, Yeon-jin does not rely
to the policeman's help, but vice versa.
When you say
"businesses outside the law", you think...
Yes.
That's why Myeong-o disappeared.
He worked on his own
because he couldn't trust me.
He also bought a plane ticket.
That means he met Yeon-jin.
And then he disappeared.
And now what?
What did you want from Myeong-o?
Now we are in the same mess.
Which one of them killed So-hee?
Park Yeon-jin.
Great!
But you know what?
Yeon-jin must know
that So-hee is at Joo Hospital.
Do you have proof?
Can you prove she killed her?
So-hee held this in her hand
the day she fell.
PARK YEON-JIN
Why do you have this?
You were there?
And now you were too.
We are in the same mess.
Damn mother!
This is crazy!
I will ask for a billion won!
Let me know when you arrange a meeting with Yeon-jin.
Then I'll give you a tile.
No matter how much money he got,
everything will be yours.
I want something else.
Something else? What?
Confession of Park Yeon-jin.
If Myeong-o got the money,
it is equal to her confession.
He said he would record the whole conversation for me.
Wait.
So-hee's death was ruled a suicide.
Can her confession
change anything?
That's why I wanted everyone to reject her.
Legally, I can't do anything.
I wanted the world to know
what she did and that she admitted it.
I wanted to be for the rest of my life
feels like it's burning.
That pus drains from her wounds.
He won't be able to laugh or eat,
they will have no more peace.
It means you can't get any more
her confession?
We can't even search
the corpse of Son Myeong-o.
What will we do?
We have to find him.
How?
Relax.
What will the findings tell me?
This is a comprehensive test
to venereal diseases.
You have also added a test for HPV,
so it will reveal both flora and infections.
But nothing else, right?
The documents you requested.
Family ties, diploma certificate
and the findings of the gynecologist.
You could have sent them by text.
Who still carries papers today?
I will review them.
- Which bank are you in?
-Please?
I'll go crazy if you're in the red.
Tell me which bank you're in, I'll do the rest.
Miss Moon?
Miss Moon!
I'm so glad to see you!
How long have we not seen each other?
You have become even more beautiful!
Choi Hye-jeong?
Do you know each other? She is my son's girlfriend.
We went to high school together.
I can't be anymore
so warm to you.
What do you mean?
She has nothing to do with you, Miss Moon.
You're going to hurt me!
Let's eat in the temple.
Please join us.
Unfortunately, I have plans.
Are you getting married?
Congratulations.
I will come earlier next time.
Of course. Go!
I so wanted Tae-uk to marry her.
Damn brat!
Why didn't you even greet her?
She was happy to see you.
I was surprised.
And we weren't too close either.
Excuse me, I'll be right back.
Dong-eun!
We didn't get to talk.
God, what a coincidence!
Nice to see you.
Can we talk now?
Shall we?
What are you doing?
Why don't you call me?
Do you know how many times I called?
Seventeen.
Speaking of which,
do you have something to tell me?
What do you mean?
Why did you see Do-yeong?
You really have nothing to tell me?
Don't change the subject!
Who asked for a meeting? You or Do-yeong?
I didn't call him.
Your dear Do-yeong has come
and asked me where the fuck Myeong-o was.
I asked you something too!
You really have nothing to tell me?
And what?
Dong-eun is Ye-sol's classmate.
And that. But I mean something else.
For what?
Tell me what you want to know.
Are you crazy?
You are crazy.
You are raising my daughter
as if it were Ha Do-yeong's.
Think carefully.
Did you find out after you gave birth to her?
or did you know before that?
I'm interested.
Are you still married?
knowing that the child is mine?
when you left me
did you know
I want to know…
did you love me
If a vein in my eye bursts,
I won't be able to go on the air tomorrow!
- Ji-won.
- Yun-seo.
Han-sol!
Hello, friends!
Seo-u!
We've been seeing each other a lot lately.
We will become friends.
What are you doing here?
I have a secret child.
I'm kidding.
I came to my friend's house.
Not a parent.
I'm glad.
I am Moon Dong-eun,
class teacher of grades 1-2.
She is my friend.
Teacher, Moon Dong-eun.
I heard
that you all went to school with Yeon-jin.
Did she tell you that?
They are not friends.
And you are her friend?
We are close friends.
There are no secrets between us.
I know her well.
I know what her skin looks like.
I want to ask you something.
Have you ever…
lost something precious?
The Open Day begins.
Subtitle translation: Davor Fröbe