Watch on dramacool.club or kissasia.xyz to support Admin
Junxi.
(Episode 10: Love Is a
Secret That Can't Be Hidden)
The vibe in here...
What am I supposed to do?
"Secret Lover"
If you ever laugh at Tuo
for not having a mom again,
I'll kick all your butts.
See if you still dare.
Tuo.
Tuo!
I finally found you.
I chased them all off.
From now on, just hang out with me.
Ignore them.
Maybe it was from that moment on...
that I wanted to always be with him,
to stay by his side.
Running away isn't protecting someone.
One lie leads to a hundred more.
And you end up hurting the
person you want to cherish.
Making them anxious and yourself uneasy.
Are you really in such a hurry?
What am I supposed to do?
Junxi.
Dad, Mom...
We...
We've known for a long time.
You finally said it!
But I haven't said anything yet.
- You haven't?
- Honey, didn't you hear him?
Honey, didn't you hear him?
I was just following your lead.
Didn't we agree?
That when Junxi told us
he and Tuo were dating,
I was supposed to follow you.
Follow you!
So you've known all along?
And you also knew
that Tuo and I are living together,
not just to split the rent,
but as a couple?
Of course.
We know
that you're both responsible kids.
You wouldn't give us
anything to worry about.
Why are you crying?
You must have been worried
we'd disapprove after finding out.
You've been stressing about
this for a long time, haven't you?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for lying to you all this time.
I just didn't know how to tell you
about my relationship with Tuo.
I was afraid you'd be upset if you knew.
I was afraid that after you found out,
you'd be disappointed in me and Tuo.
It's not his fault.
I was the one who told Junxi to lie
and hide the fact that we were dating.
You didn't lie.
You just didn't tell us.
That's different from lying.
Besides,
even though you two didn't tell us,
we already knew.
Yeah, that's right.
Even without you saying anything,
when the two of you are together,
the way you are...
It's like you only have
eyes for each other.
You can't hide it when
you really like someone.
So, after all this time,
I'm the only one in the family
who didn't know you two were dating?
And here I was worried for so long.
Mom, look.
I'm getting a bald spot from the stress.
That's what you get for
running away from home.
You deserve it.
Okay, okay, okay.
It'd serve you right if you went bald.
Go bald.
You deserve it.
You're serious about my brother, right?
Why are you looking at me like that?
I can scowl too.
If we're going to scowl,
let's do it together.
From the moment I realized I liked him,
all I've thought about
is being with him forever.
So you want to get married?
Anywhere he is,
that's my home.
This place is too.
Then why are you
scowling at me, your family?
You've been scowling since we were kids.
Junxi liked you more when we were little.
Of course.
He's my little brother.
Jealous much?
Does Junxi know?
If anything happens,
your big bro has your back.
You little brat.
Stay for dinner tonight.
By the way,
when did you and Dad
find out Tuo and I were together?
Your freshman year of college, I think.
Right, honey?
I think so.
That's when you dragged
me to that parenting workshop.
It was to understand our kids better.
But...
Tuo and I didn't get together
until our sophomore year.
So we were wrong all along?
But, son,
that just means that
before you were even dating,
you already liked him a lot.
Otherwise,
how could we have gotten it wrong?
After what your mom said,
I only just realized
that I've liked you since way back then.
Why is it so messy in here?
Let's clean it up together.
Can we clean it tomorrow?
I've missed you so much.
You just said you liked me.
Where is it?
Why has it disappeared?
What are you looking for?
Did I wake you?
It's time to wake up.
We have class this morning.
What are you looking for?
The ring you gave me.
I'm sure I put it here.
I put it away.
After we moved in,
you never wore it.
I thought you didn't really like it.
This was one of the things
making you insecure, wasn't it?
Put it on for me.
You don't have to force
yourself for my sake.
I didn't wear it because
I was afraid of losing it.
Also, us wearing matching rings
would attract too much attention.
And later,
if you decided we weren't a good match
and wanted to break up,
it would be awkward.
We're not breaking up.
Last time...
Let me finish.
That's what I thought at first.
But when you broke up with me last time,
I realized
I could never break up with you.
(Watch on dramacool.club or kissasia.xyz to support Admin)
I already like you so much
that I can't be without you.
Don't say it.
I'll never say it again.
We still have class this morning.
Let's skip.
After everything last night...
It wasn't enough.
Rock, paper, scissors.
I win.
You go to class.
Scissors.
Rock.
Paper.
What are you doing?
When we get married,
and switch to wedding rings,
only then can you take this off.
Also,
don't you dare leave
this ring at home again.
Let go.
No.
If you don't let go, how can I hug you?
It's a deal.
We'll save up for our future
wedding rings together.
Let's go...
Go where?
To class?
Or to bed?
I thought you'd turned into a workaholic.
Turns out you were just fighting with
Tuo and trying to distract yourself.
I didn't tell you because
I didn't want you to worry.
At least it all worked out in the end.
And your aunt and uncle are so supportive.
That's really wonderful.
Tuo and I promised each other
that we'd work hard to
become better people,
so they won't have to worry about us.
And with so many people supporting you,
you must be really happy.
Xiao Yang Yang.
Is that my lunch?
I got you two packets of spicy radish.
You know me so well.
Han Tuo.
Hold this for me.
Let me see.
Thanks.
Our advisor wanted
me to tell you something.
He's hoping you'll come
back as an industry mentor...
and teach a class at school.
I knew it.
Asking me back for another guest lecture...
I knew there was a catch.
Are you really...
going to reject me?
Han Tuo.
Let's just date, no strings attached.
You like me?
Of course, I do.
Why?
At first, I just thought
you were really talented.
But somewhere along the way...
it started to hurt when I saw you sad.
You don't have to answer right away.
I'll wait for your answer.
I only love Junxi.
Then I'll just have to
wait for your next fight.
And make my move when you're vulnerable.
Even then, I wouldn't choose you.
You deserve someone who truly loves you.
What do I do?
I think...
I'm starting to admire
you more and more.
Tuo.
Watch out!
You borrowed this from He Youmei?
We meet again.
Hello.
Remember.
The design blueprints are due tomorrow.
Okay.
Let's go.
Are you jealous?
Why don't you just tie me
up and keep me at home?
I'll consider it.
You didn't get the hoverboard.
Let He Youmei get it herself.
She almost made you fall.
Talk about a double standard.
Looks like Han Tuo's rubbing off on him.
Now he's a total green-eyed monster.
Then how come you're
not becoming more like me?
What did you say?
Nothing.
Xiao Yang, are you getting shy?
- Say that again.
- I didn't say anything.
What are you doing here?
Your coffee.
Thank you.
I said I was moving to Kaohsiung.
And you just up and moved out.
You even got a part-time
job to support yourself.
You think you're all grown up now, huh?
Why are you so stubborn?
You came all this way...
just to ask me this?
Where are you going?
Between a father and son...
is arguing the only
thing we have left to say?
When I was young,
all I knew was how to work.
You cried a lot as a baby.
I honestly didn't know what to do.
So I left everything to your mother.
She already had postpartum depression.
But I just kept working.
And that's what led to...
her mental health issues.
Right up until our divorce.
I know I was wrong.
But I chose to keep running away.
I always thought...
that providing you
with material things...
could make up for it.
But I was wrong again.
I'm your father.
And I'm the only family you have.
I should have been by your side.
I know.
Dad.
I've wired you your living expenses.
Um...
How have you been lately?
You're up so early.
I know I've always been busy with work.
And that I've neglected you.
That won't happen again.
Let's...
move to Kaohsiung together.
We'll have more time
to spend with each other.
I'm sure your father cares about you.
He's worried about you.
He's only saying this for your own good.
Dad.
I'll come visit you in Kaohsiung next time.
Junxi.
Jeff's looking for you.
Come in.
The 'House of Dreams' project...
you did a good job on it.
HR wanted me to ask you...
if you want to keep working part-time.
You could become a full-time
employee after graduation.
This is from the day of
the configuration error.
It's the login and
modification log for the system.
And the data from before
and after the change.
Cross-reference them, and you'll see...
who caused 50,000
players to get a free character.
Lu Junxi.
I'm not the one who keyed it in wrong.
Talking to Jeff like that
will definitely offend him.
You don't want to work
there after graduation?
It's not easy to find a job right now.
I know.
The old me...
might have chosen to stay.
But now...
I don't want to work for a company...
that makes a rookie take the fall.
They might be the top
company in the industry.
But...
I want to find the best fit for me.
It's like dating.
So has 'the best' come looking for you?
That's not the point, is it?
I'm jealous.
Go ahead.
Eat your heart out.
You're the best one.
Boss.
Your workers are so handsome.
They're not my workers.
He's my son.
Both of your sons are very handsome.
That's right.
They're both heartthrobs.
Nice.
Our dragon fruit is great too.
Ma'am, come take a look.
My dad just said...
you're his son.
After our internships are over...
let's go on a trip together.
Okay.
I think...
that was the moment...
I started to fall for you.
When was that?
Xiao Yang went to buy ice cream.
What's taking her so long?
Why are you crying again?
Daddy lied to me.
Mommy lied to me too.
Mommy really doesn't want me anymore.
Don't cry, don't cry.
If your mommy doesn't want you...
then you don't want her either.
I'll share my mom with you.
And my dad too.
My brother...
I'll share a little bit of him with you.
What about you?
I'll give you all of me.
Forever?
Forever.
I sold myself off when I was just a kid.
I'm not giving you back.
You're mine.
All mine.
Alright, alright.
I'm yours.
All yours.
Forever?
Forever.
What do you want to do next?
No way.
How about we play rock-paper-scissors?
The winner gets to order
the loser to do one thing.
Okay.
Let's play.
Scissors.
Rock.
Paper.
I win!
Han Tuo, you're so done.
Tuo.
Secret Lover - Series Finale