VIEWER ADVISORY:
THIS SERIES DEPICTS MINORS ENGAGING
IN ILLEGAL AND/OR UNSAFE ACTIVITIES.
VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED.
THIS SERIES IS INSPIRED BY
TRUE EVENTS.
HOWEVER, CERTAIN CHARACTERS,
PORTRAYALS, INCIDENTS, LOCATIONS,
AND DIALOGUES HAVE BEEN FICTIONALIZED
OR CREATED FOR DRAMATIC PURPOSES.
THIS DRAMATIC PORTRAYAL
IS PURELY FICTIONAL.
ANY RESEMBLANCE TO THE NAMES,
LIVES, HISTORIES,
OR REAL-LIFE EVENTS OF ANY PERSON,
LIVING OR DECEASED,
OR TO ANY ACTUAL PRODUCT OR ENTITY,
IS ENTIRELY FOR DRAMATIC PURPOSES
AND IS NOT INTENDED TO REPRESENT
OR REFLECT
A REAL PERSON, HISTORY, PRODUCT,
OR ENTITY.
REPUBLIC OF COLOMBIA IDENTIFICATION CARD
8. NO LOOKING BACK
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE
TO VISIT CALI THIS WEEKEND
PLANE CRASH
NO SURVIVORS
CAR BOMB DESTROYS DAS HEADQUARTERS
FOR MY WOMEN
WE RECOGNIZE THE PROFOUND
SUFFERING OF ALL VICTIMS
OF THE ATROCITIES CARRIED OUT BY
THOSE ENGAGED IN THE DRUG TRADE.
IF YOU WISH TO LEARN MORE,
PLEASE REFER TO THE FINAL REPORT
FROM THE COLOMBIAN COMMISSION
FOR THE CLARIFICATION OF TRUTH,
COEXISTENCE, AND NON-REPETITION.