=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 23=
Greetings, Your Grace.
In the end, she had no choice
but to take up the Kunwu Blade
and become the Sovereign of Spirits
feared by all spirits,
following the same path as her father.
♪Spirits are intoxicated♪
♪With obsessions♪
♪Forget the form to achieve♪
♪Yet I can't♪
♪Today, a home is granted♪
♪Joy without grief♪
♪Lanterns light the empty delusions♪
♪All are ferried across♪
♪Spirits are intoxicated♪
♪With obsessions♪
Greetings, Your Grace.
Ever since Simu became the Sovereign,
♪Yet I can't♪
rather, after her parents left,
she changed completely.
Even I found her a stranger.
She was no longer who she once was.
To keep herself on guard at all times,
it was not only her body and flesh;
she even made her heart
turn utterly cold and ruthless.
♪All are ferried across♪
(Sovereign's Hall)
Over these four hundred years,
Simu has done so much for the Mortal
and Spirit Worlds.
But no one has truly reached her,
understood her,
or done anything for her.
Then again, she has no need of it,
nor does she expect us
to give anything for her.
After all, powerful as she is,
there is little we can do
for her.
I see.
She's long accepted her fate:
Born only to die,
she endures eternity.
All she loves fades like smoke.
Only the abyss will endure
as long as she does.
Why?
Are you afraid?
Simu is a very stubborn girl.
From her parents,
she inherited an unbreakable pride.
She warms this world
with her fervor.
That is exactly why I adore her.
Your Ladyship,
am I the first one
to come out of the Prison
with my soul candle
being snuff out?
You are the first mortal to do it.
But the first spirit
was Simu.
The two most powerful spirits
in the Void,
Simu and that one,
once clashed in the Prison.
Both their soul candles went out.
Yet Simu alone, three days later,
walked back out
and relit
the soul candle.
It was a miracle.
As expected of Simu.
One free of desire stands unshaken.
Spirits are bound
by the obsessions they cling to,
so they can't break free
from the Prison's illusions.
But Simu is different.
Obsession isn't what makes her;
love is.
It is still early.
Your Ladyship, tell me more.
Gladly.
If you want,
I can talk without repetition
for three days and nights.
Simu.
I've heard much about you.
I didn't expect you...
Now that you are out of bed,
come with me.
All right.
Where are we going?
Just come with me.
(Graveyard on the Void Mountain,
the Void)
Simu,
this place is...
Over 400 years,
I've had 22 lovers.
These are their graves.
Most of them never knew
who I really was.
The time I spent with them
was on and off,
yet it totaled only 20 years.
This is the first mortal I ever liked
before my father was annihilated.
Wherever
our journey took us,
he followed me there.
His name was...
I can't remember.
I once cared for him deeply,
but now,
I can't even speak
his name aloud.
Duan Xu,
this is who I am.
My life is measured in centuries.
Time will wear everything away.
One day,
I won't even
remember your name,
let alone
the grand tales behind you
or the memories we once shared.
How long could you stay with me?
In the end,
you will be nothing more
than a tiny ripple
in my everlasting life.
Would you
accept that?
It seems
you genuinely like me.
So, I'm genuinely
rejecting you.
Foxy,
you have your dreams.
Your first 20 years were too hard.
From now on,
you should live more happily.
You'll meet a girl you love more,
start a family,
and live a happy life,
with kin you can lean on.
I know you may be heartbroken now.
But in a few months,
you'll let it go.
General Duan,
you're a gifted young hero.
What fine lady could you not wed?
Go back to the Mortal World.
If trouble finds you,
or if you need any help,
just call my name,
and I will come.
Of course.
I wouldn't help you for nothing.
I still have to trade with you
for the five senses.
Did you let me see the Void
only because of our deal?
No.
It was my thanks.
You let me feel that the Mortal World
is better than I ever expected.
So, this is my thanks to you.
You went to Prison to save me yourself.
While I was unconscious,
you stayed by my side
the whole time.
Whenever I called for you,
you would always hold my hand.
No need to thank me.
I brought you to the Void.
It was only right that I do this.
I kissed you.
I held you in my arms.
You never truly punished me.
You knew I could handle much
on my own,
but whenever I asked you,
you always went soft on me.
You are good at pouting and pleading.
Do not dodge the real issue.
What issue am I dodging?
Do you truly
have no feelings for me?
You are not in my thoughts.
After all, soon enough,
I will even forget your name.
Cry if you want.
Just don't cry in front of me.
You are my only spell bearer.
I hope all your wishes
come true.
But I am the wish you can't fulfill.
Take me out
of your wishes.
May you grow wings
and achieve your ambitions.
She fears the sound of thunder.
Now, I know her a little better.
Bad timing.
She's so cruel,
isn't she?
That's what you want, right?
Just a mere mortal.
I knew it would come to this.
He is no mere mortal.
This child is different.
He truly understands Simu.
What could he understand?
Perhaps the things that you never
managed to grasp in 300 years.
You act
as if you understand it all.
Why can't you let Bai Sanxing go
after 300 years?
Worry about yourself first.
Even if this mortal leaves,
do you think Simu will choose you?
Aren't you curious
why Bai Sanxing's soul candle died out,
yet after 300 years,
he still hasn't met annihilation?
That may sound simple enough,
but there aren't many answers.
His soul candle is still there.
That's strange.
Back then,
we watched Simu
snuff out his soul candle.
That mortal's soul candle went out too,
yet it was lit again.
He could relight his soul candle,
likely because he loved Simu deeply.
As for Bai Sanxing...
You suspect me?
Bai Sanxing was madly
in love with you.
Everyone knew it.
That's ancient history.
Before he entered the Prison,
he wanted me torn to pieces.
Why would I light his soul candle?
I'm not out of my mind.
This is very strange.
I'm afraid it may bring trouble.
Tell me.
Trouble for whom?
(This young man)
(is the most special mortal)
(to me.)
(On the battlefield, he was resolute,)
(confident, and wildly proud.)
(There was a self-destructive ferocity.)
(His heart was shattered,)
(with countless old scars,)
(yet he gathered up
the fragments himself)
(and pieced them back together)
(till it beat with fierce,
living warmth.)
(But only before me,)
(when he spoke my name,)
Simu.
(he seemed like a wild beast,)
(offering his throat and bare belly.)
(That day when he was covered in blood,)
(he did more than reach out to me.)
(He placed his heart in my hands.)
(From that moment on,)
(the way he looked at me)
(always seemed to say,)
("You could wound me with ease.")
("I've given you")
("such power.")
(Only now do I realize)
(I was actually afraid.)
This is the first time in my life
that someone has come for me.
♪Wander to the other shore
with the lantern♪
(I'm afraid I can't hold this heart,)
(and it will slip from my hands)
(and shatter on the ground.)
♪As all things turn and flow♪
♪Whether I stay or go, I'm all alone♪
(I want to shield him)
(from the suffering
of the Mortal World,)
(so this heart bears no new scars.)
(For a mortal,)
(the finest life is)
(to rise with power)
(and be happily married)
(with kids)
(and fulfilled ambitions,)
♪A century is like a dream♪
♪Let me journey across them all♪
(instead of being entangled)
(with a spirit like me.)
♪A lone lamp shines on the other shore♪
♪Accompanied by the abyss♪
♪Moments may last♪
♪Love and hate will fade away♪
(I will return his heart)
(to him intact.)
Greetings, Your Lordship.
(Ledger)
This is the ledger
Jiang Ai hid in Xuling Temple.
Now,
I place it in your hands.
How are things with Jiang Ai?
There is no movement yet.
Though you're in charge
of Jiang Ai's affairs for now,
her influence still remains.
Do not underestimate her.
Now,
she still trusts me.
I may as well seize the chance
and....
Do not be too hasty.
Once all is in readiness,
I will bring her down for good
and leave her no way back.
When that time comes,
I will have you
take her place.
You've always kept
your promise to me.
What do you want to do next?
I can help you.
There is one trouble indeed.
I have received word
that Bai Sanxing
is still alive.
Bai Sanxing?
His spirit power is formidable.
Even in the Prison,
he managed to survive.
One day, he will be a grave threat.
I understand now.
I will not let him live on.
Your Lordship,
that mortal has left the Void.
I must have been half-asleep
and opened the door by mistake.
If Her Grace finds out,
I will surely be punished.
Good thing no one saw me.
Always hiding here to read memorials.
Since when did you grow so diligent?
I just sent Mr. Duan away.
He looked utterly heartbroken.
Simu,
don't you think
you were too harsh on him?
He left
this gift for you.
He asked me to deliver it to you.
He said, "Take care."
(Map of the Void)
♪Touched memories linger like shadows♪
♪Scattered reflections
sink into my heart♪
♪If I could ♪
(There is glowworm-like light here.)
(In summer,)
(it'd gleam in scattered,)
(yellow-green lights)
(like jade shining.)
(As the ancients said,)
(rain won't wash away the light;)
(wind will only brighten it.)
(If it were in the sky,)
(it must be a star by the moon.)
♪Hope we'll experience them together♪
♪Before we forget or grow apart♪
♪Even if the day gives way to night♪
♪Grows dim and fades away♪
♪What would come of it?♪
♪I care for no one but you♪
♪I'll come near and run to you♪
♪To heal the deepest wounds♪
♪Miracles, eternity, and radiance♪
(For some reason,)
(by the wall stood)
(a cluster of rose-like plants.)
(In the blooming season,)
(their fragrance will fill the air;)
(their thorns can wound;)
(their crimson blooms vary in shade,)
(like dawn and glow,)
(set off well by plantain.)
(As the saying goes,)
(behind drawn curtains,
one naps at noon,)
(with red rose trellis
and green plantain.)
A Second-Place Scholar indeed.
What a waste to use
your gifts for this.
♪A lifetime is given
for a name to be remembered♪
♪There are passions and pains♪
Scent,
colors,
and texture.
Are you trying to give me
a wholly different Void
as your gift?
♪Even if the day gives way to night♪
♪Grows dim and fades away♪
In this lonely place,
do you mean to leave me life?
♪To heal the deepest wounds♪
Do you truly
♪Miracles, eternity, and radiance♪
have no feelings for me?
♪Walking with you through eternity♪
Foxy,
why go to such trouble for me?
Meng Wan.
Qingsheng.
- Xu.
- Chenying.
- You're finally back.
What are you doing here?
Chenying.
Look at you.
You've become sturdier.
Xu, you jest.
It has only been a month.
It's not that dramatic.
General,
long time no see.
Xu,
you've grown much thinner.
How are things in the army?
Rest easy, General. All is well.
In three days, we'll reach Nandu.
Where is Xiaoxiao?
She didn't come back with you?
She's fine.
She went home.
I should go home too.
Chenying,
let's go home together.
Your Ladyship,
what do you need?
Gently.
Find more male spirits.
Send them all to the Left Hand?
Yes.
You will go as well.
Yes, Your Ladyship.
(Void Valley, the Void)
Who's hiding here and playing tricks?
My Lord, over there!
Come out now.
(Ascension Pool)
Make sure the spirit set to jump
into the pool matches the list.
If there is another mismatch,
jump down yourselves and make up
the number.
Yes.
Wait here.
How dare you devour spirits
without permission?
Jiang Ai.
Your Ladyship.
Your Ladyship,
is something wrong?
Shall I pursue him?
He's jumped into the pool.
How to pursue?
By jumping in?
(Yu)
Why didn't the Lord
of Yuling Temple come today?
He asked for leave?
That doesn't seem right.
The Lord of Yuling Temple
has always upheld the rules.
He never misses court.
Greetings, Your Grace.
The Lord of Yuling Temple
has met disaster
and annihilation.
This...
It was so sudden.
- What happened?
- Your Grace,
even if he was
as stubborn as a mule,
you shouldn't have...
After curfew,
his Lord Token
appeared before me out of nowhere.
I traced the token's spirit power.
It came from the Prison.
When I went to look,
there was no trace of him.
Even Xusheng's memories
were tampered with.
(Yu)
What happened can't be known.
Even Xusheng was tampered with.
Who could be that capable?
You looked deep in thought just now.
Do you have any leads?
I am being punished for my offense.
I have neither men nor power now.
What leads could I have?
I will surely follow Her Grace.
From this day on, send more people
to search the Void.
Your Grace,
who are we to investigate?
Bai Sanxing.
Bai...
Bai Sanxing. Bai Sanxing.
He still hasn't been annihilated?
Well...
Just now in the Sovereign's Hall,
you told Her Grace
you've never met Bai Sanxing.
Why?
Is there a problem?
Let's put aside
how Bai Sanxing
got out of the Prison.
I know Bai Sanxing well.
You are the knot in his heart.
He has loved you for a thousand years.
He's always been unable to let go
of your rejection.
He's tried every way to claim you.
300 years ago,
you lured him into the Prison,
and he wandered lost for centuries.
After he escaped,
how could he not come for you?
He loves me?
I'd say he wanted to master me.
He always longs to claim
anything fine in the world.
Perhaps after he woke up,
something else caught his fancy,
so I was set aside for a while.
But speaking of deceit,
you are
his most loyal Vice Lord.
Now that he's escaped,
shouldn't he settle with you first?
Why did I just hear
you tell Her Grace
you'd never met Bai Sanxing?
I've never met Bai Sanxing.
Neither have I.
Instead of doubting each other,
best pray for yourself.
(Nandu, Capital of Great Liang)
The joy is shared.
Rise.
Congratulations.
It was no easy feat.
Mr. Liu.
General Duan.
General Duan, you've won great merit.
His Majesty will reward you well.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Congratulations, Mr. Fang.
Mr. Fang.
Long time no see.
You've risen fast
and become the Vice Minister of Revenue.
Congratulations.
You are too kind.
You turned the tide
and led your troops
across the Guanhe River,
storming the enemy camp alone,
and taking Awo'erqi's head.
Your merit is unmatched.
His Majesty has summoned you
back to report.
A reward must surely follow.
I offer
my congratulations in advance.
What great influence.
Indeed.
His Majesty arrives.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Long live Your Majesty.
My loyal ministers,
rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
This time,
in our battle with North Chong,
we won a sweeping victory.
For the first time in 30 years,
we crossed the Guanhe River
and reclaimed Shuozhou, Yunzhou,
and Luozhou in one stroke.
This is a great blessing
for Great Liang.
Heaven blesses Great Liang.
Congratulations, Your Majesty.
Now that the army returns in triumph,
rewards should be granted by merit.
Where is Qin Huanda?
I'm Qin Huanda.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
This time, Qin Huanda
has rendered outstanding service.
Reward him with 5,000 taels of silver
and 5,000 bolts of silk.
Further, grant him
the title Duke of Defense.
The Ministry of War
will reward the other generals.
Thank you, Your Majesty, for your grace.
The Ministry of Revenue
raised funds and provisions.
Fang even went
to deliver the supplies.
All meritorious officials
shall be duly rewarded.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Duan Xu took Awo'erqi's head
and should rank first in merit.
But he defied orders
and attacked Shuozhou
without permission,
putting the city's troops and people
in grave danger.
His merit cancels out his fault.
He is stripped of General Tabai
and bestowed
the post of Court Counselor.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪