Oh, I'm on fire again
In New York City
Oh, yeah…
It's been three months since I left Korea,
and I've had the best summer ever
Kitty, this is weird,
You're posing like you're having
- It--
I am choking on sewer steam out here,
Okay,
Wow, That's it, That's super natural,
- That… Yeah, candid,
That's… Wow,
It's radiating, just, spontaneity,
Okay, Let's check out this post,
Wait, whose hand is that?
Did you meet a girl at brunch
That may just be my other hand,
Oh my God, Kitty,
- I am not!
You've seen his Insta,
He's partying
And we've barely talked,
so I need to make sure he knows
Even if it was spent
Whenever my sister needs me,
You're gonna figure this out with Peter,
Maybe,
I don't know, Our lives are just
You know, with his job in California,
and all… all the big publishing houses
Well, lucky for you, when you publish
Those first three chapters? Page-turners,
Kitty!
If you did not want people reading it,
Plus, I had to check if you were,
if I was gonna let you help me write
I told you
- You were right,
Just like how I'm right
So if I go to NYU,
I will be over
Fear not,
On a scale of one to ten,
I feel like I'm gonna really love
You wanna cuddle me at any given point!
You stretched out my shoes
- I'm half a size bigger than you,
I am gonna miss you a 12, Kitty,
Getting to watch you experience
and figure out
I mean, like, that… that…
You know, whatever happens with Min Ho,
I think it's important that you make sure
Mm, Just make senior year count,
I will,
I can't believe I'm a senior,
There's still so many things I wanna do
I know, And that is why I got you
- I love presents!
Regret nothing, remember everything,
- Thank you, sister,
Yeah, you did,
Picture me
Looking so cute like OMG
Dreamin' 'bout ya
Treasure, let's find out…
LJ is right,
So I'm calling it my Senior Sunset List,
In Portland it's tradition for the seniors
then gather again and watch the sunset
So your Sunset List is everything
Oh, I love it!
What do you have so far,
Well, it's a work in progress,
But figure out
have a traditional Chuseok
I was wondering if we would be on it,
And I want to have a conversation
Crap, not Soon Ja, Imo-Halmoni,
- Yes,
Well, you can still call me Jiwon,
I cannot believe you are actually
Does that make me like a nepo-cousin?
Ha ha, Funny,
Kitty, is it pathetic that I'm nervous?
I don't know,
Please, you've got this,
And I've got your back,
- Thanks, Kitty,
It's nice to know
I better go now
I'll see you later?
Annyeonghee-gah-seh-yo!
You had it the first time,
Which brings me to…
…the most pressing item on my list,
Ending the situationship
and lock it in with yet another
Hi, Covey,
I was starting to think that
I can hardly believe it,
I'm really looking forward
I'm looking forward
- What a douche--
Marius!
Okay, I don't know who this guy is,
but he totally just killed the vibe,
Bringing the drama from day one?
I do love to make an entrance,
I do,
Hi!
Oh, Marius, this is Kitty,
- Hi,
I remember you lot
Then you moved here,
- Oh, the Portland Stalker,
Nobody calls me that… anymore,
Well, it's nice to meet the girl who made
Anyways, Kitty and I were about to--
I am dying to get the Four Horsemen
It's senior year, baby,
And I'm single now,
But first, I do need to take a shower,
Please? Thanks,
Sure, Yeah,
Come with?
Miss Covey!
What's a girl gotta do
uninterrupted moment
Hi, it's good to…
Still not a hugger, I see, Copy,
Thank you so much for having me back,
I have so many things planned,
I hope they include focusing on academics
you are woefully behind,
What? How? Classes haven't even started,
As a one-year exchange student,
But now, you'll also have to fulfill
But I am going to graduate, right?
I suppose you can still catch up,
You'll have to make up a few classes,
Registration starts tonight at midnight,
Be on time,
The easy ones fill up fast,
So you kissed her and then went and spent
Okay, that was work,
We lost the Yisoo deal, so from now on,
Meanwhile, Kitty was posting
With guys and girls,
It sounds to me like you're single, then,
Well, technically,
Marius,
'Sup, big Dae!
Good to see you,
- Marius,
You look well,
Yeah, likewise,
Ah, USC coaches go hard,
but better I get used to it now
- It's official?
I'm gonna be a Trojan! Fight on!
- Congrats!
- That's great, mate,
I mean, the band's all back together,
What else have I missed?
Because so far, I know that
with his job,
That's so funny,
- That's good,
Uh, Jin and I are together
Like, the happiest I've ever been,
Great, Well, I'm excited to meet
Actually, Dae and I have discussed it,
so you don't have to worry about that,
You know how cranky I get if I don't get
Yeah, sure,
So what're we all doing
Oh, I have an idea,
We could all watch the sunrise
You know what?
Yeah, but if we really want
I think we should take over
Yeah, I mean,
That means that all the teachers--
All the teachers are gonna be
You know, you do know
I mean, that is kind of perfect,
I just said "kind of,"
And of course,
Yeah, maybe, I mean…
I'm not really a morning person,
Okay, Kitty, you're gonna
I'm inviting everyone to Senior Sunrise,
I don't care if Marius thinks it's lame,
He's lame,
Yeah, Marius is all about Marius,
Which would be fine
I thought Min Ho would want
but now he's all,
Listen, Marius is an acquired taste,
Not that I've tasted him,
Spill,
Fine,
Marius and I used
When he had a girlfriend,
I know, I'm not proud of it,
And the two of us are actually
since he visited me this summer in LA,
- So please, please don't say anything,
But you cannot live with this man,
Stand your ground
I will,
Good, And I'm gonna stand my ground
How could this happen?
You're not coming back to KISS
Kitty, I tried, okay? My mom and I
She found, what, like, five million won
and tuition is 20 million,
What if we sold a few things?
My clothes?
No!
Kitty, this is all I have left
That is not true,
This is just clothes, Who cares?
Do you know me at all?
Yisoo, Valentino, Chanel?
Hello, if we sold this stuff,
You could pay for the first semester,
There is an open bed in my suite,
No, no, Okay, even if I wanted
I'd have to make tuition
and it would take hours
Oh! Min Ho's annoying friend Marius
is having a party tonight
Oh my God, his parties are legendary,
Whatever, The point is,
We'll make an Insta post,
Yuri, It's either
We're gonna do this,
Uh, we need to talk,
I need you to switch rooms with Dae,
Yeah, I… I picked up on that,
You know, you can just ask me directly,
We are friends,
You're right,
Can you please switch rooms with Dae?
See, was that so hard?
But no, I'd rather live with you,
I think we had a really good thing going,
Oh, is Jin the jealous type?
There's nothing to be jealous of,
Then what's the problem?
Okay, Oh my God, Okay,
Okay,
Kitty! Wait up!
Okay, allow me,
You don't have the upper body strength,
- I've seen you try to open a jar,
So, from Instagram, it seems like
you were having a pretty good time
Yeah, I was,
Seems like you had a good time
Yeah, I did, but that was work,
Well, seems like you have
But now that we're back,
Yeah, tell me about it,
Now I have to juggle
Right, Well, at least
I mean, did you know you have to take
Yes, Covey, What do you think
It's a basic graduation requirement here,
Take Korean Media,
Marius and I took it freshman year,
- Mm, Sounds perfect for him,
Yeah, like a fungus,
No,
Chug! Chug! Chug!
Oh!
Fighting, mate!
- Oh, I love a pop-up,
Yeah, it looks like
Indeed, We have tonight
so Yuri can pay for school
When you say living with us, you mean us?
Yes, if that's cool with you?
I mean, assuming we make enough money,
- Can I get a friends-and-family discount?
Sorry you had to resort to this,
It's fine,
It's just stuff,
How much for your boots?
Oh! Absolutely not,
Just stuff, huh?
They're vintage Yisoo,
When Juliana was sent away last year,
Min Ho, let's do
Nah, nah, I'm not drinking tonight,
But surely one shot
Nah, I can't, I… I'm good,
- Shot, shot, shot, shot!
Shot, shot, shot, shot, shot!
- Okay,
Shot, shot, shot,
Shot, shot, shot!
Why is everyone obsessed with this guy?
Did you confront the fungus
Mm-hmm,
I tried, okay?
Never mind,
Look, it's fine, Making a stink about it
and I don't need Marius
But Jin loves you, Q, Just tell him,
- Beat Marius at his own game,
Whoo!
- It's just…
…I think he's my weakness,
- Well, he's not mine,
Whoo!
Still undefeated! Who's next?
I am,
Kathy, you play beer pong?
I do, Care to make this interesting?
If I win, you switch rooms
- Can we talk?
I wasn't aware you were so concerned
Yeah, And if I win, no Senior Sunrise,
Deal, Rack 'em up,
Yeah, I… I don't know, I…
I feel like I just need
Marius and I used to hook up,
I get it, I mean, Marius is a lot,
- It's in the past, right?
I'm with you now, and you are all I want,
Come on, Come on,
Don't stop, now
Keep going
Don't stop
Now go
Don't stop, now
Keep going
Don't stop
Now go
Don't stop, now
Keep going
Don't stop
- Now go
Your turn, Kathy,
It's Kitty,
Oh, I'm still 500,000 short,
Oh, I love this song!
- Hey, Madison?
You still want these boots?
I thought they were priceless,
They're yours for… 600 thou,
I'll give you five,
Done,
Yay!
Go
Don't stop, now
Keep going, don't stop
- Now go
This is it, Kitty,
Senior year is riding on this,
- Kitty!
Good game, Kathy,
Can't wait to sleep in,
What the heck, Kitty?
I saw your post about Yuri's sale,
but I didn't expect
That is a serious offense,
No, Jiwon, you can't,
You are asking me to put my job at risk,
No, You're right, I'm sorry,
I'll give you five minutes
but this is the first and last time
You don't get special treatment
Yes,
Thank you,
Principal Lee is on his way!
What? How did he find out?
We gotta go!
My cousin's a teacher here,
- Oh, so basically you narc'd?
We only have five minutes,
Kitty! Where are you going?
To bed, It's been a crappy day,
Wait!
Where are you going? Talk to me,
I came back to KISS
I had a list of all the things
But school hasn't even started,
I'm behind all my classes,
Marius is edging me out of my friend group
- And you--
For starters, you spent your whole summer
It didn't seem like
And now that we're back,
Marius is an old friend,
He got caught up
Maybe I did too, It's our senior year,
Exactly! And time is already ticking away,
You want to know the truth?
I spent the summer replaying that kiss
just dreaming of having
I even put it on my stupid Sunset List,
This is our last year together, Min Ho,
So I guess I got caught up in thinking
I think that I was wrong,
About everything,
- Call me
Call me honey
Give me something
I can keep…
I made a list
But so far, all I've got are regrets,
And the biggest one is that Min Ho and I
but somehow oceans apart,
Registration!
No, No,
No! All the classes are taken?
Except Korean Lit,
Come on,
What is going on?
- Hi!
Lookin' back on a Sunday
Pictures from the past now
Sittin' all in the basement…
He got me my Senior Sunrise,
Guess who's re-enrolling at KISS?
- No way! Oh!
Thank you so much,
It would not have been senior year
Juliana! Madison!
Looks like we found our fourth roommate,
So, your ex is living in your suite?
This won't be weird at all,
Don't worry, I'm fine,
Yuri,
A welcome back gift,
I bought them back from Madison,
She probably doubled the price,
Thank you so much,
With friends like you and Kitty,
- Thanks,
You're looking fresh
Switch rooms with Dae,
Whoa, Okay,
I mean, if you can't stay
without your entire relationship
I already told Jin everything,
- We're solid,
Curious, how did he react
that you sent me this summer?
You know? The one of--
- Shut up,
Kitty was right,
You are a bully,
Stay away from me,
I cannot believe you did this,
Wanted to help you check it off your list,
It's the least I can do to show you
You do?
Don't be daft,
Okay, look,
Forget last night, Forget Marius,
Forget all the stupid stuff
For what it's worth,
I didn't either,
And the reality is,
I want to be the guy who gives you
Wait, no, no, I have morning breath
When you're not here
There's space in my bed
Overthink real fast now 'bout it
Oh
I was wondering,
was me being your boyfriend on the list?
It might be,
Well, I guess you can check that off too,
Yeah, your breath could use a little mint,
Whatever,
All right, everybody,
I want to propose a toast to Kitty
To senior year!
Lara Jean told me
Regret nothing, remember everything,
She was right, And I have a feeling
Hey, yo, I heard you're back in Seoul,
I'd love to see you,
But, hey… Our boy's actually
and I was hoping
Ah, Thanks, Gigi,
It's gonna rock his world
Yeah, All right,
Now you speak French
Can't keep up with me
Try and match my energy
Dancin' on the table, table
Tell 'em I'm pullin' up on site
- We'll make 'em
- With my girls, we gon' shake some
We don't run, we don't chase 'em
Turn it up, hear that bass drum
Wons and yens and dollars
Comma, comma, comma
Shake some
Break some