[peaceful music]
♪ ♪
Nice.
It took long enough,
but it's back to normal.
Mm-hmm, finally, it's
crazy how much better
you look with hair, Hajime.
No, you don't get
to have an opinion here.
-Huh?
[HAJIME] I guess fall is
right around the corner.
Oh, I haven't been
to the dungeon market in ages.
Yeah? And why's that?
You know, it's
during the busy season,
so it's hard to find the time.
[gasps] Oh, look
at that pendant!
It's so cute. I love it.
Maybe not enough
for that price, though.
This one, I'll take it.
Huh?
Thank you, sir.
And you can keep the box.
She'll be wearing it.
Ah!
Oh.
Please, no,
I can't accept this.
It's too much.
Not as much as you do for us.
And it looks nice.
Mmm.
Are you trying to pull
some womanizer ploy?
[laugh] I guess you've gotta
let me touch your boobs now.
Oh, you're awful.
[HAJIME laughs]
Hmm.
I know he was
just being nice,
but a man's never given
me a present before.
[gasps]
Why am I suddenly
stricken with chills?
[groans]
[yells] It's not what it
looks like, Rirui, I promise.
[RIRUI]
Hey, Hajime!
Huh?
Doesn't Rirui
deserve a present too?
You think so?
Well, if you insist.
Well, go on and chow down.
Don't act like you don't
love food. [chuckles]
Well, Hajime,
wrong kind of present!
[theme music]
♪ ♪
AN ADVENTURER'S
DAILY GRIND AT AGE 29
EPISODE 11:
THE POWER OF CHARM
[sulking]
So that explains it.
I was wondering why
you've been in such
a terrible mood all day.
It's not fair.
Rirui's sick of Hajime
treating her like a child.
Well, then, your womanly
charms need work.
How?
You mean like bathing
more regularly?
No, but that's a start.
I mean, real effort.
It takes a lot
of hard work if you
want to be beautiful like me.
But once you're
able to pull it off,
men will shower you
in gems and gifts.
But Hajime never gives
you nothing, Boss Lady.
[groans]
You are beautiful,
aren't you?
[yells] Yes,
he's just a moron.
He's got a gorgeous
childhood friend
waiting in the wings here.
Who does he think he is?
[grunts]
I would never,
but it is so tempting
to use my succubus
powers on him.
Huh?
[chuckles] I mean,
the mystic eye charm.
It would be enough to make him
fully submit to my every want.
[gentle music]
But the effects are temporary.
And with him,
it'd feel like cheating.
Well, it sounds
pretty good to me
if it can make
Hajime love Rirui.
Jeez, you're hardcore.
Whatever it takes, please
tell me how to use that charm,
Boss Lady.
Sorry to break it to you,
but it's different for everyone.
You'll just have to wait
for yours to develop.
Well, that stinks.
[chuckles]
Don't worry,
you'll get it soon enough.
Hey, come on, cheer up.
I'll bring a surprise
for you tomorrow.
Huh?
Like a present?
[rooster crowing]
All done.
[shimmering]
Whoa!
Oh, so cute.
You look all grown up, Rirui.
Hey, morning.
What are you all
up to down here?
Hajime!
[shimmering]
Whoa, your lips are
glistening so much,
they're almost blinding me.
Try to go easy on the bacon
or you're going to get fat.
[laughs]
[ALL grimace]
Ow!
[NATALIE]
What's wrong with you?
[VERONICA] Go search a dungeon
for some sensitivity.
[HAJIME]
What the hell?
[grumbles]
Look, I mean it.
I'm really sorry.
I just thought that your lips
were slathered in grease.
What does Rirui
have to do to make
you realize
that she's not a baby?
Hey, this is kind of awkward.
Oh, wow, that's why.
[sighs] You're great
the way you are, Rirui.
And once you grow up,
I'm sure you'll be
quite the lovely lady.
What? He thinks she's
great the way she is?
Hmm.
[grumbles]
Nowhere near good enough.
He thinks he can just brush
me off with some nice words.
If that's the way it is...
[yells]
I'll get stronger
to gain that charm.
I bet I'll get
it if I level up.
And then he'll be helpless
against my charm power.
Man, she's fired up today.
I must have encouraged
her with my words.
I don't know about that,
but whatever's happening,
she's kind of scaring me.
Oh, yeah?
[screaming]
Rirui!
[crying]
Squishy?
I'm sorry.
[screams]
Hey, OK, slow down!
I can't hold on!
Stop, you dumb beast!
I told you to stop!
Oh, that's bad!
I guess I gotta bail!
[dramatic music]
[thuds]
♪ ♪
Kill it!
You know where its heart is.
Remember when
we stripped and cleaned one?
♪ ♪
Think.
Come on.
It's right here.
[blade stabs]
[splashes]
Nicely done, Rirui.
[chuckles] Hajime!
Oh, I-- [laughs awkwardly]
Rirui is all
splattered in blood.
You really took care of it.
Maybe Boss Lady
is right after all.
Even if I did use
my charm powers on Hajime,
I bet it wouldn't feel real...
not the way this does.
RIRUI LEVELED UP.
SHE LEARNED THE CHARM SKILL.
Huh?
[shimmering]
Huh. What's that?
You earned a new skill?
Would it really be so bad
to try it
just one time, though?
[chuckles] Wink, wink.
Huh?
Oh, you get some
blood in your eye?
[playful music]
Wink, wink.
Holy moly!
What is this?
It's awesome.
Wink, wink.
[screams]
Hmm, so she gained
herself a charm skill, huh?
It looks like she needs
to level up
to use it on people, though.
But it's potent.
Rirui finally gets her
first succubus power,
and it only works
on gross things.
I bet I just need
to put more effort in.
Hmm?
[giggles]
Big wink!
Get some slime
juice in your eye now?
[groans] Why?
How do I get the thing that I
want, but it's not what I want?
THE POWER OF HER CHARM...
SEEMS INEFFECTIVE ON HUMANS.
AN ADVENTURER'S
DAILY GRIND AT AGE 29
Good morning, everyone!
And a good morning to you.
Whoa!
Hello?
It's you, Anya?
It's the mask of a deer god.
Do you like it?
I thought I'd go
ahead and make it
since the festival's
coming up soon.
There's a festival? For what?
It's held in veneration
to the deer god
who rules the domain
of bountiful harvests.
Right.
Good morning, Cocko.
Same to you.
Oh, neat.
But what's a bountiful harvest?
[sighs]
Basically,
it means there's going
to be a whole lot of food.
Yeah, they've got a bunch
of stalls at the festival,
all of them packed
with tasty stuff.
No way!
Seriously?
No joke.
Hey, you know what?
We should all run
a stall of our own.
We'll serve the meat we
bring in from the dungeon.
Yeah!
That's a great idea.
Let's make it happen.
You in, Cocko?
I suppose I can help out
since it's obvious you need me.
OK, awesome!
We're going to run
the best stall there.
That's right, we will.
[banging]
[laughter]
There you go.
It looks great.
[GIRL] I mean it.
Knock it off!
[laughs] It's
taking you forever
to make your dumb masks.
And what's it to you, Rotton?
We're being careful to make
sure our masks don't
turn out as ugly as yours.
We just want
them to look good.
Leave us alone.
[tongue slithers]
[laughter]
It looks like Rotton's
anteater is as big of a jerk
as he is.
[RIRUI]
Hey, cut it out!
Who asked you to butt in?
You're getting in line
for a licking from Kaiser?
Trust me, you better
run while you can.
It's really gross and sticky.
Hmm.
[growls]
[grumbles]
[groans]
Wink, wink.
[anteater yelps]
[playful music]
[giggles]
What?
Kaiser?
Now, lick him
from head to toe.
No!
Hey, what are you doing?
Stop it, Kaiser!
Why are you licking me?
[sloppy licking]
[yelps]
Kaiser, heel.
Leave me alone!
Oh, it's so sticky.
[giggles]
Golly.
Thanks a lot.
You really saved us.
That's the dark
power dwelling
within Rirui, unleashed
in the name of justice.
So cool!
What are you going on about?
That's awesome!
Yeah, it is.
I wish I had a dark power.
[GIRL]
You said your name's Rirui?
You wanna hang out with us,
and we can all
make deer god masks together?
[RIRUI]
Sure, let's do it!
Really? You wound up
making masks with them?
Yeah! We promised to meet up
and play with each other
on the day of the festival.
And, oh, yeah,
me and Anya are going
to run a meat stall together.
[HAJIME]
Like a vendor stall?
We're going
to cook up the meat
from our hunts in the dungeon.
[giggle]
I'm super excited
about the festival.
[gentle music]
[snore]
That's right, Rirui's stall
is doing big business.
[chuckles]
♪ ♪
Her first festival.
Not really the best memories
from when I was a kid.
Just staring at the commotion
from the alleys.
All I could ever do was watch.
All that fun stuff
I missed out on.
I'm glad Rirui will
actually get to enjoy it.
♪ ♪
I'm sensing magic beasts.
[breathing heavily]
[roar]
[WATCHMAN 1]
Here they come!
[WATCHMAN 2]
Pull over!
[WATCHMAN 3]
Get ready for them.
[growling]
[BOTH scream]
[dramatic music, grunting]
♪ ♪
Damn, what's with
these rabbit bears
attacking all of a sudden?
Oh, no, it got past me.
[footsteps thudding]
♪ ♪
Oh, adventurer.
What's up?
Um, well, a massive
horde of them suddenly
started jumping over the gate.
I've never seen
anything like it.
Weird.
What's causing it?
Wait, there are
mountain wolves too?
Don't you think the moon
is just lovely tonight?
Chair?
Yes, ma'am.
You landed
your marks perfectly.
Who's a good boy?
Me? Oh, thank you
so much, mistress.
I didn't ask
for a talking magic chair.
[slap thuds]
[shudders]
[VERONICA] You want
your reward, swine?
-[VERONICA] Here it is.
-[MAN] Oh, thank you.
Oh, thank you.
[WOMAN] Here's a bonus.
You've got plenty
of energy, given the hour.
Well, the full
moon is soon upon us.
You know us, ancient species.
It stirs our blood.
Huh?
It doesn't even look
three-quarters full.
You-- jeez, you are hopeless.
I clearly explained this all
to you when you adopted Rirui.
If you intend to raise
one of my kind,
you better get it together.
All right, I got it.
It's under control.
Have a good night.
[shudders]
[grunts]
So their blood starts
to stir as the full moon
approaches, huh?
[owl hoots]
[breathing heavily]
Strange, her charm
marking, it was glowing.
Welcome to our stall.
What can I get you?
[giggles] Anya, you've got
to put more meat on the grill.
This line's getting huge.
This is going
to be so amazing.
We're going to need to gather
up a whole bunch of meat.
Rirui's going
to hunt her heart out.
Rirui, Anyango.
-Huh?
Someone said you girls are
going to be running a stall.
Yep, we'll be
grilling up some meat.
Count on me as a customer.
Yay!
We'll be ready.
Two kids running
a stall, could be tough.
If it turns out you
girls need any help,
just give us a shout.
Oh, thank you.
That's so nice.
We better get going.
[giggling]
[RIRUI] I can't wait
to start cooking.
Rirui.
-Huh?
You have any weird
dreams last night,
maybe like a violent one?
Uh, I don't think so.
Did you dream
about your powers?
Were you using them?
How could I do that?
I was sound asleep
all night long.
Why?
Is something wrong?
Sorry.
It's nothing.
It went that way!
[footsteps thudding]
[yells]
[thuds]
[panting]
One skewer, coming
right up, sir.
[giggles]
[OLIVE] Is
everything all right?
You rarely look so concerned.
What's bothering you?
Mm.
Well, I'm guessing
you've heard all about
this magic
beast situation, right?
The nightly attacks, I mean.
[OLIVE]
I should have known.
Thank you for pitching
in every night.
We've all been so worried,
and nobody knows
what's causing it.
Once we do,
I'm putting an end to it.
Let's bring Cocko in.
I think it's time
for a strategy meeting.
Yeah, let's get real.
I should have known.
Of course, the village
would be troubled by this.
So, something on your mind?
No, nothing at all.
[thuds]
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
[HAJIME]
Rirui, wake up.
Huh?
Whoa, why the heck
would my arm be glowing?
Can you control it?
Try to stop it.
[straining]
No, it doesn't seem like I can.
It's OK.
But what's happening?
Why is my arm all glowy?
Hmm. My guess?
It's a power
sealed within you.
[gasp]
And this means
your dark forbidden power
is beginning to stir and fight
its way up to the surface.
Seriously?
Well, Rirui can't believe it.
Can it really be true?
Is my dark dragon
trying to awaken?
Man, you really
love dragons, huh?
[RIRUI] Well, it's obvious
what I have to do now.
Huh?
Yes, Rirui will tame
and fiercely
wield this dark power.
And then I'll use it
to help every last person
in the village.
Well...
that's nice,
but keep that power a secret.
Huh?
But why can't I share it?
Hm, uh...
Well, it sounds cool, right?
You've got a secret power.
[gasps] Yeah, it does!
[chuckles]
All right, back to bed.
I've still got some
leftover work to finish up.
Huh.
Yay!
Bed for me.
[giggles]
♪ ♪
[theme music]
NEXT TIME:
A HOMETOWN AND FRIENDS