(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
(Yoo Yeon Seok)
(Esom)
(Kim Kyung Nam)
(Kim Mi Kyung, Jeon Seok Ho, Son Yeo Eun, Lee Ah Rin)
(Choi Kwang Il, Jung Seung Gil, Yeon Je Hyung)
(Phantom Lawyer)
(Supported by Ministry of Culture, Sports and KOCCA)
(All people, places, and events in this drama are fictional.)
(Child actors filmed safely with guardians.)
(All scenes involving animals were staged...)
(and filmed safely by welfare standards.)
Sir.
Yes?
Hey.
Are you okay?
Who are you?
What?
I mean...
Where am I?
What's wrong?
He's reset again.
Our client is gone, and the will has been forged.
So we have no grounds to continue this trial.
Still, let's not give up. Let's wait until she gets here.
I'm sorry.
Ma'am.
Ma'am, are you okay?
- Here, have a seat. - Thank you.
I apologize.
About the will...
Did you really dictate them, ma'am?
Yes, I did.
I dictated it,
and my husband wrote it down.
Ma'am.
Why did you file a complaint against Ryeo Seon Hwa?
You said you two were like family.
From the moment I first saw him,
I fell for him.
(Ideal Shoes)
But after getting to know him,
he was far more wonderful than I ever imagined.
- Are you all right? - Yes, I'm fine. Thank you.
And so, my feelings for him grew stronger.
- Come what may, - You're not hurt, are you?
- No, I'm not hurt. - I decided to confess my feelings.
All right, take care now.
But then...
He was...
making a pair of red shoes.
I thought the shoes were for me,
and I can't tell you how excited I was.
Are they ready?
- Yes. They're almost done. - But I was wrong.
They're absolutely beautiful.
- And right there... - Pretty, aren't they?
was Seon Hwa.
I was so angry, and I went straight to a bar.
There's this man I like.
But he's in love with another woman.
I don't get what he sees in a woman who has a kid in the North.
- Seon Hwa! - Jeong Hee.
And then, a few days later,
- they took Seon Hwa away. - Put her in.
The North? You mean North Korea?
- It was him. - Seon Hwa!
- Sir. - Seon Hwa!
From that moment on, I wasn't myself.
I couldn't eat or sleep.
I couldn't even bring myself to look at his face.
But one day,
he said something to me.
Please, don't be sad anymore.
If you keep this up, you're going to get sick, Jeong Hee.
I couldn't tell him what I'd done,
which only made me more miserable.
But still, he did everything he could to comfort me.
As we tended to each other's wounds,
we grew closer and closer.
And so, with our broken hearts, we got married.
We had a child and lived that way for fifty years.
All that time,
he cherished me as his wife and as a mother to Ji Hoon, but...
I...
The guilt that I had caused the death of the woman my husband loved...
I could never shake it.
So I made a promise to myself.
That someday,
I would find Seon Hwa's son and give him what was rightfully hers.
It was the only way...
I could even begin to atone for my sin.
I understand how you feel, ma'am.
But since your husband's will was proven to be a forgery,
the current lawsuit will be dismissed.
Then...
does that mean I can't give the money to Seon Hwa's son?
I can request a settlement from the plaintiff as a goodwill gesture.
Even that won't be easy.
Mr. Kang Ji Hoon is likely already upset because of the forgery,
and he'll likely refuse to acknowledge contributions from 40 years ago.
I know this is going to sound crazy,
but what if...
What if...
Seon Hwa is still alive?
What would happen then?
What are you talking about?
I went to Seon Hwa's grave.
I wanted to bury these shoes with her.
Seon Hwa...
I know it's far too late,
but I feel like I have to return these to you now.
Seon Hwa, I'm so sorry.
(Thank you, Jeong Hee.)
Seon Hwa?
Seon Hwa...
- Seon Hwa! - But that's a place...
only my husband,
Seon Hwa, and I knew about.
We were the only three people who knew about that place.
This note must have been left by Seon Hwa.
(Thank you, Jeong Hee.)
If Ryeo Seon Hwa is alive,
then that changes everything.
- Wouldn't you agree, Ms. Han? - That may be true if she is, but...
it won't be easy to find someone who just vanished, leaving only a note.
- I'm sorry, but I should be going. - No, wait...
Hold on a second.
I know you're upset and angry.
But...
don't you feel bad for them?
For whom?
All of them.
Ms. Chae, her husband,
and Ryeo Seon Hwa too.
I'll go visit Taebaek.
If they offer a settlement, we take it, and this is over. Got it?
(Taebaek)
Now that the will has been proven to be a forgery,
the other party will agree to drop the lawsuit.
If we offer a consolation payment or settlement, they'll be satisfied.
Of course, if you prefer, sir, we don't have to give them a single cent.
That my mother reported Ryeo Seon Hwa,
and that she died in prison...
Why didn't you tell me?
I apologize for not informing you sooner, sir.
But I was only doing it for your own good.
I didn't want you to get caught up in any unnecessary emotions.
Unnecessary feelings?
Guilt, a sense of obligation, sympathy, and pity.
You know, feelings that are unhelpful in a trial.
Wasn't your goal from the very beginning...
to protect your father's inheritance?
I was simply doing everything I could to achieve that goal for you.
What about the settlement? Do you have a figure in mind?
I'll decide later whether to offer a settlement or consolation money.
First, I need to go see my mother.
I'll see you later then.
At a time like this, he's still worried about what his mother thinks?
Sir, Lawyer Han is here.
Okay.
You're here sooner than I expected.
How's your father?
You knew I'd come?
Yes. Of course.
I've even had your old office set up for you.
Let's stop wasting time and get back to work together.
Let's stop wasting time and get straight to the point.
Let's drop this case.
(Evidence for Profit Sharing Injunction)
I know claiming one-third is a stretch.
But Ms. Ryeo Seon Hwa clearly contributed,
and we have plenty of evidence.
I'd like to settle for ten percent...
of the company's assets. What do you say?
You valued a 40-year-old contribution against its current net worth?
There's no way an absurd idea like that came from you.
Was it Shin Yi Rang's idea?
It's not absurd, and it wasn't Lawyer Shin's idea.
The rational, level-headed Lawyer Han I knew...
Why have you changed so much?
You saw Shin Yi Rang pull another one of his stunts in court.
I told you. He's dangerous to be around.
Lawyer Han, you and Shin Yi Rang are completely different.
You're not compatible. It's like you're two different species.
You're right.
Lawyer Shin and I are different people.
And that's why I enjoy being with him.
Then what about me?
What?
I mean...
We at Taebaek...
need a lawyer like you.
- Taebaek has many lawyers better than me. - Whatever. Forget it.
Come back, or the settlement is off, just so you know.
- Why are you being so childish? - What, you didn't know about it?
You used to tell me off for being childish all the time.
Fine.
If you're really not going to settle,
then we'll just have to find another way.
What other way?
What?
They have no records of Seon Hwa at the prison?
That's right.
Then again, it was a very long time ago.
But...
if Seon Hwa is still alive,
then whose remains are in her grave?
By the way, who gave you the remains?
Her lawyer brought them.
I think he said he was a public defender.
But it was so long ago.
I don't know his name or any of his contact info.
I've found a way.
Goodness.
We can go through the bar association...
to find a list of public defenders...
who visited Anyang Prison around that time.
Ryeo Seon Hwa's lawyer should be on that list.
I take it the settlement didn't happen?
No. We're dropping this lawsuit.
We'll only be at a disadvantage if we continue.
I agree.
Instead, I'm thinking of starting a new lawsuit.
A new lawsuit?
We'll have Ryeo Seon Hwa's son, Cha Eun Seong, act as the plaintiff,
and file a lawsuit...
for an Injunction on Profit Distribution against the company.
That could work.
As long as we can find Ryeo Seon Hwa and get her in court,
we'll have a fighting chance.
Exactly.
What a relief.
- Sorry. - Are you tired?
I've been drafting the complaint for the past few days,
so I haven't gotten much sleep.
Here.
Want some?
Coffee.
That's a real eye-opener.
It's really good.
Maybe it's because you gave it to me.
(Shin Yi Rang Law Office)
Searching for public defenders...
who visited Anyang Prison between 1983 and 1985.
Attorney Jang Gyeong Yeop?
(Han Na Hyun, Attorney at Law)
By any chance, back in 1983,
did you know an inmate at Anyang Prison named Ryeo Seon Hwa?
We'll have to contact them one by one. This isn't working.
That's what I was thinking.
But while we're eating,
let's try not to think about work.
Sounds good.
What should I start with?
The eel...
You know, I noticed this last time too.
Our personalities are so different,
but we have the exact same taste in food.
Here.
You first.
Okay, then. One each, to be fair.
This is really good.
(Attorney Shin Yi Rang)
Yes?
Shin Yi Rang's team has agreed to drop the case.
As they should. What other choice did they have?
But in its place, Cha Eun Seong has filed a suit against Ideal Shoes,
to claim his mother Ryeo Seon Hwa's shares.
They what?
(The defendant shall pay the plaintiff a sum equivalent to...)
(one-third of the current value of Ideal Shoes' shares.)
So Han Na Hyun really wants to pick a fight?
Go right now and find out where Ryeo Seon Hwa was buried.
And get a DNA sample from Cha Eun Seong.
- Excuse me? - I hear most defectors...
from the North get in with fake identities.
That means Ryeo Seon Hwa and Cha Eun Seong...
might not actually be mother and son.
And what if the test proves they are mother and son?
Then make the results say they're not.
Do I have to spell it out for you?
If I have to do everything for you,
why bother coming to work, Director Choi?
- Don't just stand there. Get on it. - Yes, sir.
Here you go.
How have you been feeling?
I've been feeling much better since I started eating your food.
It's really nothing.
You know what they say. Food is the best medicine.
So, Yi Rang must be busy these days.
Yes. He's not overwhelmed, but he's getting a lot of clients.
I was at his last trial,
and I got to see Yi Rang make his argument.
He was a little unorthodox,
but he was really compelling.
Just like his father.
The doctor told me...
that my heart could stop at any moment.
Maybe that's why I keep...
thinking about Gi Jung.
I feel like I might have missed something,
and I'm starting to see some holes in the case.
I'm left with so many regrets.
I've told you. You don't have to do this.
I'm doing this for my own peace of mind.
If there's any way to clear Gi Jung's name,
I want to do it before I die.
By any chance...
Are there any documents he left behind?
- Documents? - Yes. You know what he was like.
Gi Jung always took such meticulous notes.
But his notebook on the case...
and other key files were nowhere to be found.
So,
I was wondering if maybe he kept them somewhere else.
I don't know.
I have a box of my husband's old papers at home, but...
I didn't see any case files in there.
And I don't recall seeing a notebook, either.
I see.
(Attorney Shin Yi Rang)
(Petition for Provisional Injunction on Profit Distribution)
(Attorney Han Na Hyun)
(Last will and Testament, Testator: Kang Dong Sik)
(Manri-dong in 1980, Manri-dong in 2025)
(Executor: Chae Jeong Hee, The 3 co-founders)
(Thank you, Jeong Hee.)
It seems Ms. Ryeo Seon Hwa left that letter...
because she knew what Ms. Chae wanted.
So why would she be in hiding?
Keeping it a secret even from her own son.
Normally, for shoes to be comfortable,
they need to be soft.
But in a dangerous place like a construction site,
it's the uncomfortable, hard-toed boots...
that keep your feet safe.
Pardon?
I don't know who this woman is,
but maybe she's hiding inside a pair of hard-toed boots.
You mean, to keep herself safe?
Exactly.
(From Lee Jeong Su)
(I'm responding to your email.)
(Regarding the time you asked about,)
(I remember an inmate at Anyang Prison...)
(named Ryeo Seon Hwa.)
Hello? I'm calling in response to your email.
Yes, that's right. About Ms. Ryeo Seon Hwa.
It says Attorney Lee Jeong Su...
spent his entire career as a public defender.
He retired a long time ago, and he's battling terminal cancer.
We might be coming back empty-handed, then.
No, if that was his intention,
he wouldn't have reached out to us in the first place.
(Garam Hospice)
Ms. Ryeo Seon Hwa was parted from her son when he was just one year old.
Do you happen to remember anything about her?
She was a woman of few words.
A quiet person.
But you could tell she was a principled and upright person.
But that's all I know.
If you want to know more,
you should talk to the other inmates. The ones who were with her.
That would be your best bet.
We considered that, but the prison no longer has the records.
I represented another female inmate.
I recall she shared a cell with Ryeo Seon Hwa.
Do you happen to remember her name?
Open that for me.
- This? - Yes, in that notebook.
Her phone number should be in there.
- Thank you, Counselor. - No, thank you.
For letting me...
do one good thing for Ms. Ryeo Seon Hwa before I go.
(Garam Hospice)
Bong Soo is great at finding people. I'll give him a call.
Honey, how can you just leave like this?
What are Ji Ah and I supposed to do?
I'm sorry...
I wanted to be there for you until the end...
Where's that coming from?
Where is...
Cut!
What is that noise? Whose phone is that?
- Whose phone is it? - It's not me.
- Darn it. - What is this?
- That's it over there. - Here. This one. Whose phone is this?
- Seriously? Who is it? - It just came out of nowhere...
All right. Thanks to you, I got kicked clean off the set,
so I'll look into it for you as soon as I leave.
I've found it.
At the place where CEO Kang's driver said...
he'd occasionally take Ms. Chae,
we found a burial mound that appears to be Ryeo Seon Hwa's grave.
Request an autopsy from the court...
and get Cha Eun Seong's DNA immediately.
A DNA test?
I understand. I'll call you back.
Taebaek has requested a paternity test.
It looks like CEO Yang has found where Ms. Ryeo Seon Hwa is buried.
That was a smart move.
This may be a lawsuit for an injunction on profit distribution,
but it's essentially an inheritance dispute.
If Ms. Chae is right and Ryeo Seon Hwa is still alive,
then the DNA test won't be a match.
But it's not like we can refuse the test.
The only way to win now is to find Ryeo Seon Hwa.
Have you heard from Bong Soo?
Yes, he said he found her current number and spoke with her.
And she knows Ms. Ryeo Seon Hwa?
Yes, she said they served time together.
He's on his way, so we should get going.
Okay.
Who are you? Why seek someone dead for over 40 years?
My name is Shin Yi Rang. I'm a lawyer.
Ryeo Seon Hwa's son is curious about his mother.
I never heard she had a son.
Then again, she was always full of secrets.
About how Ryeo Seon Hwa passed away... Could you tell me the details?
There was a fire in the prison laundry.
Seon Hwa and Sun Young were taken to the hospital with burns,
but neither of them ever came back.
So does that mean they both died?
Only Seon Hwa died.
Sun Young was treated at the hospital for a few weeks...
and was released from there when her sentence was up.
Are you still in contact with this Sun Young?
No.
We didn't exactly part as friends.
Lawyer Shin, are you thinking what I'm thinking?
That Sun Young might actually be Ryeo Seon Hwa?
If Ryeo Seon Hwa is really alive, I'd say the chances are high.
If they both suffered facial burns,
and considering this was 50 years ago,
they could've just swapped prison uniforms and fooled everyone.
Especially if the fire destroyed all the records.
It would've been even easier.
All we have to do is find this woman, Sun Young...
But where would we even find her?
That's the question.
Wait. Where did he go?
She seems like such a good, humble person.
But why was she shaking her leg?
Was she anxious about something?
(Eunseon Noodles)
(Park Sun Young)
Hello? Seon Hwa?
There are some people looking for you. You have to get out of there. Now.
Wait a minute. That is Seon Hwa!
It's her! Oh, my...
There he is.
Let's go. Hurry.
- Let's go. - Go where?
The noodle shop. Seon Hwa's there.
- Really? - What? What did he say?
He said Ryeo Seon Hwa is at the noodle shop.
Why would Ryeo Seon Hwa be at the noodle shop?
You're having a late lunch. You can't go around skipping meals.
Stop by anytime, it doesn't matter when. Okay?
All right, eat up.
Ma'am.
- The noodle shop lady? - The noodle shop lady?
Seon Hwa. Please don't run from me.
You have to at least let me apologize.
(Eunseon Noodles)
Anyone here?
Hello? Is anybody in there?
Lawyer Shin?
Mr. Cha. Was the owner not in today?
No, she was here.
She was busy with customers right through lunch.
Then she suddenly closed up shop and rushed out.
- She rushed out? - Yes.
When did she leave? She just left, right?
- Yes. What's this all about? - I'll explain later.
For now, let's go.
- Yi Rang! - Bong Soo! Turn around! Back up!
Back up? Back up where?
- No time to explain. Just follow us! - Okay.
Ms. Choi Gil Ja must have called her.
Why would she go to such lengths to hide?
Which way should I go?
We'll go left. You take the right.
Got it.
There were no turn-offs. Did she go left?
There she is! Over there!
(Hwayang River)
Do we...
have the right to do this?
She went through so much and barely made it back alive.
She's just a mother secretly making meals for her son.
If it weren't for us... she could be with her son.
But we're the ones chasing her away.
Do we really have that right?
I understand where you're coming from, Lawyer Shin.
In that case, let me go talk to her alone.
I'll just ask what she wants to do. If she says no, I'll let her go.
Hello.
Who are you?
My name is Han Na Hyun. I'm a lawyer.
You're Ryeo Seon Hwa, aren't you?
You're mistaken.
- You have the wrong person. - You were alive all this time. So why...
Why have you been living as if you were dead?
Even deceiving your own son.
You seem to be looking for someone.
Don't you think that person might have her reasons?
Everyone has their reasons.
Ms. Chae Jeong Hee certainly did too.
Chae Jeong Hee wanted to give Cha Eun Seong...
shares in Ideal Group.
To do it, she had her husband with dementia...
write a fake will.
A fake will? Jeong Hee did that?
Because she believed she was the reason you died.
She believed that because of what she told the police,
you were arrested.
And she has spent 50 years atoning for it.
I wanted to make sure I told you that.
I'll just pretend I never saw you, then.
Wait. Just a minute.
Ma'am.
Oh, my.
We found her.
We found Ryeo Seon Hwa. I'm telling you, we found her.
(Shin Yi Rang and Han Na Hyun Law Office)
Wait, hold on.
Seon Hwa.
- Jeong Hee. - Seon Hwa. You're alive.
I thought you were dead.
I didn't die.
I couldn't let myself die.
Seon Hwa.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, Seon Hwa.
It's my fault. It's all my fault you...
Seon Hwa, I'm so, so sorry. I was so foolish.
No, it's not your fault, Jeong Hee.
The lawyer told me everything. She told me about your misunderstanding.
I came here to clear up that misunderstanding.
A misunderstanding?
Long before you were at the bar...
and met with that police officer,
I already knew there were people watching me.
I was leaving after getting the letter from my son, who was defecting.
But they got to me before the letter did.
So, what I'm saying is, even if it wasn't you,
I was fated to be caught no matter what.
Seon Hwa.
But still... I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you. Thank you for being alive, Seon Hwa.
Sorry I wasn't much help.
Not at all.
It was your idea to look for Ryeo Seon Hwa, Yi Rang.
You deserve a lot of credit for them making up.
Come on, that's not true.
You're the one who convinced Ms. Ryeo Seon Hwa, Na Hyun.
You deserve way more credit.
Fine, I'll take the credit.
So where's Mr. Kang now?
He's over there.
He would be so happy if he knew what happened today.
But does he really need to know?
He is still living in the past,
back when he was 20 and in his prime.
It's so pretty.
Then, shall we go wrap up the trial?
Sounds good.
So you mean Ryeo Seon Hwa has been living as someone else,
and if the trial continues, her true identity might be exposed?
Yes.
Yang Do Kyung is the kind of man who will stop at nothing...
to get what he wants.
On top of that, if he finds out that...
Ryeo Seon Hwa is using a stolen identity,
he'll use it to turn the trial in his favor.
Why are you telling me this?
Have you forgotten that I'm the defendant in this case?
I thought you were someone I could reason with.
Because I know you very well,
Mr. Kang.
You know me well?
Yes.
Someone told me what kind of person you are.
- I see you've met my mother. - No. It was someone else.
That person said...
that shoes carry the warmth of their maker.
The warmth in your shoes...
is a reflection of your own heart.
Here, let me see.
What a warm shoe.
- Pardon? - You made a shoe that shows your heart.
Because a shoe always carries...
the warmth of its maker.
You're even better than me, son.
Here.
Thank you.
Let's go.
(DNA test results: Ryeo Seon Hwa, Cha Eun Seong)
What did I tell you?
If you wanted,
I could make it so Cha Eun Seong wouldn't get a dime.
You won.
I'm dropping the lawsuit.
What?
Wait, you're not dropping it. We've already won.
I had Cha Eun Seong's factory leather analyzed.
Results show it was made with a process 100 percent identical to ours.
Cha Eun Seong told me he produces his leather...
with a method passed down in his family.
Rather than this piece of paper...
I'm choosing to believe in Cha Eun Seong's leather.
Thank you for your efforts.
I'll have your fee wired to you immediately.
Hey, that's enough looking.
You know all my stuff is good without checking.
Gosh, a bug.
What bug? That just means it's organic, you know?
When you don't use pesticides, the bugs are naturally drawn to it, right?
Gosh, but still...
I'll take some spinach too, please.
Of course. Good choice.
You're buying some too, Na Hyun?
Yes, it looks so fresh and delicious.
Here. Let me just add...
a little something extra.
- Thank you. - What? Ma'am.
What is it?
What's the special occasion?
Ji Hoon...
He signed a leather supply contract with Seon Hwa's son.
And it's all thanks to you lawyers.
- That's great news. - Thank you.
Oh, right. Today, Seon Hwa and I...
are supposed to go see my husband.
Seon Hwa...
Wait. That's not right. She said she wasn't Seon Hwa, didn't she?
That's not right.
Hey, Sun Young, I'm heading out now.
I'll be leaving soon too.
- Where are you off to? - Just have to take care of something.
For a second, I was worried you'd just leave like you did before.
You were worried about me?
Why?
Just because.
When I see you, you remind me of my mom.
You remember your mom?
We were separated when I was too young, so I don't remember her face,
but when I eat your noodles,
it feels like my mom's cooking.
I see.
Actually, for me too.
When I see you,
you remind me so much of my son.
You have a son?
I do.
We were separated when he was young,
and he'd be about your age now.
Well... Listen.
I believe people can be family even if they're not related by blood.
I'm not trying to impose or anything,
but we could eat holiday meals together,
celebrate birthdays together,
and help each other when we're sick. That kind of thing.
I must have said too much.
I'd like that.
You would?
I said I'd like that.
From now on, just call me Eun Seong.
Eun Seong.
Let's take good care of each other.
Yes, let's.
Mom.
Yes?
Okay. Got it.
- She's here, in the restroom. - I see.
- There she is. - Oh, yes.
I hope it goes well. I'll wait here.
Thanks for bringing me.
We'll be back.
Honey.
Seon Hwa is here.
Dong Sik.
I'm too late, aren't I?
I'm so sorry.
You must be happy, right?
Getting to see her face, even if it's like this.
Seon Hwa,
I have something for you.
Actually, to be exact,
it's not from me. It's from Dong Sik.
These aren't mine.
Seon Hwa.
It's all right.
I saw the two of you at the workshop that day.
No, that's not... It's just...
All right. Here, take a look.
Here you go.
- Why are these so tight? - Gosh.
- Try them on, Jeong Hee. Come on. - But I...
- Me? - Go on.
So cool.
So beautiful.
Jeong Hee.
Dong Sik.
You're finally wearing them. Your shoes.
I didn't know.
I thought they were Seon Hwa's.
You know how your heels are delicate and get blisters easily?
That's why I specifically asked Seon Hwa to use very soft leather.
So these...
These are really my shoes?
I made them, hoping they would always bring you back home.
And know that I would always be there waiting for you.
That's what I wanted to tell you.
And I had no idea...
Jeong Hee.
I wanted to give you the moon and the stars,
my lovely Chae Jeong Hee.
I loved you.
And...
I still love you.
Thank you.
You've been a great help.
Don't mention it.
I've seen the person I needed to see...
and given her what I had to. So now, please let me go.
What? You mean right here?
Why? Can't I?
The Father is waiting for you on the rooftop.
I like it here just fine.
I got to see my wife looking so happy.
I'll have no regrets passing on from here.
Okay.
Father, you can burn the talisman now.
(Father, you can burn the talisman now.)
All right.
Mr. Kang.
There's one last thing I'd like to ask you.
What is it?
How much do you actually remember?
Sometimes, it seems like you don't remember anything at all,
and other times, it's like you know everything.
There's only one thing I remember.
Chae Jeong Hee.
Just her.
And that's why I remember everything.
If you remember the one you love,
you remember everything.
I see.
Sir.
Go in peace.
All right.
Take care.
Yes.
Doggy, come here!
He passed on peacefully.
Are you okay?
You must have grown pretty attached to him.
He really loved his wife so, so much.
But she went her whole life without ever knowing.
That's what's so heartbreaking.
Like I said.
You'll regret not saying "Thank you," "I'm sorry,"
or "I love you" when you can.
Yi Rang, if you want no regrets,
you have to show your feelings sometimes.
What is it?
I'm not going to have any regrets.
I know. That's not who you are, Yi Rang.
Because I'm going to say it right now.
You are?
I'm telling you right now.
How I feel.
Hey, Doggy!
Doggy?
Don't tell me...
Come play with me.
What's your name?
You can't just stop talking and walk away.
You can't leave me hanging like this.
Fine, whatever. Go.
So cute.
(Phantom Lawyer)
What's wrong, mister?
It's hard having so many unanswered questions.
Because I can't remember.
We have a missing elementary school student.
He's in first grade, and he was wearing yellow rain boots.
It's a boy, and he's wearing yellow rain boots.
So, are you going to find my mom and dad for me now?
A golf ball. This could be a vital clue to the location of death.
I know who the child is.
Mister, it's dangerous! Get a hold of yourself!