So late.
Maybe a case suddenly popped up.
First Division is busy…
I didn't mean them…
Ms. Kudo!
They’re here.
Hello.
I'm Kudo from the Violent Crimes Division.
I'm Hyuga, First Division.
I'm Ishizaka. I'll show you the way.
Follow me.
-Hello.
-Thank you.
Why are you coming with First Division?
I'm on time.
It's a joint investigation.
You must get here before them.
It doesn't matter.
Mr. Tagusari…
Those guys aren't a big deal anyway.
Going up.
CRIMINAL IDENTIFICATION POLICE
You can go first.
Doors closing.
They heard you.
Tagusari.
You were in charge
of the post-mortem, right?
Yes.
The male victim got in an accident
and died in his apartment
due to an acute blood clot in the brain.
A post claiming the victim had once
driven a high school student to suicide
had gone viral on social media,
so he was using
a forged ID to hide his identity.
So his real name is Jun Okochi?
The person who hit Okochi with their car
was Masaya Nogami, the father
of the deceased high school student.
After being interrogated
at the Aoi Station, he disappeared.
The deceased, Jun Okochi,
was a swimming club coach
at Ryoshin High School
until two years ago.
It's a powerhouse school
that produces Olympic athletes,
and it seems Okochi was extremely strict
in his coaching of the members.
And Nogami’s son was among those members?
Yes.
Two years ago,
Taiki Nogami’s body
was found in the Tsugumi River.
His autopsy record?
He had hyper-inflated lungs
and white froth at the mouth and nose,
so it was presumed to be
accidental death by drowning.
We processed it as an accident, back then.
But he was an elite swimmer, right?
The weather was bad that day,
and the river was overflowing.
However, now that Okochi’s
harsh coaching has come to light,
it's possible it was not an accident,
but a suicide.
So Nogami fled, afraid people
would find out he hit him on purpose.
Search thoroughly,
and take Nogami into custody.
Yes, sir!
Starting with Nogami’s inner circle?
Probably a waste of time.
He’s likely overseas now.
Airports, railways, main highways…
First Division
will check them all to find him.
You should help out too.
Without the body,
what can a medical examiner do?
Mr. Tagusari!
I managed to get in touch
with Nogami’s wife.
Got it.
Makoto.
Nogami’s motive is revenge.
Can you really arrest him?
Have you heard from your husband?
Any idea where he might be?
No…
Even after the accident the other day,
he didn't tell me anything.
Had Taiki always been into swimming?
It was his dream to go to the Olympics.
He even got into Ryoshin High School
on a sports scholarship.
But he ended up ruining his shoulder
from the harsh training.
Even so, he participated
in the tournament relay,
but he felt it was his fault they lost.
What's wrong?
Do you know of any places
your dad might go?
I don't.
Back then, did your brother
ever talk about the swimming club?
No.
Did my dad…
really kill someone?
Probably.
Hey! Mr. Tagusari!
We are still investigating right now.
Sorry to keep you waiting. Here it is.
The swimming club roster
from two years ago.
Thank you.
What happened to Taiki Nogami
was very unfortunate.
I would like to ask about the coach,
Jun Okochi.
My understanding is that
his coaching methods were appropriate.
I’m sure it was strict at times,
but it was unavoidable to get results.
The members understood that as well.
However, he also felt responsible
and stepped down soon after.
But the school was not at fault.
It was an accident.
Sounds like a textbook cover-up.
Hey, that's rude.
I’m sorry.
Yes, this is Kudo.
2024 SWIMMING CLUB - TAIKI NOGAMI
Nogami…
Hello.
Hey.
Thank you.
Was Nogami at this shop?
Yes.
I showed the staff a photo,
and they're sure it was him.
Apparently,
he was sitting in that seat all morning.
What the hell is he doing?
I've contacted headquarters
and had officers patrol this area.
Understood.
Welcome home.
I'm just here for clothes.
-So you won't be staying here for a while?
-Yes.
Hey, do we have any new toothpaste?
We do.
How are things with Nogami?
Take a look at this.
It's from a coffee shop
Nogami was seen at.
A coffee shop?
Know what it is?
I can't really say just from a photo.
You can't say because it's just a guess?
So this means Nogami is still in Kanagawa?
He's had his revenge,
he should just get out of here.
Taiki, I'll give you this.
VICTORY
Oh, wow.
Did you make it, Koki?
The failed attempt goes to you, Dad.
VICTORY
Why do I get the reject?
Taiki.
You have to win the next tournament, okay?
I will.
Nogami had been absent from work
without notice before running away.
No sign of him visiting
Taiki Nogami’s grave either.
Anything from the officers
near the coffee shop?
No reports yet.
Nogami’s credit card has been used!
-Where?
-A little past 7:00 p.m. yesterday.
He bought a suit
at a shopping mall in the prefecture.
-A suit?
-Planning to blend into the rush hour?
Check nearby security cameras.
Yes, sir!
A heart attack, huh?
There’s no external trauma,
so it doesn't seem like
there's any foul play.
Where was this body found?
He collapsed yesterday
while fishing in the river.
Send this to forensics.
Okay.
You also have an autopsy?
Found anything?
I have no clue at all.
Want a drink?
First a coffee shop, now a shopping mall.
He drank coffee for an hour,
then disguised himself in a suit.
You would usually disguise yourself first.
His moves are too unpredictable.
The locations are far apart too.
What is Nogami even thinking?
He risked detection, moving around,
and even used a credit card
that leaves a trail.
Does he have some purpose?
I'll head out for a bit.
To Haruko’s place again?
A family registry
and stamp.
How much would they be worth?
You again?
I'm leaving!
This man again?
Where did you get the info on Okochi?
I can't reveal my sources.
Then let me meet your acquaintance.
What do you plan to investigate?
Does Makoto do any cleaning at home?
We have a rotation.
The deal is that if he slacks off,
he'll pay rent.
He would follow the schedule then.
He uses my place
like it's his home, though.
It has been almost a month now, hasn't it?
Time flies.
His meeting Haruko
for the first time in a while
happened right after he came
to this police station, didn't it?
He was tracking
stolen goods from an assault case,
and found her pawnshop.
You should see her too.
Thanks for the meal.
If more time passes like this,
it will only get harder to meet.
This…
RECEIPT
These seasoning prices aren't right.
You have to check the numbers.
Vendors will rip you off!
Fine, I will.
I don't intend to meet her.
It's better if she doesn't
get involved with us anymore.
Twenty yen.
Oh, twenty.
Hello.
-The results from this morning.
-Thank you.
Do you have a meeting?
We can't track Nogami’s movements at all.
-Should we try going to the racetrack?
-Racetrack?
A desperate Nogami might be there.
You just want to go there yourself.
We’re going to reexamine his inner circle.
What a pain.
Oh, want a ride to headquarters?
Before that,
there’s a place I would like to stop by.
Burr marigolds?
Their seeds were attached
to the body found this morning.
Burr marigolds grow in vacant lots.
They are so-called "hitchhiker" plants.
Normally, the seeds
are dispersed in autumn.
So they remained until this time of year.
Have the science lesson somewhere else.
What about those seeds?
The same seeds were at
the coffee shop where Nogami was.
So Nogami is hiding there?
I don't know.
However,
the body this morning was found
on the bank of the Tsugumi River.
People don't often come here.
Perhaps that's why the seeds remain.
The report from two years ago
said Taiki Nogami's body
was discovered around here.
It must have been over there.
What are you doing?
I was washing away
the things I don't need.
Things you don't need?
A long time ago,
my dad told me,
if you have worries or pains,
just wash them away in the river.
By the time they reach the sea,
their weight will have lessened.
Did Taiki often come here with you?
He often washed away nerves
before a match.
I also made charms
and gave them to him and my dad.
That day,
my brother's charm
was on him and washed away somewhere.
And those flowers?
It wasn't me.
So, Nogami was really here.
What happened?
It seems Nogami used a taxi.
We can track his movements
with the records.
What did you come to wash away?
You wash away things
you don't need, right?
Taiki.
In the middle of the final relay,
my brother stopped swimming.
After that,
he didn't practice or do rehab.
In the end…
Taiki…
was weak.
So it's your brother's fault?
-Welcome.
-Excuse me.
I'm Kudo from the Aoi Station.
Goodbye.
Sorry to bother you while you're busy.
He's not easily found, is he?
So he didn't stay here?
However, there's no doubt that Nogami
got out of a taxi in front of this hotel.
Ms. Sasaki. The guest has arrived.
I'm sorry. The guests have arrived, so…
Thanks for your cooperation.
Please excuse us.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Please follow me.
He stayed at a coffee shop for an hour,
bought a suit,
and got out of a taxi in front
of a hotel he didn't even stay at.
I can't read Nogami’s moves.
Oh, I'll be right there.
Okay.
Found out something?
The one who gave me information on Okochi
was Taiki Nogami’s classmate.
-Was he in the swimming club too?
-Yes.
For three years. He should know things.
The police?
I'm sorry. I thought
you wouldn't meet him if I told you.
Okochi backed Taiki Nogami
into a corner, didn't he?
And it wasn't just Taiki, right?
When I looked into it a bit,
rumors of Okochi’s
excessive coaching were everywhere.
I heard there were times
he even laid hands on them.
Many members were injured
due to excessive practice too.
Was Taiki Nogami one of them?
He wouldn't let Taiki rest.
Taiki's shoulder injury worsened,
and by the final relay, he…
couldn't swim anymore.
Why did he quit the club?
What?
If it's an injury, he'd heal.
He was forced to quit.
By the advisor, Ms. Chinen.
Chinen?
Even Okochi’s coaching
was all based
on Ms. Chinen's instructions.
She eliminates anyone…
MAIKO CHINEN
…who doesn't produce results.
Is that advisor still at the school?
No.
I heard she’s working
as a prep school instructor now.
A prep school?
Apparently,
he was sitting in that seat all morning.
MISAWA PREP SCHOOL
A senior in the swimming club
told me Ms. Chinen
is getting married soon.
POLICE DATABASE
TAIKI NOGAMI
ITEMS RECOVERED FROM VICTIM
CONDITION OF SMARTPHONE, STUDENT ID,
WALLET CONTENTS, POINT CARDS
CONDITION OF PATIENT REGISTRATION CARD
YAURA ORTHOPEDIC CLINIC
TAIKI NOGAMI
Mr. Tagusari, where are you?
Nogami’s target
is the advisor, Maiko Chinen.
TANAKA - CHINEN WEDDING RECEPTION
Targeting her at the peak
of her happiness?
As revenge, it's a job well done.
You knew everything, didn't you?
On Taiki's phone,
there was a message he never sent to me.
It said that…
because of Okochi,
he could no longer swim.
I didn't…
I didn't notice anything…
So you caused the accident?
That man didn't even come to his funeral.
He abandoned his past
and lived as if Taiki never existed…
I couldn't forgive him.
That hurts, old man.
I'm Taiki's father.
Taiki?
The boy you killed.
Taiki Nogami!
Wait a minute, it wasn't me.
That was the advisor, Chinen's fault.
Chinen?
That was when I learned about Chinen.
While I was waiting in front
of Okochi’s house, the police came,
and I found out he had died.
And then you looked into Chinen?
At the coffee shop,
a prep school student
told me about this wedding.
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you for coming
to the wedding reception today.
Now, the bride and groom,
and their parents
will be at the doors
to see the guests off.
We also have a small gift
for guests coming today…
If you want to do it, go ahead.
Once you are ready,
please come to the bride and groom…
Even if I stop you here,
you'll just do it eventually.
Take care when going home.
The police will be here soon.
Please,
let it end with this.
Taiki.
I'm sorry.
VICTORY
I can't take it anymore.
You…
have a happy future waiting for you.
But for that boy,
there is no tomorrow.
Don't you ever forget Taiki!
Don't forget Taiki!
Never forget Taiki Nogami!
Never forget him!
Don't forget him!
Why didn't you wait?
Why did you act on your own?
Would you
be able to endure it?
Hey.
We caught him.
But still!
First Division isn't so idle
as to have time
to bicker with local stations.
I'll give him a stern lecture later.
Okay?
Mr. Tagusari.
He had a weapon. That was dangerous.
Don't do reckless things like that.
Mr. Tagusari.
What did you mean earlier?
If he could endure it?
Kudo. That's enough.
If your own family were murdered
and the killer was in front of you,
what would you do?
What if they were laughing,
without ever having made amends?
Of course, I would arrest them.
Because that is our job.
And what does that solve?
1995, APRIL 26
-Sakutaro!
-Yes?
They're here again.
Dad!
Minoru.
I told you not to come as it's dangerous!
It's boring at home.
Do your homework. Your homework!
Ms. Fumi, still doing
that "bili-bili" thing?
It's "rehabilitation."
I want to ride in one too.
-You can't, that's Ms. Fumi's.
-Mr. Sadao.
-Yes.
-Okay.
Here.
Go ahead.
This and…
This…
And this is?
Please cooperate with me.
I know.
-Tell us.
-I have nothing to say.
Let me hear your side.
-Hey!
-I'm busy, go home.
No!
I'll come by again tonight.
It hurts!
Hey, is the ambulance here yet?
Arrival is delayed due to a fire!
-Make way!
-Ambulance coming through!
-Stay back!
-Get back!
Thanks.
-It hurts?
-Opening the door.
-Hurry!
-Here he is!
-Here you go.
-Makoto!
Minoru.
Makoto.
Did you see the face
of the person who ran away?
I didn't see his face.
But I know who it is.
Do you?
He was arguing with Dad.
He said he would
come by our house again tonight.
Makoto…
Is Minoru okay?
He's in the hospital.
He probably doesn't know yet.
Right.
Detective.
What happened?
I'm sorry to say it at a time like this,
but as it wasn't a robbery,
we are investigating it
as a personal grudge.
Did you catch the killer?
The person who was interviewing Dad.
I looked into it,
but it wasn't that person.
What?
But we the police,
will definitely catch the killer.
MS. HARUKO ASHIKAGA
What's wrong?
Where are my mom and dad?
I want to see them.
And now, for the final farewell.
Go on.
Makoto.
Minoru!
Mom!
Dad!
Are you sleeping?
Hey!
Minoru.
Mom and dad…
They died.
They won't move anymore.
We shall now seal the caskets.
It's time to say goodbye.
Dad!
Mom!
I'll definitely find the killer!
Go in first.
Don't slack off on cleaning up, okay?
He won't come here.
Your dad stopped for your sake.
What?
Your brother probably
let him off with just Okochi.
The files on Taiki Nogami.
Why do you have them?
After analyzing the stored blood,
prednisolone, an inflammation suppressor,
was detected.
This means that a few days
before his death,
he was undergoing treatment
for his shoulder.
Taiki didn't give up?
I used his registration card
to go to the orthopedic clinic
he was visiting.
He had an appointment
for the day after he died.
Taiki Nogami was enduring harsh rehab…
And, it seems, he said
he wanted to swim once more.
Taiki…
He didn't intend to die?
Your brother
wasn't as weak as you think.
Though that last part is just a guess.
Still, no one knows the truth.
Was it your father's love?
Was he a strong brother?
Choose what makes life easier for you.
That is the truth.
MOM
Mr. Tagusari.
Box up those documents over there.
Sure.
You don't trust First Division?
Not really.
Get along with them.
You'll be collaborating often.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Get a lot of fish here?
It doesn't matter.
I just like watching the water.
Here's the information fee.
There's no way I can take
money from you, Makoto.
I'll buy you a meal then.
I said it's fine.
Come on, keep me company today.
Mogi!
Haruko?
-Can you make a meal with this fish?
-What?
We're a Chinese restaurant.
Don't be so inflexible.
Minoru?
Have you been well?
When did you come back?
About three years ago, I think.
You should have contacted me!
Before I knew it,
even your number had changed.
I mean, it's all over already.
That incident
from sixteen years ago today.
It was ruled an accident.
Haruko.
Remember what I told you
when I left this place?
The future ahead of us is longer.
Do what you love.
I kept searching for that man
the whole time.
Whenever we met,
we always talked about the case.
I wanted you to finally move forward.
But if you saw me,
you would be forced to remember the case.
-So my contact info…
-Who asked for that?
I wanted…
to see you, Haruko.
The man who was interviewing
our dad is Yuji Tsuda.
A writer, he won
a newcomer award in university.
That day, he said
he would visit again at night.
But…
that man had an alibi, right?
Then why did he vanish?
Right after the incident,
Tsuda disappeared.
He fled because he's the killer?
Sorry, Haruko.
We have been
searching for him ever since that day.
What are you going to do?
About what?
What will you do…
if you find Tsuda?
Excuse me.
Minoru.
He was brought in this morning.
He didn't have an ID, but said his name.
Is it really Tsuda?
There's no way I would mistake him.
But…
Pancreatic cancer, stage four.
He went into septic shock…
and is now in a coma.
Make no mistake, it was arson and murder.
Is there a reason she didn't run?
We won't be able to get close to Tsuda!
Is there no other way?
-In that case, we'll do it before then.
-What?
Subtitle translation by: Nix S.