=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 20=
(Zhaomu Pavilion)
Your Grace,
I've figured it out.
Indeed, some lords
falsified the roster
to fulfill the Ascension Decree.
I've punished them by the law.
But there's still no clue
to the formation
in the Void Valley.
He and I had all temples investigated.
No other spirits have been missing.
Everything is as usual.
The warrior in the tournament,
the puppet spirit that lured me,
and the formation that trapped Yan and me...
The power of the three
all comes from Chiling Secret Technique.
I guess someone set a trap
to drain my power at first.
Then when I was weak,
he could kill me.
Not too stupid.
No wonder those spirits
can cast spells
with mediocre spirit power.
So someone manipulated them.
To control this,
one must have abundant power.
This technique is mysterious too.
In the Void,
very few spirits are powerful enough
to learn this technique.
The one who had immense power
and assassinated the Sovereign
so blatantly.
It could
only be Bai Sanxing.
But Her Grace confirmed
that Bai Sanxing
was dead.
White Terror was formidable
and vengeful.
If he isn't dead
and has power again,
he'll make a comeback.
Unfortunately,
the three of us jointly sent him
into the Nine-Square Maze Prison.
It was also me
who destroyed his soul candle in person.
A spirit without his soul candle
will definitely be lost
in the Nine-Square Maze Prison.
He'll be annihilated within a century.
Bai Sanxing
must be dead.
In that case,
another powerful spirit here
is eyeing Her Grace covetously.
I need to recuperate for some time.
During this period,
I'll count on the two of you
to manage all the affairs.
Yes.
Young man, don't be stubborn.
Simu has had heavy affairs lately
and can't have both in many cases.
Go back and get some rest.
Are you here
with leads on the assassination?
When you're shut out,
why do you still worry about this?
I'm just standing out here.
I'm not expelled from the Void.
Do you remember the last two spirits
in the Void Tournament?
They fell under a secret spell.
This spell is probably related
to guilty spirits
in the Nine-Square Maze Prison.
Nine-Square Maze Prison?
That's the place spirits fear most.
A prison
for those guilty of grave offenses.
It originated from inner darkness.
Any spirit who is jailed there
will be deprived of his soul candle
and get lost in the sins
fabricated by the Prison.
He'll be tortured by obsessions
of doing everything he hates most
until he's annihilated.
This is the last place
where spirits want to go.
Only Simu dares to go there at times.
I just don't know
why she goes there.
Maybe she cares
about something inside it.
Don't overthink it.
Go back and get some sleep.
Don't waste the efforts Simu made
to cure your cold poison.
I shouldn't have acted alone
to spoil your plan.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
I won't do it again.
I'll never do it again.
I was wrong.
Simu.
You finally let me in.
After the Tournament,
I found two weird spirits.
With a strange smell,
they were like the two
that drained your power.
I followed them to Xuling Temple.
They disappeared.
I think Xuling Temple
is behind this.
Are you done?
Then take the decoction.
After this treatment,
your cold poison will be cured.
Your power is diminished
and hasn't come back.
You could cure my cold poison,
but there's no rush.
Don't you
have anything to say?
If you don't,
I'll say something.
Simu.
Can you let me help you too?
Like how you helped me in my world.
Let me do something for you.
How can you help me?
Mortals who have five senses like you
are everywhere.
What makes you special?
Because of our spell,
you think you're unique?
Maybe you're invincible in battles
of the Mortal World.
But right here,
you're a small and insignificant mortal.
After you cure me,
what will you do?
Drink it.
So your power has come back.
From the Mortal World to the Void,
no one can
actually harm me.
You don't know enough about me.
I still have time to get to know you.
No, you don't.
You don't belong here.
In that case,
why did you allow me
to come here?
Why did you indulge my every move?
You just...
Since you're so curious,
I'm telling you now.
I just had a fleeting fancy.
Now I'm no longer interested.
Since that kiss
gets you to think so much,
this kiss
will put an end.
Tomorrow, Jiang Ai
will send you back.
Everything between us...
Keep it if you want.
Otherwise, I will take it away.
Drop such unrealistic ideas
like helping me.
Foxy,
take the experiences
over this period
as a twist of fate.
Say my name.
Jiang... Jiang Ai.
What a good mood you're in.
You're in a great mood too.
You visit me even during the curfew.
To what do I owe this honor?
You're truly devoted
to Bai Sanxing.
It's been over 300 years
and you can't forget him.
It must have been hard
to bear all this time
before you assassinated Her Grace
to avenge him.
You assist Her Grace
in implementing the decrees.
How could you speak without evidence?
Why would I assassinate Her Grace
to avenge Bai Sanxing?
Bai Sanxing and you
had your differences,
but I believe
you quite enjoyed it.
You and Bai Sanxing
also shared
an unbreakable bond from the past.
After all, you were
his most capable vice lord.
In that case,
you and I are not so different.
Every thirty years,
you wander
around the Prison.
No one but Bai Sanxing
is so hard for you to let go of.
In that case,
don't you want to avenge him?
You used to be utterly loyal
to Bai Sanxing.
In the end, you still betrayed him
for the sake of power.
I guess you've never been loyal
to Bai Sanxing
or He Simu.
You're loyal
only to yourself.
Maybe you've betrayed
your new master
just to get more power.
You schemed
to get close to that mortal
just to use him
as bait
to enter the Prison
for the man you want to see.
This is what we call real betrayal.
You've been amazing.
You were,
and you still are.
Are you not used to it
when I'm not around?
Farewell.
Foxy.
Your Ladyship.
Did you come to ask me
to send you away?
Wait a minute.
I'll arrange it now.
You once promised
you would take me anywhere.
Does it still count?
Last time when Simu and I came here,
we didn't go this deep.
Young man,
it's not too late to regret now.
Xusheng,
wake up.
(Xusheng, the Void)
The mountain spirit is named Xusheng.
[*Means the void]
That's why this is the Void Mountain.
The entire mountain
was transformed from his body.
His eyes are the gate.
The Nine-Square Maze Prison
is inside his skull.
Are you saying
we're going into his skull?
Identify yourselves.
I'm Lord Jiang Ai of Xuling Temple.
Jiang Ai?
What a rare visitor.
What crime did you commit?
Why haven't I received
Her Grace's decree?
Xusheng,
don't be ridiculous.
I'm a good spirit,
sensible and law-abiding.
How could I go to prison?
I just want to take a look in there
with my friend.
He has Her Grace's aura.
Very strong.
And he's a mortal.
I can't let him in.
You're right.
However,
Her Grace might acknowledge him.
That's right.
Simu and I
have a lifelong commitment.
The last mortal
who had the Sovereign's aura
was the wife of the former sovereign.
Fine. In you come.
Take good care of this.
This is your soul candle.
Only by holding this
will you not get lost
in the Nine-Square Maze Prison.
Young man,
are you sure you'll get in there?
Did Simu ever say
I couldn't get in?
There's complete darkness
inside this prison.
When you hold the soul candle,
all you can see
is boundless darkness.
Only when your candle dies out
can you see the real prison.
In the Nine-Square Maze Prison,
evil spirits' desires are amplified.
The most painful and repeated illusions
have been created for them,
luring them to chase.
But they can't obtain anything.
Hope is given and then crushed.
It's like a donkey
with an apple dangling above.
It can see the apple
but can never eat it.
That's a fitting way to put it.
Young man, I admire you.
For Simu's sake,
you even dare to come in here.
But mortals are different from spirits.
Before, you asked me
about Simu's past.
She's been living for 400 years.
400 years.
It includes more than 146,000
days and nights.
Like a book with 146,000 pages.
Can you understand her?
She said I needn't.
Possibly because
she thinks I can't do it.
This prison is terrifying,
but when we follow
the Eight Trigrams,
we'll find the Life Gate and leave.
Your Ladyship,
I heard something.
Bai Sanxing,
you aren't annihilated yet?
Young man, move aside.
You can't take him.
Watch out, young man!
Your Ladyship,
shall we bet again?
If I can get out
of this prison alive,
tell me everything
about Simu's past.
Deal?
Don't be ridiculous.
Without the soul candle,
how can you get out of the illusion?
Duan Xu,
I accept the bet!
Make sure you come out alive!
As you expected, Your Grace,
something's wrong.
All the spirits
match the records.
But some of them only
remember going to the Ascension Pool,
but nothing after that.
I suspect these spirits
were manipulated.
This is one of them.
I interrogated him.
Sadly,
I got nothing out of him.
Simu.
Your Grace,
Bai Sanxing isn't annihilated yet.
He's still in the Prison.
You went there?
And you saw him.
That young man of yours...
Bai Sanxing broke his soul candle,
and he's lost there.
What happened?
I don't think
he can make it back.
Your Grace, it's all my fault.
I failed to protect him.
Going in to find him?
Simu,
he's lost his candle.
Even if you go in,
you won't find him.
Even if you find him,
you can't get him out.
Besides, Bai Sanxing is in there.
If he does anything,
you'll be in danger.
You think I'll be scared?
I don't want you to risk it.
Even a powerful spirit
will be annihilated if he's lost.
A mortal will die in there.
And this prison
is filled with delusional evil spirits.
A living man in there
will be torn apart.
He's lost in the illusion.
Without a soul candle,
he can't get out of this prison.
He doesn't die easily.
His fate is linked to mine.
If I can find him
and relight his candle
with mine,
he may regain consciousness.
Simu!
Using your soul candle?
If he doesn't wake up,
but extinguishes your candle,
what will happen?
You'll be lost in there
and suffer forever.
Do you want to end up like Bai Sanxing?
I'm not letting you go!
He's a mortal.
He'll die.
The longer he stays,
the more dangerous it will be.
How can you
take such a risk
for a mere mortal?
He isn't a mere mortal.
He's my spell bearer.
He belongs to me.
When I want him to live,
then he shall not die.
Xusheng,
give me a soul candle.
Spell bearer?
The one who can lend her
his five senses?
Simu. Simu!
You know very well.
You can't stop her.
(This is what this prison looks like)
(after my soul candle dies out.)
Kill.
He Simu.
I'll kill you!
He Simu,
I'll kill you.
He Simu.
Kill.
- You know Simu?
- Kill her.
I deserve to be
the Sovereign!
Kill.
Who did you teach
the technique for killing Simu
in the tournament?
Mortal?
You're a mortal.
Answer me.
Get out.
I want to get out.
Simu.
Father.
Father, help me!
Help me!
Father.
I won't help you.
Climb out on your own.
Help me!
Give me your hand!
My son is in Daizhou,
staying with his grandmother.
You got the wrong boy.
Father, give me your hand!
Simu,
there you are.
Mortal,
you just don't give up on me, do you?
Yeah.
So I came to the Void
and even entered this prison.
Have you enjoyed yourself?
If you have,
then leave.
Leave the Void.
Simu,
don't you want senses?
I'll always lend you my senses.
Having your senses
is just a game.
I'm fed up now.
You should go.
Duan Xu.
Go find Duan Xu.
You're inside an illusion
and everything is fake.
I'm taking you out.
Duan Xu,
I'm He Simu.
Foxy,
wake up.
wake up now.
Foxy,
you're too lost in illusion.
(The sense of touch.)
(I have this sense again.)
(Even the sense of smell.)
(I can smell again.)
Simu.
You're awake.
Come have breakfast.
What's wrong?
Don't space out.
Come have breakfast.
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪