( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
[Episode 2]
Boss!
Boss, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Are you hurt, Boss?
Boss, why is blood gushing out of your hand?
It's nothing.
Why is everyone barking away?
How's your hand?
Boss, you've lost so much blood.
Hao!
Who's Hao?
Hao, are you okay?
Seems like that was Liu Yi's original name.
Sis! Sis!
- Hao!
- I'm fine.
What are you doing?
Get lost!
Step aside, all of you!
Move!
Sis!
Back off!
No one is allowed to bully him!
Sis!
Go!
Back!
Step back, everyone!
He's just a kid! Stay away!
No one is allowed to bully Hao!
Hao!
Hao, are you okay?
Did they hurt you, Hao?
It's all because of me.
It's all my fault.
- Sis!
- It's all my fault.
- It's my responsibility.
I didn't protect you properly.
Sis!
I'm Hao.
See?
I'm fine now.
You're perfectly fine.
You're fine.
You're alive and well.
Sis, I'll take you home.
Home.
You're fine.
- Let's go.
- Hao...
- Come on.
Stop looking.
My backpack!
Isn't that Dual Blades Xia?
Who's that next to him?
Doesn't look like a gangster.
What are you trying to do?
What are you doing?
If a single hair on my sister
is touched, you're dead.
Can we take the alley?
What are you afraid of?
I'm here.
I'm just afraid Dad
will see me with gang members.
He'll worry about me.
I, Dual Blades Xia, have nothing to fear.
There's no need to be afraid, okay?
I should at least have this bit of aura.
That's not what I meant.
Fine, take the alley!
Move aside.
[Loyalty]
How's your sister now?
She's asleep.
You can take a look yourself.
Okay.
Step over the ancestral hall gate.
The brave soul lives and dies.
Loyalty and righteousness
engraved in the heart.
Two slashes mark the traitor.
Why won't you come in?
I won't join the gang.
Today, you've seen
all the secrets of Xiaoqi Hall.
If you don't step over,
then I'll have no choice
but to cut you down.
You won't kill me.
You just saved me.
If you kill me,
it'll be a waste of your effort.
And I don't think you're the kind of person
who just slashes and kills recklessly.
You're from Xiaoqi Hall,
the mighty Dual Blades Xia,
destined for great things.
I'm just a university student with no weapons.
Why would I be worthy of tainting your blades?
I really didn't expect this.
You really know how to flatter people, huh?
Four eyes, you want to be my lackey?
I wouldn't even want you.
Who wants to be your lackey?
No one does.
Bandage me.
All right.
It might hurt a bit.
Just bear with it.
Who do you think I am?
Since I was little,
I've had more injuries
than the books you've read.
What's this small injury compared to that?
He Chu San, why are you pressing so hard?
I'm not.
Don't pretend.
I've always thought you were dishonest.
You've been messing with me
ever since you started writing the script.
And then you went to complain to my sis.
I could tell right away
you're not a good person.
Don't think I'm clueless.
I just didn't feel like arguing with you.
Well, you must be the bigger person.
You're so smooth with your words.
- Xia Liu Yi.
- It's "Big Bro" for you.
Big Bro Liu Yi.
You have an injury on your face, too.
Come here, I'll tend to it for you.
By the way, that day backstage,
what did Xiao Man ask you?
She asked me what love is.
How did you answer her?
I didn't get a chance to answer her.
Actually, I don't know either.
This is the first time
I've written a love story.
You wrote it terribly.
But the book did say...
Love...
is when a person is willing to risk everything
to save someone else.
Big Bro Liu Yi.
Why did you save me?
He Chu San.
You really are...
so noisy.
[Become A Love Expert in Three Days]
[Love Story Encyclopedia]
[Romantic Language]
San.
San! You're back!
You didn't come home all night yesterday.
You didn't even go to Fei's place.
What happened to your head?
Tell me.
Did someone bully you outside?
No.
Dad, please tell Fei
I won't be going to work these two weeks.
I've recently joined a new project development.
I'm really busy.
Then you were at school yesterday, right?
What about your head?
A little black dog bit it.
It's fine.
By the way, Dad.
I want to ask you something.
If someone easily gets frightened
and then loses their mind,
what's a good way to treat them?
Student, you're so energetic today.
Xiao Ma, aren't we filming today?
Big Sis is sick, so she's resting today.
What about the little black dog?
What about Big Bro Liu Yi?
Who do you think you are?
Why would Boss need to tell you anything?
Four eyes!
Come here.
Then please help me to pass this to Big Sis.
This is the calming powder Dad prescribed.
And this is the answer Big Sis wanted.
Do you think just because
you've been out with Boss a few times,
you've risen in status?
Don't you know who Big Sis is?
Do you think she can take
medicine given by anyone?
You're just a useless guy.
Big Sis asked you to deliver it personally?
Give me the money.
I'm in a good mood today.
You're in luck today.
Thank you, Xiao Ma.
Go do your thing.
Hurry up.
- Deal the cards.
- Continue.
Money, give me the money.
A love letter.
Love?
Boss.
Just now, that student
asked me to deliver a letter to Big Sis.
The lead guy said
it's a love letter.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Get lost.
Sis.
It's me.
Liu Yi.
You're here.
I've taken over a few shops recently.
The boss of Guan Shan Song
gave me a bunch of stuff.
Do you like it?
What's wrong?
Why didn't you stay at the ancestral hall
for a few more days?
None of you are there.
I don't want to stay there alone.
Where's Big Bro?
Isn't he with you?
He only shows up occasionally.
And then disappears for a long time.
- He...
- Like a seagull.
He's very busy.
What about you?
You're busy, too.
You never come to see me.
Do you think I'm sick and can't recognize you?
- No.
- It's not that.
I don't mean to.
I... I don't know what happened.
You were frightened at that time.
It wasn't your fault.
Madam, it's time for your medicine.
I've been following the doctor's orders lately.
Taking my medicine on time.
I'll get better soon.
You're amazing, Big Sis.
Liu Yi, do you know?
Actually, I'm not sick.
I just get a bit upset sometimes.
I'm upset.
Why do I have to take medicine so often?
I get upset.
Why is it so easy for me to feel upset?
I'm upset that he never comes to see me.
I'm upset...
What's wrong?
He doesn't love me.
Doesn't love you?
How could that be?
Cheng Qing, you don't love me.
I'm Liu Yi.
Big Sis?
Cheng Qing.
You love me.
Then why do you rarely hug me?
When you hug me, I've looked at you seriously.
Your soul isn't here.
Your eyes...
They seem to be looking at someone far away.
You don't love me.
Where is your soul?
- Big Sis.
- Your soul has flown away.
Like that seagull.
I'm Liu Yi.
- Big Sis.
- You don't love me.
If you don't love me,
then why did you marry me?
- Big Sis.
- Why?
Who is it that you really love?
Big Sis.
Big Sis, it's me.
I'm Liu Yi.
I'm Liu Yi. It's me.
It's okay now.
L-Liu Yi.
I...
- Was I just...
- It's okay now.
It's really okay now.
Cheng Qing, you don't love me.
Your eyes...
They seem to be looking at someone far away.
Boss, Liu Yi's waiting for you.
Why are you here?
I heard you got hurt.
Why don't you stay here tonight?
You can sleep in the guest room.
Brother.
Do you have someone else on the side?
What nonsense are you talking about?
Big Sis said you don't love her.
She said there's someone else in your heart.
Do you still remember
what you said when you...
begged me to marry Xiao Man?
You're about to turn twenty.
What birthday gift do you want?
Will you agree to anything I want?
Of course.
I care about you so much.
I want...
my sister to be your wife.
You said...
you hope the three of us
can be like a real family.
Forever together.
I agreed.
That's because...
I wish the same.
And I only hope for that.
So, don't say such nonsense anymore.
There's a nice Western restaurant
near Repulse Bay.
I'll take her there in a few days.
Brother.
Brother!
Can't you love her truly?
Your tie looks good today.
It's been a week.
A whole week without filming.
Liu Yi hasn't shown up either.
I don't know when
I can return to school for classes.
If I don't go back soon,
the school will probably expel me.
Liu Yi, you're here.
Liu Yi, you play billiards really well.
Watch carefully.
Okay.
How is it?
How's your injury?
Are you blind?
All nonsense.
What about your sister?
What exactly are you trying to say?
Dad got me a new doctor...
No, my dad got me a new calming prescription,
and a blood-activating,
bruise-healing medicine.
For you and Big Sis.
I don't know if it will be useful.
I suspected you had a problem before.
- Did you have feelings for my sister?
- No.
Then why are you so nice to my sister?
I heard that when I wasn't around,
you asked around about my sister.
I was just worried about you two.
Liu Yi.
Are you bullying Chu San again?
No.
Definitely not.
Chu San, are you okay?
Just my ear feels a bit...
My ear is a bit thick.
It doesn't hurt.
Yes, Sis.
I was just teasing him.
Right?
Right, Chu San?
What's this?
These are for Big Sis.
Supplements. Tonic supplements.
Sis, you look really pretty today.
- Really?
- Yes.
Cheng Qing is taking me
to a Western restaurant for steak.
Their steaks are really delicious.
Chu San, do you like steak?
I've never had it.
Western food is too expensive.
One meal would cost me
a month's living expenses.
Then why don't you come with us?
Cheng Qing will pay.
As a reward for your letter.
No way.
Liu Yi, you should be more generous.
No, it's not about generosity.
Come with us.
It's not like there's no room.
Let's go.
Come on.
It's not like I wanted to go.
Let's go.
Hope to see you again.
Good evening, Mr. Hao.
You reserved a Christmas-themed table for two.
Do you want to change it to four people now?
We'll sit over there.
You two can sit over there.
Okay, it's rare for you
to make friends on your own.
Take care of Chu San.
- I will.
- This way.
We'll go over there.
Say, don't they make a perfect pair?
Don't you know how to eat?
Then use your hands.
Excuse me!
A pair of chopsticks, please.
Sir, this is a Western restaurant.
No one eats Western food with chopsticks.
Chopsticks.
Do you understand?
We Chinese use chopsticks when we eat.
All right, please wait a moment.
He sure talks a lot.
Thank you, Xia Liu Yi.
Also, thanks for saving me that day.
Don't flatter yourself.
You help me out.
That makes you my henchman.
Taking care of my brothers
is what a leader should do.
I'm not your henchman.
After you finish writing your script,
we won't have anything to do with each other.
Even if you die on the streets,
I won't even glance at you.
Sir, your chopsticks.
Gangster. Rogue.
Beast in human clothes.
Man with an animal's heart.
Cold and ruthless.
He Chu San!
Three second rule! It's still edible!
Cheng Qing, this place looks great.
Do you remember?
Actually, you've brought me here before.
Back then, we spent Christmas together.
We had a barbecue nearby.
We even set off fireworks.
Liu Yi was especially mischievous.
He got his butt burned by a firework.
I won't bring you along next time.
Sorry.
It got on my clothes.
These clothes are expensive.
Then I'll help you wash it.
Sorry about that.
Liu Yi is still as mischievous as ever.
Yes.
Liu Yi is becoming more like
a little troublemaker.
Cheng Qing.
Am I boring you?
Not at all.
Why would you think that?
Is the steak not to your taste?
Try mine.
Cheng Qing.
Let's get a divorce.
Are you feeling unwell?
Did you bring any medicine?
No.
I'm completely clear-headed and calm.
You...
You don't love me.
Our marriage...
If it's only been my one-sided wish,
then it's all a mistake.
- Xiao Man...
- I've known for a long time.
I just didn't want to admit it.
I thought... I loved you.
And you've always treated me so well.
We'd definitely be happy.
But I was wrong.
Love isn't in the eyes.
It's in the heart.
You treat me well because of family affection.
But what I want...
What I want is love.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to admit it so quickly.
Just lie to me for a moment.
Not even that?
I'm sorry.
You... You don't have to say sorry.
Wasn't it the same back then?
I didn't ask about your feelings
and just dragged both of us
all the way to this point.
Liu Yi wouldn't agree.
Liu Yi...
He's just too worried about me.
All along...
Even though I'm the older sister,
he's been the one trying to protect me,
and giving me everything I need.
Let's wait until the movie is over.
After the movie wraps up,
I'll tell him.
I'll say it with you.
Cheng Qing.
Can you...
tell me who you really like?
I'm sorry.
Hao Cheng Qing.
You're such an idiot.
Okay, okay, no rush.
There's enough for everyone.
This one's yours.
Take your time.
Thank you.
Come back for more.
Thanks. What kind of event is this?
- It's so lively.
- A new movie is showing.
I heard it's pretty good.
- Is that right?
- Come and see for yourself.
"Heroes of the Streets."
Starring Xia Xiao Man.
[Producer: Xia Liu Yi]
[Screenplay: He Chu San]
Do you want to watch it?
No.
You should watch it with your dad.
It'll be fun.
Look. Producer, Xia Liu Yi.
Fei.
Dad loves Cantonese opera.
He's not into trendy stuff.
I heard there'll be a performance
at the Chengzhai City God Temple tonight.
It's "The Return of the Red Plum."
If Dad knew, he'd definitely be very happy.
- Really?
- Yes.
Will I have time to change my clothes?
Plenty of time. Seven o'clock tonight.
- Really?
- Yes.
But this person is really beautiful.
- Let's go.
- Boss, look.
So many flower baskets.
Boss.
Half of the city's influential people are here
for this special preview.
Boss.
Are they going to announce you
as the young master of the hall?
Don't talk nonsense here.
Let me tell you.
They have all invested in the movie.
In the end, they're just here
for the box office share.
Of course they're happy to come.
Young master?
Stop talking nonsense.
If I find out you're making this up later,
I'll cut out your tongue.
Then... this movie is about to be released.
Big Sis is going to be famous all over town.
Exactly, exactly.
Of course.
My sister will definitely be happy.
Big Bro will definitely be happy, too.
It's almost time.
I'm going to pick up Big Bro and my sister.
Watch over this place for me.
- Don't worry.
- We got this.
Okay, over here.
- Come on, come on.
- Take care of the V.I.Ps.
[Heroes of the Streets]
[Premieres Today]
Big Bro.
Big Sis.
Hao.
- Sister.
- Don't come closer.
Come down quickly.
Come down.
Here.
Don't scare me.
Big Sis, what's wrong?
Come back quickly.
Big Sis!
Liu Yi.
Brother.
Big Bro!
Are these my Qing Long Dual Blades?
Big Bro.
I'll take you away.
Hold on to me.
Xia Liu Yi.
Aren't you supposed to be brave?
Aren't you the twin red staff expert?
If you've got the guts, come out
and carry away
your brother and sister's bodies.
I really want to see if your blades
are faster than my gun.
Fucking hell.
Spread the word.
Xia Liu Yi killed Big Boss Qing Long
and forced his crazy sister
to jump off the building.
The entire Xiaoqi Hall
is mobilized to capture the traitor.
I want him, dead or alive.
Yes.
Don't move.
Stay quiet.
Prepare some hemostatic powder for me.
And some gauze.
Yes.
Xia Liu Yi.
So, it really is you, damn brat.