I'll do it.
- What?
- I said I'll do it.
I said I'll join your study group.
Really?
What are you guys doing?
Wait, Inspector...
Assault and arson.
What's your name?
Pardon? Me?
Why are you here?
What if you get blamed for being with me?
Well...
the team leader of the study group is captured, so-
What?
What leader?
You're so easy.
Well, here. I found them while cleaning the classroom.
Thank you.
Okay.
Well, then.
Well, I...
- What?
- What you did in the training room yesterday...
and in the classroom just now...
I want to thank you for it.
No need to thank me. We're friends.
I gave you jellies and vitamins and...
when you fell asleep in the library, I waited for you so you wouldn't be late for class.
But no need to thank me for those.
I didn't thank you for those things.
I told you to think about what you did, and you're laughing?
I'm sorry.
Hey, hey, hey.
Go, go. Go forward. Go.
Go.
There are problem students like him at every school.
Don't worry so much. We'll hold a campus violence committee quickly
and get him expelled.
- Expelled?
- Vice Principal.
A wrongdoing should be followed by a punishment.
But getting him expelled is a bit-
Be quiet.
Summon his parents and prepare for the campus violence committee.
Do you understand?
Let's check out the Training Building since we didn't get there earlier.
Isn't it the school that's actually at fault?
Ms. Lee Han Gyeong.
Did I hear you wrong just now?
This school cares more about one inspector than its 600 students.
Seriously. I can't believe this...
You're making me look like a terrible person.
He's the one who's bad. Him.
He's like a thug who's violent in school.
He had no choice because he was bullied and assaulted first.
He used violence to stop the violence? Violence can't-
Violence can't be justified. I agree with you.
But as for what I have seen here for the last couple of days,
I'm not so sure.
Can students...
even defend themselves without violence?
You haven't changed, Ms. Lee Han Gyeong.
You weren't the top scorer on the Teacher Certification Exam out of luck.
Top scorer?
Yes. I remember now.
The top scorer on the Teacher Certification Exam last year, Lee Han Gyeong.
But she didn't register for some reason, and the certification was canceled.
That's you, Ms. Lee, right?
I'll become a school teacher.
Someone who has a good influence on students.
That kind of a teacher.
So, how are you planning to fix this school's problem?
Even though she was the top scorer,
what could a rookie substitute teacher do-
A study group.
A study group?
Yes, a study group.
Forming a study group was his idea.
I'll work hard on creating it with him.
Inspector, let's stop this meaningless conversation and-
It's a good idea. A study group.
Inspector.
Vice Principal,
the student wants to study. Is that a problem?
I just noticed faulty fire alarms and cigarette butts on the floor...
[Study - Join if you want to study!]
[Hwang Min Hyun]
[Han Ji Eun]
[Cha Woo Min]
[Lee Jong Hyun]
[Shin Su Hyun]
[Yoon Sang Jung / Gong Do Yu]
[Study Group]
Ga Min,
it's 6:34.
Thank you.
Ga Min,
wake up. Time to get ready for school.
Today's another day to study hard.
Se Hyeon.
What?
It's our first time running into each other here, right?
I suppose.
You look a mess.
Did you see a doctor?
Don't overreact.
Why not? We're in a study group together.
Come on.
Be quiet.
By the way,
did the inspector really approve it?
Yes.
It's a study group acknowledged by the Education Department.
That's not hard for you, right?
That's why you were so confident, right?
Yes, I can do it.
I wish you good luck, then.
The moment the study group gets canceled,
your contract will be terminated, too.
Thank you, Vice Principal.
I'm curious.
Would you be able to say naive things like a study group
even after experiencing this school more?
Five students in two weeks?
Yes. That way, he'd acknowledge it as an official club.
We're screwed.
Why? You don't think we could?
Well, you want us to find three more students who want to study, not just one.
Guys, there's a saying that goes...
What was it? The quote by Napoleon.
"My unhappiness today is the revenge of time once..."
No, not that one. The other one.
"If you wish to be a success in the world,
- promise everything, deliver nothing."
- No, no.
- "My height is the shortest on the ground, but-"
- Yes.
"The word 'impossible' is not in my dictionary."
I was expecting something special.
Yun Ga Min, Kim Se Hyeon,
don't you want to prove the Vice Principal wrong for not believing in us?
Yes, I do, but is it realistically-
We can do it.
We can find the study group members.
[Study]
- Study?
Who's this crazy person?
F***. I want to crack my head and skip a class. Agree?
- Agree.
Se Hyeon.
Yes? What?
We'll get five members easily.
You think so?
What if more than 10 students apply?
Should it be first come, first served?
Or the ones with higher grades?
Shouldn't you get removed first by that rule?
First come, first served would be good.
Hello? This is Yun Ga Min, the leader of Yuseong Technical High's study group.
You want to join the study group?
What grade and what class are you in?
This is Chu Ho Jin, Class 7, 12th Grade.
Class 7, 12th Grade. Chu...
I want to confess my love to a girl from a school nearby.
I'm too embarrassed to tell anyone.
Would you be able to give me advice?
It's been less than three hours since we put up the poster.
Are you Yun Ga Min?
I heard the rumor.
[Ranking No. 3 in 10th grade]
It's dangerous.
Cut the bullshit. Did he eat the devil's fruit?
Why would flame come out of his foot?
I saw it myself. He's f***ing strong.
Lee Hyeon Wu was swinging a piece of metal.
But Yun Ga Min or whatever was shooting flame off his foot.
Anyway, it was f***ing crazy.
You'll get f***ed at this rate.
Cut the bullshit. I can smell that loser from here.
Move. Whatever.
Are you Yun Ga Min?
I heard the rumor.
Someone finally heard the rumor.
Nice to meet you.
Hold on.
The application forms were...
They were here.
It was here...
Just one moment.
Wow, he won't even get up.
Huh?
[Application Form]
He's getting up now.
I'll get you a new one from the locker.
Did he pass out?
Did you see him hitting his head with the door?
Wow, what a crazy bastard.
Huh?
Why...
His nose is bleeding.
Are you okay? Wake up.
Wow, he's slapping someone who passed out. Isn't that too much?
The guy who beat up Lee Hyeon Wu. That bastard is f***ing evil.
Why? Did something happen again?
Hey.
No. 3 was dragged to the library like a dog
and got beat up with "The Rules of Mathematics."
And he hit his head with a planter.
And with a second planter, too.
- He was hospitalized.
- Hospitalized?
He was hospitalized.
By the way,
did our school have a library?
That kid from yesterday didn't contact you, either, right?
I don't think he came to school today.
The first applicant is suddenly sick? How sad.
I said he wasn't an applicant.
- What?
- I need to do things differently.
- How?
- If waiting doesn't get us anyone,
we should look ourselves.
Look for what?
The eyes that yearn to study.
My question is,
why does he beat someone up in the library, not the rooftop?
The rooftop is classic.
The library is huge and the sound echos.
Right.
So what, you idiot?
Gosh, you dumbass.
I can't stand you.
He wants to hear the opponent's moaning with a surround system.
Wow, what a f***ing monster.
He really is a psycho.
He's out of his mind.
Hey, hey, hey.
The ramen is...
The clear-eyed ones are always the craziest ones.
Who does he want for his study group or whatever?
Someone who wants to study, I'm sure. It's a study group.
No one wants to study at this school.
- I know, you f***er.
- You son of a bitch.
He wants bastards who refuse to study
so he could torture them by making them study.
- Who refuses to study?
- That makes sense.
- You get it, right?
- I'm screwed. I should pat my hair down.
Take your stupid clothes off first.
Let's go. There's no one here.
F***.
That f***er.
- You almost got screwed.
- Are you okay?
He's asking for help, isn't he?
Doesn't he look f***ing tortured?
- I know.
- F***.
I almost was forced to join his study group.
- Hey.
- What? What? What?
How strange.
It's obvious.
You can't find anyone who wants to study at this school.
It's not that.
I don't see anyone at all.
Huh? Park Geon Yeop?
Do you know him?
Yes, we're middle school classmates.
He left for the US to study in 7th grade. When did he come back?
He studied in the US?
Hey, hey, hey! Don't mess with him!
Shit.
I heard you came from the US.
You must speak English well.
Do you want to join our study group?
Study group?
Yes.
You look confident.
Or do you not care about people around you getting hurt?
Good job.
See you tomorrow.
The call is not going through.
You'll be connected to the voicemail after the beep...
[Lee Hyeon Wu - Class 4, 10th Grade]
[Lee Hyeon Wu - Student Transcript]
[50% discount coupon for Vita Study's online lecture!]
Must we form a study group?
Why don't you just go to academies?
Daechi-dong, Mok-dong, and Noryangjin. I've been everywhere.
There are online lectures, too.
Jeon Seung Jae, Choi Chi Yeol, Jeon Jong Ryeol...
Okay.
I'm sorry.
By the way, shouldn't you play sports instead of studying with your physique?
Sports?
I only play sports to build stamina for studying.
I know. That's why you started,
but you could do that instead if you're gifted.
But I prefer studying.
What? Aren't you too obviously disappointed?
We don't have a single applicant.
Let's go out.
- Pardon?
- You need to switch things up sometimes.
Let's go.
Ga Min.
How about this one?
I have this book at home.
- Really?
- Yes.
- How about this one?
- That, too.
Ga Min, how about this?
Se Hyeon, how about this one?
I like all of them.
Wow.
What are you doing there?
No, it's nothing.
- Thank you.
Thank you for this food.
- Let's eat.
- Bon appetit.
It's so tasty.
It's good.
Can I pick three?
Yes. They look tasty. Pick some.
Are there usually this many?
I'll have the rice and chocolate...
By the way, Ga Min, I have a question.
Why do you buy so many pens?
This pen has nice cornering. It's for math since it's good for numbers.
This is for dictating teachers since it doesn't bleed.
This blue one is good for your memories because it boosts serotonin.
And this is a new one. It has a nice balance. I want to try it.
What are you, a pen expert?
What kind of pen do you use?
Me?
I use the Monami pen that cost 300 won.
Monami pen that costs 300 won.
That was the secret.
It feels sincere and grounded somehow.
It's like the Gungseo font.
I should've gotten that, too.
What a shame.
By the way, why did you come to Yuseong when you were the top scorer?
I know. You could've gone to a better school.
The thing is...
A lot of crazy things happened to me then.
So, I forgot to register.
How cool.
Yes, totally.
Anyway, since we switched things up today,
let's not give up on the study group and work harder.
Okay.
Fighting.
- Fighting!
What's this doing here?
What?
It's gone.
What? What is?
My book must've gotten into Ms. Lee's bag.
You can get it back tomorrow.
What? What book was it?
I heard you have a curfew.
Right.
Here it is.
[Yun Ga Min, Class 4, 10th Grade]
You came, Ms. Lee.
Hyeon Wu.
[Missed Call - Ms. Lee]
Hyeon Wu,
what are you doing right now?
We want to join the study group, too.
You told me to visit anytime.
This isn't what I meant.
Maybe not?
I don't...
want to report you to the police. Leave.
Let's talk at school tomorrow.
By the way, Ms. Lee,
I'd die if I just left like this.
Hyeon Wu,
I'm starting to get angry right now.
- So-
- Ms. Lee,
you came to our school a few days ago.
What did you do that you already got a target on your back?
I got a target on my back?
Who else?
No way. You really don't know.
What do I not know?
- I'm talking about Han Ul.
- Han Ul?
Han Ul told me to stop you from teaching.
But I don't know what I'm supposed to do.
Could you tell me?
[Yun Ga Min, Class 4, 10th Grade]
The call is not going through.
You'll be connected to the voicemail after the beep.
Once you're connected, there will be...
Ms. Lee,
do you know why people are scared even though the police are around?
Because the police come when everything is over.
What? Who-
What the hell!
Hey, you bastard!
Son of a bitch!
You're the one by the drum, right?
Geon Yeop.
How did you know to come here?
There he is.
Hey.
Give me your phone.
Hey, I found them!
Hey, guys,
let's calm down and-
I'm sorry, Ms. Lee.
I should've told you sooner.
He's a ruthless bastard who beats his teachers and women.
Come at me.
Instead, be ready to die.
[Yun Ga Min, Class 4, 10th Grade]
Hey, they got them!
Who's this bastard?
I think I've seen him somewhere.
I remember that bastard.
You're Park Geon Yeop from Segyeong Middle School, right?
Do you know him?
You know him, too. He was all over the news.
When he was in middle school?
Don't you remember the random murder?
Geez Louise!
I remembered when he squirmed after getting punched in the left abdomen.
He was stabbed there.
Kick him.
Stop!
What's this?
Ms. Lee, are you okay?
Let go.
Hey, don't get scared.
He can't fight all of us-
Where did he go this time?
[Work-out: Nunchaku training]
Nunchaku?
♫ We the backpackers ♫
♫ Strong resolutions packed in our backpacks ♫
♫ We're backpackers even if our shoes wear out ♫
♫ We're backpackers ♫
♫ I always start without fear ♫
♫ I'm barefoot from the beginning ♫
♫ My eyes see it, they're no bagpipes ♫
Fight!
♫ You don't know the basics, stupid ♫
♫ I'm ready to fight ♫
♫ We the backpackers ♫
♫ Strong resolutions packed in our backpacks ♫
♫ We're the backpackers, yeah ♫
It's hard to train with them because they're poorly made.
Are you okay, Ms. Lee?
Did you get injured-
I heard you know about that case.
We can't end things this way, then.
What are you saying, you f***er?
Geon Yeop, please. Stop.
Try to remember.
You must've heard something because you're Pi Han Ul's underling.
I don't know! F***.
You opened Ms. Lee's door with this, huh?
I'm thinking of opening your mouth with this.
Hey! Stop him!
Watch your teeth.
- That's enough.
- Let go.
I don't know why you're so angry, but you're going too far.
That's enough, you said?
How could I? My mom died.
So, don't interfere and leave.
Don't let go! F***!
- Let go!
- Don't!
Ms. Lee,
do whatever you want to do with those guys who ran away.
Fair punishment?
Don't believe in that kind of stuff.
I'm telling you this because you remind me of my mom.
You wanted me in your study group, right?
Huh?
- Yeah.
- Wake up.
This is Yuseong Technical High.
Hey, Ga Min.
Here.
Ms. Lee, are you sure you'll be okay?
Yes.
Don't worry about me. Go home and study.
And...
you know we still have plenty of time, right?
["As You Think, So Shall You Become." - Bruce Lee]
[112*]
(Number for police in Korea)
Ms. Lee,
It's Hun Jae.
Please open the door.
I need to tell you something.
Ms. Lee, Could you forgive me just once?
I'm sorry.
Han Ul made me do it.
He'd kill me if I didn't listen to him.
I'm so sorry. Please forgive me just once.
Please.
I'm sorry.
Fine.
But I want to ask you something.
[Yuseong Technical High School]
[Get five members in two weeks. 1. Yun Ga Min. 2. Kim Se Hyeon]
There are only a few days left now.
Don't give up. We can do it.
Geez, you scared me.
What do we do?
- This is it, right?
- Yes.
You're sure, right?
I'm telling you.
Do you want to do it?
It obviously has to be you.
No, you can go, too.
It's okay. Go before I change my mind.
Right. Before you change your mind.
By the way, what was the name again?
Ji Woo. Lee Ji Woo.
Oh, didn't I tell you?
Yuseong Technical High is...
co-ed.
[Study Group]