Your fans, they have rights to call it.
Be prepared for consequences.
You know how it feels like when your life
is going down the cliff.
You son of a bitch! You're so tough in
game, why don't you shoot me in real life?
Bambi? Did you tell someone
else that Anyone is Dream?
Now everyone knows her
identity. I'm heading to your place.
Did you tell Diesel that I'm Anyone?
You've never f... king changed.
Dream!
Diesel!
An ambulance…
Bambi.
I'll handle this.
Who did this to you?
Dad, can you…
Find an ambulance for my
friend please? Someone shot her.
Can you send help?
Okay. Thank you.
Is he gonna help her?
Can you hold her?
My Dad will send someone to help.
Don't let anyone find out that I'm here.
Take care of Dream.
Diesel? Where are you going?
Please help my friend!
Please!
Please help her!
Let's follow up on a case of 17-year-old
female student got shot.
She was admitted to the hospital already.
We still can't find out who the gunman is.
Our team is asking
around for the witnesses.
She deserved it for taking side with Bambi.
Bambi? How is Dream?
Did the doctor say anything?
She's still in an emergency room.
No one came out. I Danupha's relative?
I'm her sister.
Can you fill out the form and
get me her ID card please?
Thank you. Please save her.
Sure, when her guardian arrives,
please tell them. I Sure, thanks.
Where's her phone?
Do you know who did it? The home invader?
Her mom called.
Bambi? How are you?
Did you get hurt as well?
How's Dream? Did her parents come?
What's going on? What did you do?
Why did he shoot her?
I don't know.
Is there anything you haven't told me?
If you didn't do anything,
who would shoot her like that?
Anyone is…
Can I stay with you for a week?
Did you tell Diesel that I'm Anyone?
You've never f... king changed.
Dream!
I don't know who did it. I
don't know why he did it.
He could come back to
shoot you as well. I Mom!
I have no idea.
I don't know.
Alright, I'm sorry.
Breaking news from a school girl got shot.
It is reported that
they caught a gunman already.
He is a 17-year-old student from
international school. I My
people found him already.
Job did it.
Job found out about that girl
because of you.
Same passcode?
I think we talked about this already.
I'm sorry.
Car key?
If you cause so many troubles
when you're out of the house,
then from now on
you need to stay inside.
You can't go anywhere.
Do you want to know how I've been?
You're a grown-up now.
How long do I need to coddle you?
Alright, next step
is your road map.
We'll start with the second
season of Paint Your Dream.
Marketing team will prepare for Asia tour.
This one is for you, Namkhang,
because on the last day of the tour,
we will announce your solo album.
In the meantime, I want you to expand
your fan base as much as possible.
You get it right?
Move on to TVC.
I think that both of you
should be presenters for
at least seven products.
If we follow the plan, we'll earn enough
to make our first feature film.
This one is for you.
You can share your input to writing team
about the characters
you'd like to portrait.
On one condition,
you have to reach this goal only,
if it's less than this, we don't
have enough fund to do so.
You get it right?
Can the number be a littler lower?
It's twice more than last year.
Pure.
I need to be honest with
you, but think about it,
who choose to be in this industry?
You need to be more professional.
Don't you even think that your
lifeline is more important than others.
Look around this room.
Did you see the
consequences of your actions?
Who disappeared from
this room because of you?
Tang loved you so much.
But I think she loved you two too much.
That's why I replaced her with Boss.
You need to focus
and stop dragging people
down to hell with you.
Pure,
I know that you're worried about Bambi.
But Tang got fired.
Be careful of your action.
I need to leave.
Hello. How is Dream?
She's better. I'll be right back.
How are you?
It's because of me.
It's because of me again.
If I hadn't let her stay here,
if I hadn't told Diesel about her,
if I hadn't been so selfish,
if I hadn't wanted any of these,
it wouldn't have turned out to be this way.
Don't blame yourself like that.
Things happened.
But I believe that it will be okay.
You called me so many times.
I'm sorry, I didn't touch my phone.
It's okay.
What is it?
Jib texted me to go to see
Ms.Duangtawan tomorrow.
But I don't want to anymore.
I
I don't want it anymore.
It still won't help it if you
stay here and stress out.
You should get out of the
hospital to do something.
I know that you feel guilty about Dream.
But you should wait
until she wakes up first.
Just try it.
We can use weeds for Ikebana arrangement,
if we accept it and see
beauty in imperfections.
Even wilted weeds
can be pretty if they're in the right place.
The speech that you said in live,
I admired it.
I know this director and he's
looking for a new face for his film.
I think it should suit
you well, you should try.
Kimia started out with something
like this, I offered her a role.
I think.
I'm not sure
if I'm the one for this role.
You know what?
Weeds that weren't chosen
for Ikebana arrangement
they became unwanted and
neglected plants by their owners.
They will be plucked out.
If you go to this audition,
you can go further than what you said.
You could be as famous as Kimia.
And this will benefit our brand.
This is not a request.
If you refuse to do so,
perhaps you wouldn't
be valued to us anymore.
This is Job, a gunman of a feminist.
Bambi brought it for you, I saw it outside
so I brought it in.
How are you?
Still alive.
If you got nothing to say, then leave.
I want to talk to you.
About f... king what?
You never talk to me.
You got me so bad earlier as well.
What about you?
You let your Dad
protect your guilt, you lied,
you didn't take
responsibilities for anything.
You have no idea what I faced.
And you know what I encountered?
You know what others encountered?
You know how is the woman that you hurt?
You don't know, you don't
know anything about anyone.
All you care is yourself.
You live a comfortable life.
Selfish one.
You'll end up just like your Dad.
I can't choose.
You should be the one who gets me the most.
How can I choose?
Can I choose my own Dad? I I can't either.
You also have a problem with your Dad.
But I choose not to be like him.
I only have good intentions to you.
I hope that deep down you
wouldn't end up like your Dad.
But look what you did to me,
you told me off, you blocked
me and you told me to go away.
What do you think I'd feel?
I'm so disappointed in you.
I just want to be your friend.
Fine, I'm sorry. I didn't mean to.
Thank you for your good intentions but I
I don't get it. I Diesel!
Diesel! Diesel! I I'm so sorry.
Diesel! Stop!
Are you crazy? Stop! I I'm stupid.
That's right, I'm so stupid.
Stupid.
You don't have to do that.
I don't know.
I have no idea.
Come here.
It's alright.
It's fine.
I'm sorry.
This place makes me think of the past.
All the wounds and bad stories that I made.
No matter how far I tried to run.
These memories still keep haunting me.
Cut! Cut!
Okay, fine.
What about this?
Ms.Duangtawan sent a clip
of your speech and I saw it.
I want you to try
sharing what happened.
What was going on back then.
I promise you that it's gonna
be a director and us to see.
That's it.
Well…
I
I used to be friend with that rapper.
And I want to have my own song.
So I asked for his help.
That song was supposed to be his.
But he gave it to me because
he liked me.
I didn't really like him so I rejected him.
He must be furious so
he wrote a song to diss me.
And my best friend
helped me write that speech.
She wrote that because
that's what she believed.
She believed in me.
After that,
she caught me lying about something.
I got a chance to tell her the truth.
But I didn't.
If I hadn't lied to her,
she wouldn't have…
Okay.
It's okay. What about this?
I want you to think of this
feeling and tell it to the camera.
Look at the camera.
Ready?
Action!
This place makes me think of the past.
All the wounds and
bad stories that I made.
No matter how far I tried to run.
These memories still keep haunting me.
Dream can go home.
If her wound is hurting or swelling up,
you can bring her back to heal it.
Okay. Thank you.
Can I have some snacks?
I brought it for her last night.
I'm not sure if the doctor
allows her to have it.
It's her favorite. I Sure, she can.
Congrats on going home.
What is it?
How is she?
She's fine.
But her wound hurt this morning.
The doctor let het go home now.
Can she go back home?
Please?
If she wants to, then fine.
But she needs to understand that
if we can't change her opinion,
then she can't change mine either.
Whatever,
in the end,
I never want anything to happen to her.
No matter what
she's still my daughter.
Cut! I Cut!
Please take care of them.
Pure, well…
Can you act it short and clean?
When you smile, can you do it faster?
One more time, okay?
Reset!
My smile didn't look real?
You can do it.
And…action!
Cut! Lower the product and
focus on the face. I And action!
Cut! I need you to smile more
than the last one. I And action!
Cut! Cut!
Give me sultry smile.
Cut! No smile at all.
Cut! More smile than the last one.
Cut! I Action!
No smile at all. Cut!
Pure? Are you okay?
Didn't you sleep well last night?
Take a look at him.
Are you alright?
This is not our fault at all.
Why didn't they talk it through first?
Drop the attitude, the
clients are watching.
This is normal for shooting TVC.
Hang in there, okay? I That's right.
Hang in there.
Let's rolling.
One more time, okay?
And…action!
Hello, everyone.
I'm here with the hottest BL couple
on soeical media.
Please welcome Pure and Namkhang. I Hello.
You're all settled in, right?
Let me get to the point.
About Paint Your Dream series,
it's so blown up and it gains big success.
On behalf of your fans, I need to ask
have you ever thought of your partner
more than just a scene partner?
Well,
we worked so hard on this series
and we played according to the
director and the characters' emotions.
The characters' emotions.
If that so,
well, Pure must feel the same thing.
That's right.
When we're acting,
of course we can feel it.
So cute, you see that?
They're so supportive of each other.
I started to see where this is going.
Since you're here already,
can you reenact one of your scenes
right here right now?
The scene that people've
been talking about.
This is not included in the script.
Well, just a little.
Okay? Your fans have been asking for it.
Just a little.
Can you teach me water coloring?
Can you?
When you paint,
you need to wipe it off first,
so it won't get messy.
Cut!
It's something like this and
please watch the rest in the series.
Oh my! You almost gave me a heart attack.
Can we take a break brieftly?
Then we'll come back to see
if they really know each other.
They will play a game
called Know Your Partner.
You passed an audition.
Next step, the director wanted to see your
chemistry with the rest of the cast members.
If you didn't show up,
you're automatically out.
Dream.
Bambi? I Hello.
Why didn't you call us first?
I'm here to talk to dream.
Sure.
I'll catch up with you.
What's going on?
I want to apologize to you face to face.
I'm sorry.
Sorry
about everything.
I know that you won't
believe a word that I said.
But I want you to know
that since we've made up,
I felt really bad.
I don't know how to tell you the truth.
I don't know when to tell you.
I'm scared.
I lost you once and I..
This time.
I don't want to lose you again.
Why did you realize about it
after you ratted me out to Diesel?
You came here to say sorry,
expected me to forgive you and that's it?
You can't do as you pleased.
You have to be responsible
of your own actions.
What changed you?
What do you want?
You don't have to tell me actually.
In the end, we can't be friends again.
I'm sorry.
Can't you give me another chance?
I'm sorry that I was selfish
that I was a bad friend,
that I lied to you,
I just want to be friend with you.
I'm sorry.
I still want to be friend with
you. Get well soon. From Bambi.
What're you doing?
Can you come out to see me?
You're done? Are you hungry?
Are you okay?
You're done with shooting?
I can't do this any
longer, I felt like a robot.
People gave me orders and I just followed.
Well done.
How are you? What were you doing earlier?
Am I disturbing you?
Do you remember about
my audition for a film?
I've never heard of this film.
I
I don't want to go. I What?
It's Toey's film.
He's so famous.
Are you sure? Everyone
would kill to work with Toey.
Do you want to run lines
with me? Just for fun.
I want to see you act.
Sure, let's do this.
Are you crazy? Why do you want a cage for?
My birds,
I can't leave them.
They are… / Wait.
I think you should take it slow this time.
This line is important.
Let's do it again.
You go first.
Sure, let's do this.
Are you crazy? Why do you want a cage for?
I can't leave my birds.
They're the only things
that I love. I Okay, wait.
I don't think you quite understand it,
they want to interpret it like this,
to present birds as freedom.
When you speak the line,
can you make me feel that?
Let's try again.
Let's go. I Can we stop?
You said that you wanted to run lines.
I did that because I wanted to see you act.
I didn't think that it'd be this serious.
It's just running lines
and you can't focus on it.
You think you can star in the film?
What's wrong with you today?
Are you mad or something?
I'm not irritating, I don't know.
I mean running lines is part of acting.
If you don't want it to be
that serious, then it's fine.
You don't have to do it. I really think…
It will be a waste of
time if you don't mean it.
It's like…
You got the part so easily, you
don't have to take it seriously.
Easy?
Didn't I say that I didn't
want to get this role?
Why?
You want this role?
You want it so bad? Or you want to
audition it and now you're jealous of me?
I'm sorry.
Actually
you were right about it.
Otherwise, it wouldn't
have hit me this bad.
I'm sorry
for talking to you like that.
I
I really don't want to do this anymore.
I thought that I could make it through.
I thought that I could do it but.
I couldn't do it anymore, it's like.
I lie to my audience every day.
I think I.
I feel really bad about it.
I don't like this feeling.
I get you but…
When I try to do something.
I suddenly see Dream's face.
I try to let it go
but I couldn't.
You went to see Bambi again, didn't you?
Why didn't you think it through?
Hey!
I think I need to tell you this.
I think we shouldn't continue
with the second season.
I want to quit. I F... king quit what?
What the hell?
Listen to me.
It looks good at the end.
I know that you want it, I want it too.
How do you know that they're
not fooling us with the dream?
Look at our jobs, they never protect us.
I think we should call it off, I don't
want to waste their time anymore.
They could invest on someone else
instead. I Are you out of your mind!?
You know that I want this
job, I want this opportunity.
My Dad is still lying and disabled at home.
How could you say that?
You selfish son of a bitch!
Can you listen to me? I
Listen to f... king what?
If we quit now, we still have fans.
We can find our own way,
we don't have to rely on them.
Please stop talking.
The more you say it,
the more shitty you sound.
What about this?
I've been thinking about this.
I'll announce on the stage
of our next fan meeting
that I'll take a break,
that I want to focus on my personal life
and my solo works.
But I'll
ask the fans to take care of you.
I believe that
everyone still loves and
supports you the same.
I truly believe that.
If you want to quit,
can I say this?
You will stop acting
and you will announce your girlfriend.
I'll cheer you and Bambi on this journey.
I believe that the fans will understand
and bless us. I What
the hell is wrong with you?
You don't care about me.
Why do I need to care about you?
Where are you? It's
about time for audition.
If you can't make it on time,
then you're automatically out.
If you refuse to do so,
perhaps you wouldn't
be valued to us anymore.
Don't you want this life so bad?
What changed you?
What do you want?
Should we quit them all?
Everything that we're doing.
That easy?
It is that easy.
Let's live a normal life.
And ignore them all.
Can you please stand by for a sec?
Hey,
I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologize to me.
It's my own fault.
If it wasn't because of you,
I wouldn't have been here.
I should thank you instead.
I'm sorry.
Really sorry.
You know that
you're my best friend.
From now on,
you can follow your dream and do it well.
Don't you worry
about my debts.
I can handle this.
I
I still want to be your friend.
I'm sorry.
Stop with that face
alreay, you look so ugly.
Don't you want to look good?
You're right.
It's time.
Can I hear you scream
for them one more time?
Let's meet Pure and Namkhang.
Okay, that's quite enough.
Wow! So many people
come here to see both of you.
Right. I Okay.
The first season has been so successful.
It's on the trend every single day.
I heard that both of you
have something special to
share with your fans, right?
That's right.
We have something
really important to share.
It's one crucial milestone for both of us.
First of all, I'd like
to thank everyone for your support
all along this journey.
I'd like to say thank you
for your encouragement.
I will never forget this feeling.
The feeling that
you all give to us, thank you.
Should we quit them all?
Everything that we're doing.
That easy?
It is that easy.
I'm gonna say goodbye to the
second season since the beginning.
And you don't have to go auditioning.
And we will find something fun to do.
Right…
And ignore them all.
Therefore…
Both of us…
Will create even better memories.
Please continue to support us
in the second season.
You can't do as you pleased
- if you're not ready for its consequences.
- Dream.
Do you know how one person
could inspire an art piece?
It's their true self.
What's wrong? Your
home isn't your safe zone?
I think my dad can't change.
Tokyo, your boy is here.
You're so lucky to meet
someone like us, you know that?
If I want something, I need
to trade it with something else.
I've risked it with
everything, what about you?
You said you'd stop starring in BL series.
Can I ask for another
chance, Ms.Duangtawan?