Characters, actions, places, occupations,
and events in this series are fictional
and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge
or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
I wish you get to do what you love.
I wish you can start your own company.
I wish you’ll be a lovely girlfriend to me
for a long time.
I wish we can celebrate your birthday
together every year.
4 YEARS AGO.
-Blow the candles. It’s hot.
-Wait a sec.
Come on. Blow them.
Will you promise me…
that we will spend my birthday together
every year?
Sure.
I will never let anyone
hold your birthday cake.
-Yay! Happy Birthday, Prim!
-Happy birthday.
1 YEAR AGO.
Happy f*cking birthday.
Cut.
Joy, can you move around
and go with the flow more?
Sure.
Shasha is so beautiful.
She looks good at every angle.
Her face is so unique.
Really?
But I see you say the same compliment
to every model, Joy.
Please do what I said.
Yes.
Prim, can I unbutton her jacket?
I think it will look cooler.
Of course.
I trust your fashion sense.
Even if you compliment me,
I won’t give you a discount on my fee.
Can you unbutton the jacket?
You do it.
When you unbutton it,
I’ll arrange your jacket.
I’m a model, not a stylist.
Don’t you know what your job is?
Yes, I do.
But I thought
you would help make it easier.
Let’s do it again.
Please maintain
the cool look like earlier.
You can go with the flow of the music.
We can’t work overtime today.
I won’t.
But look at the model your client chose.
Is she going to keep shooting
until our memory card is full?
Why are you nagging her?
Why do you dislike her so much?
Did she steal your girlfriend?
I don’t dislike her.
But I just find her smug.
Her fee is so damn high.
It takes up most of the budget
for the production.
Who are you? Why did you take my picture?
I’m a trainee.
I’m your long-time fan.
I took the picture as a memory.
Are you here as a trainee or as a fan?
Shasha, I’ll take care of it.
I already told the staff
not to take your picture.
She’s new.
I’ll warn her. I’m sorry.
You should be more professional.
How can you let this happen?
Woon, I’m not in the mood for shooting.
I need time to calm down.
Let her have a break.
If she takes a break,
we may need to work overtime.
We only need a few more shots
to wrap up the shooting.
Andy.
Yes?
Did you check everything?
Nothing can go wrong.
Of course, Mrs. Nin.
I took care of everything.
Where is Dada?
She has arrived.
She’s getting her makeup done.
Hurry up and get it done
before the finale walk.
Sure.
Come on. We don’t have much time.
Hurry up.
Hi.
Bambi!
When did you get back?
I flew back this morning.
I came back in time to attend this show
at my mom’s request.
You’ve been away for so long.
Is that the finale dress?
It’s beautiful.
Yes, it’s really beautiful.
Your mom’s designs are always trendy.
A beautiful dress
is for a beautiful woman.
Thank you for today.
I gave you a little extra
for the overtime.
It’s okay, Gorya.
Instead, you can buy me drinks later.
Are you going to Prim’s birthday party
at Blossom?
I won’t miss it.
See you there.
Okay. Is there anything else
I can help with?
I need to go home and doll up.
You should go.
You seem to need a lot of dolling up.
You are so mean.
-I’m leaving.
-You should go. See you later.
Bye.
Can you unzip the dress?
Where is your manager?
She went to the car to get something.
Are you going to Blossom tonight?
Yes.
It’s Prim’s birthday.
I’ve asked you to go to the club with me.
But you said no every time.
I don’t like you
You’re not my type.
What is your type?
I can be your type.
So cocky.
Not everyone likes you.
Won’t you give me any chance?
You're not my type.
No matter how much you try,
my answer is still no.
Aren’t you too quick to judge?
Sha.
Are you done?
Why does it take you so long
to change your outfit?
I asked Gorya to unzip for me.
Do you really need to get her?
She’s challenging.
Hurry up.
Why didn’t you tell me
that you came back?
I wanted to surprise you.
I thought you liked theatrics.
Stop getting on my nerves.
You ruined my show.
You lied to Dada
that I wanted you to do the finale walk.
I’ve worked for this show for months.
It’s all ruined.
Ruined? How?
Everyone is talking about it.
They all l want to know where I’ve been.
I planned to announce it
on the microphone.
But you stopped me.
How long are you going to stay?
What do you plan to do?
I sent you to school, but you dropped out.
Why do I need to study?
When I can leech off you.
Am I right?
Stop being sarcastic.
If you’re going to come back
and live with me,
you’d better behave.
Otherwise, I will send you back.
This time, you will have no choice.
Cheers.
Excuse me. I’ll be right back.
Happy birthday, Prim.
You turned 25.
You are at the crucial age of 25.
It’s the year where you will either
rise to the top or fall to rock bottom.
Ant, you are cursing me, aren’t you?
I will never fall.
Because I got everything under control.
Yes, you do.
When you turn 40,
you will realize
nothing is under your control.
Ant, you don’t look like
you’re in your 40s.
You look like you're about our age.
Min.
You really mean it when you said that.
Well said, sister.
Hey, her boyfriend would be upset
if he saw you kiss her.
He doesn’t like it
when she hangs out with us.
We are just like sisters.
I have a girlfriend.
More importantly,
I’m done with straight girls.
I don’t want to fall for
straight girls again.
Prim, do you have anything you want
for your birthday this year?
No.
I’m happy with my work.
I make enough money.
I help my mom and sister
to live comfortably.
I have good friends.
That is enough for me.
If you’re always busy with work,
when will you find a girlfriend?
I haven’t found anyone
good enough to date.
So I’m just enjoying my life for now.
Right?
You said I was boasting about my life.
Let’s drink it up, Ant.
You, too.
Can I have fun with you?
Cheers.
Cheers. Bottoms up.
Praew.
Can you take a picture for us?
Let’s take a picture.
Alright. One, two, three.
Okay.
Beautiful.
PARK: I’M WAITING AT THE ENTRANCE.
When will you finish it?
I see you’ve been drinking it for a while.
Why are you here?
I’m not going back with you.
Today is Prim’s birthday.
Why didn’t you answer my call?
What were you doing?
I was having fun with my friends.
I wasn’t staring at the phone
all the time.
You meet them every day.
Isn’t that enough?
Why?
Are you going back to her place
to celebrate her birthday?
Are you crazy?
You get jealous because of Prim.
Why? I can’t do that?
This is too much, Park.
If you’re going act like a jerk,
maybe we should break up.
Are you breaking up with me
to date a girl?
If you like women,
why didn’t you date them?
Why the f*ck are you dating me?
No need for the F word.
I can date anyone I want.
I’m breaking up with you
because you are a jerk.
I let you mistreat me for too long.
Hey.
Let me go.
You need to go home to talk.
I’m not going.
I’m going back in.
You must come home with me.
I’m not going.
Did you push me?
I should have done it a long time ago.
Don’t attack her from the back.
She broke up with you.
You should have walked away.
It’s none of your damn business, lesbo!
I’m a lesbian. So what?
It’s none of your f*cking business.
-Stop it.
-Help. Help me.
This man is going to hit me.
Please call the police.
Take a video of his behavior.
-Let’s call the police.
-How could he hit a woman?
He was going to hit her.
Min, let’s go. I’ll give you a ride home.
Let’s go.
I can go home by myself.
What the heck are you filming?
Thank you.
He is threatening when he is mad.
Are you okay?
Don’t worry. I can handle it.
It’s good that you broke up with him.
He didn’t show you any respect.
Yes.
I should have broken up with him
a long time ago.
But you need to be careful.
A guy like him may not let go easily.
Did he grab you this hard?
Your wrist is all red.
There are also fingernail scratches.
Shall we go inside and treat your wound?
You must be really hurt.
It’s okay.
Thanks a lot.
I’ll do it at home.
Thank you.
You are petite but quite tough.
Prim.
Can I stay over at your place tonight?
I have a new project to present to you.
You are drunk, but still think about work?
I’m not drunk.
I just want to talk to you.
I have many things
I want to talk to you about.
Does it have to be tonight?
Why?
Are you taking someone home?
No.
Sure.
You can sleep at my place tonight.
You are pretty.
No need to add the makeup.
I know that. No need to tell me that.
Did Prim invite you to her party?
No.
I came here myself,
not to attend her party.
Here must be
a great hunting ground for you.
There must be a lot of your fans here.
Probably, but I’m not interested in them.
Whom I’m interested in
is with someone else.
You should have realized by now that…
you are not everyone’s favorite.
Do you want to come to the afterparty
at my condo?
How is it? Did that jerk hurt you?
If you need help, call me.
Okay.
Is she okay?
Yes.
Min always fights with her boyfriend.
I told her to break up with him
several times.
But she still puts up with him.
This is something
she has to let go of on her own.
She will learn her lesson
when she gets hurt.
That’s true.
What I told her to do,
I can’t do it myself.
You have someone you can’t get over?
Yes.
But I’m moving on.
I don’t want to waste my time.
That’s true.
The things that give us headaches.
We just screw them.
If we are going to do it,
we need to be sure that we are not drunk.
I’m not drunk.
I fully know what I’m doing.
If we kiss,
can we still work together and be friends?
What if I want to be more than that?
I can’t give you that right now.
If we are going to do it tonight,
it’s just for fun.
Are you okay with it?
Wait a sec.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Bambi.
What are you doing here?
I brought you a birthday cake.
Like we did every year.
It’s okay.
I don’t want it.
Are you still mad at me?
I miss your birthday only once.
This cake is bigger than last year's.
I made it myself.
You should go.
This is not a good time.
I’ll blow out the candles
and make a wish for you.
Wishing you to stay rich, beautiful,
and cool like this forever.
Yay!
If you’re done, you can go now.
I have a guest.
What kind of guest?
Why did they come to see you at this hour?
She’s my guest.
She’s not an uninvited guest like you.
Bambi.
Oops.
Did I interrupt you?
Sorry.
Bambi, what are you doing? Get out.
Don’t be so rude to me.
I brought you the cake.
Let’s eat it together.
You can invite your friend to join us.
Taste it. It’s delicious.
Do you want to taste it?
I’ll share it with you.
It’s delicious.
I’m Bambi.
I’m Prim’s ex-girlfriend.
But we are still friends.
I’m Gorya.
I was her junior at school.
I’m also working with her.
So you’re hitting on a junior now?
That’s wicked.
Bambi, that’s enough. Get out.
Can I eat the cake first?
Please.
Gorya.
I’m sorry.
Tonight is not good for me.
It’s okay. I understand.
I’ll leave.
I’ll talk to you later.
I’ll walk you downstairs.
It’s okay.
I can go home by myself.
You can stay with her.
Oh.
Are you leaving?
You should eat the cake with us first.
It’s okay.
I don’t eat dessert at night.
But it’s delicious.
Hey.
Why did you turn it off?
I was enjoying it.
When did you come back?
Today.
I came back for your birthday.
I don’t believe you.
I mean it.
I worked hard to make your birthday cake.
Stop lying.
I can tell you bought it.
You will never work hard
to make a cake for anyone.
Hey, don’t underestimate me.
If I got a bit more practice,
I could open a bakery shop.
Let me go.
Do you know how much I miss you?
Where have you been?
Why did you never contact me?
I…
I wasn’t in the mood.
I didn’t want to contact anyone.
I wanted to hide from the world.
Have you ever thought about
how I would feel?
You’ve disappeared for a year.
I’ve tried to contact you.
But you’ve never sent me any news.
Now, you are back. You said you miss me.
Come on, Bambi.
What about my feelings?
I’m sorry.
You know how I am.
Yes.
Aren’t you going to change it?
But I’m back to keep my promise.
Promise?
It was broken since you left me
without any explanation.
Get out.
Get up.
Go home.
No.
Can’t I sleep here tonight?
Look at me.
I’m too tired to go home.
Let me go.
Hey.
It’s your birthday.
You shouldn’t sleep alone.
Wouldn’t it be better
to sleep with your ex?
Right?
It’s okay. I can sleep alone.
But I put on ribbons to be your gift.
Fine.
If you won’t leave, you can sleep here.
Don’t turn on the music
and bother the neighbors.
You’re so annoying.
Yes, boss.
Prim.
What?
Good night, birthday girl.
♪ Why did you come back? ♪
♪ To break up with me? ♪
♪ To remind me that
I’m not the one for you? ♪
♪ When you are back,
I miss you even more ♪
♪ Can you please leave? ♪
What are you listening to?
Excuse me.
What?
What are you listening to?
Amy Winehouse.
You have good taste in music.
I also like her music.
If you like this genre of music,
I have many artists to recommend to you.
Why don’t we…
exchange our playlists?
Are you…
flirting with me?
What?
You’re asking me to listen to the music
and share my playlist with you.
You are definitely hitting on me.
Can I do that?
What are you doing?
Nothing. I just scroll through my phone.
I saw you were filming her.
What were you filming?
This man was
secretly filming you working out.
Why did you film me?
I didn’t do it. I was just watching you.
I saw you filmed her.
Please delete the video.
Delete what?
I didn’t film anything.
You are not that pretty.
( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
Hey.
Whether I’m pretty or not,
it’s not the point.
If you didn’t do it,
just give me your phone.
Damn.
You are a pervert.
You have dozens of
hidden camera videos of women.
Shasha, take his picture and post it
to expose him on social media.
Also, call the police to arrest him.
Don’t take my photo.
Why? Are you feeling embarrassed?
You can’t take my picture. Stop it.
What is wrong with you?
You can’t take my picture.
What’s going on?
He’s a pervert.
He secretly films women
when we are working out.
Call the police to arrest him.
Please go wait outside.
Get out.
-Go.
-Here is the evidence.
Thanks.
It’s okay.
I hate guys who take advantage of women.
He did it when we are in a public gym.
Is there any place safe for women?
I’m not even wearing a revealing outfit.
What the hell did he secretly film me?
Even if you were all covered
or wore a turtle-neck t-shirt.
If he wanted to film you,
he would do it anyway.
So you can wear whatever you want.
Next time we run into each other,
you don’t need to hide from me.
I’m not going to hit on you every time.
I’ve got to go.
Bambi is back?
When?
Yesterday.
She went to your place?
Did you two get back together?
Don’t do it.
Don’t you remember she wrecked you
so badly that you couldn’t work?
Min, calm down.
I haven’t done anything.
I told her to leave.
I’ve learned my lesson.
I’m not like you.
Don’t talk back at me.
I already took care of it.
Prim.
Hello.
Hello, Praew.
Your work is amazing. I like it.
Thank you.
Hello, Min.
Your photos are beautiful. I like them.
I’m telling you she will be famous.
She has a bright future waiting.
Thank you, Prim.
I just keep practicing.
I’ll be right back.
Yeah.
How did you come up with the concept?
I think women’s backs
have their own charms.
They portray what women
have been through in life.
This woman was in a toxic relationship.
She stayed in the relationship
because she was scared.
What was she scared of?
She was scared that no one would love her.
Do you want me to take your picture?
No.
I’m very shy.
My life is not that interesting.
Every life is interesting.
It’s up to who is looking at it.
I have to decline it.
But I want to ask you to work with me.
My client wants a photoshoot
with a girl power concept like this.
Sure. I’m happy to work with you.
I think you need to come up
with a new concept.
It has to be sharper than this.
Go back and fix it. I’ll help you review.
Yes.
I’m here to apply for a job, Prim.
What are you doing, Bambi?
What do you want?
I’m not kidding.
I’m here to apply for a job.
I don’t want to live aimlessly anymore.
I want to be useful.
Then what are you doing?
There’s no job for you here.
Can’t you find a job for your friend?
I want to be a better person.
I’m trying.
I need your support.
Or…
why don’t you hire me as your secretary?
You know…
how good I am at taking care of you.
Go find a job somewhere else.
There’s no job for you here.
We don’t accept unpredictable people
to work here.
Those who one moment want to be together,
the next moment want to break up.
(Will you promise me that we will spend
my birthday together every year?)
(Sure.)
(I’ll never let anyone
hold your birthday cake.)
Can I eat it now?
Yes.
Come. I’ll eat it now.
(I wish you get to do what you love.)
(I wish you can start your own company.)
(I wish you’ll be a lovely girlfriend
to me for a long time.)
Is it that hard to say you love me first?
If I do that,
will you be my girlfriend?
From now on, you can take care of me
as your girlfriend.
Here.
I’m creating a new brand.
Its target is teenagers.
Why don’t you learn about the business?
It’s better than partying every night
and causing trouble.
You’re only worried that
I will cause trouble.
Have you ever asked
how I was doing when I lived abroad?
All you want to do is send me away.
Hello, Yanin.
Shasha, my model.
You are the prettiest.
I look pretty because of your dress.
Your designs are always trendy.
People of all ages love it.
Shasha, this is Bambi, my daughter.
She just came back from the U.S.
I think you two are the same age.
Nice to meet you.
Excuse me. I’ll let you two talk.
I often saw you on fashion accounts on IG.
I’m your fan.
Thank you.
I’ve heard your name a lot.
I finally met you.
Really?
People talked about me?
What did they say? Tell me.
Did they say nice things about me?
Of course.
Someone like you
has nothing bad to be said about.
I hope it is true.
It’s good that my mom
changed her design style.
I think her previous collections
are a bit outdated.
Do you like it because I’m wearing it?
When you have a good model,
any outfit can look good.
I like you. You have high self-confidence.
I think we can be friends.
Sure. Let’s get to know each other.
Do you want to do something fun with me?
1 WEEK LATER.
Prim.
Gorya.
What are you doing here?
Min told me to receive a brief
from a new client.
She said it’s urgent.
All her works are urgent.
She said the client is a clothing brand.
Their brand is not widely known.
So they want to make a fashion video.
They have a high budget.
So I quickly accepted this job.
We do it for money.
Gorya.
I’m sorry about that night.
It’s okay. I understand.
Is she the one you can’t get over?
Yes.
I’d been dating her since college
until I started to work.
We were dating for several years.
She suddenly came back.
I don’t know what she wants.
Whatever she wants from you.
If you don’t give it to her,
there’s nothing she can do.
Let’s go in.
Do you have any information about them?
Could they be a scammer?
I don’t think so.
I heard that they are a new brand.
I think they want to keep it a secret.
They wanted to pick the staff themselves.
They specifically requested you.
So I picked the team that you trust
to work on this project.
Gorya will take care of the clothing.
Praew will take
the behind-the-scenes photos.
I want to give her a try.
A try for what?
I want to see how she works.
What are you thinking?
Is that so?
Damn, are you serious?
Hello, Shasha.
Yes, the client wants her to be
the model for this collection.
Be nice to her for money.
This is a dream team.
Hello, Gorya.
I can’t seem to avoid you.
When did they say the meeting would begin?
1 p.m.
1 p.m.?
But it’s almost 2 p.m.
I know they are our client.
But they should have told us
if they would be late.
If I knew they would be this late,
I would have waited in my office.
They should show us some respect.
Your client is here.
Shall we begin the meeting?
Cut.
If you approach me
by pretending to be my client,
I’m telling you it won’t work.
Did you hire a Michelin-star chef
to cook at your condo?
Only for a special date.
Then what?
Even though you look really pretty
when you cry,
I still want to see you smile.