[wild sound]
[horse neighing]
[dried leaves crunching]
[footsteps, dried leaves crunching]
[horse neighing]
[loud thud]
[suspense music]
[growling]
Stop.
[horse neighing]
[horse exhales sharply]
Alexander!
Alexander! O' Alexander!
Tell me.
We should turn back.
It'd be dangerous
to continue through the jungle.
And what's so dangerous here, Ambhu?
Betaal.
And pray, what are Betaals?
Bloodsuckers that drink men dry.
Ah!
[horse huffing]
Well, I'm Alexander,
conqueror of Greece, Egypt,
every land and its people.
From mountains to rivers,
my name makes the world tremble!
And you think...
you think I'll be scared of some
bedtime story?
[groaning]
[urging horse forward]
Let's move!
[horse neighing]
[growling]
[horse exhales sharply]
[urging horse forward]
Ambhu.
Yes, sir?
Go check ahead.
NOW!
[suspense music]
ALL CLEAR!
[fire whooshing]
NOOO!!!
[Swords clank]
[evil laughter]
[growling]
[groaning]
So you want to conquer India huh?
[Screaming]
[Tittle music]
Welcome
to the Mystical Mysteries of Midnight!
A graveyard watchman turns
into a monster, so beware,
Brought to you proudly
by Ranjeet vests and underwear!
In today's breaking news
we will feature a grave,
every night from which emerges a demon,
a demon...
Yes, one more time...
a demon!
[Coughs]
Come on, sir, what are you doing?
How long do you expect me
to stay cooped up for just 50 bucks, man?
Bugger off!
- Mr. Demon...
- Buzz off!
- Come on, Mr. Demon...
Mr. Demon...
[laughing]
50 bucks!
Congrats, bro,
you just turned into a meme.
[Chuckling]
This is funny.
[laughing]
Your "funny"
won't get this Danny his Sandy.
Girls have some standards too, you know?
What do I lack, bro?
First things first, change your Insta DP.
We've been trekking two days
and you haven't posted once, you know.
Exactly!
Come on, bro,
up your rizz.
Come on!
Now watch my flex!
[exhales heavily]
Where you off to?
Alok?
[tongue click]
#GoingWildInWilderness
Who's gonna pitch your tent?
- Let's go.
- Hold your horses, man. Wait for us!
- Wait for us!
- Wait, Alok.
Where are we heading?
Feels like we're turning into cavemen.
It's not safe to go
this deep into the forest.
[Breathing Heavily]
Even those jungle guys said
it's virgin to venture into the forest.
You mean "Varjit" aka forbidden?
Yeah, whatever.
[Breathing Heavily]
[groaning]
[exhales]
[Breathing Heavily]
What happened?
Tripped over something.
There's nothing here.
Let's go.
Let's move.
[Breathing Heavily]
Bro, don't you think this
is getting dangerous?
We got no network here.
Now this is real adventure!
Come on, guys.
[Birds chirping]
[Sighs]
What's wrong with you?
I came here for this shot.
Once an idiot always an idiot.
[Camera Clicks]
[Breathing]
[Wild sound]
[bear roaring]
[Breathing Heavily]
HELP!!!
[Screaming]
Run! Run!
Don't run, guys!
- Run! Run! Run!
- Shoo! Shoo!
Shit!
Shit! Shit! Shit!
MUMMY!!!
[Screaming]
[groaning]
HELP!!!
[intense music]
[dried leaves crunching]
[Screaming]
[intense music]
[Winces in pain]
[Screaming]
[intense music]
[panting]
[Breathing Heavily]
[music builds up]
[Screaming]
[bear roaring]
[bear growling]
[Breathing Heavily]
[thumping heartbeat]
[Birds chirping]
[gentle music]
[gentle music continues]
- [Screaming]
- [startled gasp]
[dramatic music]
[clinking stones]
You're not cut out for adventure, dude,
you can't even start a fire.
[Birds chirping]
[Sighs]
[startled gasp]
What are you doing?
I've been rubbing forever...
no sparks yet.
[whistling]
[thumping heartbeat]
There it is...
What?
The sparks.
Huh?
Hunger! I mean I'm feeling hungry.
You shouldn't have stepped out.
It's dangerous for you out here.
Just out here?
There's a bloody snake in the pot.
So?
If it bit me,
it'd poison my future generations.
Thanks for saving me.
My friends are real idiots...
They won't search long
before declaring me dead.
I lost my phone.
I can't contact my parents.
I should leave--
You're not fully recovered yet.
Once you are,
I'll take you home.
I can stay, if you promise
to take me back yourself.
[Sighs]
Your village's nearby, right?
What's your name?
Tadaka.
And yours?
Strange.
Oh, your name is Strange.
No, your name is strange.
No, my name's Tadaka.
I'm Alok.
Strange Alok.
You will not make
any noise until you get better.
And you'll stay in there.
[bear growling]
[Screaming]
[panting]
[bear roaring]
[roar in the distance]
[slurping]
[growling]
[Mystical music]
[Mystical song]
[fire crackling]
Rakhtrambha ! (I'll protect through blood!)
Sasakhtrambha !
(I'll protect through strength!)
[Mystical song continues]
[Chirping insects]
[growling]
[bats screeching]
Not an animal...
Bring me a human!
A human!
[Mystical song]
[objects clattering]
[birds chirping]
[cassette clicking]
Should I tell you, hmm?
Yes.
Or keep mum?
No.
Guess what lies in my heart, today.
What is it?
[gentle music]
Should I tell you, hmm?
Or keep mum?
Guess what lies in my heart, today.
If you guess it right, I'll bow to you,
I'll make you my master too,
This is my promise to you.
Really?
Should I tell you, hmm?
Or keep mum?
Guess what lies in my heart, today.
If you guess it right, I'll bow to you,
I'll make you my master too,
This is my promise to you.
[peppy music]
[sneezes]
[glass shattering]
[bats squeaking]
It's okay, it's alright.
It's all good.
[Chuckling]
By the way, what were you doing
way inside the forest?
I got here by mistake.
I'm such an ass.
An ass?
But you look human.
PJ?
[laughing]
Nice one.
Well, this man here's PJs are so poor
they're straight below the poverty line.
Man?
Man.
Humans in general?
People like you and me?
Not me...
You.
Right, I forgot.
You are not a human,
you're an angel.
[soft music]
[thumping heartbeat]
[growling]
[loud thud]
Tadaka?
She's gone?
Tadaka!
[bats squeaking]
Tadaka, I'm so sorry.
I got carried away.
Come on, you know me.
Tadaka!
[dried leaves crunching]
Tadaka, is that you?
Cut the hide-and-seek.
Tadaka!
She was here a second ago.
[panting]
[Screaming]
Who are you? Stop.
Who are these guys?
Stop.
Statue.
Don't come closer.
I... I will...
- [Screaming]
- [growling]
- [Hissing]
Veeran... let him go.
You brought a human here.
He came here by mistake.
Yakshasan refused to eat the animal.
He's been starving for years.
Let's hand him over to Yakshasan instead.
No.
Handing him over to Yakshasan
isn't your decision to make.
Then you can't decide his fate either.
[loud thud]
[high-pitched tone]
Alok?
Are you alright?
[Breathing Heavily]
He's awake. Let him go.
Tadaka broke a rule.
She brought a human here.
He came here by mistake. Let him go.
He can't leave.
Why? What did he do wrong?
It's forbidden to bring him here.
He doesn't know about us.
He didn't see anything.
He knows nothing. Just let him go.
How can we just let him go?
[growling]
Hi, I'm Alok Goyal,
reporter, Azad News!
Nice personality.
One of my reels went viral,
you've probably seen it.
It goes like this:
A graveyard watchman turns
into a monster, so beware,
[growling]
Alok, Alok...
Quiet.
What?
Keep quiet.
Qui--
We should burn him alive.
- No.
- What are you saying?
We should burn him alive.
What is he saying?
He wants to burn you alive.
He wants you to bathe me?
Go ahead, I'm feeling really sticky.
Shush.
[high-pitched tone]
[Gasping]
Uncle, like seriously, what's she saying?
Straight to the gallows?
Who does that?
Let's just talk this through.
I want a lawyer.
He's human.
His blood is poisonous.
We should let him go.
No!
No way, Jose!
Yes! Yes, please!
What are you doing?!
He wants to free you...
WHAT?!
He wants to f...
Ugh.
Look, I'm the only reporter
of my kind here.
If anything happens to me,
you're all getting boycotted.
Alok...
I'll take responsibility of him.
He knows nothing.
Lock him up in the dungeon.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
You're right.
Alok...
Hey! Don't touch me! Don't you dare!
I couldn't hear him, but you could, right?
No, come on, guys!
I'm the only son of the Baniya family.
You don't know my father,
he's a bloody rascal.
And a retired income tax officer to boot.
He'll charge you penalties
that'll wipe out your retirement fund.
Tadaka, a little help?
Please help.
Why are you climbing all these stairs?
Are you planning to throw me down?
- Let me go.
- Why have we brought him here?
- We were ordered to take him to the dungeon.
- Put me down right now.
There's only one being
who gives orders here.
Let's talk, okay?
- He's in there, starving.
- Listen to me.
Let's talk man-to-man.
Stop. Yes. Put me down.
- Very good. Thank you. Thank you.
- Throw him.
Throw him where?
NOOOO!
[Screaming]
Ouch! That hurts!
Oh shit.
Mummy...
What are you doing?
You can't just dump me here and leave!
Hello?
It's dark in here.
I'm scared of the dark, bro.
I get panic attacks.
I have anxiety issues.
Darkness triggers my childhood trauma.
Get me out of here!
Hello?
[Breathing Heavily]
Where did they go?
What is this place?
[Breathing Heavily]
Mom always insisted
I memorize the Hanuman Chalisa,
but I never did.
Now I'm paying the price.
O dear lord, I earnestly pray,
please keep the evil away.
- [bats squeaking]
- [Screaming]
[panting]
[metal clanking]
[growling]
[Screaming]
I can hear...?
Now you show up, my dear,
These longing teeth have waited years.
You mean "these longing eyes", right?
Eyes get blamed for no reason.
It's the teeth that enjoy the real fun.
- Teeth?
- Yes.
Who are you anyway?
A wretched soul, much like you,
Bound in chains for decades through.
Sir, I'm terrified in here
and you're recounting poetry?
You've only been here a minute,
I've spent decades in this cave.
What more can you expect from a prisoner?
[metal clanking]
But why keep you prisoner?
Why not?
Why can't they hold me prisoner?
Of course they can, you totally qualify.
What's wrong with me?
You've got everything it takes, sir.
You're totally qualified to be a prisoner.
- Right?
- Right.
[exhales heavily]
[growling]
[evil laughter]
Relax mate, relax.
It's alright.
I was just joking.
Oh my god!
Sir, you know English?
I've drunk the blood of enough Englishmen
to pick up their tongue!
Ben Stokes!
Who's Ben Stokes?
An Englishman.
[tongue click]
An Englishman, you say?
An Englishman!
Oh, those glory days...
[evil laughter]
Thamma! Thamma! Thamma! Thamma!
Blood of Englishmen?
You were a freedom fighter?
You were a revolutionary?
Of course, I was a revolutionary.
Wow.
Come here now.
Give me your blood,
and I'll give you a life of indulgence.
Come here...
come closer.
Hurry up.
Come closer.
Come here now.
[Screaming]
Agh...
Tadaka!
Let's go.
[Screaming]
Tadaka!
Veeran, go get them!
[Screaming]
Alok...
come on, let's move.
- No, I can't.
- Get up!
[growling]
[Mystical song]
- Easy, easy, easy.
- Alok, close your eyes!
Who are you... the Wonder Girl?
Shh.
[sniffing]
Don't panic.
They won't find us in this dense forest.
They will sniff you out.
What are they, sniffer dogs?
Now they won't be able to...
[Breathing Heavily]
Veeran!
[Romantic music]
- Alok, you see that truck?
- Yeah.
You need to jump from here.
- Okay?
- Me?
- Yes.
- From here?
I've never even thrown a bloody stone
from this height.
How do you expect me to jump
from this height?
- Alok, we don't have time.
- No.
- You have to go.
- Yes.
- What about you?
We're forbidden from going any further.
You saved my life. Not once but twice.
I can't leave you behind.
They'll throw you in that cave.
[Sighs]
Alok, they're almost here.
Go!
Yes.
They'll kill you
and throw me in that cave.
Go, Alok!
[panting]
Hurry.
Go on.
Go.
Hurry.
Look,
I have no intention of dying together.
That leaves us with only one option:
How about
we live together instead, hmm?!
[Sighs]
Once you're fully recovered,
I'll take you home.
[Sombre music]
[Grunts]
[Winces in pain]
Girl, you have no fear!
You should totally go for the Olympics.
You could probably bring home
three or four golds, easy.
Though not officially,
still yours I'll forever be.
Yours I'll forever be.
[gentle music]
Though not officially,
still yours I'll forever be.
Yours I'll forever be.
Whether or not I am there with you.
Love that no one can understand but you,
Something that's only felt by you.
Something that cannot
be measured or subdued,
Something that even time
can't hold from you.
Love that I have for you,
not just my heart but all of me too.
[Sanskrit Chants]
Sir, Mr. Alok's hit the afterlife!
Now Mr. Alok's entered heaven!
[Sobs]
If you've got that kind of pull up there,
why not just call him back?
Huh?
Mom?
Alok...
Alok!
ALOK!!!
- My child!
- Mom!
Mom! Mom!
My son's back.
My son is back.
Mom, I'm fine.
My son's back.
Take that off.
Dad!
Oh Dad!
A true influencer, indeed...
an influencer-priest!
Thank God!
Alok!
Alok is alive!
Sudha... Sudha, listen...
Yes.
Something tells me he's not our son.
Sudha, he could be an imposter.
Someone who'll milk this situation later.
You mean he'll take advantage of you?
Even the garbage man
won't pick up your trash
without you begging him to.
Who'd take advantage of you?
- You...
- It's fine, Mom.
Let Dad clear his doubts.
- No way.
- Mom...
This won't take long.
[Sighs]
So you're Alok.
Alok Goyal?
Yes, Dad.
We used to have a dog.
What was its name?
Moti.
What percentile did you get
in high school?
56!
Huh?
[laughing]
Okay, fine... 55.6%.
- Yes.
- Dad, can we go outside now and--
Hold on... wait.
Back there...
Uh, you've got a mole on your bum...
[unzipping the pants]
Here you go.
Pull your pants up.
I wanted to see the mole,
not your dump hole.
Now cut the drama,
or should I share your internet history
screenshots with Mom?
Hey... MY SON!!!
My Alok... my Goyal!
[Chuckling]
Okay.
Mom, how do you even live with this man?
They say blood recognizes blood.
He can't even do that.
Let it go, son.
This man's blood's negative too.
What's your name, dear?
Tadaka.
Tadaka?
Sounds like a demon's name.
It's Tarika. Her name is Tarika...
She saved my life.
Without her,
it would've been game over for me.
Seems like your "game over"
happened a long time ago.
Mom, Dad, a bear attacked me.
Then she just appeared out of nowhere.
Nursed me back to health.
You didn't just save him,
you saved us too.
No, I only saved him.
[Chuckling]
Oh, my innocent Tarika...
Why is she here?
Up in the mountains,
her stepmom and step-uncle
tried forcing her to marry some old creep.
I stopped it.
I said, "Nope,
this wedding's not happening."
Sounds like a movie plot.
It's not a movie plot,
it's a saga of cruelty.
Cruelty?
Yeah, her stepmom's cruelty.
Good call, son.
I'm glad you brought her here.
She stays here now.
Here? Why?
Why you ask?
She saved Alok's life.
Eight years ago you had an accident.
Right.
Did we make the doctor
who saved you stay with us?
End of discussion.
She stays.
She saved him. Full and final.
Come on, let me show you the house.
My son's back.
She saved him.
Just like that...?
Hallelujah! Hallelujah!
What is your name?
[laughing]
The hand of God is with youuu.
Hallelujah! Hallelujah!
HALLELUJAH!
[Clapping]
Hallelujah! Hallelujah!
Danger looms over India!
The enemy's set a beauty trap.
She says "Hi" to ensnare,
then hooks them with a "Love you, dear".
The young men of our country
are falling victim to Honey Traps!
She'll call to you,
but don't go near,
She'll trap your heart,
so don't get caught here.
Love isn't easy, better know that,
It's a trap, and you'll get caught flat.
[eerie music]
Alok, here's your favorite Rajma
(kidney beans).
Wow,
I've been dying to have this.
You didn't take anything.
Here, have this, dear.
Tomorrow I'll make 'chole bathoore'
(fried bread with chickpeas).
I'll make any vegetarian dish you want,
you just have to name it.
She's a great cook.
What would you like?
Barasingha ! (reindeer)
Barasingha ?
Singhada ! (Water chestnuts)
Big Singhada ! (Big water chestnuts)
It's their specialty.
They are huge.
[Chuckling]
I wouldn't even mind a rabbit if I--
If she could keep it as a pet!
They raise rabbits.
So, who's in your family besides rabbits?
No one.
What do you mean by "no one"?
No one means no one.
She's a true, pure orphan.
She lost her parents young.
[tongue click]
If her parents died,
How did the stepmom come into the picture?
Stepmom, who?
- The one forcing her to marry?
- [Coughs]
Oh, her!
Yes, her.
So, do you have a stepmom or not?
No.
No?
No,
she means she isn't a mother,
she is a witch.
Then where did this witchy-stepmom
come from if her parents were dead?
Come on now,
this isn't the time to ask such things.
It's the right time.
It's just eight o'clock.
- Well where did she come from?--
- Papa!--
Rajma, stepma...
Speak up now.
Come on, tell me,
where did she come from?
- [sneezes]
- [glass shattering]
[eerie music]
[Chuckling]
I'm not hungry.
No problem.
Go rest in your room.
You can have some milk before bed.
[chair creaks]
Sudha...
Something's fishy.
It's a sap trap.
Huh?
Honey trap.
She says "Hi" to ensnare,
then hooks them with a "Love you, dear".
Mark my words, she'll steal our land
and property one day.
I knew it.
Right?
This is what happens
if you binge on crime shows.
What's a beautiful girl like her doing
with Alok if it's not a honey trap?
What do you mean?
Alok's a goof, an idiot...
he's nothing special.
Shut up!
My son looks like a superstar.
He's taken after my brother.
Gone senile...
[Dog Barking]
[Hissing]
What happened, Tarika?
Is there something wrong with my name?
No... not at all.
Tadaka's just a bit weird for the city,
that's why... Tarika.
Do you know what Tarika means?
A star!
That's exactly what you are.
Your ways, name, food, culture...
everything's different.
You're different.
I understand.
But my parents won't.
That's why I lied to placate them.
We can't lie.
Why not?
A lie that helps someone isn't a lie,
it's the truth.
Truly?
Nope, a lie.
A lie?
I get it.
Your culture forbids lying.
But here, it's a whole different game.
Umm,
I know it's not like your airplane.
It's a little different.
Just adjust for a few days.
And adjust to Mom's clothes for a bit too.
We'll get you new clothes
first thing tomorrow.
[dramatic music]
Tarika?
She was here a second ago.
Where'd she go?
Tarika!
[Knock On Door]
Tarika?
[door creaking]
Tarika... Tadaka!
Tadaka!
[Screaming]
[maniacal laughter]
Shush.
Why are you laughing like that?
It's just how I laugh.
Okay...
But what are you doing under the bed?
I like it here.
Me too.
[thumping heartbeat]
I can hear your heart beat.
It's racing.
My heart always races when I'm with you.
[Romantic music]
[Hissing]
Alok!
What are you doing down there?
Mom, I was just...
showing Tarika my room.
Fine.
[Sighs]
Give her some milk once you're done.
Hmm?
Yes.
Okay.
My son's all grown up now.
She loves him,
she loves him not.
[metal clanking]
She loves him,
she loves him not.
[Breathing Heavily]
You're a Betaal and he's human...
yet he still escaped?
Shame on you, Veeran.
I can't even show my teeth
to anyone now, thanks to you.
I tried my best to stop him.
But Tadaka ran away with that human.
What now?
I...
What's with all the "I... I... I..."?
You'll keep whining
if you drink goat's blood.
Start drinking human blood.
We're forbidden from drinking human blood.
What Tadaka did was also forbidden.
What?
She fell in love.
Love?
Yes.
That's why Tadaka saved
that human and ran away.
That love will cause her
to make more mistakes in the future.
So what are your orders?
GO GET HIM BACK!!!
[yawning]
[Dog Barking]
[bats squeaking]
[Window Opens]
Su... Sudha!
Sudha!
SUDHAAA!
Tarika isn't a honey trap.
What?
She's paranormal.
I know...
she's normal.
Hey...
I know this will sound strange...
Go on.
She's possessed by a bat's spirit.
Huh?
A bat.
I once got a wedding proposal
from a lawyer.
He earned well too.
But I chose you.
Today, that lawyer's wife
must be sleeping peacefully.
Come on Sudha, I'm not kidding.
I just saw her jump
from Alok's window on to a tree.
No human can do that.
She's possessed by a bat!
If I got possessed by a lioness,
you'd be in deep trouble.
Sudha, please, just hear me out.
GO TO SLEEP!
Good night.
[suspense music]
[Snoring]
[Dog Barking]
Tarika!
[Footsteps]
[dog whimpers]
[startled gasp]
Tadaka...
What are you doing?
You were going to...
Nope, not happening!
You can't.
I totally can.
Quite easily, in fact.
He's a dog!
He's so cute...
and chubby,
just like a rabbit!
Hand him over.
Give me that dog.
Come here, boy.
He's really making you hungry, huh?
Hmm.
I'll sort you some food tomorrow.
Okay?
Wait.
Go away.
Shoo!
[dog panting]
What, you'd eat a lizard too?
Let's go.
[Car Door Opens]
[Car Door Closes]
Sir, your car's crooked.
Park it properly
or I'll file a complaint.
Go on, do it.
I'm running late, man.
Why are you messing around?
Alok, we tore the place
apart looking for you that day.
Thanks, bro.
You two bolted
with your tails between your legs.
Sorry, dude.
Thank God Tarika saved me.
Otherwise I'd...
Wait, Tarika? That mountain girl?
How do you even know about her?
The whole group won't shut up about her.
So, what's she like?
I don't think she's all that beautiful.
[Chuckling]
[sighs heavily]
By the way, you look really pretty tonight.
What am I doing here dressed like this?
It's our first date.
I wanted it to be a bit special.
Spe--
It's a top-notch place.
They've got great selection of meat here.
- I'm not bad at heart,
- Disgusting!
I have just one fault I confess.
Not out of habit,
I drink for the thirst, no less.
[gentle music]
So tell me, what happens to the drink-bearers
when my cup stops brinking?
I'd rather stop living than stop drinking.
If I had to count the glasses that
I keep downing, I'd rather stop counting,
I'd rather stop living than stop drinking.
- Your eyes...
- Poison, baby.
- Your words...
Your attitude is delicious,
- Your moves...
- Poison, baby.
- The way you groove...
Even your atrocity is precious.
As soon as I took a sip of the drink,
I felt younger, years gone in a blink.
With a glass in hand
there's nothing I won't do,
All the things without that drink
I couldn't pull through.
I'd crack a bottle on the head of anyone
who's prying,
I'd rather stop living
than stop my drinking.
So tell me, what happens to the drink-bearers
when my cup stops brinking?
I'd rather stop living than stop drinking.
- Your eyes...
- Poison, baby.
- Your words...
Your attitude is delicious,
- Your moves...
- Poison, baby.
- The way you groove...
Even your atrocity is precious.
Poison, baby.
Poison... baby.
What the hell was that about?
We're in Delhi.
Here, even eye contact
is taken out of context.
Guys think a girl's easy.
I don't know what came over me.
My head was spinning.
You don't drink often?
Never had it before.
That's why.
Let's head home.
I'll make you some lemonade, sober you up.
[car horn blaring]
Stop the car!
Stop! Stop the car!
[car horn blaring]
Stop!
Use blinkers, man. Use blinkers!
Overtake them.
Step on it! Step on it!
Come on, step on it!
How dare you!
Where are you taking your sister-in-law?
STOP THE CAR!
- Stop the car!
- Let us have some fun too.
Why are they following us?
- Where are you taking your sister-in-law?
- Stop the car!
I need to lose them.
Shit.
Hey sweetheart!
Don't you get it?!
Follow him... go after him!
- Overtake him... overtake him!
- Follow him... go after him!
Step on it! Step on it!
Shit. Shit. Shit.
Where will you go now?
Come on out, kiddo...
- Jimmy's waiting for you.
- Come on out.
Stay in the car.
I'll handle this.
Okay?
Come on out, ma'am. We won't hurt you.
Come to daddy, kiddo.
[Car Door Opens]
[laughing]
Scared already?
Hey, kiddo!
Why do all girls go
for clean-shaven losers?
We can clean up too, bro.
[Chuckling]
Hey baby-steps...
Hey baby-steps... hurry up already!
I don't have time to waste.
Move faster!
Let's talk, bro.
You're in big trouble.
Shut it.
- Let's talk.
- Let's talk?
Yeah.
She's a nice girl.
Why chase her if she isn't interested?
She is interested.
Who was she with at the party?
Jimmy.
So why'd she leave with you?
That's cheating, dude.
Wait here.
These kids will look after you.
I'll handle her.
Let it go, bro.
Just take some cash and sort it out.
I can pay you.
I don't want trouble, bro.
He'll pay us, he says!
I don't want any trouble either,
I want something else.
[Coughs]
Cigarette smoking is injurious to--
[Slapping]
[Winces in pain]
Go fetch your sister-in-law.
Be nice. Tell her Jimmy's calling her.
[laughing]
[growling]
[dramatic music]
[Hissing]
[suspense music]
[shouting]
[Winces in pain]
[glass shattering]
[music builds up]
[growling]
[glass shattering]
[Screaming]
[suspense music]
[Gun Firing]
[growling]
[music intensifies]
Tadaka!!!
[growling]
Wh... what are you doing?
[music intensifies]
Let's get out of here. Hurry up!
[Footsteps]
[Car Door Opens, closes]
[Car Engine Starts]
[growling]
[Bones Cracking]
Alright, now tell me...
That.. What was that?
What were you going to do?
Speak up... why are you so quiet now, huh?
You're... a man-eater?
No, no way.
No! Stay back! One arm distance!
I'm not a man-eater.
Then?
I wasn't going to eat him.
I was going to drink his blood.
BLOODDDD?
You were going to drink his blood?
I'd never make such a mistake.
But when they started hitting you,
I don't know what came over me...
I lost control.
But... blood?!
Do you really drink blood?
Yes, I drink blood.
That's a weird habit.
There are so many drinks in the world,
yet you choose blood!
Why are you doing this?
- Alok...
- No, no, no, stay back.
You relishing a barasingha
is still something I can relate to.
People have exotic taste buds.
They eat anything...
dogs, cats, jackal or even bats.
But who drink blood, dude?!
Alok...
Wait a second... Are you a vampire?
Vampire?
Like in those horror movies?
They drink blood,
get burned by sunlight, sleep in coffins,
and have no shadows.
Close cousins of ghosts?
Invisible in mirrors.
I can see you.
Are you a hybrid?
Alok...
- Stop right there.
- We are Betaals.
We are Betaals.
We only drink blood.
"We ONLY drink blood."
What a claim!
- Alok...
- No!
Don't come closer, I'll smash you.
How would I even explain
to the world who and what you are?
Tomorrow at dinner when Mom asks
what Tarika wants... what will I say?
"Nothing, Mom,
just give her some fresh blood!"
Only the veteran actor Dharmendra
has the right to say,
"I'll drink your blood, you dog."
He too just says it,
never actually drinks it.
SHIT!!!
Here I thought you were a Wonder Girl,
turns out you're Dracula.
Dracula?
Who's that?
You don't know who Dracula is?
Collar up, fangs out, walks like this.
I mean...
He's got to be related to you somehow.
You might not know him.
Maybe he's one of your uncles.
Alok, we don't drink human blood anymore.
Why should I believe you?
Why?
Isn't it enough that I said we don't?
I don't know.
We used to drink human blood...
but only of those less human, more beasts.
But after 1947, things changed.
What do you mean?
[Screaming]
[glass shattering]
Riots broke out.
Rioters were rolling into town,
packed into trains.
[people wailing]
We went there to drink the killers' blood
and save the innocent.
But when we arrived, we were stunned.
There weren't rioters,
just innocent people
who'd slaughtered each other,
and were lying dead.
We'd never seen that much blood.
No other animal kills like that
for no reason.
From that day, we decided
humans are poisonous
because their blood is toxic.
So we stopped drinking their blood.
[blood dripping]
[Gasping]
You are lying.
Back in that cave, that poet...
he wanted to drink my blood.
That's why we locked him
in the cursed mountain.
Who is he?
The most powerful,
deadliest of us all...
Yakshashan.
Our ancestor.
The one who made us Betaals.
Our hero...
our Thamma.
[dramatic music]
[growling]
We all agreed not to drink human blood,
but Yakshashan refused.
[evil laughter]
[growling]
You broke the rule.
You will be punished.
Your rules are baseless.
Drinking human blood is in our nature.
One day, we'll turn them all
and rule the world.
We will rule!
We want to break free
from this curse of drinking blood.
[metal clanking]
You're our ancestor.
You created us.
That's why we keep offering
animal sacrifices to keep you alive.
From now on,
you'll stay imprisoned in this cave.
For how long do you think
you can keep me imprisoned?
Hundred years of toil and pain,
The day one of you breaks the rule
and turns a human into a Betaal...
I'll be free.
FREE!!!
You said you imprisoned Yakshashan
after the 1947 incident.
You were there?
I mean... How?
I'm not human.
I don't have a heartbeat.
But you do.
[thumping heartbeat]
And that's what pulls me to you.
It just... compels me.
[doorbell rings]
[Dog Barking]
[Door Opens]
Who are you?
Inspector P.K. Yadav.
Oh. Goyal.
Hello.
All good, Officer?
No Mr. Goyal,
I'm afraid things aren't looking good.
Oh, so you are here seeking a donation?
Do I look like the one
who'd seek a donation?
I'm here to investigate.
Investigate what?
Something happened with a couple of boys.
Do you know anything about it?
No.
If I did, I'd tell you.
I'd do anything for the police.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Okay, so what have you done
for the police?
I've watched Singham eight times.
Big fan.
Big fan, sir.
[Tense music]
What's your name?
Tarika.
Tadaka.
Tadaka or Tarika?
Only Tarika.
So, Ms. "Only Tarika,"
were you at a party earlier?
Hmm?
Yes.
Hmm.
Did some guys misbehave with you there?
Did they cause trouble?
That's what I want to discuss...
in private.
Let's go.
[Door Closes]
[fabric rustling]
Rakhtrambha ! (I'll protect through blood!)
Sasakhtrambha !
(I'll protect through strength!)
[Hissing]
You...?!
You too?
Me too.
Knew it...
knew who you were the second
I saw those guys.
Why did you kill them?
Kill them?
You killed them, right?
Hmm?
Good thing you just broke their necks.
Biting them and drinking blood
would've been caused a lot of trouble.
Where did you come from?
Why did you kill them?
They...
they were hurting Alok.
My head was spinning.
I lost control.
I can't remember what happened next.
For 172 years,
it has been my responsibility,
to maintain the equilibrium
between humans and our kind.
And you're messing up that balance.
Alok's making you lose control.
You could hurt him and his family.
You could attack them,
bite them, drink their blood.
You should leave
before you cause more trouble.
GO.
[growling]
Congratulations, son.
She finally got caught.
Come on, Dad.
[Door Opens]
All okay, dear?
Tarika?
So... what happened?
[suspense music]
Why aren't you saying anything?
I have to leave, Alok.
What did the officer say?
Don't worry, whatever it is,
I'll handle it.
He knows what I did to those guys.
What did you do?
What exactly does he know?
The police found their bodies.
Did you kill them?
I don't know.
What do you mean by "you don't know"?
All I know is you might be
in danger because of me.
You said you don't drink human blood--
I'm a Betaal, Alok!
What if I lose control one day
and hurt you?
[Breathing Heavily]
[intense music]
Whether or not I am there with you.
[thumping heartbeat]
I want to be with you...
but I just can't.
Our worlds are too different.
I have to go.
Please, don't leave.
[Hissing]
[intense music]
What more could I want than you
remembering me your whole life through,
Whether or not I am there with you.
Even without being beside you,
Each day, each moment,
I'll still be with you,
Whether or not I am there with you.
I am not away from you,
I'm right there where you are too.
I'll always flourish in you,
Whether or not I am there with you.
[car screeching]
[car horn blaring]
Tarika, please don't go.
I don't want to lose you.
Tarika, please stay.
Please don't go.
Stop the bus.
[bus horn blaring]
[Tire Screeching]
[Gasping]
[car crash]
[Winces in pain]
[fire crackling]
[grunting]
Alok!
[Breathing Heavily]
What more could I want than you
- remembering me your whole life through,
- Alok...
Whether or not I am there with you.
- Whether or not I am there with you.
- [Screaming]
Whether or not I am there with you.
[Ambulance Siren]
Quick! Quick! Right!
[Phone Ringing]
Sorry, ma'am, you can't come inside.
[suspense music]
This way. Tarika!
Tarika!
Where is Alok?
WHERE IS ALOK?!!!
[defibrillator charging]
[electric jolt]
[flatline tone]
[Footsteps]
Doctor, Alok...?
I'm sorry.
Sudha...
[Crying]
[bats screeching]
[growling]
[bats squeaking]
[Gibberish]
[dramatic music]
[growling]
[Mystical song]
[evil laughter]
FREEDOOM!
The patient's not in the room.
He's not?
[Door Opens]
Alok...?
Alok!
Where's Alok?
[fabric rustling]
Alok!
[Door Opens]
[suspense music]
[music builds up]
[glass shattering]
[Door Opens]
[dramatic music]
[slurping]
[Tense music]
[Hissing]
[growling]
ALOKKK!!!
[Gasping]
What's wrong?
Are you alright?
Aa...
Where's Alok?
He's fine, Alok is fine.
He's been discharged.
He's sleeping in his room.
I saw him at the hospital.
Good you found him.
Alok woke up and somehow
went upstairs by mistake.
He got upstairs by mistake?
Yes.
Then he ended up
in the blood bank by mistake?
Yes.
Who makes such detailed mistakes, huh?
What about the teeth?
What teeth?
Alok's teeth!
Which teeth? Whose teeth? What--
He tried to attack his own father!
Huh?
[Gibberish]
The doctor said
you might be delusional after
your head injury
and say strange things.
You should rest.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
[Grunts]
[clock ticking]
[dramatic music]
Tadaka, what's wrong with me?
I acted strangely
at the hospital yesterday.
Today, I feel weird.
I can't feel my pulse or heartbeat.
Rakhtrambha ! (I'll protect through blood!)
Sasakhtrambha !
(I'll protect through strength!)
[Breathing Heavily]
Huh?
[Grunts]
[Crying]
[Sighs]
[Sobs]
You turned me?
So I'm dead now?
I'm not human anymore?
Shit!
Shit! Shit! Shit!
What do I even do now?
My life, dreams, ambitions...
it's all over now.
How do I even face social media?
How will I ever enjoy Rajma-chawal
(kidney beans with rice) again?
Guess there goes my life insurance too.
Why did you do this?
You would be dead if I didn't, Alok.
Killing me and then saying I would
be dead otherwise makes zero sense!
You were so quick to preach back then...
Humans are this, humans are that.
They have hatred in their blood.
Humans are poisonous.
They are like cloves, garlic and what not.
What was that about?
And what about your rules?
You said you cannot bite humans.
So why did you bite me?
[Romantic music]
Whether or not I am there with you.
You were dying, Alok...
I didn't want to lose you.
Love that no one can understand but you,
Something that's only felt by through you.
Something that cannot
be measured or subdued,
Something that even time
can't hold from you.
I am not away from you,
I'm right there where you are too.
Now I am free of them too,
Whether or not I am there with you.
If not as a human, then as a Betaal...
I just wanted to stay with you, Alok.
Even if it was just
for a little while longer.
Why just a little longer?
Now I want to be
with you forever and ever and ever.
By the way, even dying a hundred
times for this kiss is totally worth it.
Whether or not I am there with you.
With you...
Like a bird,
I wish to fly through the boundless sky,
Today I'm free in the garden
where the world lies.
Like a bird, I wish to fly...
[evil laughter]
We've got good news!
[metal clanking]
How about treating me to the blood
of a diabetic as something sweet?
It's been ages since such fires were lit.
Tadaka bit that human
and turned him into a Betaal!
But Yakshasan...
No ifs or buts!
Your Thamma will be free...
And Tadaka will be locked away here.
[exhales heavily]
What's eating you, Rakhtash?
The king of kings is back.
Aren't you going to give me
a grand welcome?
Hurry up and make arrangements.
I'll get warmed up...
After all, soon I'll rule...
the world!
[evil laughter]
Like a bird,
I wish to fly through the boundless sky,
Today I'm free in the garden
where the world lies.
I've broken the cardinal rule,
and that could set Yakshasan free.
Who knows what he'll do then?
He'll drink human blood, obviously.
Tell me something, you Betaals...
Sorry...
"We" Betaals... why do we drink blood?
Did our ancestors not fancy
any other drink?
We need to kill humans
to recharge ourselves.
Ever thought about that?
No, never.
We weren't created to kill,
we were created to protect.
To protect?
The great demon Rakhtbeej
had a boon from Lord Shiva.
Every drop of his blood
would spawn another Rakhtbeej.
[music builds up]
When all the Gods lost to him,
they turned to the Goddess for help.
She fought fiercely with Rakhtbeej,
but every strike that drew his blood
created more Rakhtbeej.
So, to kill them and drink their blood,
the Goddess created Betaal.
[fire crackling]
Betaals:
born of darkness,
they drink blood,
they never die.
We were created to protect the earth.
All our rules exist for that.
Now you must follow them too,
to protect the earth.
How the hell am I supposed
to protect anyone when I'm scared stiff?
How can I protect the entire damn earth?
What if something happens to me?
How can I--
[Winces in pain]
Hey, drop the act...
you're absolutely fine.
[unzips the jacket]
You'll be indestructible.
You won't get hurt.
You won't feel any pain.
Got it?
This is crazy!
I'm slowly getting it.
You'll go through a lot of changes.
Now you've got to learn
to control yourself.
Control.
[cupboard door opens]
At first, the sun will bother you,
stepping out won't be easy.
But slowly, you'll get used to it.
Hey!
Your car's parked all crooked...
straighten it.
Your strength will grow immensely,
you won't even realize
how powerful you've become.
[peppy music]
[Beeping]
(Upbeat Music)
And your speed...
your speed will surpass even a cheetah's.
See you inside, sir.
(Upbeat Music)
The thirst for blood will grow
every time you see humans.
But you've got to control it.
(Upbeat Music)
Mummy...
[Hissing]
Alok...
Alok! Alok!
Open your mouth!
Show me your teeth!
Goyal, flash those punching-machine-like
teeth right now!
Are you a dentist?
The other day you wanted to see
the mole on my hip,
today you want to see my teeth.
I'm not showing them. What will you do?
- I'm out of here.
- Show them!
Where did they vanish to?
[growling]
This is what he does, Inspector!
My son is a demon.
That girl turned him into a demon.
She has got him under her spell.
She is a witch.
[Chuckling]
Come on, Mr. Goyal,
every in-law claims
their daughter-in-law is a witch.
She's not even my daughter-in-law.
Fine, your future daughter-in-law then.
How's she going to be
that if I don't let her?
Mr. Goyal, you call your son a demon,
and your daughter-in-law a witch.
What about your wife?
What do you think she is?
A vengeful spirit?
[laughing]
Now's not the time to laugh.
Save my son, please.
That girl's dangerous.
She can do anything.
Obviously, she is a woman.
Women can do anything.
But you're the police.
Aren't you going to do something?
Of course I am.
Tell me,
did you tell anyone else about this?
No. Not a word.
Good.
I'll make sure she's sent away.
Go home. P.K.
P.K.?
P.K. Yadav, Inspector.
Yes.
It's my job to send her away now.
Fine. It's your responsibility now.
Okay.
[Footsteps]
We have to end the new Betaal
to get Tadaka back.
No way.
We can't do that.
That's against the rules.
Then maybe it's time to change the rules.
Only a Thamma can change rules.
And we've got a Thamma.
Not our Thamma.
A Thamma with a heartbeat...
Only he can lead us forward.
That's nonsense.
Humans turn into Betaals
when their heart stops.
So how can Betaals' hero,
messiah,
the new Thamma,
have a heartbeat?
That's just folklore.
No one like that's ever coming.
Our Thamma's been the same
for centuries...
The Great Yakshasan.
Go find Tadaka and that Betaal
and bring them here.
[exhales heavily]
It's tough, huh?
I know.
Really tough.
Now jump.
Okay.
What?!
Jump.
- From here?
- Yes.
Are you serious?
[gentle music]
(Upbeat Music)
What was that?!
See? You were scared for nothing.
Me? Scared?
Nah, I don't scare that easily.
You offered your hand so sweetly that...
[growling]
Huh?
What's this?
You can't lie anymore.
Fangs pop out whenever we lie.
By themselves?
Uh-huh.
I can't even bloody lie anymore!
Control. Control.
Come on, let's go home.
Yes, let's go home.
Not like that.
How about we hop, skip,
and jump home?
Hop, skip, and jump?
(Upbeat Music)
[Sighs]
I'm good now.
Could do better.
There's a lot that's going
to get better now.
[Chuckling]
Dad! What are you doing in my room?
That's so creepy.
Who's being creepy here, me or you?
Where did you even come from?
Outside.
Everyone comes in from outside, son...
but through the door.
Not by jumping in through the balcony.
Are you stalking me?
Do you see anything written here?
Yes. No.
Then why are you assuming it?
Tell me, what are you hiding from me?
Nothing.
[Hissing]
What was that?
Nothing.
No, no, no...
Let me see.
- No. Just drop it.
- Let me see them.
Just let it go.
What's wrong with your nails?
- Just let it go.
- Let me see them!
[growling]
[Screaming]
The... the punching-machine-like teeth!
I was suspicious back at the hospital.
So I was right.
What's going on here?
Your son is dead.
But he's right here.
That day, he actually died
in a highway accident.
He died?
Then what is this?
His wandering soul?
The one that likes to wear a coat?
He's not a spirit.
Then?
I bit him and turned him like me.
Huh?
What do you mean "like you"?
So you're dead too?
[Hissing]
[Screaming]
What game are you playing with me?
My heart doesn't beat, Dad.
No heartbeat.
I know you won't believe it,
but it is what it is.
Aa... Alok...
Alok...
My son...
[Sobs]
You...
You... you're dead?
[Sobs]
If I tell Sudha, she'd...
We thought you'd support us in old age.
I will, Dad.
Now, I'll be your evergreen support.
You'll grow old,
but your support will always stay young.
No, you're not Alok.
You're my son's spirit. You're not Alok.
I'm not a spirit, Dad...
but close.
I'm a Betaal.
Betaal?
That's what our species are called.
[Footsteps]
He has turned into a Betaal.
I knew it!
I knew you "witch"
would spell doom for my son!
If I hadn't done this,
he'd have died in the hospital.
I couldn't let him die.
I love Alok.
Couldn't you love someone else?
You should've chosen someone
from your own community.
Some tall, dark, red-eyed guy with fangs.
Don't worry, son.
I'll get the best doctor.
I'll get the best heart doctor,
transplant your heart,
bring your heartbeat back.
Doctors can't help, Dad.
If not a doctor, then a tantric
or miracle performing sage could help.
No one can do anything, Dad.
Not even God.
How about the hand of God?
Hmm?
Don't worry, son.
The hand of God is with youuuu.
Why don't you get it?
How do I explain?
I'll tell you a story. Listen carefully.
It's a full moon night,
moonlight falls on the earth...
And the moment it hits, my brother goes...
Grrrr!
Grrrr?!
Oh my God,
your brother's a Bhediya (wolf)!
Exactly!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Yes.
He's a perverted human,
with a wolf inside.
Amazing! We desperately need a Bhediya .
Okay.
Tell me,
how exactly did your brother
turn into a Bhediya ?
Long story.
You could easily make a movie
with a post-credit scene out of it.
I'll tell you some other time.
Right now, I am here because
he's dealing with a big problem.
So just hear me out.
Why are you here instead of him?
He's been thrashed so badly,
he can't face anyone anymore.
Impossible! Bhediya is so powerful!
Who thrashed him?
A monster... with a chopped off thingy.
With a chopped off what?
A chopped-off body part.
During the fight,
that monster did things I can't even say.
He did that?
No, he didn't do THAT!
Come on, man!
My brother fought the monster.
So the monster thrashed him so badly...
How did he thrash him?
Like this.
Now that poor guy
can't fully turn into a Bhediya .
All he can do is... Dame Un Grrr!
You're quite skilled.
You helped capture that wretched Munjya .
You've got a solution for this too, right?
Any powder, pill, elixir of life?
Anything?
Think with your mind, not your hand.
(Gibberish)
Stop it.
Hey, Padre!
[Table bell ringing]
Padre, my brother?
[dramatic music]
Hey!
That's my brother! That's my brother!
Yes, Bhediya :
The protector of the jungle!
Right.
To boost his power, he needs
to drink the blood
of a bloodsucker.
A bloodsucker?
A leech! You mean a leech!
[laughing]
No,
I mean a special species.
They look like humans
and drink human blood.
Betaal!
He sinks his fangs right into the vein
and drinks the blood.
Yes.
Like Dracula?
Something like that.
But that species is extinct.
Extinct? No, don't say that.
[Clears throat]
Sorry, It looks difficult.
You keep shouting,
"Hand of God! Hand of God!"
You've got to do something.
Don't you know that
the glaciers are melting
and extinct species are coming back?
Huge tusked elephants, flying crocodiles,
good actors.
Padre, please, just two minutes.
Just two minutes.
- What happened?
- There's an emergency.
What's the emergency?
Am I invisible or what?
I'm still sitting here talking to him,
and you just barged in!
A desperate father is begging you.
Only two minutes.
Please.
No, Uncle, don't. You can take three.
Thank you, son, thank you.
Bittu! What are you doing in Delhi, bro?
Who's Bittu?
Now, what's the emergency?
The emergency...
Sir, there's a boy who a witchy girl...
- Dad...
- Give me a minute, let me explain.
A boy was bitten here by a witchy girl.
Now he's become like her.
Sex change?
No, no, no sex change.
He's turned into a demon, just like her.
His heart doesn't beat.
He gets wild at the sight of blood.
He's dead, yet alive.
You are talking about him, right?
No sir, he's talking about someone else.
[growling]
Hey! Hey Betaal!
Miracle!
What a coincidence!
You know about them?
Yes.
I knew it! I knew you'd know!
So tell me Padre,
is there any way to cure a Betaal
and make him human again?
You can make an omelette
from an egg, right?
Right.
But can an omelette ever turn back
into an egg?
I wouldn't know... I'm vegetarian.
Oh.
Then...
You can make ketchup from tomatoes, right?
Right.
But can ketchup ever turn back
into tomatoes?
- No. No way.
- No.
Similarly, human to Betaal, possible.
But Betaal to human...
impossible.
[Sobs]
Don't say that.
Don't say it, please.
You don't say that.
Be happy.
Congratulations.
For what?
Your family's light can't be extinguished
even with a fire extinguisher.
He's immortal.
You're our last hope.
Please save him.
Please.
I can understand your feelings.
But I am telling you
with all my experience...
Nothing can be done.
Accept it.
There is no cure?
No chance.
Alok?
Goyal?
Goyal?!
Greetings, Uncle.
Sir, don't forget
to transfer my fees of Rs. 10,000!
Alok, listen...
Why should I listen to you?
Why should I, huh?
The girl you call a witch
and demon gave me a new life.
And your son loves her.
And he always will.
[whistling]
That's no way to call anyone.
I have a name - Jana, JD, Janardhan.
What is it?
[tongue click]
What?
(Indistinct)
What are you saying?
[laughing]
Thank you, Padre. Thank you.
[whistling]
Gift!
Make your brother sniff it.
Elixir of life.
- Yes.
Okay.
Miracle! Miracle! Miracle! Miracle!
[Indistinct Chattering]
[dramatic music]
[panting]
Mom, give the phone to Tarika.
Okay, hang on.
Alok.
Tarika, listen up.
Those guys from your tribe who were
chasing us in the jungle the other day...
they're here.
They're following me.
Alok, get out of there now.
Get to high ground, I'm on my way.
Okay.
Hey, are you blind of what?
[Hissing]
Hey!
[music builds up]
[Traffic Noise]
[bats screeching]
[loud thud]
[intense music]
Who the hell are you?
And why'd you fling that rag in my face?
Forget the rag...
I know all about you.
What...
what do you know?
I know you're a Betaal.
Doesn't matter who I am.
What do you want, bro?
Your blood.
Oh, you Wannabe Wolverine,
you're going to resort
to bloodshed now, huh?
Hey Dracula on a budget!
I will drink your blood today.
[growling]
What's with the overacting?
Who's overacting, huh?
[growling]
[Grunts]
Cut the crap.
Let me have your blood, or else...
Why the hell do you even want blood?
I'm the one who drinks blood here.
[Grunts]
Look, I'm asking nicely.
Let me have your blood.
Oh, you want my blood?
[Chuckling]
Then come here...
and take it yourself.
Tommy...
Come on.
[Breathing Heavily]
[wolf howling]
[Grunts]
I am... I am Bhediya!
I came from the jungle
to shake up the town,
With blood-soaked fangs,
I'll strike them down.
[Screaming]
I'll hunt you down,
no one can save you from me,
Now I tear through bone,
along with flesh with glee.
Cut it out, bro.
That's enough.
[Winces in pain]
Under moonlit skies, I vanish to shadow,
From jungle to towers, I prowl unseen,
Who dares face this beast so mean?
No one survives me,
I am such a catastrophe,
[Grunts]
[Romantic music]
[glass shattering]
[electric jolt]
[growling]
[dramatic music]
Who's this guy?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
I don't.
You can kill him, right?
Ye-- No! No!
What kind of a Betaal are you?
Yes.
What do we do now?
What do we do?
[dramatic music]
Let's go.
What the hell?
This... is... crazy!
Who am I?! I must be dreaming!
[growling]
[Breathing Heavily]
[peppy music]
All through the jungle,
word is spreading, news is heading!
Hey! A flower has bloomed
without his underwear!
- Hey! A flower has bloomed
- Jana!
without his underwear!
Why did you drag me here?
He's the one who'll spill everything.
[Knock On Door]
[Door Opens]
Tadaka?
What's he doing here?
He...
Rakhtrambha ! (I'll protect through blood!)
Sasakhtrambha !
(I'll protect through strength!)
Oh.
You too?
He's a cop.
How can he...?
What have you done?
This is a disaster.
You bit him.
I told you to leave, didn't I?
Do you even know what you've done?
You could--
I know. Everything.
Mr. Yadav, we came for your help.
What happened?
Some weird guy attacked me.
He's got fangs and long nails like ours.
He's beefed up.
Moves like an animal-like this.
Archenemies.
Virus.
Yapum.
Bhediya .
Where'd you see him?
Here.
How does it matter anyway?
And why would I even be his enemy?
Not just you, all of us are.
It's ancestral thing.
They've been thirsty
for our blood for centuries.
He didn't drink your blood, did he?
He wouldn't dare.
I offered a drop upfront.
I said, "Here, son, enjoy."
You idiot! You fool! You dumbo!
Couldn't you pick anyone else to bite?
What's wrong?
This is a catastrophe.
What's wrong, she asks!
One drop of Betaal blood makes
Bhediya ten times deadlier.
Ten times!
Now he'll hunt him like a maniac.
He won't rest till he drains him dry.
I won't let him get hurt.
He'll crush you like an ant. An ant!
I told you to leave.
You've messed up the balance.
Tarika, you've broken the balance.
Now what do I tell them?
What do I tell them, huh?
We're all in danger now.
All of us.
[Breathing Heavily]
Listen carefully.
I and my crew will have to protect him.
Your crew?
Come with me, I'll show you the crew.
But... not like that.
These clothes won't cut it.
[peppy music]
[liquid pouring]
[growling]
[Indistinct Chattering]
Welcome to our world.
Don't worry, everyone here's just like us.
Yes.
Amazing.
Wait till I show you something
even crazier inside.
Come.
[peppy music]
Look at our treasure.
All those bottles contain blood?
The rarest of the rare.
Try this.
Whose blood is it?
One who never beheld his beloved's gaze,
What life has he lived,
who never knew love's blaze?
I've seen her somewhere before.
She's the queen of Chanderi.
- What life has he lived,
- Yes, exactly.
who never knew love's blaze?
One who never...
One who never knew love's blaze.
One who has never lost himself in a gaze,
What life has he lived,
who never knew love's blaze?
[peppy music]
[Sighs]
Amazing!
If you seek true love,
Pray with power enough.
This is no road for the weak or meek,
Love calls for the brave,
the strong, the unique.
I'll get you something special. Wait.
Too good!
[laughing]
Alexander!
3000-years-old.
The one who never expressed his love
in any way,
What life has he lived,
who never knew love's blaze?
One who never beheld his beloved's gaze,
What life has he lived,
who never knew love's blaze?
One who never...
One who never knew love's blaze.
What life has he lived,
who never knew love's blaze?
[groaning]
Mr. Alok, wake up.
[Sighs]
Looks like the Englishman's blood
didn't sit well with you.
Where's Tarika?
She's gone.
Gone?
How can she just leave?
I sent her back...
with Veeran.
She didn't tell you everything.
About what?
[Hissing]
Come on, Tadaka.
It's time to head back.
No.
[growling]
You have to go back.
You broke the cardinal rule.
The day you bit Alok,
you knew this would happen.
Now Yakshasan will be free,
and you'll be locked up instead.
For a hundred years.
No.
I'm not leaving Alok.
You knew biting Alok meant
your imprisonment,
yet you broke the rule.
But Alok?
Bhediya is hunting him.
We'll keep Alok safe here.
But that means you have to go.
Do you want to save him or not?
I have no intention of dying together.
How about
we live together instead, hmm?!
Can I see him once before I leave?
[intense music]
Didn't think this is how we would part ways
I have so many things still left to say
Impossible that you
will ever escape my heart
Wish I could take us back to the start...
Tarika risked everything to save me?
Why didn't she tell me?
I have to go find her.
You're not going anywhere!
[growling]
There's a dangerous Bhediya out there.
You'll stay in this city,
under our watch.
And Tarika?
Forget her.
Just forget about her.
Go home and stay low.
Don't step out unless I say so.
Understood?
Did you hear me?
Where were you all night?
Tarika's not home either.
She's gone.
Where to?
Back where she came from.
She broke their cardinal rule for me.
Now she'll be punished for it...
for eternity.
And I'll be stuck here...
without Tarika.
Maybe that's my punishment.
Goyal...
I thought hard after meeting that Padre.
Now I finally get it.
Whoever you are...
Dead or alive...
you're still my son.
You might drink blood...
but you're still my flesh and blood.
Go ahead, drink it.
I'm already 60.
For approximately the next 40 years,
Tarika's my daughter-in-law.
Daughter-in-law?
Look,
no one else can stay
with you this long anyway.
At least, not a human.
Your heart doesn't beat,
but it still loves Tarika.
That love helps you stay human.
Go... bring her back.
I can't, Dad.
Their rules won't let me leave.
What rules? Which rules?
Tarika broke every rule to be
with you, right?
Didn't she?
Then you should break every rule too,
just to be with her.
Come on now.
Come on. Get up.
Go, Goyal.
Enjoy your life after death.
Live long.
[intense music]
[footsteps, dried leaves crunching]
[suspense music]
Thamma! Thamma! Thamma! Thamma!
[Mystical song]
[Mystical music]
[metal clanking]
I can't explain how good
I feel being free after 75 years!
That dark cave bored me to death.
While singing to kill time,
the throat-slasher got a sore throat.
Did you lot get a sore throat too?
Speak up!
Thamma!
Louder!
All together now!
Thamma! Thamma!
Thamma!
I've been longing to hear this.
From today, your Thamma is free.
[evil laughter]
And from now on,
whatever I say becomes law.
We'll drink human blood,
spawn new Betaals,
build our army.
And she will be freed too.
Are you ready?
As you wish.
Meanwhile, will you do the honours
of chanting the mantras?
Can't you see I wanna break free?
Hurry up!
Thamma! Thamma! Thamma! Thamma!
Hundred years of toil and pain,
Hundred years bound in fire's chain,
Liberate the body's frame,
Liberate the soul the same.
[metal clanking]
[Sighs]
Tadaka...
Thank you.
The first time you ran away
with that boy, I knew
"This is the girl
who'll free me
and trap herself in love...
and shackles too."
[evil laughter]
You could still be free.
But I'm sorry, he's not agreeing.
So now, thanks again,
from the bottom of my heart.
Bye-bye...
for a hundred years.
Thamma! Thamma!
Take her away.
Excuse me, mister.
Alok?
Hi.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to taste a Barasingha
(Reindeer).
What?
It's your favourite, right?
Alok!
I'm here for you, obviously.
You're getting locked up for 100 years
and didn't even care inform me.
That's not fair.
Alok, forget all this and just run.
I have to take this punishment.
I broke the rule.
To hell with rules.
Yaku sir... I mean, Yakshasan sir.
Sir, I'm not here to fight,
I'm here to talk.
Let's negotiate, okay?
Hundred years is too much.
Keep her in for a week or two,
then set her free.
Okay, fine, let's meet halfway.
How about one month? Done?
Two months, final.
Attack!
[Grunts]
[growling]
[Screaming]
[Grunts]
You lost to a rookie Betaal who knows
no better than a newly-wed groom?
Pathetic!
Shame on you!
You've embarrassed me!
[Winces in pain]
Come to me...
Come.
[slurping]
[metal clanking]
Alok...
You can't...
You can't break them.
Alok... nobody can break them.
You should leave.
I won't!
I'm not going anywhere.
If I was meant to go,
I would have at the accident.
But your love saved me.
And now, nothing
in the world can keep us apart.
We can't fight this, Alok.
You should go.
Yakshasan is very powerful.
He can kill you too.
Take my advice... just go.
You should--
What worries do we have anymore?
We're ready to go through it all together
Forget about a 100 years
Can't fathom going a moment without you
Even this means
that we perish in this flame
Whether or not I am there with you.
So, you think,
you'll be able to live without me...
for hundred years?
Hundred years?!
It's hard to survive even
a second without you!
Yakshasan, you bloody...
What happened?
Why did you guys stop?
Continue.
Come on, I haven't seen any romance
in the past 75 years!
Keep going... continue.
Come down here...
I'll show you some real action too.
Action in romance... I love it!
[intense music]
[Grunts]
[growling]
[Mystical song]
Hey...
You're not fit to be a Betaal.
[growling]
That lover of yours...
[Winces in pain]
Hundred years of toil and pain,
Hundred years bound in fire's chain,
Liberate the body's frame,
Liberate the soul the same.
[shackles unlocking]
[Gasping]
Remember...
I am your Thamma!
Your romeo seems to have gone pale.
[Grunts]
[growling]
[dramatic music]
Thamma! Thamma!
[Winces in pain]
[Gasping]
Let this be a warning
to every single one of you.
Defy your Thamma and your fate
will be the same as his.
You actually believed you
could stand against Yakshasan, huh?
[evil laughter]
[sad music]
Alok...
Alok! Alok!
No... no... no... no way!
Alok!
Alok! Alok!
ALOK!!!
[Screaming]
[Mystical song]
[Winces in pain]
[growling]
Alok, stop!
You're not like him.
There's still love in your heart.
There's still light in your soul.
You're different.
Don't do it.
Please, for me?
Hundred years bound in fire's chain,
Bound the body's frame,
Bound the soul the same.
Take him away
and lock him up in the cursed mountain.
[metal clanking]
[Grunts]
[thumping heartbeat]
[Gasping]
The reign of Yakshasan's terror is over.
After years, Goddess has broken her curse
and sent us a new Thamma -
The one who'll set a new balance
between humans and Betaals.
From now on, nobody bows to anyone.
For the first time ever,
there's a Betaal with a heartbeat.
This miracle didn't just happen.
There has to be a reason,
a purpose behind it.
Starting today, we begin a new era.
Are you ready?
Thamma! Thamma! Thamma!
Thamma! Thamma! Thamma! Thamma!
Thamma! Thamma!
[suspense music]
[growling]
[dramatic music]
This is catastrophic!
Someone helped Yakshasan escape!
Yakshasan is like the Rakhtbeej
of the modern world.
He'll feast on human blood,
summon dark powers,
and build his own army.
If that happens, the world is finished.
No...
Yakshasan may build his army,
but we will rise up to the challenge
and put an end to it!
No, it's not that simple!
Once he drinks human blood,
his power will be unstoppable.
The only way to defeat him is
to become stronger than him.
Stronger how?
By drinking the blood of Bhediya .
Where on earth do we even find a Bhediya ?
[suspense music]
[gentle music]
If I miss you, I won't care at all,
If you forget me,
I won't complain at all.
To please your heart,
in this world so wide,
There's nothing here you won't find.
Even if you can't be mine,
I'll still be fine.
Why, O' Lord?
Why did I fall in love?
For now I weep in blood,
Why, Dear Lord?
I'm not so broken, not so small,
That I can't rise again each time I fall.
You were my habit, not my fate,
Not something that cannot be changed.
Not something that time can't heal,
Trust me, this wound is not that deep.
My heart is broken, but not so much,
That it cannot mend again as such.
Even if you can't be mine,
I'll still be fine.
Why, O' Lord?
Why did I fall in love?
For now I weep in blood,
Why, Dear Lord?
Even if you can't be mine,
I'll still be fine.
What more could I want than you
remembering me your whole life through,
Whether or not I am there with you.
Even without being beside you,
Each day, each moment,
I'll still be with you,
Whether or not I am there with you.
I am not away from you,
I'm right there where you are too.
I'll always flourish in you,
Whether or not I am there with you.
Love that no one can understand but you,
Something that's only felt by you.
Something that cannot
be measured or subdued,
Something that even time
can't hold from you.
Love that no one can understand but you,
Something that's only felt by you.
Something that cannot
be measured or subdued,
Something that even time
can't hold from you.