Previously on
Seducing Drake Palma.
Lord, please let me
meet some friends.
Even just one!
Do you have a partner yet?
- How about us instead?
- Huh?
I have a boyfriend!
Wait, Drake!
Ahhh!
No, I meant for the
Freshman Walk.
Do you have a partner yet?
Do you want to pair up?
Ouch, Drake!
Who’s that?
That’s Shaira.
So, how’s my husband?
You know, you look different.
More matured, more...
mysterious?
Tss.
Don’t worry.
I got you.
Tripp?
This is safe.
You’re really sure?
What the heck?!
Are you ready?
Let’s go!
Don’t speed up!
Tripp, that’s enough!
Right?
Alys!
You’re too cute!
Stop it!
- Wait, you’re really cute!
- Alys!
Why are you laughing
at my husband?
“Husband?”
Yeah.
My husband.
Why are you with him?
You’re married?
Well, actually –
Shut up.
Wait, who are you?
I’m Shaira.
Drake’s wife.
Drake!
What?
She’s the wife?
Then I’m just a girlfriend?
Something doesn’t add up here!
Why am I even explaining myself?
Go home and rest.
But I can’t sleep!
Why would it be Drake’s
problem, who is my boyfriend,
if she can’t sleep?
What is with this girl?
Come on, Drake.
Drake –
Ahh!
Oh my ankle,
it hurts so bad, Drake!
And here’s my boyfriend,
helping the “wife”.
What is happening?
We just ended up in different
schools, and this is what happens?
Drake, can you accompany me?
My ankle is killing me!
What is happening?
There’s definitely a
conspiracy going on!
Ugh! Annoying!
Is he cheating on me?
And in the unit next door, seriously?
I know that Drake can be
dense and blunt, but...
I never thought
he’d be a two-timer.
Great, Alys.
I know your brain is weak,
but in a situation like this,
at least think about your pride.
You can save some of it sometimes.
Drake said he’d take me home
because my place is
far from his condo.
Well, it didn’t happen.
He seems busy with his “wife”.
What will happen to me
as his girlfriend?
Why did the picky girl
end up here?
Here he goes again.
You want some? Mmm.
Yuck, gross!
You just sipped from that and
now you’re handing it to me?
I was right to call
you “the picky girl”.
Why are you even here?
Because...
Because?
Because I had a
fight with my boyfriend.
He keeps prioritizing
that girl over me—
his actual girlfriend!
That’s what’s difficult
with you women.
You jump to conclusions.
You don’t want to
look for reasons.
Alys, don’t let your eyes wander.
Concentrate on the face.
So, why did he leave you?
Because the girl
twisted her ankle.
That’s what I’m saying.
Okay, let’s say it’s me,
and your boyfriend is here,
and I’m dying, and
he’s not even scratched—
who are you going to?
That’s a wild example!
Of course I’d pick you!
See? That’s all it is!
Even so, I’m
still his girlfriend.
You’re impossible to talk to.
You only think like that because
you don’t have a girlfriend.
Oh, wow.
I don’t have one now,
but who knows?
I might have soon.
Why? Are you courting someone?
Courting? That’s so outdated!
Playboy!
Playboy? I don’t
even have a girlfriend.
I’ve never even had a girlfriend.
That’s a wild accusation.
Tss.
Why am I even bothering
to talk to this Tripp guy?
I might get influenced
by his bullying.
Alys, where are you going?
I’m going home.
What? It’s already 10 PM.
That’s dangerous!
It’s fine, I’ll just hail a cab.
Alys, I’m not letting you go
home alone this late, okay?
- Can you slow down a bit?
- What?!
I said slow down!
What?
That one again?
Chill, I’ll slow down.
I’ll just change.
Oh my God.
Tripp Marco!
Hang on, Miss Perez!
Let me off here,
right now!
Let me off right here!
Okay, sure, if you say so.
I’m easy to talk to.
Ouch!
It’s like I’m always about
to die when I’m with you!
Do you think you’re in a race
when you’re driving?
And you’re hitting me
like you’re my girlfriend—
If I were your girlfriend,
you’d be in bigger trouble!
I seriously thought I
was going to die earlier!
Ouch.
Bye!
Drake?
What are you doing here?
Did I tell you to leave?
Hmm?
If I didn’t tell you to
leave, then don’t leave!
Because you’re with your “wife!”
Are you jealous?
Why would I be jealous?
I’m way too cute to get jealous
over that squid-looking girl.
Why are you laughing?
What’s funny?
You. You’re funny.
What’s going on?
And in the unit next door, seriously?
Is he cheating on me?
Go home. I’m not feeling well.
We’ll just end up fighting.
Seriously, let me go!
If you don’t have
anything sensible to say,
just go home and let go of me!
I hate explaining things.
How am I supposed to
understand if you don’t explain?
She’s nothing to me, okay?
You’re my girlfriend.
Why do I feel like this?
I don’t feel like I’m
his girlfriend, not once.
We don’t even hold hands.
It’s like Alys and
Drake—just two people.
There’s no “us”.
Are you still mad?
Go home.
You’re mad.
Well, you know that I’m mad!
Why are you even asking?!
I’m asking because I’m
trying to understand you.
Can’t you give me some credits for trying?
Drake, we’ve been dating for months now!
What?
You know what’s funny?
It feels like we’re nothing.
This is like a joke.
Do you get it?
Why are you mad?
Okay, let’s go through it one by one.
Wait, no—it’s really
just one reason.
Because I feel you don’t
take me seriously.
What made you think
that I’m not serious?
Hello? Why am I only finding
out now that you have a wife?
Do you honestly
think that I’ll date you
if I’m already married?
Are you that dumb?
Fine, I’m dumb!
Is it my fault I’m dumb
when it comes to you?!
Sorry, I just like
you this much!
You’re such a noob, noob.
Then explain to this noob—
who was that girl earlier?
Her name is Shaira
and don’t mind her.
Then why did you help her?
Why are you like that?
I was trying to be a gentleman.
You’re not even a gentleman.
Precisely why I was trying.
Before, I thought
all girls were dumb.
But then I met you.
And I realized
that I was wrong.
I’ll only say this once.
I’m falling.
I’m almost there.
Look who’s here?
Ugh!
I forgot that this squid-like girl lives in
the same condo as Drake!
What now?
What are you? Drake’s groupie?
No, I am not Drake’s groupie.
I’m his girlfriend.
Is there something
funny about what I said?
Is it funny that I’m
Drake’s girlfriend?
What’s wrong with this squid?
Oh my gosh, she’s
delusional—“girlfriend,” seriously?!
I’m going to cry.
Pardon my reaction—it’s
just that you’re actually really funny.
Who are you again?
Alys Perez.
It was nice meeting you, Alys,
but I don’t really shake
random stranger’s hands.
Don’t take it personal, though.
It’s not even been a
week since I met this girl,
and she’s already jumped
to the top of my hate list.
What are you doing here, anyway?
Oh, Drake and I have a date.
“Date”?
Stop daydreaming... again.
Dates aren’t Drake’s thing.
Well now, it’s his thing.
Hi, Drake, good morning!
Hi, Drakey baby!
Why are you here?
We have a date, remember?
I messaged you on soc-med.
Ah.
Let’s go?
Give me a minute.
I told you so.
Dates are our thing.
Ha-ha-ha.
Whatever!
Gosh, Drake’s books are
making me dizzy.
but they’re kind of
the same as Tripp’s.
Why am I even thinking
about Tripp Marco?
He’s so annoying,
always asking me to
treat him at the café.
Do I look like his wallet?
Should I answer this?
What is it?
Good morning to you too, Alys!
What do you want now?
I need a date tomorrow.
I’m busy. Bye!
Wow, after I dropped you
off last night, this is what I get?
You’re unfair,
that’s blackmail.
Come on, go with me tomorrow,
I just need someone with me!
Where is that anyway?
There’s an art exhibit
in QC tomorrow.
Come with me.
Don’t you have other friends?
None. Just you.
Why was I born
with a kind heart?
Fine!
You’ll go with me?
Pick me up tomorrow.
All expenses paid, okay?
Bye!
I’m turning off my phone
so Drake and I won’t be disturbed.
It’s our day.
Just Drake and Alys and love!
My boyfriend’s so handsome.
Good thing I’m cute!
Tss.
What did I do this time?
You’re staring.
It’s creeping me out.
It’s because you’re handsome.
You’re only dating me because
of my face. Wicked Alys.
Well, that’s just a bonus.
I like you because...
I like you.
Need I say more?
Let’s go.
Okay.
Wait.
I thought we’re leaving.
What’s that?
Hold my hand.
Huh?
You said I lack affection, right?
Hold my hand.
Let’s go.
Lord, what did I do to
feel this much giddiness?
Way to go, Alys!
Next time,
intertwined fingers is my goal.
Oh my gosh, he chose me over
that squid-like girl.
This is remarkable!
I feel giddy.
Hi, Drake!
Mind if I join you?
You won’t mind, right?
I’m just so, so, so, bored!
Silence means yes, right?
I’m so excited! Let’s go!
So, where are we going?
To hell, you want to join?
Excuse me, did you say
anything of importance?
Didn’t think so.
I’m so excited for today, we’re
gonna have so, so much fun!
Oh my.
What are you looking at?
Hey!
Wait!
Of course, I won’t let my
dignity be stepped on.
So, I got in the shotgun
seat right away.
This is the girlfriend’s seat.
She can’t take it from me.
Shaira.
Yes, hubby?
Can you please
check if the tire is flat?
Of course, anything for you.
Why did Drake ask her to check?
Couldn’t it have been me?
I know how to check a
flat tire too, you know.
Wait!
What about Shaira?
Drake!
Wait!
What the heck?!
Ugh!
Why did you leave Shaira?
She’s annoying.
What if she gets mad?
I don’t care. I can
handle her being mad at me.
I can’t handle you
not talking to me.
You’re ugly!
Weirdo!
You’re annoying, you’re ugly.
You’re making me feel giddy.
It's my job after all.
Drake, are we eating here?
Hey, where are we going?
Where are we eating?
I’m so hungry.
I’m tired.
Don’t use that face on me.
I won’t give you a
ride inside this mall.
What face?
That face –
puppy eyes, pouty lips –
it’s adorable, but stop it.
I won’t give you a piggy back ride.
Tss.
Fine!
[in Japanese] Welcome!
There you go, a great
place for us to eat.
After all that walking,
only ramen will satisfy you.
It’s delicious.
You really love ramen, don’t you?
Oh right, I was gonna
ask for his number.
How do I even do this?
It’s embarrassing,
I’m the girl, and I’m the
one asking for his number.
Um, Drake...
Mmm?
Can I ask for...?
Your Pork Tonkatsu Ramen.
Prawn Tempura Rice Bowl.
Enjoy your food!
Ramen is really Drake’s favorite.
Ramen is all it takes for him
to give in.
I’ll ask Aunt Liana to teach me
when she gets back from abroad.
For all I know,
his “almost there” could
suddenly become “already there”.
Come on, let’s go this way!
Let’s go here instead!
Imagine you’re punching
that squid-like girl.
Who?
Secret.
You’re really a noob.
Why can’t I shoot?
You’re cheating!
It’s too far!
Stop!
3...2...1!
Come on, jump!
Jump!
Wait, let’s jump together!
What the hell?
He kissed me?
Oh my gosh!
Miss?
Yes?
Did you take a video?
Uhm, which one – when
you fell, or when you kissed?
All of it.
Yes.
Can you AirShare it?
Sure!
Thank you!
Miss, can you delete it?
Okay.
Let me see.
Very good, thank you!
- Wow.
- Tea.
Thank you!
You’ve been all smiles
for a while now.
I’m on the way, where are you?
I won’t ride your motorcycle, FYI.
Wow, bestie,
you’re improving.
Your fingers are practically
worn out from texting.
Are you texting Drake?
I wish I was just
talking to Drake instead.
Okay, that’s your story to tell.
I can go until 3:00 PM.
I have practical test tomorrow,
I need to practice.
By the way, how’s SCA?
Hey.
I asked how’s SCA?
It’s okay.
“Okay”?
Bestie, I don’t want
to be there anymore.
Everyone’s so
smart, I can’t keep up!
Why, is it that hard?
I thought that clothing technology
would be easy, but…
Bestie,
it's just our first week and we’re
already submitting portfolios –
due next week!
You can do it, bestie!
Bestie, I really can’t – I
can’t do this anymore!
Didn’t you say you wanted to be
a fashion designer like my mom?
You got this, come on!
Who would’ve thought being
a designer was this hard?
I thought it was just drawing
here, there, everywhere –
that easy.
Oh, Kent texted –
he and Sheen are waiting for me.
I’m going now.
Wait, let me just fix my things.
In all fairness, huh?
It’s only been a week since we started
college, and you’re becoming more girly.
It’s weird.
Is it because you’re in love?
Alys, you’re so annoying!
I’m going!
Wait.
I want to go with you.
Next time, okay?
Don’t you have plans?
Well, maybe I can say
I suddenly have to go
somewhere.
Up to you!
Are you coming or not?
You’re taking so long to decide.
Okay then, I’ll leave you here.
Bye, bestie. Love you!
Bye. Love you.
Hey, Princess!
Daddy!
How are you?
- Is that for me?
- Yeah, for you, of course!
Thank you, Dad!
What brings you here?
Oh, you and Aunt
Liana fought again, huh?
No, we didn’t fight.
Actually, I went home to ask you
how was your first week in school.
So, was it okay?
School was fine.
“Fine”?
I mean, nothing superb?
I don’t know, Daddy.
My friends aren’t there.
School feels kinds of lonely
without my friends around.
Make friends.
Believe me, you’ll be fine.
Okay?
Anyways,
another reason why
I’m home is because
I wanna ask about your debut.
What do you want?
OMG!
Alys?
Huh?
I said, what do you
want for your birthday?
Your Aunt Liana wants to know.
Daddy really loves Aunt Liana
even though they
don’t have kids.
I wish they did.
Talking to baby Dane
gets tiring sometimes.
Um, I don’t really know yet.
You don’t know?
Okay.
When you figure it out,
tell me, okay?
I’m sure your mom’s going to
plan something for your birthday.
And what I want to give you is something
you wouldn’t expect to receive.
Okay, Daddy.
Okay?
- Okay.
- Deal, huh?
Mhm.
Ma’am Alys, Tripp
is here to see you.
Who’s Tripp?
A friend of mine, Daddy.
A friend, you say.
Well,
I want to meet this “friend.”
Uncle Cyriel?
Oh, Tripp!
- Uncle.
- So it’s you!
- Hello.
- How are you?
I’m good. How are you?
Wait, do you know Alys?
Yes. How about you?
She’s my daughter.
Oh!
Small world, Uncle!
Small world!
So, why are you here?
Uhm...
Alys and I are going to
check out the art exhibit in QC.
Oh, okay.
So, you pursued Fine Arts?
Uh, no, Uncle.
No, Uncle.
I took Business Ad –
as my dad specifically ordered.
We’re going just to unwind.
Wow!
So he’s close with Dad?
Tripp is close to my Daddy Cyriel.
Drake is close to my Dad Andy.
Wow, what’s next –
Sheen is close with Mommy?
Alright then.
Sweetheart, sorry, I’ve got
another appointment, okay?
Okay, Daddy.
- Sorry.
- Thank you for coming.
Tell Dana and Andy
I’ll be back tomorrow.
Okay.
- Okay?
- Okay.
- Tripp...
- Uncle.
You take good care
of my daughter, alright?
- Of course, Uncle.
- Alright, bye.
Bye, sweetheart.
- Thank you, Daddy, bye. Love you.
- Bye.
Ouch!
That hurts!
You’re such an Amazon!
What Amazon are you
talking about?
You’re the one acting all close!
Why are you close with my Daddy?
Well, our dads are
business partners, okay?
Stop hitting!
You’re really like an Amazon!
Why did you just get here now?
I’ve been waiting for you.
You said you didn’t
like my motorbike,
so I went home first,
that’s why it took longer.
Did you wait?
And holy cayote!
Did he just try to charm me?
No, it’s fine.
Let’s go!
Let’s go.
Shall we?
After you.
Show off.
Drake’s car is still
my forever favorite.
Ready?
How was your first week?
Your cousin Tripp,
I thought...
you’d go to same school
and he’d be your classmate.
But he went to Brenford.
Are you two talking?
Why would I?
Are we close?
Come on, Drake,
Tripp is your cousin.
Why are you two
fighting? Fix that.
I’m not angry,
I just don’t care.
But, Drake, you’re cousins
– make peace already.
If you’re upset, fix it!
I’m not upset, what else
can’t you understand?
If you two don’t talk,
and we’re at a reunion,
and your mom finds out,
what will she think?
She’ll be sad.
I don’t care.
Oh, I know.
It’s about Shaira.
She wasn’t even your girlfriend.
She never said yes.
And you guys
were in sixth grade.
And now you have a girlfriend.
That was ages ago!
Tss.
Drake!
You left me yesterday!
Drake, why did you leave me?
I was with my girlfriend.
You got to be kidding me.
Drake, you know I’ve been waiting
for you for since like forever.
I didn’t even date anyone
because I only liked you.
And then now you’re going
to tell that you already have Alys?
Drake, that is so unfair!
What the heck?
Are you serious with her?
See?
You’re not even sure.
That means I still have a chance!
Now what?
You didn’t want to stay earlier.
Now, you don’t want to leave.
Shhh! Keep quiet!
It’s beautiful.
Isn’t it great?
Shhh!
It’s happening again.
But you know what,
you’re really good.
It’s my first time seeing a
gallery with that kind of concept.
- It’s beautiful, right?
- Your photos are amazing!
- Told you so!
- Legit. You weren’t lying.
No, not really.
It’s no big deal.
You’re being humble!
- Seriously.
- You know what?
Drake?
Oh my gosh, I just have so
much fun with you, Drake!
Here’s our ride.
Such a gentleman.
Oopsies!
Come on, jump!
Jump!
Wait, let’s jump together!
Wait.
I’ve never seen her this happy.
And this makes me happy, too.
I’m almost there, Alys.
Almost there.
On the next episode of
Seducing Drake Palma.
I shouldn’t even ask him, right?
Drama doesn’t suit you.
You’re an Amazon, remember?
One question, one answer.
What’s going on
with you and Tripp?
Go on in with your boyfriend.
He’s not my boyfriend.
You said I didn’t know
anything about love problems,
so I’m trying to make you laugh.
You’re cousins?!
Our fathers are brothers.
We’re both Palmas –
and both handsome.
You jerk!
After everything I cried to
him about, he’s your cousin?!
Just tell me already!
I knew it, nothing good
ever comes from that Shaira!
What makes you say that?
Don’t you know, she and
Drake are always together!