Come on. Shake your hands.
Shake your hands.
Come on, breathe.
A little ahead. Towards the edge.
-Okay.
Ma’am, you’ll have to wait that side.
-No, please wait.
Okay, okay. Sorry.
No, waiting on the bridge is too risky. She’ll have to go.
-Wait. Please wait.
You’ve put on the helmet. You are safe now.
I told her about us.
-Whom?
Kriti! I told Kriti.
I told her that things have been happening between us.
Why? Did I ask you to tell her or leave her?
I wanted to try to get serious about us.
But why are you talking in the past tense?
When am I going to try it now?
Come on, now. Let’s get ready.
The only thing left is the jump.
There's no need to be scared.
Step ahead. A little ahead.
Please don’t forget me.
That’s it? Only two boys fell for you?
Not enough to only like me.
They have to like my mother as well.
We're a package deal, you see.
Are you looking at your reflection in the spoon?
Did she feel giddy again today? Hello?
Did she feel…
Okay, okay. Good.
Yes, the tremors are common.
Just put on the television for her.
She won't really watch but at least she won't bother you.
Hello? Hello?
You do enough for your mother.
What is enough?
There's no such thing as ‘enough’.
It's okay to choose yourself once in a while.
You need not feel like such a criminal about it.
Will you please stop constantly staring
at your reflection? What a bore.
I'm not sure if Vismay heard me clearly.
He's sweet. The poor thing.
Not as much of a poor thing as you think.
Why is that funny?
It’s not going to be just one.
I'm planning to start a whole chain.
So, you are going to start a whole chain of gyms.
-No. It’s a body sculpting studio.
That's the same as a gym!
-No!
The focus will be on fitness and the shape of the body.
That is the same as a gym.
-No.
Why don’t you tell me about your plan?
I just want to give away all my things and set off.
Where to?
-Anywhere.
Never stop at any one place. Just keep going.
All my bags are packed, I’m ready to go.
I’m standin’ here outside your door.
Cause I’m leavin’ on a jet plane,
Don’t know when I’ll be back again.
What happened?
Hey, what’s the matter?
Let me see.
What is it?
Don’t go.
Where am I going?
-I mean ever.
Don't ever go anywhere.
Just be with me. Always.
I’m serious.
Never leave me. Promise?
-Okay.
No. Say it. Say you promise.
I’m not going to…
-Say it.
Okay. Promise.
Still doing translations?
I've been doing a lot of subtitling work recently.
Films and other things.
So, are you in Tokyo on a holiday or…?
-No, on work.
The same thing?
Wow. The plan changed?
It just did.
So, what do you do now?
I do…things. I keep busy.
Excuse me ma’am, your table is ready.
Thank you.
Cheers.
-Cheers.
Ma’am.
-Thank you so much.
The people here seem peaceful.
-A little too peaceful.
You won’t even catch them chatting on the train.
-No, I mean they seem content.
Do they?
-Hmm.
Actually, if they had toilet seats like these everywhere,
anyone would seem content.
I sat on the commode in my hotel…
such a wonderfully warm seat.
And so many options for washing your bum!
I’ve never been more grateful.
How are you still single?
Who said I am?
-You’re not?
I am.
And you?
Enough. I’m done.
-Have more, come on.
It’s sake. You won’t feel cold.
Come on. Down it.
Cheers.
-Cheers.
By the way, what’s with the policy
of not talking about your work?
What?
There’s no policy.
I don’t want to tell you.
Why?
Because you always judge.
Wait, hold on. ‘Always’?
When was the last time we met?
Yes, okay, sorry. You used to.
But a person’s true nature never changes, right?
What?
-Your mind is made up. Leave it.
Oh no. Okay, fine. I’ll tell you.
-No, no, no…I don’t even want to know.
Why wouldn’t I want to share it with you?
-Who knows?
Come on.
-No, no, no, no. I don’t want to know anymore.
Now, I want to tell you. Listen to me!
-No, no, no!
Hello? I’m glad you called.
I’m sorry. I got carried away…
Right now?
Sure, okay.
I’ll be right there.
Hello!
Where are you?
Who is it? Who is he talking to?
We’re not missing you! He’s lying!
Are you at home? Are you at home?
Yes.
Hold, hold, hold.
What did you want?
I want you…here…now.
Right now. Right here.
When my uncle died, my cousin
stopped being able to listen to music.
Hmm. The universe always maintains its balance.
Yes, when something is destroyed, something else is created.
My uncle died in the Kedarnath floods.
We didn’t even get to see him.
At least you got to say a final goodbye.
At least you were prepared.
Lavender perfume reduces stress. Especially when you’re sad.
Especially when you’ve experienced loss.
Balance. It’s about balance in the universe.
-When one leaves, another arrives.
What’s wrong?
We’re sorry if one of us said the wrong thing.
Listen…just come out. Let’s talk.
You should be with people right now.
Why have you locked yourself in there alone?
At least say something. I’m getting worried.
I’m pregnant.
I said I’m pregnant.
Aren’t you going to say anything?
Yes, of course I do.
Wait.
This way, Ma’am.
Please.
-Thanks.
Thank you.
-Thank you.
Ma’am, sake.
Cheers
Yes, Sir?
Are we going to talk?
Wait, let me order first.
Yes, sir?
Salmon?
And…Tuna Sashimi
-Thank you, Sir.
Can you take off your sunglasses at least?
-Why?
Kartu, why aren’t you saying anything?
I’m watching.
Why don’t you show him our home?
What’s there to show?
Don’t you understand?
I’m asking you to show him the house.
You can start.
Tell him your friends’ names.
Tomoki, Ayano, Riko, Kiho.
And what’s her name? Your girlfriend?
Masako.
Aren’t you going to eat?
-No, I’m a pescatarian.
What’s that?
-I only eat fish.
It’s just a phase.
Are you an old friend of Ma’s?
-Yes, I am.
From school?
-No.
So, not that old.
I should get going. I have got a meeting.
-Oh...
Don’t you want to see the house?
Sure.
-Let’s go then.
His name is ‘Table’. This is where I study.
His name is ‘Bed’. This is where I sleep and read.
His name is ‘Rug’. This is where I draw and read.
His name is ‘Cat’.
Her name is ‘Window’.
Nice. You have a lovely room.
Wow.
Isn’t this Mount Fuji?
Yes. Fuji is my friend.
This mountain?
-Yes. Fuji and I are very close.
Did you make this drawing?
-Yes. It took me three whole days.
Kartu, you liar! It was already on
the wall when we moved in here.
Your friend is wonderful, Kartu.
Hold on. Only my Ma and my Pa are allowed to call me ‘Kartu’.
And Nori-ba chan. And Haru-ji chan.
And my friend Tomoki. And my friend Fuji-san, of course.
I’m sorry, Kartikeya. I’ll keep in mind.
-It’s okay.
Are these your friends too?
-No! That’s my Ma and Pa.
They are very old friends. From school.
His name is Vismay.
It’s not all that shocking.
We grew up next door to each other.
No one knows me like he does.
So, you married him. Wow.
I was completely alone after you cut me off.
I had no one else in Pune. I was alone.
So, I made the decision to shift here with him.
What?
-Nothing.
Say it.
-It’s nothing.
I’m happy to see that you got everything you ever wanted.
I got none of what I wanted.
Here, take this.
Aren’t you coming home?
-No.
Why not?
-You’ve given me enough to digest.
That’s not fair.
-Sure, that’s not fair.
Congratulations. Whatever. Bye.
Her cupboard is emptied.
We don’t have to do this all today.
We can do it later.
No. Today is fine.
You have been looking after your mother for all these years.
Do you even know any other kind of life?
Weren’t you a mother to her?
I can imagine myself as a mother.
Are you immediately going to take on a new responsibility?
But then I’m being selfish, right?
-Yes. And why not? Please be selfish.
So, we’re both saying we don’t want this right now?
I’m saying…
we’ll do whatever you want.
She cannot always be the one to make the difficult decision.
-I’m trying to be sensitive.
Okay.
Hello. How are you?
-Good.
Are you sure you want to go ahead with it?
-Yes.
Okay, then. Lie down. I’ll explain the procedure to you.
-Okay.
We will first put your legs in the stirrups,
then anaesthetize your cervix.
It is called a para-cervical block.
After that, we will use a rod –
Here?
-Yes, please. Lie down.
A rod will be inserted and then we
will clear everything using a suction tube.
It’s a short ten minute procedure.
Let me know if you feel uneasy. And don’t be afraid.
Is the block done?
-Yes, ma’am.
Okay. Get the instruments ready.
Drum. And the cap and mask.
-Yes, ma’am.
Okay, let’s start.
I can’t imagine what is going to happen.
She is allowed to be confused.
She should tell him.
He is his son. He has the right to know.
I’m confused.
Are you really?
Or are you going to ask for advice
and then as always do exactly as you wish?
Is that what I do?
You said you didn’t know where to go.
I said let’s shift to Japan.
You asked if we should get married.
I said okay, but I wanted to work on our relationship.
Then you said we should get married but
let’s not get involved and keep each other trapped.
Yes, but I –
-When I asked you why get married at all.
You said, “For Kartu’s sake.”
If you didn’t want this, you shouldn’t have agreed.
I was alone. I was afraid.
So, in the moment, I did what I thought was right for Kartikeya.
I had made it absolutely clear to you that
I felt nothing for you but friendship.
Did you or did you not make me agree to what you wanted?
-Stop!
The last thing we need is the two of you fighting.
-Yes, please.
I’m sorry.
-I’m sorry, too.
If he hadn’t come here out of the blue,
everything would have been fine.
But he has come.
What are you going to do now?
My arm is asleep.
Rub your nails together.
I thought this was supposed to help with falling hair.
Oh, yes. That’s right.
I’m off.
Let me know if you need anything.
You’ll stay, won’t you?
-Of course.
Dinner?
I’m not hungry.
-Me neither.
If we make it through this, we can face anything.
We’re not through this yet.
I’m saying that whatever is happening to us,
is a meaningful experience.
And?
What about it?
Why do you immediately have to attack me?
Try to understand my point.
You’re right. It’s a meaningful experience.
What do we do about it?
What can we do?
Let’s get married.
Done.
Sure?
-Of course. I’m not going anywhere.
Let’s do a registered one.
-Perfect. As it is I hate my relatives.
Shall we do it tomorrow?
-I’ll ask Appo and Betty if they’ll be our witnesses.
You have to apply first.
Then they give you a date for the registration.
Whatever the process is, we’ll do it.
Great.
-Done.
Done.
Or should we live together first?
Even this is a good option. What do you think?
Come in.
It’s big.
Black money.
Will there be enough light on the ground floor?
It’s cloudy today. Look at how many windows there are.
Is this a common area?
-No, it’s yours. Private.
Do people throw down trash?
-Oh, no. These are cultured people.
The kitchen is quite cramped. Is there a gas pipeline?
Almost. The pipe’s been laid all the way till the square nearby.
So, there isn’t.
-No, not yet.
Bedroom.
It’s spacious.
-Yes.
Bed.
-No, no. Bed.
There’s a strange odour.
You can smell the sewage in the bedroom.
It is what it is. The house is good, the landlord is good.
Most importantly, he is open-minded.
What’s that supposed to mean?
It’s not supposed to mean anything.
It means he is tall and handsome and smart and generous.
What’s the deposit?
-Finalize it first. We can figure the rest later.
Give us a few minutes to discuss it. We’ll let you know.
-Sure.
Why’re you behaving so pleased in front of him?
Why will he ever reduce the rent?
Who cares?
-I do.
You like it, right?
I can imagine us drinking tea out there.
I can imagine us doing a lot more.
You have a condom?
-I don’t even have my wallet.
Do you want to get me pregnant again?
Sorry.
No, I’m sorry.
Sorry, sorry.
I’m sorry.
That was unfair.
It’s a lovely flat.
Yes, it does feel like home.
Let me, for a moment,
rise and kiss the sky.
Wrapped in the hush of your thought,
my body fills with colour.
There is fear.
And yet, something certain beneath it.
If we walk together,
where could we not reach,
what sky could hold us back?
Don’t go…
my love, don’t go.
Body to body,
we catch, we burn, we become smoke.
Shame loosens, slips away,
fades into air.
Your lips, a slow poison,
sweet, dissolving.
And in this city of hearts,
nothing but smoke, everywhere just smoke.
Body to body,
we catch, we burn, we become smoke.
Shame loosens, slips away,
fades into air.
Your lips, a slow poison,
sweet, dissolving.
Body to body,
we catch, we burn, we become smoke.
Don’t shut this door now,
Don’t look elsewhere,
Come back, here,
to where you belong, to me.
Don’t drift away again,
Refuse nothing,
Tell me what you want,
just all of it.
Let us hold each other, steady,
you in me and me in you.
Let us live this wanting,
restlessness,
again and again,
yet again.
We met and stayed,
pressed close, no holding back.
All the ifs and buts fell silent.
A new tremor ran through the body.
Everyone before you,
just noise, false, forgettable.
And you, as you are, even now –
The way you smiled,
the way you stood before me,
shame slipped away,
slipped away the pride.
Yesterday dissolved,
tomorrow dismissed,
There is only this,
this moment, this breath, now.
Don’t leave.
Don’t turn back.
And look into me,
deeper, deeper still.
Further in.
Further, until you fill me.
Within me.
Only within me.
No more going deeper now,
no more talk of love.
No knots, no fixing,
no ties, no holding.
Love. Just a beautiful intoxication.
Uncontained, unclaimed.
No cages, no shut doors.
No holding on. Let me breathe.
No footsteps to follow,
no tides to answer.
No debts, no promises.
No sentiment, no judgement.
No feeling to name,
No healing to chase,
no ceiling above.
I am open, I am free.
Completely, entirely free.
Body to body, we catch,
we burn, we become smoke.
Shame loosens, slips away,
fades into air.
Your lips, a slow poison,
sweet, dissolving.
And in this city of hearts,
nothing but smoke, everywhere just smoke.
Body to body,
we catch, we burn, we become smoke.
Shame loosens, slips away,
fades into air.
Your lips, a slow poison,
sweet, dissolving.
And in this city of hearts,
nothing but smoke, everywhere just smoke.
Were you at Poona Club the other day?
When?
Day before yesterday or maybe a day before that.
Maybe.
Anand told me.
He even said ‘hi’ to you but you were distracted.
It was probably Bridge night.
It’s a good thing you didn’t wait up.
Hello.
Farooq has responded.
I’ve forwarded it to you.
I’ll check.
Sorry, we had to cancel yesterday’s plan.
-What plan?
We were going to come over yesterday.
Oh, is it?
I told Mom…he’s an important guy. And was hyper excited
to meet yesterday. He really insisted and I couldn’t say no.
Water.
My new proposal’s been receiving a good response.
-Good.
I mean it’s the same plan.
Body building.
It’s not just body building. Body sclup -…
It’s going to be a body-sculpting studio.
-Body-sculpting studio.
It’s going to be grand.
There’s going to be a three-floored building with trainers and
dieticians and many other things. It’s not as simple as it seems.
And I don’t just want to do it in this city.
I want to start a whole chain.
How much money do you need?
I’ll manage.
Did you give the car for servicing?
The car?
No. It slipped my mind.
What do you do?
I’m a translator.
Meaning?
Meaning…I translate.
Marathi to English, Spanish to English, German to English, etcetera.
Why?
Good money?
-No, not really.
So then?
I mean not at the level at which I am currently working.
And I haven’t yet explored all my options.
Why not?
I’m not sure.
If you interrogate her, how do you expect her to open up?
There should be some comfort level first.
Let her get comfortable, she’ll answer you in five languages.
Excuse me.
Is he coming back?
-Not if you’re going to start crying again.
We’re never coming here again.
-Okay, let’s not.
I feel physical pain from being around that man.
I don’t know how Mom tolerates him. I’ve told her
so many times to leave him; that I’ll support her if she does.
I don’t want that man in my life.
-Why did you have to speak for me?
I was trying to defend you!
-I was doing just fine.
But it was for you!
See!
We’re fighting because of him!
You’re too good for me.
He could see it.
I think everyone can.
-Okay, enough. Let’s go home.
Let’s never look at his face again.
Okay. Never again.
Did you change the display again?
Yes, you asked me to.
No, I said keep all the Tsukudani at the
bottom and the boiled beans on top.
That was yesterday.
Not yesterday. I told you this morning.
What you just had was Shiro Miso. Okay?
The one before?
Komi…Kome Miso?
-Yes! He’s a professional.
You should try some eel.
Try the Yamato simmered eel with Tsukudani.
When do you leave?
In another two days.
Come back towards the end of
March to see the cherry blossoms.
And we have to go to Fuji.
-Of course.
I’m home.
Fuji-san is everywhere. On walls,
on T-shirts, on thousand yen bills.
You can see Fuji from anywhere.
Tokyo Tower, Shinkansen, even the plane!
But if you’re not lucky, you won’t see it at all.
It’s a moody mountain.
Just like that, it will decide not to open its heart to you.
And if you’re very very very lucky, on a clear day,
you can see it upside down, reflected perfectly in the lake below.
I am sorry, but I really don’t understand
what can happen by just looking at it?
A lot can happen.
As you share a silence with Fuji-san,
you may be able to hear yourself.
The mountain can help you see
something you’ve been blind to.
Ma?
-Hmm?
May I say something?
Hmm.
He is a good guy.
What was he like when you were friends?
He was…
the sweetest boy that I met.
Why didn’t you stay in touch?
Because we had a fight.
-Over what?
It was a grown up fight, Kartu.
You won’t understand yet.
-Okay.
Are you cold?
-Yes.
Come.
Ma?
-Hmm?
May I say something?
I think he likes me.
Obviously. Everybody likes you.
That’s what you think.
But some of my classmates don’t like me. Okay?
Okay.
Let’s tell him to come to Tokyo again.
Okay. Let’s.
For sure?
Hmm.
Not sleepy?
-No.
Shall we read something?
-No. You are tired.
Let us.
So…
for four thousand years, the volcano had remained quiet.
But recently,
something inside it began to stir.
Spic and span.
Clean, clean, clean.
Sparkling clean.
Nice.
Not bad.
-I know, I know, I know.
You are drenched.
My bike broke down and it was pouring.
Weren’t you supposed to go to the office only once a week?
-Yes.
So then, how come today?
It’s a complicated copy. It’s some report for
the comparative study of three pesticides.
What’s for dinner?
Pasta!
Nice.
Shall I help?
-No.
What should I chop?
Why do you have so much energy at this time of the day?
-“I have the power!”
I need money.
A lot of it.
I have to return all the money
I borrowed through my mum’s treatment.
I have to return money to relatives.
I have to repay the loan.
Okay.
-It’s a lot.
Okay, okay. Calm down.
I can understand the stress. But…
There’s no need to panic. We’ll manage somehow.
This is the last thought on my mind when
I go to sleep and the first when I wake up.
We’ll figure it out.
-How?
There’s always a way.
Money isn’t worth thinking about so much.
Let’s ask dad?
Whom?
It’s a negligible amount for your dad.
And we’ll return every penny. We will…
What?
You know how much I despise that man.
You have a right to that money.
Why should we have to beg for it elsewhere?
Why can’t we find a way on our own?
How are we going to do that?
Please tell me. I’m all ears.
What do we do?
-How can I come up with an instant solution just like that?
But there is always a way.
Like there was with your funding?
I pay the rent. I pay all the bills.
I pay the maid. I cover most of the household expenses.
I am translating anything that comes my way.
I have no relief.
I’m sick of negotiating, of begging people to pay me
40 paise per word instead of 25; if not 40, 35 at least.
How do you manage your expenses?
The eating and drinking out? Petrol?
Mom sends some money each month. Very little.
You won’t even have to meet him.
Please, please, please…please!
I promise I’ll repay him as soon as possible. I swear.
-No.
Okay.
We’ll figure it out.
Are you ready?
Take the card on top.
Look closely. Memorize it.
-Done.
Now fold it. Give that to me.
Hey, hold on to this.
Give the card back.
-Oh, I have to give it back?
Obviously. I’m not looking at it.
Come here. Are you eating something?
-Not at the moment, no.
Open your mouth?
Now I am going to reveal to you what the card was.
-Yes.
It was not a card with a digit.
-That’s right.
And it was a red coloured card.
It was a card of hearts.
And it was a king!
-Where’s the proof?
It’s right here.
Open your mouth, please.
Open?
The pizza is here.
-Guys, listen! I am not done with the tricks yet.
No, please! Siddhu, listen…
You okay?
What’s going on?
Mount Everest.
-Village.
Bonfire?
-Tree?
Tribals.
Warli painting.
A triangle?
-Evolution!
Five, four, three, two, one! Time up!
Your time’s up! You lose! It’s over. It’s done.
What was the word?
It’s Africa!
How is this Africa?
You’ve drawn everything except Africa.
These are the pyramids right here.
These are people dancing.
Sit down. You need a break.
You need to rest for ten minutes.
Why didn’t you just draw the map of Africa.
It’s basic. Everyone knows that much.
That’s so basic. Isn’t it so basic?
What does your T-shirt say?
Paraguay.
-Paraguay.
Betty, put on the world map, will you?
Enough now, you guys lost.
-Here is the world map.
Where is it then? Paraguay?
Look for it.
Why don’t you show us?
-These two are playing their own game.
Come on, tell us. Where is Paraguay?
Exactly where it was yesterday.
No, no. This isn’t time for your comedy. Show us.
Let it be. Who gives a shit about Paraguay?
Come on. It’s so basic.
Why don’t you Google it?
Do you want to? Paraguay?
Okay, okay. Okay.
Tell me, is it a country or a city?
A country…?
-Yes, ‘a country’ question mark? Or ‘a country’ full stop?
Come on!
Okay, guys enough. Enough, enough.
It’s the capital of Argentina. Got it? That’s it. Done.
I had forgotten.
-It’s okay!
It can happen.
-Of course, it can happen.
It’s not! It’s not the capital of Argentina!
Just say you don’t know. What’s the problem?
If you don’t know, you don’t know. So, what?
Okay, okay. Last question guys.
What language do they speak in Paraguay?
Go for it.
Mexican? Italian? Adriatic? Or Spanish?
Or none of the above.
Go for Phone-A-Friend. Call your dad.
Sorry.
Okay, okay, silence.
So which language do they speak in over there?
What was the third option?
-What was it indeed?
I think it was ‘Adriatic’.
-Adriatic.
Adriatic is a sea.
Bye.
-Bye.
Take care.
-Bye, Betty!
Hey, bye.
-Bye.
Take care.
-Yes.
See you.
Let’s go, guys.
- Let’s go.
The keys?
See you on the new year’s eve. Bye.
Do you have them?
Let’s go.
Come on.
What happened?
Was there news about the funding?
Okay, come on. Get in the car.
We’ll go home and talk. Let’s go.
How can you treat me like this?
Such hatred?
This much?
So, the entire car is made here?
Most of its interior parts are.
Different auto components are made here in the press shop.
We weld them together and send them to the company.
The final assembly happens in the respective companies.
It’s Sunday today.
-So?
I thought you called because it was a holiday.
Can’t I wish to meet you on a working day?
How is work?
-Great.
Good. So where are you opening the first studio?
-Good morning, Sir!
Thank you for not calling it a gym.
Where do I come for the opening then? When is it?
-Calm down. I’m not there yet.
You must have ordered the equipment by now, right?
Have you secured the space?
I have a couple of options in mind.
But I haven’t confirmed anything in person yet.
As long as the money is sorted,
everything else falls into place.
It is as good as done.
Where is the finance coming from finally?
There are a couple of people. It’s all happening.
Let’s see. It’ll happen. Consider it done!
What if it doesn’t work?
-What?
What if the plan doesn’t work out?
I don’t have the option to fail.
Why not?
-I just don’t.
Everyone has the option to fail.
If you realize that things are not working out despite
trying your level best, it’s okay to give up, you know.
That’s not a possibility for me.
Have you called me here to convince me to give up?
-What’s wrong with giving up?
Why must every single person have a success story of some kind?
-They must.
Why?
-Because they must.
But why?
I don’t have an explanation.
No, that’s not okay. If you think everyone must have
a success story, you have to be able to say why.
Anything can be made to seem sensible
if you say it at gunpoint like this.
So, what I am saying does seem sensible to you?
Leave me alone.
What is the problem?
Your father is a diamond merchant.
At least four more generations in your family need not work at all.
Why bother then?
Do you only work to be able to make money?
Absolutely not. But I know why I work.
I’m asking you why you do.
I want to prove a point.
To whom?
No one.
Thank you very much.
How’s work?
Could you please take the Octopus?
I won’t be able to eat it.
Give it to me.
Work?
-All good.
It was tough initially but this year our company
has released two new games into the international market.
How come you turned to video games?
Once I stopped trying to prove
a point to anybody else, it found me.
And how was the meeting you came here for?
Not bad.
They’ve agreed to let us use
the new software they’ve developed.
Congratulations.
Could you please also take the Shrimp?
Sure.
I don’t want to come in between the two of you.
What should I do?
It hasn’t been easy for her.
She has taken a lot of
time and effort to build her world.
Now, Haru-san, Nori-san, Kartu and
I together make her whole.
So, you’re not going to be able to pick and choose.
‘I’ll take the Tuna but not the Octopus.’
‘The Salmon is okay but not the Shrimp.’
Not possible. Okay?
I’m taking all the papers.
You know our bank manager?
Banerjee?
-Banerjee, yes.
He said that the meeting is just a formality.
The loan should come through.
Consider it done.
Let’s buy a new laptop tomorrow.
A brand new one.
Hey…Hey!
Shall we celebrate today?
Fuji-san. Noon.
Yes.
Yes, Vismay?
We have to take care of this plaster for six weeks.
Make sure it doesn’t get wet.
His arm is fractured. But the doctor has said there’s
nothing to worry about. It should be better soon.
The bank manager was being uncooperative.
So, he lost his temper and
smashed his glass table with his own hand.
Please don’t say anything to him right now.
We’ll talk to him later.
What sense does it make, if in a fit of rage,
you end up causing harm to yourself?
Kartu?
Hey, champ.
If you had to leave so soon,
why did you even bother coming back?
Vismay…
-Not okay.
Once you let him into Kartu’s life, every decision
from that point on, will have to be Kartu’s own.
I’ve known Kartu since he was born.
I’ve brought him up along with you.
Whatever you decide,
I cannot walk away from Kartu’s life.
I mean, I refuse.
He is as much my son as he is the two of yours.
Hey, hi!
How cheap can you be!
You know how much it bothers me, don’t you?
You know how much I can’t stand it!
You know it! You know!
Hey, control yourself!
You! Don’t interfere! This has nothing to do with you!
Hey, you. Do not interfere.
Wasn’t I clear enough? What part did you not understand?
-Hey! Hey, stop!
I told you clearly! Don’t you understand?
Shut up! Let me go. Leave me be!
Don’t you get it? Don’t you get it?
Sorry.
-Sorry.
Is it such a problem for you to see my side of things?
And then you have the audacity to tell my Dad
to not tell me about the money you borrowed from him.
He didn’t listen to me, did he?
-Mom told me.
Did you try to see my side of things?
Did you even notice me working my ass off?
It’s so humiliating to constantly have to take on substandard work.
Do you even understand the concept of money?
People spend their whole lives trying to make money and still…
-Oh, shut your trap!
Enough.
Let’s put an end to this. It’s not working.
Okay. Let’s stop.
What do you do when you get angry?
I never get angry.
Shut up.
I don’t. Really.
Nothing makes you angry?
-Nope. Ask anyone.
Ever since I was a baby, I just don’t get angry.
-Liar!
Go ahead. Try to make me lose my temper.
To tell you the truth, whenever I get angry, I feel like crying.
Even I cry sometimes.
-Really?
To tell you the truth, I cry at the drop of a hat.
I cry a lot. Ma says crying is good.
Your Ma is right.
What was Ma like back when you were friends?
She was hardworking.
And very funny.
And she was a chatterbox.
When she doesn’t have answers, she uses her hands a lot.
-Does she? How?
Like this.
Like this?
-Yes.
Did she do that back then too?
Maybe. I didn’t notice.
How soon can I be discharged?
Well, for now just take it slow and get lots of rest.
My wife is alone at home, that’s why…
If you stay calm and get your rest properly,
we could let you go by tomorrow afternoon.
Please behave yourself!
Luckily it was not a fracture, it is a contusion.
Ah that’s a relief!
He is a mischievous boy, this one.
Now be a good boy!
Be a good boy!
Kartikeya?
What’s going on?
Are you trying to trick me?
Listen…
Is it okay if I don’t brush tonight?
Okay.
But you won’t tell her.
You don’t tell her either.
Hi.
Everything is fine.
I locked up at the shop and handed the key to Nori-san.
We had dinner on the way home. And Kartu is fast asleep.
Have you put your phone for charging?
-Yes.
I don’t know how I would have managed today if it weren’t for you.
It’s not such a big deal.
Give me a minute, please?
I’ve made milkshake.
-Milkshake?
Kartu makes for the best company.
We’ve been getting along well.
Really?
-Yes, really.
Are you going to tell him?
He needs to know.
I remember when Kartu and I
went for our first walk together.
That tiny little palm gripping mine.
My heart melted.
That’s when I thought for the first time,
I might be able to love unconditionally.
Kartu gave me this car because I’m in the hospital.
He said, “Haru-san, you shouldn’t feel alone.”
You can see he loves the boy already.
If it is so obvious, why can’t he see it?
May be he is scared.
Some people don’t see
things on their own.
They’ve to be shown.
Kartikeya…
It’s very late now.
I’m switching off the lights.
You need to sleep now. Okay?
Come here.
What is it?
Listen…
-Hmmm.
It would be okay if you called me Kartu now.
Five minutes. I Promise.
Okay.
-Okay.
Chef special Chicken Afghani and Baigun Bhaja
will be ready in an hour. Just one hour.
Have you diced the onion?
-Yes.
Where is it?
Inside.
Inside where?
On the kitchen counter.
-Where on the kitchen counter?
It’s right there. Just look.
-Okay!
I’ll just have a quick shower.
No, no. Just cancel it then.
Yes, cancel it and refund the money.
Yes, okay.
Who was that?
-Leave it.
Come on.
What did you want a refund for?
For the cake.
Our cake?
-Hmm.
Sorry?
-Yes.
Why?
-They didn’t have a baked one.
Come on.
I pre-ordered it day before yesterday.
Why do they accept orders if they can’t deliver?
Look here. Which one?
So, which one have you ordered now?
-No cake.
What do you mean no cake?
I mean I haven’t ordered any cake instead.
So, there’s no cake coming?
-No.
So, what are we going to cut then?
We can cut the chicken.
I hate those disgusting gelatin cakes.
You could have checked with me once.
-It’s fine. Just let it go.
I wouldn’t have minded a gelatin cake.
You don’t even eat cake. I don’t know why you’re whining.
-I wanted one today.
Today may not be important to you, but I’m excited about it.
Oh, please. What is this mood?
‘My cake’. ‘I like it’. ‘I don’t want it’.
So selfish.
You don’t give a rat’s ass about the other person.
-No, I don’t.
Exactly. You don’t. The other person doesn’t matter.
It doesn’t concern you. You don’t even notice.
You don’t want to listen to the other person at all.
Everything has to centre around I, me, myself.
Who cares about anyone else? They’re empty-headed.
They’re too dumb to care about.
And what about you?
“I’m such a victim”. “No one listens to me.”
“Nothing ever works out for me.” “My Dad is this; my Dad is that.”
“My Mom is this...”
But you still want to drive your Dad’s car!
What had I asked you to do with the onions?
What?
The onion.
When I said I’d cook chicken,
what had I asked you to do with the onions?
What did you ask for? You said dice them.
Did I ask you to slice it or chop it?
Oh, did you specify?
I had clearly asked you to slice the onions.
Okay, maybe you did.
-Not, not maybe. I had asked you to slice the onions.
Okay, fine.
Why didn’t you listen to me?
What have I done then?
-Look at what you have done.
You have chopped it. You have chopped it.
How does it matter? It was whole and now it isn’t.
Seriously?
You have no respect for me.
-What did you say?
If you want me to hear, you’re going to have to speak louder.
-You do not respect me!
Why? Because I didn’t cut the onion the way you wanted?
-Yes.
Okay. Next time, I’ll make sure it is chopped.
-Not chopped, sliced!
Okay, sliced.
Happy second anniversary.
Let’s not talk about onions anymore.
Systematic desensitization.
What?
This…this thing that you do to me.
It is systematic desensitization.
-Don’t throw nonsensical jargon from Instagram at me.
Ignore anything the other person ever says or asks for.
Until they start to believe they’re unworthy.
That they don’t deserve to be treated well.
If that’s the case, why don’t you leave me.
Get up, come on. Leave me and go.
We’re not bound to each other. Come on, get up. Leave.
Go, get going now.
Go!
As depressing as it is to be with you, it is more depressing to be alone.
Whose problem is that?
-It’s mine!
It is my problem. So then? Yes, it is my problem.
Why should I respect you?
‘Why’?
-Yes. Why?
What about you is worth taking seriously?
Is there nothing?
-What is?
Do you not get anything from me?
-What do I get?
How much more will you take?
How much more?
I feel empty.
I can only give if I’m left with anything.
Don’t be in a hurry.
Think about it carefully and seriously.
What do I get from you?
You’re constantly cursing your Dad.
He gave me money, at least.
He asked about my wellbeing.
When have you ever supported me with anything?
-Do the two of you talk behind my back?
He asked me if the pressure from the loan is any less.
Did it occur to you to ask?
Return the money you borrowed.
How does it concern you?
Where’s your phone?
What?
-Transfer the money to me right now.
What are you doing?
Return the money.
-My phone isn’t in there.
What did you do with the money?
What do you mean?
I returned it to the people I had borrowed money from.
All of it?
-Most of it.
And the rest?
-It’s in the bank.
Where is your phone?
Where is it? Where have you kept your phone?
-I won’t give it to you!
Return the money. Return it.
-I do plan to return it. But to your Dad.
What is my Dad to you even?
If we’re not going to be together,
what is my Dad to you?
Oh, I see. So now we’re not going to be together, are we?
-Just return the bloody money!
I won’t return it.
Not today, not tomorrow, not ever.
Let’s see what you do.
Give me your phone.
-Let me go.
Give me the phone.
-No, I won’t.
Give it to me.
-No!
Give me the phone. Give it.
Give the phone.
What is the password?
-Not going to tell you.
What’s the password? Tell me the password.
-No. Never.
Give me the password.
-I am not going to. Don’t you get it?
Tell me the password.
-No!
Tell me the password. Tell me the password now.
-Put down my laptop.
Tell me the password.
-Put down my laptop, please.
Password.
-Please put down the laptop.
Tell me the password.
-Put down my laptop first.
Tell me the password!
-Put down my laptop.
Password.
-Put the laptop down!
Give me the password. One last time.
-Put down my laptop!
Just give me the password.
I am asking you the last time.
-Put the laptop away first.
Password.
-Put the laptop down. Put it down please.
Put it…
You are a curse.
Nothing can remain alive near you.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Where are you going?
-Leave me, let me go.
I’m sorry. I’m sorry. I’m so sorry.
-Let me go. Let go!
I’m sorry.
-Leave me.
You promised you would never leave me.
Please!
He’s asleep.
I’m almost done.
-Okay.
If I came back in a year, would Kartu recognize me?
-Of course. Why wouldn’t he?
Actually, one year is a long time for a seven year old.
Why do you want to meet him again?
Why did you come looking for me the other day then?
I’m starving. Can we start?
Vismay is a good guy.
It’s not as easy as it looks.
What?
I want the best for you. Do you not find that believable?
I do.
I honestly do.
When did we stop listening to each other?
I don’t remember.
How is it going to help to remember?
Everyone and their mother-in-law did a
post mortem of our relationship after you left.
Oh, God!
People acquire exceptional clarity when
they are analysing other people’s relationships.
How can the very thing one fell in love with,
become so frustrating afterwards?
We lived under the same roof
but led two very different lives.
And they overlapped less and less.
Hi!
Please meet me once.
-No.
I won’t ever force you to again.
I promise.
-No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Please meet me. Just once. Please.
-No.
Please.
Fuji-san. Tomorrow.
Okay.
Hello? Hello. Hello!
We were supposed to meet today. I waited for you.
When will you leave me alone?
I have something to tell you.
Please listen to me. Please listen…
Please listen to me.
Could you, once and for all…
…once and for all, kindly go to hell?
Hey! What’s the matter?
I’m pregnant.
I said I’m pregnant.
Can’t you see? What are you some kind of moron?
-Hey!
And I don’t want to have an abortion this time. Please!
Hello! Can you hear me?
This is what happens.
It’s not enough to want to remember.
What happens if both people
remember the same past differently?
I know I behaved badly.
Not a single day goes by when I don’t
regret my behaviour from that time.
But the fact remains that not once did you
try and see the situation my point of view.
I...
-No.
I would share so many ideas
with you about my studio.
And I could see it clearly in your eyes that
you had absolutely no confidence in me.
What on earth was that idea even?
Even you let it go, didn’t you?
-Sure, I did. I did. But that’s not the point.
You could have said to me once, “You are capable.”
“If not this, then something else. But you will
make something of yourself for sure.”
But you…what was it you said?
“What do I get from you?”
And, “Why do you deserve to be respected?”
Did you once say, “Sorry, you have a lot on your plate.
You’re carrying a very heavy burden.”
How is that going to occur to anyone under so much pressure?
-And was I not under pressure?
When you abandoned me and refused to associate with me in the end,
did you know what kind of a condition I was in?
I don’t think you ever loved me.
Actually, I think all you ever felt was hatred.
Sometimes it’s hard to tell the difference between
extreme love and extreme hatred.
You okay?
So, the sleeping rule only applies to me alone?
No.
-I don’t want to sleep.
So, then what do you want to do?
What do you want to do?
Dance.
You want to dance?
Okay. Here we go.
Which dance?
-Put me down first. How can I dance like this?
Sure, you can. Sure, you can.
Yes, you can.
My favourite song!
-Is it?
Ma, this is a dormant volcano, right?
Hmm.
So, there is lava inside?
Yes.
We should leave.
You have a flight to catch.
Let’s stay for a bit.
Just a little bit longer.