This is a work of fiction.
Underage drinking is strongly prohibited and illegal.
Scenes involving alcohol with forceful consumption and shameful acts are not encouraged. Please view this as a comedy. Furthermore, all characters appearing in this work are of legal age.
This is bad...
You're the only one who's going to fail.
No way. I'm the only one who's going to fail?
If they find out...
I'll die of embarrassment!
You're not good at mask clearing.
Luckily, I have a mask.
And there's a pool and the ocean nearby.
The only problem is how to practice
without those guys finding out.
I can't get them drunk or lock them up.
-Iori?
-I can knock them out.
But it's dinner time now.
Maybe I could poison them!
What are you smiling about?
Chisa! It's not nice to eavesdrop!
Not as bad as poisoning people.
Hey! We're going to go rent a car.
We're going to the market.
Hey, Chisa! They're calling you.
He's acting suspicious.
Be passionate, my friends
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
GRAND BLUE DREAMING
Be passionate, my friends
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
An expanding ocean of possibilities
Summer is our amore
We'll swear to the crystal clear sky
Summer is in our hands
Be passionate, my friends
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
With a cheerful heart
Don't mess with me
Keep going even if you fall
And let summer take it all
All right. Use this.
What's wrong?
What does it look like?
How are we all supposed to fit in this?
Tokki, did you mess up the reservation?
No. I made the right reservation.
Oh, I mixed up four people and eight people.
How can you mix that up?
Sorry, sorry.
I'll get another car.
Another car?
As an apology,
I'm going to give you a convertible
with lots of room in the back seat!
-Seriously?
-A convertible?
-How is it?
-Well, there is lots of room.
-It feels liberating.
-So, no problems.
-No, no, no!
-Bring the car for eight people!
We don't have big cars like that here.
What's wrong with this shop?
Have a nice trip!
-What?
-Hey, old man!
What are we going to do?
This car is manual.
-Sorry. I forgot to bring my license.
-Me too.
I can only drive automatics.
Life is short.
The sky is so blue.
You guys are so rude!
Wow, this is a good ride!
Hey! I forgot to tell you.
The roads here are all on private land.
This old guy really has some nerve.
-Bye!
-Here we go!
Everyone, hold on to something!
Cakey is driving a manual?
She's really used to it.
How come you're so used to manuals?
I'm not used to it!
Well, this is amazing.
No way!
Are you trying to say that a city girl like me
drove a car to help out in rice fields?
I see. So that's why.
Then we have nothing to worry about.
This work is an original copyrighted material
of the Content Provider. Unauthorized reproduction
or distribution of this work in any form or manner is prohibited. Some viewers might find this work disturbing as it may contain strong language, a degree of violence or adult situations. Viewer discretion is advised. Please watch it at your own risk.
The story, names, characters and incidents portrayed
in this work are fictitious. No identification with actual
persons, organizations, religions, places and products is intended. The Content Provider, the producers and related parties shall have no liability, as to the accuracy, legality, safety or suitability for any purpose of the information provided in this work. The views and opinions expressed herein do not reflect the views and opinions of the Content Provider, or any of its affiliates, partners, subsidiaries, or Licensee.
-This isn't bad!
-Yeah!
-I feel like having a beer.
-Yeah.
At least wait until tonight!
-An oncoming car.
-This is bad. Hide!
Great! No problem.
It didn't look like anyone was riding back here.
It just looked like a normal truck carrying a few corpses.
What are you doing?
What are they doing?
All right. Pick something you'd like to eat.
When we get back, let's each make a dish!
Oh, nice idea.
-All right. Good luck!
-Yeah!
Lalako-tan!
There's lots of unusual things here.
It tests our ability to choose ingredients.
I wonder what the guys are going to choose.
Are you okay?
Yeah. I'll go ask them.
Welcome! What would you like?
-Oh, there you are.
-I...
want to eat an old man.
What's wrong, Cakey?
What happened?
Azusa...
was trying to eat the old man at the fish stall.
An old man at a fish stall?
What did you see?
I probably just heard wrong.
Really?
Then that's good.
-I'm going to ask Tokita.
-Okay.
I don't get what's going on. Just go.
-Um...
-Oh, I see. I...
want Hamasaki's wife.
-Aina?
-Tokita...
What about him?
-Tokita was trying to get with a married woman.
-Hold on.
What did you hear just now?
Maybe you heard wrong.
I heard it clearly!
You must be hearing things.
Then let's go and find out together.
I don't mind.
Oh, dear.
Welcome! What are you looking for?
He's just shopping like normal.
There's nothing weird going on.
You think so?
You must have misunderstood, Aina.
They wouldn't do anything weird in a place like this.
You're right.
-We have everything. Just tell me what you're looking for.
-All right.
A chubby high school student.
Out!
What's he trying to buy here?
I told you!
Should we turn him in?
We should talk to him first.
Wait, you two.
-I think you guys have the wrong idea.
-What?
Those are all names of fish.
-Really?
-What amazing names!
Then what Azusa and Tokita said just now...
-They were trying to buy fish?
-Yeah.
Of course, they wouldn't actually
try to buy stuff like that.
Well... I knew what was going on all along.
You were surprised too.
-Excuse me.
-Hi, welcome.
I need a poisonous fish
that can knock an adult out with one bite.
We don't sell things like that here.
It's not nice spying on people while they shop!
You're the one who was trying to buy a poisonous fish!
You're planning something weird again!
It didn't work. If I don't do something...
I'm going to end up dying of embarrassment!
Okay, everybody draw one.
What for?
It's to decide who cooks first.
We won't all fit in the kitchen.
-We're going to take turns cooking in pairs.
-That's why.
I just have to draw one, right?
Cooking in pairs?
That means if I can get Kohei paired up with Cakey...
I can practice while they're cooking!
-I'm number four.
-I'm number two.
Please pair me up with Chisa.
-Iori?
-Please, God!
Please!
Yeah!
Hey, Chisa! We're paired up!
Aina, That guy is gross. Can you switch with me?
Why are you saying that, Chisa?
We'll have fun cooking together as a pair!
-He is gross.
-What are you going to do?
I'm going to hold onto the knife the whole time.
Iori, you went overboard.
What do you mean?
No way. Did Azusa notice?
You went overboard with everything.
You're trying to make Kohei jealous, right?
Yeah!
Is that good? You're crying?
It's our turn to cook.
Why are you so far away?
Even if I practice, it's hard doing it on my own.
Should I tell her what's going on and ask her to help?
Hey, Chisa.
-What?
-Actually...
I'll get some tea.
That's the issue.
So that's what's going on.
So, Chisa, to help me practice...
will you go out with me?
What's going on? Why did Iori just ask Chisa that?
Calm down. I might have gotten the wrong idea,
just like when we were shopping.
-Are you serious?
-Yeah. I'm serious.
-I've fallen in love.
-I don't have the wrong idea!
But, Chisa...
You said you could never imagine dating him...
-Really? I'm glad.
-No!
-Are you sure you're okay with me?
-Yeah. You're the only one.
What's wrong, Cakey?
-Chisa and Iori...
-What happened to them?
She was against it until just a few days ago!
What are you talking about?
I don't want to talk about it.
I bet you just have the wrong idea again.
If you don't have any weights, you'll float.
It'll be hard to practice.
Then we can just put heavy things on me.
Can you tie me up?
What's going on? Is what Cakey said just now true?
Was she talking about the awakening of a sexual fetish?
No. I can't tell from just that one sentence.
That's kind of dangerous.
I see. Then can you at least...
I have to confirm the truth!
...step on me with all your strength?
How was it?
You're right...
I never imagined he'd awaken...
I see. So he did awaken.
I'm back!
-Welcome back.
-Sorry I'm late.
-Is dinner okay?
-No problem.
-It's our turn now.
-I'm glad I'm on time.
Dinner is fine, but...
For some reason,
Iori and the others are acting strange.
-Iori?
-What did you do?
Nothing in particular.
Chisa?
Sorry to ask you to come.
That's Iori's voice.
What if--? Are they trying to sneak in
some alone time since they're dating now?
I'm going to get wet.
You should take off your clothes.
Okay, I'm taking my clothes off.
-Okay. Let's do it.
-What?
What are you doing?
Cakey! What are you doing here?
That's what I was about to say!
You were acting weird. Now you're doing weird things!
This is-- I dropped my wallet in the pool.
Liar!
Iori, tell me the truth.
You've been hiding something since yesterday, right?
It's no use. I'll tell you the truth.
-Cakey...
-Yeah?
We're practicing diving.
Why won't you tell me the truth?
I did tell you the truth!
You're engaged in some sort of advanced adult activity!
No, this is for beginners.
Aina, we really are practicing diving.
-Really?
-Why do you believe it when Chisa says it?
We were practicing mask clearing.
I see.
Then you should have told me earlier.
I didn't want you to laugh at me.
I wouldn't laugh at you!
I would've helped you if you had told me.
-Really?
-That'd be a big help.
So, what should I do?
Oh, well, then...
-Don't struggle!
-Stop kicking!
Hello. Is this the police?
There's still water in my mask.
You're almost there.
Maybe you're still afraid of the water.
It's come down to this. Let's do it.
It?
Yeah. We did it before.
I'm in a bathtub.
-You did this before?
-I had nothing to do with it.
Does that really work?
-No. It didn't work at all.
-What?
Then why are you doing it?
I thought...
I'd be able to get closer here.
I want to do everything I can.
Anyway, you can go to sleep.
-Okay.
-Don't overdo it.
Thanks for coming.
-Goodnight.
Yeah, good night.
Well, then...
All right. Not bad.
Excuse me.
I'm from the police.
Someone reported a girl and a guy
engaging in unusual behavior.
Well... I think there's been a mistake.
I didn't see anyone suspicious.
-Oh, really?
-Yes.
I didn't see any dangerous people like that.
Just in case, I'm going to look around
to make sure there's no one suspicious here.
I understand.
I can't get out.
You're saying Iori's in bed because he caught a cold?
That's right.
When I woke up, his face was red.
I was surprised.
-Iori's always like that!
-Even the way idiots get sick is different.
His fever isn't that high, so I think he'll be okay.
He can't participate in today's lessons.
It's because of what I said.
No, it's not your fault.
This is obviously his own fault.
Anyway...
Let's let Iori sleep.
Aina and Kohei have to concentrate
on getting their licenses.
-Yes!
-Okay.
I feel better after sleeping.
Oh, you look like you're feeling better, Iori.
Azusa, you didn't go diving?
-Yeah.
-Sorry. It's my fault.
What are you talking about?
So, how are you feeling?
I'm feeling much better.
It'd be best if you took some medicine,
but the pharmacy isn't open.
There's no need for that.
No, Iori!
You're going in the ocean tomorrow.
So, you have to fully recover.
They didn't have any medicine,
but they had this.
Azusa, what's that?
A famous home remedy. You don't know it?
I know. I do know.
The only problem is...
Is it number 1 or 2?
All right, Iori.
Yes?
Stick out your neck.
Good, it's number 1!
-What's wrong?
-Nothing.
-Here. Okay.
-Thank you.
ANOTHER ONE
Can you pull down your pants next?
No, a combination technique!
Azusa, you don't have to do this for me!
No, no. There's no medicine.
So we have to do this.
No. If I don't do something,
something else other than my health
is going to be destroyed!
I'm going to look for some other medicine!
This is perfect for medicine, right?
True. It disinfects, stimulates perspiration,
and induces sleep.
It's also rich in nutrients.
It's the best medicine!
Sick people shouldn't drink it though.
But, if I drink now and fall sleep,
I won't be able to sleep at night.
You haven't been able to sleep at night anyway.
That's for a different reason.
A different reason?
You know...
I feel nervous sleeping next to you and Nanaka,
so I can't fall asleep.
Oh, I didn't know that.
Sorry about that.
Azusa?
-Hey, Iori.
-Yes?
Do you want to have sex?
-What are you saying!?
-You won't be nervous anymore, right?
No! It's not something to do so casually!
That's so rude.
I don't do it with just any guy.
But I do like you.
I'm fine with doing it once.
She's acting like it's a sport!
I'm half joking.
It'd be bad if things got awkward between us.
Half?
Yeah. Half.
If you seriously want to do it, I'm okay with that.
I'm being tested!
I'm...
really...
being tested right now!
I'm...
going to say no.
That's too bad.
By the way, Azusa...
You like Tokita as well as Nanaka, right?
That's right.
Why don't you go after Tokita?
Tokki is kind of, you know...
I'd be wasting my time chasing him.
So it's different with Nanaka?
A waste of time? Why?
Don't you know, Iori?
-What?
-Tokki, you know...
has a girlfriend.
-He has a girlfriend?
-Yeah. A girlfriend.
-A homosexual?
-Why would she be homosexual?
Homo sapiens?
So you were asking about her species?
She is a human.
I see. Tokita has a girlfriend!
That's right!
-Let's drink.
-What's wrong all of a sudden?
Darn! Why does he have a girlfriend but not me?
Wow, you're drinking a lot!
Congratulations on getting your license.
You're real divers now.
-Congratulations.
-I'm not sure about her though.
-I'm going to get better!
-That's the right attitude!
All right! We're going to Miyakojima tomorrow!
Let's have a toast first!
It looks like they already did.
He's all better. Good.
Oh, dear. They're so impatient!
A masochist...
DEEP BLUE AL FINE
KAYA MIZUKI
A fairytale whispers
In a fake world
Hiding in the complete darkness
I reach for the forbidden fruit
In my last days
Now I know the meaning of the song about hope
A broken gear will never stop again
Even if I were to lose everything
I'd still want you to know
Trapped in the sky so far away
I'm praying with ripped off wings
Because we span together
The vows of arpeggio
If life sparkles only to the beat
Of the resonating stars
I'll sacrifice everything
Till death do us apart
Thanks, everybody!
Yeah!
Hey, don't act so crazy, freshman.
All right. Let's begin.
NEXT EPISODE
"OTORI"