When you're close to someone,
maybe you just naturally
want to be even closer.
No wonder when he
wrapped that scarf around me,
I had this sudden urge to kiss him.
On the days we can't see each other,
I find myself dying to hear his voice.
[Episode 4: It's Good to Have You Here]
Old Chen, our son is back.
At least say hello.
You're back.
How were your final exams?
They were fine.
I think I'll be top of the class.
That's good.
Keep it up.
Still the same bad attitude.
Ke Ke, the flight must have been tiring.
Go to your room and get some rest.
I'll make you something delicious tonight.
Go on.
Here, Lei Lei.
Have some braised pork.
It's your favorite.
- Thanks.
- I started cooking early this morning
and let it simmer for hours.
It melts in your mouth.
- Eat up, eat up.
- Eat.
- Okay, okay.
- While it's hot.
[Yu Lei]
Would that be too sudden?
Ke Ke, we have guests coming over later.
Don't forget to shower
and change your clothes.
Mom. Coming!
How's this?
- Look at this.
- Look.
This is pretty funny.
Yeah, look at that.
Hello?
- Mom, it's Aunt Chen on the phone for you.
- Okay.
Go take it.
Son, come here.
I'll take it.
Chen.
It's been a few days.
Son, who are you waiting for a call from?
No one.
Just a classmate.
- A classmate?
- Yup.
A boy or a girl?
A guy. A male classmate.
Cheers!
Come on, eat up.
Ke Ke has grown into
such a handsome young man.
And he's so smart.
He's definitely going to
have a bright future.
He just spent a few extra years in school.
At least he's not illiterate.
In the future, I'll be happy as long as
he doesn't cause me trouble.
Mr. Chen, you're too modest.
If my silly kid
could get into a school
as good as Mingde University,
I'd be over the moon.
Enough talk.
Let's have a drink.
I'm done, everyone.
- I'll head out first.
- Okay.
Hey.
That's so interesting.
- I really loved it.
- That actor is very famous.
Okay, see you there!
- Old Yu.
- Yeah?
Aunt Chen wants you to come along too.
Get your coat, let's go.
What's the rush? Alright, alright.
The number you have dialed is not answering.
Please try again later.
Hey.
It's school break
and you're still running at school?
Let me guess.
Could it be that
you failed your fitness test last semester,
and you have to retake the 800m
when school starts?
Can't I just be exercising?
You big gorilla. Mind your own business.
At your speed,
even an old lady will pass you.
You! Why do you have so much to say?
Just run.
You should be grateful
to have a coach like me.
Seriously.
Right, right.
Go, go! Pick it up!
How was it?
- Yes!
- I think you'll pass, right?
Not bad.
Well... thanks.
Look at you, little poodle,
actually saying thank you.
Shut up.
I'm going to find Yu Lei.
[Victoria Italian Restaurant]
Hey. A few days ago, didn't you say
that you'd spend the break
practicing your running?
It's only been a few days,
and you're dragging me out to play again.
Work hard, play hard. It's all about balance.
Li Ming has been training at school
all winter break.
Why don't you ask him for some tips?
They're selling toys over there.
Let's go check it out.
- Let's go.
- Come take a look, everything's on sale!
Come see!
Great deals here! Take a look!
Look at this.
Come see! Take a look!
They're very cheap, miss.
- Hit it!
- Go, go, go!
Can you do it?
- Quick, quick!
- Chen Ke, go hit those mobs over there.
Sorry about that. Force of habit.
Get him, get him!
Yu Lei! Come save me!
- Quick, I'm out of health!
- Coming, coming!
Hurry! Hurry!
Yeah!
Not bad!
I'm feeling hot.
I'm going to shower first.
You carry on first.
I haven't had enough fun yet.
[Certificate of Merit, Top 3 Student]
[First Prize for Hosting, Yu Lei]
Yu Lei?
Yu Lei is in the shower.
Me?
I'm Yu Lei's little sweetheart.
What do you want with him?
Stop it, give it back!
Hello? Hi.
Who is this?
It's me, Chen Ke.
Chen Ke!
Why are you only calling me now?
I missed you so much!
Stop it!
Yu Lei, since when is Ouyang Han
your "sweetheart"?
Get out of here!
No. Ouyang just came to my place
to play games.
He's just messing with you. Don't mind him.
Why would I mind?
Anyway, I just wanted to tell you
that I got a new phone.
Okay, go ahead.
- Write this down.
- Okay.
Okay, I got it.
Yeah.
Okay.
Is Ouyang Han still staying at your place?
Ke Ke, it's getting late.
Go to sleep.
I know.
My mom is nagging me to sleep again.
My mom just did the same thing.
I thought it was still early,
but I looked at the clock
and it's already 1 AM.
- Wait, no. It's already 1:30 AM.
- What?
My phone is burning up.
Tell you what. Let's count to three,
and then we both hang up.
Okay.
One.
Two.
Three.
Why didn't you hang up?
- You hang up first.
- No, you.
You first.
Fine. I'm hanging up now.
Okay.
2001.
Winter break.
Sunny.
I'm grateful for technology.
Even though we're far apart,
we can still talk every day.
It's like we were never separated.
Whenever I think about it,
my heart feels like a bird,
singing a melody I've never heard before.
I forgot to tell you,
my mom has seen me glued to my phone lately.
She thinks I'm in love.
Goodnight.
Late at night, I wake up drenched in sweat.
That dream felt so real.
I can still feel the warmth on my lips.
It's a strange feeling, but...
deep down, I'm a little happy.
Dinner's ready!
Come and eat.
Eat more, son.
Put the phone away.
Focus on your meal.
Old Chen, what are you doing?
The boy is on his school break.
By the way, there's a dinner tonight.
Director Zhao's son is taking
the college entrance exam next year.
He knows you're at Mingde University,
so he specifically asked me
to bring you along
to share some of your experience.
Why is there a dinner every single day?
You're getting more and more disrespectful.
You barely even acknowledge me when I speak.
Give me the phone.
Chen Ke.
What's wrong with you?
Are you trying to rebel?
Alright, alright.
Stop shouting.
Can we just eat?
I know exactly what you're going to say.
I'm disrespectful,
disobedient, embarrassing you,
and I think I'm all grown up now. Right?
You...
Lost for words?
Are you going to slap me again?
You say I don't listen to you,
but every time you come home late
from those dinners,
and Mom tries to talk to you,
do you ever listen to her?
When things happen at school
and I come home to tell you,
do you ever listen to me?
Ke Ke, that's enough.
You always just
wash your hands of everything.
You haven't even been to
a single parent-teacher meeting.
Do you even consider this place a home?
To you, I'm just a son you can brag about
to others.
That's my only value to you, isn't it?
Since you can't stand the sight of me,
I'll pack my things
and go back to school right now.
- Ke Ke!
- You...
Hello, Professor.
This is Chen Ke.
Is it possible to return to campus early?
- Hello, son?
- Hi, Mom.
You're already back at school, aren't you?
I'm in my dorm. Don't worry.
Honestly, why did you have to
go back a week early?
Mom, since Dad was so unhappy
with me being there,
leaving early is exactly
what he wanted, right?
Your father, he's just...
Mom, I think my roommate is back.
- I have to go. Take care of yourself.
- Okay.
Surprise!
Well? Are you surprised?
Didn't see that coming, did you?
[Comrades: Almost A Love Story]
I didn't realize you missed me this much.
I didn't.
I was just bored being home alone.
Really?
Was it because I wasn't there
that you were bored?
Wow, you really think highly of yourself.
I'm ignoring you.
Ta-da!
Ignoring me?
Then I'll just give this to someone else.
Childish.
Why are you giving me this?
Do you remember when we watched
that movie together?
I said you were crying like a little squirrel,
and you said I was like a sly old fox.
So, we make a perfect pair.
Why did you pick the cute one for yourself,
and give me the...
Fine. If you like the fox better,
we can swap.
You already gave it to me.
I'm not swapping.
What?
Wong Fei Hung?
(Famous martial artist and folk hero)
Where's my gift?
If you don't have one, just say so.
Why are you hitting me?
Come on. I want to show you something.
Where? Where are we going?
How do you have the key to the piano room?
Don't worry.
After Professor Meng heard me play last time,
he applied for a key for me
so I can come and practice whenever I want.
I didn't realize you'd become
so privileged so quickly.
It's not like that.
Why do you always carry this around?
When I was little
and learning from my grandma,
she told me to always have it with me.
Every time I play,
I record it so I can listen back later.
It helps me see where I need to improve.
So, it's just become a habit over the years.
I bring it whenever I'm going to play piano.
So, you brought me here
just to watch you practice?
You helped me fulfill
my grandma's wish last time.
I didn't know how to thank you.
But now I've thought of something.
What is it?
Sorry, I haven't finished the ending yet.
It's beautiful.
What piece is that?
I've never heard it before.
Is it Bach?
Beethoven?
Mozart?
None of them.
It's a melody I hummed out during the break.
I thought it sounded nice,
so I wrote it down.
I told myself that when I got back,
you'd be the first person to hear it.
So, you wrote a song just for us?
And I'm the first person
in the world to hear it.
What do you think?
Ke Ke, I love it.
Well, if you like it,
I can teach you how to play it.
Don't worry, I'm a good teacher.
I think I'll pass.
Look at my hands.
They're like bear paws.
I can't play the piano.
Don't say that.
Your hands are cute.
They don't look like bear paws at all.
Do I look like a lucky cat then?
How was your break?
It was good.
I haven't exercised properly all break.
I didn't have much going on,
so I came back early.
What's up?
Ouyang?
Yu Lei! I was just looking for you.
You...
What? What are you looking at?
What's with the hair?
It's my new look. What do you think?
Pretty good, right?
It took me forever.
Chen Ke, what do you think?
Oh, look, it's the copycat.
Who are you calling a copycat?
They say wearing the same outfit isn't scary.
It's only awkward for the ugly one.
You!
Let me play with that.
Just you wait.
Yu Lei, isn't the Student Union
recruiting new members?
Let's go together.
Sure.
Ke Ke, come with us.
You guys go ahead.
- But...
- Let's go.
They'll run out of forms if we're late.
Thank you.
Next.
Hello, everyone. My name is Yu Lei.
I'm a freshman in the Law School.
I'm applying to join the Student Union's
Organizing Department.
Yu Lei, tell us,
why do you want to join the Student Union?
And what are your strengths?
I want to join the Student Union
because I want to make a real difference
and serve my fellow students.
I also want to challenge myself
and improve my skills.
As for my strengths,
I'm outgoing and energetic,
and I'm a good communicator.
Back in high school,
I was class president
and Student Union president.
And last year, I hosted the school's
freshman orientation gala.
I have experience organizing events,
so I believe I can quickly adapt
to the pace of the Student Union.
If you were asked
to organize a large-scale event,
how would you go about it?
First, I would define
the goals and the budget.
Then, I'd put together a team
and delegate tasks.
During the planning phase,
I'd hold regular meetings
to make sure everything is on track.
Finally, after the event,
I'd review what happened
to prepare for the next one.
Is this you?
Why am I not on here?
- Excuse me.
- Excuse me. Coming through.
I'm in the Arts Department!
That's great.
Yu Lei, you're there!
No big deal. Piece of cake.
I wish we were both on the list.
Keep looking, maybe you're there.
Found it! I'm right there.
It's okay, there's always next time.
I thought that was me.
Don't worry, look again.
It's fine. There's always next year.
Let's go eat to celebrate.
- Okay. Alright. Let's go.
- Let's go.
- I don't think she's even as good as me.
- Exactly.
- He got in too.
- Oh, wait.
- What?
- I'll text Chen Ke and ask him to join us.
Actually, I just remembered
I have something to do.
I'll head out first.
You guys go ahead and eat.
Okay. See you later then.
What are you doing?
Why aren't you eating?
I'm on a diet.
Please. Give me a break.
You, on a diet?
None of your business.
Look, I know it's about the Student Union.
It's not a big deal.
Here. Just eat. And drink.
You'll feel better once you've had something.
I don't want your charity.
No thanks.
Well, I'm leaving it here.
Eat it or leave it.
I have class. I'm off.
Wait.
Now what?
Well...
I passed my 800m retake.
I never got to say thank you.
It was nothing. Don't worry about it.
See ya.
The food looks good today.
Yeah.
Well, if it isn't our campus celebrity.
I'm surprised you're eating
with us commoners.
D-Don't be like that.
Come, sit down.
Here. Have a chicken leg.
I'm fine.
He Jin, are you looking for a seat?
Sit here.
I think I'll pass.
A regular guy like me
isn't worthy of sitting with
the future Student Union president.
What's that supposed to mean?
Everyone knows the current president,
Zhang Han, is your cousin.
It helps to have friends in high places.
There's also a saying:
"Promote talent regardless of kinship."
Yu Lei has good grades, he's popular,
and he's capable.
If you're not happy,
you should have applied yourself.
It's a fair competition.
Don't be so passive-aggressive
just because you didn't make it.
It just makes you look like a sore loser.
It's okay.
He Jin applied too, but he didn't get in.
He's just jealous. Don't let it get to you.
You want to leave the Student Union? Why?
No reason.
I just suddenly feel like the responsibility
is bigger than I thought.
I don't think I'm cut out for it.
Then why did you apply?
I...
Is it because of me?
Because people are talking?
Are they gossiping about you?
No.
I just don't want to do it anymore.
Yu Lei, if you're doing this
because you're afraid of
what people will say about us,
then let me be clear.
Every single candidate was discussed
and reviewed by the entire committee.
The faculty advisors
also oversaw the process.
Even though I'm the president,
I only have one vote.
Everyone believes in you.
There was no favoritism.
But I don't have the confidence
to do a good job now.
No confidence?
I never thought
I'd hear those words from you.
Haven't you always been the one
charging ahead with a smile?
There are billions of people in this world,
and everyone has their own opinion.
We can't control what they say.
We can only control what we do.
As long as we have a clear conscience
and do our jobs well,
what others say shouldn't matter.
Lei Lei, the Student Union
is a serious organization.
It's not a place where you can just
quit on a whim.
So today, I'm not accepting your resignation.
But I...
I can see that you're upset.
And you shouldn't make any big decisions
when you're like this.
Go back and think about it.
I'll come find you the day after tomorrow.
If you still feel the same way then,
I'll respect your decision.
I've always looked up to my cousin.
I remember once, I failed a math test,
and locked myself in my room to cry.
When she found out,
she didn't say a word,
she just rushed over to my house.
That night,
she stayed with me
until I understood every single problem.
She told me that failure isn't scary.
What matters is what you learn from it.
She really cares about you.
She does.
And another time,
I was in a city-wide speech competition.
I was so nervous,
so she took time off school
to come and cheer for me.
She even taught me how to
calm my nerves before going on stage.
I won first place that time,
all thanks to her encouragement.
She's smart, capable,
and she excels at everything she does.
She's always been my idol.
I want to be just like her.
But now...
But you're already doing so well.
I know my cousin is a fair person.
She's honest and upright.
She would never show favoritism
just because I'm her relative.
I don't care what people say about me.
I can take it.
But because of this, people might think...
she's being unfair.
I didn't think it through at the time.
I think it's better if I just quit.
Yu Lei, when you take an exam,
is it you or your cousin taking it?
Me, of course.
Why?
And the orientation gala. Was it you hosting,
or was it her?
Since you're the one doing all these things,
it proves your ability.
Everyone can see that.
Mingde University is a top school.
It's full of brilliant people.
They wouldn't let someone incompetent
join the Student Union
just because of connections.
Why can't you just trust
everyone's judgment?
But... I...
They say love is always feeling like
you haven't done enough.
I think you're only this conflicted
because you care so much about her.
You're afraid people will misunderstand her.
But she trusts you.
She's not afraid of the gossip,
so why are you?
A few jealous people
talking behind your back
won't change anything.
It only shows their own insecurity
and jealousy.
Alright.
Come practice baseball with me.
Maybe you'll feel better after some exercise.
Ke Ke, thank you.
I think I've got it now.
Don't mention it.
I just want you to be happy.
I used to hear the story of
Hou Yi shooting the suns.
For some reason,
I always thought it was a very sad story.
The sun had nine brothers, but in the end,
it was the only one left.
How lonely that must be.
The newspapers say only children
are like little suns.
But I'd rather be a star.
That way, I'd have so many companions,
and I'd never be lonely.
So, in your heart,
am I one of those stars too?
Yes,
but also no.
I think we're like binary stars.
Orbiting each other, bound together.
Pulled by gravity,
we can never be apart.
Ke Ke, it's good to have you here.
A new school year has begun.
We've just finished recruiting for the clubs
and the Student Union.
Every department has new members.
Please look out for one another.
If you have any questions or need any help,
you can always come to me.
That's all for today's meeting.
- Alright.
- Okay, let's go.
Let's go get something to eat.
I'm heading out.
Let's go over those notes later.
Sure.
- Sis.
- Lei Lei.
How's everything in
the Organizing Department?
It's going well.
That's good.
The head of the department
was just praising you the other day.
He said you're the most proactive
of all the new members.
Of course!
I can't let the president down, can I?
There you go again.
Who was it that was crying about quitting?
You're like a completely
different person now.
Actually, it's all thanks to Chen Ke.
I was just being stubborn,
and he helped me see things clearly.
Well, Chen Ke seems to
understand you pretty well.
He does.
We're like soulmates.
A rare connection.
Lei Lei, what do you think of Chen Ke?
He's great.
Why do you ask?
No reason. Just curious.
Just getting to know him.
It's been a while since we've eaten together.
What do you want? My treat.
I want stir-fry!
Alright.
Yu Lei, Chen Ke only showed you a few times,
and you've already got the hang of it.
I had a good teacher.
Yu Lei.
About that thing I asked you to look into...
- The competition in Tianjin?
- Yeah.
Don't worry. I've already signed you guys up.
See? Here's the invitation.
Thank you so much, Yu Lei!
No problem.
Since I'm in the Student Union,
I have to serve the people, right?
Guys! We're going to the competition!
Yu Lei got us the invitation!
- No way!
- Really?
- Let me see!
- What do you think, Ke Ke?
Surprised? Didn't see that coming, did you?
Guys, don't we owe Yu Lei a proper thank you?
Yu Lei!
Ke Ke.
What's wrong?
Aren't you happy about the competition?
I am.
It's just...
Why didn't you tell me about this sooner?
When the club president came to me,
I thought if I could get you all in,
you and everyone else would be so happy.
So I asked him to keep it a secret.
I wanted it to be a surprise.
What's wrong?
Did I do something wrong?
No. I'm happy.
That's weird.
How did it run out so fast?
Maybe someone's taking it.
I heard that happens in other dorms.
They steal supplements, even toilet paper.
Don't look at me. I didn't take it.
Stop guessing.
Maybe I just forgot to put the cap back on.
Anyway, just keep an eye on your stuff.
He Jin, can't you soak your feet earlier?
It's so late.
It's my routine.
But you can't study while you're doing it.
You're being so loud.
We're trying to sleep.
Yeah, He Jin.
I don't need this extra time
after lights out.
Forget it. It's late.
Let's just get some rest.
We have an early class tomorrow.
The competition is getting closer.
I'm actually starting to feel nervous.
Don't be.
The most important thing is to have fun.
Oh, right. It'll be your birthday then.
We should celebrate together.
Okay. I'm looking forward to it.
It's late.
I'm going to sleep.
Early summer, 2001.
Always sunny.
I should be happy that Yu Lei is so popular,
but I'm not.
I always imagined my moments of glory
would be shared only with him.
Why is that?
Who is it?
Are they crazy?
Who calls this late at night?
Hello?
Okay. I'm coming.
What's wrong? What happened?
Something happened.
Chen Ke got burned by boiling water.
What?
[Next Episode]
Chen Ke, Chen Ke.
All you care about is Chen Ke.
Can't you just look at me for once?
Let me tell you, Ouyang Han,
I can see you as a friend,
or even a brother, but never as a lover.
If I'm the best Ouyang Han I can be,
will someone love me then?
Of course they will.
Believe it or not, I'll take care of you.