[somber music playing]
[reporter 1] Around 20 shell casings
were found at the scene.
[reporter 2] A little before 2:00 a.m.
in Vauclin, gunfire reportedly broke out
inside a nightclub according to
the first findings of the investigation.
[reporter 1] And a young mother
in critical condition.
This is the toll of a shooting that
took place at a local club last night.
[reporter 3] This is already the second
shooting inside a nightclub this year.
[reporter 2] …in a nightclub last night
which cost the life of a young man,
while a young woman is still hospitalized
in serious condition.
[reporter 4] …faced with the
growing violence and recent shootings,
as a result of the explosion
in drug trafficking in Martinique.
[somber music continues]
[reporter 4] Martinique witnessed
its 25th murder by firearm this year…
[reporter 5] Perpetrators
are getting younger.
According to a police source,
80% of armed people in Martinique
are between 14 and 25 years old.
- [helicopter whirring]
- [somber music continues]
- [music fades]
- [door opens]
[man] Gentlemen, please come in.
We called you in because these men
would like to ask you a few questions.
[officer] We're here
as a part of an investigation.
We're looking for your brother.
We'd like to speak with him.
Which one?
Kingsley.
We're searching for Kingsley.
For what purpose?
[officer] We just want
to ask him some questions.
We went to your house and saw Marvin.
He knows nothing, of course.
Questions about what?
[officer] It's important.
That's all we can say.
Do you know where he is or not?
BORDER POLICE
For now, he hasn't done anything.
If you see him,
you can pass along the message.
We'd like to talk to him.
He knows the victim very well.
He's clashed with him before.
No way, that's impossible.
He wouldn't.
What were you doing on the mainland?
I was visiting my boyfriend.
- So when did you last see your brother?
- At the appointment with the judge.
When she gave my siblings to a pedophile.
You know, the moment
when y'all forgot to do your own jobs.
- Young lady--
- Don't "young lady" me!
Ambre, listen, please.
[officer] Okay, calm down.
We just want to speak with him.
- He never calls you?
- We sometimes message each other.
He's an adult. He does what he wants.
Is he living alone?
He's not living with you?
We're all split up since Mom's passing.
Us two board at the school.
[officer] But you never see your brother?
You don't know what he's up to?
We're no longer a family! That's a fact!
["Reality" by Lov'Nee playing]
MY BROTHER DID SOMETHING STUPID.
I'M SWITCHING PHONES
- [school bell ringing]
- [kids chatting indistinctly]
[pensive rap song continues playing]
So now I'm a liar.
My baby brother's a dealer.
My older brother's an assassin.
I'm very proud, can't you tell?
We can't be sure it's him.
Stop taking me for a fool
like you do with everyone else.
[Kylian exhales]
So?
No one knows where he is.
We'll find him soon enough.
And do what after?
He's going to get busted, bro.
What if he rats us out?
He would never do that.
And what if he does?
What do you want me to do?
For real, tell me. I'm interested.
Nothing. It's not your problem anymore.
That true?
Whose problem is it?
- [tense music playing]
- [Fatso] What the fuck is he here for?
[Kylian] Was he following me?
[Marco] Drive.
Drive where?
- You'll see. Drive.
- This isn't how you treat a partner.
You're a crappy-ass partner. Let's go.
[car starting]
[tense music playing]
NIGHT OF TERROR IN FORT-DE-FRANCE
SHOOTING RAISES CONCERNS OF DRUG VIOLENCE
[Marco] Is our merchandise safe?
What do you think?
We're gonna lose them
because of your asshole brother.
Where you get that bullshit?
Your brother's gonna get arrested.
You'll be arrested after that.
Someone will talk.
Cops will be everywhere.
They'll set an example.
[angrily] Do I look like an example?
With millions
of our money floating around?
- Didn't I tell you to not make any noise?
- [knife flicks]
We don't do business
with someone who attracts so much trouble.
You know exactly what needs to happen.
[somber music playing]
No.
You prefer that we do this to Léo?
You'll receive
small pieces of him each day.
He's gonna be going far away
and never coming back.
He won't be a problem.
My boss always says…
only death is guaranteed, understand?
[in Spanish] "Only death… is guaranteed."
[somber music continues]
- [music fades]
- [insects chirping softly]
[knock on door]
[in English] Yes?
- [woman] Open up.
- Who is it?
[woman] What are you afraid of? Open up.
What do you want?
Don't play dumb with me.
- [man] He's not here.
- Where'd he go?
Who?
- [blow lands]
- Ahh!
[loudly] Where'd he go?
I don't know.
- [blow landing]
- [pensive music playing]
[darkly expectant music playing]
[music fades]
[whistles softly]
[whistles]
- [Mathis] King!
- ["Ti Milo" by Lé Will & Deuspi playing]
- [Thaïs] King!
- [Kingsley chuckling]
- [Thaïs] Where were you?
- Not far, alligators.
- [Nolan] You're the alligator.
- No, I'm not.
- [upbeat song continues in background]
- [King chuckles]
There's a present for y'all in there.
[bag rustling]
Oh yum, candy!
[Mathis] Hey!
Will you tell us a story?
Mmm, which one?
The story of the lions and the beasts.
Hmm, okay.
We've got to be super quiet.
Whisper like mice.
- All set?
- [kids] All set.
King, you're here?
No, I'm not here.
Come.
[Kingsley] Mmm.
- And Léo, where's he?
- On a language trip.
Oh! Where to?
Okay, alligators,
Today, I'm going to tell you
the secret story of the phantom resort.
Because, as you know, phantoms also
have the right to have vacation.
So it all begins in a very large mansion…
that's full of little cute phantoms.
But there is one
that is different among them.
[girl in Spanish]
One, two, three, four, five…
six, seven, eight, nine, ten…
eleven, twelve,
thirteen, fourteen, fifteen…
sixteen, seventeen,
eighteen, nineteen, twenty!
Here I come!
This is the Art.
I don't understand.
In this house, the places,
the shadows are your friends.
You need to observe,
remember, and blend in.
This is the Art.
[in English] Crazy!
[in Spanish] What are you doing, Diablo?
Nothing, boss.
Are you getting attached to the kid?
You'll have to kill him, you know.
Yes, boss.
And he'll need to scream a bit…
so that his brother can hear him.
Good.
[in English] And then the baby phantom
returned home excited,
because he met a little girl phantom,
so now they talk nonstop,
messaging all the time on WhooWhoo,
the app made for phantoms.
All right, everyone to bed.
[kid grunts softly]
SherKhan?
[Kingsley] Hmm?
He was murdered.
No way!
You didn't know?
And his cousin, Vincez?
If SherKhan is dead, he's good.
[dark music playing]
[exhales]
I'm sorry. I can't trust anybody.
I didn't mean to kill him.
He tried to set me up, bro.
Is that the gun?
- [Kingsley] Yeah.
- You can't keep it. Let me take it.
No.
Does the family know?
What do we do now?
I don't know.
Police are looking for you.
I've gotta go, brother.
You fucked everything up.
- What did I fuck up, exactly?
- Everything!
I had a plan with no flaws.
And it's over because of you.
That's your problem, man.
It's also Léo's problem.
What do you mean?
Do you know how much money one ton is?
A total of nearly ten million.
And I had one ton, King.
They should've been shipped,
but they can't move.
You know what they want to make me do?
Kill your ass.
You need to disappear.
You've gotta move on… for a long time.
It's the only way to save yourself
and us too.
What does that have to do with Léo?
They took him as guarantee.
I don't know
what they'll do to him if you stay.
Wait, you made Léo a hostage, bro?
You're barbaric!
You piece of shit, that's demented!
How could you?
[angrily] You're damn stupid, King!
You fucking asshole!
We could've sorted this whole thing out.
And kept the kids safe for good.
But, no, you gotta
fuck it all up if you can.
What did our family get out of it?
Tell me!
Do you even care about our family, huh?
You gave them Léo!
Only a fucking asshole
would do that kind of shit.
Imagine what Mom would say if you told her
that you gave Léo as a hostage!
And you ask me to fucking disappear?
To repair your shitty mistakes?
It's your problem, Kylian, understand?
You sort this out.
I'm not going anywhere.
[sighs]
[door unlocks]
- Were you careful like I told you?
- Yeah, I didn't see anyone.
What the hell happened to you?
Nothing.
How's that nothing?
[dark music playing]
Margot.
They showed up.
They want me
to tell them when you're here.
SherKhan's men?
Yeah.
Damn.
It's becoming serious.
Truly.
I'll leave.
Leave to where?
I've gotta sell those fast.
You got a plan?
Shove them up your own ass
and board a plane yourself. [laughs]
Yeah, you're right.
I'll find a way. I'm resourceful.
I'm the King, right?
Undeniably.
Yeah.
[banging on door]
What do you want?
Visitor.
[snaps fingers]
We've all received this.
Fatso, Peace, my brother, and me.
UNION OF DOCKWORKERS
AND DOCKS OF MARTINIQUE
[gentle music playing]
[sighs heavily] I didn't get anything.
He sent it to those who could do the job.
[Kylian sucks teeth]
Jean-Claude.
That son of a bitch.
He put a hit on my brother.
He's one of many.
Why are you here?
Because you're alone.
- [gentle music continues]
- [sighs]
[softly] I don't know how to fix this.
[Pearl] Come here.
That's a disgusting thing to do.
Doesn't he have a brother?
Beats me.
It'll change nothing
if we go after his family.
King has too many enemies.
Even Fatso wants him dead.
Even your brother.
[laughs softly] Ludo wouldn't do anything.
If I say "do this," he will.
Make King leave,
that'll calm everyone down.
He's very stubborn.
[Pearl sighs heavily]
Then what would he do?
He was on drugs. He's an idiot.
Where do you get your personality?
My mom, for sure.
What would your mother do?
I'm not sure.
She'd make sure
everyone pays for their part.
If someone had forced her
to chop off her arm,
she would definitely take revenge.
She'd chop off both of theirs.
[doorbell rings]
- [Chloé] What's this about now?
- I've gotta speak to Marv.
Didn't bring the whole crew?
Outside.
[angrily] Hey, Kylian!
If you got something to say, say it here.
- I'll be back.
- Marvin!
I'll be back.
[sucks teeth]
Not cool to come here, brother.
- This will blow up in my face.
- They're bailing on me.
Because of King?
They're bailing on me.
[indistinct muted chatter]
[man] We gotta be more careful
about who we let in here.
[woman] Do you have my money?
I lent you 50 euros last week!
You need to give me my share!
I'm running low on cash
and need to buy food.
Are you listening to me?
- You need to give me my money!
- [Marvin] Yuck!
Stop being such a deadbeat husband
and give me what you owe me and the kids!
Are you listening to me? Look at me!
Look at me, you piece of shit!
I know you've been using my money
for drugs and gambling with your boys.
Stop being a dick!
Look at me and pay up,
you spineless manchild!
- [lighter flicks]
- [woman humming indistinctly]
[woman] You won't get away with this,
you piece of shit!
- [Nat] It's not me.
- What you talkin' about?
What are you doin'?
I'm keeping watch.
For what?
My little family.
Here, this is my house.
What… What are you doing here?
Did you bring my ring like I asked?
[bag unzips]
We have a job we need you for, Nathanaël.
You'll get twice as much when it's done.
You've never needed me
for anything before.
Okay, but now we do.
That's it, Marvin.
You've found yourself in shit too.
We all end up in it. Relax.
We'll be reunited… as a family.
Obviously.
And here…
will be a home for both of us.
- [laughs]
- Want to help us or not, man?
[darkly intriguing music playing]
[keypad beeping]
[Kylian] Wait here.
[darkly intriguing music continues]
Milord.
What are you doin'?
I'm making sure everything's okay.
I'm taking over, you can go.
Okay, but the plan was for me to be here.
So I'm staying.
It's all right, I told you to move along.
- Okay.
- [darkly intriguing music continues]
Looking for this, buddy?
Get in.
Get a move on, my man!
Now keep still!
- Keep still, man!
- Calm down, bro.
- Calm down, okay?
- Shut up or I'll blow!
- Fuck, I'm sitting! I'm--
- Give me the phone! The phone, give me it!
- Oh hell yeah, brother!
- [tapping loudly]
- We showed them!
- Stop it, Nat! Please, Nat.
And the cash?
The cash! Come on, guys! [clapping]
[softly] That's my ring.
The bougainvillea,
that's your plant, yeah?
Take it, bro.
It isn't Frodo's Ring of Power.
[uplifting music playing]
Thank you. [sniffles]
Seriously, brother.
[uplifting music continues]
- You've always been a Lafleur, Nat.
- [sniffles]
We never forgot.
[uplifting music continues]
Stop harassing Annabelle
and coming unannounced, all right?
[uplifting music continues]
Okay, family.
Okay, my brothers.
Respect, respect.
[music fading]
[Fatso] We all got one.
Someone put a hit on Kingsley Lafleur.
The police are watching you.
They're watching us too, but…
but if you want to try,
we can fill you in on where he goes daily…
and when he does.
Who's he to you guys?
Y'all saved his ass once before.
Not by me. That was Milord.
Milord isn't with y'all?
Milord caused a fucking mess
and screwed us.
It's over.
We…
could be with you guys.
Us?
Y'all managing after SherKhan's death?
Do you have his connections…
to get supplies?
To export?
Do you still have Croquet's boats?
[sighs]
- What do you propose, then?
- We rebuild the business.
It's all upside. We've got all we need.
Who is that?
He's a hitman. I've seen him around.
[Fatso] Take a seat.
He won't do anything with the cops here.
[rooster crows in distance]
- [Kylian on speaker] Can they hear me?
- Yes.
Well, Alexy…
I heard rumors.
You've all received envelopes.
I see you've made new friends.
Where you holdin' our stuff?
Your stuff is safe here.
Is that Milord?
[Fatso] Shit's really gonna go down.
[Kylian] Alexy,
if anything happens to King…
anything at all, even a cold,
you can forget about your share.
And if I find out you helped,
each of you will get shot.
And you two there, SherKhan's lackeys.
Go after my family
and I'll go after yours.
All right?
Brothers, sisters, cousins,
kids, adults, I won't discriminate.
Don't get started.
You don't know how I'll end it.
I hope I've made myself clear.
There's a spider under the table.
Oh fuck!
[rooster crows in distance]
[Kylian] Could it go to Trinidad?
I've been all over with it, bro.
- How much?
- 5%.
Five percent of what?
The stuff you've hidden away.
- [sighs]
- Pretty cheap to save your brother.
[darkly intriguing music playing]
[Kingsley whistles]
[whistles]
Are you okay?
All good here.
[laughs] You wanted to tell me something?
- Kylian said that you have to leave.
- [sighs]
- Are you on an undercover mission?
- He said that I could make you understand.
- Did he tell you about Léo?
- No.
- Why?
- [chuckles] Yeah, right. Forget about it.
Go, please!
I'm afraid they'll hurt you.
There's a boat waiting for you
in the Génipa mangrove.
You'll go to Trinidad
where a contact will help you.
That scumbag fucker planned for all this.
He'd love to see me out of the way.
No, he wants to save you, King!
All of us want you safe!
You think you don't matter to us?
And the kids?
Imagine their pain if you're gone.
To get settled.
Fuck, this really blows.
[Kingsley inhales sharply]
["EDEN" by Mob BoBoy playing]
- ["EDEN" continues playing]
- [inaudible]
- Didier?
- ["EDEN" continues playing]
[Didier] Here's what you'll tell
the person who sent you here.
You go tell them to fuck themselves.
If they want my help,
they should just come to me.
- So I came to you myself.
- [music stops]
How much you got?
One ton.
DUCOS PENITENTIARY
[door buzzing]
It seems that you have information
about the death of SherKhan?
Possibly.
Talk.
[sputtering] Yo, well, talk? Talk…
This isn't for free, all right, bro?
If I talk, I can't stay here.
I'd be a walking corpse.
Sharing here wouldn't be safe.
I want to get out with an ankle monitor.
- That's above my rank.
- Bring me a person with the rank.
Kingsley Lafleur, is he your son?
No.
My son is Kylian Lafleur.
[ominous music playing]
Lafleur!
Let's go.
- Why?
- Move it.
[suspenseful music playing]
Where are we going?
To the station.
[suspenseful music continues]
Hungry?
[sings softly]
♪ Well, have a seat, Milord ♪
♪ Come sit down at my table ♪
♪ It's very cold, freezing outside ♪
♪ Here, it's comfortable ♪
Not familiar with Édith Piaf?
You should know
King dropped by here the other day.
I lent him a pile of money.
I predict, with the situation,
he won't be able to repay me.
And?
Do you know what collateral is?
I see you do.
With the repayment on the principal,
a fee of 15% on your family profits.
That's what collateral is.
The profits of the Lafleur family?
Flourishing, by your father's testimony.
My father?
He seems very family-oriented.
He's just talking bullshit.
I urged my policemen buddies
to abstain from verifying, but…
they might at any moment.
Your business affairs,
do they investigate those too?
No one's bold enough to investigate.
We could make a bargain then.
Maybe you could do something
to help my brother.
What?
Just protect him
so he can remain on the island.
From whom?
Everybody.
He's a burden, your brother.
No.
I don't want anything to do with him.
He's bound to fuck things up.
I prefer working with folks
that don't diss my family.
I could bring
lots of problems to your family.
I could bring lots
of unwanted problems to yours too.
You know that.
[dark music building]
VIDEO MESSAGE
[dark music continues]
- [woman in Spanish] Cristina?
- Yes, Mom?
[woman] Come over here, sweetheart.
It's time.
[man whistles on video]
Are you filming?
[Léo on video] Are you filming?
[gun fires]
[in English] No!
- No!
- [somber music playing]
[exclaims]
[whimpers] Oh, fuck!
[sobbing]
[sobbing] Léo! Oh God…
[phone ringing]
- [ringing continues]
- [crying]
[ringing continues]
Léo?
Yeah, hey, brother.
I've got something to share.
You see this thing?
Well, I got shot straight in the head.
Boom!
But, relax, it was a blank,
not a real bullet, bro.
It hurt like hell, though.
But it was to toughen me up, you know?
So I can be fierce.
- What's wrong, are you crying?
- No.
You all right?
Oh! They asked me to tell you something.
[in Spanish] "The only guarantee…
is death."
[in English] Do you understand?
Is there someone there? Put him on.
[in Spanish] He wants to talk to you.
CALL ENDED
[phone clatters]
[Lily] Kylian? Are you okay?
What's happening?
Kylian!
What's wrong?
I'm in deep shit.
I'm visiting my uncle, maybe he can help.
No, he can't.
I just spoke with Croquet.
It's impossible.
You were with him?
Tell me what's happening.
I'm being forced to pick
and chop either my left or my right arm.
If I can't choose, I'll lose both of 'em.
[pensive music playing]
This isn't your world.
I want to stay with you.
No.
I'll call you, all right?
I want to help you.
It's beyond both of us.
Call me, please? Promise?
- Yeah, promise.
- [pensive music continues]
[pensive music building]
- [music fades]
- [laughing]
- Tag, you're it!
- Ahh! Cannonball!
[indistinct chatter]
- [kid 1] Your turn!
- [kid 2] It's your turn!
[chatter continues]
- [kid] Hey!
- [chatter and laughter]
[kid] Let's do it again!
That's so sweet.
Right after the message. Ambre, look.
[Annabelle] What?
Seriously, Belle?
You're being a bunch of clowns
with this behavior.
[sucks teeth]
Don't be like that.
- Ridiculous.
- Let go just a bit, Ambre.
Okay, you're mad, we get it.
But, look, we're all together.
That's great, no?
Together?
Do you realize
we're all now complicit in this?
If they get busted, we'll get busted too.
True, so we should be helping each other.
Who are you?
I am your brother.
- [Thaïs] Who's your daddy?
- Daddy Lafleur.
The rings.
I came up with the idea.
Don't worry, you'll get yours someday.
- We have to get King out before nightfall.
- I have it under control.
Sorry, but I can't.
I'm trying, but I can't.
It's too hard for me.
[Thaïs] King!
- [Nolan] King!
- [Thaïs] Kingsley!
- Hi, there, alligators!
- Are you coming to swim?
Oh no! You guys are all wet!
[sighs heavily]
- [Mathis] Let's go, let's go, let's go!
- Okay, okay, give me a second.
Yeah, all right.
[kids laughing]
- [Mathis] Come on, come on, come on!
- [kids laughing]
- [Thaïs] Come on, hurry up!
- [Kingsley exclaiming]
Nobody followed me, don't worry.
[Mathis] There's so many fish today.
- Move out of my way, Thaïs.
- Come on, girls!
Cleansing bath time, guys.
- That's only for New Years.
- And did you cleanse on New Years or not?
- Get in the water, Cass.
- [sighs]
Let's wash off the super bad vibes.
But first, it's makeup time.
[kids laughing]
- I'm a ghost.
- Keep still, King.
[laughter continues]
Your turn, Kiki!
Come on,
it's your turn to cleanse yourself.
- [Thaïs] Wait for me!
- [Nat] Whoo! This is dope! Bring it on!
Kick his ass! kick his ass!
- Motherfucker, Léo should have been here.
- [Kylian gasps]
Hey, King.
King!
One down.
Free from all bad curses!
- You let this happen for real?
- We had no choice, King.
- You had no choice? No choice?
- We had no choice.
Come on, it's cleansing time!
[Annabelle laughing] It's King's turn!
No, no, no! Hey! Hey! Get away!
[Cassandra] Your turn, King!
Kick his ass! Kick his ass! Kick his ass!
[imitates gun firing]
[Kingsley] No more! No more!
- [Cassandra] King!
- [Annabelle laughing]
[laughing] Stop!
[Annabelle yelps and laughs]
[Thaïs laughing] Ahh! This is so much fun!
[Nolan laughing] Stay still!
- [Cassandra] Take some chips.
- [Thaïs] Thank you.
[Cassandra] Do you want more?
[Thaïs] Yes, please, can I have more?
- [Annabelle] Me too.
- [Marvin] Me three. Thanks, Cass.
[Cassandra] No problem.
There's enough for everyone.
- [sighs heavily]
- [family chatting indistinctly]
You were right.
The streets are really shitty.
You were right from the start.
I'm sorry.
True, but now that's useless.
Yeah, I know. Even so.
I heard your last rap song.
[humming tune]
You're great at it.
What are you planning to do?
I'll be leaving.
To where?
Far away.
I've gotta stop fuckin' up.
I started working on a new song, you know.
Can you play it?
- [Nolan] Hurry up, Thaïs!
- [Mathis] Keep up with us, Thaïs, okay?
[Annabelle] I have the keys.
I'll open the door, just wait.
Hold on!
[bittersweet music playing]
[Annabelle] Give me that.
[Marvin] Thaïs. Pants.
[Annabelle] Careful with your heads.
- [bittersweet music continues]
- [Annabelle] Don't put it like that.
Who will I meet at the port?
Someone trustworthy.
Could you sell these for me?
And send me the cash?
I'll have someone send you the rest.
[Marvin] Give me the other bag, Nolan.
- [Kingsley sighs]
- [Marvin] Go sit down.
[Annabelle] Give me that bag.
I won't be back
by the time they're able to come home.
They'll be safe if I leave?
Léo as well?
Promise?
Promise.
It'll fix all this, right?
Yeah, it will.
[bittersweet music continues]
It's all your fault.
But I admit, it's also my fault.
Take care of the kids, Milord.
[bittersweet music building]
[indistinct chatter]
[Nolan] Can we play I Spy
on the ride home?
I'll miss ya!
- See ya later!
- [Kingsley] See you later!
[bittersweet music building]
["La Tête haute" sung by Ambre playing]
["La Tête haute" continues playing]
- [gun fires]
- [music stops]
There's a car coming!
[gun fires]
[car approaching]
["La Tête haute" playing on car stereo]
[kids bickering indistinctly]
[bickering continues]
["La Tête haute" fading into background]
[majestic music playing]
- [sighs heavily]
- [majestic music continues]
[gun cocks]
[JC] Is there space to negotiate?
There was. Not anymore.
[gun fires]
DUCOS PENITENTIARY
[majestic music continues]
[majestic music building]
[crying softly] I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
[music fading]
[darkly intriguing music playing]
[darkly intriguing music continues]