[If you don't turn yourself in,
your limbs will rot and you'll die]
[All characters and events are fictional,
and any resemblance is coincidental]
[Scenes with children and animals were filmed
safely under professional supervision]
Did I hear that wrong?
Aren't you gonna keep humming?
At first, it was just about
scaring people a little.
But I kind of liked it
when people were afraid of me.
Like I've become someone important.
Then, was there a first incident
that led you to commit murder?
What's wrong with today?
It all started with just a stone.
Who is there?
Is anyone there?
If I hadn't been hit by that stone,
or if I hadn't been seen,
would things have been different?
It started by accident,
but it also feels like my fate.
Have you
ever been found out as the killer?
I guess not.
If I had, I wouldn't have gotten away
with it this long, right?
Don't you agree?
Here, please have some.
Wow, thank you!
[Episode 7]
You are Seok Man's sister-in-law, right?
He works at my house,
but now we're just like siblings.
I thought you were siblings
since you always took such good care of him.
Oh, family is nothing special.
If you live together like this,
everyone becomes family.
Still, I feel bad for Seok Man.
His family scattered everywhere
looking for work.
He came here when he was about eighteen.
Do you happen to know
when he started limping?
I heard he had polio when he was young.
So he can't run?
Oh dear, how could he run with those legs?
Even walking is hard for him,
as he's always unsteady.
When we get to the hospital,
behave and get treated properly.
Don't cause trouble.
Alright.
[Police]
- What is this?
- We're from the prosecutor's office.
We're here to transfer
Lee Ki Beom to the detention center.
Pardon?
We haven't received any notice about that.
Then check with the station.
- What are you waiting for? Get him out.
- Yes, sir.
Wait a minute!
Wait!
Who gave you permission for this? Huh?
You can't just do this all of a sudden! Wait!
Lee Ki Beom has been safely
transferred to the detention center.
[Kangseng, Muwon]
Visitations are also banned.
Alright, thank you for your hard work.
You can head home from there.
No need to worry.
I've taken care of everything.
Thank you for your help!
I told you, you shouldn't beat him so badly.
I just lost my temper
when I heard you were attacked, sir.
Wow, I didn't know
you guys cared about me this much.
Well, if that's the reason,
I should
take responsibility
for both of you till the end.
Thank you!
Get back to your work.
Yes, I'll get going, sir.
Thank you!
Hey, is this really
something to be thankful for?
That punk made us do everything.
Listen.
Watch what you say.
If either of us mentions Prosecutor Cha,
we're both done.
Keep that in mind.
Seok Man, now,
do you remember the faces
of the detectives who arrested Ki Beom?
Yeah.
Point them out for me.
[Investigation Division]
These two here.
Jang Myeong Do, Do Hyeong Gu.
You knew Ki Beom's family
was looking for him.
But why didn't you say anything?
They said they wouldn't
let me off if I talked.
So these two are the ones who threatened you?
Yeah.
But Seok Man,
why were you there that day?
I mean, around Lee Joo Hee's place.
And at that hour,
with your bad leg.
Well, that's...
I don't really remember. Is that important?
That's okay.
That can happen.
I forget things all the time.
[Kangseng Police Station]
Thank you for all the trouble.
It's nothing.
Seok Man.
What kind of guy is Ki Beom, in your opinion?
- Ki Beom?
- Yeah.
Well,
he's good-looking, kind,
and popular with women.
But what makes you ask?
It feels like someone
is deliberately framing him.
Like they hold a grudge against him.
Anyone comes to mind?
There are a few guys who pick fights
with Ki Beom sometimes.
What kind of guys?
They say he flirts with all the women
in the neighborhood.
I guess they're jealous
because Ki Beom is so popular.
That's ridiculous, don't you think?
I should get going now.
Okay.
Sorry, I can't even take you home.
It's fine. I'll just take the bus.
Alright.
What are you doing here?
Your daughter-in-law made me promise
before she left.
She told me to make sure
you take your medicine.
She had no one else to ask,
so she came to you?
Forget it. Take that away.
You don't need to do this anymore.
We're nothing to each other now.
Even if you hate me,
please take your medicine.
Everyone is blaming Ki Beom.
Are you just going to lie here?
We should tell them that Ki Beom
isn't like that, and he's innocent.
If they don't believe us,
we'll say it a thousand times.
It's too much for me to handle it alone.
So please, get your strength back.
Here.
[Witness Statement Record]
With a statement like this,
Lee Ki Beom could be found not guilty.
Please open an internal investigation
into Jang Myeong Do and Do Hyeong Gu.
We can't even question the victim,
and you want an internal investigation?
We can't question the victim?
What do you mean?
Today, Lee Ki Beom was transferred to
the detention center. No visits permitted.
Si Young was one step ahead of us.
So why would you reveal
your hand to the enemy like that?
Ugh, jeez...
What now? We already took a hit like that.
Want me to tell you that punk's weakness?
Why would I turn it down?
Come here, closer.
I shouldn't be saying this as his brother,
but I feel bad for you, so I'll tell you.
He's
basically still a kid.
He's still scared of his father.
He'll do anything to
avoid disappointing his father.
[Kangseng Daily]
Wait, is that true?
Yes, we secured a witness.
Illegal arrest, and even the victim's purse.
If that's true, then Ki Beom
might not be the real killer.
Actually, Lee Ki Beom confessed to
everything the day he was arrested.
Was he tortured or something?
I knew it.
Ki Beom isn't the kind of guy
who could kill someone.
We should break the news first.
Think this through.
But if Lee Ki Beom is the real killer,
we'll face backlash.
We still have to report it.
That's what journalists do.
Ji Won!
Yeah.
Someone came to see you.
Who?
Do what?
A favor.
[Kangseng Daily]
Just add one sentence to your article.
"The special investigation team
has found another prime suspect."
First of all, is that even true?
Who is that?
I can't reveal that yet.
Don't worry. I'm not bluffing.
If you can't even reveal it, why publish it?
Ki Beom's been locked up in the detention.
Visitation is banned,
so I can't even see him.
- What?
- They've completely silenced him,
so we can't even start the investigation.
Now Ki Beom can't get out
based only on Im Seok Man's testimony.
This is insane.
If we say a new suspect has appeared,
they won't be able to
treat Ki Beom recklessly like before.
Because they might think
he's not the real killer.
So you're saying you didn't even
report the suspect to the police?
The suspect is Im Seok Man, right?
That's right, huh?
I had a bad feeling when you kept asking
whether he could run or not.
First Ki Beom, then Ki Hwan,
and now Seok Man?
Is this because of Park Ae Sook's purse?
That's why you suspect Seok Man?
There's even more.
Ki Beom was arrested in front of
Lee Joo Hee's place, where she was killed.
And Seok Man witnessed it,
meaning he was there
at the time of the murder.
But Seok Man's limping...
So,
I'm going to check it out.
Check out what?
Whether he can run or not?
No.
Even if he can't run,
whether he could still commit the crime.
That day, the killer definitely chased me.
Did you see him running?
Of course he ran, if he was chasing me.
He hit me with a rock.
What if he threw it instead?
You're making a big story out of this.
Don't worry. I won't act rashly.
I'm going to check every step carefully.
Until then,
the suspect's identity
will be kept strictly confidential.
Please write the article.
Even if I can't show my hand,
they need to know
theirs might be a losing one.
What did Tae Joo say?
Did he tell you not to publish the article?
Do you have a ball or something?
A ball?
Stand here for a moment, okay?
When I give the signal, throw this. Got it?
Hit you with this? Won't it hurt?
Talk after you hit me.
Okay.
Start!
One,
two,
three,
four,
five... now!
Ji Won...
Ji Won, what happened?
Did it hit you?
You...
What?
It hit, huh?
I... almost got hit.
Darn it.
That actually works?
Yeah?
Right.
Have the rest join
the special investigation team as planned.
Why bring in a special investigation team?
The case is basically wrapped up.
Is it necessary?
At Kang Tae Joo's request.
What?
I thought you two were friends.
Guess you're not that close.
[Real killer caught, or a forced confession?]
A prime suspect
in the Kangseng serial killings, Mr. Lee,
has been found to have been illegally
arrested by the police, sparking controversy.
It has been confirmed that he was
actually apprehended five days earlier
- than the arrest date announced by police.
- Where's Prosecutor Cha?
- He stepped out for a moment.
- What he went through during that time
remains unknown.
Mr. Lee confessed all crimes
immediately after arrest,
but there are suspicions he was
coerced or abused during detention.
If it's revealed as a coerced confession,
the repercussions will be even greater.
Meanwhile, a newly formed task force
has identified another key suspect,
so the focus is on which of the two suspects
is the real killer.
Put together the internal audit team.
Immediately!
[Real killer caught, or a forced confession?]
"Another prime suspect?"
That punk's even hiding his cards from me?
The police announced they will
use the latest forensic techniques
to identify the real killer.
Detective Kang!
I need to talk to you.
A prime suspect even the prosecutor
doesn't know about?
"Prime suspect"? We're investigating
because there's suspicion.
Anyway, Ms. Seo's been
hearing things somewhere...
Why didn't you report it?
There's no concrete evidence yet.
Cut the crap, you punk!
You think I don't know you?
Once you feel suspicious,
you just charge ahead.
And I end up regretting it.
Feels like I'm the one
who put Ki Beom in this mess.
I actually learn from my mistakes,
unlike someone.
Who is the suspect?
I'll tell you when the investigation is over.
Then what is this?
"New forensic techniques." What's that about?
Oh, that?
That's not fully verified, either.
Are you kidding me?
What are you up to?
What do you mean?
I said I'd investigate properly
and report back, Prosecutor Cha.
Just wait quietly.
I only need to check just one thing.
- "Just one thing"?
- Yeah.
Just one thing.
Oh, let me check one thing now.
When you got stabbed,
did you see anything about the suspect?
Like, was there anything
memorable about his walk?
I don't know, darn it!
Just one thing?
- Sir!
- Yeah.
Did you check it out?
Yes.
Im Seok Man is type B.
[Medical Record, Im Seok Man, Type B]
- Okay, let's go!
- Yes, sir.
Now that it's exposed in the press,
an internal audit is unavoidable.
What about keeping
the detectives' mouths shut?
You don't need to worry.
They won't bring me up.
It so happens that
your mother's condition has worsened.
Take some time off for now.
And stay out of any trouble.
- But...
- About the audit,
I'll wrap it up as quickly as possible.
You're lucky you have your brother.
How long are you going to rely on him?
You're leaving?
Yeah, I have to. I've got a mountain of work.
My mother...
Is she very ill?
- Oh, you're here.
- Hello.
Please put them somewhere visible.
Oh my, your son brought you
beautiful flowers.
I'll go put them in a vase.
Mother.
I'm here.
Oh? Oh, dear.
My baby's here?
Si Young, where's your report card?
Your grades didn't drop, right?
You don't need to worry about that anymore.
Si Young,
don't go against your father.
Your father is a scary man.
He's the kind of person
who would kick you and me out.
Mom, I'm a prosecutor.
A prosecutor of the Republic of Korea.
No one can treat me recklessly.
Not even my father.
And I'm getting married.
To a daughter from a very prestigious family.
Oh, dear.
Oh my, thank you.
Oh my, thank you. Thank you.
Oh goodness, thank you.
Please be at ease, Mom.
Don't worry about anything.
Okay.
Oh my, thank you.
Oh, thank you.
Do you admit to the illegal arrest
of Lee Ki Beom?
I told you already.
I wasn't trying to illegally arrest him,
but the prosecutor in charge was
in critical condition, so we had no choice!
We didn't even know
when the prosecutor would wake up.
And if the 48-hour
emergency detention limit passed,
what would happen to the suspect?
Are we just supposed to release him?
What did you do while detaining him?
Did you torture him or something?
Torture? We just asked him questions.
- You verbally abused him, right?
- Let's not be harsh on fellow detectives.
Honestly, you know you have to shout a bit
and make things tense to get people to talk.
Jeez...
Seok Man, I steamed some potatoes.
Feed the kids and take care of the laundry.
Yes, take care!
Girls, Mom's heading out for a bit.
- Bye, Mom!
- Okay.
Hey girls, are you hungry?
Want some potatoes?
Kyeong Jin! I told you not to scribble here!
This belongs to my friend!
- Stop, don't cry.
- Uncle, I hate you.
I'm sorry.
You're hungry, right?
Should we eat some potatoes?
Oh, it's hot!
Me too, me too!
I want to climb up too!
Come on up, come on up!
Girls, let's eat potatoes!
Su Jin!
Su Jin, are you okay? Are you hurt?
No.
Wow, Uncle is super fast.
Of course, I'm really good at running.
I told you not to climb dangerous places!
I won't do it again.
Promise!
You must stay safe and grow up strong.
So you can grow up fast and marry me someday.
What brings you here again?
Seok Man, you're type B, right?
Yes.
Oh, what should I do?
I think I'm going to have to ask you
for an embarrassing favor.
What kind of favor?
Well, take off your underwear.
What?
Underwear.
Deliver this to Dr. Jo right away.
Yes, sir.
[Hair of an unidentified suspect]
But how did you get him
to take off his underwear?
Are you curious?
I begged him.
How did you get him to do it?
"The higher-ups set a quota.
We each have to collect
pubic hair from 20 B-type men.
Please help me out."
He actually took off
his underwear? The suspect?
I said the killer's the one who won't do it.
Come on.
Are you type B?
Want to take off your underwear?
Want me to pull your hair out?
Hurry up, you punk!
And tell them to contact me
as soon as the results are out.
- Yes, understood.
- Yeah.
What is this?
Give it here!
Hold on.
Unidentified suspect...
Is there an unidentified suspect?
- Is it a four-syllable name?
- Jeez.
Who is it? You know, right?
I don't know, either.
- You're lying, punk.
- Stop it.
You follow Kang Tae Joo around all day.
How can you not know?
I really don't know!
Be straight with me.
- Huh? Bluffing, right?
- What do you mean, bluffing?
You know Park Ae Sook's purse
was found at the bookstore, right?
This guy was the one who put it there.
- What?
- Do you think that's all?
He was also at the Lee Joo Hee
murder scene, they say.
I should go.
Is that true?
Yes, that's what Detective Park said.
- He was at the Lee Joo Hee murder scene too?
- Yes.
That can't be.
Back then, Detective Do and I were
searching the area to catch Lee Ki Beom.
There wasn't anyone suspicious.
Except for the limping guy.
Wait.
The limping guy?
Yes.
I only need to check just one thing.
When you got stabbed,
did you see anything about the suspect?
Like, was there anything
memorable about his walk?
Why are you telling me this only now!
- Who was it? Did you identify him?
- Well...
You didn't?
He just knows Lee Ki Beom so...
He's an acquaintance of Lee Ki Beom?
Yes.
But please don't worry.
- We made sure he keeps his mouth shut.
- I'm not asking about that. Who is he!
[Kangseng Branch]
When you were arrested,
who saw you?
I heard it's someone you know.
I don't know.
I think you've misunderstood something.
Evidence has emerged suggesting
he might be the real killer.
What do you mean?
It's him!
He's the one who placed
Park Ae Sook's purse in your bookstore.
You know that purse is the decisive evidence
framing you as the real killer, right?
That's why we're investigating you.
Cooperate with us.
Honestly, if he's the real killer,
isn't that good for you too?
Name him.
That guy can't be the one.
- What?
- He's not the killer!
You punk!
The prosecutor is speaking. How dare you!
- That's enough.
- I'll finish up shortly.
Enough, enough!
Get your head straight!
It was the same back then too.
They told me to name one fellow protester.
And they'd let me go.
They coaxed, soothed, hit, and threatened me.
So I named him.
I got out safely as promised,
but my friend...
My friend didn't get out safely.
I could never go back to the school
where my friend never returned.
I can't lose another friend like that.
It looks like Detective Kang is
on a wild goose chase this time.
He can't even walk properly.
He's escaped multiple times,
but how could a limping man...
No, no!
Can't you see that?
Pardon?
Lee Ki Beom, that punk,
if he's the killer, would he react like that?
Is Lee Ki Beom really the killer?
Ki Beom!
Tae Joo!
You can't.
Visits are not allowed.
We're family.
[Police Officer ID: Kang Tae Joo]
We just need five minutes. Five minutes.
Only five minutes.
How are you feeling?
I'm getting better.
I'm sorry.
Honestly, I suspected you.
When I heard you followed Min Ji that day,
I thought maybe you did more than
just gave her an umbrella.
That's your job, right?
I don't blame you.
Tae Joo.
I can get out, right?
I need to get out
before Sun Young gives birth.
By then, it'd be too late.
Before Sun Young starts showing,
you need to hold the wedding.
Okay.
[Italian Bakery]
You must have been
shocked by the news, right?
I never imagined Lee Ki Beom
would be illegally arrested.
I'm ashamed as a prosecutor.
No,
you got injured while rescuing me
and were in the hospital.
No, that can't be an excuse.
I'll handle the investigation
properly from now on.
Does that mean Ki Beom can be released?
Fortunately, there's a witness.
They say it's Lee Ki Beom's friend.
If we find him...
Which of Ki Beom's friends
are you talking about?
I don't really know his name, but,
only that he has a leg problem.
Im Seok Man?
Seok Man?
Who?
Officer.
Find out everything you can
about Im Seok Man right now.
See if he has a criminal record
and what his blood type is.
His blood type is B.
He doesn't have a criminal record.
You two, go grab some coffee for a bit.
- Yes, sir.
What is this?
Data comparing the suspect's body hair
found at the scene with that of Im Seok Man.
Is that true?
Yes, the suspect hair sample you sent
also showed high levels
of titanium and sodium.
It matches the killer.
[Radioisotope Analysis Report]
Radioisotope analysis?
Is this it? Is this what you call
a scientific investigation technique?
You wanted to know.
Not the National Forensic Service
but the Korea
Atomic Energy Research Institute?
You see that?
[Korea Atomic Energy Research Institute]
The suspect is a laborer who sweats a lot,
seemingly in a job like a welder
who works with metal.
Im Seok Man fits this report perfectly.
And the one who brought Park Ae Sook's purse
to Lee Ki Beom's bookstore
was Im Seok Man.
Do you think that's a coincidence?
They said Im Seok Man can't even run.
He can run.
I saw it with my own eyes.
This is driving me crazy.
Changing suspects before trial?
That's not a big deal.
But once the trial begins,
there's no turning back.
He'll do anything to
avoid disappointing his father.
If the suspect you indicted
is found not guilty,
with your father's election coming up soon...
Are you really okay with that?
Seok Man's not here.
Where did he go?
I'm not sure. Did Seok Man go to work today?
What work is there? No outside jobs today.
He said he was going to meet his friend.
Seok Man!
What are you doing here at this hour?
Well...
I have something to return to you.
What friend?
I don't know. He said
he was returning a handkerchief.
Is this it?
Hey, this isn't yours!
Hey, can I take a look at it?
What is it?
A handkerchief.
A handkerchief?
You mean Ki Beom's handkerchief?
Yeah.
Why do you have that?
Ki Beom seemed to have left it at my place.
When exactly was that?
Well...
- I'm not sure.
- Think carefully.
Since when was it there?
I don't really remember.
Where is it now? Is it at your house?
- Yeah.
- Let's go to your house.
Now?
What are you doing? Hurry up.
Okay.
Sun Young, slow down a bit.
Hurry up. We don't have time.
Are you mad at me?
Because of the handkerchief?
That too, and...
You saw Ki Beom getting arrested, right?
Why didn't you say anything?
You knew I was looking for Ki Beom, so why?
I...
I really thought
Ki Beom was the killer.
What?
Otherwise, the police wouldn't
have arrested him so forcefully.
How could you suspect Ki Beom?
You know him better than anyone.
But the police back then were so...
Do you think everything
the police do is right?
Do you really believe that?
There are innocent people
in this world, many of them!
Ki Beom is one of them!
It's all because of that handkerchief!
You really don't remember
when it first showed up at your place?
Well...
Ji Won was hospitalized
on the same day as me, so...
September 7th!
Was it before or after that?
- I don't really remember...
- Don't just say you don't remember.
Try to think carefully.
Maybe before?
Before? Are you sure?
Then what happens?
What else?
It means he can clear his name!
After Ki Beom lost it,
the killer must have had it,
so the killer isn't Ki Beom but the one
who had that handkerchief at the time...
Sun Young.
Don't come any closer!
Don't tell me
the killer
is you?
What?
Answer me!
You... How could you...
You trust Ki Beom that much,
but why not me...
Sun Young, are you okay?
Stay back!
Don't come near me!
Why are you acting like this? What did I do?
Sun Young!
Im Seok Man, you punk!
- Sun Young, are you okay?
- Im Seok Man!
Are you alright?
You are under arrest
as a serial murder suspect.
No, it's not me!
Stop this!
It really wasn't me.
Why would I ever kill anyone?
Why would I...
Then what is this?
How did this end up with you?
That's...
I have no idea.
Obviously Ki Beom must've dropped it.
That's just how he is.
He says it's precious, but then
he just drops things like that.
After all the efforts Sun Young
put into making it...
There are a few guys who pick fights
with Ki Beom sometimes.
They say he flirts with all the women
in the neighborhood.
I guess they're jealous
because Ki Beom is so popular.
So,
you like Sun Young, huh?
That's why you hate Ki Beom?
Because Ki Beom likes Sun Young?
I liked her first!
What?
I said I liked her first.
- Whoa.
- It's just like mine.
It's really pretty.
I made this myself.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Thanks.
I've got something for you too.
Something for me?
Close your eyes.
Even though he knew I liked her,
he still confessed to Sun Young.
What kind of friend does that?
They've spent so much time together,
and you just barged in like that, you punk.
You planted that purse
to frame Ki Beom, didn't you?
No.
That's not true, Tae Joo!
Don't call me that!
It's disgusting and terrifying
that someone like you
was around my family.
Do you know how many people
died because of you?
And you still call yourself human?
Tae Joo...
Say my name again,
and I'll tear your mouth open.
Confess and repent as soon as possible.
Spend the rest of your life
atoning for those you killed.
Over the past two years in Kangseng,
seven women were murdered
in the Kangseng Serial Murder Case.
The suspect has finally been arrested.
How did you manage to arrest the suspect?
We found the item used in the crime
at the suspect's residence,
and through radioactive isotope analysis
by the Atomic Energy Research Institute,
we confirmed the suspect is the killer.
So you're certain
he's the real killer this time?
Yes, we're certain.
Huh? What's all this?
Are we having a feast?
Ji Won!
Ji Won, you're here.
You too, hurry up and help.
There's still a ton to do.
You're missing the most important thing.
For someone just out of jail,
nothing beats tofu.
Tofu? Come on.
On a day like this, we should give him meat.
Jeez, ma'am.
He needs to eat this
so he doesn't end up going back there.
Bring it here. I'll cook it.
When is Ki Beom coming back?
Ki Hwan went to pick him up,
- so he'll be here soon.
- Oh.
Everyone's waiting for you at home.
Sun Young is there too.
She is?
Mom gave you two her permission.
Is that true?
But, how...
Sun Young really went through a lot.
I can't wait to see everyone.
Hey, what's wrong?
I'm just a little hungry.
Oh, man.
You must be starving.
The food in detention center
can't be any good, right?
Mom actually prepared a lot of food for you.
Oh, right!
Your sister-in-law told us to get a cake.
Your birthday has already passed.
What cake?
Let's just go straight home.
No, it'll only take a minute.
- Ki Hwan.
- Yeah?
I'm gonna sleep for a bit.
Yeah, sure. Sleep comfortably.
I'll wake you up once we're home.
Ki Beom.
Ki Beom, wake up! You're home.
Look at your bruised face.
You've been through a lot, right?
I thought I'd never see you again.
Don't say that.
I'm really glad you came back safe.
Sun Young.
Let's live
like normal people now.
Get married like others,
have kids like others,
and grow old together.
Just like everyone else.
Just like
everyone else...
Hey, Ki Beom, I went in
and saw your favorite cake right there, so...
Are you sleeping?
Ki Beom?
Ki Beom!
What's wrong with you?
Hey, Ki Beom!
Hey, hey... Ki Beom!
Ki Beom, snap out of it!
Ki Beom...
Ki Beom!
What's wrong with you?
Hey!
Ki Beom!
[Stop]
[Murderer, get out
Condolences]
Look over there. That's Kang Tae Joo, right?
Yeah, that's him.
That punk took Ki Beom away.
- Oh, dear.
- How shameless.
How dare you even show your face here?
Tae Joo...
Where is Ki Beom?
You killed him.
You killed him!
Ki Beom...
I'm... I'm sorry.
Bring him back!
Bring my precious boy back to me!
My sweet, kind boy...
My precious boy...
Bring him back!
Bring him back! Bring him back!
Take her inside.
Ki Hwan...
I have something to say to Ki Beom.
I'm sorry!
But I can't see you anymore.
Please just go.
Ki Hwan...
Go.
They said it was sepsis
caused by organ failure.
It seems his condition
was already serious in detention.
Even the guards told him to
go to the hospital first after release.
How could a perfectly healthy person
end up like this overnight?
I...
I did this. It was me.
I ruined everything.
I...
killed Ki Beom.
Tae Joo.
- I...
- Tae Joo.
Look at me. Look at me!
You can't fall apart now.
We have to make those punks
who did that to Ki Beom pay.
None of them even came to the funeral.
No one is even asking for forgiveness.
How can people be like this?
Where is Cha Si Young?
He went to a funeral.
A funeral?
That punk?
[Condolences]
- Assemblyman!
- Oh my, it's been a while.
Take it easy.
- It's been so long.
- How do you do?
Ki Beom...
This place is like a festival.
Without any guilt,
or any sorrow,
they just laugh and chatter.
To those who caused your death,
you've already
been forgotten.
So don't forgive anyone.
Even me,
who is helplessly kneeling
before them.
Have you
ever been found out as the killer?
I guess not.
If I had, I wouldn't have gotten away
with it this long, right?
Don't you agree?
What about Ki Beom?
Did Ki Beom
know you were the killer?
No, he didn't.
Ki Beom, I'll buy you a cake, so just wait...
Hey, Ki Beom, what's wrong?
Are you hurt somewhere?
Why are you like this?
What's wrong with you?
- Ki Hwan...
- Oh dear.
This isn't good.
We should go to the hospital.
Did you do that?
What?
You told Tae Joo
that I followed Min Ji out?
Huh?
That wasn't me. It was you.
It's raining!
This won't do.
I'll bring her an umbrella and then go home.
You just lock up and go.
Don't touch this! I'll deal with it tomorrow.
[Umbrella, 600 won]
Got it.
You said you'd bring Min Ji an umbrella
and followed her out, right?
Did I?
You just got confused, huh?
Of course.
What other reason would there be?
You need to get to a hospital.
Ki Beom...
Ki Hwan.
Don't touch Sun Young,
no matter what.
Mark my words.
I need to go get the cake.
Just wait a little!
Ki Beom
knew nothing.
So Ki Beom knew, huh?
I said he didn't know.
Why won't you believe me?
It doesn't mean you're certain
that he didn't know.
It's still only an assumption.
Lee Ki Hwan!
Sit.
Let's talk more.
That name.
It's been a long time since I've heard that.
Now you're starting to
sound like the Tae Joo I knew.
Now, move aside.
We seek the death penalty,
the maximum sentence under the law.
Are you still human?
How could you frame me with that accusation?
Seok Man, did you really kill them?
Those women...
I killed them...
Tae Joo, let's never see each other again.
This is... Sun Young! Kang Sun Young!
I think Sun Young is trying to kill herself.
How can we give up?
One person is dead,
and the other is falsely accused.
Sun Young, it's dangerous! Come down!