Officail Website : kissasia.id  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
♪ Hold me tight,
let the darkness drown me ♪
♪ Even one second of truth is enough
to lose myself in it ♪
♪ Hold me tight,
let the darkness drown me ♪
♪ Even one second of truth is enough
to lose myself in it ♪
♪ Whether you're light or a lie,
I can't pull myself away ♪
♪ In this game,
truth or lie no longer matters ♪
[Queen of Darkness]
[Episode 11]
Even if you want compensation,
you shouldn't ask Ti Cha for it.
Because,
this child isn't his at all.
Wait.
You...
We must quickly establish Ti Cha
as the father.
Or the timeline will give it away.
Yao.
Let's do it your way.
After all, this is Song family's blood.
As for Ti Cha.
Well, that takes some weight
off my shoulders.
You!
All of you.
Fine then!
So I'm the fool in this, huh?
I'm not letting this slide!
Yao!
- I'll make you pay!
- Yao.
- Even my own dad betrayed me.
- I'll kill you!
I don't want to live anymore!
Dad, why are you doing this to me?
What's the point of living now?
Stop fighting!
- Don't hit her!
- I'll make you pay!
Someone help! Yao!
I'll kill you! I'll make you pay!
I don't want to live anymore.
Fang Yao has been driven out.
Now you can hand over
all the backup copies of the video, huh?
A transaction
requires chips of equal value.
For example,
agree to let me, as a board member,
run for the chairman position.
The Song family's scandals
must never leak.
Once word gets out,
can your Song family
bear the consequences?
Fine.
It's a deal.
Congratulations,
Director An.
Now you've secured your place
in the Song family,
and entered the group.
Instead of taking the hits,
strike first.
Only by standing higher,
and possessing greater power,
can I truly protect myself.
The you standing here now
no longer needs my protection.
Without your support,
it would have been hard
for me to get here.
It's just that
there are too many unknowns ahead.
Maybe keeping things as they are
is the best choice for now.
Alright then.
So,
I'll wait
till you find your way
through the darkness.
I should get ready for
tomorrow's shareholders' meeting.
Today's coffee
is a bit bitter.
Tomorrow's the shareholders' meeting.
An Ning. This thorn
not only hasn't been removed,
but has been driven in deeper.
Don't worry.
Your eyesore
is my own deep-seated splinter.
But lately, things have been tense.
Too many whispers in the air.
I'm worried...
You are just a dog I raised.
Dare to bargain after failing your task?
Aren't you worried about your life?
Getting knocked out last time
was my carelessness.
I'll handle your business
without hesitation.
But making others risk their lives with me
requires money to buy loyalty.
Don't worry.
This time I will stake everything.
The shareholders' meeting
is your battlefield.
Leave this part to me.
An Ning is late.
Looks like she's decided to give up.
Then...
Who said I gave up?
You have neither real power
nor foundation
in the group.
What makes you think
you can challenge me?
Why humiliate yourself like that?
Who's humiliating whom
is still up for debate.
[Enterprise Digital Transformation] It's.
[Six Major Pain Points
and Supplier Solutions]
[Understanding Digital Transformation]
the digital
[in Enterprise] era now.
Officail Website : kissasia.id  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Physical enterprises moving online
is the unstoppable trend.
[Lack of Strategic Planning
in Digital Transformation]
[Fragmented Tech Implementations, Stakeholders
Disengagement Risks, Competitive Disadvantage]
[Organizational Structure Challenges]
[Rigid Hierarchies Impede Agility]
[Siloed Operations Limit Collaboration,
Cultural Resistance to Change]
To write our own legendary story,
rather than becoming dust of history.
I remind you all
choose your side wisely.
Otherwise,
don't expect me to show mercy.
[Longxing Group Chairman Election]
[Proportion of candidate vote]
We're family.
I don't want to embarrass you.
Leaving gracefully
is better for everyone.
I vote for An Ning.
♪ Hold me tight,
let the darkness drown me ♪
♪ Even one second of truth is enough
to lose myself in it ♪
As a shareholder holding 10%
of Longxing Group,
I believe An Ning is outstanding.
She has the ability to
lead the group to new heights.
So.
I support her
to become the new Chairman
of the group.
[Longxing Group Chairman Election]
[Proportion of candidate vote]
I heard you lost your memory
in a car crash.
The Chairman's health
is directly tied to the stock price.
If that's the case,
can you really run the Group properly?
And also,
you were previously a housewife.
You lack practical experience.
What if the group goes under
under your leadership?
Can you really take that responsibility?
- Yeah.
- Exactly.
I might be speaking out of turn.
You and Chairman Song,
your father-in-law,
are at each other's throats now.
If it were in ancient times,
that'd be seen as a major betrayal.
Someone with flawed feminine virtue
and family discord.
Can she really lead the group?
What a joke.
You talk about my amnesia.
But you're not amnesiac,
how did you manage to
drop the stock price by 20%?
Don't tell me you're just being clueless?
I remember now.
You gambled overseas
and couldn't pay them back.
Because of that,
rumors about the company went wild.
And you.
Every project you handled
ended up a disaster.
You're practically the industry's
bad luck charm.
The group isn't your family.
I have no obligation to look after you
like a housewife.
From now on,
please stay out of group business.
As for you.
You're hardly worth mentioning.
You only got in
because you're kin to my father‑in‑law.
Quietly be a parasite.
Don't start causing trouble now.
And don't talk to me
about feminine virtue.
Got it?
I'm the new chairman.
If you're earning from this company,
but you only do things that hold it back.
I won't tolerate it.
Any other questions?
If there are no questions,
I'll officially start at the group on Monday.
♪ Rules quietly
fall into a street without light ♪
♪ Falling like an extinguished spark ♪
♪ I break through
every preset blurry line ♪
I thought you had left.
When you need me,
I'll be there.
When you can handle things alone,
I'll step back.
Do you remember
the question you asked me before?
If one day,
I find out you're not who I think you are.
Will I still treat you this way?
Now I can give you the answer.
Who I'm willing to risk everything for
is the you right here.
Not the past.
Just focus on what's ahead.
♪ Inside a web hastily woven
from endless lies ♪
♪ Freedom blooms into love's twin flame ♪
♪ Mist coils around the sleeping forest ♪
♪ Memories scattered
through cracks of darkness ♪
♪ How to escape this real-feeling dream ♪
♪ Lies reflect in water's gleam ♪
♪ Traces of existence
can never be erased ♪
♪ How to find the self I can't reclaim ♪
♪ Fly away, hear she says ♪
♪ She'll fly out from
thorns of woven lies ♪
♪ Pierce the fog,
shatter this dream tonight ♪
♪ Burn like fire ♪
♪ Just burn like fire ♪
♪ The maze in the abyss starts to clear ♪
♪ Yet night keep on whispering ♪
♪ Surrender to fate,
no clear direction ahead ♪
♪ She will rise as the dawn
that breaks the darkness ♪
♪ Never slowing down,
for tomorrow cannot be stopped ♪
♪ Surrender to love and find the way ♪
♪ Even if fate tries to forget her ♪
♪ Never despair,
for the heart burns with endless light ♪
♪ Waiting for dawn ♪
[Copyright of this short drama
belongs to]
[Shanghai Chuqi Weishi
Culture Media Co., Ltd.]
[and Youku Information Technology (Beijing)
[Co., Ltd.]
[Youku Information Technology (Beijing)
[holds exclusive global online
and broadcast rights]