( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
[This drama is fictional and any similarity
with reality is purely coincidental.]
[Production guidelines were followed
when filming children and animals.]
I even wonder why
[Episode 5]
I'm talking about this right now.
It's just that I want you to feel a bit
at ease, at least for today.
Does this mean
I'm falling for you?
- I mean...
- Wait a minute.
Sorry, but you should go first.
Can I have a word with you?
- That's not it.
- Not what, exactly?
You're not doing this because you like me.
It's just because you saw my mom's text
and felt bad for me.
Do you start liking someone
just because you pity them?
I don't.
I wasn't sure how to define this
until I said it out loud,
but now I'm sure.
To be precise, it's because I like you.
President, I...
I mean, I just...
I don't think this will work.
I'll pretend I didn't hear any of this.
No...
Right, he's the President.
Born into wealth.
If I got involved, I'd only get hurt.
And that would be the best-case scenario.
My Yeol Mu...
Yeah.
I did the right thing. I did good.
Does this mean I'm falling for you?
To be precise, it's because I like you.
Ah, it drives me crazy.
Why is my heart beating so wildly?
It's okay.
What have I done?
Jeez.
What is this, some new workout?
Does that help clear your head?
I'm not in the mood for jokes.
Sorry.
Anyone would think you
just confessed and got rejected.
Is it true?
Hui Won said she doesn't like you?
I don't know.
How am I supposed to face her at work now?
Why couldn't you?
The rejecter should feel awkward.
The rejected should be proud.
Is being honest about your feelings a crime?
Square your shoulders! Engage your core!
Down.
- What's wrong?
- Wait, I've got a cramp! A cramp!
That hurts!
Ouch, it hurts.
Hold on, I've got a cramp too.
Yes, I understand.
Then text me right away.
I'll check my schedule and get back to you.
Okay.
My life got completely ruined because of you.
You should never have been born.
Why didn't you contact me?
That day, I...
How shameless of me.
After saying those things, I...
Why is this so hard on us?
How can I face him from now on?
Being honest isn't a crime.
Where did she pop up from all of a sudden?
Where did she go?
Wait, we don't need to make things awkward.
Last time, targeting campers,
we briefly ran a pairing promotion
where people could enjoy our Taehan Beer
alongside various camping events.
The results showed good response
and decent sales performance.
Given the recent increase
in camping enthusiasts,
for Taehan beer to position itself
as the best beer for camping,
we believe these initiatives
need to be long-term
and substantive, not just one-off events.
That's why we...
Are you avoiding me?
- Me?
- Am I making you uncomfortable?
Oh, not at all.
It's a misunderstanding, really.
Misunderstanding?
If there's nothing else, I've got work to do.
She's avoiding me.
Why do we keep running into
each other? This is awkward.
Jang Hui Won, why didn't you
answer your phone?
What happened yesterday?
I told you to text me when you
got home, but no response.
Jeez.
I'm the one who turned him down,
yet I seem more bothered by it.
Are you listening?
Yeah.
I'm asking what happened.
Are you two dating?
No, no, it's not like that.
If it wasn't that, then
what did you say to him?
Honestly, I regretted it the whole way home.
I shouldn't have stepped aside.
Why?
Well...
You must've been really embarrassed.
I mean,
he came at you so recklessly,
right in front of me...
You're the type to get startled
and run away when someone suddenly pushes in.
So, it bothered me that I couldn't step in
and protect you.
Oh.
I thought...
Protect me from what? We're friends.
My sleepiness is gone. Need to go back.
Thanks for the drink.
This is driving me crazy.
Weren't you close with Reporter Park?
He pulled that postpartum care center
no-alcohol article immediately last time.
It's not easy being the target
of everyone's anger.
A reporter needs to have persistence.
I had him disciplined
through the Deputy Editor.
Oh.
Good job. Well done.
Since it's come to this,
let's stir things up a bit.
If we damage Taehan Liquor's image,
the board will have
no choice but to step in, right?
- How?
- You know Oh Jin Woo, Taehan Liquor's model?
Seems he was recently scammed
big time in an investment.
There's no one easier to control
than someone desperate for money.
Slip him some cash
and ask him to stir up
just enough controversy...
How are you going to clean up
the mess after that?
Instead of money to buy his silence,
how about buying him a drink?
Heard he likes his drinks, right?
A drink?
People who like drinking often make mistakes.
Ah, Team Leader.
Yes?
What's with our ace? Why the long face?
Like someone who just lost a big sale.
What? This is even more suspicious.
Tell me. My lips are sealed.
I know, yes, I know.
Um...
This isn't about me, it's about a friend.
Okay.
So, someone confessed
to my friend's female friend
right in front of him.
Logically, as a friend,
he should be supportive,
but secretly, it seems he hopes
she'll reject the confession.
Hold on.
So, did that friend commit
some serious crime?
Or does he have some major flaw?
No, it's nothing like that.
No? Then the answer is simple.
He likes her. That female friend.
Pardon?
Are you stupid, Assistant Manager Cha?
You should've made a scene,
but why just watch?
It's always the ones who don't
even know their own feelings,
hiding behind friendship
and saying, 'We're friends forever!'
I'm getting married.
What?
You'll come to the wedding, right?
Hui Won.
[Wedding day]
[Kang Du Jun and Jang Hui Won]
No way.
This makes no sense.
No!
That's so shallow.
I said no!
Assistant Manager Cha! Assistant Manager Cha!
- Yes?
- Oh, dear.
It's not too late! Go after her!
Running after a bus that's already gone
will only make you sore.
No, this isn't about me.
Don't thank me. It's nothing.
I mean, I just...
I don't think this will work.
I'll pretend I didn't hear any of this.
If there's nothing else, I've got work to do.
We did upper body yesterday.
How about lower body today?
I noticed your core strength
was a bit weak yesterday.
Your shoulders seem a bit slumped too.
I'll stick with you one-on-one
and coach you properly.
Forget it. I'll just rest today.
Not in the mood.
I see it now. There is a reason
your shoulders are slumped.
What is it this time?
Tell me everything.
Wasn't it you who told me
to stand tall and be confident?
What's the point of being confident
if she won't even face me?
Is Hui Won avoiding you?
On second thought, I'd feel pressured too.
I mean, it's not just a coworker,
it's the President confessing his feelings.
Who would just accept that so easily?
Maybe in dramas.
Is that so?
Was I only thinking about my own feelings?
Emotions don't work the way we want them to.
Still, in times like this, honesty is best.
What if I'm honest and she avoids me again?
Ah, come on.
Sitting here worrying
won't solve anything, you know?
You've got something you're good at.
Just...
Go for it head-on.
You startled me.
Where are you going?
You don't need to know.
You...
He's surprisingly good
at listening to others.
May I have a word?
This doesn't seem like a misunderstanding.
It is a misunderstanding. Got proof?
The fact you're asking
for proof tells me everything.
This won't do.
It seems my confession
is making you uncomfortable.
No, it's not that.
I'm not asking for an answer.
I was just frustrated.
If I didn't say it, it felt like
I was lying to myself. It's just venting.
Whether I hide my feelings
or hold them back, that's for me to handle.
So stop avoiding me from now on.
Because I want to keep seeing you.
Who's there?
Get over here, quick!
Still, you shouldn't shove someone like that.
I got a cramp! A cramp!
Jeez.
Says she has a cramp but runs just fine.
I told you.
I can't even breathe if I can't see you.
Not for a day, not even a single second.
You're my oxygen.
So don't avoid me.
I'm not avoiding you!
Then what is it?
You avoid eye contact,
run away when we meet,
and pretend not to hear me when I call you.
Well... I don't know
why I'm like this either.
Does this mean I'm falling for you?
Whether I hide my feelings or hold them back,
that's for me to handle.
So stop avoiding me from now on.
Because I want to keep seeing you.
Why is he being so honest?
Whenever I think of you,
my heart keeps going thump thump.
Don't hide those feelings.
- Did she...
- I'll take responsibility.
I thought she said Du Jun.
Ah, I must be crazy. Why am I like this?
I need to get a grip.
Has he always been that tall?
Let's keep the new product lineup
for the first-half of next year as is.
But earlier, I noticed
the promotional items tied
to food brand collaborations
seem to lack competitor analysis data.
What? What's wrong with me?
Report back immediately.
Oh, and I heard the Try Golden Ratio Glass
got great feedback.
When launching the new product...
Share today's discussion
with Purchasing and Marketing,
and we'll schedule a follow-up for details.
Yes.
Oh.
Um...
Oh you...
I guess I went way too hard...
in those meetings
and now my throat's on fire.
Yes.
Ah, why is this happening? Is it defective?
It happens occasionally.
Of course.
Just a moment.
Why won't this open?
Ow, darn it.
Wow, this is no ordinary bottle.
Excuse me for a moment.
Well then...
That was so cool.
Confess twice and you'll lose your mind.
Did Hui Won say yes then?
Someone like you wouldn't understand.
You're not the Kang Du Jun I know.
Where did that cold, sharp-eyed guy go?
Where did this clumsy guy come from?
Who are you?
Clumsy guy?
You're the clumsy one.
Every single day is popcorn-worthy drama.
What's that now?
Around 11 p.m. last night in Gangnam, Seoul,
celebrity Mr. Oh crashed
into a tree while drunk driving.
[Actor Oh's DUI crash]
According to police,
after drinking with acquaintances,
[Actor Oh's drunk driving]
he caused the accident on his way home.
[Actor Oh's BAC at license revocation level]
At the time of arrest, his BAC was 0.143%.
[Actor Oh crashed into a tree]
Fortunately, there were no casualties,
[Controversy over the 5-year beer ad model]
but Mr. Oh has been a beer model
for a liquor company for five years,
making the shock even greater.
[Actor Oh's DUI accident]
Due to this incident,
- projects starring Oh...
- Look.
It's that model is Oh Jin Woo.
What? Isn't he their model?
Try!
That's right. The liquor model got a DUI?
- Is he insane?
- Jeez.
Mr. Oh has admitted to all charges.
[Beer ad model DUI]
And his agency announced
a full suspension of activities...
Yes, it's the New Product Development Team.
You'll need to contact the PR team
for model and promotion inquiries.
Would you like me to
connect you to the PR team?
Yes, this is Taehan Liquor.
We're also currently looking into the matter.
Could someone take that call?
Yes, Taehan Liquor Sales Team.
Yes, well... about that...
You should contact
the PR team to sort that out.
We're the Sales Team here.
Yes, thank you.
We're swamped.
Sorry I'm late.
I'll get straight to the point.
Do you have a solution for this situation?
We're working on a solution.
Working on it?
Our Southeast Asia exports have collapsed.
The damages alone are 8 million dollars!
Does it make sense that Taehan Liquor
is shaking the entire group's stock price?
First the postpartum
care center beer incident,
then the new product plagiarism allegations.
With these back-to-back scandals,
people are even talking about owner risk now.
If we can't fix this,
it'll be hard to keep our footing.
That's right.
- That's enough.
- Right.
The model's DUI didn't happen
because of President Kang.
Questioning his management skills
over this is...
He said they're working on a solution.
Let's give him one more chance.
Has the CEO of REM Entertainment
responded yet?
They just notified us they'll join
the entertainment group meeting.
As they should.
Betraying me would only hurt them.
- The time?
- Reserved for 7 p.m.
Okay.
This should be enough of a warning.
People who like drinking often make mistakes.
The outdoor brands have already
quickly cut ties with Oh Jin Woo.
Let's replace our model quickly too.
We can't let our company name
be associated with a DUI offender.
Did you know there are memes
mocking Try Beer now?
That's why entertainment companies
are backing out.
They don't want to be
associated with controversy.
Did we encourage drinking?
Honestly, that actor messed up.
Exactly.
We built up exports to Southeast Asia
with this Asian Prince branding.
And this is how he repays us?
What do we do now? It'd be hard
to find someone with a clean record.
We have to find someone.
A new model to revitalize our image.
Four days should be enough, right?
Find a new model within four days?
No. Find one and shoot ads in four days.
Why is everyone so quiet?
This is an emergency.
The conditions are too strict.
It's not easy to find someone
better than Oh Jin Woo.
Who did you recommend, Team Leader?
- Ji Eun Kyu.
- What?
He's an idol.
Look at his eyes.
How pure they are!
When I look into those eyes,
I feel my soul being cleansed.
Come on, he's not sexy.
What then? All the A-list actors
are being blocked by their agencies.
Does the model really need to be famous?
Try Beer has many loyal customers,
so a fresh face might work.
True.
Isn't there a sexy man like a bitter stout?
A sexy man...
No idea.
Clueless.
What should we do?
See? You have no answers either.
Kang Du Jun.
Huh? Did you just say Kang Du Jun?
- Yes.
- Huh?
What?
- Me?
- You just said Kang Du Jun.
No, that's not what I meant.
Oh, that's kind of brilliant.
Crazy. The President as our model?
But President Kang has that sexy vibe, right?
No, no.
I was just spouting nonsense for a second.
No, it's not bad.
Since you brought it up, make a proposal too.
- Me?
- Yes.
We don't have time if we want
to shoot within four days.
This is the time to shine,
so our team gets some credit.
- Right?
- Exactly.
Having the President as our model!
Isn't that insane?
I asked them to find a new model,
and their solution is me? Are you kidding?
Why not?
I thought it was perfect
as soon as I heard it.
Look!
[Proposal]
The new proposal with you as the model.
Isn't this exactly the brilliant idea
to turn crisis into opportunity?
No, forget that. Who did it?
Seriously, who proposed this ridiculous plan?
Well...
It's Manager Jang?
I brought her as you requested,
so you two can discuss it.
Surprise!
What do you think?
Why not make your debut as a model?
So, you pictured me as a sexy guy
like a slightly bitter stout?
Isn't this practically a confession?
That's not it.
It's not? Then fine. I guess I don't
have a reason to do it either.
Wait, what I meant was...
Manager Jang is leaving now.
No, I mean...
As soon as I heard the concept,
you were the only person
I thought of, President.
The more I worked on the proposal,
the clearer it became that our brand
identity and your image
are a perfect match.
[Try Beer]
Look here.
Try Beer's signature clean, refreshing image
combined with the new urban,
sophisticated masculinity we're adding...
Okay.
Understood.
Seems like you really
studied me in a short time.
Well, in that case,
I'll accept, but I have one condition.
A condition?
You've been through a lot.
So I heard he accepted after setting
some kind of condition?
Yeah, right.
Agreeing to his condition
should've been enough.
Why do you have to show up
at the set where he's shooting?
I'm fine.
But is the President really okay?
Yeah, he doesn't look okay at all.
Where's the brave soul that'll tell him 'no'?
Alright, President!
Drink the beer and show us
a joyful expression.
Oh, gosh.
Well, just...
Give us a bright smile.
Drink the beer, cheer,
and flash a bright smile.
Smile.
Sm... Smile.
Ugh, jeez.
What are you all doing?
Say something!
Man, even a robot would
smile better than that.
Oh.
Let's take a 10-minute break.
Yes, okay.
Oh, my.
Will a break make him smile?
It's his first time.
But I'm genuinely curious.
How much cooler the President
will look all dressed up.
He'll look like a celebrity, won't he?
Even as a fellow man, I admit he's handsome.
Looking at him
takes me back to my 20s.
If I dressed up,
I could rival a celebrity too.
Exactly. If they're shooting at the company,
we should sneak a peek.
Where's the shoot?
Team Leader, if it's close, are you going?
Why not?
Huh? I got the location from Manager Jang.
Oh my goodness.
It'd be great if you put
this much effort in every day.
It's closer to the office than expected.
Really? Let's go check it out.
Can we really go check it out?
Secretary Go will be with the President,
so won't Manager Jang feel
left out if no one's with her?
As teammates, nothing wrong with going.
So, should I start the car now?
We can't go empty-handed.
Should we get coffee and dessert?
There's that new cafe in front of the office.
Word is their coffee is really good.
Shall we buy some?
- Deal!
- Deal.
But we have to finish the proposal today.
Is everyone really okay time-wise?
Oh, right.
That's why we came in on the weekend.
If that proposal is the issue,
we'll have to handle it tonight.
I really want to go too,
but I have plans with a friend tonight.
Ugh, my little bunnies at home
are waiting for me.
I need to rush home
to take over parenting duties.
I have a book club meeting.
Tak Soo always seems to
have plans whenever I see him.
Well, if no one can make it, I'll skip too.
I guess I should text my crush.
Ugh, seems like today's just not our day.
Everyone seems busy this weekend,
so let's wrap this up quickly and go.
Understood.
Hey, you're really not going, huh?
I won't ask twice, okay?
You're really not going?
I won't ask thrice.
But this mirror only shows my nose.
Restrained emotions naturally
look more sophisticated.
People just don't get that.
What's so important
about looking sophisticated?
It has to feel more real than reality itself.
Only then will people crave beer
just from seeing the ad.
I'm not even a real actor.
How am I supposed to do that?
And can't we replace that director?
He keeps getting annoyed at everything.
Watch me.
Now, imagine you're copying me.
Make your eyes like shrimp.
Pull your cheekbones up as high as possible.
Smile.
Why aren't you looking at me?
Now, try it like this.
Up, up, up.
That's it.
Wait, is this really right?
Earlier you complained I looked like a robot.
Then watch me.
Hey!
Huh? You smiled.
See? It works.
You look cool when you smile.
Now.
What am I supposed to do?
Just once, just once.
Do it just once for me, please.
What do you mean 'just once'? Forget it.
Why? Please do it, just once.
- Just once.
- No.
- What...
- Just do this once for me.
Oh, oh.
Oh, good. Good.
Okay, okay.
What happened in that short time?
So natural! One more time!
Yeah!
Good, well done.
Much better.
Newborn clothes are this tiny?
Wow, so adorable.
But I still don't know Yeol Mu's gender.
Who cares? Pink works for
both boys and girls.
Oh my, it's too cute.
How about this one?
Hello? Hey, focus, focus.
You're acting weird today.
You've been glued to your phone all day.
She's been at the shoot
for ages, and still no reply?
Guess she's busy.
I heard today's shoot is important.
Aren't you going to pick one?
You asked me to pick a present for Hui Won.
This, a pregnancy gift.
I never said it was a pregnancy gift, though.
Huh?
Hey, it's not even her birthday yet.
Should we make up a random holiday to buy it?
Why? Don't you want to buy it for her?
No, that's not it.
Fine, let's take a look.
See this. Isn't it adorable?
It even has pockets, look.
It is kinda cute.
Why that reaction?
Then how about this? This is super cute too.
Check this out.
Just buy whatever you like.
Whatever you pick will look pretty anyway.
Hey, Cha Min Uk.
Maybe I'm hungry, so I can't focus.
Shall we grab something to eat?
Let's go.
Why's he acting like that today?
Right, going to the shoot won't help.
Should be working instead.
Weekend work isn't new.
That's just how I am.
- Oh! You scared me!
- Oh.
Goodness! What are you doing, Manager Nah?
You startled me.
Why'd you come back?
Well, my wife just called
saying she took the kids to her parents'.
What? That means you're free!
Isn't that great? Why come back?
Every day it's chaotic,
but weekends alone feel too lonely.
Might as well catch up on work.
Huh? But why aren't you
going home, Team Leader?
I'm Team Leader Bang.
Gotta do at least this much
to keep my team leader position.
Oh my!
Why are you here, Assistant Manager Choi?
Now that I think about it,
Manager Jang and I joined
the company together.
But I'm still an assistant manager.
I'm going to work hard
and aim for a promotion.
Isn't it that your crush hasn't replied?
No, it's not!
Didn't you already leave?
Oh, you scared me!
I left my book club book here.
I just came back to get this.
Well, I should get going...
Get going...
I think it's okay to slip up once in a while.
Huh? Why are you still here?
The main character always shows up last.
The future of our Taehan Liquor.
I knew you'd come back.
Look at how tight our team is.
Gives me chills.
Well, yes.
We are the future of Taehan Liquor.
I'm feeling generous. Coffee's on me today!
What's the occasion?
You used to stretch every penny
raising three kids.
On a day like today,
how could I not buy coffee?
Tak Soo! That coffee shop earlier.
- Yes.
- Let's try
that famous coffee.
Yes, I'll get you there safely.
Wait, stop!
Where did you learn
to pull out your card in front of a senior?
The famous coffee plus dessert,
I'm buying today.
Now, follow me!
Great!
Coffee! Coffee!
Alright, let's enjoy that together.
Oh.
[Secretary Go]
Ms. Hui Won, did you get home safely?
Huh, I didn't know I could make this face.
[Secretary Go]
[Image saved to gallery]
Wow, Kang Du Jun.
Congrats on your model debut.
Ah, what's with that tone?
[Si Hyeong: Kang Du Jun's
model debut is fire]
[Saved]
[Try Beer's New Face?
Turns Out It's Taehan Liquor's President!]
[Trouble at Taehan Liquor,
Owner Steps In Personally to Save It]
[Try Beer's New Face?
Turns Out It's Taehan Liquor's President!]
[Trouble at Taehan Liquor,
Owner Steps In Personally to Save It]
[Try Beer's New Face?
Turns Out It's Taehan Liquor's President!]
[Trouble at Taehan Liquor,
Owner Steps In Personally to Save It]
[Who's the Actor in the Try Beer Commercial?]
[Trouble at Taehan Liquor,
Owner Steps In Personally to Save It]
Wow, look at him!
[Owner Steps In Personally to Save It]
Who is it? Look at this.
He's really handsome, isn't he?
Who is he?
[Try Beer's New Face]
He's freaking handsome.
[Who's the Actor in the Try Beer Commercial?]
[Try Beer's New Face?
Turns Out It's Taehan Liquor's President!]
[Trouble at Taehan Liquor,
Owner Steps In Personally to Save It]
[Vice Chairman Kang Moo Young]
It's me.
Do you know what happened?
How did he even think of modeling?
From the New Product Development Team?
Was the one who proposed it...
Jang Hui Won?
So this is how things are going?
You've already seen it?
Yeah.
Our Du Jun, how does he pose so well?
Is it because he takes after me?
Well.
Anyway, he can do anything.
Yeah, should I set him up with someone?
Sis.
Yes.
Who do you think I am?
I already picked someone as Du Jun's partner.
You mean our picky Mrs. Han
has taken a liking to someone?
I met her when I went
for a massage last time.
She's got it, I tell you.
Just hearing her voice, I felt it click.
Who on earth is she to cause such a fuss?
Has Du Jun met her too?
Well.
Not yet, but...
I have a plan for that.
Mr. Kim, go!
[Try Beer's New Face]
[The model outshines the beer.
Filling out the application after seeing it]
[This is the best perk]
The reaction is pretty hot.
- Welcome.
- Huh? It's Kang Du Jun.
Gosh, he's hot.
Wow, he's really tall.
He's cool.
He's really handsome.
What brings him here?
He really is handsome.
So hot.
One lemon tea, please.
Make it very cold, with lots of ice.
One cafe latte, please.
- Yes.
- I got this one.
Got your card.
But isn't something too cold
bad for a pregnant woman?
Ah, my Yeol Mu is super hot right now.
Yeol Mu?
Already picked a nickname
for the baby? Without asking me?
It's my choice, okay?
Did I do something wrong again?
Yeol Mu.
Actually, that's kinda cute.
- Passed.
- By the way,
you look really excited right now.
Is it thrilling with all these new fans?
Well.
If someone's jealous,
that might make it more thrilling.
Who? Me?
Are we even that close?
Already forgot my condition?
Well, in that case,
I'll accept, but I have one condition.
- A condition?
- When you go to the OB-GYN next time,
take me with you.
What?
Aren't we close enough to worry about
morning sickness and check the ultrasound?
Crazy.
Shh.
Isn't it time to go to the hospital?
When it's time, just tell me.
I'll go with you.
No, what if someone recognizes you
now that you're so famous?
I'm not that famous yet.
But still, I can just wear a hat and mask.
And that'll do it?
You really think your height
doesn't stand out?
With that nose bridge and those
deep eyes, they're truly one of a kind.
Your nose bridge latte is ready...
Cafe latte and lemon tea are ready.
Okay, coming.
Ah, this is so embarrassing.
Ah, seriously.
Jeez.
Manager Jang really made it again.
Everyone's buzzing about
who came up with the idea
to make the boss the ad model.
I just made a recommendation.
My friends are seriously envious,
saying the boss' face alone
is enough of a perk.
Oh, so you're eyeing something
way out of your league?
You never know how things will turn out.
Remember that civil servant friend
I mentioned?
The one who only looks at status, not looks?
Well, she just sent me a wedding invitation.
Guess what, she's marrying
a ridiculously wealthy man.
So her wish came true?
Wow, how did she even pull that off?
I was curious too, so I asked.
How on earth did you reel him in?
Wasn't there opposition from his family?
And guess what she said!
- She got pregnant!
- Ah.
So she planned it?
Who knows, whether it was
planned or just lucky.
But I guess it happened
because they like each other.
Assistant Manager, are you jealous?
Jealous?
I care about looks!
You are jealous, right?
I don't plan to rise in status
through marriage!
What do you take me for?
If you're jealous, just admit it.
With that much jealousy...
My, my.
What's up with your boss?
[Try Beer's New Face]
He doesn't seem the type.
But he only did this
because it was your idea, right?
No, he had no choice
because of the company image.
She went through some trouble for nothing.
Just for giving one wrong opinion,
she ended up taking the fall.
Huh? Was it really a wrong suggestion?
Weren't you just thinking of your boss
while imagining a cool and sexy image?
Hey!
But if your coworkers find out
later, you'll be teased.
They'll say it was a biased
recommendation, right?
Well, what would people say
if they found out I'm pregnant?
Wouldn't they first wonder who the dad is?
Why? Did someone say something?
No, it's not that.
I just wonder if people would think
I got pregnant just to marry rich
and change my fate.
Hey, that's not true.
You did nothing wrong,
so who would say anything?
Still, wouldn't strangers misunderstand?
Like saying I got pregnant first
to trap some guy.
Bring them all here.
I'll show them how ridiculous that is
by punching them one by one with facts.
- Jeez.
- Jeez?
Hey, I have a black belt in Taekwondo.
Ugh, forget it.
You once cried because it was too tough,
and now you're showing off your belt?
Well...
I'm just conserving my strength,
but it's not like I don't have it.
Wanna see it? Huh? How should I show you?
Yeah, go ahead, touch it.
Ugh, forget it!
- Hey, now! Right now!
- What do you mean?
What's with you?
Ugh, annoying.
- Cheers.
Jeez.
I ate way too much today. I'm stuffed.
I need to use the restroom.
Go ahead and keep looking out for her
behind her back all you want.
Hui Won's not gonna notice.
Huh? What did you say?
Forget it.
Hey, where are you going?
I'm telling you this
for the first and last time.
Think carefully
whether what you feel now
is love or friendship.
[Gallery]
Hey, what is it?
What is it? What?
Am I not allowed to see it?
[2 years ago]
If you open your eyes,
that's three years of bad luck.
Oh, seriously.
- One, two...
- When can I see it?
- Ta-da!
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
[Mi Ran, Happy Birthday]
♪ To our beloved Mi Ran ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Wait, make a wish first!
Oh, right.
What? You both said you were busy today.
We were busy preparing a surprise event.
Look at this, this and this.
[Happy Birthday]
Don't even get me started.
We took leave this morning
to clean and decorate the place.
And she insisted on baking the cake himself.
We put in some effort.
Come on, it's your birthday.
Hey, I used premium ingredients
from the flour to the butter. All for you.
Really?
Huh?
Hey, Hwang Mi Ran's crying.
Hey, camera! Get the camera!
Hey, Hwang Mi Ran's crying! Hurry!
- Hey, over here!
- That's it.
Time to take the picture now.
- No, no, no!
- Look here.
- No, come here, come here!
- Together?
Okay, okay, together.
- One, two, three!
Okay, got it.
Hey, one more, take one more!
Why did it have to be Hui Won?
Hui Won is so precious to me.
I can't even get jealous.
She said we'd go out together,
and she left alone because she's tired?
Ah.
The night air is cool,
and it feels good to walk after so long.
It would've been better if we were drunk.
That part's disappointing, right?
I'm telling you this
for the first and last time.
Think carefully whether what you feel
now is love or friendship.
So nice.
Hey, you should apologize.
[14 years ago]
He's cleaning now
because he showed you his homework.
He got in trouble because of you.
Aren't you going to apologize?
Sorry.
If you have a conscience,
you should do the cleaning too.
It's fine.
What do you mean it's fine?
Ignoring it even though you know it's wrong?
I told you not to.
I can't stand seeing someone
get away with ignoring things.
I don't like it!
Why are you just smiling?
If you're thankful, buy me some tteokbokki.
I'll add eggs too. Two of them.
Mister!
You should apologize.
Who rides like that?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
As long as you're not hurt,
that's all that matters.
Let's go.
Thanks for walking me home.
It's cold.
Hurry home, or you'll catch a cold.
You know you can't afford to get sick, right?
Yeah, next time let's all hang out
together with Mi Ran.
I should go.
Bye.
Ah, hurry up. You'll catch a cold.
Got it.
Yes!
- Fighting!
- Cheers.
Think carefully
whether what you feel now
is love or friendship.
Weren't we supposed to
stick together forever?
Friendship.
I guess it's not.
You saw the stock price recovered, right?
That's because the ad shoot
went well this time.
I heard Thailand reopened
contract discussions too.
If Thailand goes well, other countries
might change their minds too.
Please keep monitoring the real-time updates.
Yes, sir.
Just know that Ms. Hui Won played
a big part in making this happen.
Good.
Hi.
[Taehan Liquor Company]
That's unexpected.
You shot the commercials yourself.
Someone has to take responsibility.
Responsibility?
But someone who rushes into marriage
shouldn't preach about responsibility.
Marriage just means there's
another person to share responsibility.
It doesn't really change anything.
So there's no need to bother
contacting our model
or giving pocket money to the agencies.
Okay.
Let's bury the past nicely.
Jang Hui Won.
How are things with that woman these days?
Your parents don't know yet.
They'd be thrilled if they knew their son
got someone pregnant before marriage.
But do the employees know
that Hui Won is pregnant?
Well, anyone can get pregnant.
What matters is whose child it is.
That's enough.
Still, she must feel relieved.
When Hui Won is having a hard time,
you can just hold her hand.
Well.
If it gets tough this time,
will you let go of her hand again?
Like last time?
I've put salt
in the second drawer, so use it.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Did President Han say something again?
She always comes without notice, seriously.
It's nothing.
What time is the buyer meeting?
In 30 minutes.
Are you sure you're okay?
I'm okay.
You go first. I'll be there soon.
[Global partnership between
Taehan Liquor and JINSH Co]
Nice to meet you.
I'm glad we can collaborate like this.
It's an honor for us to be working with you.
I'm very happy too.
If it gets tough this time,
will you let go of her hand again?
Like last time?
President?
[Global partnership between
Taehan Liquor and JINSH Co]
No problem.
Don't let go.
Don't give up, please, brother.
Brother, please.
Brother! No!
What do I do?
Will you let go of her hand again?
Like last time?
President, are you not feeling well?
You are burning.
If you feel dizzy, maybe lean on me?
[Epilogue]
Oh, you startled me!
Why are you so surprised?
Why are you so late?
There's a meeting in 20 minutes!
I didn't want to be late.
When I go outside now,
people won't leave me alone.
But they leave you alone just fine.
You don't know how the world works, do you?
If I go outside, there are
people recognizing me now.
Manager Jang just happened to see that.
Oh, thrilling. Feels so new.
Are you excited about getting fans?
Or are you excited because Manager Jang
saw and got jealous?
A tall figure like this can't be hidden.
With that nose bridge and those deep eyes,
they're truly one of a kind.
That's what Manager Jang said.
Goodness.
You were all like 'who on earth
came up with this idea?'
And now you're looking so happy.
And what exactly did you
make Manager Jang promise?
You don't need to know.
By the way, where did this mirror
come from? I can only see my nose.
Hey, that's mine.
It's yours? Even your mirror's
a mini version of you.
Jeez. If you model twice, it's really
going to be a big deal.
Oh, right.
Can you get me a hat and mask?
- Why?
- What if people recognize me?
Manager Jang said that again.
You're so annoying.
Give it to me.
It's almost time to get off work.
Do you like Jang Hui Won?
Is that not allowed?
Are you trying to pick a fight right now?
You keep acting childish
while competing with the President.
You've been acting strange lately.
- Get out.
- Do you really not know why I'm like this?
Give me Taehan Liquor.
What if I say no?
You'll see for yourself why you
have no choice but to say yes.
It's a safe and reliable place.
I told you I'm keeping this baby.
A shameful secret
I never want anyone to know?
That's the kind of relationship it is.
For me, that day was really wonderful.