Look into my eyes.
There's no fear. There's only light.
I am the light.
The light is me.
There's no fear.
There's only light.
Only light.
- That's him, in the uniform.
- Thanks.
Christian Habersaat?
Sorry for barging in like this.
I didn't know you were retiring today.
- I'm being forced to retire.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
I'm Rose Knudsen.
I was sent here to speak to you.
- About what?
- From Department Q? Carl sent me.
I've tried to reach Carl
for three months.
- Now he sends his assistant...
- I'm not his assistant.
- I'm a detective.
- I'm afraid you're too late.
I promise to make this brief,
because there's one thing I know:
People would rather drink than listen
to a bitter retiring policeman like me.
So here's what I want to say to you.
Figure out what motivates you.
Is it conscience? Necessity?
Is it loyalty?
Thoroughness?
What do you say, Bak?
Well, I suppose it's all of the above.
But let's say cheers to that.
With the risk of sounding
somewhat lofty...
I believe in justice.
Christian... Stop.
Stop!
Tell them to put down their weapons.
- Right now.
- Do as he says. Put down your guns.
Get the camera.
Come here. Closer.
Christian, listen. Stop it.
Christian?
BOUNDLESS
INCOMING CALL
ROSE KNUDSEN
DEAR MONA
WILL YOU MARRY ME?
- It's Carl.
- He shot himself.
Christian Habersaat. At his reception.
- Bloody hell. Were you there?
- Of course I was. You told me to go.
- You shouldn't be there. Come home.
- I want to stay for the funeral.
- For his funeral?
- Carl, he shot himself in front of me.
- I understand.
- What's this about, Carl?
- He'd written your name inside his hand.
- My name on his hand?
- Why the hell did he do that?
- I assumed you could tell me.
- How the hell should I know?
- You've got to come here, Carl.
- What's up?
- I have to go to Bornholm.
Good thing you called.
Tell me about Christian Habersaat.
Well...
The man was depressed.
He wasn't right in the head.
He spent the past seven years on some
case about a girl found dead in a tree.
The Alberte Schneider case.
They mentioned it yesterday.
A nasty affair. She was only 21.
They closed the case.
- Murdered in traffic.
- You mean a hit-and-run?
Yes, apparently.
But Habersaat couldn't let it go.
Things went downhill from there.
The case became an obsession for him.
He stops sleeping. He gets weird.
Friends and colleagues get fed up.
Finally his wife leaves him,
and all that's left is work.
You'll pick me up, right? I won't stay
on that island longer than I have to.
- He was your friend, wasn't he?
- I wouldn't call it that.
We attended the police academy together.
Me and Christian, Hardy, Bak.
The police commissioner here.
- What was he like? Christian?
- He was a good guy.
I haven't seen him for years, so it was
strange when he started calling.
He called you for three months,
and you never called back.
I know, and I feel bad about it now.
I should have.
- You didn't want to speak to him.
- Yes, I did. Shut up now.
He looked like my dad.
Christian Habersaat?
He did?
It's intense,
seeing a person shoot themselves.
- How's... that thing going?
- That thing?
Yeah, your dad thing.
My dad thing?
Blessed be the God and Father
of our Lord Jesus Christ -
- who according to His mercy
has caused us to be born again -
- through the resurrection of Jesus
Christ from the dead...
Christian Habersaat,
from dust you came...
to dust you shall return.
From dust you shall arise.
Figure out what motivates you.
Is it conscience? Necessity?
I saw him the day before.
He was fine then.
He was disappointed, though,
that you were ignoring his calls.
You think he shot himself
just to get Carl over here?
- What would he want to talk to me about?
- The Alberte Schneider case.
What? Nonsense.
For Christian,
everything was about Alberte Schneider.
- So that case really fucked him up?
- It fucked up the whole island.
When Bak closed the case,
Christian took it all home.
I think you should go by his house and
have a look. He would've appreciated it.
Carl?
- Long time, no see.
- You're so right.
Yep, it's a mess.
I guess I should have seen it coming.
- Seen what coming?
- Would you mind introducing us?
This is Rose, Department Q.
Henrik Bak.
- Rose Knudsen.
- Police Commissioner Henrik Bak.
We went
to the police academy together, so, uh...
It's funny,
we used to call him Pussy-Carl.
But Christian,
he was a good police officer.
- Right until Alberte got in the way.
- In the way? Of what?
- Of his work, or...?
- 250 people die in traffic each year.
You don't have to build a space rocket
every time.
So, no reason for you to stick around.
You didn't tell me
he'd written my name in his hand.
Not the first time
a suicide victim addresses his motive.
You're saying I'm his motive?
I thought it was Alberte Schneider.
As far as I remember, Christian had
plenty of reason to hate you.
- Are you being serious?
- Yes, I am.
- Bak, you bloody idiot.
- That's typical you. Always smarter.
It was like that at the academy, too.
Everyone looked up to you.
They looked up to me?
You must be mistaken.
It was always like: "Carl, Carl, Carl."
"Carl will make it big-time."
Yet here I am: Chief Commissioner.
And you?
What are you exactly, Carl?
- What the hell are we talking about?
- I'm saying that you should go home.
And take your assistant with you.
- You're the dumbest person I know.
- Goodbye, Carl.
Fucking jerk.
- Did we get the house key?
- Yes.
Then let's go.
Now this is a renovation project
that came to a halt.
THE ALBERTE SCHNEIDER CASE
SHUT DOWN
Carl, come here for a second.
- What the hell is this picture?
- Holy shit.
It must be a forensic image
that's been digitally manipulated.
- Is that her?
- Alberte? I guess so.
Jesus, the guy was religious about it.
Carl?
Someone's in the house.
Hello?
Fuck!
Hey. Hey! Are you with me?
Hey, look at me!
Hey. What's your name?
Christ!
Goddammit...
- Has he got a pulse?
- No pulse.
Copenhagen Police.
We need an ambulance.
- A young man in his 20s has OD'ed.
- Come on!
I'M SORRY DAD
He's dead.
It's Bjarke, Habersaat's only son.
A sad fate who's been in and out
of rehab since he was a teenager.
- Who is his mother?
- June Habersaat, Christian's ex-wife.
She was at the funeral too.
Why write "I'm sorry" to your dad
who's been dead for days?
- Birkedal?
- Coming. Thanks.
- Let's get back to Copenhagen.
- We can't go to Copenhagen now.
Habersaat tried to get you
to look at this case for months.
It's not our job. I think
we can make the 9 PM departure.
Or we could grab some food first,
and take the late ferry. You coming?
Carl.
Why are you stopping here?
- I'm staying.
- What do you mean?
- There's a case here.
- No, you're coming home with me.
Otherwise
there are grounds for dismissal.
- You're firing me?
- Yes.
I mean... yes.
Oh, come on.
Get the fuck out of the car, Carl.
It's your mess to deal with.
Don't call me. I won't pick up.
Hi, Carl.
- Assad? What are you doing here?
- Rose called, so I took the last ferry.
- She told me what it's about.
- I don't even know it's about.
That's why she called me.
She thinks you're an idiot.
- Have you got a single or double bed?
- You're not sleeping here.
Everything's booked.
That's why they gave you the basement.
- I'm a heavy sleeper.
- Sleep heavily in the car. Goodnight.
Carl.
I've had it. Assad! Assad!
Hey, Assad!
Argh, goddammit!
- For Christ's sake.
- What's up, Carl?
- What the hell? You're out here?
- I like sleeping outside.
Yeah, it is nice.
What's up with that Bak?
Did you fuck his wife?
God, no. I sure as hell haven't.
I don't think he even has.
But you and Habersaat
were good friends?
Yes, we were pretty close.
Rowdy young guys,
driving around, drinking beers.
Then what happened between you?
Oh, you know, we just drifted apart.
Christian got one of the local
girls pregnant and stuck around.
- Was it that woman, June?
- Yes.
June.
And Bjarke was their kid?
Wasn't that thirty years ago?
Yeah. Yes, I guess it was.
- Did you know her?
- What?
Did you know her? June?
Rose, you know what?
Let's do it. Let's stay.
But we'll run things without Bak.
We'll do it our way.
Good decision.
Pussy-Carl.
Feel the light on you.
- I feel the light.
- The light is strength.
- Light is strength.
Good, Wanda.
How the hell did she end up
all the way up there?
The report supposes she's biking along,
gets hit, flips over in the air -
- and lands on that branch.
Calculations prove it's possible
if the car was driving fast enough.
Of course.
They are all idiots.
We know she was seen taking off
at 5:15 AM on her red bike.
- Why bike here at the crack of dawn?
- Does the report say anything?
It supposes she was going swimming
off a cliff down that road.
Let me get this straight.
She's hit over there, smack, flies up -
- lands on the branch.
They send tyre tracks to every mechanic
on the island...
Let's get started.
I brought some things from Habersaat's.
We need to go collect more.
I'm going to the folk high school
to ask about Alberte.
- I'll come with you.
- Let's go.
- I've got some business here...
- See you.
Our principal is at a meeting
of the island. Can I help you?
Rose Knudsen, Copenhagen Police.
- Simon Fabian. I'm the concierge here.
- Assad. Detective.
- You mean caretaker, in Danish?
- Exactly.
- How long have you worked here?
- Nearly 11 years.
So you were here
when Alberte Schneider attended?
- Did you know her?
- I strive to know all our students.
- Why?
- So I can better help them.
It's hard being young. A place like this
is full of temptation, you know?
Okay, can you show us her old room?
This was her room.
But she moved out prematurely.
- What was on the walls?
- Her own things, mostly.
She was constantly drawing.
At first, she loved drawing animals...
Especially dead ones.
Talented. Very ambitious...
It was very gloomy.
Over time, it became lighter,
more spiritual.
- You seem to know a lot about art.
- I've picked up a thing or two.
I collected all her things in a box
when emptying her room.
- May we take a look?
- Sure. I'd like to ask her family first.
- Did she date anyone?
- She was somewhat exclusive.
Just a few. She preferred them older,
as far as I remember.
- Anyone in particular?
- I couldn't say, Rose.
That would be disloyal, wouldn't it?
- Disloyal to whom?
- Alberte, of course.
- Thanks. We'll just take a look around.
- Let me know if I can help.
My workshop's in the basement.
Feel free to stop by if you need me.
- Fucking idiot.
- He just thought you were hot.
- Should we listen to the lecture?
- I have to pick up Carl.
Come get me afterwards.
I'm going to speak to some people.
Continue swaying softly...
Press your palms against
your neighbour's.
Turn your faces towards the light.
Feel how the light and heat spreads
through your body.
Feel the heat.
Do you feel the unique energy
that arises between you?
Yes!
Good.
This is what our community is all about.
We capture this energy,
so you can find a path to yourself.
Find out who you were before you let
others decide a direction for you.
Does it feel good?
- Hi, June.
- What do you want?
I saw you at the funeral.
Can we talk?
Come around back.
So, what is it you want?
Are you okay?
Am I okay? Okay with my son just dying?
Or okay with you being here?
I was the one who found Bjarke.
I'm so sorry.
He was... He was a really fine boy.
But that's why you're here, right?
To ask about Bjarke?
- Why do you think that?
- You know why.
Um...
Bjarke was...
Bjarke was your son.
- Bjarke was my son?
- Yes.
You know that.
How the hell could I know that?
What the hell? You can't just say that.
We had an agreement. You would have
it removed. We discussed it.
Yes, we discussed it,
and then you disappeared.
I wouldn't say "disappeared".
Why didn't you call me?
Would it have made any difference?
Would you have come back to play family?
That's not the point.
Maybe I would have.
This is madness.
It's not okay, June.
- I'm about to get married.
- Well, congratulations.
June!
June.
All our stories and traumas
create holes inside us.
And if we don't deal with them
and take responsibility -
- they become powerful enough
to ruin our lives.
But we don't want that.
We want to fill them with light.
Light and love.
So ask yourselves:
What is my story?
And will I let it ruin my life?
Thank you for listening
I know it was long.
Thank you for coming.
Thanks to the school for hosting us.
Did you like what you heard?
Yes. It was... yes.
- Good. What's your name?
- I'm Rose.
Rose.
I'll leave you in peace to absorb.
- Absorb what?
- The light.
- Oh, right.
- But...
You're welcome to stop by sometime.
So, finally you stopped by.
- Bjarke's dead.
- Yeah. A pity, eh?
Was he really my son?
- Says who?
- June.
So, again you come
to her little sister for gossip?
Except I'm not in love with you anymore,
so you don't have much to bargain with.
Fuck off.
Come closer, goddammit,
and I'll tell you what I know.
I know... that Bjarke...
was yours!
It was that bitch Alberte
who killed him.
Alberte killed him?
But she's been dead for five years.
They go swimming every morning
at dawn.
Are you talking about Bjarke?
No, Bjarke's scared of dead animals.
He's scared of everything.
He's weird, but this guy...
You can't tell by looking at him.
But he's frightening.
And he wants her so badly.
What's his name?
Who the hell are you talking about?
You need to go, Carl. You can't be here.
Get out of here!
Leave!
Oh, it's you, stupid dog!
You want a beating?
Scram.
I didn't say anything!
Hello?
Beautiful weapon, eh?
- I came to see Alberte's things.
- Yes. They're right over there.
I haven't spoken to her family yet,
but I'm sure we can work it out.
This is yours?
Where'd you get it?
The history teacher. When he died,
he left me his gun collection.
I'm taking this with me.
- And I'm taking Alberte's things.
- Of course.
Move out of the way, please.
You're very pretty, Rose.
You need to move, now.
Well done, sweetie.
Where's that box?
Have you got anything else
of Alberte's?
- Is this everything?
- Yes, goddammit.
38 stitches? They could hardly
stop the bleeding. 38 stitches.
I heard you.
- It was a bit much, Rose.
- It was self-defence. Understood?
It was violence.
If Bak reports it, you'll be suspended.
- So you're going to fire me? Again?
- Do you get that you went too far?
I get it.
- Do you need to talk?
- What I need is to work. Okay?
Get a hold of yourself.
- What's that?
- A kind of business card.
I... I got an identical coin
at that lecture at the school.
"The Osiris Academy of Enlightenment."
She talked about the sun
and the light...
Each muscle, each fibre,
each cell in your body -
- loosens, relaxes, lets go.
You're not your darkness.
You're not your pain.
- You're not your fear.
- I'm not my fear.
And let go. Let go.
And exhale.
Can we talk in private?
Wanda's gone missing,
and has been for a few days.
Isn't she just in contemplative exile
somewhere?
Have you checked the cleansing room?
No. I haven't.
We were meant to meet
on the North Cliff this morning.
- She never came.
- Why didn't you tell me?
We have a responsibility
for these people.
Give her a little time.
I wondered if you and Assad
would mind -
- dealing with these Osiris people
tomorrow?
Oh, how come?
That woman's a bit too woo-woo for me.
Sure. No problem.
It's a deal.
What's up with you? Are you okay?
- Bjarke...
- Yes?
He was my son.
- What?
- Yes.
Holy shit.
I don't know why I'm saying this.
I think I needed to tell someone.
June just told me. She just...
I didn't know.
It's a bit overwhelming,
to be honest.
Well...
I'll just get this.
- Hi, darling.
- Hi, Mona.
- What are you up to?
- Oh, we're...
- Not much.
- Did something happen?
No, no. Everything's fine.
Just fine.
- What's that sound?
- It's Assad. He's snoring.
We're sharing a room.
I'm about to shoot him.
- I miss you.
- I miss you too.
- What are you doing here?
- I came to see the house one last time.
This is Bjarke's childhood home.
I'm sorry about the other day.
I got so angry. It wasn't fair.
Don't worry about it.
And likewise.
Did Christian know?
That Bjarke was mine?
No.
Did you tell Bjarke?
- Maybe I should have.
- Why?
The two of them were never close.
What did Bjarke mean by what he wrote
on the mirror? "I'm sorry, Dad."
I think Bjarke felt ashamed.
He was special.
He had a diagnosis.
Christian just couldn't accept it.
So Bjarke began taking drugs -
- and was always in and out of rehab.
It ended in disaster.
Eventually Christian stopped
talking to him.
I'm sorry to hear that, June.
Sorry it ended up that way.
Truly.
You knew him best.
Why would he shoot himself that way?
I don't know.
He came out to see me
a few months ago.
All confused,
rambling on about how...
He thought Bjarke had killed Alberte.
- That Bjarke did it? Why?
- I don't know.
We got into a fight about it,
and he broke down.
I think he couldn't take it anymore.
He was seeing ghosts everywhere.
Carl speaking.
I'll be right there.
I have to go.
THE ALBERTE SCHNEIDER CASE
CLOSES DOWN
Let's go.
- That church sure is round.
- Because it's a round church.
Thank you, Carl.
Bornholm is certainly beautiful.
- You've never been here before?
- Nope.
- Not ever?
- No, never.
- It is beautiful, all right.
- Ever been to Baghdad?
- Never? Not ever?
- No, I haven't been to Baghdad.
Why the hell would I go there?
Good. Let me see it again.
Thank you.
- Copenhagen Police.
- Welcome. I'm Pirjo.
We'd like to ask you about Alberte
Schneider. She was a part of this, right?
- Yes, she was.
- Is there someplace we could talk?
Of course.
- What was her name?
- Pirjo.
- Piro?
I remember Alberte perfectly well.
We loved her.
It was horrible, what happened.
Atu and I were devastated.
- Who's Atu?
- Atu is our spiritual leader.
He and I founded this place together.
This is our life's work.
What was Alberte's relation
to the place?
Alberte attended the folk high school,
but... But then she came to us.
- Are you associated with the school?
- No.
We go all over to talk about
what we believe in.
What about this Atu?
Can we talk to him?
Of course you can "talk to this Atu",
but right now -
- he's on the North Cliff
for his morning prayer.
That's where he recharges his batteries.
Well, what else do you do
besides charging batteries?
We praise the light,
and Osiris is our god.
But above all, we work with love.
A whole lot of love.
I'll show you our generator.
It collects power from thousands
of solar panels we've set up.
- You sell the sun?
- It's our contribution to humanity.
We supply ourselves and sell the rest.
- That way, everyone can be here for free.
- How admirable.
It's important for me to state
that we don't exploit members for money.
We take care of them
and fulfil their needs.
And if I wanted to join your club?
Then what?
Do you, Carl?
All you have to do is stay here -
- and spend seven days
in the cleansing room.
I think I'll pass.
This Atu, when will he be back?
Unfortunately,
I don't think he'll be back today.
But I'm sure he'd be happy
to speak to you another time.
I'll show you our solar panels.
I think she seemed all right. That Pia.
Pirjo, Carl.
Prio.
It always makes me depressed.
I've seen enough of it in Iraq.
People wearing identical clothes
thinking they have all the answers.
But they don't.
They never do.
- Yes?
- Marie Frandsen has been hospitalised.
Someone cut her tongue out,
and Bak doesn't want you to know.
Someone cut her tongue out?
Marie,
I'm so sorry about what happened.
But, um...
Can I ask you some questions?
Did you see who it was?
Was it a woman?
It was a man who did it.
Do you know him?
You know him?
Can you try to tell me his name?
I know it's difficult.
S?
Just relax. Relax.
Here. Try writing it.
S, V...
K...
SVK?
That's all? SVK? Is that all you know?
Do you know anything else?
Is Lola here?
No.
How come?
It's time.
It is?
We had guests?
The police.
They asked about Alberte.
What did you tell them?
I told it like it is.
That we loved her.
Yes, we did.
Very dearly.
Welcome to the local news.
Reporting from today's press conference
about the woman -
- whose body washed ashore today.
The body was identified as 26-year-old
former folk high school student -
- Wanda Hoffmann from Hamburg.
Her family has been notified.
It's still too early
to exclude a criminal act.
But the North Cliff is a known
suicide location for young people.
What's going on, Carl? You're running
a full investigation behind my back?
That's correct. The woman was
presumably four months along.
She was pregnant.
Did she jump of her own volition too?
Like Alberte jumped up in that tree?
Fucking lousy police work.
You have no talent, Bak.
- Why did you close that case?
- Shut the fuck up.
The ferry leaves in an hour.
And that blockhead is going with you.
And your psycho bimbo out there.
You're done here.
The thing about you is
that you're dumb.
Good, old-fashioned dumb.
Hillbilly-style dumb.
Christian used to laugh and say:
"Luckily he's too dumb to be corrupt."
- Did he laugh when you fucked June?
- No, but she did when you tried.
Hey, hey, hey. Relax.
Relax!
- Hey! Leave me alone.
- You've got one hour, Carl!
Then you're out of here.
That goes for you too. And you.
This is unbelievable.
Haabersaat shoots himself.
His son OD's.
His sister-in-law loses her tongue.
- And what do we do? We go home.
- No, we're kicked off the island.
I told you it wasn't our case. We have
everything, we'll investigate from home.
What about the caretaker?
Who's following up on the guns?
The guns were registered and legal.
And he's not going anywhere.
You made sure of that, Rose.
But Carl, it is annoying
to deal with your old shit.
Rose, did you tell those cult people
that you're with the police?
No. Why?
- You could become one of them.
- You want her to infiltrate them?
Dig around. Alberte was part of it.
What did they think of her?
Insane, we don't know who they are.
They do yoga and grow vegetables.
Are you afraid she'll choke on a carrot?
The problem is
all of Bornholm's police are trailing us.
When we park on the ferry,
you could sneak away.
- I have a better idea.
- What's that?
Assad, give me your phone.
- Why?
- Just give it to me.
You'll hand in your own.
Call me from this one, once a day.
- Keep a low profile and blend in.
- Okay.
- This is way too risky.
- Can I please just do my job?
- This is a bad idea.
- I'm done with your sensitive bullshit.
- This is not a well-thought-out plan.
- I'm an officer. I can wipe my own ass.
- I'm the cleaner.
- No, you're more than that.
I know who you are.
You're Shirley, Wanda's friend.
Yes.
Are you nervous, Shirley?
Come a bit closer.
And stop. Breathe.
- How long have you been here?
- Four months.
Have you figured out
what you need to let go of?
Not yet.
I have. You don't need to be ashamed
of being a fat girl.
You just have to say it out loud.
Then the pain will go away.
We love you, Shirley. We know that
there's so much to love about you.
You need to say:
"I'm a fat girl."
I know it's hard,
but it will set you free.
- I'm a fat girl.
- Louder.
I'm a fat girl.
Say it like you mean it.
- I am a fat girl.
- I'm a fat girl.
- You are a fat girl.
- I'm a fat girl. I'm a fat girl.
- Enjoy saying it. Enjoy who you are.
- I am a fat girl.
- Enjoy it!
Well done.
Take Wanda's belt with you.
She forgot it last time.
I gave it to her, but it seemed like
it had been hidden beneath the mattress.
You know that they were lovers.
Maybe it's just a coincidence.
- No. She's been gone for four days.
- Then we'll go speak to Atu tomorrow.
- Will you go to the police with me?
- Oh, Shirley.
- Is that really necessary?
- Yes. Something feels very wrong.
Okay. If you feel so strongly about it,
we'll do it.
Thank you.
Oh, poor thing.
- Carl!
- Help Assad.
- Hello.
- Hi, Gordon.
- Gordon, didn't you study art history?
- Sure, for a few semesters.
Take a look at these drawings.
Alberte did them.
She had talent.
Her line is impressive.
It's the same man in all the drawings.
The dimensions are the same.
Same broad shoulders. Narrow waist.
That one down there. It's the only
woman. I think it's a self-portrait.
Is she pregnant?
- Maybe.
- That curve of her belly.
That red pigment beneath
his left armpit repeats too.
- That must've been important to her.
- What do you think it is?
Dunno. A wound? A tattoo, maybe?
- What do you think, Assad?
- Very nice.
Very nice?
Thanks for your input.
He's looking over his shoulder here.
Bloody hell.
- They're siblings.
- Who?
- Pirjo. And that guy Atu.
- What makes you think that?
- This note, among Habersaat's papers.
- Life is short and replete with fear.
Fear of the violence...
The drought,
the power psychoses of old men...
Clowns.
They have the same mother,
from near Stockholm -
- but two different fathers.
One is Danish, the other Swedish.
Pirjo was sent to an orphanage
at the age of four -
- while Atu went to his father
in Copenhagen.
His father was an addict too, so Atu
was later removed by the authorities.
- But are we afraid? Are we afraid?
- No. No!
Pirjo and Atu have no contact
in those years...
No, we aren't afraid.
Because we've stepped into the light.
But they reconnect as teenagers.
They bonded strongly, Habersaat writes.
An "us versus the world" logic.
We know. Us right here, we know.
But right out there, they don't know.
They don't understand that to heal
the world, we have to heal ourselves.
They founded the cult in 2008,
and it quickly gained a following.
And our numbers are growing.
- Just look at this new, beautiful face.
- That's Rose.
You've come to a place where
we thank the sun for life and its gifts.
We're not a religion.
Religions eclipse the sun.
They're humans' attempt
to systematise fear.
We prefer to let go of the fear that's
preventing you, Rose, from being you.
Let's welcome her.
- This is too suspicious, Carl.
- Just because they have other beliefs?
No, because Rose is there, among them.
That's what worries me.
Hi!
I took the liberty to hang some clothes
for you.
- Oh, that's for me? Thanks.
- If you'd like.
Everything here is voluntary.
I'm so glad you came.
But, if you'd like,
I'd love to accept your phone.
Yes, of course.
Here you go.
Come into the light, lovely Rose.
Okay, so we've got Bjarke.
We've got Simon Fabian.
And we've got Stefan von Kristoff.
- We have... Mickey...
- What did you say his name was?
Stefan von Kristoff.
Alberte's art teacher at the school.
- SVK?
- Yes... So what?
Crazy-Marie, whose tongue was cut out,
wrote SVK when I asked her who did it.
- I couldn't figure out who it was.
- What's his deal?
Christian Habersaat believed
that they had a relationship...
In the image in Habersaat's house
she has a tattoo on her calf.
Or, I thought it was a tattoo.
It isn't there in any other photos.
I think it's a signature.
SVK's signature.
The picture of Alberte is an artwork.
- He can't just be some sleazy teacher.
- Former teacher.
He gets fired
due to inappropriate sexual behaviour.
We're onto something here.
Find out where he lives.
Copenhagen Police.
Hey! Copenhagen Police.
Turn that thing off.
Turn it off.
- Are you SVK... What was it?
- Stefan von Kristoff.
We're here regarding Alberte Schneider,
your former student. Is that correct?
Yes, that's me.
And I know why you're here.
You've finally realised that I took
that photo of Alberte in the tree -
- and you're thinking:
"My, my. He must be the murderer."
But I'll have to disappoint you,
because it isn't me.
So let's not waste each other's time.
- Tell us about that picture.
- Not much to tell.
I found Alberte in the tree early
one morning and I took the picture.
That picture was my breakthrough.
I've sold thousands of copies.
- Where do you sell it?
- Online.
- The dark web?
- Yes. I'm big in the dark.
- How did you take the picture?
- With my camera.
What were you doing out there
so early in the morning?
There's something you have to
know about Alberte.
Alberte was by far the most
talented student I ever had.
I was envious of her.
Yes, I envied her a little.
At one point, she wanted
to learn to draw animals.
So we cycled out early in the morning
and found them. Untouched roadkill.
Then we cycled back.
I didn't teach her to draw.
She knew how to do that.
I taught her to see.
I taught her to see beyond the surface.
Did you have a relationship?
- I was in love with Alberte.
- Was it reciprocal?
I thought so.
For a brief while.
Until she got pregnant with someone else.
Pregnant with who?
It wasn't you?
Knocking up a student
isn't a great career move.
I had no career.
That's what was so humiliating.
- How?
- As a man without success. As an artist.
- You know how that stuff works.
- How does it work?
One makes an effort, one toils away,
one hopes, one falls in love.
And then one is left.
One is made a fool of.
And then one finds out
the whole world doesn't give a shit.
So that morning, you found Alberte.
Yes, I found Alberte by the tree.
Dead...
Hit by a car.
And then I took that picture.
By the tree?
You said, "by the tree".
- The police found Alberte in the tree.
- In the tree. I found her in the tree.
- Did you find her in or by the tree?
- In it. I photographed her in the tree.
- That's what I'm saying.
- So why didn't you call the police?
Instead you start taking pictures.
You know what I think?
I think you killed Alberte,
hoisted her into the tree -
- snapped your photos and got famous
among a bunch of necrophile idiots.
Stefan?
The woman called Marie Frandsen,
from Bornholm. You know her?
- No.
- They call her Crazy-Marie.
She says she knows you.
For fuck's sake!
- Good morning, Rose.
- Good morning.
Atu wants to see you.
What exactly is happening?
- Only one.
- Oh, right. Only one.
Pirjo speaks so highly of you, Rose.
Oh, does she?
Thanks.
It made me so eager to meet you.
- Do you like it here?
- Yes.
- It's exciting.
- Do you mind if I just look at you?
Is that weird?
No, no.
Or... It's fine.
Give me your hands.
I'm going to ask you some questions,
but don't answer them.
Okay.
Are you on guard, Rose?
Do you believe me?
Who is your best friend?
Did he take happiness with him?
And leave you with shame?
Do you miss the orgasm?
Can you forgive the evil?
Is the pain greater than the meaning?
Next question I want you to answer:
Are you sad, Rose?
Tell me about it.
- I can't.
- Was it a man?
A man who was meant
to take care of you?
But he didn't take care of you.
He hurt you.
Did he abuse you?
Was it your father?
He went on.
And on, and on, and on...
I couldn't take anymore.
So one day I beat him up.
Thrashed and battered him.
Destroyed him.
He was hospitalised.
When they discharged him
from the hospital...
He hanged himself.
It was me.
- I killed him.
- No, you didn't.
You fought for your life.
He made holes in your soul.
That's the worst thing you can do
to a person.
Now we'll fill them with light.
Look into my eyes. There's no fear.
There's only light.
There's no fear.
There's no fear. There's only light.
No fear, only light.
I'm with you.
I am in you.
The sun is in my hands.
Feel them get warmer.
Warmer, and warmer, and warmer.
There's no fear. There's only light.
No fear, only light.
You're safe.
Sleep.
- Did you buy it?
- Yes, I got it.
- Have you heard from the lab?
- I'm still waiting on the DNA samples.
I'm going to call Rose.
There's been no word for three days.
- Carl, they've called from...
- Just a moment.
It's important. The duty officer says
SVK wants to talk.
- The case isn't complete yet.
- But he wants to confess to something.
- What?
- That he pulled Alberte into the tree.
Then I found her at the roadside,
bleeding from her nose...
And from her head, her ears.
She was so beautiful.
White as a ghost.
Ice cold. She had no pulse.
So I took a picture.
And another.
Then I had the idea of lifting her up
into the tree and arranging her there.
When I did it, I knew: This was
the most beautiful sight I'd ever see.
And that's my crime.
I didn't kill her.
I found her,
and I did something unforgivable.
That's why I didn't contact
the police that morning.
I regret it every day.
I'd like to believe you, Stefan.
For a man so full of regret,
your crime paid off quite well.
- How much did you charge for the photo?
- I haven't sold it yet.
- You said you've sold thousands.
- Not the original.
- Why not?
- Because the piece isn't finished.
- When will it be finished?
- Once I'm finished.
Hi, Klaus.
Just put it there.
Thanks.
You were in Bornholm last Wednesday.
Did you visit Marie Frandsen?
I told you, I don't know who she is.
Marie Frandsen had her tongue cut out
last Wednesday.
Assad bought this on your online portal
for 66,000 kroner.
We've taken some DNA samples.
It's Marie Frandsen's tongue.
Oh? I don't know where
my material comes from.
It could be anyone's tongue.
That's the work. That's the context
in which it should be understood.
Are you sad you never got
your own exhibition?
- What?
- I've made some calls.
You once held such promise
at the Academy of Art. What happened?
How did you end up
at some lousy folk high school?
It must have been a huge defeat.
- My art isn't for everyone.
- You can say that again.
And there's Alberte.
So full of talent.
And so she had to die.
I've done my homework, Stefan.
You're a nobody.
You've always been a nobody,
and you always will be.
Your audience is necrophiliacs
who get off on corpses and cut-off limbs.
There's another thing. You said Alberte
was bleeding from her nose and ears.
It's just that dead people don't bleed.
No.
She was alive when you found her?
Are you finished?
You sure are clever, aren't you?
You've really been practising.
May I borrow your computer?
- For what?
- Go ahead.
Now, take a look
and tell me what you see.
Now tell me, why is SVK big in the dark?
Now she's alive. Now she's dead.
Now she's alive, now she's dead.
A young girl's final breath,
right there.
Right at that moment.
No one's ever done that before.
- She was alive when you put her there.
- She was dying. I didn't kill her.
- You're a sick person.
- I'm SVK.
- Do you think he did it?
- Don't you agree?
- But why won't he confess?
- He's hoping to get off lightly.
- Maybe he hit her by accident.
- It's simple. He was in love with her.
So he killed her and turned her
into an art installation.
I'll just call Rose.
How are you feeling?
- I'm well.
- Good.
Yes.
Now.
Eat, my darling.
Thank you.
Look into my eyes.
Light is strength.
Light is power.
Light is strength. Light is power.
I am the light.
I am light.
The light is in me.
I am light. The light is me.
Use me to drive out the darkness.
I am nothing. Light is everything.
I am nothing. The light is everything.
Light is strength. Light is power.
You're happy.
Are you...?
Finally.
A child of the sun.
Pure in bloodline.
Little sister.
Mother would have been proud.
- Do you think so?
- Yes.
Finally.
We celebrate the conception
of a child of the sun.
A child of a goddess. A child who carries
the light inside. Who is the light.
We celebrate the conception
of a child of the sun.
A child who carries the light inside.
He shall arrive in flesh and blood.
Shall pass on the light to all
who accept it -
- and so all will be possible.
All is possible.
All is possible!
She's turned off her phone.
- Yes?
- Are you sitting down?
- We're in the car. What do you think?
- SVK has escaped.
Escaped? Surely he's being monitored?
I was told
that he banged his head into the wall.
Again and again
until blood sprayed out.
He called a guard
and was sent to the emergency room.
I've sent you a video. Take a look.
The officers guarding the entrance
didn't check for other exits.
So, SVK just gets up
and walks out the back door.
- Just like that?
- Just like that.
- Bloody amateurs.
- Everybody is out looking for him.
- How do I rewind?
- The button on the left.
- What is he saying?
- Something he needs to do.
I have something I need to complete.
I hate unfinished work.
Gordon, are you there?
I think I know where he is.
We're on our way to his workplace.
We need backup, fast.
Welcome!
Tonight, my artwork featuring Alberte
will be completed.
And to think, you are a part of it!
So come closer,
walk towards the light.
We have our masterpieces.
We have men with guns,
we have the whirr of cameras -
- so smile at the darkness.
Because they're watching you.
The whole world is your audience.
Stop.
Yes, where am I?
Look at the shadow.
Is that me?
- Hands up so we can see them.
- Stop when I tell you to.
- Hey.
- Hey, Stefan!
- Was it real? Is it me hanging there?
- Where the hell is he?
No. The shadow isn't real.
Look at it. I've invented him.
The shadow doesn't give a shit.
He does whatever he wants.
He invades other artworks.
Tonight he invades my work,
which consists of Alberte in the tree.
A poor artist who was
at the right place at the wrong time.
And you, primates with guns.
Is that the real story of Alberte?
Is it true?
But what is real? What is true?
Isn't it all just tricks
waiting to be revealed?
Like the life you think you live,
versus the one you're actually living.
Like Alberte who was killed
by a roadside -
- but died in a tree.
How pathetic I was at that school.
What pathetic lives we lead.
But it wasn't me.
It wasn't me who did it!
But you refuse to believe that!
Look towards the light!
How pathetic I was at that school.
What pathetic lives we lead.
- Hands up so we can see them!
- Look towards the light.
- The sun will guide you.
- Put them up.
Farewell.
It was less fun than expected.
But at least
the artwork has been completed.
Do you take that as a confession?
- It's Carl.
- Hi, it's June.
- Did I wake you?
- Yes.
Oh, sorry. I've been up all night
looking at old photos -
- of Bjarke as a baby.
And I was just wondering -
- if you might want
to see some of them?
Sure, I do.
Would you like to come over tonight
for a glass of wine?
I would, but I've left Bornholm.
Oh, well, it was just a thought.
Call me if you come back.
- I will.
- Carl?
- I hope you know that I did my best.
- What?
- Right, of course.
- I'll send you the pictures.
Who was it?
A woman in deep grief.
She just lost her son.
How tragic.
Terribly tragic.
Mona?
He was my son, too.
I knew her thirty years ago.
She just never told me...
- That it was your son?
- Yes.
It stirs up a lot of old stuff.
Okay.
Carl.
You've got to sort it out.
Do what needs to be done,
and come home when you feel ready.
Because I hope you will.
- Superintendent Birkedal.
- It's Carl Mørck.
I was wondering, what did the autopsy
say about Bjarke Habersaat?
It said: "Cause of death, overdose."
- "Full of heroin, vodka and benzos."
- Did you find anything at his house?
Yeah, some old payslips and a computer
with some photos. I haven't looked at it.
- Could you send it to me?
- Do I need to know why?
Nope. And neither does Bak.
You're lucky Bak is an arsehole.
You'll have it in thirty.
PREGNANT
PREGNANT?
Assad, we're going to Bornholm
to see Atu.
- What about Rose?
- We need to get her out of there.
Hi, June. It's Carl. I'm back.
I want to talk to you about some things.
It appears Bjarke was part
of the sun cult.
Do you know anything about that?
I'm afraid Christian was right.
Bjarke was involved in Alberte's murder.
Call me as soon as possible,
and I'll explain.
Rose.
You look happy?
Atu took me for prayers
at the North Cliff. I can't describe it.
- You don't have to. I know.
- Of course.
I've actually spoken to Atu,
and we've decided you're ready.
Ready for what?
- For cleansing.
- Cleansing?
Everyone must undergo
seven days of cleansing -
- to be granted
permanent membership.
- Seven days? That's a long time.
- Yes.
You can ask Lola,
who's been in there for five days now.
We take our shoes off in here.
Holy shit.
You sleep here, of course,
and the toilet's there.
Damn, it's hot.
So's the sun.
- Who are you?
- Who am I? What do you mean?
Are you police?
No.
I think you are.
No, I'm not.
I want to get out.
I let myself in. I hope that's okay.
Hi, Carl.
I'm actually here to speak to Atu.
Or Frank, as he's really called.
He's your brother, right?
What happened?
You're bleeding.
I was practising some karate.
Frank had a relationship with Alberte,
didn't he? A sexual relationship?
He has a sexual relationship
with nearly everyone here.
Bjarke Habersaat.
- Yes?
- What do you know about him?
I first met him at a lecture
at the folk high school.
He was curious, so he came to us.
We took him in and embraced him.
Then he suddenly disappeared.
I heard he was living with his mum.
He was special.
Very... his own.
Unique.
- That Frank, could I talk to him?
- His name is Atu.
Can I talk to him?
- Have you seen Rose?
- No.
Have you seen Rose?
- Atu has an office down here.
- In the generator room? Okay.
After you.
Who knows you're here?
- Hello? Who knows you're here?
- Rose. Only Rose.
Rose isn't here anymore.
Who else knows?
- What did you do to her?
- I haven't done anything.
I liked Rose. You sent her here.
It's your fault.
- Answer me. Who else knows?
- Did you kill her?
Did she get too close to your brother?
So she had to die? Like the others?
You're trivialising me,
and it's disrespectful.
The other girls were pregnant.
- Couldn't you become pregnant?
- Yes, I can become pregnant.
And only I can give birth to his child.
- Are you pregnant now?
- Yes, I am.
You're bleeding.
I can get you to the hospital.
Let me go.
Hello!
Have you seen Rose?
Carl?
Hey, Carl.
Can you hear me?
Hey, Carl! Carl, goddammit!
- Where is she? Pirjo, that bitch.
- She's up there.
I can't find Rose.
Up you go.
Easy, easy. Just a second.
Let me just... Ouch.
Lola? Lola!
Please. Come on.
Yes!
What's happened?
I lost her.
Forgive me.
Come sit with me.
Please.
I've always loved sitting here with you.
Police!
What's the police doing here?
- I think they know.
- Know what?
Everything.
I did it for your sake.
I did it for you.
I don't know what you're talking about.
This has nothing to do with me.
Don't go! Please.
Don't leave me.
Don't leave me. Don't leave me...
It's burning! It's burning!
She's dead. Come on.
Rose!
Rose?
Are you okay?
We can't find Atu.
I think I know where he is.
Atu!
Stay away from the edge.
- Use me to drive out the darkness.
- Hey! Frank.
We have some questions
about Alberte Schneider.
Get away from the edge.
Light is strength.
Light is power.
Carl?
Stay on him.
Don't you dare accuse Bjarke
like Christian did.
My son isn't a murderer.
Don't you get it? They used him -
- because he loved them.
Because for the first time -
- he felt like he belonged somewhere.
For Christ's sake, June.
Bjarke came out to me one evening.
He was completely beside himself.
Alberte was a threat to the cult
because she was pregnant.
- Said who?
- The sister.
She did the talking.
But he, the Sun King,
knows everything.
Bjarke was afraid,
but he also felt chosen.
They had such power over him.
I tried to calm him down,
but I couldn't reach him.
The next morning,
I drove out here to speak to Atu.
I just wanted to talk.
And then I see her -
- and there's no one else around.
It was just an impulse.
It was so easy, it happened so fast.
I just wanted Bjarke
to continue being happy.
I did it for our son.
But they kicked him out anyway.
Atu said the sun didn't want him.
That's why he started taking drugs again.
He was so lonely.
June, get in the car, and stay there.
Yes.
- June? Call an ambulance.
- She needs to be cut out, Carl.
Copenhagen Police.
There's been a crash...
Carl.
Carl, we need to leave.
- I'm sorry, June.
- Move!
- Hi.
- Hi, Gordon.
Hello, Gordon.
It's all coming down.
And the boxes go in the basement.
Rose?
You okay?
Yes.