I'm glad we beat that forest dragon
without any losses.
Those ramparts you made
served their purpose.
That's true. Without them,
it might've been a different story.
I have a proposal, Lord Van.
Now that you've made
those sturdy ramparts,
why not turn your attention
to city planning next?
City planning?
You mentioned before that I should aim
to build a city for 10,000 to live in.
Yes.
To accomplish that and fashion an
attractive city, we'll need new residents.
I see.
Lord Van.
Bell and Rango have returned with folk
from the Mary Chamber of Commerce.
They said they'd buy the materials
from the forest dragon.
Great.
First, we'll sell the dragon materials.
Then we'll make a city
everyone can enjoy living in.
EASYGOING TERRITORY DEFENSE
BY THE OPTIMISTIC LORD
EPISODE 7: EARNEST MERCHANTS
AND RECEIVING A PROUD TITLE
I wonder how much the Mary Chamber
of Commerce merchants will buy them for.
It's a dragon.
A large forest dragon at that.
Its scales, claws, fangs, and eyes
are all in pretty good condition.
You'll probably get at least 100 platinum.
If I remember correctly, one platinum
is worth around 100 million yen.
So 100 would mean...
A dragon is worth 10 billion yen?!
Did I just win the jackpot?
I had my doubts, but...
It's real, all right.
So what do you think?
Lord Van. Please entrust these materials
to the Mary Chamber of Commerce.
We're the most reputable traders
and have the royal family's backing,
so we'll buy them from you
at the highest price you'll get, too.
That's great news.
By the way, how much can we sell them for?
Given the current market,
I'd say about 60 platinum.
Huh? I thought I'd won the jackpot.
Wait there a sec.
I'll consult with Bell and Rango.
Oh, please hold on a minute.
Those brothers are still young
as merchants go. We can offer a proper—
Sounds like we might not get
as much as I thought.
They quoted me 60 platinum.
That's crazy.
It's obvious this is
all of the highest quality.
You imbeciles!
You two are part of the Mary Chamber
of Commerce, too, y'know. Play along!
H-Hold on a second.
As merchants, we should give
a proper appraisal.
No other merchants are coming
to this remote village for a whole year!
Even if we only offer 60 platinum,
that brat has no choice but to sell.
Got it? Now shut up and do as we say!
I can hear you all as well.
Well, one platinum is worth 100 million.
I guess I can't blame them for haggling.
Even so...
We brothers aim to do things fairly,
no matter who we're dealing with
or what we're negotiating over.
We believe that will lead
to greater future profit.
And with Lord Van,
it'll definitely pay off!
You dolts...
When the president learns of this, you'll
be kicked out of Mary Chamber of Commerce.
Imbeciles.
They'll regret this!
Are you sure? You'll be kicked out
of the Mary Chamber of Commerce.
Yes.
It was the only choice.
Then, hey...
Why not found your own trading company?
Huh?!
You make it sound easy.
I-Is it difficult?
You have to fulfill three conditions
to establish a trading company.
First, pay the Merchants' Guild
registration fee.
Second, own your own shop.
And third, get an endorsement
from a titled noble.
The first two are easy enough,
but that last one's an issue.
The only person with a title
who's likely to help us is...
Sure, I don't mind.
Huh? You'll do it?
I hear the Mary Chamber of Commerce
is favored by the royal family.
Won't they harass you?
Think about it.
If I found a small trading company
as a newly elevated noble,
recognizing it is no skin off their noses.
If anything, it'd be a bad look
for the royal family if they didn't.
I see.
Besides, I have no land
or knights of my own,
so if I want to climb the ladder,
I need to do things
that will get people talking.
If I do this, word will spread that
I helped two earnest merchants.
In that case, why not say
you defeated that dragon, Panamera?
People will talk about that,
and it means my family won't find out.
Your thought process
has the oddest blind spots.
Dragons are rarely slain.
Even if I said I'd killed it, they'd want
to know in detail how I'd managed it,
and their own investigations
would lead to you anyway.
What will I do if my family
summons me home?
There's one way to avoid that.
Huh?
It's simple. Get yourself a title.
A title?
All nobles have a title.
I've worked my way up
from knight, the lowest title,
but since you're the son of a marquis,
they'd probably make you
a baron to start with.
Lord Van, get yourself a title
and found a new house.
What is this woman saying?
You just need to declare
that you slew the dragon.
All I really did was pin it down.
No way. That would make me
really stand out, wouldn't it?
And that dissatisfies you?
You can become famous for being
the eight-year-old who slew a dragon,
and use that achievement
to earn a title.
That said...
I do understand how you feel, young man.
When I first earned my title,
I gained more enemies,
and people trying to use me
came out of the woodwork.
However...
I reduced all of them to ash.
To ash?
So if any new enemies show up, don't
hesitate to fire your ballistae at them.
A dozen corpses in your wake
will stop people opposing you.
I just learned a terrifying tip
for navigating life.
But if I claim it was all my doing,
you can't use it to support
your own bid for promotion.
Young man.
Are you worried about me?
I don't think I've done anything to have
an-eight-year old worrying about me,
so perhaps I misheard.
No, I didn't mean it.
In fact, I'm now worried
about my own safety.
Please don't eat me.
You always have an amusing retort.
Don't worry. I won't eat you
for another five years.
So to help you grow even bigger,
I'll let you take the glory
for slaying this dragon.
I don't believe it.
I apparently only have
five years left to live.
Huh?! Lady Panamera?!
She'll endorse us?!
That means...
Yup. You can found your own
trading company, Bell and Rango.
All right!
Getting down to it, will you please
sell those dragon materials to us?
Of course.
We want to repay you for all you've done
for us, so how does 130 platinum sound?
That much?
Thanks. We have a deal.
Right!
Okay, let's go to the royal capital
to sell all this stuff.
There aren't any carriages?
Right. The Mary Chamber of Commerce
merchants just left with it.
What were they thinking?
They're waiting for you
to come crying to them.
If you can't transport the goods,
you have no choice but to listen to them.
Then, I'll make a new
carriage for you two.
You will?
In that case, you can have
my warhorse to pull the carriage.
They're well-trained, and their stamina
and speed are on another level.
I bet Bell and Rango are
regretting their decision now.
Those foolish brothers.
They'll come crying to us in no time.
Wh-What's that?
Viscountess Cayenne?
That was Bell and Rango, wasn't it?
Why were they with the viscountess?
H-Hold on a sec...
With the cooperation of a noble, they
could start their own trading company!
No way!
KINGDOM OF SCUDERIA
ROYAL CAPITAL, AUDIENCE CHAMBER
So the social climber is here again.
Still, I assumed you had come
to petition me for a higher rank.
Yet you want me to grant
a title to someone else?
That's correct...
King Dino.
KINGDOM OF SCUDERIA'S KING
DINO EN TSORA BELLRINET
Viscountess Cayenne, I do not see
this man you seek a title for.
The man in question is the lord
of a remote village.
He's currently shoring up his village, so
he couldn't make it to the royal capital.
Why would you recommend
such a man to the nobility?
For his great deeds so far, and
his potential that overshadows them.
Oh?
Given your prowess, for you to recommend
him means I can expect great things, yes?
Still, what manner of feats could
he have achieved in a village so remote,
we haven't stationed troops
or knights there?
He slew a forest dragon.
What? Is that even possible?
And he "slew" it? He didn't drive it off?
Is this lord an elemental mage?
No, his magical aptitude
is for production magic.
Production magic?
Who is this man?
The son of Marquis Fertio,
Van Nei Fertio.
A lord who is barely eight years old.
Oh? An eight year old child
in charge of a remote village?
Give me more details.
I will. The moment that young boy arrived
in the village he was to rule over,
he found it under attack by bandits.
However, he protected the village
and killed the bandits
with the few subordinates
and adventurers escorting him.
Aha. So he joined battle
and triumphed at such a young age?
After that, the young boy
used his production magic
to surround the village
with walls, put in a moat,
rebuild the ramshackle homes,
and improve the village's defenses.
Then, this dragon attacked that village?
Yes. I assisted in the slaying of the
dragon, but all I did was pin it down.
Lord Van and his subordinates
used their strength
to slay it without suffering
a single casualty.
That sounds hard to believe.
This is a fang from the slain dragon.
I'd love for you to
come see, Your Majesty.
To see how much this village has changed
in its short time under Van's stewardship.
I'm sure a man as wise as Your Majesty
would make him the lord
of a territory even greater in size
for the sake of our nation's defense.
Interesting.
Van Nei Fertio, huh? I would like
to meet him as soon as possible.
Let it be known that
Van Nei Fertio slew a dragon!
To honor this achievement,
he has been made a baron!
That's Marquis Fertio's son.
The fourth son they called a prodigy?
A child slew a dragon?
Well, young man,
things are about to get interesting.
You'd better be grateful.
After Panamera and
the others left the village,
I remade the uniform houses
into something fancier,
then reconstructed the village center.
All in all, my city building
was proceeding smoothly.
Then, in addition to that...
I built some towers.
They're incredibly tall.
And you've made two of them.
Yup.
This one's Oligo Tower, and the one
on the other side is Grape Tower.
Towers serve as symbols of a settlement
and allow us to detect enemies from afar,
so this has also fortified our defenses.
Everyone in the village can
now enjoy their lives in peace.
Lord Van, I'll prepare
your lunch immediately.
Oh, hey. Why don't we go eat lunch
at the top of the tower?
Let's dig in.
Till, your homemade egg
sandwiches are delicious.
I'm glad you like them.
Yes, they're not bad.
The view from the top
of this tower is great, too.
Now that we have
proper buildings and facilities,
it might be time to start
officially calling this a town.
First, it was Van Village,
and now, I bet you're planning to call it
something silly like Van Town, aren't you?
What's wrong with that?
I think Van Town would be a lovely name.
It would be fitting.
Van Town does have a nice ring to it.
Seriously, I'm ending this conversation
before you actually start calling it that.
Everyone just says whatever they want.
Right, Lady Arte?
Uh, yes.
U-Um, Lord Van?
What is it?
I-If you don't mind, could you
just call me Arte from now on?
Huh? Are you sure?
Y-Yes. I think that will make it easier
for you to speak to me.
Okay. "Arte" it is.
Even though she asked me to say that,
she looks embarrassed.
Okay, everyone.
Would we all like some post-meal dessert?
Dessert?
Ta-da!
Whoa!
Cake!
- Did you make this, Till?
- Yes.
But how?
After Bell and Rango
set up shop in the village,
I was able to get all the ingredients
I needed to make a cake.
Wow, really?
Man.
This might be turning
into a pretty nice village.
It's delicious.
Indeed.
So delish.
It's sweet.
Huh? You're not having any, Till?
I got a bit too into baking cakes lately,
so I've been eating cake every day.
And my weight is in a perilous situation.
I-I see.
Hmm?
What's the matter, Khamsin?
Lord Van, look over there.
They don't look like
soldiers or adventurers.
I wonder who they are.
U-Um, is this village Seatoh?
Seatoh?
I hear a people called the Seatoh lived on
this land before there was a village here.
As a result, many refer
to this village as Seatoh.
So this village did have a name all along?
Then, it's really true.
It's changed so drastically,
I still find it hard to believe.
So what brings you here?
We've come from the neighboring village.
We are taxed heavily but we have
few young people to do the work.
We can hardly make ends meet.
So we came here to talk it over
with the folk in Seatoh.
Why do you have few young people?
Our young ones didn't choose
to leave the village.
They were taken by the count to bolster
his forces in preparation for war.
Oh, so they're from a village
in Ferdinatto County?
I really shouldn't be welcoming
in people from another domain,
but I'm fairly sure these people
risked their lives to make it this far.
Then, what would you say
to relocating here?
Y-You mean you'd take us in?
But none of us have any money.
That won't be an issue if you don't
have to pay taxes for a while.
We have food, and I can
prepare homes for you.
I-Is this heaven?
How many villagers are there in total?
Only ten of us made the trip today,
but our village's population is about 300.
Will you be all right
with one house per family?
I can't believe it.
This sounds like a dream.
Okay, I'll get a few adventurers to go
with you to escort all the villagers here.
Is it really all right for us
to accept such kindness?
I'll also lend you some carriages
to help with your belongings.
Oh, that won't be necessary.
We have cows, so they can carry all that.
Cows? You have cows? Dairy cows?
The county has rich pastures,
so we have ten cows.
Wow. Cows, cows, cows!
They produce milk. We can make
cheese, butter, and so on.
This could be the village's
major new industry.
That's right!
Still, Lord Van sure is generous.
He's taking in 300 people, just like that.
Plus, the reward for this quest
is way too generous.
Hey, you two.
We're almost there, so keep a sharp eye
on our surroundings, will you?
Last time, you two were
so absorbed in idle chitchat,
we were attacked by
that forest dragon. Remember?
Yeah, but that...
That wasn't our fault.
No talking back!
Go on now! Back to your posts!
Yes, ma'am.
Are you okay?
Yes, thank you.
We're almost there. Hang in there.
Honestly, I was against this.
We're going from the middle of nowhere
to somewhere even more remote.
It's true.
You are heading to a more remote village.
But this particular
remote village is paradise.
Welcome to Seatoh.
I'm sure you're all worn out
from your journey,
so fill up on barbecued meat,
then get a good night's rest
in the homes I've prepared for you.
U-Um, i-is it really okay to eat it?
Yup. Go eat your fill.
Till?
Leave it to me.
Come on. Over here.
Everyone, help yourselves.
There's so much meat.
Is it really okay to eat this?
- It's delicious.
- Yum!
It's so good.
It was hard work preparing homes
and a barbecue for 300 people,
but it was well worth the effort.
Um, my lord?
Is there, um, any work for us to do?
Work?
We want a way to earn a living.
None of us have any savings.
Oh, right. Everyone's
wracked with anxiety.
Well...
In that case, could I ask you to help run
the inn or the new shops we're opening?
I'll also need people to help
cultivate some new fields.
We can handle the fields,
but we've never run businesses before.
It'll be fine.
You can leave calculating the money
to those who can do it,
so all you have to focus on
is what you're capable of.
Ever since Lord Van came,
life in this village has improved so much,
you'd hardly recognize it.
So we'll all do everything we can to
help you enjoy your lives here as well.
Is this really all right, though?
You're doing so much for us.
Till, I think it's about time.
Sure.
Here you go.
- What are those?
- Whoa.
They're shortcakes.
I asked your village chief to lend us some
of your cows' milk to make fresh cream.
What is this?
They look delicious.
Thank you so much!
You're doing us a favor by moving here,
so we're just helping each other.
Soon enough, we'll have
a trading company in this village.
This village will develop even further
and get even more comfortable,
so I hope you'll all relax
and enjoy your new lives here.
I think I might actually be able
to live a good life here.
Me, too.
- Same here.
- Me, too! Me, too!
Everyone had their hands full
just trying to survive,
but they have hope now, and their minds
have turned to how to enjoy their lives.
Lord Van.
The village's population has grown,
but we're still a long way
from being a city of 10,000.
You'll need to continue
developing this village.
All right.
I'll keep working hard
on my task of city building!
NEXT EPISODE: A POSTAPOCALYPTIC BAND'S
ROWDY DUNGEON EXPLORATION