This is the new girl group
the company is pushing for now,
SESPA.
The sales they made in 10 days
are what you couldn't make in 2 years.
Actually, I'm really scared...
I'm scared of losing my fans...
and all of you.
Mr. Lee.
Our team works well together
and we have a lot of stage experience.
If you can't achieve the goal this time,
Wonder-X will be disbanded.
Understand?
[SE Entertainment's Corridor]
Have you heard?
Wonder-X might be disbanded.
Really?
They just won the Best Performance Award.
Their music festival performance
caused quite a buzz too.
What's the point of awards?
They're not earning money.
They don't have that many fans,
much less loyal fans.
Their album sales are poor.
The commercials they get
are small ones too.
I heard after evaluation, the company
thinks they're not profiting that well,
so it's better to disband them
and transfer the members
with potential to other groups.
The rest will be terminated or ignored.
That's such a pity.
Jung Ji-eun is a good dancer.
Her fancam views are...
We need to show our best.
That would be better.
That's what Mr. Lee likes.
The proposal is almost ready.
Let's talk to Mr. Lee now.
We did our best,
so there's nothing to regret.
-Mm!
Let's go together
and let Mr. Lee see
our value.
Sounds good.
I'm sure we can convince him.
Wonder-X won't be disbanded.
Let's go for it!
Go for it!
Let's do our best.
Let's do it.
Of course.
You're here.
The decision about Wonder-X's disbandment
will be made soon.
There's no need to say more.
Mr. Lee,
this is the proposal we prepared.
We modified it ourselves.
It can improve our team's business value.
Proposal?
What's the point?
You barely have fans,
and your albums are not selling.
You barely have any profits
made through ads.
The ROI is too low.
Mr. Lee.
We can upload promotional videos
on social media.
We can also create buzz
by working with beauty influencers.
We can also attract fans
through variety shows.
Variety shows?
Promotional videos?
It's not that simple.
The new group SESPA's album sales
reached 10 times yours
the moment they made their debut.
As an idol group,
they are much better than you.
Mr. Lee.
Our team works well together.
We also have a lot of stage experience.
At the last concert,
our fancam received way more views
than popular groups.
Our dance moves are also in-sync,
and we have good dance skills.
As long as you give us a chance,
we can definitely do better.
Mr. Lee.
Give us just 3 months.
We guarantee that the number
of our social media followers will double,
and our album sales will increase
by more than 50%.
If these plans fail,
we will
do as you instruct us to.
Are you confident?
Yes, we are.
We'll do our best.
We will do our best.
Sure.
I'll give you just 3 more months.
But let me make it clear:
the company won't invest any more in you.
You'll have to fight
for your opportunities.
If you can't achieve the goal this time,
Wonder-X will be disbanded.
Do you understand?
Thank you, Mr. Lee.
We won't let you down.
Thank you,
Mr. Lee.
Thank you.
Thank you!
Very well.
Shall we practice dancing?
Okay.
-Okay.
5, 6, 7, 8.
I'm exhausted.
Shall we paste one goal each?
Okay!
Ji-eun.
[Reach the goal within 3 months.
-Wonder-X, Jung Ji-eun]
Nice!
Okay!
Oh, right!
Gather over here.
All right.
Our chance
has come.
We must do our best
and achieve our goal.
Let's do it!
Shall we film our practice videos
and upload them to our official channel?
That's a great idea!
If we follow the plan,
we should be able to accomplish
all of that.
That's right.
Wonder-X, let's go!
Never give up!
-Let's go!
Oh, right.
Shall we take a video
for our fans too?
Sounds good!
Things like live streams and Q&amp;A—
our fans will like it.
Yes.
Good idea.
Come on.
One, two, three.
1, 2, 3.
[The next day]
Have a look.
This is the new girl group
the company is pushing for now,
SESPA.
The sales they made in 10 days
is what you couldn't make in 2 years.
The disbandment of Wonder-X
won't be a hard decision
for the management to make.
The entertainment industry is cruel.
You'll be eliminated if you don't shine.
Think it through.
Unless there's a miracle...
[Mr. Jang, where are you?]
[I'm almost there.]
[You'll come pick me up, right?]
Jessica is here. I have to go pick her up.
You guys,
pack up and leave in 5 minutes.
The practice room
will be used by SESPA tonight.
The company's performance this year
depends on them.
Let's call it a day for now.
There's no point in practicing.
Right, Yebin-unnie?
The company is going to disband us!
What are we practicing for?
Who said we're disbanding?
Unnie.
The whole company knows.
The employees, other groups,
and even the trainees know...
Our ROI is low.
And we don't have many fans.
There's no need to keep us around, Unnie.
It's just a rumor.
Wonder-X will never disband.
How do you know?
Are you the CEO?
Is it something you can decide?
This is a group I've been protecting
since I was a trainee.
Our dream,
passion, sweat,
and the award we won together—
I'll protect it no matter what.
Don't cry.
Practice hard.
I will protect this team.
We will stand on the stage together.
Don't cry.
[Because of SESPA's appearance,
Wonder-X has to move to the warehouse]
Shall we start with cleaning up?
Gosh, SESPA.
Darn it.
If it weren't for them...
Minah, what's wrong?
SESPA.
Have some water.
Yebin-unnie.
I think Minah-unnie needs some rest.
You don't look
that well either.
Seriously.
Bin.
Are your hands still shaking?
Ji-eun.
I'm scared.
Minah must be scared too.
I...
I thought I'd be fine holding it in.
Lean on me.
It's okay.
No matter what the company's decision is,
our team
will not disappear.
I'm heading out for a while.
Now?
The typhoon is coming soon.
Yeah.
I'm meeting a producer I know.
I have to show him
our new song and proposal quickly.
Can't you go tomorrow?
I want to do things
as fast as I can.
I'll go with you.
No need.
Just in case.
Let's go together.
I'll make it quick.
[Wonder-X:
the birth of a new 3-member girl group]
[The team: Kang Yebin,
Jung Ji-eun, Song Minah]
[Debut story and goal]
[3-member girl group]
[The team]
[Kang Yebin]
[Jung Ji-eun]
[Song Minah]
[Wonder-X]
Bin.
Why are you all wet?
Why didn't you take a taxi?
Where's your phone?
It was raining too heavily
I couldn't get a taxi.
My phone died too.
Today...
Let's take a shower first.
I'll get you your pajamas.
I...
failed today too.
What failed?
The producer said
Wonder-X is in danger.
We have few fans
and our performances are just so-so.
He told us
to be mentally prepared for disbandment.
Let's take a shower now
and talk tomorrow, okay?
I feel useless.
I can't protect
anything I want to.
Don't say things like that,
okay?
You're already doing your very best.
Take a hot bath
and call it a day for today.
Let's talk tomorrow.
[Visual and performance strategy]
Bin.
Why are you shouldering everything?
You're already tired enough.
Because there's no other way.
If I break down,
you and
our whole team will...
Bin, you're not alone.
You have Minah
and me.
Ji-eun.
Actually, I'm really scared.
I'm scared of losing my fans...
and all of you.
Bin.
Don't be afraid.
You're not alone.
You have me.
I'm not going anywhere.
Hmm?
I'll always be by your side.
Let's get through this together.
Okay?