You!
And you!
You are the student committee, but you are the ones who breached the rules.
What are the rules for if you don’t keep them?
You’re lucky no one caught you
or all of us would be screwed.
But Miss Al,
we didn’t get caught, did we?
Stop backtalking.
Even though you didn’t get caught,
I, as the student president, will punish you guys myself.
Every one of you must clean the student committee room for the whole semester.
Don’t even let me see PM2.5 dust in here.
But…
No ‘buts.’
Unless you want toilet cleaning duty too.
Do you want that?
Hello.
Good morning, seniors.
Oh.
I guess you guys are busy.
I’ll leave you to it then. Goodbye.
You too, Tinh.
Come here.
Hey, Alpha.
Don’t punish him.
We, seniors, should take responsibility.
Fine.
There will be no punishment for you because you’re younger.
Really?
But…
you must be Mawin’s assistant for the whole semester.
Huh?
(Though I could get through last night without punishment,)
(there’s still a big deal waiting for me today.)
(I almost forgot that I have a basketball game with Blossom.)
How’s your foot?
Does it feel any better?
Mhm.
It’s been better.
Ongsa.
Are you really competing with Blossom?
Mhm.
I must collect all the fees.
How about I try to talk to her?
It’s okay.
I’ll handle it.
But your foot hurts.
You can’t play.
(Why am I always the one who gets help from Sun?)
Thank you, Sun,
but this time I want to try it myself
without any help.
Then do your best.
I’ll be cheering for you.
Mhm.
(I hope Sun develops a more positive opinion toward you, Ongsa.)
Ongsa, do your best.
Fight hard, girl.
Don’t back down.
You can do it.
Ongsa!
Ongsa, keep fighting.
Ongsa, hang in there.
Go, girl!
- Ongsa, go!
- Ongsa, keep going.
Ongsa, keep fighting.
I’m giving you blessings…
Ongsa, go, go.
One point for Blue.
Blossom, you did great.
It’s okay, Ongsa. Try again.
You can do it. Start over.
Go, Ongsa.
Ongsa, keep fighting.
Keep fighting, Ongsa.
Hey!
Two points for Blue.
Ongsa, are you hurt?
Ongsa, keep going. You can do it.
Ongsa, fight her.
Ongsa, keep fighting.
You can do it.
Keep going.
Keep trying, Ongsa.
You can do it.
Hey!
Hey, Blossom, are you okay?
Ongsa, the ball.
Get the ball.
Ongsa, hurry up.
Shoot.
Ongsa, you can do it.
Go, Ongsa.
Shoot it.
Ongsa, shoot.
Ongsa, go for it.
You can do it.
Fight!
Whoo-hoo.
The game ended.
Blue wins by 8-0.
(In the end, you’re still a loser as always, Ongsa.)
Here.
The fee.
But I lost.
How could an amateur beat a member of the school team, right?
Your leg also hurts.
I was impressed you could steal the ball from me at all.
For such a timid person, you’re one hell of a fighter.
Here.
Thank you.
(At least you did it, Ongsa.)
(You have collected all the money.)
Hello, Aylin.
Can you hear me?
I guess you can.
I’m done with the basketball game.
Waiting for you in front of Building 3 as always.
Do you hear me?
You do.
See you.
Ongsa.
See? I told you you could do it.
But I lost.
I could collect all the money because Blossom was nice enough.
But it’s because you didn’t give up.
What you did today was so cool.
(Cool?)
(Did she just say I was cool?)
Why are you making that face?
Don’t you believe me?
Um…
No one has ever said I was cool before.
Really?
Then listen to me carefully.
What you did today was so damn cool.
So cool that you’d attract all the girls in our school if you were a guy.
(Right. I forgot.)
(You’re not a guy, Ongsa.)
You’re exaggerating.
It’s true.
Not exaggerating.
Ongsa, you’re the coolest.
I’m headed home now.
See you tomorrow.
Get home safe.
Bye-bye.
Are you all right, human?
It’s nothing.
Is it about Sun?
Hey!
How did you know that?
I took a wild guess.
Aylin.
Please don’t tell anyone about this.
About human Ongsa liking human Sun?
Hey!
What?
Ongsa, you like Sun?
Hey!
Our Astronomy Club will be holding Astrological Fortune Readings.
You two must be the fortune tellers on the Club Fair day.
Aylin and I?
For our Astronomy Club,
keep fighting.
Fight.
Borrowing power from the stars to foretell fortune requires you to sell the power of your own soul.
Ongsa, Do you want my help with Sun?
Sun, would you like your fortune told?
I was born on Friday.
Ongsa was born on Tuesday.
That’s why I felt like we hit it off especially well.
Our fortunes are compatible.
Let’s say I like someone.
How likely is it that the person will reciprocate my feelings?
Very likely.
That person must like you very much.