CHAPTER 1:
I AM A WEB NOVEL WRITER
Yeon-hui had been friends with Ho
since childhood.
HO
BITTER-SWEET HEART
He's a man of few words and can be blunt,
but the way he takes care of her
makes her heart swoon.
She met Jin in college.
JIN
RAY OF SUNSHINE
He's so sweet you'd think he's an angel.
Fans are split between
shipping YeonHo
and YeonJin
as the ultimate couple.
But personally…
I told you never to show your face again.
You drive me so crazy I can't stand it.
Why?
Why on earth?
Why couldn't we have met sooner?
…I'm all in on HoJin.
-Idiot.
-The desperation in their eyes
from having to hide their true feelings.
Sorry.
Hello, dad.
What did you say?
I've decided to remarry Geum-yeong.
From now on, you and Ho are brothers.
I hope you'll get along
as well as you do now.
Hang on a moment.
I can't take this anymore.
Are you out of your mind?
Hey! I'm talking to you!
Sorry?
Didn't you say this is the last episode?
-Right.
-Yet you're pulling this kind of crap?
I've put up with everything so far,
but the story is dragging so much.
How can they only find out
they like each other in the last episode?
And then out of the blue
they become brothers?
What a crock!
Well, we might get a season two.
Are you insane?
You think you'll get a season two
after this nonsense?
Nobody even wants to read your novel!
That's harsh.
Is that her?
The hack author whose characters,
plot, structure and writing
are all a complete mess?
Where is she?
-Over there.
-Arrest her.
Hands up! Step away from the keyboard!
Don't touch that!
-What…
-Hands in the air!
What did I do?
You know as well as anyone
how much your novel sucks.
Writing a novel that sucks
isn't a crime!
Oh, yes it is!
Article 1, Clause 1 of the Web Novel Act.
Boring authors shall be punished.
Accordingly, Yeo Eui-ju,
I'm arresting you.
No. You can't.
No.
No!
I really thought I'd been arrested.
PAZER WEB NOVEL PORTAL
I'm…
…a writer.
My genre is…
BL.
BL: ABBREVIATION OF BOYS' LOVE
PRIZE
WRITING CONTEST
My pen name is
Imuk.
My novel…
THEY CAME TOGETHER
…has only been read by me.
The one with two views
was just a random click.
They could've at least
left a snarky comment.
ZERO REVIEWS
Yeo Eui-do.
The only person
who knows I write BL web novels.
Coke.
YEO EUI-DO
COKE ADDICT BROTHER
He's using it to blackmail me.
EPISODE 1
What am I going to write next?
I can't afford another bomb.
Your leg must be sore. It's really tight.
Did you shower?
You smell great.
Is that what I bought for you?
You're so tense. We'd better keep at it.
Get up.
Let's work on your top.
Not here!
Then let's go inside.
It's too early for that!
Did you sleep well last night?
I couldn't sleep at all because of you.
Because you weren't there.
Tonight,
-I don't want to be alone.
What's up with her?
Is she here for me?
-Wasn't that a dude?
-It was a girl.
-Are your eyes okay?
-They're fine.
What's up with Dong-ju?
He got a cramp.
Why did Gi-jeon carry him?
For the exercise.
CHAPTER 2:
DO YOU KNOW WHY STUDENTS WEAR UNIFORMS?
EUI-JU'S HOUSE
SHIN, YOON-JU, EUI-JU, EUI-DO, SUNI
Hey, mom,
have the twins who used to live
at the white house move away?
Have they?
It looks like a bunch of guys
have moved in.
Really?
I heard the twins' dad got promoted.
Maybe he transferred to HQ.
Why didn't they say goodbye?
What about us?
When are we moving?
Don't you like it here?
I turned down a promotion.
Eat up.
Pervert!
I'm done.
Have some more.
If I have more, I'll be late.
See you later.
-Have a good day!
-Watch out for cars!
I said I'd go by myself.
Why are you being so stubborn?
Let's go together.
I hate the smell
of the air freshener in that car.
Hang on.
I'll go with you.
Forget it. Mind your own business.
What's this?
Isn't that those guys from yesterday?
Hey, Ga Woo-su!
I can't.
-You know I can't.
-Give it a rest!
Unbelievable!
You're annoying me.
A lovers' spat?
Just listen to me. Please.
Until when?
Let's just take the car and make it easy.
How long do I have to do what you want?
I said I'd go by myself.
What an asshole!
The guys are almost ready.
Just give them a minute.
What a nice guy.
He'll be kicking himself later.
Don't be such a drama queen.
-Woo-su!
-I hope it's not stuck to my forehead.
Wait here.
What a hottie!
You were filming.
-Sorry?
-I saw you. Delete it.
I wasn't.
I was just trying to see
if I had a bug on my face.
I'm not the kind of person
who films people on the sly.
I'll let you slide
if you apologize and delete it,
so think wisely.
But I wasn't filming you.
-What's going on?
-She was filming us.
Probably going to upload it
for the comments.
ZERO COMMENTS
For the comments?
Yeah, comments!
I'd love some comments.
The more, the better.
I didn't get a single snarky comment
despite the soapy ending.
Do you know how humiliating it is
to have zero comments for 100 episodes?
Don't change the subject.
Give it a rest.
You weren't filming?
No.
She said she wasn't.
I saw her. Hiding like this.
I want to check.
What are you doing?
-Let go.
-Don't do it.
I didn't film you.
No, no.
No, please, no.
The screen's cracked.
What are you going to do about this?
How could you do this!
I can't believe this!
You should have just shown me.
I'm sorry, kid.
He's very sensitive about being filmed.
That's why he overreacted.
We'll compensate you for the damage.
Forget it!
Do you know why students wear uniforms?
So they can be identified.
If any footage of this turns up online,
I'll make you regret it.
Asshole!
Hey!
Are you still here?
Just get in and come with us
or we'll be late.
Give me a second.
Slow down.
JEONJU MURIM GIRLS' HIGH
CHAPTER 3:
SO, THAT ASSHOLE IS MY…
Hey, Eui-ju!
My best friend, Choi Go-ya.
A gifted artist.
She's been dating continuously
since sixth grade.
I think I've put on two kilos.
All I did was eat and sleep.
Yikes! What happened?
Some guy moved in next door.
He thought I was filming him
and asked to see my phone.
I tried to stop him and…
And you just let him be?
You should have made him pay to repair it.
Or at least got his number to hound him.
I didn't want any more to do with him.
He looked like a complete jerk.
What? Who is it?
My ex.
You broke up again?
You said he was the hottest guy
at your art academy.
When am I finally going to meet
my last love?
Must be nice.
I haven't even met my first love.
Is the reason my novels are lame
because I've never dated?
Well…
Dating might be helpful.
But the more you do it,
the more it bursts your bubble.
Since you still have
a rose-tinted view of dating,
wouldn't that make you write better?
-You think?
-Yeah.
Why? Is it not going well?
You said you were done.
Yeah, I kind of am.
When can I read it?
You won't tell me the title
or your pen name.
Are you sure we're friends?
I told you I'm going to take it
to my grave.
What if you hit the big time?
Are you still going to keep it secret?
The big time?
You'll be the first one I tell.
I would love it if that happened.
Hey, Go-ya! Eui-ju!
-Hey!
-What's going on?
-What is it?
-Quickly!
Quickly!
Hey! Can you see?
I heard it was happening and it did!
Wow. All the new teachers are guys.
And not just any old guys.
They're complete hotties. Total studs.
I can't believe it.
Take a look.
Those looks! Those bodies!
I'm going crazy.
I've never wanted to go into
the teachers' office so much.
This is unbearable!
But Young-hee's locked the door
so we can't get in.
She's introducing the new teachers,
so why is she keeping them from us?
PE, Jung Gi-jeon.
JUNG GI-JEON
He represented Korea.
He was the first Korean to finish
fourth in the luge at the Winter Games.
Damn it! Look at that body.
Noh Da-ju. A polyglot.
He'll teach Japanese and freshman English.
He even did a TUD talk
on the secret to mastering languages.
Rumor has it, he's the youngest son
of a chaebol family.
I'm so glad I lived to see this.
Korean literature, Yoon Dong-ju.
Had a poem published
in Literary Youth in 2020.
Something like My Mother.
Found him.
My last love.
Hang on.
That guy teaches Korean literature?
Then surely not.
No way.
Ga Woo-su.
Our new math teacher.
Thanks to his outstanding research
in college…
GA WOO-SU
…several Ivy League schools
tried to recruit him,
but he chose to come here instead.
That asshole?
He's a member of Mensa.
Did you hear that?
That's the kind of person he is.
To put it another way, he's a math genius.
Dropped my…
Did you see?
Da-ju is just my type.
The age of Ha E-den is finally over.
Hey, how can you even compare?
Ha E-den was just a little cute.
Are you talking about me?
This early in the morning?
HA E-DEN
MUSIC TEACHER
Not at all.
Oh, Go-ya. That was cold. That hurt.
Thank you for being
our temporary homeroom teacher.
-Thank you.
-Hello, sir.
-Good morning.
No, it's not good.
Have they lost their minds all together?
MURIM GIRLS' HIGH 11TH GRADE CLASS 2
From now on, I'm going to put on
full make-up every day.
Who have you got your eye on?
His name is Dong-ju.
My future husband.
What should I major in
to be the perfect wife and mother?
I think he'd like the quiet, modest type.
I like the Japanese teacher.
Get back to your lashes.
-Who are you going for?
-For what?
Your bias?
We shouldn't overlap.
Forget it. Bias? What a crock.
But he's not even your type.
My type's changed.
Hang on a sec.
-I just got a chill.
-Why?
That means one of those four
is going to be our new homeroom teacher.
Shut up!
EUN HA-SU
TOP OF THE SCHOOL, PRESENCE
Will you be quiet?
Class hasn't started yet.
At least don't disturb others.
She thinks she owns the place.
Fancy a snack?
Shall we pop out?
Where are you going?
BRACKET BY SPORT
KOREAN LITERATURE TIMETABLE
MR. GA WOO-SU
MURIM GIRLS' HIGH
11TH GRADE TEACHERS' OFFICE
KOREAN LITERATURE TIMETABLE
Are you doing coloring?
It's so I don't get confused.
Are you feeling off?
Want some antacids?
No, I'll be fine.
Are you disinfecting?
Don't be so weird.
Butt out.
In the jungle of the workplace,
don't you know standing out
means certain death?
You know nothing
about the ways of the world.
Switch with me. I can't take him.
Don't be like that.
I want to sit facing you.
I miss you even when I can see you.
Just stay there. It's designated seating.
I don't want to sit facing that bat.
What!
I told you not to call me that.
That word is like Voldemort to me.
I don't even want it on my lips.
Don't you know I hate it?
Of course you do. That's why you said it.
You're Ga Woo-su, the genius.
There's no way you don't know.
My hippocampus actually does something.
It doesn't just handle learning
and memory, it also regulates emotions.
That's why I can't sit facing you.
Don't insult my hippocampus.
You memory freak!
Hey, fruit bat!
What? Glasses monkey!
Glasses monkey?
Will you two cut it out?
MURIM GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
How do you know he's your last love?
You only just met him.
Love is…
like the first snow.
Love at first sight.
When you see them,
you know that person is meant for you.
That's how it is, kiddo.
It hits you when you least expect it.
Then all those other guys you dated…
None of them were your first snow?
I thought they were,
but they were just frost.
My first snow came today.
When will I get my first snow?
I told you.
When you least expect it.
Suddenly,
when you're defenseless,
-like a smack to the back of the head.
-Thank you.
-Ouch!
-Bye.
-How much?
-It's 2,000 won.
-Thank you.
Lucky you.
You're experiencing first snow
with the new teacher.
Whereas my first meeting was a disaster.
Whatever.
Anyhow,
that's why he mentioned uniforms.
He was basically saying,
"I'll see you at school."
What's the use in being a genius
if he has a shitty personality?
What is it?
NO WAY
I'M YOUR HOMEROOM TEACHER
Subtitle: Paul Carver