(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
So what? Are you going to hit on him?
If he actually falls for you, what will you do, Michael?
What are you gonna do?
Do whatever I want to do.
Can you stop scaring me like that?
Zero points.
I’m starting to keep score from now on.
Give me some encouragement.
You’re doing really well.
My tail’s wagging already.
You’re unbelievable.
I’m sorry.
But I meant it.
Are you mad?
No.
It’s my first time seeing you flustered.
Don’t do that again.
That’s hard. I can’t promise that.
I’m deducting points.
This time,
I’ll let you deduct them.
Hey.
Why are you staring at me like that?
I'm mad at you.
About the kiss?
About how you made me lose my composure.
What kind of person are you?
You’re ridiculously adorable.
Especially when you’re mad.
Even more irresistible.
- Get out.
- No.
Why are you doing this?
We’re not even dating.
I ask you to be my boyfriend every hour.
Just say yes already.
A message came in.
I’m in Chiang Mai now.
Mr. Yuseong, when would you be available?
So we can arrange a meeting.
Would next week work for you?
That works.
See you then.
Who’s that?
A client.
Kim Taemin.
Korean?
Half-Korean.
He’s a writer.
He’s hired me for several pieces already.
Then why does he call you Yuseong?
Is your name Yuseong or what?
Yuseong is Korean
for “shooting star.”
Let go. I need to work.
Go ahead and work.
I’ll sit here and watch.
I have to paint it on canvas for your dad.
Direk, damn it.
He’s always ruining my happiness.
Don’t you dare run away from me.
I’ll take John hostage. Get over here.
You’re dead.
What’s your dream?
I want to have my own gallery.
That’s not related to what you studied, is it?
Yeah, it’s not.
I studied biology just because I liked it.
What about your dream?
I want to make music.
I like playing the drums.
I’ve played guitar since I was a kid.
I even made songs with my friends back in high school.
The ones you played at the San Fran house.
But I haven’t done much lately.
Your songs are good.
What a shame.
Yeah.
It’s a shame.
Then why did you study medicine?
I promised my mom when I was little
that I’d become a doctor and treat her.
I guess it stuck with me.
If you achieve your dream,
will you go back to making music?
I don’t know.
It’s been a long time.
As someone who’s listened to your songs,
if you were an artist,
I’d want you to keep making music.
Crazy man.
Do you have class?
No.
Then why are you up so early?
I want to finish Direk Uncle’s painting.
So I can continue working on Kim’s project next week.
Oh.
Hey.
Are you free next month?
Why?
I’ve got an important race coming up.
I was thinking of asking you to come watch.
I want some support.
What if I don’t go?
Won’t you still win?
Of course I would.
But if you’re there...
it just feels good.
Hey.
I’ll go shower first.
That’s quite a heavy course load.
Oh.
Is that a heart?
Yeah.
Don’t let me have one too, you guys.
So, how’s it going with that kid? Did he fall for you yet?
Not yet.
I’m stuck in the brother zone or whatever.
That’s rough.
- Why are you pitying me?
- I pity Daotok.
- Having you haunt him like a ghost.
- Hey, North, you jerk.
If I die and become a ghost, I’ll snap your neck first, North.
Hey! I’ll snap yours first.
Damn it.
Hey, North.
Do you know
Kim?
- Kim?
- Yeah.
Hmm.
Oh, Daotok’s client who’s a writer, right, P'?
You know him?
Well,
I see him quite often.
They’ve worked together for a long time.
So? Tell me.
I’ve got a feeling.
He’s not just an ordinary client.
Damn. What do you mean?
- What do you mean?
- Well.
Would a normal client ask him out to dinner like this?
No way, P'.
But
I don’t think Daotok’s interested.
But the other guy? Not so sure.
From the chats I’ve seen, something feels off.
- Are you messing with me?
- Messing with you? No way.
Fine. Believe it or not.
P' Jo,
I’m heading to class now.
- Alright. Study hard.
- Yes.
I’m off.
I wasn’t messing with you. Seriously.
Yeah, study hard. You should tell that to yourself too.
You’re the last person who should say that to me.
So what about that kid?
He said he’s opened his heart to me.
But he still won’t be my boyfriend.
So I ask him to be my boyfriend every day.
That’s it.
Hill said this kind of thing takes time.
I get it, Jo.
But
I’m just impatient.
Yeah. Does Hill know about this?
Yeah.
Hill said he’s really proud of this friend.
You mean you?
Then why did he scold me when I was courting North?
Damn, does he think you’re better than me?
- Hill?
- Of course.
Why though?
Hey, Jo.
I’ve got an important race next month.
Help me practice, will you?
I haven’t raced in a while.
- You wanna lose or what?
- Get on, idiot.
You haven’t raced in ages either. You’re probably rusty.
Let’s see then.
Bring it on.
Go, P' Jo! You can do it!
Damn, not rusty at all.
That support really helps.
But honestly, our stats aren’t bad.
If we went pro,
we’d be killing it.
Right? Why are we torturing ourselves like this?
Yeah.
Damn, Jo.
You make me want to quit for the millionth time, you jerk.
Damn.
If you quit, I quit too.
Hey, no way.
You’ve come this far.
You’ve got to do it for Hill.
Why would I do it for Hill?
What?
- So Hill can be proud of you.
- Oh, come on.
Water.
Hey.
Where's mine?
You’ve got hands and feet. Get it yourself, P'.
Yeah, I’ve got hands and feet.
- But no boyfriend.
- Ouch.
Damn it.
Why am I roasting myself?
Just bring him to the race on the actual day.
I already asked him.
Not sure if he’ll be free though.
How about this.
I’ll drag him there myself. He listens to me anyway.
Yeah, thanks.
You’re the cutest.
No wonder I practically raised you with my feet.
With your feet? Seriously?
But if you don’t win him over, it’s fine. At least you’ll gain a little brother.
What little brother? What big brother?
I don’t want any of that.
I’m gonna be his husband.
Hey!
I didn’t think you were this serious about him.
I didn’t think so either.
He’s changed my life.
I think
I’ve started seeing things a little differently.
How so?
He’s the one who makes me want to chase my dream again,
after I already gave up on it.
Damn, the way I talk is cool as hell.
Hey, guys.
Do you think
I could be the main character?
Damn, I shouldn’t have praised you.
Hey.
Wait, did you just praise me, North?
- Whatever.
- What a damn waste of time.
Cutest, seriously.
Hey, wait.
Why didn’t you tie your shoelaces properly?
They’re this long.
What if you trip, hit your head, and die?
I take care of you this well.
Do I get extra points?
Well, if you didn’t just curse me to trip and die,
I would’ve added some.
That’s not a curse.
That’s called a warning.
Fine, I’ll add three more points.
So
what’s the total now?
Not telling you.
Hey, that’s cheating.
Hey, what if it hits a million?
Wait.
- Hmm?
- Which one should I get?
What’s the difference?
Better question—how are they even similar?
Then you just get them all.
That’s wasteful.
It’s Direk’s money. He hired you to draw, so he has to buy your supplies too. Got it?
Mr. Yuseong.
Hello.
What a coincidence.
Hello, Mr. Kim.
It’s been a while.
Yes.
Excuse me.
- Are you Mr. Yuseong’s friend?
- No.
No.
We’re brothers.
Brothers.
What’s up, little brother?
Big brother, what’s your name?
Fu—
Arthit.
I’m Kim Taemin. Nice to meet you.
We can discuss the details another day.
Is that okay?
I’ve been pretty busy lately, and school’s hectic too.
It might take a bit of time.
That’s totally fine.
I can wait.
Are you mad?
Mad about what?
About calling us brothers.
Well,
it’s not wrong, is it?
Wait till I become your husband.
Then we’ll talk.
But whatever.
I’m just annoyed.
He clearly likes you.
At first, I thought North was messing with me.
But after meeting him,
damn,
he really does like you.
Whatever.
Thinking about it is just a waste of time.
Um.
If he weren’t your client,
I would’ve punched him in the face just now.
Good.
You need to learn how to control your temper.
Be a good boy.
Hey, you’re praising me like I’m a dog.
At least give me a bone or something.
Should I bow my head?
Go on, pat my head.
Then bend down.
Hey.
At least let me be the tiger when we’re outside.
You can just put your stuff in my room.
Why?
Why not leave it in my room?
P'Pae said the electrical repairs are done.
Just move in with me already, okay?
Please?
We’re not even together.
Damn.
That hurts, asshole.
Hey.
Can’t you at least upgrade my status a bit?
We can be “talking,” at least.
Are we even talking?
I am. You’re the one who’s not talking to me.
- Hey.
- Hmm?
Why do you want to be my boyfriend?
What?
That’s a weird question.
When you love someone,
of course you’d want a proper status.
Hmm?
But if you need time,
I can wait.
Next month.
Hmm?
I’ve got a big race next month.
I’ll try to get myself ready.
You mean...
If I win the race—
or just finish it?
Well...
Winning would be nice.
That’s more like it. At least give the one who’s waiting a goal to hold on to.
Yeah, that seriously boosts my motivation for the race.
But...
You don’t have to force yourself.
I really can wait.
Not at all.
I’m not forcing myself.
I just want to try.
For me?
For us.
Just leave your stuff there.
When you said you’d try for us—
do you know
how happy that made me?
I used to wonder
if I could ever be patient for you.
But this—
this is the answer.
So—
you’d better be ready soon.
Or you’re in serious trouble.
I’m in trouble.
Big trouble.
Alright, everyone.
That’s it for today.
We’ll meet again next time.
You’re dismissed.
I have an appointment with Khun Kim this afternoon.
You have to go when I’m with me.
You are absolutely not meeting him alone.
Aren’t you pretty busy?
Where are you meeting?
I’m not sure yet.
Maybe a café around the condo.
Then go to this café.
Why this one?
Just—
If I say go there, just go.
Mr. Yoo Sung.
This way, please.
Please.
So what, that client likes Dao or something?
Yeah.
So you’re jealous and want me to keep an eye on them?
Yeah, damn right.
Didn’t expect you to admit it so easily.
When you’re done, I’ll go there.
What the hell?
At least give me time to prepare.
Fine, I’ll help you keep watch.
I’ve been wanting to stick my nose in anyway.
Mr. Yoo Sung.
How about we visit some inspiring places together?
I’ve been pretty busy lately.
And I’ve got classes too.
Oh, I see.
Then how about going on a day off?
I’ve noticed there are quite a few interesting places around here.
Oh.
I’ve got work to do, yeah.
The table’s dirty.
So?
I’d rather decline.
Why is that?
Is it because of Arthit?
Last time, you said you were just like brothers.
But he was clearly showing otherwise.
Khun Kim, could you take a look at this background?
I think a large door backdrop might work better here.
Sure.
May I speak frankly for a moment?
Last time—
I felt uncomfortable for you.
Why didn’t you just reject him directly?
I wasn’t uncomfortable.
They’re holding hands, damn it. Hurry up, you bastard.
I’m sorry.
Why?
Because of Arthit?
Yes.
But you two aren’t even dating.
In that case—
I won’t give up.
Please give up, Khun Kim.
I don’t see you that way.
And I never will.
I don’t understand.
Why do you like a guy like that?
Like what?
He’s indecisive.
And he’s not sincere. When we first met,
he was rude to me.
No manners at all.
The way you’re acting right now is rude too, Khun Kim.
I’d like you to apologize to him.
I’m sorry.
I was out of line.
I promise
I won’t think that way again.
I’m truly sorry.
I guess I realized it too late, didn’t I?
Even though
I should have met you first.
You really like him that much, don’t you?
Yes.
I understand.
I’ll get going now.
Good luck, sir.
Why are you here?
I came to pick you up.
Damn.
We’ve known each other forever,
and this is the first time I’ve heard you say “krub.”
Gives me goosebumps.
Why’d you button up your shirt?
Why?
You don’t like it?
No.
I’m just not used to it.
Yeah.
I’m not used to it either.
That’s much better.
Just be yourself, the way you want to be.
Come to think of it, saying “krub” isn’t that bad.
Right?
Damn, I'm so hot.
- Meen.
- Hmm?
How’d you get here?
I called a ride. Why?
Then drive my car back for me.
This one?
- Yeah.
- What about you?
I’ll go back with my wife.
Right?
- You—
- No way.
My tire’s flat anyway.
Hey, I’m not that heavy, okay?
Damn it, Arthit.
You’re built like a giant.
That’s not gonna work.
It is.
Let’s go.
You-.
Easy, babe.
Go full speed, Dao.
Hey!
Why are you driving so slow?
You’re heavy. Can you stop hugging me?
No.
The whole reason I’m riding pillion is so I can hold you.
Get off.
Don’t chase me away.
I’ve never ridden pillion with anyone like this before.
Does it feel bad that I’m hugging you?
No.
Stay with me.
Why don’t you stay in your own room?
Well—
My room’s been too lonely without you.
You packed up all your stuff and ran off like that.
You even took John with you.
- But you forgot something.
- Forgot what?
You forgot me.
Oh.
- Then leave that there too.
- Hey!
“Leave”? You’re really using that word?
Are you going to leave me?
I won’t.
Can’t we just talk nicely?
What’s wrong with this?
It’s just… this is—
What about it?
Please let me go.
Are you trying to tease me right now?
No.
I’m pleading with you.
Tell me.
What did you talk about with Kim?
At first, it was about work.
And then?
Then he said he likes me.
And what did you say?
You must really like him, don’t you?
I must’ve realized my feelings too late, right?
No.
Even if you had realized it sooner,
my answer would still be the same.
It has to be him.
What made you decide to hit the gym?
So I’ll have the strength to take you on.
Working out to build up stamina,
so you can go at it with me?
Exactly.
That’s actually a good thing.
So when you’re ready,
you can stay with me all the way to the finish line,
instead of passing out halfway.
Long time no see.
After this,
want to grab something to eat?
Please?
Please, Arthit.
I’ve really missed you.
No one satisfies me the way you do.
Please, Arthit.
I’m not being unreasonable. I’m not asking for anything.
Just have some fun together again.
Please.
Did you see that?
Yeah.
Are you jealous at all?
See how damn hot I am?
Don’t just stay silent like that.
I’m gonna get sulky, you know.
I am.
Seriously.
I wasn’t okay.
That’s why I didn’t want to look.
So I came into the restroom instead.
Does that count as being jealous?
I can hold your arm too, you know.
Who is she?
I don’t even know.
Just someone you had a brief thing with, right?
Yeah.
But we haven’t seen each other in ages.
The reason I let her do that earlier
was just to see if you’d get jealous.
So… am I allowed to be jealous?
Of course.
You’re allowed anything.
Do you still have feelings for her?
No.
I only have feelings for you.
You have no idea
how crazy you drive me.
I’ve never felt this way about anyone before,
except you.
I understand now.
Can we talk for a minute?
Let go.
I said let go.
Let go, damn it.
What the hell is going on?
I was just wondering if you're dating with him.
You came together,
and I just wanted to talk, that’s all.
Are you okay?
Does it hurt anywhere?
He twisted my arm.
- You saw it.
- But she was about to slap me first.
- You little bastard.
- Who are you calling a little bastard?
P’ Arthit.
Let’s go.
Wait.
I’m sorry.
What are you apologizing for?
You didn’t do anything wrong.
Well…
You almost got hurt.
I can protect myself.
This won’t happen again.
I promise.
Bow your head.
You’re patting my head like I’m a sulky dog.
Stop overthinking.
Again.
No more.
Give me a kiss.
I give you an inch and you take a mile.
Can’t you let your guard down a little?
Just a little, okay?
Can I sleep with you?
Why don’t you sleep in your own room?
I miss John.
John.
Johnny.
Johnny dear.
My little John.
Stop.
I’m sorry.
I didn’t mean to.
I knew I wouldn’t be able to hold back.
But I still wanted to hold you while we sleep.
I’m sorry.
Get out.
No.
Please let me hold you while I sleep.
You’re still asking?
- Fine, I’ll let you do it back.
- Are you crazy?
Then…
Hit me with this soft pillow.
Mm.
Go on—Ow! Wait, that hurts!
Ow!
Ow, that hurts! That’s enough!
- Ow!
- I said don’t do that again.
That hurts.
Don’t do that again.
Until we’re officially dating.
Okay?
Mm.
Okay.
I’m trying to get myself ready too.
You mean…
For that kind of thing too?
Of course.
So
don’t do it again.
So that means
we have to wait until I finish the race,
and until you agree to be my boyfriend,
right?
Mm.
Okay.
The race is about to start.
Are you excited?
No.
I’m more excited for after it’s over.
From now on,
there won’t be any more “no,” right?
Mm.
No matter what the result is,
my answer will be the same.
Damn, I’m so freaking excited.
This whole “big brother” thing ends right here.
Bring it on, you bastards.
From now on,
no one’s gonna dare tease me again.
Oh, you came too?
If I trained you, I’ve got to come see my student.
I’m not here to cheer for you.
- I’m here to see my friend officially off the market.
- Damn, that’s smooth.
Go on. It’s time.
Mm.
I’m off.
Just wait for my victory.
And get ready to say yes.
Do your best.
Mm.
I’ve heard about the agreement between you two.
From now on,
it might be a bit tough for you, Daotok.
It’s not tough at all, sir.
Not like that at all.
Let me speak as a father.
A father who wants his child to be happy.
Arthit is my only child.
He’s my whole life.
If he loves you,
then I love you too.
And if you have feelings for him,
don’t ever leave him.
I will.
I promise.
Shit, he’s here!
- Hey!
- You can do it! I’ll be waiting for you, P’Thit!
That was fucking fast.
Final lap!
Hey, P’Thit!
No matter what the result is,
my answer stays the same.
Just wait for my victory.
And get ready to say yes.
He scored! P’Thit scored!
It’s in!
He won!
P’Jo! P’Thit scored!
Hey!
You’re just being a sore loser.
Why?
Do you hate me that much?
If you want revenge,
then beat me first.
Big talk, huh?
Why don’t all of you come at me at once?
Hey!
The match ended a while ago. Why isn’t he here yet?
Sir, something’s wrong!
Young Master—
What is it? What happened to Arthit?
Hey!
What the hell are you doing?!
Young Master!
Thit! Hey, Thit!
Thit!
P’Jo, don’t!
P’Jo, please don’t!
Are you okay, son?
I won.
Thit…
Arthit…
Hey.
Aren’t you scared?
(I told you to leave.)
No.
What are you even scared of?
I don’t know.
What about you?
What are you scared of?
I’m scared you won’t love me.
Then there’s nothing to be scared of.
Flirting again, huh?
What’s with you, Daotok?
I’m asking you seriously.
Are you trying to kill me with that sweetness or what?
Did someone hire you or something?
I’m starting to get suspicious.
That’s right.
Someone did hire me.
To make you fall for me.
And then dump you.
That’s messed up.
- You mean the one who hired you?
- You.
How much did they pay you?
Hmm…
One million.
I’ll give you a hundred million.
To accept my love.
No.
Not enough?
You don’t need to hire me at all.
Because I already love you.
Earlier, when you asked what I was scared of,
and I said I didn’t know—
now I know.
I’m scared.
Scared of losing you.
I can’t lose you.
I really can’t lose you.
I already had someone investigate.
It was the other side.
They were probably afraid of losing and losing a lot of money.
- Shall I handle it?
- No need for Johan to step in.
I won’t let them get away with this.
North.
What if he doesn’t wake up, North?
He said if he wins,
he’d ask me to be his boyfriend.
Go in peace, my friend.
And I’m still waiting right here.