Previously on Seducing Drake Palma.
Hey, Drake.
Do we have a monthsary?
Tss.
Oh!
The best thing to do
is to take your shirt off.
I know!
Let’s just say we got
together on September 31!
Stupid.
There’s no September 31.
Can we rehearse the garter part?
Drake and Alys, please.
Miss Blossom.
Whatever.
Every 31st will be our monthsary,
so we only have to celebrate
seven times a year.
We’re graduating in
a few months.
Once we start college,
we’ll go our separate ways.
Who says that I’m gonna
break-up with you?
Hmm?
I’m territorial.
If someone said that to you,
wouldn’t you fold?
I love you, Drake Palma!
It has been two weeks
after the “I’m territorial” moment.
Of course, there’s progress.
We have lunch
maybe twice a week.
Naturally, the girls were shocked.
They couldn’t contain
their jealousy!
We even became a hot
topic in school because...
of course, we are always together.
We’re doing fine
until Christmas.
Merry Christmas!
I felt a little sad since
he didn’t give me a gift.
But even though it was raining,
he still came to make it up to me.
Thank you!
I also told him we’ll have a vacation
during Christmas break,
so we wouldn’t see each other.
He just said, “OK.”
Oh, well.
I forgot to save
that annoying guy’s number.
And then...
New Year came.
But…
will anything actually change?
Alys!
Come down here, it’s New Year!
Come!
Come on, sweetheart! Let’s go!
Okay, Mom!
I’ll be right there!
Hi, Mom.
Dad’s getting married soon.
I don’t think I can stop them.
I don’t think there’s
anything I can do.
I’m sorry, Mom.
But I met someone.
She’s interesting.
She’s nice.
I know you’d like her, Mom.
I miss you, Mom.
Bestie, let’s go!
They’re waiting for
us at the wedding!
Can’t you wait?
You’re so slow!
You’re trying to look
pretty for Drake, aren’t you?
She’s trying to make herself pretty.
Whatever!
Who told you to
wait for me, anyway?
I don’t know with you!
I told you I don’t
know anyone there!
Why would I go alone?
You’re in such a rush, but you’re
not even part of the entourage!
Okay, I’m ready!
Let’s go!
- Hey, wait a second!
- Let’s go!
See?
Bestie, wait up!
Hurry up.
Good luck.
Thank you.
- Uncle Steve!
- Hi, Uncle!
Hello!
Wow, you look
good today.
You’re so handsome.
Glad your wedding
pushed through.
Wasn’t it supposed
to be in October?
Moved to February?
Just kidding!
Go on inside,
the coordinator’s already there.
Thanks, Uncle. Congrats!
Hurry up!
Mom’s so annoying!
She really made me
look like a rice cake!
Good thing I convinced her to
let me wear doll shoes instead.
Wearing six-inch
heels is so stressful!
I feel like a model!
Hi, Miss Beautiful!
Why are you here, gate crasher?
Come on, Bee.
I’m here because of you.
Stop winking like that!
You look crazy!
We’re at a wedding,
and you’re acting up!
You look beautiful today, Bee!
Maybe you dressed up
because of me.
Right?
Honestly, I don’t know
where you get that nerve!
You’re so handsome, huh?
I know!
That’s why you’re so
in love with me.
Dream on.
But sure, tell yourself that.
It’s free to dream!
Exactly!
Bee, you’re my dream!
One more word and
I swear I’ll hurt you!
Bee, wait!
Oh no, Bee!
I’m sorry!
What did you just do,
Kent Justin Valdez?
Shh, quiet down!
What the hell?!
- Be quiet! This is your fault!
- I’m sorry.
I’ll take care of it, Bee.
You can thank me in
advance for this.
Why are you taking
your clothes off?
I’m saving you.
He looks handsome.
I’m so lucky to have him.
Thank you.
What about you, Bee?
Are you going to change?
What’s the plan?
Uh…
I’ll buy new clothes.
Come on, I’ll go with you.
Alright, everyone,
get ready!
The bride is here!
Entourage, to your places please!
We’ve already
practiced this, okay?
Sweetheart, are you listening?
Yes.
Okay.
My heart, can you calm down?
This weirdo might find out
I have a crush on him.
Shall we?
She’s stunning.
Huhu.
How can my cute face compete with
Aunt Katrina’s goddess beauty?
Staring is rude.
You think so?
You’re not handsome.
I know.
Good that you know.
I don’t want to be handsome.
I just want to be loved.
By you, perhaps?
Was that a pick-up line by
Drake Sebastian Palma?
Pick-up line–
The Drake Palma Way?
Today isn’t just
about vows or rings–
it’s about two hearts
choosing each other...
fully, freely, and faithfully.
In front of God and the
people who matter most.
So let me ask you, Steve –
do you receive Katrina
as the love of your life?
Do you promise to stand by
her side not just when it’s easy,
but when love asks for
patience, grace and courage?
Will you be her safe
place, her partner in faith,
and her greatest encourager
everyday God gives you together?
Yes, I do.
And Katrina,
do you receive Steve as your
husband and your heart’s companion?
Will you choose him again
and again through storms,
through laughter, through every
ordinary day that becomes sacred
because it is shared?
I do.
With the authority
that God has given me,
to say the word that you’ve
been waiting for,
I pronounce you
husband and wife.
You may now kiss the bride.
We’ll get off here, Sir.
- Let’s go, Bee.
- Go down.
- Give me your stuff.
- So slow.
Here, I’ll help you.
- Thank you.
- Hurry up.
Bee, wait up!
See? We missed everything!
We just got here
and now we’re leaving?
Annoying.
Hey!
Why are you scaring me?
You’re thinking too deeply.
Why are you spacing out?
Why are you dressed like that?
Where did you go?
Oh my gosh!
Did something happen?
Uhh…
Oh, you see that?
Who would've thought that the girl who
is scared of love would eventually give in?
Ouch!
You’re talking too much,
you sound crazy!
My dress got torn and KL helped me
to get a new one?
Yiee, “KL”!
They already have a
term of endearment.
Shut up.
“KL” means “little pest”!
Tss.
As if!
- You’re the one who’s “KL”!
- What?
You’re pretending to not care.
What?
You’re enjoying this too much!
Whatever, I’m going home.
You just got here and
now you’re leaving again?
Mom and I are going to Batangas.
Dad suddenly planned a family outing.
Yiee, KL is coming with you!
Is he coming?
It’s a family outing!
Why not? KL’s family too, right?
Go ask your Mom!
There’s your boyfriend, Bestie!
Bye, Bestie!
Aja!
Bye, Alys!
Why are you following me?
Of course, I’m coming with you!
Where you go, I go!
Oh my gosh, he’s coming closer!
Okay.
Should I keep a
poker face or smile?
Shocks, I feel pressured.
Breathe, Alys, breathe.
Stay calm.
Just act cool.
Stay cool, okay?
What?
Let’s go.
Where?
Reception. Stupid.
At the hotel! Where else?
Why would I go
with you to the hotel?
You’re my crush but
I won’t give you my body.
Are you scared?
Pervert!
I’m your boyfriend,
and you’re my girlfriend.
It’s about time.
Drake, stop joking like that!
It’s not funny!
I’m dead serious...
...love.
Love?
Should I go with him to the hotel?
No!
Don’t fall for his sweet talk!
I must go away from
that possessive maniac.
Bird brain.
Drake.
I’m kidding.
I know the words
“wait” and “respect.”
I’ll wait at our table.
Okay?
Lord, is it Valentine’s Day today?
I’m thriving today!
Kei.
What is it now, Sheen?
Can I talk to you?
About what?
If it’s about getting
back together again,
my answer is still no.
Kei...
why did you leave me?
About this again?
I need closure.
I love you.
And I want to move
on with my life.
I still have doubts
about myself.
I want to be completely sure
when I say I love you.
I don’t love Drake.
I just find him interesting.
We wouldn’t have lasted
almost a year if I didn’t love you.
Kei.
I loved you, Sheen.
Believe me.
But…
I fell out of love.
Kei...
did I do something wrong?
None. None, Sheen.
I was wrong, not you.
You’re too good for me.
I’m so sorry.
So…
this is it.
This is what?
I guess...
this is goodbye.
I loved you, Kei.
Drake is taking so long
to come back.
- Congratulations, Steve!
- Thanks!
I’ll just be there,
I’ll walk around.
Uncle Steve!
Alys!
Congrats, Uncle Steve!
Thanks!
Why is Aya not with you?
She left early,
something suddenly came up.
Oh, I see.
I’m actually looking for Katrina.
Hold on, enjoy yourself
here, I’ll go find her.
Sure, Uncle. Congrats again!
Where’s Drake, anyway?
He knows I don’t know anyone
here, and he still left me alone.
Interesting.
Wrong timing.
Maybe next time.
Stop this, Aki!
Your Dad and I are married!
I know.
Good!
Then stop this already!
I can’t.
Please, Aki!
Alys is here!
She’s your girlfriend!
I know, but I want you!
Your Dad and I are married.
What part of that
don’t you understand?
I’m blinded by you!
Do you think I want this?
Hell no!
Because you keep
on entertaining me.
I know you want me, too!
I don’t like you, Drake.
Not romantically!
You want to know the truth?
I’m just concerned about you because I know
how hung up you are on your Mom’s death.
You’re a witch!
Maybe I am.
But right now, I’m your stepmom.
And Alys is in your life.
Choose her.
Stop messing with her feelings.
That’s enough, Drake!
I’m sorry, Mom.
I could not stop Dad
from marrying her.
But I’ll still try.
For you.
Where did she go?
Why woud you do that, Drake?
Why are you playing
with my feelings?
Oh hi, Alys!
You’re still up?
How was the wedding?
Princess, are you okay?
Yeah, Mom.
I’m just really thirsty.
Are you sure you’re okay?
Well, if you’re not feeling well,
just let me know, okay?
I’ll go ahead, I’ll rest up.
Okay? Good night.
Thanks, Mom.
Why am I crying?
I don’t cry this easily.
Only Mom,
Dane,
Dad Andy, and Daddy Cyriel
have made me cry like this.
Why am I crying over you...
Drake Sebastian Palma?
Bestie,
is something
bothering you?
Please, Aki!
Alys is here!
She’s your girlfriend!
I know, but I want you!
I don’t even know
why I’m like this.
I haven’t been able
to sleep for days.
Every time I close my eyes,
I hear Drake and
Aunt Katrina talking.
I don’t even have
the right to feel hurt.
I’m just his girlfriend,
not the one he loves.
Hey.
Are you sick?
Why are you studying?
I thought you’re concerned.
I am concerned.
What’s going on with you?
I don’t even know.
Maybe this is just how it is.
You focus on something else–
so you don’t have to
think about the things that hurt you.
What is it?
Nothing, I’m just bored.
You’re studying
out of boredom?
You know what,
let’s just have lunch.
Fight your boredom
with food, Bestie!
I don’t want go out.
I’m not ready to see Drake.
I’m still hurting.
Let’s go?
I brought food. You go ahead.
Wow!
Really? Where is it?
Let me see!
From Singapore,
- Wow! That’s a lot.
- it’s from Daddy.
Aunt Liana's based there now.
Your stepmom?
Wow, that’s a
lot and imported too!
Don’t try to steal some.
You’re so selfish.
I'm close with Uncle Cy!
Come on, Bestie.
Let me have some.
Share your blessings!
I don’t want.
Selfish.
I’ll just eat by
myself at the cafeteria.
Wow, she really won’t share!
Whatever!
I’m done with you!
I’m not giving you food.
This is all mine.
Tss.
Lunch.
I’m still full.
This is hard.
I can’t just ignore him.
I can’t be cold either.
It’s not his fault I
ended up liking him.
My gosh, life’s so confusing!
Why can’t we just like each other,
end of story?
Lunch.
I said I’m full.
Eat.
There might be poison in here.
Then, good!
You’re seriously insane.
I really love this ramen.
Wow, even the ramen gets loved.
Shut up and eat.
I said I’m still full—
Are you trying to kill me?
It’s good, right?
Why would I do
that to my girlfriend?
Girlfriend, but he keeps hurting me.
About that, Drake...
we should break up.
Why is it like this?
Why is he treating me
differently now?
I like it better when he’s not
looking at me,
when he’s ignoring me,
when he’s not talking to me.
I hate this.
Oh, well.
I said can we break up already?
Why?
Because you don’t even like me.
And I don’t like you either.
I don’t want to.
Let’s just break up, please?
Your reason is not
enough, Miss Perez.
I said I don’t want this anymore!
I want out!
You’re the one who
volunteered to be my girlfriend.
Take responsibility.
Eat.
I really bought that for you.
Don’t make this
hard for me, Drake.
Wow.
It’s so serene here.
You’re such a loner here.
Sheen!
What are you doing here?
Nothing. Just for a change.
How about you?
Why aren’t you with Kent?
He’s at the cafeteria with Aya.
He’s totally into
your best friend.
They’re cute, right?
They look good together.
Sheen, are you okay?
We’re really broken up now, Alys.
What do you mean "really"?
Weren’t you
broken up already?
This time it’s final.
We’re really done.
There’s no going back.
It’s fine!
At least now,
I can really move on.
It’s okay, Sheen.
Who knows, once you’re
in St. Collete Academy,
you might meet someone
better than Kei, right?
I don’t know.
Whatever.
For now, I’m just going to
enjoy being single.
Right, best friend?
Of course!
Let’s eat.
That’s for me?
Drake!
Drake, what the heck?!
Drake, what’s going on?!
What was that?!
Hey!
What’s your problem?
Why did you do that?
Let go of me, Drake!
Let go!
Next time,
when I give you something,
don’t give it to someone else!
Why are you yelling?!
Because you’re forcing me to!
Haven’t you heard
of “sharing is caring”?
It’s useless.
I forgot that you’re
in love with him.
You’re right.
Would you do me a favor
and break up with me?
Since he’s broken up with Kei,
maybe I stand—
You don’t stand a chance.
Not when I’m around.
You’re horrible!
You’re so horrible!
Why won’t you let me go?!
You like Aunt Katrina, don’t you?!
I know, Drake.
I know you’re just
playing with me,
so please, let’s end this.
You’re so unfair, Drake.
What if—
I’m already starting
to fall for you?
That’s just it?
I’m the one who gets hurt
because you don’t love me?
I can’t promise to
catch you when you fall,
but I assure you
that I’ll be here
while you’re falling.
Am I supposed to
feel giddy about that?
Tss.
I can’t promise...
that I’ll learn to love you,
because I don’t make
promises that I can’t keep.
But I promise...
that I’ll try to fall
while you’re falling.
What if you don’t fall?
Then I’ll be left crying again?
I’ll wipe your tears then.
Why is it like this?
Even if he says he’ll split
my heart into five,
I would still feel giddy about it.
You're so mean.
I’m not a prince.
I’m not charming.
I can cause pain
without realizing it.
Game over.
You lost again, Alys.
But you’ll try to love me, too.
Right?
You’ll try not to hurt me?
And we won’t regret this?
So...
can I say this now?
I like you so much,
Drake Sebastian Palma!
And I promise
to try and make you fall for me.
Bee, where do
you want to go later?
You want to go the mall?
How about a movie?
Dinner date?
Coffee?
You’re so persistent, KL!
Come on, Bee!
I’ve been courting
you for months!
Don’t you have plans
to say yes?
Then stop courting me!
Bee, you know I
love you so much,
that’s why I can’t stop.
Then wait for nothing!
Huh?
So I really don’t have a chance?
Okay.
Bernadette?
What?
That witch broke…
…my heart!
Ouch!
Hey, are you okay?
So, Bernadette…
can you be my girlfriend?
Yes, fine! We’re together now!
Look at this KL guy!
He has the nerve to say he loves
me, then suddenly gives up?
We’re a couple.
You’re a jerk, Kent!
You’re betraying me
after I said yes?
- When did you say yes?
- Just now!
Really, Bee? No joke?
We’re done.
Bee, I didn’t know
you love me, too!
Yes!
It’s hard to have
a playboy boyfriend.
My gosh.
Hey, why are you turning
your back on me?
Wait, Bee!
Here’s my diary.
What?
- Sheen’s a cry baby.
- Yes.
And you keep a diary?
You two are such
weird best friends!
Says the girl with a voodoo doll at home!
Why do you even have a diary?
Of course!
So I won’t forget everything
important that happens to me!
Like now!
There!
See?
February 29.
The - witch - said - yes!
Excuse my handwriting.
See—ouch!
Don’t hit me on the head!
Bee…
- Hi, Sheen!
- Hi, Kei!
What’s up?
Nothing much.
Do you want to grab a snack?
Lunch break’s almost over.
Oh, is it?
Okay, I’ll just go
by myself then.
I’ll come with you!
Let’s skip the first class?
You’re still lazy to study, huh?
You’re right.
You know I’m the bad one.
Why are you only eating now?
Drake was rude.
Why? What did he do?
He threw away my food!
Seriously?
He’s probably jealous
because I was with Alys earlier.
That’s what you get when you
eat with someone’s girl, Sheen.
What can I do?
Alys is my best friend.
Let’s go.
Home sweet home!
Drake!
Tss.
I missed your grumpiness!
Drake, let’s eat later, okay?
What do you want?
Can we talk?
For what?
About you and Alys.
Why do you care?
Because I’m your stepmom.
Shut up, you’re not my Mom!
Please Aki, just help me out!
I’m trying here!
Okay, then.
Stop, will you?
You can’t replace my Mom.
At least try, Aki.
Just for everything
we’ve been through.
Tss.
For what, huh?
For me to remember that
I lost you to my Dad?
For me to realize how foolish I am
to make me think—
that you’re in love with me?
When in fact you only used
me to get through my Dad.
You want me to consider that?
What is he talking about?
Steve, I can explain.
Are you having an
affair with my son?
You’ve got it wrong.
Get out of my house.
Steve, please.
Steve, I’m pregnant!
Who’s the father?
Drake or me?
You got impressive choices.
Father and son.
Steve!
This is it, Mom.
This family is yours.
Hey, Kei!
Sheen!
Can we talk?
Right now?
Yes, please?
Okay.
What is it, Kei?
I’m leaving.
Huh?
I said I’m leaving.
Where are you going?
Russia.
My whole family’s migrating.
Mmm.
So why are you telling me this?
Call it selfish,
but I don’t care.
Sheen…
can we get back together, please?
Just until I leave.
Please.
Please be mine again.
Bestie, let’s go to Uncle Steve!
Come on, Bestie.
They just got back from Hawaii.
Maybe they have souvenirs
for us, right?
Souvenirs, right? Souvenirs!
You look like a souvenir, Aya!
Bestie…
Bestie, come on.
Let’s go.
Aya, can we do that later?
Because...
it’s only 7:00 AM.
We’ll end up waking them up!
Okay.
Just wake me up when it’s time.
Hey, your shoes!
You’re really feeling it.
Ugh!
Good morning, Mom!
Good morning, Dad!
Good morning!
Good morning, princess!
Mom, how’s Dane?
Well, actually he’s doing good!
Your Nana told me he
has a girlfriend already.
What?
He already has a girlfriend?
Why does he have a girlfriend?
You’re overreacting!
Of course, he’s handsome.
That’s why he has a girlfriend.
Who else would he take after? Ahem!
Obviously from his Dad, right?
But Mommy, Dane is mine only!
Oh my God, Alys, he’s really yours!
And you know what,
he’s gonna come home soon.
What?
He’s coming home soon?
- Yes, really soon!
- When?
He’s gonna continue
his studies here!
Oh my God!
I miss Dane–
Alys, you didn’t
even wake me up!
Oh!
You’re here, Uncle, Aunt!
Good morning! Let’s eat!
- Good morning!
- So yummy!
It’s really good!
It’s so good!
Eat!
Ugh, Uncle Steve’s
not even here.
Where did he go?
It’s Saturday,
they don’t have work.
So what?
They can’t go out?
Maybe the couple went on a date.
You stay here, Bestie! I’m out!
It’s boring here!
Hey, Aya!
You’re acting up again.
Ma’am, Sir Drake
asked me to give you this.
Oh, thank you.
“Go away.”
Fine, then!
What drama is this now, Drake?
What do you mean “go away”?
Tss.
Are you mad?
Drake!
I’m tired, okay?
Why are you tired?
We don’t even have
any homework or projects.
You’re so annoying.
And what if I am?
Just go home.
Why?
I’m in a really bad mood!
I’ll also be in a bad mood
if you keep ignoring me!
I’ll keep bothering you.
Do you want that?
Fine!
Hi, Aunt!
Drake,
is there a problem?
If I tell you,
would you hate me?
I’ll try not to.
Can’t you just say that you
won’t hate me no matter what?
I don’t want to lie to you.
We’re human too, right?
We make mistakes.
And I can’t guarantee
I’ll love you forever—
because things can change, right?
Like now,
whatever you’re going to say,
I can’t promise how I’ll react.
But rest assured—
I won’t leave you,
even if I hate you.
Continue being honest, Alys.
I like that about you.
Uhm, Drake?
Hmm?
This is the first time
you called me “Alys.”
Alys.
So now, what’s
really the problem?
Katrina’s pregnant.
Oh my gosh!
You’re going to have a sibling!
Aren’t you happy?
My sibling...
or my child.
What do you mean?
Alys, what if I’m the father?
What would you do?
Are you serious?
Let’s eat.
That’s for me?
Drake!
Drake, what the heck?!
Why is she sharing
what I gave her?
Is he that special?
She doesn’t want to eat with me.
But with Sheen?
Is she really in
love with that wimp?
- What’s going on?
- Wait...
- He’s just trying to eat!
- Why am I mad?
- Am I jealous?
- Like—what the heck?
I like you so much,
Drake Sebastian Palma!
And I promise
to try and make you fall for me.
Stay with me, Alys.
Stay.
Bear with me.
Bear with me, please.
On the next episode of
Seducing Drake Palma.
Drake...
if you’ve got a problem,
just leave my house.
But I’ll buy you your own condo.
Pack my things.
Tss.
Fine!
I love packing, anyways.
Suitcase number one:
Uniform and school stuff.
Suitcase number two: Your clothes.
Suitcase number three:
All your beauty products.
I feel like I’m Drake’s housewife,
picking out what he’ll wear.
You’ve got it all wrong!
Then why are you
holding my underwear?
It was an accident!
Just an accident?