Characters, actions, places, occupations,
and events in this series are fictional
and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge
or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
It’s your birthday.
You shouldn’t sleep alone.
Wouldn’t it be better
to sleep with your ex?
Do you want to come to the afterparty
at my condo?
Do you want me to take your picture?
Shasha, this is Bambi, my daughter.
Do you want to do something fun with me?
When did they say the meeting would begin?
1 p.m.
But they should have told us
if they would be late.
Your client is here.
Shall we begin the meeting?
Let me go.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Your girlfriend slid into my DMs.
I already said no to her.
But your girlfriend wouldn’t stop.
It’s your job
to keep your girlfriend in check.
You failed to do that.
Now, you blamed it on me.
You are a real loser.
Liar.
She told me that you slid into her DMs.
And you believed her?
You let her lead you by the nose.
You’ve got a big mouth.
I’ll slap some sense into you.
What the f*ck is wrong with you?
Don’t gang up on me.
Did you just kick me?
Hold her.
What the f*ck!?
Hey, stop.
Stop it. Stop!
Stop!
Don’t gang up on her.
Prim.
Don’t get in my way.
I’m going to slap this brat.
She got the nerve to seduce my girlfriend.
From what I heard, she didn’t do anything.
Your girlfriend made a move on her.
Prim.
You are my friend.
Why are you protecting this slut?
I side with her
because she didn’t do anything wrong.
If you want to slap her,
then you have to fight me first.
Damn it. Let’s go.
Are you okay?
Bambi is finding an excuse
to talk to Prim again.
But she is our client.
She’s not just a client.
She’s also Prim’s ex.
She hired Prim to work on the project
for her mom’s brand.
She probably hopes
it will help her make up with Prim.
Unfortunately, the past is the past.
That’s wicked.
Prim should have a girlfriend like me.
How can you compete with her?
She was born with a silver spoon.
Cut.
Shasha, you look amazing.
I picked the right model.
Thank you for giving me the opportunity.
To be honest,
you could be the model for the campaign.
You are pretty, elegant, and glamorous.
I’ll pass.
I want to be the boss
sitting next to the director.
What’s up between you and the director?
She’s my ex.
Do you want to get back together?
It’s just a project.
If I knew Bambi’s mom owns this brand,
I wouldn’t take this job.
I didn’t want to put you in a tough spot.
But I already took the deposit.
It’s okay.
Money comes first.
I can handle it. Don’t worry.
What about you? Are you okay?
I broke up with him.
I can’t stand it anymore.
He got jealous of everyone,
especially you.
He told me to sell my share in the company
and go work with him.
Why are you laughing?
I haven’t said anything.
It’s good that you broke up with him.
You deserve a better man.
I hope I will find one.
Speak of the devil.
What else does he want from me?
I sent the photos to my mom.
She loves them.
She’s your fan.
We finally get to work together.
If you’re coming in
as a client to win me back,
it’s not going to work.
Win you back?
This is strictly business.
It is nothing personal.
Why are your clothes so revealing?
It’s intentional.
It’s a trend.
I’m your client.
But it doesn’t seem to work.
I guess I have to come up with a new plan.
No plan will ever work on me.
Since you disappeared from my life,
I realized I have many great choices
waiting for me.
But none of them is better than me, right?
Prim.
We are ready for the shooting.
May I help you, Bambi?
No.
It’s nothing.
I just want to compliment you.
You are talented.
Thank you for working on my project.
Thank you.
But I chose to work on this project
Because it’s Prim’s project.
I’m sorry for interrupting you that day.
I didn’t know
that Prim would take you to her place.
She always waited for me
to celebrate her birthday together.
It’s okay.
Prim already told me that you are her ex.
Now, you are just a client.
When the project is done,
you two will be over.
About that night.
I’m sure I’ll get another chance.
I still have plenty of opportunities.
Her ex is back.
I think you’re running out of your chance.
Most people like to focus on the present.
The past is a lesson to remind us
not to make the same mistake.
Bambi, you should move on from her.
That’s too bad.
I like moving on in circles.
Keep trying.
Excuse me. I need to get back to work.
I’m making a living out of my hard work.
Min.
Wait a sec.
Look.
I shot the photos in many styles.
I’m not sure which style you will prefer.
Wow, they look great.
You’re really good
at taking women’s pictures.
You know how to capture their beauty.
I saw this from your previous work.
That’s why I asked you to work with us.
Thank you.
I like watching beautiful women.
Especially a woman with a sweet face
and bright eyes like you,
I love to watch them from every angle.
Because they look good from any angle.
You don’t need to compliment me.
I won’t give you a raise anyway.
I mean it, Min.
I know…
no matter how pretty or talented you are,
you still want someone to appreciate you.
You are pretty cute.
You are my style.
What did you say?
I mean, I like your dressing style.
What are you thinking?
You like only my dressing style?
Fine.
Today, you only like my dressing style.
Tomorrow, you may like
something else about me.
Look at this picture.
I love this picture.
It’s beautiful.
Prim will have nothing to complain about.
Excuse me.
I came to pick up the dress
that I have borrowed.
Our brand has a new rule.
We no longer lend our dresses.
You guys don’t take good care
of our dresses.
They often returned in a bad condition.
But I always take good care
of your dresses.
They are returned in the original state.
I’ve never caused any damage
to your dresses.
There’s nothing I can do.
I have to follow the rules.
I’m begging.
My client really wants to wear your dress.
Because of the new rule, I can’t help you.
Miss.
Yes.
I’m Shasha’s stylist.
Hello, Tle.
A stylist came here to borrow a dress.
She said you want a dress to wear
to a birthday party.
Woonsen didn’t say anything about it.
What is the name of the stylist?
What’s your name?
I’m Gorya.
Her name is Gorya.
(Do you know her?)
Gorya.
She is my personal stylist.
I forgot that I’m going to
Aya’s birthday party.
(Your dress is the perfect match
for the party’s theme.)
(Can I borrow it?)
Okay, Shasha.
Since it’s you, I’ll take care of it.
Don’t worry.
Thank you.
If it weren’t for Shasha,
I would never let you borrow it.
Don’t forget to post on social media
to promote my brand.
Of course. Thank you.
Hold on.
My birthday was several months ago.
What are you talking about?
I’ll show you
that no one can say no to me.
Sairoong, come here to watch the screen.
Can I let her watch the screen closely?
She’s a creative trainee.
It will help with her training.
Fine.
She seems to be eager to learn from you.
Alright.
You need to check if the footage matches
the storyboard and script.
You can watch on your screen.
Yes, it matches.
How was it?
After working on the set,
do you still want to
work on the production team?
It’s hectic but also fun.
Since I have a chance
to learn from a talented person like you.
I will give my all.
Let’s get back to work.
Can I see another footage?
Prim.
I don’t want her
to be in the room anymore.
The project is confidential.
I’m worried it might leak.
What?
She won’t tell anyone.
She’s worked on the project
from the beginning.
I won’t disclose clients’ info to anyone.
Prim taught me that.
I still don’t trust you.
I spent millions on this project.
What am I going to do
if it’s ruined by a big-mouthed trainee?
You said she can be trusted.
How well do you know her?
Will you take responsibility for her?
Are you here to learn?
Or are you here for something else?
Bambi.
I’m the one who accepted her
into the company.
She can be trusted.
Then she needs to learn
from other projects.
This is my project.
I choose who will be on my team.
Her?
I didn’t choose her.
Sairoong.
You can go home.
I’ll assign you to another project.
Yes, Prim.
I’m sorry.
Bye.
Bambi.
Can you separate work
from personal feelings?
Teach me about the work.
Have you turned into a scammer?
Can’t I borrow your name?
We’ve worked together.
If you called me and asked me for a favor,
you wouldn’t have to lie to her.
Fine. I’m sorry.
I know what I did was wrong.
If it were not necessary,
I wouldn’t have done it.
Criminals always have excuses.
Do you really need to call me a criminal?
Isn’t it too harsh?
It’s just an analogy.
Don’t get upset.
I don’t mind helping you.
Since I helped you,
I should get something in return.
Sure.
I’ll help style you for an event.
Okay?
I don’t want it.
I already have Woonsen take care of it.
What do you want from me?
You know what I want from you.
I know.
But I won’t give it to you.
Don’t you say no too quickly?
Why don’t you give me a chance?
Let’s go out on a date with me tonight.
No.
Why would I need to do that?
It has nothing to do with my work.
Fine.
I’ll make it about your work.
I’ll call Tle and tell her
that you dropped my name and lied to her.
What will happen…
if everyone in the industry knows
that you are a scammer?
Hello, Tle.
This is Shasha.
Where?
I’ll call and talk to her tomorrow.
She’s probably shocked.
See you at Blossom.
Bye.
Move.
-I have an errand to do.
-Are you mad at me?
Why?
That kid has a big mouth.
She shouldn’t be on the team.
Can you say that you fired her
because of the project’s confidentiality?
Part of it, yes.
Can’t you tell
that she has a crush on you?
Huh?
What does it have to do with the project?
Be professional.
I am your client.
I have a right to do that.
Bambi.
You’re ruining my management system.
What would she think of me?
She can tell others
that we aren’t being professional.
Why do you care?
She’s just a trainee.
You can get a new one.
Do you have feelings for her?
The stylist and the trainee,
are you going to hog them all?
Listen.
I can sleep with whoever I want.
You have no right to get jealous.
I’m sorry.
I didn’t think it was a big deal.
I didn’t think
it would damage your reputation.
I’ll call her tomorrow.
I’ll ask her to come back.
And from now on,
when you get close to her,
I won’t say anything.
Even if your face is next to hers,
I won’t care.
Don’t.
I’ll take care of it.
Where are you going?
I…
Can I come with you?
I don’t have any friends here.
That’s good.
You need to learn to live alone.
So you will be
more understanding of others.
Aren’t you being too harsh on me?
No, I’m being too gentle.
You can follow me only once.
Don’t cause any trouble.
Yes, Boss.
That model is so hot.
She’s always with a different girl
every time I see her.
I want to be one of them.
I want to have a girlfriend like her.
For me, I will never date anyone like her.
If I’m going to go back to her place
and sleep with her,
she must be my girlfriend.
(You know what I want from you.)
You are very punctual.
My time is precious.
Just do what you want to do.
Why are you in such a hurry?
The night is long.
I can’t force myself to do something
I don’t want to do for long.
I’ll have an allergic reaction.
I will get rashes.
Here you go.
Thank you.
I hope you enjoy it.
Do you hire a Michelin-star chef
to cook for all your dates?
Only for a special date.
This is not a date.
This is…
a business deal.
You can call it whatever you want.
But you are in my room.
So what?
What is the next step in your plan?
What are you going to do?
I don’t have any plan.
I just want to invite you
to have dinner with me.
I want us to get to know each other.
I want it to be a special night for you.
You don’t need to try to impress me.
A fancy meal at a luxurious condo.
It can’t compete with a meal
at a homey diner.
Expensive food
doesn’t mean it’s delicious.
You don’t like it.
Maybe it’s because you haven’t tried it.
Sometimes, you need to have good taste
to appreciate certain dishes.
How is it? Does it taste good?
It’s good.
I just haven’t acquired the taste yet.
Delicious food,
you need to slowly taste it.
Hi, Min.
I went to work.
And Bambi asked to tag along.
Sure.
We are in a nightclub.
We are here to dance, right?
I’m sorry, Min.
I don’t know that you’re here
to have a heart-to-heart.
I thought you came here to party.
I’ll let you two talk.
I’ll go order a drink.
Please take care of my bag, Prim.
I’ll have a vodka cherry.
Now, you have lost the right
to criticize me.
What? I haven’t done anything.
When the project is over,
I will cut all contact with her.
I’m serious.
Your room looks nice.
Can I ask if you bought or rented it?
I bought it.
Models must make a lot of money.
You have been working
for only a few years.
You can buy a condo
worth ten million baht.
I’m working my butt off.
I can barely afford a condo in a suburb.
Why don’t you find a rich girlfriend?
She may buy you a condo.
No.
I will be more proud
to buy it with the money I earn.
It’s better to pretend to be nice
to a person I don’t love.
It’s a waste of time.
It’s not a big deal.
Everyone does the things they don’t like
to get what they want.
Just like you came to see me tonight.
Why do you want me so badly?
You are pretty…
and cute.
That’s all?
I heard it too many times.
I like your looks.
But I don’t know much about
your personality.
You hired a Michelin Star chef
to cook for us.
We drink wine.
We listen to classical music.
Then what?
What do hot people usually do?
I have my way.
But you seem to see through me.
You are now on top of me.
So I need to change my plan.
What’s the point of playing games?
It’s a waste of time.
To be honest,
you must have some feelings for me.
Those who have good taste
always fall for me.
Sorry.
I’m not that easy.
So I’ll choose to be
a person with bad taste tonight.
What did you take a picture of?
I took a picture of a beautiful woman
who sits here, crying alone.
Don’t take my picture again
if I don’t ask you.
I’m sorry.
I just wanted to make conversation.
Are you okay?
Even if I’m not okay,
I will act as if I am.
Are you crying for that jerk?
Yes, he is a jerk.
But we shared many good memories.
Though you shared good memories,
it can’t make up for the bad things
he did to you.
You sound experienced.
Have you been in a relationship?
Currently no.
I’m pretty good at relationship theories.
I can give good advice to my friends.
But when it comes to my own relationship,
I’m also a mess.
As we all know.
Though you look really pretty
when you cry,
I’d rather see you smile.
Smile.
Come on.
♪ When I fall in love with you,
I feel like I’m dancing along with music ♪
How did you know the song?
I’m not that young.
♪ It’s like I’m dancing in spotlights ♪
♪ From now on, we will have each other ♪
♪ My night will never get lonely ♪
♪ You will be the music in my heart ♪
Stay strong.
Stop crying.
Where do you take it?
Didn’t you say
you would have only one drink?
This is the fourth glass.
The drinks here are not strong.
I won’t get drunk.
You know you always get all chaotic
when you’re drunk.
But you will take care of me
if I’m drunk, right?
Is that so?
Yes.
When I wasn’t with you,
who took care of you?
I had to take care of myself.
It was sad, wasn’t it?
Let go of me.
You seem to be having a good time.
Hey, Shasha.
What are you doing here?
I feel bored staying at home.
So I decided to go out.
I tagged along with Prim.
I don’t have any friends here.
Prim is the only one who takes me around.
A friend and an ex are not the same.
Are you getting back together?
Exes can be friends.
Okay, if you insist that you are friends.
Does it mean…
Bambi is still available?
I think so.
Because no one steps up to claim me.
Can I join you?
Prim, Prim, Prim.
Thank you.
-Can I put a heart sticker on you?
-Sure.
I’ll put it on you, too.
Here.
You’re giving me two roses?
Thank you.
Hold on.
Sit down.
You’re unbelievable.
I allow you to get drunk only tonight.
After this, I don’t want you to feel hurt
because of him again.
Don’t lecture me.
I saw Bambi with Shasha.
You don’t need to take care of me.
For me, friends come first.
Are you alright?
Prim.
Is Min okay?
As you see.
Praew.
Can you watch Min for me?
I need to go in to get my friend.
Sure.
Thank you.
Min, I’ll be right back.
Are you okay?
I’ll be right back.
Please take care of her.
Pretty girl.
How are you doing?
Look at you.
You are so wasted.
Do I still look pretty?
Yes.
But I don’t want you to get drunk
because of that jerk.
Min.
You deserve to find good love.
Have you ever fallen in love?
I…
Min.
Why are you still single?
What’s wrong with being single?
Being single gives me freedom.
I don’t need to worry
if that person is mad or loves me.
It’s better to love myself.
That’s true.
Just view love as if it’s a game.
If you feel first, you will lose.
Yes.
When I date someone,
I always set clear rules
to define the relationship.
If they are too demanding,
I will leave them.
Those who set the rules
usually end up breaking them.
It depends…
if the person is worth enough
for me to break the rules.
Bambi.
Let’s go home.
Why leave so soon?
I’m not even drunk yet.
Do you need to wait
until you’re drunk to go home?
You know you get messy
when you’re drunk.
That was the old me.
The new me only falls asleep
when I’m drunk.
Do as you want.
I’m taking Min home.
Don’t worry, Prim.
I’ll take care of her.
Fine.
I don’t want a burden anyway.
Easy.
Lie down properly.
You are so heavy.
You sleep here for the meantime.
I’ll tidy up my room.
Then you can go in to sleep.
Thank you, bestie.
You should go take care of Bambi.
I can take care of myself.
What Bambi?
We are back at my room. She is not here.
Oh.
Where is she?
Why didn’t she come with us?
I don’t know.
Did you get dumped?
It’s okay.
Shut up.
Min.
You get messy when you’re drunk.
Are you avoiding me again?
No, I’m not.
Why would I have to do that?
Don’t worry.
You clearly said no to me.
I’ll stop pursuing you.
I know that
you have your eye on the director.
It’s good that you know.
So we can work without worries.
I’m not saying this to discourage you.
FYI.
Prim and Bambi are getting back together.
Hey.
If she were going to choose you,
she would have done it a long time ago.
She won’t keep you guessing like this.
Am I right?
Don’t speak for Prim.
She is unlike you.
Okay.
If you think you can compete with her ex,
then give it a try.
I’m telling you.
You will never be her only one.
Prim.
You looked tired.
You should get some rest.
I’ll go out to buy a coffee.
-Do you want one?
-Yes. Can you get me an Americano?
Thank you, bro.
Sure.
Actually, you don’t need to be here.
I’ll send a draft to you later.
No.
I want to see
the production process in detail.
Thank you for inviting me
to go with you last night.
I haven’t had this much fun
in a long time.
I didn’t invite you.
You invited yourself.
Shasha is even more attractive
in real life.
Whatever you’re going to do, be careful.
Careful of what?
Are you jealous?
Didn’t you say…
we’re not together,
so I have no right to feel jealous?
I’m not jealous.
I just want to warn you.
But if you don’t want to hear it,
it’s fine.
You can live however you want.
Bambi.
Get up.
No matter how many years have passed,
you’re still a bad liar.
Your facial expression and voice,
they show that you still care about me.
You don’t want anyone to be close to me.
What do you want, Bambi?
I just want to have you in my life.
Can we do that?
But as what?
Let’s get back together, Prim.
You’re still single.
Yes, I’m single.
But I’m not ready
to deal with your troubles.
I won’t cause you any trouble.
I will only make your heart flutter.
Are you okay?
I’m fine.
Hey.
Let me see.
It’s all red.
Don’t forget to get an ice pack
when you get home.
If they try to pick a fight with you again,
tell them that you are my friend.
I’ll take care of it.
Okay.
Thank you, Prim.
It’s not a big deal.
It’s good that
you are both pretty and tough.
You encouraged me and called me beautiful.
I now feel fired up.
You are pretty, I mean it.
You are my type.
Really?
Yes.
But I don’t want to be
in a relationship right now.
I want to focus on studying.
I’ll do it when I’m ready.
I’ll wait until you are ready.
Great.
♪ Wait until the day
you have no one left ♪
♪ Mark my words,
it’s because you are acting like this ♪
♪ You never care, look after,
love, or value me ♪
♪ I feel so satisfied
to see you cry today ♪
Bambi.
You got the wrong person.
Are you getting back with her?
It’s hard to get over your ex.
The new Min,
are you ready to try new things?
What are the new things
you’re talking about?
For example, kiss a girl.
Didn’t you say I’m not your type?
You can be my type for one night.
You have to admit I’m your only one.
You have a long way to prove yourself.