Happy New Year, Jay.
I feel like I'm going crazy.
Or am I crazy?
A lot has happened since I wore this uniform.
Episode E!!!
Why did you do that, Jay-jay?
You almost got carried away!
You are really crazy!
You are weak!
Later I'll go see King Asshole.
And after that…
I have already accepted Yuri's proposal.
So I shouldn't do this to Keifer.
Control yourself, Jay.
Yes?
Wow!
Jay, the room looks very nice.
Is this part of your New Year's resolution?
Yes, Auntie. A new look for a new life.
By the way, Yuri asked for permission.
He said he would pick you up. He might already be downstairs.
Okay, I'll go down a little bit.
Okay.
Yuri…
That's right.
I'm already engaged, so I shouldn't think about Keifer anymore.
You can do it, Jay-jay.
Let's forget what happened on New Year's Day.
Good morning.
Bring it to me, I'll take it.
No, it's okay. It's not heavy.
Why did you choose me? I can ride a bike by myself.
Of course - the fiance's duty.
Fiancee…
Wow, that sounds really heavy.
I'm not used to it.
Let's go.
No
She's not going with you.
Leave.
You are not the one who decides here.
Aries, it's okay. I want to talk to Yuri too.
If you had just listened to me,
You will not be created in the covenant.
Right?
Engagement ceremony...
Preparation...
Let's go.
Are you okay?
You have calmed down.
Of course, I'm fine.
Have you spoken to Angelo?
I'm not ready to talk to him yet.
I'm sorry, Jay.
I'm not honest about my feelings for you.
But from now on, I will be more honest.
We are engaged.
So I should be honest with him about what happened on New Year's Day.
Um, I have to confess something—
Is it about Keifer?
It's okay, Jay.
I don't want to hear any more.
I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologize.
I understand you,
But I will wait for you, Jay, no matter how long.
Until our wedding day.
If that's what it takes.
Yuri.
I'm fine, Jay.
Don't worry.
My only wish is for you to give me a chance.
Please don't close your heart.
I hope you still choose me in the end.
Honestly
I don't even know how I feel about Yuri.
Is there a crime?
Because he was kind to me?
Or is it because of my duty to my family?
Whatever happens, happens.
Um...
How will we tell our classmates?
I don't think they need to know.
Why?
It would cause chaos if they found out -
Especially since they know Keifer has feelings for you.
Yes, you're right. It can cause problems.
Great idea.
There.
That's good.
Ouch!
What is that for?
I don't want anything awkward between us, Jay.
Be like Jay, every time we're together.
And I will do the same.
You are right.
Ouch! That really hurts!
Isn't that enough, want one on your forehead too?
Let's go. We might be late.
Wait, wait.
- What? - I forgot something.
What?
I will go ahead.
Can I ask for another favor?
What?
Can you stop taking me home?
Someone might, you know, notice.
Okay.
Okay, Jay-jay. We'll do what's right.
You're engaged to Yuri, it's time to forget about Keif.
Fight!
S. Insults on the first day back?
Or do you miss my lips?
What? Kiefer!
- Stop this. - Why?
- What do you mean "why"? Keifer, please - stop what you're doing?
This! What are you doing right now? Stop flirting with me.
What's wrong if I flirt with you?
What's wrong if I flirt with the person I love?
It's wrong.
It's like I'm cheating on Yuri.
We are already engaged.
Stay away from me.
Cheating?
We are not in a relationship.
So how do we trick him?
You're not cheating Yuri.
Because we are not in a relationship.
If so, leave me alone!
We don't have a relationship, but...
You are mine.
You know what you're crazy about.
Crazy for you?
Yes, I think so.
I will wait for you, Jay, no matter how long.
Until our wedding day.
Fight!
You will pay for this!
Welcome back, guys!
Come on, hurry up, let's play a game.
Hey!
How was your vacation?
It's okay. What about you and Mika?
Apparently, they're out of condoms.
He even asked me for some. Said it wasn't enough.
- He asked you? - Stupid!
Ah!
Unbelievable!
– Ugh! - Hey!
You've all gone on vacation, but you're still bitter.
Are you -
Stop! It's the new year, have you changed?
- Of course, man! - That's right!
He gambled away all his Christmas money.
- Obviously. - You're really something.
You have no money!
Hey, hey! What's going on?
How is Grace?
She has a lot of passion.
- She is always hungry. - That's normal.
Just like you.
Oh really?
Oh, oh.
- It's too early in the morning. - You're disturbing me earlier!
Hey!
Collect your donations for food.
Ignore? What's wrong with him?
Where is Ci-N?
He's not here. He's not answering my calls.
Huh? What happened to him?
Should I go to their house later?
But what if his evil brother is there?
Hello, brother!
Bad!
What happened to your lips?
Did you go into battle?
Looks like your lips have seen some action, Keif.
Do you want lipstick?
You deserve it.
S.
Hey, what's up?
- Hey! - Hey!
To us, it seems like nothing has changed.
Hey, it didn't hit!
Throw it!
Ah! Hehe!
Fight!
Cool with that.
But the truth is that there have already been many changes.
- Hey, brother. - Ah!
Be determined, be determined.
Welcome back, class!
We have already started planning your retreat.
Are we included in that, sir?
All students attend a retreat before graduation.
Really? So we're really done with school, right?
What I can say is
There will be many activities during the break.
When, sir?
There is no exact date yet, but it will be sooner than the usual retreat.
It's just a little difficult because of the final exam.
What are the final exams?
There is a fifth exam.
And it determines whether the student passes the exam or not.
Huh?
Why is there a fifth exam?
What if the student doesn't pass the exam?
Don't worry Jay, I got you.
You will finish your studies.
Food!
Is that all?
That's all we have left.
You haven't been able to go into the store yet.
-Really! -You really are!
Okay, okay, okay.
Wow, hurry up, it's time to go in!
Do you hear anything?
One time!
It's okay here.
- Let's break it. - Ah!
Plate.
Rice.
More.
Just eat it already.
Move to one side.
And if I don't want to?
Do you want me to tell them what we did before New Year's Eve?
What do you want?
Nothing.
You just look cute when you eat.
Doesn't it look bad?
Yes! Go away!
Please help share.
Are all of those yours?
Is Jay in trouble?
No, he was just joking.
Are you sure?
Remember that you are mine.
Hey!
No one follows me!
No one follows you.
It's so good there!
Very refreshing!
I'm sure no one will bother me here.
Let me call you poor.
He won't answer.
Ouch!
Fight!
Who is that?
Edric!
I thought it was someone else!
What are you doing here?
Sorry.
I just can't help it.
Are you having problems?
I'm angry with myself!
I am such a coward!
Why?
Unfaithful love is very difficult!
I can't even tell her...
Or show her.
Yes, it's really hard.
But at least you're sure.
There is only one person.
It's even harder when you're stuck between two.
But who is it?
Wow, she's so pretty!
Freya is really beautiful.
Well, what is she really like?
Is that Freya?
F-Freya is what you're talking about?
Yes.
Jay, it's been a long time.
Wow, what a revelation.
But...
Let's keep this between us, okay?
Promise?
Don't you have any food?
Is that food?
Yes, we are eating downstairs.
And you are being amazing here.
Who is this?
- Auntie, I'm really hungry, I promise. - Look.
Don't worry, there's another box there.
All of that is for you.
Do we have guests?
Relax, there's more in the kitchen.
- This is delicious, aunt. - Good?
CNN?
You idiot!
What happened to you?
Do you know how worried I am?
Really?
Are you worried about me?
Wow, that's so sweet, Jay.
Don't do this, Jay-jay!
Sorry, aunt.
This child didn't go to school today.
I'll leave you two to catch up.
I will prepare dinner.
Thank you, aunt.
You have some nerves!
Enjoying too much food?
Why aren't you in class?
It hurts, Jay!
- Oh, really! - I'll tell you, aunt!
What happened to you?
What's the problem?
Because…
My brother locked me up.
He said...
He is sending me to London because I keep causing trouble.
Said I was wasting my potential.
Of course, I won't allow it.
Yes, he locked me in my room.
I'm worried about you.
Sorry…
He confiscated my equipment.
I can't send you a message.
Is that what he did?
He didn't hit you?
No!
Do you know why?
Why?
Because I ran away.
- Seriously? - Yes.
He said if I don't listen, I should leave.
Where are you going?
Here. With you!
Don't let them go crazy?!
Why not? Angelo said it was okay.
What is Angelo?
You created it!
Angelo, are you okay?
Yes, that's true.
Oh - see?
It hurts!
My new house.
They won't look for you?
No, Mom knows.
I told her.
Wow.
Of all the people who left the house, you were the only one who asked permission.
Great.
Of course - so Mom knows where I'm going.
Where are you going to sleep?
Angelo speaks in your room.
My room?
- Do you want some? - Yes.
Race you to your room!
Stupid! There's nothing to eat!
Hey!
Sh-N!
[Song in-N]
Good morning.
Get up! Your pillow is soaked with your saliva.
Ci-N, you are so cool!
It's so early!
I'll go ahead, Jay.
Go downstairs to eat.
Oh, it feels like home.
Oh, oh.
Has Aries done anything for you?
What? What did he do?
Let's go.
Huh?
Ci, wait - talk to me.
What has Aries done to you?
Is that true, Jay?
Are you leaving section E?
Did Aries tell you?
He said I should stay away from you because you are leaving.
No, don't stay away from me.
- Crazy. - Don't listen to him.
Who said that?
Who said you would leave Episode E?
Who is fighting?
Is there a cockfight?
Jay, are you leaving episode E?
No!
But that's what he said!
Why does he say that?
You don't want to be with us anymore, Jay?
We can still tolerate your bitter attitude.
I think we are strong in the E section.
– Ugh! - Yes.
We think nothing can separate us.
- Exactly. - Terrifying!
It's not like that!
Is it Aries?!
Keifer, stop!
Jay, don't leave! Stay on the E!
- Don't leave! - Enough!
- I don't care! - No, please!!
What is happening here?!
Jay-jay leaves the E!
-Stop! - Yes, please!
Is that true?
I am not!
Look - I'll explain later!
Go to Keifer first, he might go to Aries! Hurry up!
-Say, no one leaves! - Please!
I'm not leaving!
- That's terrible! - Really?
Yes! That's what I said!
Aries told me to choose:
I left the E section,
Or he won't give me my father's number.
But I chose you, right?! How are you?!
Come on, we have to follow Keifer!
Hurry up!
- Come on! - I don't want to! Why?
Are you paying me for this? I don't want to!
Get up!
Come here.
Is that it?!
Come on, hurry up!
What? Please end this now!
Okay, let's end it here.
Can anyone stop them?
Enough! Stop it!
I think the rumor is true, it's really messy here.
Can those losers get out of here?
Especially you!
That's enough! Don't you dare talk to Jay-jay like that!
Jay-jay, you need to leave.
Things are out of control because of you.
Like if.
Stop it, let's go.
Not unless you swear!
Swear before Aries, you will never leave us!
Now!
Sorry.
I'm sorry, Aries.
I've said this before, and I'll say it again.
I am not leaving Section E.
Yes!
Won't karma catch you for that?
That's your decision.
I hope you won't regret it.
You just lost the opportunity to be with your father.
How stupid!
Is this what you used to call Jay-jay?
Forgot who I am?
I always get what I want.
S.
Don't worry, Jay.
I promise I will connect you with your father.
How did you know I was here?
Oh! Edrix said you were walking around, here to get some fresh air.
It's not even a week into class, but you're already in the game.
My hand hurts.
Do it for me.
Ouch!
Sopheap!
Who told you to go into battle at that time?
Always lose your temper.
I'm sorry.
Wow! You know how to apologize.
"I'm sorry." Say it again.
Another one coming. Again.
Stop making fun of me.
I just apologize to you.
Why just me?
I'm sure you have a long list of people you need to apologize to.
Who is first? Aries and then -
I don't care.
I don't feel for them.
Only for you.
Whatever!
Please stay.
Keifer…
I'm not giving up on you, Jay.
I will fight for you.
What kind of dream?
It didn't happen, but it felt very real.
Enough, Jay-jay!
Good morning Jay! See you later.
CNN?
(Visit the website www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
I'm going ahead, Jay!
You couldn't wake up, you kept moaning.
Chuy!
That groom will definitely take it from me later.
Is he really leaving me?
And even took my motorbike with me!
- What? - It looks like you're late too.
I woke up late, how about you?
I also woke up late.
Okay, let's go.
What's wrong with you?
Don't look back.
- Why? - Someone is following us.
Wait, don't look.
What?
Call Keifer.
Huh?
Quickly.
Wait, wait.
There is a girl.
Hey, run!
Hey!
Jay-jay, I told you to leave, why are you still here?
Jay is leaving!
Girl!
I won't leave you here alone!
Go!
Are you okay?
I'm fine, how about you?
What is that?!
Do you think you've won?
That's just a hint of what's to come.
What do you need from us?
Hers.
We know she is Keifer's girlfriend.
Huh?! He's not my boyfriend!
He said to himself, "We have no relationship!"
Do you think we will believe you?
Jay, we have to avoid them.
How?
Just surrender Keifer's girlfriend to us so it's over.
This man is annoying.
Insisting on wanting everything, I'm not his girlfriend!
And it would be even messier if I gave her to you.
Hey!
We will move forward.
Where are you?
Why do I feel like something is wrong?
Can you contact her?
You don't have to hide it from me.
I already know.
I say this so it's clear...
I'm not backing down.
Even though we're engaged?
I don't care.
Let Jay-jay decide.
I will stop when she tells me to.
Why isn't Jay-jay still here?
Do you know where she is?
No
Kiefer!
The tracker shows that Jay-jay is resting in the hospital.
What?!
Drix go!
Guys, here!
Where is Jay?
I'm going crazy.
Miss, is there a Jasper Jean Mariano here?
Let me check.
Hurry up, miss!
I don't have time!
Sir, there is no Jasper Jean Mariano recognized here.
- Huh? - What time does she go to school?
A while ago, check again! Faster!
Excuse me, sir, but there is -
Miss, please check again.
Man, here!
Hey!
Jay, I'm coming.
Good thing the wound isn't deep.
You should not lift heavy objects for a week.
Where is Jay-jay?
She was there a while ago.
She disappeared suddenly, she was probably shocked and bleeding.
What did you say?
I don't know, brother.
She just started shaking when she saw me bleeding.
She didn't say...
She keeps crying.
Fuck ។
Since Mr. Ram's team is weak.
Everyone came out of nowhere.
And they all want to get Jay-jay
Because she's Keifer's girlfriend.
I don't know either.
I'm grateful that David came to help us.
If it weren't for him, we wouldn't have even made it to the hospital.
Rory, your coffee.
Next time, call me.
Don't try to be a hero.
Hello?
How is she?
She looked scared when I found them.
With all that blood, I thought it was her who was stabbed.
But she just hugged Rory.
Why did this happen?
What crazy thing did Keifer do to get Jay-jay involved again?
They all want to use Jay-jay to beat Keifer.
Huh?
Keifer never uses his head!
So, what are your plans?
Not yet.
But when I came back, they were better prepared.
Why?
Why am I not black?
Why don't I attack them, as I did to Cyrus and Ram?
A lot has happened since I wore this uniform.
Stop it!
But of them all, this is the worst.
Hey!
Keifer…
No.
Don't cry.
I'm here, don't cry.
Please don't cry, I'm here.
Don't cry, it's okay.
I am here.
Don't cry.
It's okay.
Is this your blood?
Are you in pain?
No
I think the same incident with Ram will happen again.
I'm scared.
It's okay, everything is fine.
Everything is fine.
Stop crying.
It's okay.
I saw a lot of blood.
But I didn't fall or hurt anyone.
And we will find the reason.
But for now, please clean up.
I know this is wrong because Yuri is already my fiancé.
But why do I feel this way?
When it comes to Keifer,
My feelings are specific.
Wait, what will you do?
You need to rest.
Just shut up and let me.
I'm not giving up on you, Jay.
I will fight for you.
Is this still a dream?
Wow, someone wake me up!
The game opens.
Don't let them take what's yours.
Because they dare to move boldly.
Follow your heart.
Don't listen to the noise and don't give them an inch.
Are you the one who teaches them?
Out of all the boys in Section E, 5 of us can do martial arts.
Six if you include mayo too.
Oh "Khat"!
- "Kapoor!" - Parker!
You said "Kapi"!
Fool, it's a park!
If I'm stupid, what about you?
You are interested!
Ah!
Offensive words.
I am jealous.
I can't help it, Jay.
You agree to be my fiancé.
Fuck it because of Jay-jay?!
Wait!
It's not what it seems!
Set!
Even blame Kit!
Stop talking to Jay-jay!
Go flirt on the E!
You are no different from Ella!