Oh, it's Tonfah?
Yes. I study here, and I
happened to run into Phoon.
Did Phoon mention Fun at all?
Didn't I already tell you?
You can study wherever you want,
but don't get involved with Tonfah again.
Is he hiding something from you?
Maybe.
I don't know… it's like if I make
even the slightest wrong move,
I'll lose him forever.
Are you sure he's just your brother?
Phoon is P'Fah's important little brother.
Do you even realize how
damn annoying you are, P'Fah?
To Thorfun.
In the end,
Phoon chose to hurt the
person I loved the most,
to protect someone else I loved.
Now there's no P'Fah anymore.
I hope Dad will love me a little more.
P'Fah asked if I hate him now.
No way. Even if I died, I'd still love P'Fah.
The person I hate the most in the world
is myself.
A world without Fun and
P'Fah feels so hard to live in.
But I already promised Fun.
So I'll try to live well.
Please pray for me, Fun.
Freshman?
Yeah, freshman.
Do we need to sign our names?
They told us to register here.
Uh… I'm Easter.
I'm Typhoon.
I'll treat.
Why?
Because you waited for me earlier.
It's really okay, though.
- Try it.
- So who are we waiting for?
My roommate.
Where the hell is he?
Why isn't he here yet?
Man, speak of the devil. Hurry up.
Phoon.
This is my roommate, North.
♪♪♪North—this is Phoon, my friend.
Wow, so I'm “♪♪♪North” now?
Yeah, suits you perfectly.
- Did you order mine not sweet?
- I did.
I ordered it extra sweet.
I don't like it.
Well, I do.
- If you like it, eat it yourself.
- Fine, but you're paying.
Again?
Phoon, don't go hanging
out with people like this.
I'm North, first-year
electrical engineering.
I'm Typhoon, first-year veterinary.
- Where are you from?
- Phuket.
Seriously?
Can you speak Southern Thai?
- I can't.
- Oh, you can't?
- What about you, North?
- I'm from Lampang.
But I'm not very good at it yet. I still
need to learn. I'll teach you later, okay?
Got it?
Translate it. Put subtitles up now.
Make them big. I'm confused.
Au means speaking. Bo-Chang
means you're not good at it.
Life in university isn't
as bad as I thought.
I think I'm doing pretty well.
Fun, you don't have to worry.
I met really good friends.
So good that I wonder
if someone like me really deserves them.
Didn't you say turn left? I followed you!
Well, that is left.
That's right.
But sometimes fate likes to play tricks.
Sorry.
Whatever.
Ter said someone would
come pick us up, right?
So we'll...
- Let's wait around here.
- Because no matter how far I get lost,
You're Ter's friend, right?
P'Fah will always find me.
P'Hill.
Snacks.
- Hi, Easter.
- Hi.
Here's a sandwich.
- Want some?
- Yeah, sure.
That's it for today. You can all go home.
Yay! Let's go!
Hey.
Let's go reading today.
So diligent.
Of course.
P'Mhor are always studying,
and I also want to see P'Hill.
That's called wanting to see your
boyfriend, not studying. Don't make excuses.
Here, Phoon. You want to take the
med exam, right? Got P'Mhor to tutor you.
Come on, please.
Even though deep down
I don't want you to pass.
Look at him, cursing his own friend.
Hey, I'm not cursing anyone.
What, you want me to stay alone
with you in the faculty or something?
- What's wrong with being with me?
- See? This is exactly what happens when I'm with you.
Phoon, look at your friend.
I'm gonna miss you.
Come on, let's go.
Mm.
Ugh, you're overthinking it
like it's an exam. Let's go.
- Fine, I'll go too.
- That's right, Foam. If Phoon's going, you have to go too.
I can't. I've got plans today.
With who?
I'm allowed to have plans
sometimes, you know.
You've got plans every day.
Just remember this—let your
girlfriend help you during exams then.
Ugh, stop nagging.
Hurry up, Phoon.
Our gang only has two people now.
Huh? Where's everyone else?
Probably buying snacks.
- They're on their way.
- Oh.
You sleep your life away.
And eating my space too.
That's just how it is.
Maybe… this is for the best.
Auntie Nuan.
Yes, Auntie Nuan.
How have you been, Phoon?
I'm doing well.
And you, Auntie Nuan?
I'm fine. Why haven't
you contacted me at all?
I'm sorry, Auntie. I've
been really busy lately.
Phoon, have you heard?
The house has been sold.
- Really?
- Yes.
Today the Mister asked me to
come pack things up for the last time.
There are still some of your things left, Phoon.
I just couldn't bring myself to throw them away.
Will you come back to the house?
Yes.
I still have some free days next week.
Alright then. Call me when you arrive.
I'll be waiting.
Okay.
Fun.
Another piece of proof of
the memories we shared…
Is about to disappear.
So what will you do next, Auntie Nuan?
I'll probably go back home
and take care of my grandchild.
I'm getting old already.
I don't think I'll look for another job.
That's good. You'll finally get some rest.
You raised me and Fun for so many years.
Shall we go see Fun first?
Yes.
Auntie Nuan…
Is it possible… that Fun is still here?
Phoon
I don't want to say this, but
still…
Those who have passed on are gone.
If you keep holding
on, it will only hurt more.
Fun wouldn't want you to be in pain either.
Fun…
Auntie misses you.
I'm back.
Did you miss me?
I'm sorry that I…
Couldn't come see you
every day like before.
You must've been so lonely.
I dream about you too, Fun.
In my dreams, it feels so real…
Sometimes I think…
You'll really come see me.
I'm sorry for being selfish.
Would you be mad at me, Fun,
if I wished you could stay?
I don't want you to go anywhere at all.
These are all that's left of Fun's things.
What should we do?
Can we donate them?
Would that be okay?
I think…
Fun would want them to be useful to others.
I'm not sure if I should say this,
but there's something.
I want you to know.
What is it?
Fun knew from the very beginning
that you weren't the
biological child of this family.
Really?
That night, Fun and I overheard
Miss and Mister arguing.
I was afraid Fun might not take it well,
but it turned out that…
Fun…
Still loved you just the same.
But after Fun passed away,
everything started to fall apart.
I didn't know what to do either.
Phoon, you're not the one
who destroyed this family.
Fun never thought that way.
Please don't blame yourself.
Thank you.
The truth I wanted you
to come see… is all of this.
Mister wanted me to throw these away.
But I secretly kept them.
What are they?
They've been sent since
you were one year old, Phoon.
Every year.
Around March.
Your birth month.
There's no sender's name, but…
There is a recipient's name.
My mom?
Miss threw away many of them already.
This is all I could secretly keep.
It's okay.
This is already enough.
Thank you, Auntie Nuan.
I hope things are the
way you think they are.
At least your real
mother still thinks of you.
But she must have had some reason…
That kept her from coming to see you.
Yes.
I hope she had a reason.
Any reason at all.
As long as it wasn't
because she didn't love me.
Back from Phuket yet?
Yeah, just got back to my room.
We're having a dinner party.
What's the occasion?
The occasion is that we feel like eating.
Who's going?
Me, North, P'Hill, and P'Hill's friends.
P'Hill's friends?
Yeah, lots of people. It'll be fun.
But…
Alright, I'll go.
Cool. I'll pick you up.
Mm, okay.
So are you going or not?
I think I won't go.
Because of Phoon?
Yeah.
He'd probably feel more
comfortable if I didn't go.
You should talk it out
already. It's awkward.
Does he even want to talk to me?
He can't even look at my face.
Okay, I'll stop. You get like
this every time Phoon comes up.
I'll tell them you're busy.
Mm.
P'Fah, look. The sky's so beautiful today.
Even though it rained so hard last night.
It's nice that the sky can
make you smile this much.
Hey!
So where the hell did Fah go?
He's busy.
What do you mean, busy?
Why are you asking so many
questions? Busy means busy.
You're annoying as hell.
Damn it, Jo, I only said two sentences.
- Asshole.
- Asshole?
What kind of asshole?
Hill, look at him picking on me.
Hey, didn't you say you were busy?
The more I think about it, the
more I feel like being free is better.
What do you mean, “being free is better”?
Arthit, I want to sit here.
The hell's wrong with you? There's
tons of space—go sit somewhere else.
Go sit next to Jo. Your fling.
Jo? My fling?
Yeah.
This asshole?
Come on, hurry up.
I'm doing this just for you.
I don't even want to sit there.
Next to that poser.
Want to move to another table?
Hey.
Long time no see.
Yeah.
Phoon, want some shrimp?
- Huh?
- Careful, it's dripping.
Looks damn good. Share some with me.
- Share what?
- The shrimp.
- What shrimp?
- The one you're peeling right now.
If you want shrimp, order your own.
Wow, North, you've got some nerve.
I never once complained about
you eating my stuff from the fridge.
- Stuff from the fridge?
- Yeah.
Weren't you buying it to share?
To share?
- Share with you?
- Yeah.
- You're the one stealing.
- Then just tell me next time.
Basic manners say you should ask first.
Since when do I have manners?
- You don't.
- Exactly.
- Give it to me.
- Don't eat it.
Two pieces. Peel them too.
Always me.
Good job.
Hey, peel it properly.
Shrimp. It's shrimp. Keep it neat.
Thank you.
Hey, why are they taking so long to pay?
Yeah, seriously.
Or are P'Mhor arguing over who should pay?
One thing's for sure—P'Arthit
won't be one of them.
Phoon.
Hm?
I've got something I want to ask you.
Jeez, you're stalling again.
When are you gonna ask?
I'll ask.
- So what's going on between you and P'Fah?
- Huh?
Damn it, North. You really
don't beat around the bush.
Who would even know how to answer that?
You keep going “uh… uh…” like that.
It's a long story.
Are you guys ready to hear it?
Ready. Totally ready.
Yeah, go on.
So…
So?
Me and P'Fah…
Yeah? What about it?
What are you guys talking about?
Oh—nothing, P'Hill.
I'm so full. Let's head back.
Bye, P'. Bye.
Bye, P'Hill.
See you.
What were you guys talking about?
Hmm… top-level secret.
If you want to know,
transfer some money first.
Go get it at home.
I'm heading off.
P'Jo, have you transferred yet?
- I'm coming with you, Jo.
- Why are you coming?
Dao? How did you get here?
Ta-da!
I called him myself.
I felt like the problem you're dealing with is
too big for just me and North to handle alone.
Don't tell me everyone
showing up this morning
was because of me and P'Fah?
Yeah.
So how long are you gonna
make me wait? Come inside.
- Fine.
- Go on in, Dao. Don't be shy.
Hey, aren't you gonna grab some snacks?
Come on, I'm starving.
Alright, you guys. Start talking.
Today, no need to wait
for Foam. He chose sleep.
Think about it—between friends
and sleep, he chose sleep.
And you? Between friends
and food, what do you choose?
- I choose 'between'
- Choose what? Be clear.
I choose everything.
I'll give you one more chance.
Fine—eating with friends.
You're such a glutton.
Come on, North.
Aren't you gonna eat?
Alright, let's do this.
The reason we're all here today...
Mm.
So what is it, exactly?
It's about me.
Yeah, I know it's about
you—but can you actually tell us?
It's about me.
My story.
Fine, then. I won't pry.
I just don't know how to explain it—like...
Relax, Maew. Just kidding.
So what is it?
Can you tell us?
Is it a secret?
A big secret?
A really big one.
I don't want anyone to know.
Especially...
P'Mhor.
But I have one request.
After I tell you
don't hate me, okay?
We don't hate you.
Even if you will scratch
us, we won't hate it.
You said it yourself—remember that.
In case one day you
feel like scratching us.
Yeah, no one's gonna hate you.
- You can relax.
- Then...
- Start talking.
- Yeah, go on.
So that's why you like taking
pictures of the sky, right?
Because you like P'Fah.
Honestly, after hearing everything
what the hell is wrong with your dad?
It makes me so mad just listening to it.
Thanks for getting angry on my behalf.
Yeah… not everyone
is ready to be a parent.
But still
he's already my dad.
And he's the only one I have left.
Yeah… you're really strong.
- Me?
- Yeah.
After all that, you can still smile.
You're seriously amazing.
Ah.
Hey, it's okay. Come on, group hug.
- Ouch!
- I'm joining too.
Thanks, everyone.
Alright, alright.
So… who's comforting who here?
It's just sad, okay?
Come on, it's not even your story.
It's okay.
Is that P'Fun?
Yeah.
You still keep the photo up like this.
Don't you miss her like crazy?
I miss her a lot.
My tear is back—pause it first.
Hey!
I've got a great idea for you.
Here.
Why don't we put our photo up?
Isn't that a bad idea?
Here—right here. You're the guardian
spirit, so you belong down here.
Ah—hey!
So I have to study while
staring at your faces?
- Exactly.
- Yep.
Like we're keeping you company.
That's nice.
He kind of like it.
- Don't ask me for more, though.
- Yea.
That's all I've got.
Just one photo.
So what are you gonna do about P'Fah?
I honestly don't know yet.
Are you just gonna let
things stay awkward like this?
It's just…
Not a good idea.
It's way too awkward.
Yeah, I noticed.
I think you and P'Fah are
- weird.
- Do you think P'Fah's mad at me, North?
For pushing him away like that?
If it were me?
I'd punch you.
- That bad?
- That bad. With a mouth like that, you deserve it.
Then you'd be first in line.
- I probably do deserve a punch.
- Yeah, bring your face here.
- Say no more.
- Hey, what are you doing?
He wants to get punched, is that okay?
(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
You scare him. Come here.
I've been thinking about this all along.
That I could get over P'Fah.
If I just stayed out of it, it should end.
But the more we see each other,
the more distant we feel.
I guess I just regret it.
That things can't go back to how they were.
And it hurts.
If in the end, I have to lose P'Fah.
So what was “before” like, then?
Well…
We took care of each other.
We worried about each other. We meant well.
I just want him to know that
if he has no one,
and he turns around,
he'll always find me right here.
No matter who I am in his life.
No matter who you are in his life?
I've got it.
A way for Maew to talk to P'Fah,
to look after him,
and let P'Fah know someone always cares.
What is it?
He's here.
Hey!
Let's see—what was the
first thing you gave P'Fah?
- What is it?
- A sandwich and chocolate milk.
Isn't that too basic?
I didn't know what he
liked, so I bought what I like.
But I think P'Fah would like it.
Hey, I already re-check with P'Hill.
You can take the stuff
and leave it before class.
Mm.
Have you written him a letter yet?
I have.
See? A smiling picture.
Even with zero expectations,
I'm still disappointed.
Why didn't you write at least a message?
So he'd know how you feel.
It's my first one. I didn't
know what to write.
Um… Hello.
That's way too basic.
You've gotta write more than that,
so he'll remember you.
P'Fah, I freaking like you so much.
Hey, that works!
I'm kidding.
Ugh.
But we agree, though.
We think he'd find it kind of funny.
Yeah, just write it. Trust me.
Okay.
Come on, you practiced forging
handwriting, right? Let me see.
I
Really like P'.
So much.
But if you call him “P',” won't
he know we're freshmen?
Yeah.
I think you should write “you.”
That way he won't know
if it's a senior or a junior.
Right?
- “You?”
- Yeah, write “you.” Better that way.
Smart for once.
In my whole life.
I really, really like you.
So much.
- Yeah.
- That's it. Exactly.
Let's do this.
Let's go. Let's go.
Do you think this method will really work?
You're already this far.
You can't back out now.
Or if Maew's not ready,
should we come another day?
Today's the day.
Be more confident.
Come on.
Hey, P'Arthit.
You scared the hell out of me.
What should we do?
Phoon, now's the moment.
Put it down there. He'll see it.
He'll take it to P'Fah himself. Go.
Right now.
Damn it.
P'Fah has hundreds of friends.
Why does it have to be
this idiot who needs to pee?
Then it has to be this idiot.
- On me.
- Huh?
Be careful, okay?
- North, stop messing around. Hurry up.
- Relax.
Why don't you rappel down next time?
To: Tonfah.
Do you think I'm a delivery rider or what?
Hey!
- What?!
- He just ate it.
What's wrong with him?
How come?
It's okay.
It's okay, man.
It's just a snack.
But I think the letter should reach him.
Yeah.
I guess.
Wait
I don't know, what if he ate the letter too?
Who the hell eats letters, North?
His name's Arthit, right?
Yeah, P'Fah's friend.
Bad attitude.
If he were nice, would he eat
someone else's stuff like that?
Fah.
Someone left this for you.
- Is it good?
- Yeah, it's good.
How many pieces is this today already?
You've got a lot of admirers lately.
Yeah.
Open it.
I thought you ate it all.
There's more.
Hey, there's milk left.
I really like you so much.
What are you smiling about?
Nothing.
Cute.
Is it worked?
Speak of the devil.
We'll begin the next
mission starting tomorrow.
I'd like to inform you that I've
found a delivery person for you.
Bobby is willing to deliver for you every
morning in exchange for one can of cola.
I guarantee that P'Fah will never
be able to trace it back to you. Over.
Copy that. Out!
Why chocolate milk anyway?
Because I like it.
And you bought just one?
- I could've bought them all.
- Ooh, big spender.
Hey!
That one's Bobby's.
Who's Bobby?
Cupid.
I mean Bobby.
He's a friend of my cousin.
Some distant relative, and...
Huh?
Well, Bobby is...
Just one is fine.
One is enough to fill P'Arthit anyway.
Better than throwing it away.
Yeah.
So about the letter...
Do you know what you're going to write yet?
Hmm.
I honestly have no idea yet.
Don't forget, man. Your first letter has to
make a grand debut. So he'll remember you.
Enough already.
Why make such a big deal out of it?
So P'Fah will be impressed.
I'll give it a try.
How dare you take my snacks out?
Where's the letter?
Here. I'm about to write it.
Hurry up. I've got class, you know.
What do you think of my handwriting?
- Looks natural?
- Hey, it works. Pretty convincing.
You're good at forging handwriting too.
Not weird, right?
Heh. Perfect.
Give this to Bobby too.
Roger that.
Count on me.
Hey.
See you.
P'Fah.
Um… someone asked me to give this to you.
Yes.
Thank you.
This morning, the weather is nice.
The sky is clear.
The sun isn't too harsh.
It's a good start to the day.
I hope you'll be happy all day long.
That Bobby guy delivered
it straight to P'Fah himself.
So what did P'Fah say?
He didn't say anything.
Okay.
Hey, it's fine. You're just getting started.
Yeah.
Don't you realize how many
people send him stuff every day?
True. This kind of thing takes consistency.
If you keep sending them,
you'll win him over eventually.
Exactly.
But...
Honestly, I don't want
to compete with anyone.
I just want to be by
P'Fah's side, in any way.
So many people like him anyway.
I don't think it has to be me.
- But it's impossible not to nope, right?
- Hope.
Well…
Just a little.
Only a little, though.
Yeah, so...
Why send letters anyway?
- Honestly, wouldn't adding him on LINE be easier?
- Come on.
I'd probably get blocked right away.
Maew likes writing letters,
so he's using the way he likes.
To express his feelings
to someone he likes.
That feels best.
Yeah, I mean...
Writing letters…
It's like reflecting on your own feelings.
Besides getting to...
Write to the person you love,
You also get to understand yourself.
Even if he doesn't reply to your letters.
Even if P'Tonfah doesn't reply,
At least he'll know that.
Someone out there likes him.
Yeah.
True.
That's better than liking
someone for nothing.
What do you mean,
liking someone for nothing?
Liking them and keeping it to yourself.
If you love someone and they don't
even know, what's the point in the end?
For me, meant well only has meaning
when it actually reaches someone.
Hey, hey. Ow.
So when you realized you liked P'Jo,
What did you do?
I told him straight up.
And I even gave him my gear.
- He gave him his gear before they were even dating.
- Of course.
If I like him, why would I hold back?
I don't think I could do that.
You don't have to be like
me. What you're doing is fine.
Don't overthink it yet.
Wait and see how P'Tonfah reacts first.
If he really isn't okay with
it, then you can step back.
Huh? Step back?
Hey, just back off like that?
- You just started.
- True.
I think you should keep sending letters
like this and see how he responds first.
But in the end, you have to let him know
that you're Typhoon who likes him.
Not just the kid next door.
Come on. You've got this.
Don't overthink it, Maew.
Is it good?
With them around, even
heavy things feel lighter.
I felt like I'd been given a
special blessing by you, Fun.
Since having friends,
I no longer felt abandoned.
Don't worry, Fun.
I'm stronger now.
I eat more, sleep more,
Smile and laugh,
And much happier.
And most importantly, I finally had
the courage to follow my own feelings.
From now on, it's up to P'Fah.
The weather is nice this morning.
The sky is clear, and
the sun isn't too hot.
It's a good way to start the day.
I hope you'll be happy all day.
Mm.
I don't think P'Fah likes it.
I won't tease you then.
I'm going.
Hello? Yes, yes.
Hurry up, hurry.
Let's go, go.
P'Fah, enjoy your meal.
Thank you.
You seem more okay than I expected.
How so?
I thought you were
going to back off already.
P'Fah didn't reply.
And there are other competitors too.
It's not that bad, even
though I want to talk to him.
If this is all it gets to
be, then this is all it is.
Do you remember what you told me, North?
At least it reached him.
My feelings.
I'm glad you're okay.
You've really grown up, Maew.
Jo, look at Fah. He's being possessive.
I guess you haven't eaten breakfast yet.
You might be wondering why I often give
you tuna sandwiches and chocolate milk.
It's not because I don't
know what else to give you.
I just think they taste good.
Hey.
What is it?
What's this?
Just open it.
Chocolate milk and
sandwiches really are delicious.
Make sure you finish them.
Caught you.
So, do you like him?
Not to the point of liking him yet.
I just want to get to know him more.
I feel like I could float right now.
Does he like you, or
the person in the letters?
He keeps trying to draw a line between us.
But I've never crossed that line.
Look at this. P'Fah is
totally flirting with you.
So what about the person
who sent the letters?
I think he's pretty cute.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Don't you want to know who he is?