If you really like her, face it.
Thank you.
Because of you, I've gathered my strength to fight.
If you don't choose me,
I'll destroy Gorya's life right now.
Let me go!
No one will ever have any problems with my girlfriend.
Huh?
I've been gone a while.
The school is as chaotic as before.
I trust everything's in order.
My pleasure to work with you on this project.
Likewise.
Keep in touch.
It's has been extremely busy at work lately.
Yes.
How is the trouble at the school going?
I checked. It's not Thyme's doing this time.
The kid who did it sorted it out.
But Thyme took care of the damages and handled everything himself.
Really?
By the way... do you know anything about this girl?
Not at all.
She might be one of the collaterals?
She happens to be a collateral in too many incidents.
Are you flying back to Thailand tonight?
Take care of it.
Make sure everything is put back in its rightful place.
Don't disappoint me.
You know well
that I hate changes,
any kind of changes.
Tulip symbolizes first love that is so romantic,
which fits well with the current mental state of Gorya
that is full of confusion
now that the man of her dreams has returned.
Bite me.
No! This is for sale.
What's the matter, Gorya?
Ren has been back for over a week.
Are you still hung up on him?
It's not that. I just feel a bit uneasy.
He... really has changed.
So?
Ren, why didn't you tell us you're coming back?
He never does.
He didn't tell us when he left.
He didn't tell us when he's back.
Missed you, dude.
Was I away for that long?
Hold on.
I haven't told you.
Gorya and I have agreed to go steady.
Wait, when did I agree...
Really?
I'm happy for you.
Now that Ren's back,
this calls for a celebration.
F4 reunion?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Are you coming?
Ren, this is exclusive to F4.
Girlfriends are not allowed.
Hey!
Bye!
I don't know. He's not the same.
Have you talked or done anything with him?
I haven't seen him. He's always with F4.
There it is. You can try to approach him.
If you feel weird, find something to talk to him about
or give him something.
Right, I haven't given back his handkerchief.
That thing? Hasn't it crumbled into pieces?
Use that handkerchief.
Give it back and find a moment to talk.
There's no point in you getting stuck in your head.
You haven't even talked to him. How can you know
if he's the same or different?
He may not have changed a bit.
You're right.
I'm with my F4 gang today.
(He's enjoying himself the most.)
Hey, Ren!
Man, you dog.
Heck! Take a look!
Mmm? Geez.
Take a screenshot!
Zoom it in!
What's wrong with your phone?
It's broken again!
Charger! Let's find a charger!
Where is it?
My girls... total chaos.
Let me borrow yours.
As Kocher High School was founded in 1986,
our school has created a large number of valuable members of society.
Today, I want to see all you here focus...
Announcement. Miss Thitara Jundee.
Miss Thitara Jundee,
come meet me at the back of the meeting hall. Now.
It's you. Can't you remember your name?
What are you looking at? Get up now.
Can't you see the teacher is waiting?
Come on.
I told you it's important and most urgent.
You know how many missed calls I got from you?
Here.
Look.
Here, see?
(Gorya - 83 missed calls)
See how many missed calls.
Look. Take a look.
What do you want from me?
My phone is broken.
Yeah, I figured as much.
Here, I got this for you.
What is this?
Don't you know?
It's a cellphone. Take it.
I know what it is.
Why would you give it to me? I don't want it.
Why are you being difficult?
Do you know how frustrating it is when I can't get a hold of you?
And wasn't it partly my fault that your phone is broken?
No, it's not.
Will you take it or not?
No.
No?
In that case, I'll leave it here.
Finders Keepers.
There's a phone here. Come and get it.
Fine. Are you happy?
Great.
Now I can contact you this Saturday for our date.
What date?
Our date. You and me.
We're going on an F4 kind of date.
An F4 kind of date?
I don't want to know what it's like.
And I don't want to go.
But I want to make it up to you.
Make sure your phone is on.
I'll tell you the time and place.
See you.
But I haven't said that I'll go.
You haven't said you won't come either.
I will not...
I can't hear. Hello, Kavin. What's up?
Ren wants to go out again?
What's going on with him since he got back from France?
Well, he wants to go, huh?
OK. OK.
You still hide out here like before?
I thought you wouldn't come here anymore.
Why?
I don't know. You seem different.
Don't you draw anymore?
I lost my sketchbook.
How has dating Thyme been treating you?
I'm not dating Thyme.
We're not a couple.
Thyme just assumes things.
You don't need to be so jumpy.
Even if you're dating him, we can still be friends.
That's right.
Or do you want to be more than friends?
We can date behind his back.
Thyme doesn't need to know.
That's all.
I'm kidding.
You're easily shocked.
Did you take it seriously?
Umm... I just wanted to return your handkerchief.
I forgot that you had it.
I should go.
Something...
you realize how important it is only when you get it back.
I didn't come back too late, did I?
(Maytee O Garden)
I can't take it anymore!
What's wrong with him?
He seduced you hard.
As old as I am, I couldn't help but... be infatuated.
True. But I think I'm jealous of my friend here.
She has admirers left and right.
One is her first crush who makes her heart flutter.
The other is a maniac that annoys her.
Who annoys her?
Don't tell me it's Thyme.
I thought you said he'd stopped bullying you.
I thought things were better.
Things are messier, uncle.
Don't just take my word for it.
(Thyme is happy.)
(Thyme is mad.)
(Reply now.)
It's kind of cute.
He has his stickers.
Let's come back to you.
What are you going to do?
Just say no?
I wanted to say no. But I could imagine a world of headaches that follows.
If I say no, there'll be more trouble from him.
True.
You should just go out and get it over with.
I'm going to the zoo with Tesla this Saturday anyway.
Tesla your boyfriend?
Yes.
If you don't have any idea where to go,
you can invite Thyme to come with us.
A double date like the movie.
I actually want to go.
The problem isn't me though.
What?
No way!
Do you want me to hang out with your friend, Gorya?
And the zoo? Please. It's so childish.
Do you want me to be a 'first' wheel?
I'm not going to correct that.
Whatever. I'm not going.
Fine, if you don't want to, don't come. I'm hanging up.
See? I knew it. It's over.
Can't you just be civil to each other?
Look at this, uncle. Look.
It's not over.
Answer it. Talk to him properly.
You can squeeze it while talking.
It may help relieve the pressure.
Are you not going to make it up to me?
Do I have to do everything you want?
I should be asking you that question.
Isn't it you who want to go to the zoo?
That's right.
What do you want? Tell me.
How about you ask me nicely?
Try this.
"P'Thyme, you're the coolest kha."
Why do I have to say that?
P'Thyme, you're the coolest kha.
"Would you please go on a date with me Nong Gorya kha?"
Would you please go on a date with me Nong Gorya kha?
And then...
Meow, meow.
I'll meow your ass.
If you don't do it, I won't go.
Come on. You're almost there.
Meow, meow.
This is legendary.
Agree.
Twirl for me.
You're going too far.
Just two times. Come on.
Actually, I haven't been to the zoo in a long time.
If you don't want to go, I can go instead.
You don't need to do that.
I show you mercy and you get off easy today.
Recognize that, Gorya. Hanging up now.
Argh! I can't stand it any longer!
What's wrong with him?
Does he earn a baht every time he gets his way and that's why he's so rich?
Calm down, meow, meow.
Kaning, don't tease me.
Geez, can it get any crazier?
Hello.
Welcome.
A date with Thyme?
A double date?
It's going to be crazy.
I'm really worried.
Aww... it's going to be fine.
Seeing that you're fine enough
to be worried about this kind of thing
is quite a relief.
You seem a bit odd, Tia.
Something on your mind?
It's nothing.
I'm just worried about you.
If there's something that makes you feel uncomfortable,
you can tell me.
OK?
Lately, there's Thyme.
And...
There's Ren.
He seems strange
like a different person.
That's normal, Gorya.
Anyone can change.
Look at Thyme.
From that day to today,
he's changed quite a lot.
Listen.
Being something you've never been before,
doing something you've never done before,
it's not easy.
It's not something that just happens.
There must be something important that affects you and changes you.
And I think
the most powerful thing
is love.
I'm always here for you.
Don't forget.
If there's any trouble, let me know right away.
Sure thing.
If Thyme wreaks havoc, I'll tell on him.
Sure.
I'll give him what he deserves.
I just want to squeeze you.
You can stop right here.
I can get home easily from here.
Thank you for the ride.
- See you, Gorya. - See you.
(Kaning: See you at the entrance of Safari World at 1 p.m.)
(And I think)
(the most powerful thing)
(is love.)
You're here again.
Ren, let me ask you honestly.
How was your trip to France?
France was like in the postcard.
What you imagined in your head,
that's exactly what it's like.
No.
I meant what happened with Mira.
I just wanted to know.
Oh.
Are you worried about me?
No need.
Mira was so happy when she saw me.
Thank you
for telling me not to avert my eyes from the problem.
When I took a close look, it turned out to be very good.
Really?
Really.
Let's talk about you now.
How has it been?
Same old.
Nothing to tell.
My life is boring.
That's not true at all.
Your life is colorful.
But I believe you about it being the same.
Are you the same in all aspects?
Because I'm not.
My bus is here.
I have to go.
What's going on with him?
Who are you stressing out about?
You have to ask? It's P'...
Which P' are you talking about?
Why didn't you pick up when I called? Where's your cellphone?
I must've forgotten it at the flower shop.
You look suspicious.
It's true. After the flower shop, I came straight home.
I didn't make a stop anywhere or see anyone.
Fine. It's just a cellphone.
What about tomorrow? When and where do you want to meet?
Do I pick you up?
No need. Let's meet in front of the zoo at the entrance.
1:00 p.m.
If you're there and it's raining, find a place to take cover.
Wisecrack, huh?
If you're late, I'll make you pay.
Be on time.
Hanging up.
Wait a sec.
Where did you get this from?
Thyme got it for me.
Huh?
You know it's not right.
Sis, don't just yell at me.
Dear, should we take this a dowry?
How can he be so insane?
It's going to be a long exhausting day tomorrow.
Ren! Ren! Ren! Ren!
Ren. I need a favor.
What is it?
It's not a big deal or anything. I just wanted to know...
how an ordinary person dresses when going to the zoo.
And I...
want your opinion.
Come on.
How about this? Is it OK?
Don't you think it's going to be too warm?
Warm?
True.
Not too warm.
This is not going to be too warm. Very thin.
That's too thin.
Here, wearing a tiger to see a tiger.
Here.
No?
This one.
You're going to the zoo, Thyme.
The zoo. The zoo.
Jiw, give me the binoculars.
This is it.
I went on safari in Africa in this getup.
Look. Here we go.
Are you laughing? Are you laughing at me?
What's wrong with my outfit? I'm serious about this.
Why aren't you serious with me? Why are you laughing?
I'm laughing because you're taking it seriously.
Speaking of which,
since you've been back, you hardly laugh.
I asked you about what happened there, but you wouldn't say anything.
You seem confused. Are you OK?
Let me choose a shirt for you.
Oh yeah, I was going to ask you to give it back to Gorya.
She dropped it when she met me.
Sis, are you going on a date or to war?
I don't know what mess Thyme will make.
I'm afraid.
Are you afraid that Thyme will be trouble
or that you won't be beautiful?
Don't tease me.
Sis, on a day like this, you don't need to do much.
Be your natural self.
Nothing is better than that.
Wow, wise words coming from you.
No, I got it from an ad.
Take a shower already.
I got it for you in case you want to add more confidence.
What am I not confident about?
Everything.
Be confident. Don't think too much.
When you're confident, things will work out for you.
Don't forget to use it.
Dress in a way that you feel confident.
What are you frustrated about? I didn't come late.
I'm not frustrated.
Are you sure?
Why do you look like that?
Your... outfit is cute.
What? The birds are loud.
- Your outfit is cute. - What?
Why do you keep asking me that?
I wasn't frustrated at first but I'm getting there.
Fine, I won't ask you anymore.
Please don't get upset today.
If not for me, do it for Kaning.
I love Kaning as much as my family.
Don't you think I have a calm 'demoner'?
Demeanor!
Your boyfriend is funny.
Are you doing word jokes?
Like... oops wrong word. No, that's correct.
Hello, Thyme. I'm Kaning.
This is Tesla, my boyfriend.
Tesla, this is Thyme and Gorya.
Bro, you can be chill with me.
OK, let's go inside.
It's now a 'suspicious' time.
Auspicious. Get it?
Why didn't you correct me?
Let's go in.
- Gorya. - Hmm?
Let's go inside.
It's going to be a disaster.
Hey!
No.
Gorya, look at this. Look at this.
Looks good.
Very good.
Yes.
- Boo! - Argh!
This is the first time in my life, I see someone eating ice cream with such anger.
What should we do, Gorya?
Thyme, look at this. Isn't it cute?
What kind of animal is this?
Who knows? Do you want it?
No, it's expensive.
I'll take one. Do you accept a credit card?
Shit! You're a sugar daddy.
I heard you're loaded.
How rich are you?
How about buying the whole booth?
No, why don't you buy the entire zoo?
Smartass.
The dolphin show is showing soon.
Let's split and we can meet up back here.
Let's do that. See you later.
Let's go, Tesla.
Tesla! Look at him. Look.
He's a smartass, right? 'Yes.' Right?
He is, right? 'Yes.' Right?
My ice cream is now melting on the floor.
Damn it! Look how much of a smartass he is. I can't.
Gorya, look. He said that guy is a smartass. Can't you see?
- Thyme. - Do you have another one?
I'll buy all.
I'll hit his face with this.
Should I hit him? "Yes, you should."
Hey,
I'm sorry.
I didn't know that Kaning's boyfriend would be like this.
You guys should learn how to pick a good guy.
Like me. Can't you find another one like me?
Sure.
How's today going so far?
Not including Tesla, it's going well.
I've never been out like this.
You've been great today.
You've been patient all day.
Thank you.
No need to thank me.
I just want to be a good boyfriend.
Thyme, let me set the record straight.
I didn't say yes to being your girlfriend that day.
We're not a couple.
I know.
I know that we're not a couple. You haven't said yes.
And I know what you're going to say today if I ask.
But I do it hoping I might soften your heart a bit.
So...
When I am confident, I will ask you.
Don't hurry to give your answer.
You do what you want again.
What else can I do?
I can only...
wait until you feel the same as I do.
You can be as strong-willed as you want.
I'll wait anyway.
You know that?
That's all it takes to make you blush.
You pinch my cheek so it turns red.
Let's take a picture.
My outfit works.
You said like you have hundreds of them.
More like thousands.
It's good that I had Ren to help me choose.
I wouldn't make it otherwise.
(Are you the same in all aspects?)
Gorya, your phone.
About that...
Thinking about it more carefully, I must've left it on the bus.
Really?
The last time I used it, I was talking to you at the shop.
Then, I took the bus home.
Didn't you make a stop to see someone?
No.
Don't buy another one for me.
I don't want to trouble you.
I'm going to the restroom.
Kaning's not my type. So bland.
Yeah.
I just wanted to switch for a change. She seemed so gullible.
But Kaning's friend... what's her name?
Gorya or something. She's really cute.
If I'd met her first, I would've gone for her.
No Kaning for me. Thank you.
That's right.
I have to go.
What's with the face, boy?
You're not that into her, are you?
I bet you're like me. Nail and bail.
Hey.
This Gorya... can I do her next?
What did you say?
What did you just say?
Thyme!
How could you say that?
How could you say that about Gorya?
Thyme, stop! What's wrong?
Gorya, let's go.
Are you alright?
Thyme, wait.
Let go of me.
Thyme, let's talk it out first.
Why did you do that?
I can't stand that guy and his foul mouth.
Tesla is just a guy who talks crap.
Couldn't you be a bit more patient?
Patient? Wasn't I patient enough today, Gorya?
Do you know what he said about you?
Whatever he said didn't give you the right to punch him.
You can't use violence to solve every problem.
That punch was mercy. I could've stomped him to the ground.
I used to think
that you're becoming a better person.
But it's a false hope.
You know why? Because you're still the same.
And I hate this kind of person.
(If it's important, you should hold on to it.)
You broke up?
It's not your fault, Kaning.
Tesla may have been upset.
This and that.
I don't know.
He may have wanted to break up with me for a while.
But if it's because of Thyme, you can't blame yourself.
How can I not?
I'm OK really. I'll get better soon.
You also have to sort things out, OK?
I have to go.
Talk later.
Thanks.
Hey,
is Thyme that bad?
Ouch!
Damn it!
Stop being upset over this, Thyme.
Shit!
Argh!
Take it easy. Here you go.
When are you going to clear the air with Gorya?
Gorya is something.
Does she think she's the only one who can get mad?
She wouldn't listen when I tried to explain.
She never sees me as a good person anyway.
I'd rather go back to the way I was.
Shit!
What's this for?
You couldn't cool down.
So we had to snap you out of it.
Be the same old you.
And make it up to Gorya.
Gorya has to make it up to me.
Professor, please teach him a lesson.
You know how you were back then.
It's not that surprising for Gorya to misunderstand you.
But it doesn't matter who's right or wrong anyway.
What really matters is whether you love her.
When you love someone, you're willing to approach them
no matter how angry or frustrated you are.
Got it?
Certain things need to be talked through.
If you don't,
you'll never know what the other person thinks.
Sometimes silence doesn't help.
You may not understand each other.
It doesn't mean you don't love each other.
Clear it up before it's too late.
Trust us on this.
You're good at saying something cool.
Of course.
So if she calls, you should make it up to her.
Thyme, is that Gorya?
- Gorya? - Yeah.
Hi, honey. Where are you?
You want to play?
Hello, Thyme.
(You guys are the worst!)
(Gorya, please be patient with Thyme.)
Rumor has it that he bought an apartment in Paris.
This is certainly something to congratulate and be jealous of.
Hey, you! You!
Don't you remember what I told you?
Be nice and win her back.
Fine, I'll be back.
How did we end up being matchmakers for these two?
I wonder.
News about the latest relationship of the hottest actor Dominique Shun.
A paparazzi leaked some photos
saying that they've known each other for over a year.
People speculate that they fell in love
when Dominique joined an immigration campaign earlier this year.
The Thai girl in focus is an ex-celeb
Mira - Renita Asavarattanakul.
Oh no, Ren must have found out a while ago.
(Rumor has it that he bought an apartment in Paris.)
Ren's phone is turned off.
So?
You heard?
You've known about it for a while, haven't you?
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have urged you to follow Mira.
Being brave enough to face the fact like you said
is surely better.
But you got rejected.
No.
It's the opposite.
Because of you,
I learned how Mira truly felt.
We talked.
We opened our hearts.
We spent time together.
It's the best time of my life.
So what happened?
Love alone is not enough.
It showed me
how Mira and I were so different.
It started from a small feeling
that I couldn't support her in any way.
And that feeling grew bigger.
It's strange...
we were so close.
Before I knew it,
I felt that she was drifting away.
Further and further.
And one day I realized that my world and her world
were certainly different.
It's true what they say.
No matter how much you love someone,
it doesn't mean you belong together.
So I decided to walk out of her life.
Truth hurts so much.
But it's good for her.
See?
She met someone better than me.
Don't say that.
It may be a misunderstanding.
No.
I'm not fooling myself this time.
(I wish you find new love that's better than me.)
This is the truth.
But it's good.
A worthless guy like me
will only hold Mira back.
Right?
Don't say that you're worthless.
How can you be worthless?
Don't you remember that day?
If you hadn't been there,
who knows what would've happened to me?
Don't think you're worthless
just because she doesn't love you.
I know that what I'm about to say
may not matter to you.
But you're precious to me.
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't be here.
You are never worthless,
at least that's how I feel.
Since the first day we met,
you've been an important person to me.
You're supposed to console me but you're crying harder.
Let's just stay like this for a while.
The car is ready with your suitcase in it.
You seem to particularly like tulips lately.
It means 'you never forget your first love', right?
No.
Have you heard about tulip mania?
It's a tulip crisis.
From the most expensive flower,
everything changed overnight.
I keep it to remind myself that changes are always dangerous.
The higher something rises to the top,
when it crashes,
the more dangerous it will get.
Kavin, MJ.
I made up my mind.
Ren is out of F4.
Are you serious?
Are you really going to break up F4?
Stop ignoring us.
Why is it so difficult to clear the air with Ren?
Let me ask you something.
If you have to choose between Thyme and me,
who would you choose?
Where are you going?
Ren asked me to meet at the school.
Great. I have something to talk to him.