(In Mourning)
(Sino-Japanese Trade Association
Appointment Ceremony)
(Letter of Appointment)
Congratulations, you're the president
of the Japanese Chamber of Commerce now.
Miss?
Miss.
You're back, miss.
- Congratulations.
- Congratulations, President Shen.
Congratulations.
Miss Lin is back.
=Echoes of Gang City=
=Episode 10=
(The Last Meeting)
It was you
who had people hide the news
of my father's death from me.
Yes.
You took over the Lin family business.
You're the new president
of the Sino-Japanese Chamber of Commerce.
Yes.
I, Lin Shuyi,
from this day on, cut all ties with you.
No matter how many lifetimes
there may be,
we are through for good.
(Former Fiancé)
Get out!
Miss Lin, Mr. Shen...
And this.
Mr. Fu said
it was once a whole piece.
But now the broken jade
can never be whole again.
He's done his best to repair it.
He hopes you'll still find
a good match in the future.
Mr. Shen, this is rude.
Things have been tense lately.
You should stop your operation for now.
We've broken off the engagement.
What I do
is none of your business.
Perfect. Take it back.
Gathering all the businessmen here
and threatening them
is an insult to our national pride.
We're all doing our best
to resist and push back.
We will never forget our principles.
This is a small token from us.
Mr. Shen.
Since your appointment,
trade between our harbors
has been running more smoothly.
It's just that shipping
through Xiangshao Harbor has declined.
The Xiangshao route
is Gang City's matter.
If you can't handle it,
there's even less I can do.
But don't worry.
The chamber will step in to assist,
mediate wherever possible,
and help everyone
through this.
It's a fine evening.
Let's set everything aside
and enjoy ourselves.
I'm reassured by your words.
Mr. Shen, Miss Lin is here.
They
are here too.
Thank you for your donations.
I thank you on behalf
of all the children at the orphanage.
Miss Lin, be careful.
Let's go.
Who are you?
Mr. Shen asked to speak with you.
You're injured.
Mr. Shen, you should
take care of yourself.
You're concerned about me?
There are more than just me
who want you dead now.
I'd rather you not die
at someone else's hands.
You're insane!
You chose this path.
You should know
nothing will happen between us.
You attend so many charity banquets
every day.
Are you not tired?
You might as well marry me.
You can have anything you want.
I'd rather die
than have anything to do with you.
Mr. Shen,
those people were here
to assassinate Miss Lin.
Why not you tell her the truth
so she can protect herself?
She knows exactly what she's facing.
But every extra charity ticket she sells
means thirty more crates
of medical supplies for the front line.
Shuyi won't give up.
What about you?
Me?
I look like a lost cause now.
If she stays tied to me,
she'll only face more danger.
I understand.
It's just hard to accept.
When everything is over,
I'll ask for her forgiveness.
I believe that day won't be far.
It won't be long.
Headline!
(Discount)
Two dead in the dance hall.
City on lockdown. Killer at large.
Headline!
Two dead in the dance hall.
City on lockdown. Killer at large.
What's wrong?
(Assassinate Lin Shuyi tonight)
Inform Mr. Zhou now.
Watch out!
Madam Liu, come here!
Miss!
Let's go.
What do we do now?
Keep a close watch.
Orders from above.
She must die tonight.
What are you doing here, Mr. Shen?
Go through the back door.
♪Tonight the rain falls soft and slow♪
♪Blending with letters left unread
drifting through the air♪
♪You turn and look back at me♪
♪In those same eyes familiar tears
quietly appear♪
♪It feels like we have carried so much♪
♪So many questions time itself
could not make clear♪
♪The moment you walked into my life♪
♪Every dream I had became something
I want with you near♪
♪How many letters have I written
just for you?♪
♪If only you could truly hear
what my heart is trying to say♪
♪From this life on no distance
could keep us apart♪
♪The promise we made♪
♪Will find its way to be fulfilled
one day♪
♪But I want more
than just that fleeting gaze♪
♪Still I have not heard your answer♪
♪Can we still rewrite the ending
we face?♪
♪When regrets begin to turn around you
will hear it all♪
♪Everything that leads me back to you♪