(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
STILL SHINING
Tae-seo.
The people you long to see
never appear in your dreams.
Tae-seo.
So…
this isn't a dream.
She'd never appear in one.
You're up.
I found a place that was open
this early in the morning.
These were leftovers from yesterday.
The mushy ones were even cheaper.
You should blend these.
Wait, you don't have a blender.
You should cut out the bad bits.
You didn't have food waste bags either.
You should buy some…
Stop staring.
Want some grapes?
I washed the ones that were still decent.
Have one.
It must be sour after brushing.
It's good.
Why didn't you wake me up?
When do you get off work?
At 6:00 p.m. You should've woken me up.
We could've stayed up all night together.
From now on, I'm going to be in Seoul
managing an old guesthouse,
so we can meet up for a bit after work.
We live close by now.
Take care.
-Bye.
-Okay, bye.
STILL SHINING
Due to the morning commute,
the train is very crowded.
Please be considerate of others.
We hope that somewhere today, joy…
something that brings you joy awaits you.
Thank you.
Hey, look at the compliments
coming in about Yeon Tae-seo.
Five, six.
What did he say?
"I hope something
that brings you joy awaits you."
I like that! Right?
He only ever says the train is
"Coming to a stop" or "Departing."
-Hey!
-Yes?
What did you say today?
Nothing much. Have a good one.
I hope you find joy too.
Right, you too.
Tae-seo.
Shall we go?
I heard this is a famous photo spot.
Yeon Namsan.
It's okay for you to face me now.
This can't be real.
It feels like a dream.
Do you want to walk a bit further?
Or want to take more photos here?
Let's go a bit further.
I dropped by a photo store on my way home
and had it developed.
Good night, Tae-seo.
I'll put these in the wash
at the laundromat on my way home.
Please put them in the dryer later,
and then bring them back here.
You'll have to make two trips.
I didn't hear anything about a laundromat.
I was told a professional laundry service
picks them up and brings them back.
They used to.
They quit a month ago.
The boss said he'd look for another one,
but who knows if he is.
I should eat a hearty meal
and keep my energy up.
PAYMENT COMPLETE
I'll come see you at work.
At work…
If I stop by Unit 203 after work,
it'll be around the time you get off.
I'll come to you.
I want to spend a day in your shoes.
All the things you see every day in Seoul,
I want to see too.
DONGJAK STATION EXIT 2
Mo Eun-a.
-Can I ask something?
-Sure.
Will you be staying in Unit 203?
Just for the time being.
They felt bad and let me
have the house for two weeks.
And I found a place to live.
It's where the previous manager lived.
The dates work out perfectly.
The Monday after next.
Are you free then? Anytime in the evening?
Hold on, I'll check.
I'm going to have a small party that day.
My roommate, you, and me.
The three of us. Nothing fancy.
The start of my life in Seoul.
I can make it.
It won't be easy
to follow my daily routine.
-What are you doing?
-What?
Do I need a full warm-up?
No, we're going to run.
Why are you only warming up your hands?
Come on, do your legs too.
One, two.
Three, four.
The other side.
I'm exhausted.
Let's take a break.
Are you okay?
So you see this every day
on your way home.
You'd have a great view
of the fireworks festival.
I was always so jealous
when Seoul would hold fireworks festivals.
It's right there.
That way.
It's that way.
So that's Yeouido.
Where's your energy?
So…
I don't know many restaurants
or any good food spots,
but this one's the best place I've tried,
and the food's high in protein.
There's one thing
I'm worried about though.
He's here.
You're both acting so shocked.
How could I not be shocked by this?
I've never seen Yeon Tae-seo
hang out with anyone else.
Right.
Yeon Tae-seo's always alone.
He'd always been studying by himself.
He has no friends.
Geez, were you like that over there too?
Boring, like eating rice with no meat?
Ma'am!
-Soju?
-You bet.
-Ma'am, I'm taking a bottle of soju!
-Okay.
Did Tae-seo ever mention me?
-Your name is…
-Mo Eun-a.
He bad-mouthed me, right? What did he say?
Come on, why does that matter?
The present is what counts.
You don't know who I am.
Right, today's the first time…
Actually, no!
You must be that…
By any chance, how old…
Never mind.
What? Tell me! Who is he talking about?
-No clue.
-That older girl.
Just drink.
Geez, how did that older girl
end up being forgotten like that?
Hey, Yeon Tae-seo.
We only dated briefly.
She was crazy about him. I even cried.
Now, I'm curious.
What did she do?
She was very pure.
Stop making things up.
She was purely persistent.
-And also, when was that again?
-"Also"?
-Perhaps…
-Nothing.
Right, there's nothing in my glass.
It looks like you can really drink.
Only take a glass or two.
I can't drink more than that.
I'd only drink just one glass
with the guests too.
Guests?
I used to run a guesthouse.
I poured my heart and soul into it,
but I got blindsided.
They took everything.
Man, that must've been hard. Cheers!
I got way too serious.
I'll stop here.
Yeah, we only just met.
I was a little thrown off.
Sorry.
A lot of girls liked Tae-seo
in high school, right?
-Nope. We went to an all-boys school.
-Yeah, it was all boys.
What?
But when he first transferred,
his bag was full of girls' name tags.
What? It was only one or two.
It must be from the study center.
You did something behind my back!
Hey, who did you get name tags from?
I told you it's rude to point like that.
Who was it?
Hey.
I saw that. Ma'am!
You don't allow takeout here.
Why does A-sol's family
always get special treatment?
Just let it go.
Are you okay? You were drinking a lot.
Yeah, I'm pleasantly tipsy.
So you were here
before you came to Yeonwoo.
Earlier…
what did you mean by "blindsided"?
I was living in the residence hall,
and then I thought I'd try living
in a proper house for once.
But I didn't rewrite the contract
when I turned it into a guesthouse.
They said it was fine.
But when I started doing well,
they kicked me out.
Then, I came to Seoul
and met Yeon Tae-seo.
How long did you go out
with that older girl?
A year.
A year is quite a long while
for Yeon Tae-seo.
That's how long I've known her for.
I dated her for…
less than a month, I think.
You?
That person you're ending things with.
How long did you two date?
About three months.
I've known him for longer.
Your profile hasn't changed.
We usually sat next to each other.
In the library and on bus trips.
It's strange, but when I think of you,
I think of your profile.
But something's different.
Maybe it's the air around you?
You're exactly the same.
I looked like this when I was 20?
No way.
There's something that's different.
You…
do these gestures when you're talking now.
What is this?
Did I not do that before?
You too, actually.
It was when you casually said earlier,
"A year."
That didn't feel like you.
But then again, maybe it is like you.
You and I both…
Well,
it's our first time seeing someone
we broke up with after ten years.
We didn't break up.
It didn't happen in person.
How can we break up
without even seeing each other?
-Hey…
-That's what I kept telling myself.
Then, I eventually accepted it.
"We didn't break up."
"I can't break up with Tae-seo like this."
We ended things in July, so…
I told myself that for six months.
Then…
Then?
Then, I stopped convincing myself.
What about you?
You didn't think of it that way at all?
When it's over, it's over.
I didn't think
there would be anything more.
It's over.
What we had then is over.
Now…
we're different,
but also the same…
No.
Never mind.
I'm surprised by that too.
It's the same.
My feelings are the same.
You're someone I liked ten years ago,
but I still feel the same way.
I didn't know that would be possible,
but it's been seamless.
Me too.
It was like that the moment I saw you.
I guess no one can defeat
Mo Eun-a from ten years ago…
except Mo Eun-a herself.
That's really nice.
It feels like
everything's been made up for.
Then…
we're back together again?
Thanks, Tae-seo.
Why would they fight in a study café?
Geez, kids are scary these days.
You can sit down. It's okay to ignore him.
Okay.
She's that girl from ten years ago, right?
I pretended not to know on purpose
and even talked about that older girl.
I made it sound like
you did just fine without her.
Give me one too.
-You don't smoke.
-Just give me one.
-Did you sleep well?
-Yes, we did.
I thought this might help you find
some nice places to visit around here.
Yes, thank you. We'll take a look.
Tell me what needs to stay
or be thrown away.
I'm cleaning out the back house.
You don't need to clean it out.
You want me to leave your things to rot?
Just tell me what you'll keep.
Send all the clothes and bedding
to the community center.
They'll sort it out themselves.
Just send the items
I've listed to Yeonwoo.
You're not even going to Yeonwoo.
Send me your address in Seoul
that I can send these to.
I'll come see you after I finish work.
Tell me your nearest station.
I'll go only as far as there.
Hello.
I'm Train Operator Choi Su-cheol.
-I took photos of Oido Station.
-Right.
-Hello.
I believe we've only spoken over texts
since train operators
rarely get to see each other.
Did you hear
about the frame size and wood type?
I did, but actually…
I'd like to change the photo.
Could you take a look?
-Do you have it with you?
-Yes.
Some had been taken before,
and a few were retaken.
-They're really good.
-Thank you.
-Sorry, one second.
-Sure.
I have to stay here this evening.
I'm meeting my boss for the first time
since coming to Seoul.
I think he has something to say to me.
Let's meet another day.
Those flowers…
Don't put them in the rooms.
If we stop doing that later,
people will complain.
And in the break room,
do not use the gas
under any circumstances.
There was a manager
who once secretly ate and slept there,
and then a fire broke out one night.
Okay.
What about the laundry service?
I'm trying to find one.
But maybe I'll make a laundry room.
What do you think?
A professional service is much better.
They use different equipment.
Washing machines
are really good these days.
By the way, when Hae-jin
handed over duties to you,
she didn't mention that
we don't have reservations from next week.
It's being rented out for two weeks.
They'll be filming here,
so it won't be busy.
You can just stay here
until you clock out.
SEONG-CHAN
YOU'RE NOT EVEN GOING TO YEONWOO
SEND ME YOUR ADDRESS IN SEOUL
THAT I CAN SEND THESE TO
Just leave my things to rot
in the back house.
Someone's exhausted.
Eun-a.
No, I just…
Sorry.
It's just that…
Somehow,
when I was feeling exhausted after work,
you're standing here right in front of me.
The very person I wanted to see.
How?
You should've said you wanted to see me.
Well…
It's not that hard.
I can be here in no time.
You made it through well today
in this tough city.
I need Yeon Tae-seo's broad back.
Not my arms but my back?
I need your back for today.
This feels nice.
Let's meet at my workplace today.
I'll send you the address.
You're really good at your job.
What is it?
The lamp's broken, so I'm checking it.
-Just wait one second.
-Okay.
Nice.
Thanks for the ice cream.
Hey.
I need some coffee.
Say "Ah."
Eat this. They say it helps you wake up.
Thanks. You're helping me focus.
Why does he want to change the photo?
Well…
Now that the exhibition
is really happening,
I guess he's unsure.
He even brought his old photos.
But I like that one.
Me too.
He said he'll think about it some more.
Is there anything I can do?
I want to help.
Should I clean up?
No, it's okay.
Put these photos on the board for me.
-Any way I want to?
-Sure.
Are these scraps? Can I use them?
Sure.
Are you going to keep living in Seoul?
That might be difficult.
Hui-seo's just bought me some time.
When my grandparents become
too much for him, I need to move back.
Was that your plan from the start?
Yeah.
Just for a brief while,
I thought I could put myself first.
My life here
has an expiration date.
Hui-seo might be able to handle it.
It'll be hard.
He still can't travel outside Yeonwoo.
He's made a life for himself in that town,
and I'm proud of him.
I can't wish for more.
Until when?
Why aren't you answering?
You asked, so I thought about it.
But…
I don't really know if that's up to me.
It could be sooner than expected
or much later.
I'll think about it when I get there.
Will you be able to settle things quickly
when the time comes?
I have to.
I hope it goes the way you want.
Do you…
see yourself getting married?
Yeah.
What about you?
I've never even dared to think about it.
You're going to live
in either Seoul or Yeonwoo, right?
I'll have to see.
Deciding where to live
isn't as easy as it seems.
Still,
wherever it is,
I feel comfortable when I'm with you.
When you're traveling,
that place feels like reality,
and your actual home feels distant.
But when you come back,
your home feels real,
and where you were feels distant,
as if it was fake.
It felt unreal being in Seoul.
I ended up coming here out of nowhere.
I told myself this wasn't real
and I was trapped inside a lie.
But when I look at you,
this place feels real.
I think, "That's right."
"It was here."
You were here,
so it became real.
You said the same thing back then.
You remember that?
So…
stay right by my side.
Okay, I will.
When was your loneliest birthday?
Where did that come from?
We've never celebrated our birthdays.
Mine's July 28th,
the day before you transferred.
Yours is November 9th.
But you never told me,
so we just spent it studying.
Tell me. I just need to write the date.
When was your loneliest birthday?
It was in 2016 when I was in the army.
Besides 2016.
Last year? I'll pick last year.
Were you lonely last year?
You told me to think about it,
so I did just that.
It doesn't mean anything.
Ta-da!
Congratulations on the last birthday
of your twenties.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
NOVEMBER 9, 2024
And my present?
Your present?
Your present…
Happy birthday.
Happy?
Hui-seo's calling.
It must be urgent.
You should pick up.
One second.
Hey, Hui-seo.
You know Grandma's going
to the hospital next week?
I know. She's getting a checkup.
I'm going to take her,
so I just called to tell you not to worry.
Weren't you worried?
Why would I be? You'll do just fine.
Anyway, just give Grandma a call.
Do I really have to remind you
to call her though?
You could at least say,
"I should be there, but I can't go.
Man, I feel terrible."
Is that so hard?
Don't you even feel sorry for me?
Thank you,
Hui-seo.
Sure.
Don't forget to call Grandma.
I'll call first thing in the morning.
Okay, bye.
This is for 2023.
This is for 2022.
This is for 2021.
This godeulppaegi kimchi is amazing.
Have it with some soup.
I made a lot of kimchi.
Who knows what might happen
when I visit the hospital next week?
You're just going in for a checkup
and coming straight home.
Tae-seo likes kimchi,
but there's no way to get it to him.
Why is there so much?
It's a year's worth.
Some of it's for other clients too.
Will Tae-seo be home?
Of course not.
I can't fit into his schedule.
I can just leave these inside.
It seems he got more jobs.
-Jobs?
-Yeah.
What on earth is he up to?
I'm coming with you.
I'll be coming back late at night
after I visit all my clients.
That's fine by me.
My brother will be shocked to see me.
Are you sure you can go?
What about the post office?
I worked the morning shift today.
Are you here to pick up the wood?
Don't tell my grandma.
I'll say I'm going to work.
Grandma.
Jin-su said he can bring
the kimchi to Tae-seo.
Could you pack some up?
Goodness.
Thank you so much.
I'll go pack it up right now, okay?
Sure.
"Amy Park."
Amy Park.
I came to see you.
This is nice.
I can't believe how nice it is.
Have a pleasant stay.
Eun-a.
Mo Eun-a!
Here, give it to me.
Geez, I knew he'd be living like this.
Cup noodles and rice snacks.
Honestly.
You're beaming
now that you're at your brother's.
He'll be happy to see you.
-You should go do your rounds.
-Okay.
I'll call you on my way here.
I'll come as soon as possible.
Don't worry about me.
This is my brother's place.
I can sleep over if I have to.
-See you.
-Bye.
Geez, look at all that laundry
lying around.
One, two.
He still wears his gym shorts?
Are they his favorite or something?
Of course, he's not here.
I sent the painting by courier.
He complained there was no elevator.
-He left it in front of…
-Excuse me?
Granny.
It looks like Mo Eun-a's house
got international mail again.
It's from Hawaii this time.
Granny?
Granny!
You're Mr. Yeon Tae-seo's brother?
Yes, why do you ask?
I told him I'd send it by courier,
but I had time so I came in person.
You can just leave it here.
Okay.
I'll leave it with you.
Hi, Hyang-gi. What is it?
Could you help me up?
Right, sure.
3 MISSED CALLS
OLD HOUSE IM A-SOL
-I can't get into it right now.
-Sorry?
Your grandmother collapsed.
I met your brother at your house.
We're on our way to the hospital,
so please come right away.
I'll explain everything later.
I was told you know which hospital it is.
Please put Hui-seo on the phone.
He's asleep. I think it was the nerves.
He's allowed to visit his brother, right?
As for me, I was going to send
the painting by courier, but--
Hui-seo.
You can hear me, right?
I just finished my work,
so I can come right away.
Don't get anxious
and massage your leg on the way.
Don't be nervous. Keep breathing.
It's okay.
Okay, Tae-seo.
Hello? I don't think
I can make tomorrow's shift.
Yes. Okay, thank you.
Let's get some bean sprout and rice soup.
I'm feeling a bit sick
after all that wine on the plane.
I need to cure my hangover.
I'll have one delivered here, ma'am.
Let's go to a restaurant and eat!
That hits the spot.
I feel so much better now.
It's a good thing
you broke up with Seong-chan.
He has to have you all to himself
and make you work with only him,
so you end up all alone.
So you still talk to him.
But he's not a bad person.
He's paying for the lawsuit.
He doesn't even have that kind of money.
He's going to spend
his entire life savings on that suit.
That's not going to solve anything.
I'm not done yet.
Don't stay at Na-yeong's either.
Why are you wandering around
as if you don't have a home?
When Na-yeong told me where you worked,
she acted like
she was doing me a huge favor.
There's only one person
who knows where I am and told Na-yeong.
Now, to the main point.
The guesthouse you used to run.
You need to go back to it.
Seong-chan's bent on a lawsuit
I didn't even ask for, and now you.
What's with you two? What is your deal?
I don't know what he's thinking.
I came to settle your situation.
That guesthouse you ran.
Seong-chan only found out
about it through me.
How else would he have known?
I knew about it because
I was going around looking into things.
I'm saying the property owner
is someone I know.
I'm going to settle this.
You just take back what's yours
and go back to living your life.
You're at it again.
Are you that desperate to play my mom?
You should be good to your own mother
and stop causing her grief.
I'm here because my mom made such a fuss.
She prays for you at dawn every day.
She barely knows you,
and yet she prefers you over me.
You have the right to stay there
until your lease is up,
so run your guesthouse.
After that, I can't stop them.
Then…
go back to Yeonwoo.
It's your home.
-If you don't like Yeonwoo…
-You go to Yeonwoo.
It's been empty for ten years.
Anything else you want me to do?
Anything while I'm there?
You're not going to do
what I ask you to do anyway.
I asked you to stay by his side.
I have a lot to say too.
This grief
can only be shared
by you and me.
In this world…
there's no one else.
We should at least
look out for each other
and be honest about how we feel.
Let's stay together today.
At least for today.
I won't be able to sleep
from the jet lag anyway,
so let's catch up…
This is exactly why I didn't want to come.
I'm on my way to Yeonwoo.
My grandma suddenly collapsed.
Hui-seo's not doing so well either,
so I'm going to stay with him.
Is she okay?
She has to be.
This grief
can only be shared
by you and me.
Let's stay together today.
At least for today.
Eun-a, is that you?
Hello.
First off, we've taken care
of the bleeding.
Given the patient's age,
recovery may take a bit longer.
But the surgery went well,
so let's see how it goes.
-All right, then.
-Thank you.
Basically…
Grandma wanted to send you
some of her godeulppaegi kimchi,
and I wanted to lift her spirits
before the checkup.
That's why I went…
Good.
It's about time you got out of Yeonwoo.
It's purely psychological,
so be confident in yourself.
You have strength in your leg,
so you'll be discharged in a week.
You're perfectly healthy.
It's swollen.
Don't tell Grandma.
It won't help with her recovery.
And do that girl's frame for free.
The girl who drove me here.
I will.
I had some extra soft tofu stew
at a famous spot,
and I'm about to depart now.
How did the surgery go?
It went well.
What a relief.
I kept imagining the worst,
so I couldn't even eat properly.
Where are you right now?
Grandpa.
Hey.
The person who drove Hui-seo here
is still in Gangneung.
She's heading to Seoul now,
so I'm going to drive her back.
Yeah, you should.
Don't worry about things here.
The surgery went well, so she'll be fine.
I'll come right back tomorrow morning.
Just rest at home.
You'll be driving all night.
No, I'll come.
TAE-SEO, I'LL WAIT FOR YOU
KEEP ME UPDATED EVEN IF IT'S LATE
I was wondering whether I should
stay the night and leave tomorrow.
If you get short-term car insurance,
I can drive your car.
Add me as the driver. I'll pay the fee.
That's a thing?
ONE-DAY CAR INSURANCE
I found it.
I'd be very grateful.
I'm the one who's grateful.
Hui-seo never really comes to my place.
So that's where you live. Your place.
It kicks in at midnight, so…
Can we stay for ten more minutes?
Sure.
The surgery went well.
You don't need to worry.
I knew it would.
I know your grandma well.
She's strong.
-Hey, Hyeong-seok.
-Hey!
Was the name tag…
Was it Im Ji-sol?
If it was, you can't do that to me.
You should've told me.
It wasn't.
I asked her out
and got completely humiliated.
When I think about that time…
It still makes me cringe.
I must've been out of my mind back then.
Hey, hang up.
I'm going to call Mi-ju.
Yeah, you do that. Bye.
Im Ji-sol?
Im Ji-sol…
Im A-sol.
You can sleep the whole way there.
You must be exhausted.
It's a long night drive,
so I should keep you company.
I'll drive to where you live.
No, you can drive to yours.
My place isn't far from there.
It'll be dawn when we get to Seoul.
You won't be able to find a cab.
-All right, let's go.
-Okay.
By the way…
Weren't you asleep?
Earlier…
you said you'd drive to where I live.
How did you know?
When we first met,
you went home while we were talking
to get the painting.
You said it was five minutes
from where we met.
Right.
And you're the only person who's allowed
takeout at the restaurant with my frame.
And you studied
at Hyeong-seok's study center.
My name tag's in Yeonwoo, isn't it?
No wonder I felt drawn to that place.
Then, let's be friends from now on.
You don't mind, right?
Well…
Okay, we've cleared that up.
Anything you want to ask me
about the past?
-You can go ahead.
-I don't.
Go to sleep, Ms. Im. We'll be a while.
I said we should be friends.
Sleep.
SEONG-CHAN
You know how to get home from here, right?
I came because I missed her,
but maybe I shouldn't have come.
How's Eun-a?
It's just upsetting
to see her struggling alone
in an empty guesthouse.
Get away from there.
STILL SHINING
You put so much care and effort
into that place.
Now you can have it all back.
What exactly is the problem?
Does that Seong-chan guy
have something to do with your guesthouse?
I'm not in Seoul.
Missing each other,
being drained emotionally…
I'll explain everything in person.
We were talking about our future
just the other day.
I have to make it back today.
In the past decade of Eun-a's life,
he was the only one present.
Subtitle translation by: Hyesoo Lee