ظآزJust To Meet You, you fell for meظآز
ظآزJust to meet me, into my trap you fellظآز
ظآزWanna┬بtry a breathless love?ظآز
ظآزEvery move hits the heart, close and sureظآز
ظآزJust To Meet You, you love my┬بplayful charmظآز
ظآزJust to meet me,
my romantic little schemes for youظآز
ظآزWanna play another brand-new game?ظآز
ظآزLayer by layer, we close the gapظآز
=Just To Meet You=
(This is my last wedding.)
(Once I get this money,)
(I can hire someone to find Xiaodi.)
- Xiaodi.
- If he dies,
then that's just his fate.
We can't afford his treatment.
I'm begging you.
His condition is critical.
The surgery can't be delayed any longer.
Please save Xiaodi.
(Xiaodi.)
(You have to stay alive.)
I'll agree to the marriage.
(Once I get the money from the Li family,)
(I'll take you for surgery.)
(Li Family Wedding Venue)
With that face and that figure,
no wonder she's known
as the "Bloody Peony"of Manlong.
What's the point?
Three husbands already died
after marrying her.
(Jiang Niannian)
This wedding
(Liu Yexi, Madam of the Li Family)
can't afford a single mistake.
(Zhong Minghui, Li Family Butler)
Don't worry, Ma'am.
Once she goes in,
she's not coming out alive.
I'm rich.
So much money.
Xiaodi's surgery is finally covered.
Oh my!
A dead man.
I knew Liu Qin was up to no good.
I, Jiang Niannian,
have been married three times.
I've seen it all.
Marrying a dead man?
That doesn't scare me.
=Episode 1=
=My Husband Came Back from the Dead!=
Jiang Feng.
Liu Qin.
You're trying to kill me?
Once I get out,
I'll make you pay.
(Before I go,)
(let me see)
(what my last husband)
(looks like.)
Such a handsome faceظخ
What a waste
to be buried here.
Still alive.
From my experience,
a dead husband
is the best husband.
Jiang...
Niannian.
Mr. Ghost.
No,
Handsome Ghost,
please let me go.
I'm not Jiang Niannian
who is your match.
(Ye Lang, Young Master of the Li Family)
It's you.
I've finally found you.
(A lustful ghost?)
Are you a human or a ghost?
You're warm.
You have a heartbeat.
And...
Pecs.
So,
not scared of me being a ghost?
(Money matters most.)
(If I can take all burial goods with me,)
(I'll make a fortune.)
Since you're still alive,
then how about we...
What's that sound?
Oh no.
A bomb!
Only fifteen seconds left.
There's no way to take it all.
- Now go.
- What are you doing?
- It's about to explode!
- No.
I still haven't got that gold necklace.
What are you doing?
I won't let anything happen to you.
There's still time.
I can't walk away with nothing.
At a time like this,
do you want money or your life?
(It's all gone.)
(This whole job)
(was a total loss all around.)
Are you hurt?
Do you feel unwell anywhere?
No idea if there are more bombs around.
You should stay close to me.
(I think the explosives were meant for you.)
(The mastermind won't stop)
(if he finds out we're still alive.)
I think
we should split up for now.
Besides,
I don't want to drag you down.
Niannian,
I just don't want anyone to hurt you.
But I don't want
to drag you into this either.
Once this crisis is over,
if fate allows,
we'll meet again.
(Maybe never.)
Xiaodi is missing.
And his brain cancer needs treatment.
I got nothing this time.
I'm going back for Jiang Feng and Liu Qin.
I'll make them pay it all back.
Anyone there?
(That was fast.)
(Was the snake your doing?)
(This time,)
(I won't let you get hurt again.)
Niannian.
Jiang Niannian!
Niannian!
What are you doing here?
Didn't you say
if it's fate,
we'd meet again?
(A watch worth 30 million.)
(I'll take it.)
What?
Did that hurt?
You saved me.
Aren't you scared I'll use you again?
Try it.
See
if you can still walk.
To think you could do that too.
Of course.
After all...
I'm
the one my family
sees as a thorn.
I didn't expect
you've been through the same.
I'm the family outcast too.
I won't let anyone hurt you again.
And you're not afraid
that I might hurt you?
No, I'm not.
Even if you wanted me dead,
I'd accept it.
As long as you don't leave me.
Don't worry.
I'm not leaving you.
You clueless...
idiot.
Keep dreaming your sweet dream.
I don't pity men.
Ye Lang.
Ye Lang!
You liar.
I really like you.
Please don't leave me.
That face...
That body...
Way better than my first three husbands.
So today,
I'm taking your money,
and you.
ظآزClose your eyesظآز
ظآزWhat do you see?ظآز
ظآزIt's quiet in the skyظآز
ظآزI love youظآز
ظآزAnd don't be shyظآز
ظآزCome to meظآز
ظآزDeep inside of your mindظآز
ظآزYou want tooظآز
ظآزLike a fireظآز
ظآزAnd all the words that you never sayظآز
Niannian.
Niannian?
Niannian, stop it.
Niannian.
Jiang Niannian, where are you?
(Previous Life)
Niannian.
From now on,
let's never be apart again.
Niannian.
It turns out
that when people are truly happy,
they can actually feel pain.
Go to hell.
Why did you
kill me?
(I won't repeat my past life's mistake.)
Look.
I don't care
if you have to search all of Manlong,
find her.
ظآزStitched-up lips
tear open a blood-red duskظآز
ظآزYou return reborn,
seeing through all my cracksظآز
ظآزThis tenderness, a trap or a gift? ظآز
ظآزStill, I'd wager my next life on itظآز
ظآزJust for a moment to recognize you againظآز
ظآزYou are the blazing light in my despairظآز
ظآزLighting the edges of my frozen wingsظآز
ظآزI burn myself,
leaping into an illusion of fireظآز
ظآزBreaking free
from dead vines in the ashesظآز
ظآزYou are the brightest star in the nightظآز
ظآزAwakening my dormant fateظآز
ظآزFreeing me from this half-life prisonظآز
ظآزAs the bells shatter the pastظآز
ظآزLife finds its way againظآز