♪Shrugging off past burdens♪
♪Beneath the mask, who am I?♪
♪Release and find wider shores♪
♪Love's a riddle, and rain pours heavy♪
♪Crossed paths, now downward fall♪
♪From dust arises starlight's spark♪
♪Tearing through
the night's dense blockade♪
♪Heart's flame illuminates all solitude♪
♪Let time's sails drift endlessly♪
♪Through wandering exile♪
♪Breaking free from the cocoon,
I start anew♪
♪Moon as song, life as flame♪
♪Nameless heart clings fiercely♪
♪Let me♪
♪Charge toward the next raging river♪
♪Moon darts, snow falls♪
♪We tread rugged paths to reunite♪
♪Hands held tight♪
♪We forever live for love's sake♪
♪Shadow's spear burns fiercely♪
=Legend of The Female General=
=Episode 32=
Take your positions.
Offer incense.
Present jade and silk.
Kneel.
Bow.
Rise.
Bow again.
Bow thrice.
Rise.
Get up.
The winter sacrificial ceremony
is concluded.
Officials,
please proceed to Longtai Hall.
Yan He.
When did you arrive?
I always thought
you were short and thin,
but never expected you were a woman.
Well...
Do you look down on me
and disdain being friends with me
because I'm a woman now?
Do you think
I am that kind of base person?
I'm angry because
you and Xiao Jue hid this from me.
We had to.
I didn't want to either.
By the way,
how is your wife recently?
She's quite well.
The baby
has behaved.
But the Huayuan battle
turned out like this,
how dare He Rufei show his face here?
Excellent.
Everyone is here.
Let's go.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Rise, everyone.
I am Maningbu,
greetings to Emperor Wei.
You have traveled far,
must be weary.
As a foreign envoy,
I've heard of
your ear for talent
and prudent governance.
What a model ruler of our age.
I deeply respect you.
Today,
I want to offer you a toast.
Your words
are really flattering me.
Your generous hospitality
really moves me.
Wei and Wutuo are neighbors,
so we should share brotherly bonds
as we do now in harmony.
With this opportunity,
Wutuo wishes to ally with Wei,
bonding our relationship,
and ending all conflicts.
If we can truly cease the war,
nothing could be better.
After our alliance is sealed
and establish trade markets,
I'm sure we can
get peace and benefits.
Regarding the trade markets,
details to be confirmed.
Please be more patient.
It seems Wei
lacks sincerity in facilitating
the alliance.
What?
We must let Wutuo gain all advantages
to prove our sincerity?
Marquis Wu'an.
You are
being too arrogant.
Whether the trade markets open
is not
for you to decide.
You fought Wutuo several times,
yet now you speak
for Wutuo.
Have their blows made you
a turncoat now?
Your Majesty,
when I led the Fuyue Army
to quell rebellions,
my goal
was the Wei's prosperity and peace.
My lifelong wish
is to safeguard
the Wei's land for you.
Apart from that,
there's nothing more.
Your Majesty, please trust
my loyalty.
General Feihong is a loyal,
peerless warrior unmatched
by a thousand.
He would never
commit acts of treason.
But the question remains:
Are you General Feihong?
Nonsense.
Your Majesty,
I have
to accuse He Rufei
of three major crimes.
Three major crimes?
What do you mean?
First crime:
Substitution fraud
by stealing General Feihong's identity.
- What?
Is this true?
Please summon a witness.
This person can verify
the truth of my claim.
Summon!
By the imperial decree,
summon him!
Commander of Rundu Li Kuang.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
So you're the Commander of Rundu
Li Kuang.
In the Rundu battle,
you deserve recognition.
Please rise.
- Thank you.
(Commander,)
it's been days.
You are...
He Yan?
I'm He Yan
who fought
with you at Rundu.
I am Li Kuang.
Greetings, General Feihong.
Commander Li.
You'd read
this letter after we leave.
Jujube and turtle...
Come back soon.
We Eight Warriors
were born into poverty.
Most were illiterate,
so we devised
such a crude method
for communication.
These codes are
known only to us eight
and General Feihong.
Now seven were gone,
leaving only
me and
General Feihong.
Rise.
I
am late.
Sorry, General.
Rise.
You're not late,
but arrive in time.
I
dare not claim merit.
If not for General Fengyun
and General Feihong's
timely aid,
Rundu's people
would've been killed
by Wutuo.
Li, explain yourself.
The ones who saved Rundu
were General Fengyun
and Marquis Wu'an.
Why mentioned General Feihong?
Because
Marquis Wu'an
is the genuine General Feihong!
General He,
what do you have to say?
Your Majesty,
this man conspires with He Yan
in a vile scheme
to frame me!
That's strange.
Li Kuang served as your deputy,
sharing life-and-death struggles
and fighting with you.
Why would he frame you now?
Perhaps in the Rundu Battle,
my late reinforcements
angered him,
making him He Yan's pawn.
He Rufei.
Why didn't you save
your former deputy?
His statements
are full of inconsistencies.
He's deliberately slandering me.
I'm innocent!
Please judge fairly.
It seems you deny
the first crime charge.
Marquis Wu'an.
Second one.
Second crime:
To conceal his false identity,
he eliminated
his comrades!
I have evidence
to present.
Get it to me.
Yes.
(To Xiao Jue)
(Assassination, in Chonghuai)
The assassins outside Chonghuai.
General He,
have you forgotten them?
My lord,
we discovered
tattooed markings on
one assassin's body.
He might be a former prisoner.
By tracing these markings,
we can determine
when and where he was imprisoned,
thus,
we can know his real name
and background.
Yang Mingzhi has replied.
He found the assassins' origins.
They're linked to He Rufei.
So,
that tattooed assassin was
a distant relative
of He Mansion's steward.
They did everything
to eliminate me.
You thought
that dead men
could tell nothing.
But traces can't be erased.
Dead men still tell us something.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Your steward
acted so recklessly,
yet you know nothing?
I failed to supervise him.
Your Majesty, forgive me.
Besides repeated attempts to kill me,
in the Huayuan Battle,
the Fuyue Army's Seven Tiger Generals
were ambushed and killed together.
It's another scheme
by He Rufei!
Things change in the battlefields.
We have
to be flexible.
He Rufei.
I don't care who you are.
But you fought in
the Huayuan Battle.
Just tell me,
did you truly abandon
thousands of soldiers
for personal gain?
Punish He Rufei severely, Your Majesty!
Avenge the unjustly slain
from the Huayuan Battle!
Punish He Rufei severely, Your Majesty!
Avenge the unjustly slain
from the Huayuan Battle!
Third crime:
Colluding with Wutuo,
and treason against Wei!
False accusations!
He Yan.
You have no evidence
at all.
I do!
- It's her!
- Indeed.
(Why is she here?)
Your Majesty,
these letters
are secretly hidden by He Rufei.
And I stole them.
They contain
evidence
of He Rufei's treason.
Get them to me.
A Madam He seeks audience
outside the hall.
Madam He?
Who's that?
Bring her in.
Yes.
I heard the Tianxing Platform
is about to hold a night banquet.
These letters
should prove helpful.
Thank you.
General Fengyun.
I have a favor to ask.
Please help me enter the palace,
so I can present these letters myself.
No way.
It'd be dangerous.
Madam He.
Don't get involved in it.
Madam He, you don't need to.
General.
I'm doing this for Yan.
I know Rufei resents her.
I watched them
harmed her once,
and I must stop them now.
Please help me, General.
Alright.
I'll help you.
Regarding the evidence,
please inform Yan
to reassure her.
But don't tell her that I'd present
the evidence myself.
Your Majesty.
I can testify
that my stepson He Rufei
is not General Feihong at all.
I'm the descendant of a scholar,
living at home with my young daughter.
He Yuansheng coveted
my family's reputation.
Since my family had declined,
he forced me into the He Mansion.
Unexpectedly, soon after,
He Rufei fell gravely ill.
Physicians predicted he'd die early.
He Yuansheng feared losing his title,
yet couldn't bear to abandon his son.
He thought adopting a boy
might let him breed evil ambition,
and be hard to control.
So he made my daughter
disguised as a man
and swap identities with He Rufei.
My daughter has been clever
and favors martial arts.
She joined the army early
and risked her life in battlefields,
earning the title General Feihong.
When she returned,
Rufei had recovered fully.
When Your Majesty awarded,
He Rufei was so greedy,
and He Yuansheng feared
He Yan would expose them,
so...
they...
So they poisoned
and blinded her.
Later,
they silenced her.
Your Majesty.
My daughter He Yan
is the genuine General Feihong!
- This...
- What!
What's wrong?
Don't trust her!
Your Majesty.
This woman is too sick
to think clearly.
What she said
is completely nonsense.
I...
I was telling all the truth.
Your Majesty, please trust me.
I told no lies.
If I did,
may lightning strike me,
and I'd die horribly,
descend to the netherworld,
and never to escape.
Your Majesty, please trust me.
Hold justice for my daughter.
Your Majesty,
please summon physicians!
Go summon them!
Yes.
Imperial physician!
Your Majesty, please trust me.
I was telling all the truth.
I'll stake my life
to prove it.
Why?
As a mother,
I tried to protect everything.
Yet in the end,
I failed to protect anything.
A shameless person
like me
doesn't deserve to live longer.
Rufei,
repent your sins.
Rufei.
Repent your sins.
Ingrate!
Madam.
You're sick.
Really sick!
Your Majesty,
the poison has spread,
and she is beyond cure.
Don't cry.
I'm not worth your tears.
Mother.
I...
I finally heard
you call me Mother.
Wonderful.
Cloaked in lotus splendor,
yet adrift without anchor.
Yan.
Live...
Live
well.
Mother!
Monster!
Mother.
Take Madam He away first.
Let her rest in peace.
Mother.
He Yan.
He Rufei.
Though we're nominally siblings,
we're destined to fight.
He Rufei!
You deceived me,
falsely claimed official titles,
attempted to silence witnesses,
slaughtered your comrades,
and betrayed the Wei!
How heinous!
Unforgivable!
Now we have witnesses and evidence!
How dare you still deny it?
This matter isn't concluded yet.
Your Majesty shouldn't
convict General He
hastily.
Marquis Wu'an.
How dare you draw sword
before the Emperor?
This is great disrespect!
What?
Chancellor Xu, did you forget
that those letters
also implicate you?
Your Majesty.
He Rufei committed countless crimes,
but he's been
manipulated by Xu Jingfu.
Xu Jingfu is the true
mastermind
who's making trouble
and betraying the Wei!
- Nonsense!
Exactly.
Back in Mingshui,
you killed 30,000 Xiao Army soldiers
to eliminate political rivals.
Back in Yezhou,
you used someone
to kill Sun Xiangfu
to hide your embezzlement.
Back in Jiyang,
you colluded with Wutuo,
leading us to nearly lose Jiyang.
In Huayuan and Rundu,
you let He Rufei slaughter
the seven generals,
causing Rundu's siege.
And you secretly
negotiated peace with Wutuo.
Everything you've done
serves only your personal gain.
He corrupts the court,
threatens the peace,
and damages the people!
His guilt is heinous!
He Yan.
You said Chancellor Xu was behind this.
Where's your proof?
He Yan speaks the truth.
I am the witness!
I have
long been Chancellor Xu's disciple,
and always respected him.
But over time,
I realized he
wasn't a virtuous minister
I believed.
But he has shown me great kindness.
I struggled for a long time,
yet I couldn't watch him
keep making mistakes.
So yesterday,
I caught the Wutuo spy
who's disguised
as Ganming Pavilion's owner.
After the interrogation,
he gave me
a letter
from Chancellor Xu
to Wutuo envoy, Maningbu.
He promises Maningbu
to promote
the trade market establishment.
Get it to me.
Yes.
(To Maningbu)
(Trade Market Cooperation, Xu Jingfu)
Now,
I've taken that Wutuo spy
outside the hall.
He can confront against
Envoy Maningbu.
Bring him.
No need.
You dare defy the imperial decree?
You have aged.
- He...
- What...
What does he want?
You're deceived by traitors,
believing slanders,
wronging loyal ministers!
This grieves me deeply.
As
the Chancellor of Wei,
I bear the duty to purge the villains
and eliminate treacherous officials!
Guards!
Fuyue Army, heed my command!
Purge the villains!
- He's committing treason!
Xu Jingfu!
How dare you commit treason!
Your Majesty,
I've done
all those things.
You trust villains and alienated
worthy ministers like me,
failing to be a wise emperor.
Naturally, I must step forward
to uphold justice!
You treacherous rebel!
How dare you say such words
and plot to usurp the throne!
Your Majesty,
don't get me wrong.
I've been loyal to the nation.
Once you
issue a penitential edict
and abdicates,
I shall
enthrone the young prince,
purge the court,
and restore the governance!
Fuyue Army, heed my command!
Purge the villains!
You...
His Majesty has
asked the Nine Banners Battalion
to stand by
to subdue the rebels!
Nine Banners Battalion, heed my command!
Capture the traitors!
Yes!
Nine Banners Battalion?
Why are they here?
Useless!
The rebels
have been suppressed.
He Rufei.
Most Fuyue Army soldiers
fought alongside me
through life and death.
He Rufei.
How could they
obey an impostor like you?
Great!
So Your Majesty
collaborated with Commander Xiao
in this deception!
Well played!
You have schemed thoroughly,
but overlooked your own arrogance.
Master,
you often taught me
to serve the emperor
and help the people.
Yet what you've done
threatens
the nation
and damages the people.
I beg you,
please stop.
Zilan,
I've treated you well.
How dare you join forces with them
to conspire against me!
What benefits
did they promise you
to make you
act so ungratefully
regardless my kindness to you?
You ingrate!
You preach benevolence,
but in my view,
you're just exploiting favors for gain.
National interests
outweigh personal favors.
As the Chancellor,
don't you know
such a basic idea?
Master,
just surrender.
Am I wrong?
Everything I've done
was for the Wei's
future!
You military officials
only resort to wars.
Aren't the soldiers who die in battle
the Wei's citizens?
Aren't the vast military funds
spent year after year
the hard-earned money of Wei's people?
You military officials
chase military glory,
while ignoring the people's suffering!
You're the true criminals of Wei!
Nonsense!
You were the one who started the war!
Our army surged
with unstoppable momentum
and crushed the Wutuo forces.
If we won
the Mingshui Battle,
the war would be concluded
and peace would come.
But you're blinded by personal ambition.
To eliminate dissidents,
you conspired with enemies,
sacrificing thousands
of Xiao Army soldiers!
Yet you didn't repent.
To cover your crimes,
you aided Wutuo, our enemy,
and exposed the Wei's people
to endless warfare!
Xu Jingfu.
You said what you've done
was for the Wei's future,
yet what you've done
serves only your personal gains.
Xiao Jue.
Don't you understand?
Military officials secure,
while civil officials govern.
What strategies
do you military officials
have, except for warfare?
Everything I've done
was for the Wei!
Your Majesty,
my loyalty is
beyond question!
If everyone had
such loyalty as yours,
then the nation
would be doomed.
Yan He.
Li Kuang.
Yes!
Take Xu Jingfu and He Rufei
into custody.
After the joint trial,
execute them.
Yes!
I'll walk myself.
Mr. Xiao.
How should we
deal with
this Envoy Maningbu?
Your Majesty,
since Maningbu represents Wutuo
as the envoy,
we should
detain him at the embassy,
and write to the King of Wutuo,
stating his crimes.
His disposition rests solely
on the King of Wutuo's response.
Move!
Marquis Wu'an.
Technically, you're from the He family.
The He family
disguised a daughter,
deceiving the Emperor.
You are also at fault.
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪I've seen the mountains♪
♪And trodden through ice♪
♪Day after day, I venture alone♪
♪Destiny is my creed♪
♪Ideals surge beneath the surface♪
♪Igniting the flame against the winds♪
♪A restless yearning in my soul♪
♪Gazing through the mire♪
♪Who cares about this boundless void♪
♪Charge ahead with blazing fervor♪
♪Stubbornly fighting with my life♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪