Tomorrow,
we'll head back for New Year.
Mother turns 60 this year,
we'd better bring generous gifts.
And the fifth sister-in-law,
she's the legit daughter
of Lord Changxing.
Now she's expecting,
and my brother's been
sent far off to Hanyang.
Heard Mother's personally
overseeing her every need.
We can't afford to treat her lightly.
I've added 20 percent
on top of the usual gifts.
Mother.
Your cough
sounds worse.
It's nothing,
really.
Madam Ji's not going back?
She didn't fall asleep
till well past midnight.
She woke up feeling off,
so she's not going.
Then I'm not going either.
I'll stay and take care of Madam.
Miss, you're truly devoted.
But this is your first time
paying New Year's respects there.
You should go no matter what.
The main house
has been urging us
to move back for years,
saying family should stay together.
They're merely
after Madam's dowry.
That's why Madam
won't move back.
Master knows it too.
But the main house's been
nobility for generations,
how could they be short on cash?
Big noble families these days
are all show on the outside only.
Nine out of ten are broke.
You'll see when you get there.
Indeed,
we better stay sharp.
No wonder Father
moved out right after the engagement
with the Ji family.
He was already protecting against this.
He really plays it smart.
People in the capital are all schemers.
Madam's too kind,
easy to get taken advantage of.
Good thing you came, Miss.
With you here,
you can help Madam
make the right decisions.
Miss,
what a show!
Of course.
This is the old family estate
from the late master's time.
Way better than our place.
Even Ji Mansion
can't match this.
Right, Jinzhao?
Yeah,
even Ji Mansion
wouldn't spend like this.
Guess the main house's loaded.
Wait,
Uncle Deyuan is just
a Fourth-Rank Investigating Censor,
where'd all this money come from?
From the main house fortune, of course.
Second sister-in-law,
my respects to you.
Happy new year.
Good day to you, Dezhao.
Second Aunt, happy new year.
Happy new year everyone.
This must be Jinzhao.
What a beauty.
It's cold outside,
let's head in.
Come.
Happy new year, Mother.
Happy new year, Grandma.
Alright get up.
Finally everyone's here.
Dezhao.
Jinrong.
Jinxian.
Come to my study,
let's have some tea.
Take a seat.
First time
seeing Jinzhao.
She's turned out
so graceful
and gorgeous,
like a crabapple bloom.
So it seems
all those rumors outside
were just nonsense.
Have you been betrothed?
Not yet, Grandma.
Not yet?
Didn't you already
have a betrothal
with Lord Liu Siyu's family?
Lian,
don't talk like that.
Jinzhao is older than you,
call her sister.
Lian,
you said I was engaged to the Liu family,
how did you know that?
It was Lan,
she wrote it in a letter.
What exactly
did Lan say?
She said
the Liu family came to propose,
but you had your eye on Lord Xian,
so you looked down on Liu Xiancheng.
I didn't say that!
That's exactly what you meant.
I just said
Jinzhao and Lord Xian
are on good terms.
I never said anything else.
But…
Enough.
The Young Lord
is not someone you can gossip about.
Exactly.
The Young Lord is far above us.
Any dealings with our family
are only
out of courtesy
to the Gu Manor's connections.
As for the Liu family.
Lian,
Lan only said they came to propose,
not that the match was set.
Right?
But…
Yes.
That's right.
A proposal isn't a betrothal.
If every proposal
counted as a betrothal,
there'd be no end to it.
If this gets out,
it'll look like our family is eager
to marry off daughters.
Lian,
you're still a Gu girl,
mind what you say.
And Lan,
don't spread things
about me anymore.
We may not
have grown up together,
but I'm still your sister.
We're family.
Even if you don't think for me,
you should think of Father
and the Gu family.
Do you think so?
Yes.
I know I was wrong.
Alright.
We're all family.
Talk it out
and it's fine,
nothing serious.
Both Lan
and Jinzhao
are good girls.
They'll both
find good matches.
Especially Jinzhao.
I heard
your maternal grandmother
left you all her properties
in the capital
as your dowry.
You'll need
a fine husband indeed.
I'll keep an eye out for you as well.
Lian did have a match
with the legit son
of Lord Yao Ping,
Vice Minister of Justice.
Everyone praised it,
said it's a good match.
How did I become the topic?
I don't care for this talk.
You all carry on.
Lan,
let's go watch the opera.
Alright,
all of you, go enjoy the opera.
Mother,
hasn't arrived yet.
Her again.
She's late every time.
It's all your fault.
If I hadn't gone to pick you up,
I wouldn't be late.
I only said I was coming,
never asked you to pick me up.
You said you were coming,
how could I not go pick you up?
Young Lord, you're here.
Greetings, Young Lord,
Aunt.
Greetings, Ma'am.
Happy New Year.
Happy New Year, Young Lord.
Please sit.
Mother, listen.
We sent someone
to ask before the New Year,
he said he wouldn't come this year.
This morning,
he suddenly sent word
saying he was coming,
so I had to rush out to pick him up.
He really does change his mind on a whim,
making me late.
Your pregnancy is progressing,
need to be extra careful.
It doesn't matter being late or not.
Just take it easy.
Since everyone's here,
let's go watch the opera.
Lian,
look after your sisters.
Especially Jinzhao,
it's her first time here.
Me looking after her?
She's older than me,
she doesn't need my care.
Lord Xian,
let's go.
What's the rush?
I'm older than you too,
so I don't need your care either.
What's taking so long?
Hurry up!
Let's go!
Grandma, I'll stay with you.
I'm going with you.
She's the obedient one.
Let's go.
You sisters sit here,
chat and laugh a bit,
that's how it should be.
All the operas chosen today
- are good.
- Glad you like them.
I like them all.
Good.
What are you doing?
Still looking?
Go take a closer look then.
Stop talking nonsense!
Don't think
I don't know what you're thinking.
Jinzhao has a thing for him?
I think you're the one who's interested.
Think about
his status.
Even I don't dare think too much.
You really are bold.
I'm not thinking anything.
I just
think he looks good
and took a few extra glances.
He really does look good.
But that temper of his,
better not test it.
Don't know
what he sees in Jinzhao,
he actually pays more attention to her.
My Father said
Jinzhao even dares to talk back
to Uncle Dezhao
in front of outsiders.
Is that true?
Don't even bring it up!
Ever since she came back,
my life's been hard!
Even wanting an extra dish,
I have to go to the kitchen
and pay extra to get it.
And you just put up with it?
What else can I do?
She's the legit daughter,
what am I?
So what if she's the legit daughter?
I'm a legit daughter too!
I've never bullied anyone.
Do you know what Cao Cao's
two biggest mistakes in his life were?
One was mistakenly executing Cai Mao,
the other was letting Guan Yu go.
Cai Mao should've been put to good use.
But Guan Yu
should've been killed.
Don't you agree?
Second Aunt,
this opera is really good.
Which troupe is it from?
It's the Spring Grass Troupe
from south of the city.
This is truly outrageous!
I need to change clothes.
Miss, this way please.
I need to change too.
Wait a moment!
Let's go together
after this act.
Running away without a fight,
doesn't suit you.
Can you stop following me?
Your handkerchief…
Young Lord,
I can't afford to offend you!
And I don't want another whipping!
Please just let me go,
can you?
You can't afford to offend me,
so you can afford Chen Yanyun?
What did you say?
Don't talk nonsense!
Nonsense?
New Year's Eve, City God Temple festival,
I saw it myself
that Chen guy
jumped into the river to save you.
That never happened!
You're spreading rumors!
If I'm spreading rumors,
may I be struck by lightning.
And if you're lying,
you too.
Meeting you already
feels like I've been struck by lightning!
There's a higher spot,
go stand there and say it if you dare!
You think I won't?
Of course you dare!
You'd dare anything!
You are
the noble Young Lord!
What wouldn't you dare?
What are people like us
worth in your eyes?
You just say
and do whatever you want!
Gu Jinzhao,
you've gone too far!
So what if I have?
Kill me if you can!
You…
You ungrateful thing!
If I weren't considering
you once saved my life…
Xian, Jinzhao.
Aunt.
What are you two doing here?
Her handkerchief fell,
I picked it up for her.
I'm returning it now.
Young Lord is mistaken,
this isn't mine.
I clearly saw it was yours!
How can you lie like that?
How is it not yours?
How could I not
recognize my own thing?
It's cold in the courtyard,
I'll take my leave, Aunt,
Young Lord.
I was going to go
get my hand warmer anyway.
Gu Jinzhao!
Enough.
She said it's not hers.
Are you going
to force her to take it?
What handkerchief?
Give it to me.
Why would I give it to you?
I picked it up.
Where are you going?
The feast is about to start!
All grown up now,
still no sense of propriety.
Miss,
but Young Lord's already of age.
Yes,
he's of age.
That's not fair!
You are two people!
Ma'am,
ladies,
young masters!
The snacks are here!
- 30,000 coins.
- Snacks are here!
The handkerchief's still with Xian.
If he goes crazy
and takes it out,
and someone notices
my stitching matches it,
I'm in trouble.
You're all set, right?
Nicely done!
Lan's lotus
is well done too.
Jinzhao.
What's wrong?
Second Aunt,
my embroidery isn't good,
not worth showing.
It's fine.
Ma'am just likes
girls doing needlework.
So we're all just
keeping her entertained.
Don't take it seriously.
Thank you for the advice, Second Aunt.
Second Madam, please come quick!
Coming!
Keep stitching.
Lan,
how is
your lotus so good?
I just learned a bit from my mother.
Your mother's that good too?
Isn't she from a merchant family?
Oh right,
you mean "mother".
- Uncle.
- What are you looking at?
Try this pastry.
Just because of my
"merchant's daughter" comment?
[Jinxian,]
[your turn!]
Did it hit your nerve too?
Why are you shaking your head?
You people
from merchant families
are always so petty!
Say it
if you've got the guts.
Since you act so high and mighty,
why are you wearing
a fake gold cicada hairpin?
What did you say?
Fake?
Then I'll say it straight.
This gold cicada hairpin
is this autumn's design
from my maternal family's jewelry shop.
Just that cicada alone
used three taels of gold.
If I'm not mistaken,
the one you're wearing
is hollow, gold-plated.
Don't believe me? Look,
the gold on the sides
is already worn off.
Nonsense!
Nonsense or not,
you know in your heart.
If you want proof,
take it off
and drop it in water.
If it floats,
that'd be something.
Girls,
how's the embroidery?
Grandma.
This lotus
looks almost alive.
You must
have practiced a lot.
Thank you, Grandma.
A koi?
A bit weaker than the lotus.
Grandma!
Still not bad.
How's Jinzhao's work?
Let me have a look.
Grandma,
my skills are poor,
it's not well done.
Even if it's not good,
you can still show it!
No way, Jinzhao,
this…
did you really make it?
What's this supposed to be?
Look at this!
This…
This is…
It's a butterfly.
A butterfly?
I thought
it was a moth!
What,
your mother
never taught you needlework?
Oh right,
you were kicked out as a child
and raised by your grandmother.
I heard the Ji family
is the richest in Tongzhou.
Well,
what's the point
of a big dowry?
Proper upbringing still matters.
It's Jinzhao's.
With skills like that,
how will you face
your in-laws later?
Lian,
the Ji family in Tongzhou are your elders,
how can you talk like that?
Exactly.
My poor skills are on me,
what does it have
to do with my grandparents?
Right.
That wasn't fair, Lian.
I heard
Mrs. Ji
hired Ms. Xue
from Silken Pavilion
just to teach
her needlework.
Then why
is it so crude?
Is that all Silken Pavilion can teach?
Maybe you're new here,
just playing it down, right?
We're all family,
no need to be so modest.
I happen to have
a handkerchief she embroidered herself.
You'll see once you look.
Mother,
look!
This orchid,
both form and spirit are perfect!
So lifelike.
What's that she stitched?
Let me see.
Jinzhao stitched it.
It's really well done.
Jinzhao,
did you really embroider this?
Yes.
My luck's
great today!
Jinzhao.
Jinxian,
I need to speak
to the Young Lord alone.
Okay, I'll leave you to chat.
Mad?
Mad I made you admit
the handkerchief was yours?
Get this straight,
I was helping you.
Thanks for the help, Young Lord.
Next time, please don't.
So I was wrong?
You gave my handkerchief
to Lan,
what do you think she'll think?
So that's what you're worried about?
She won't say anything.
How do you know she won't?
When I speak,
who dares not listen,
besides you?
What about Aunt?
She was there.
She saw
what happened.
Jinzhao,
why are you so fussy?
What are you afraid of?
She's my sister!
You wouldn't understand.
Jinzhao, where are you going?
Slow down.
Everything has its fate.
This cat
was probably bitten
in a fight.
It won't live long.
Saving it now
will only make it
suffer more.
So by your logic,
I shouldn't have saved you
at Blessed Fane either.
You've got your own fate anyway.
Do you want to save it
or put it out of its misery?
My lord.
What are you staring at?
Always causing me trouble.
Didn't expect you
to be so patient with a cat,
yet so cruel to people.
You've got a death wish?
Want another whipping?
Looks like you really resent me.
Wouldn't you?
I didn't provoke you at all
and still got whipped.
And that Mr. Zhang.
He fell seriously ill
just because of your prank.
He's totally innocent!
He's innocent?
I'm the innocent one!
If you hadn't
stood me up for no reason,
why would I lose my temper?
Stood you up?
When did I ever do that?
Playing dumb?
I sent you an invitation
and you snubbed me.
What,
was I supposed to tolerate that?
Invitation?
I never got anything.
Xianhuai.
So,
the handkerchief
was given to the Young Lord
by Ms. Jinzhao?
Then…
Wouldn't that be a private exchange?
It's not her first time
doing that.
Jinzhao, you're here.
Still up so late?
Come in.
I came to thank you
for speaking up for me.
You mean
the embroidery thing?
We're sisters.
They were mocking your grandmother,
of course I'd defend you.
So I won't pursue
you hiding Ye Xian's invitation
from me.
What invitation?
Well,
whether Ye Xian pursues it,
that's another matter.
What are you talking about?
When I first returned,
you had no issue with me.
I…
I suppose lately
things have changed in the house.
Because of me,
Concubine Song took some losses.
So you resent me.
You think my return
got in your way.
I've never thought that.
I'm a straightforward person.
Yes, I'm the legit daughter
and you're not.
But since I was a baby,
I grew up at my grandmother's.
I never lived a day
as a true legit daughter.
And you,
since birth,
you were the only miss in the house.
Not legit,
yet treated like one.
What I'm saying
is just to tell you
that in my eyes there's no such divide.
You don't need to see me as a rival.
Jinzhao, that's really unfair
of you to say.
How am I supposed to take that?
I've said my piece.
If you take it in, good.
If not,
and you keep stirring trouble,
I'm not the type
to repay evil with kindness.
Qingpu, let's go.
So fake and pretentious!
I don't believe
that if roles were reversed,
she could still be so detached!
Just talking big
without feeling it herself.
Let's go!
[Didn't expect you]
[to be so patient with a cat,]
[yet so cruel to people.]
Miss.
Sis.
What are you doing outside?
Aren't you cold?
Cold is good,
keeps the mind clear.
Always full of strange ideas.
You're afraid of the cold,
I'll help you inside.
Sis,
please sit.
Before the New Year,
I attended a banquet
for Lord Wuning's birthday banquet,
and ran into Viscount Weiyuan's wife.
Only then did I know
their second son is already engaged
to the youngest daughter
of Lord Wuning,
Qiu Fang.
I remember he's about your age,
maybe even a few months younger.
To be honest,
mother also mentioned your marriage.
I said,
Xian's always had
his own ideas since childhood,
so this
should be his decision.
Do you think so?
Why are you laughing?
I'm just laughing
that you always like
to beat around the bush.
Doesn't it get tiring?
Fine,
I'll be direct then.
You're of age now,
and you're the only heir of the family.
Mother and father plan
to start looking for a match this spring.
Get married early,
so you can carry on
the family line.
Yeah.
Even if I die early,
you'll all feel more at ease, right?
What are you saying?
Since you care so much
about continuing the family line,
go have your own children.
Even letting your husband
take concubines is fine.
Why drag me into it?
I can't handle you anymore?
You wouldn't happen
to like a Gu girl, would you?
Is it that Jinzhao?
So what if it is?
And what if it isn't?
If it isn't, good.
If it is,
then I advise you,
forget it early.
You're the heir,
destined to inherit
the entire Marquis Manor.
A girl from the Gu family,
let alone Jinzhao,
even Lian wouldn't be
a match for you.
I shouldn't have
let you stay
at the Gu Manor so often.
All these girls
have only caused unnecessary trouble.
I'll keep this
from our parents for now.
But you'd better know it.
If father and mother find out,
you know what the consequences will be.
If you truly care for her,
you should cut those feelings off
early.
Xianhuai!
Miss.
Go pack the Young Lord's things,
he's returning to Marquis Manor.
This…
What,
do my words not carry weight anymore?
I wouldn't dare.
I'll…
go pack now.
People always say gold and silver
can't compare to something made by hand.
Giving these to Mr. Chen,
let alone him,
I even find it tacky.
[Mr. Jinrong's here!]
Greetings, Jinzhao.
You're…
Just picking out a few suitable gifts
for some social visits.
Jinrong,
what is it?
Here's the thing.
A while ago,
I went to Yong'an Bridge
and accidentally saw you
with Mr. Chen's nephew,
Chen Xuanqing.
Well, don't misunderstand.
I saw it,
but I won't spread it.
Not even
to father and mother.
Don't worry.
A few days ago,
you wanted to borrow 200 taels from me,
I've got it ready.
Well…
Thank you, Jinzhao!
But,
since it's a loan, there are rules.
Even between siblings,
we still need signatures and fingerprints.
Of course.
Borrowed: 200 taels.
Any collateral?
I…
If you don't have anything suitable,
the jade bracelet
you gave me that day will do, alright?
Alright!
You really are straightforward.
Six-month term,
with three months' interest
added upon maturity…
This…
This is "9 out, 13 return"?
Jinzhao, you…
I didn't expect you
to know pawnshop rules so well,
even that kind of loan sharking math.
Well,
at that rate,
I'm afraid I won't be able to pay it back.
Are you out of your mind?
That jade bracelet was
a gift from you anyway.
Even if you can't repay it,
what's there to fear?
Oh, right!
I really was being silly.
Thank you, Jinzhao.
Alright.
If no objections,
just sign and press your seal.
Okay.
Same handwriting,
same fingerprint.
This pawn ticket
really is yours.
This…
You…
Wait,
I specifically skipped
Ji's pawnshop
and went to He's,
how did you…
You didn't know.
He's Pawnshop
also has a 30% share from the Ji family.
An official kiln vase
and a jade ring,
valued at 150 taels.
What do you need so much silver for?
Is it also for your classmate's sister's
dowry?
This is…
Say it!
What are you borrowing so much money for?
You've even learned to pawn things now!
If you lie,
I'll take this ticket
straight to mother
or even father!
No!
Jinzhao,
please don't tell them!
I'll tell you.
Actually…
It was the month before last,
a classmate of mine was
going back to his hometown
and invited us over for a drink.
I accidentally broke
a teacup there.
What teacup
costs 150 taels of silver?
It's Chenghua doucai kiln!
That jade thumb ring
was from mother.
The pawn deadline is coming up,
and I don't have money to redeem it.
So I came to ask you for a loan.
Whatever it takes,
I have to get it back.
Really.
Qingpu,
bring a 200 tael bank draft.
Yes, Miss.
Thank you, Jinzhao!
First a classmate's sister,
then an imperial kiln teacup.
All nonsense.
Qingpu,
ask Mr. Ping to send two men
to watch him closely.
I want to see
what he's really doing.
Yes, Miss.
Watch out!
What happened?
My lord,
someone almost hit us.
When did the capital
get so polite?
Not even a curse.
No wonder,
he's rushing off to gamble.
A gambling house.
No signboard?
You don't know, my lord.
The more hidden it is,
the bigger the business.
It must have backing.
Whoever runs this
is really shady.
Go.
Let's go, this way.
It's near.
Masters, please come in.
[Good luck today.]
Gu Jinrong?
Didn't expect him
to be a gambler.
Turns out he is.
Wonder if Miss Gu
knows about this.
She definitely doesn't.
Otherwise, with her temper,
she'd kill him.
Let's go.
Go.
So,
he's not gambling himself,
he's recruiting for the gambling house?
Exactly.
I saw it myself.
Mr. Jingrong didn't play,
he led those gamblers
into a private room.
So,
he's working for the gambling house
as a frontman.
A frontman.
Normally,
that should pay well.
Then why does he still pawn things?
Because that private room
was rented by him.
Gambling house rules say,
to lease a room,
one should pay three months upfront.
Mr. Jingrong
must be short on money,
that's why
he pawned things.
I see.
This needs to be handled fast.
Even if he doesn't gamble himself,
luring others in is worse
than gambling himself.
The Ministry of Rites
sent the imperial exam pass list
for this round.
Sir,
people are talking outside,
saying Mr. Xuanqing
has your backing.
He'll likely rank top
in the palace exam.
Too much attention
may not be a good thing.
Then,
can we stop it?
How can we?
If His Majesty and my teacher
both intend to promote him,
how could I
refuse their goodwill?
Sir,
the Ji family sent gifts.
Leave them there.
According to Mr. Luo,
these were personally chosen
by Miss Gu.
He said they were not enough
to repay you for saving Miss Gu,
just a token of gratitude
and to ease their own conscience.
He's got a silver tongue.
This is…
A double-barreled telescope!
Much clearer
than the single-tube one.
The Ji family is wealthy.
When Fujian opened trade back then,
they also
took a share of the profits.
Half the Western goods
you see in the capital now
are brought in
by the Ji family's merchant ships.
Miss Gu really put thought into this.
What is this?
Looks like…
a pair of eyeglasses.
I've heard of them.
For people with poor eyesight, right?
Are you sure Mr. Luo said
these gifts were all
chosen by Miss Gu herself?
Yes.
They also said
those were things you could use.
Throw them all out.
Yes.
Forget it.