WOULD YOU MARRY ME?
ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES,
ORGANIZATIONS, ETC. ARE FICTIONAL
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED
WITH GUARDIANS PRESENT
ANIMALS WERE FILMED
UNDER EXPERT SUPERVISION AND WELFARE RULES
FINAL EPISODE
COLLABORATION ON LICENSING
THE BEAUTÉ DEPARTMENT STORE IN YONGDU
STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL
You should
take the fall for this.
You'll hear from a prosecutor.
That damn mayor of Yongdu...
He acted all high and mighty
about running for president.
And now, look at the mess he caused.
Looks like you'll be the one
putting up with this.
I feel bad for you.
Someone has to take responsibility.
Since I am the CEO,
I should be the one taking responsibility.
But as you know,
all the paperwork and accounts
were created by you.
So, I don't think
there's anything I can do.
DELIVERED BY BAEK SANGHYEON
Sanghyeon.
If you get through this,
my dad will make it worth your while.
You know that
from everything he's done for you.
Honestly, he's given you in folds
compared to what you've done.
Don't you agree?
Hey.
You milked that gold ring prank
that I pulled when we were young.
I've always been grateful to Chairman.
And to you, too.
Up until now,
I didn't have to worry about money
or about going hungry.
It's all thanks to you.
I wasn't trying to get credit or anything.
Hey, Sanghyeon.
You're smart,
so you know what to say
to the prosecutors.
I trust you.
Nice tie, man.
Sungwoo.
Did you ever,
even once, think of me as your friend?
What are you talking about?
Of course, we're friends.
You and I are the same age.
Not like that.
Not as a tool for you to use
every time you get yourself in trouble...
but have you ever
thought of me as a real friend?
Geez, what's with you today?
Hey, we're friends, aren't we?
Of course, we're friends.
You and I are the same age.
What did I expect?
If you received a favor,
just repay them exactly what you owe.
I think anything beyond that is excessive.
I guess I don't really know
how much you owe them,
but haven't you worked hard enough
that it's all been paid off?
Then you don't need
to do any more for them.
Yes. I'm on the way now.
Get moving!
Yes, I'm here.
Get inside!
Hurry up and come in!
4TH-GENERATION HEIR OF MYUNGSOONDANG
KIM WOOJU'S FRAUD SCANDAL EXPOSED
I greet all you respectable journalists.
I'm Kim Wooju,
an ordinary man who lives in Seoul.
I stand here today to expose the successor
of a mid-sized company
breaking up a family with his affairs
and attempt to make
an illegal profit of millions.
I believe his immoral and unjust act
must come out.
4TH-GENERATION HEIR OF MYUNGSOONDANG
KIM WOOJU'S FRAUD SCANDAL EXPOSED
I'm sure you all know this bakery.
That's right.
It's Myungsoondang.
And this man...
He is the head of their marketing team,
and the chairwoman's grandson.
His name is Kim Wooju.
KIM WOOJU
And this woman
is currently my legal wife,
and her name is Yoo Meri.
And this document is
the proof of our marriage.
A few months ago,
from the Beauté Department Store
raffle event held for newlyweds,
she won a five-million-dollar house
at Beauté Palace...
Wait a minute.
The property value
must've gone up.
PROPERTY SALE PRICE GRAPH
It's 5.7 million dollars now?
Rounding up to six million dollars.
Six million...
MERI
You're too late, Meri.
This will be the end of you.
She won a six-million-dollar house
at Beauté Palace.
The call cannot
be connected. Transferring to...
Oh, my gosh.
The call cannot
be connected. Transferring to...
What?
A press conference?
I got a call from him.
I think he's going to cause trouble.
Where is he?
-He's here.
-He's coming.
Was it lobbying on behalf of the company?
Is it true that you followed
orders from Beauté Group CEO?
Did you create illegal lobbying funds
-for the mayor of Yongdu?
-Please, a word.
What do you think of this incident?
What's your relation to it?
I cooperated fully with the investigation.
-Wait.
-One more thing...
Just one more comment.
-Are you acknowledging it then?
-Please wait!
Excuse me.
MISSED CALL
CEO
You bastard!
What do you think you're doing?
I acknowledged the part I played.
Then why is the prosecution asking for me?
Because I didn't admit
to things I had no hand in.
What the heck are you saying?
Hey.
You talked, didn't you?
This is why they say
you should never trust the ungrateful.
How could you repay
our kindness like this, you trash?
I think I repaid you enough
for what you've done for me.
I'll pay for my own sins.
So, you should pay for your own sins.
Hey, Baek.
Baek Sanghyeon!
Goddamn it!
EXPOSED
I greet all you respectable journalists.
I'm Kim Wooju...
an ordinary man who lives in Seoul.
I stand here today to expose the successor
of a mid-sized company
for breaking up a family
with his affairs...
Wait a minute.
This jerk...
Did he expose everything
including the Beauté Palace?
Hey!
You know the Beauté Palace winner.
You mean Ms. Yoo Meri?
Yes, her.
-Did we transfer the ownership?
-Not yet.
Three months isn't up yet,
we need a few more days.
-Hurry it up!
-Okay.
If they find out
that it was a lobbying gift...
Pardon?
I mean...
People might get the wrong idea.
So, transfer the ownership
and make sure there's nothing suspicious.
Okay, sir.
That was for the raffle.
It had always been for the raffle.
-Got it?
-Yes, sir.
-Have you got it?
-Yes, for the raffle.
Oh, sir?
There's something more urgent.
What now?
It's this...
PRESS RELEASE
FOR KIM WOOJU'S PRESS CONFERENCE
Some crazy guy sent an email to the press,
saying that he'll expose
how the raffle event was a fraud.
A press conference?
Go and prevent it now.
If this hits the media,
people will start
focusing on Beauté Palace.
-Okay.
-If they dig up anything,
it'll blow back on me in no time.
-Do you get me?
-Yes, sir.
If you get it, hurry up.
Okay.
Is this the head of the legal team?
It's an emergency.
4TH-GEN HEIR OF MYUNGSOONDANG
KIM WOOJU'S FRAUD SCANDAL EXPOSED
Did they not get my email?
YONGDU CITY, BEAUTÉ
BEAUTÉ DEPARTMENT STORE SUSPECTED
OF GIVING ILLEGAL POLITICAL FUNDS
Beauté?
EX-MAYOR BYEON JONGSIK
INDICTED FOR BRIBERY
AND VIOLATION OF THE POLITICAL FUNDS ACT
-Get rid of it.
-Yes, sir.
Take off the banner.
And take photos as evidence.
Wait a minute.
Hey, wait...
What are you doing?
We're from the legal team
of Beauté Department Store.
STATEMENT OF COMPLAINT
We're suing you for defamation
and interference with business.
What?
You called in the press
to spread false information, right?
To say that there was
a fake newlywed couple
who received the prize
at our company's event.
Oh, that...
That's not false information.
I have proof.
Truth doesn't matter.
If it's true,
it's defamation for revealing facts,
and if it's false,
it's defamation for spreading lies.
Either way,
the moment our department store
is mentioned,
we'll estimate the business loss
caused by defamation
and file a claim for damages.
"Claim for damages"?
One, two, three, four...
10 million dollars?
-Wait, please.
-Hey, stop.
-Sir, you need to move.
-Please wait!
It's all true.
-Please hear me out!
-You'll get hurt.
Please wait!
Wait, please!
Oh, gosh.
I told you you'd get hurt.
I don't have this money.
10 MILLION DOLLARS
Wooju.
Meri.
Did you tell the department store?
What did you say
that caused all this fuss?
I only found out by coming here.
So, it wasn't you?
Meri...
Can I ask you to think over this again?
I don't have any money.
You...
You know well that I can't sleep
when I get things like this
because it makes me so anxious.
Don't be like this.
Could you please talk to Beauté
and ask them to drop the lawsuit?
How am I supposed to do that?
There's nothing I can do, either.
Please, Meri.
For old times' sake.
No...
You and I...
We were lovers once.
Please?
Why did you have to take things this far?
What made you take it this far?
I know.
I know because I was like that.
You did this because you hate me.
Still, you shouldn't have
done this to him.
Wooju.
These days,
I'm really happy and at ease.
I think I like him a lot.
So...
I want you to be happy, too.
I wish you'd move on from all this.
Seeing you broken
and falling apart like this
doesn't make me happy
or satisfied.
Let's forget that you hurt me
and your hatred toward me.
Let's forget it all...
and just keep the good memories.
How about that?
Can you do that for me?
WOULD YOU MARRY ME?
FAMILY REGISTRATION
-Hello.
-Hi.
SEOUL FAMILY COURT
DIVORCE DECREE
It's been submitted.
Thank you.
Get in.
This is it
since the house was already furnished.
Shall we get going then?
So much has happened at this place.
Let's go.
Hello, Ms. Yoo Meri.
I'm calling from Beauté Department Store.
Did you not hear from Mr. Baek?
Pardon?
A divorce?
Yes, I got a divorce.
Because I'm no longer a newlywed,
I don't have the right to keep the prize.
Wait, hold on.
But we need to transfer the ownership.
Can't we just give it to you?
But I'm not fit for it,
so I can't accept it.
I'm really sorry.
No, that's not... Ms. Yoo...
Ms. Yoo... She...
She hung up.
-Was that Beauté?
-Yes.
I wonder if Mr. Baek didn't report it.
Beauté seems to be unaware of it.
They're chaotic right now
because of the illegal lobbying funds.
I saw it on the news.
Anyway, aren't you sad?
You mean about the house?
I am.
I really am.
When will I ever get to live
in a house like that?
But...
I found something
much more precious than that.
What's that?
You know what it is.
I really don't. What is it?
Never mind if you don't.
What is it?
Let's just listen to some music.
Okay.
Play something upbeat.
Wow, the sound system is great.
It's amazing, right?
It's quite expensive.
MANAGING DIRECTOR BAEK SANGHYEON
YOON JINGYEONG
Yes, hello?
What happened?
I saw the news.
Regarding Mr. Kim Wooju,
it'll be swept under the rug.
If it's revealed
that it was for the bribe,
the company will also be in trouble.
So, you don't need to worry about it.
That's not it.
I'm worried about you.
According to the news,
they said you came clean.
You told me to pay for my sins
and live without shame.
When did I say that?
Maybe I heard it wrong.
What I meant was,
in the world of crime,
it's only right
that virtue triumphs over vice
and justice prevails.
Well, I was only telling you to take
responsibility for what you did wrong,
not for the things you didn't.
That's what I did.
I only acknowledged
the things that I did wrong.
Just like you told me to.
So, what happens now?
Well...
Since I'm under
non-custodial investigation,
I'm sure they'll reach a verdict soon.
Don't tell me...
You're not actually going
to prison or anything, right?
The night view looks
especially beautiful tonight.
I think...
I'll think of you a lot from time to time.
Can I ask you a favor?
Can you call her?
Yes, ma'am.
I think it's better
with the shadows.
-Should we try?
-Twenty...
Negative 30.
Yes, this is Yoo Meri.
-It's me.
-Pardon?
Wooju's grandma.
Hello, Chairwoman.
I'm being discharged today.
So, sometime next week,
let's meet at home.
Oh, I'm always free.
I'll come by
if you call me when you're free.
Yes, thank you.
Goodbye, ma'am.
Was that a call from the chairwoman?
Yeah.
That startled me.
That was such a surprise.
I heard that the chairwoman
is getting discharged.
I wonder if she'll start work right away.
I think that'd be a bit difficult
since she'll need
to take it easy for a while.
Also, considering her age.
Then the acting chairman
will be Mr. Kim, right?
Since Director Jang isn't here.
That's probable.
-Oh, no.
-Why?
Don't you think I've been
a bit rude to Ms. Yoo recently?
Perhaps...
...just a little.
I bet I'm on her bad side now.
If you are,
then what about Ms. Oh?
What about me?
Nothing.
You must have a lot of free time, Sejung,
worrying about such things.
It's not like Ms. Yoo
is getting married right now.
Focus on work.
Also, you never really know with couples
until they walk down the aisle.
Oh, good morning, Ms. Yoo.
Here.
Thank you.
You really didn't need to.
Seriously.
We should. It's give and take.
"Give and take"?
We're a family, aren't we?
You're upsetting me now.
Come sit.
Thank you.
You heard that Chairwoman
has been discharged, right?
-Yes.
-She's going to visit her soon.
Is that so?
Then I should give you some advice.
Are you good at omok?
Omok?
-A bit.
-She's really good at it.
She even wins against the computer.
She's the Lee Sedol of omok.
Really?
The chairwoman is also the queen of omok.
She almost never loses.
Then should I go play omok with her?
No.
What will you do if you win against her?
I think it was about ten years ago.
A factory manager beat her once,
and he had a rough week after that.
She wouldn't even look him in the eye
for a whole week.
He was totally out of her favor.
Then, I shouldn't win.
That's right.
This is really important advice.
No one would've told you but me.
Thank you.
Do you have any other advice?
SAUNA
-Jinhwa.
-Yes?
What should we have for dinner?
How about Szechuan-style
sweet and sour pork?
I'll make it for you.
We just need to buy pork.
Hey, look at you all excited
about the cooking school these days.
I think that's where my hidden talent is.
I can't even be bothered
to shop for groceries.
Let's just eat out.
Call Wooju out.
Geez, I was going to show off my skills.
Mom.
Isn't that Wooju?
Hey, it is.
That's a woman in front of him.
Who is that?
I'm Lee Soyeong,
a reporter from Junghan Magazine.
I saw that you
canceled the press conference.
Could you tell me about it?
The moment
our department store is mentioned,
we'll estimate the business loss
caused by defamation
and file a claim for damages.
It's nothing.
I had it all wrong.
I'm sorry for all the trouble I've caused.
Excuse me.
Please wait.
If you called for a press conference,
you must've had some kind of proof
that the Myungsoondang's heir
committed fraud.
I'd prefer it
if you stopped asking me about it.
Excuse me.
Here.
If you ever change your mind,
please call me.
A press conference?
Who is the heir of Myungsoondang?
Do you know him?
No, how would I know someone like that?
The reporter came to me by mistake.
Tell me now.
Tell us.
Otherwise, I'm going to ask her directly.
Myungsoondang's Kim Wooju...
That's right.
This is the guy.
He was in Wooju's hospital room.
And at that store, too.
We saw him there with Meri.
It's him, right?
Oh, my.
Oh, my gosh.
Meri really hit the jackpot.
How is she marrying
into such a rich family?
But seriously,
look at this guy.
He looks so classy.
Mom, I'm more envious
of how handsome he is
than the fact that she's marrying rich.
Oh, I could just...
You startled me.
This is unbelievable.
-Hey.
-Yeah?
His family
is from Myungsoondang, right?
You already seem happy at the thought
of getting a granddaughter-in-law.
I'm just happy to get rid of Wooju.
Still, it's a relief
that I get to see him
getting married before I die.
Perhaps that's why Wooju's dad woke me up.
You should live to see
your great-grandchild.
Don't say that.
What if they ask me to babysit?
I'm old-fashioned, so I can't pamper kids
the way moms do these days.
You look beautiful today, as always.
There's still time, please rest a bit.
Because you told me not to,
I haven't looked
into Ms. Yoo Meri's personal background.
But...
are you sure about this?
I met her a couple of times.
She seemed like a good person.
I haven't lost my touch yet.
Yes, ma'am.
Ask them where they are.
Yes.
We're at the flower shop
in front of the house.
We'll be there soon.
Okay.
I think Grandma is in a hurry to meet you.
Do I look okay today?
You look beautiful.
Let's go.
That must be them.
-Okay, I'll go and let them in.
-Sure.
Mom, this house is...
You said you had something to tell me
about Ms. Yoo Meri.
I do.
Let me introduce myself first.
I am
the ex-mother-in-law of Meri,
who is currently dating your grandson.
And I'm her ex-sister-in-law.
Mother-in-law?
Don't tell me...
Didn't you know she's a divorcée?
See?
She was about to ruin another man's life.
Gosh.
Please, take your time
and tell me what you mean.
Yes, ma'am.
-That girl, Meri...
-That girl...
Yes, we've arrived.
Pardon?
She asked to see you alone.
What? All of a sudden...
Oh, okay.
I'm sorry.
I don't think you can meet Grandma today.
She says she's suddenly not feeling well.
Oh, really?
Is she very sick?
Well, I'm not so sure.
I'll have to go see her.
Do you mind waiting in the car?
No, don't worry about me, and go in.
Go on.
I'll get going.
What's...
Is Ms. Yoo Meri
divorced?
We were going to tell you about that
along with everything else.
"Everything else"?
I guess there's more
that I'd be surprised about.
Meri...
Can I ask you to think over this again?
I don't have any money.
Could you please talk to Beauté
and ask them to drop the lawsuit?
Why did you have to take things this far?
What made you take it this far?
Seeing you broken
and falling apart like this
doesn't make me happy
or satisfied.
Let's forget that you hurt me
and your hatred toward me.
Let's forget it all...
and just keep the good memories.
Maybe I'm being punished.
All the good days are behind me...
and I lost a good woman like Meri.
Meri,
I'm sorry.
I know it's late,
but I really mean it.
I'm really sorry.
I want you to be happy, too.
SISTER
What?
What am I doing?
Meri?
Why would she call me?
What?
You went where?
Why would you do that?
Stop it already.
You and Mom both,
please stop it already!
Oh, gosh...
CEO YOO MERI
KIM WOOJU
Meri.
It looks like my mom
went to see Mr. Kim's grandma.
I think she said some things about you.
I'm really sorry.
I apologize on her behalf.
I'm sorry.
I don't think you can meet Grandma today.
She says she's suddenly not feeling well.
So, that's what happened.
What?
She even committed fraud?
MYUNGSOON
-Hello.
-Hi.
I was just wondering
how Chairwoman is doing.
Oh, it wasn't something serious.
She said she was
just not feeling her best.
I see.
Didn't she say anything else?
No.
Did you get home safely?
I'm on my way now.
I'll rearrange the meeting
for some other time when there's a chance.
-For the time being...
-About that.
Don't worry about it too much.
It's not urgent.
Yes.
Good night.
MOM
No, that one.
-They're all the same.
-Mom.
Hey, sweetie.
Didn't you say that you were
going to meet his grandma?
Why didn't you call
to tell me how it went?
I've been waiting forever.
You didn't meet her?
Well...
What?
Mom, are you sure about this?
My gosh.
It doesn't matter
whether I'm sure or not, okay?
I'm going to settle this once and for all.
Okay, I get it. Calm down.
Calm down.
Mom, isn't that them?
-Where?
-There.
Gosh, yes.
Right, wait a minute.
Wait.
Hey!
Oh, my gosh. Who are you?
Oh, my. Meri's mother!
-Let's end this together!
-No, stop!
I'll make you pay for everything
-Ms. Oh!
-you did to my daughter!
What's happening? Jinhwa!
-Let's end this together!
-Ms. Oh!
I'm going to make you pay
for what you did to my daughter!
-Why are you...
-Ms. Oh!
Stop this!
-Hey!
-How dare you mess with my sister?
-Who's this? Let me go.
-How dare you?
Hey!
Please, help.
-To my daughter...
-Please, help me.
-Ms. Oh!
-You're so dead.
Please, help me!
You're here early.
What?
Isn't today your trial?
I came in case you were upset
about a guy standing you up again.
What?
What is it?
Do you think I'm drowning my sorrows
because a guy stood me up?
I'm not.
Are you trying to flirt with me?
Someone comforted me recently.
I realized that money
isn't everything in this world.
Thanks to that person,
I feel so much at ease now.
I'm not sure who that person is,
but they must be a really great person.
Anyway, I like your attitude now.
Respect.
Respect
Your trial...
I hope it goes well.
I'll get going first.
Wait for me!
By the way,
why did you ask me for such a favor?
Because I had no one to ask.
Wait, is that really it?
You can say no.
That's not what I'm saying.
I'm just curious.
Like, when do I start?
This comes with a lot
of responsibility, doesn't it?
Wait for me!
Hurry up!
Oh, seriously.
You're too fast.
We thought everything
would go smoothly,
but as we each carried
our own unspoken worries,
life got busier, and we drifted apart.
Did I tell you
that Eungsoo quit the company?
No, you mean Mr. Jang?
He suddenly wants to become
an esports team owner.
He wanted to chase his passion,
so he handed in his resignation last week.
I see.
-I didn't know he liked games.
-He does.
He's busy these days
scouting professional gamers.
And it makes me busy, too,
trying to fill in for him.
You also seemed busy,
seeing how you call less.
It's because of the meetings.
With the new project,
it's been a bit hectic
going back and forth from Daejeon.
Oh, I see.
MADAM KO
Can you give me a minute?
I'd like to pay, please.
Please sign here.
-Thank you.
No, I told you already.
Unlike how you think...
No, I mean...
Grandma, can you please reconsider?
I'm sorry. I have to get home.
It's fine. Your grandma is asking for you.
You should get going.
Since everyone is here,
I'll tell you my decisions.
Grandma, can you please reconsider?
No, I mean...
MYUNGSIK
Hi.
Where are you?
I'm at the playground
in front of my house.
I came out for fresh air
since the wind is nice.
"Came out for fresh air"?
I bet you were out this whole time.
Pardon?
You haven't even changed.
What are you doing all alone at this hour?
Wooju.
I was on my way to your place to see you.
And I saw you just sitting here,
glowing under the lights
with that stunning beauty.
What did your grandma say?
I'm sure she called you in
because she had something to say.
She's against us, right?
What?
Wooju's mom paid a visit to your grandma.
I think I know what she told her.
I'm fine,
so don't struggle in between.
I'm not struggling.
I heard you
talking to your grandma at the restaurant.
Grandma, can you please reconsider?
I'm very grateful for the offer,
but I'm not ready
to take over the company yet.
How about we hire a professional manager?
You should've stayed to hear the rest.
Grandma wants me to take over the company.
-What?
-Geez.
You went off in your own head again.
Well, she didn't ask
to see me again, so...
About that, she said
she needs a bit more time.
What?
She even committed fraud?
But you said it yourself,
anyone can make mistakes.
What matters is having the heart
and the will to make things right.
Grandma...
I have a headache.
Let me think about it.
Do you know how anxious
I've been, waiting for her permission?
You should've told me.
Do you know why she called me in today?
She gave me this.
She said, you can earn money whenever,
eat delicious food whenever,
and travel whenever.
But there's a time for a proposal.
She also said, if I ever meet someone
I want to spend the rest of my life with,
I shouldn't lose her.
Meri.
Would you marry me?
Meri?
Yes.
Well,
someone said I shouldn't answer too fast.
I was counting to ten,
but I failed.
I've made many mistakes,
but thank you
for forgiving me and accepting me.
Sure.
I hope you learned a lot from this.
Make sure to keep it in your mind.
I'll keep it in mind.
I will, too.
Officail Website : kissasian.be  Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Mom!
I heard Wooju's fiancée is coming.
Mom, look to your left.
She's here.
Nice to meet you, Ms. Kim.
My name is Yoo Meri.
Hi, I'm...
Wooju's aunt.
This is his cousin.
Say hi.
We already know each other.
Aren't I right?
-Have you been well?
-Yes.
You know,
she resembles her mother a lot.
Yeah, she does. She also looks fierce.
-Yeah.
-Right?
Have you seen my mother?
We visited Yeosu, actually.
We went there ourselves
on Grandma's order.
It was quite far.
YOUNGSOOK'S RESTAURANT
How about this rolled omelet?
Oh, my.
This place is delicious.
Mom, try it.
-Stop eating.
-Just try it.
Just put it in your mouth.
-Okay.
-You must be from Seoul.
How did you know?
You're not using dialect.
I see.
Are you the owner?
-What?
-How's the business?
How much is the profit?
How would I know?
I'm just a kitchen assistant.
She's the owner.
Geez, those were just testers.
But he's making a meal out of it.
If he eats like that
and doesn't buy anything,
he's completely shameless.
We're going to buy all of these.
Could you pack these two up for us?
Oh, no.
Wait.
You can't take these, instead...
Here, take this.
Okay, then. But these cost the same,
yet it's half the amount.
Are you treating us differently
because we're not locals?
-We're also in this business.
-It's not like that.
-It's half the amount.
-Gosh, it's...
-Hello.
-Oh, hey, Bohyeon.
Wait a moment.
Let's see.
I packed all your favorites.
Here.
Enjoy it with your sister.
Thank you.
Thanks. Go on, now.
Bye.
Gosh, you're too generous.
The business will fail at this rate.
Nonsense.
Oh, my. I'm sorry.
Her mother died when she was younger,
and her father's not home
as he's a fisherman.
She's still a kid,
but she's got a younger one to look after.
So, I feel bad for her.
But she's too proud a girl
to take them for free.
So, what else can I do
but give her a lot more?
I'm not treating you differently,
so don't be upset.
Oh, okay.
-So, you're from Seoul?
-Yes.
Since you've been so gracious,
let's see...
Here.
-Pollock pancakes?
-Pollock pancakes.
This is on the house.
Our pollock pancakes
are amazing.
Hi, Mom.
I just saw Ms. Yoo Meri's mother,
and I think...
you'll like her.
Like so, in relation to your marriage,
we played a very important role.
Thank you.
Then I guess all that's left is
to set a date for the family meeting.
About that...
We're thinking of delaying our wedding.
Why?
Well, I just accepted the CEO position.
So, I think it's only right
to focus more on the company right now.
Meri also agreed to it.
Yes, I also thought
that'd be for the best.
Is that right?
If you both agree, then okay.
I guess
I'll just have to live longer.
Oh, Mom...
Son, this isn't the time for you to laugh.
It's not too late yet.
How about I set you up?
I'm a believer in natural encounters, Mom.
I don't do blind dates, so no set-ups.
It's not too late.
Meri, do you have any friends
you can introduce?
I have many.
What do you think? Can you set him up?
What kind of woman are you into?
-Someone unlike Mom.
-Someone like me.
You guys are
going to live here from now on.
This is also a place people stay in,
so get used to it fast, okay?
Especially you, Sweet.
You've been looking so down lately,
just sleeping all the time.
Or was it Sour?
Oh, this is really confusing.
Are you guys twins?
How did your owner differentiate you two?
Meal time.
Dear Mr. Baek.
It's gotten quite cold
in the morning and at night.
Winter must be near,
judging by the days also getting shorter.
You're doing well, right?
It's been all hospital and home for me,
but lately, I've really been
enjoying raising the turtles.
I can't even tell
a turtle from a terrapin,
but I've been turning into a turtle expert
from trying to tell
the twin-like Sweet and Sour apart,
You said I just need to feed them
and change their water from time to time.
But guess what?
I also have to check
if they're still alive
because they're way too quiet.
I think they're introverts,
taking after you.
I'll be participating
in the Boston Marathon next spring.
I'll complete it and send you
a proof photo at the Charles River.
Would you like to join me
for the next November's
New York City Marathon?
I can complete the course now.
If you want to match my pace,
you'll have to train hard until then.
I'll take good care of your turtles,
so don't worry and stay healthy.
BEFORE I KNEW YOU,
I GOT ALONG WITHOUT POETRY
Like these turtles,
who are dependent on their strong shells,
I hope you're growing stronger
through your days there.
I'll write to you again.
1 YEAR LATER
An outdoor wedding?
It looks like it's going to rain.
Tell me about it.
Why do I have to carry things like this?
What's wrong with it?
The grass smells nice.
Also, I always dreamed
of having an outdoor wedding.
He's right.
And they say you live happily
if it rains on your wedding day.
So, I guess it's lucky.
How lucky!
Whatever.
What's wrong?
Wait...
What's this?
I can't believe this. These are new!
Oh, my clothes are new, too.
Me too.
Oh, no...
"Ms. Yoo Meri..."
My shoes...
-Oh, hello.
-Hi.
Oh, no. Are you hurt?
No, it's just my heel.
I see.
-No, not there.
-Let's see...
"Thank you for attending today's..."
I heard your business is soaring.
Oh, not at all.
It went a bit viral on social media,
and let's just say I don't have time
to go to the bathroom.
-Thank you.
Hello, what would you like?
Can we get two packs
of green onion kimchi?
-And two packs of seaweed stems, please.
-Okay.
I heard the side dishes here
are really good.
Really? Thank you.
Gosh, thanks to Sori,
we went viral on social media.
I don't even have time
to go to the bathroom.
You could be buying a building soon.
Why not? Let me buy a building.
-Hello.
-Hi.
What is this one?
It's made
by mixing dried radish
with seasonings such as
red pepper powder and soy sauce.
I see.
-Can I try?
-Yes.
-Thank you.
-Yes, of course.
-Here.
-Thank you.
We have more stuff inside,
so please do take a look.
Oh, my.
At this rate, your business might outshine
Myungsoondang overseas.
Nonsense.
It's all thanks to my youngest daughter.
Anyway, how's your son's business?
What was it?
I heard it was something to do with games.
Every time I see him,
I think about
how lucky people without kids are.
`
It's because he's a son.
Is our youngest daughter here
seeing someone?
Do you have someone
to recommend?
There's no need to look far
when the right one might be close by.
Right.
Let's check out the men from the company.
-Right.
-Take a look.
Well...
How about someone who runs a game company?
-Let's see.
-Me?
"Now is a reading of the marriage vows
to celebrate the couple's union
and a congratulatory speech."
Hey, you look like the groom today.
Thank you.
But don't talk to me. I have to focus.
Okay, fine.
Don't make a mistake.
-Do well.
-Okay, thanks.
Have you arrived?
We will now begin
the wedding of Kim Wooju and Yoo Meri.
Could all the guests please be seated?
We will now begin the wedding ceremony
of the groom, Mr. Kim Wooju,
and the bride, Ms. Yoo Meri.
Bride and groom,
prepare for your entrance.
Luck comes in disguise.
Hello?
When the greatest luck
of my life came to me...
I won?
But you're the only one I can turn to.
Could you
be my husband?
I thought happiness
was finally coming my way,
but luck built on lies can't be real.
Maybe, in all those desperate moments
clinging to that house,
what I truly wanted
wasn't a fake home
I had to hide from everyone...
but a single person who could love me
no matter who I was.
It's because I like you.
Whatever it is that you do,
I'll stay right next to you.
Meeting someone like that.
Isn't that what luck is really about?
Such luck comes like fate
in the most desperate moments.
Who will take care of him?
Keep it.
Some days were happy,
and some days were not.
Whenever waves of sorrow
and loneliness crashed over me,
I lost my way and wandered.
But maybe all that time
was a path leading me to you.
As if we had promised to meet
after a long journey apart.
Every moment of our lives
was leading us toward one another.
I love you.
I love you, too.
WOULD YOU MARRY ME?
Translated by Susanna Kim