Wait...
Is that...?
Huh? You know him?
Well, not exactly.
But I saw him meeting Senkawa
after cram school once.
Wait, really?
Oh...
I have no idea how they
know each other, though.
I see.
Hey.
Isn't that Senkawa?
Oh.
"Contrast"
(Episode 5: Why did you kiss me?)
That girl's friend over there...
He's the one we saw before, right?
Yeah.
Is the guy with him your friend too?
Shouldn't you go say hi?
Wait, don't tell me...
Is that the guy?
Huh?
You mentioned him before, didn't you?
The athletic, nice-looking guy.
The one you said was pretty cool.
What's the deal?
Are you guys...
dating?
We're not dating.
Even if we aren't...
dating...
Akira.
I think we...
should probably end this.
Wait, what...?
Here.
Thanks...
It's because you're so kind, Akira.
I ended up taking advantage of that.
I'm sorry that our situation
caused you so much trouble.
No.
It's not your fault.
It's not great that we
were seen just now, is it?
Do you think he'll ask about it next time?
I actually
told him beforehand that I was
meeting my brother's friend.
If that's the case, he probably
won't suspect anything.
But...
I'm going to tell Kanata everything.
You know,
you don't necessarily
have to be that honest.
If you want to keep things going,
there's no need to go that far...
I feel like... I have to
be straight with him.
I don't want there to be a lie in the
middle of everything Kanata loves.
He's been so sincere with me,
even without knowing the truth.
I don't think I can live with myself.
But
I'm not expecting him to just accept it.
Wanting to come clean
is just me being selfish.
Even if it hurts him?
He might not even want to know the truth.
It could really crush him,
and he might never be able to let it go.
There are things only the
people involved can understand.
Feelings that no one else can truly grasp.
Finding a way for
neither of you to get hurt
is probably impossible.
I don't want to see you get hurt.
My brother...
I really can't compare to him.
Do you feel a bit inferior?
How should I put it...
I didn't think I cared that much,
but he's great at school and sports,
and he has so many friends.
I guess...
I really do feel inferior.
I have an older sister.
She's like a female version
of Hikaru—good at everything.
My parents were always comparing us.
I see...
So,
to be honest, I didn't
really like Hikaru at first.
But then, I ended up really liking him.
Did something happen?
Oh, you don't have to
tell me if you don't want to.
I just didn't know who I
could talk about this with.
If there's anything you're unsure about,
or something you want to confirm,
you can always talk to me.
I used to like someone.
Oh?
So it's a crush.
Did you get dumped?
It wasn't even that. I got rejected
before I could even say anything.
Rejected?
Did they have a boyfriend?
We went to different middle schools,
but we were in the same cram school.
We became close.
And then,
one time we were
talking about who we liked.
Yeah.
That person...
was a guy.
I see.
Wait,
did he figure it out and shut you
down before you could confess?
I think so...
After that,
it was like he knew how I felt,
and he started avoiding me.
Ah... I get it.
Then...
he started acting like I was a nuisance.
Huh?
It was really hard.
It was painful.
I couldn't focus on my studies at all.
In the end, I just quit cram school...
You've been through a lot.
The idea that my very existence
made him uncomfortable...
That was the hardest part to take.
You've been
carrying this all by yourself
for a long time, haven't you?
It must have been so lonely
not being able to tell anyone.
Kanda-san,
don't you find it weird?
That I'm...
Weird?
I'm gay.
Wait, what?
Surprised?
A little...
By the way, Hikaru doesn't know either.
This is our little secret, okay?
To be even more blunt,
I like Hikaru.
But my brother...
He's totally straight.
And he has a girlfriend now.
This kind of love...
It's okay if it doesn't go anywhere.
That's the only way I can
move on to someone else.
I don't really get it...
Yeah, I don't really get it either.
But for now, that's how I keep my balance.
Balance?
If you can find your own
way to balance things,
it might make things a bit easier.
I want you to teach
me the way you do that.
Hikaru's gonna kill me.
My brother...
doesn't know anything.
Well then...
How about one more secret?
It's over.
No,
this grade is beyond help.
Whatever.
I'll just wing it and see what happens.
Are you an idiot?
The next round of finals will
affect your college apps.
- Seriously?! That's bad.
- Get it together!
Kanata.
Didn't you say you have a long weekend
and no club activities?
Yeah.
Let's have an intensive study camp.
Huh?
Otherwise, you're definitely
going to end up in summer school.
Count me out...
Hey...
Stop trying to act cool.
Give it back!
Oh, wait.
How about we use my family's villa?
What? You have a villa?
No one's using it right now.
Oh, that sounds great.
I'll go invite Mizuki and the others.
And
let's invite Senkawa too.
Huh?
If it's just us slackers studying together,
we won't get anywhere.
But...
Please?
Yo.
Hey.
Oh, did you eat lunch yet?
Ah...
I forgot mine today.
Oh! Want half of mine?
No... I'm good.
Okay then.
Um...
Oh...
Sorry.
It's fine...
What's up?
Well,
actually...
I have a favor to ask.
You're so forgetful.
- Shut up.
- What's your problem?
Hey, watch it! That's dangerous.
Uh... are you guys
actually planning to study?
Of course.
Mr. Honor Student.
Thanks so much for coming.
Sorry we're late.
So you're the legendary honor student.
Huh?
The more the merrier,
right? Better for brainstorming.
Plus, it'd be too much for
Senkawa to teach us all alone.
I'm Yurika.
I think I'm in the next class over.
Oh...
Alright, let's head out.
- Let's go!
- Come on.
- I'm so excited!
- Me too.
Welcome!
Wow, this is amazing.
This is insane!
It's so beautiful.
Even the balcony is huge!
My family used to come here
a lot during summer break.
But no one's been here lately.
Don't worry, though. It gets
cleaned and maintained regularly.
Seriously? You're loaded...
Huh?
Mizuki...
Help me.
Which one? Where are you stuck?
This equation...
Senkawa.
I don't really get this one...
Where?
Right here.
Oh, yeah.
This one is tricky.
When you're trying to tell them apart,
it's easier if you look
for the preposition.
Oh, I see.
Thanks.
Are you stuck on anything?
No...
Okay.
Ugh, I'm done!
Hey, you barely even started.
Alright, let's take a break.
Sweet.
Honestly,
I knew this would happen...
Let's go, Kanata.
Oh, okay.
Akira, you come too.
Wait, isn't this a bit much?
Come on, come on!
Let's go.
Just don't fall off.
Wait, I'm the only one
with brakes over here!
Stop it!
- Hello!
- Hey there!
Ah!
Makki!
Let's eat!
Yeah.
Mmm, this is good.
- This is great.
- Seriously, so good.
- Ooh, let me try another one.
- Go for it.
- Here.
- Thanks.
Everyone, gather 'round!
Yeah!
Go for it!
Nice!
- But this...
- If it were me, I'd throw it like this.
Grab it from the side, then toss it out.
Uh, that's a bit weird.
Nice, nice, nice!
Whoa! Watch out!
Makki!
Ouch!
Ah...
Can't sleep either?
Yeah...
Right.
We basically just came here to play.
Sorry about that.
It was fun, though.
By the way,
why were you so cold the other day?
Huh?
Your brother isn't here right now, is he?
Oh...
No...
He's in Kyoto.
I see.
I got the wrong idea.
I thought your brother was there, and...
your brother's friend.
I thought you were
hanging out with them.
Do you always meet that guy alone?
Yeah...
He looks like he has a job.
What do you guys usually do?
Like, play video games or something?
Sorry.
You don't have to
answer if you don't want to.
Everyone has things
they'd rather not talk about.
Kanata.
Listen to me.
Yeah.
It's okay.
- Kanata...
- I said it's fine.
That guy
is my brother's friend,
and he used to be my tutor.
I...
Well...
A lot happened in middle school.
And...
I talked to him about everything,
and he helped me out...
We ended up in that kind of relationship.
What do you mean,
"that kind of relationship"?
The person you said you kissed...
Was it him?
Then why did you kiss me?
I'm...
not the person you think I am, Kanata.
I'm not like you.
I'm not that strong,
and I'm not that innocent.
Akira.
Do you like him?
It's not like that.
He's always had someone else he likes.
Then why...?
That's just how we both...
kept our balance.
But
it's all over now.
Because I
fell for you.
So...
I'm sorry.
(Preview) Looks like I'll be
playing in the next prelim.
Of course I'm going.
I figured you wouldn't
want me there, Kanata.
Go for it!
Why are you apologizing for liking me?