[Mei Dong, Wanted Criminal]
Mr. Zhou.
Dong,
how have you been?
Things are good,
all thanks to you.
Is there something you need, Rong?
Come on.
As your buddy,
I just called to check on you.
Can't I show some care for you?
Of course, you can.
My Rong always looks out for his men.
Alright, cut the nonsense.
There's something
I need your help with.
Just say it, Rong.
No matter what it is,
I'll get it done for you.
I've got
300 million sitting idle right now.
Help me transfer it from the country
to your account.
Rong, give me a second.
I...
Let go of me.
Let's go.
Rong,
h-how much?
300 million.
Is it urgent?
The sooner, the better.
Rong,
with an amount this big
and you being in such a rush,
the handling fee
is gonna be a bit high.
How much?
Thirty percent.
You're that desperate for money?
Rong,
if we're not in a hurry,
I can transfer it
in small batches over time.
I guarantee I can get it done
in half a year.
I charge everyone else 15%,
but for you, I'll do 10%.
How's that?
I'm okay with 10%.
What about the half-year timeframe?
Half a year is too long.
I've got palms to grease
at every level.
I can't help it either.
Dong,
you think I, Zhou Rong,
can't find anyone else
to launder money, huh?
Rong,
the scrutiny on domestic accounts
right now is insane.
If you don't trust me,
you can ask around.
But I guarantee
nobody launders money
faster or safer
[Faster, Safer]
than me.
[Born with Luck]
[Episode 13]
Chief.
Chief!
Still nothing
from Zhou Rong and Lang Bowen?
Chief,
how about this?
We can't just keep waiting like this.
We need to do something.
Chief!
I've got a clue.
This is
the surveillance footage of the kidnappers
that we found
based on the clues
provided by Zheng Yongbing.
[Hexiang Road]
It's these two.
Can't see their faces clearly though.
[Hexiang Road]
You can't see their faces,
so how do you know
it's these two?
Why are we back on
the provincial capital case again?
Chief Zhang, I think...
Take a look at this.
[Sanjiangkou South Toll Gate]
This is the footage
from the highway entrance
30 meters away, two minutes later.
What's wrong?
Why didn't these two suspects
appear again
on the roadside?
[Sanjiangkou South]
They got into a vehicle.
That's their car.
PingC·08915.
Find this vehicle.
Yes.
Wait a minute!
Chief Zhang,
I've reported it
to the Provincial Department.
The Criminal Investigation Corps
has ordered us
to cooperate fully with
the provincial task force.
They'll be here tomorrow.
If they have any requests,
we'll fully cooperate then.
Right now, our full focus
is to find these two people.
Find them.
What about
our own case then?
Borne on a favorable wind,
I'll rise to the clouds.
[Taxi]
Look!
I told you there was!
What is that?
It's so heavy.
This is so cool.
With this...
The crowning touch, see?
[Taxi]
What the heck are you doing?
You scared me.
Now we can take passengers.
Dropping our own case to go play assistant
for someone else?
I'm going to see Chief Zhang.
Captain Wang!
Captain Wang.
Speak.
Do you know who's in charge of
the provincial capital explosion case?
Who?
Yan Liang.
Captain of
the Provincial Criminal Investigation Corps.
I don't care who he is!
We should handle our own cases!
Captain Wang,
how do you still not understand
the Chief's intentions?
Yan Liang
is a well-known criminal psychology expert
in the province.
He once deduced a suspect's escape plan
from nothing but their handwriting.
He's a legendary figure.
Think about it—
if we cooperate with him this time,
it's only reasonable
that he supports us with something, right?
No matter how cunning
Zhou Rong and Lang Bowen are,
can they really be his match?
Yan Liang and his team
will arrive tomorrow.
All the more reason not to!
Come on, everyone!
Drop whatever you're doing!
Chief Zhang,
look.
Not just the criminal investigation unit,
but everyone in the station
who's free
has been pulled in to help.
At this rate of screening,
that Xiali car—
I'll tell you straight—
won't escape even if it grows wings!
Is this really appropriate?
Will it hold everyone up...
As long as we can solve the case.
Chief,
found it.
This was captured
on the early morning of the 3rd.
[Ping'an West Road, Sanjiangkou,
Ping'an Province]
Okay.
Find these two cars!
[Zhou Rong]
Hello, who is it?
It's me.
Mr. Zhou.
Anything up?
Alright, do it your way.
So what's the next step?
Mr. Zhou, next,
we can do this.
I'll find a safe place,
register a company,
and then hire a lawyer
to contact your company officially.
The last image of that car
was captured on this road.
But the suburban cameras are sparse,
so it's hard to pinpoint
its exact location.
Buddy, need a cab?
Need a cab?
No.
We just started our business.
Yeah, we can give you a discount.
Not even with a discount.
Hold on.
Where are you going?
Nowhere. Go.
-Nut. Seriously.
-What does that mean?
This guy...
[Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau]
Song Xing is still looking for the car,
but there isn't much hope.
Yan Liang and his team are almost here.
We've found the Land Rover!
Found it?
Yes.
How many kidnappers are in the car?
Both of them.
Where are they now?
Senbo Expressway Toll Station.
That means they've left Sanjiangkou.
They've left the city.
Chase them immediately.
Tell the canteen to prepare lunch!
Yan Liang and the others are almost here!
We have to give the Provincial Department
a big gift!
Chief Zhang! Chief Zhang!
That video you just saw...
was from three days ago.
Why didn't you say so earlier?
You didn't ask.
Should we still pursue them?
Pursue what?
Never mind leaving the city—
they've probably left
the province already.
Chief,
we found the owner of the Land Rover!
The owner is Yang Wei,
[Basic information; Name: Yang Wei]
an ex-convict
who's now living off loan sharking.
[Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau
Personal Information Form]
The car is his.
Good.
Finding the owner
at least gives us something.
See if you can track down Yang Wei.
What did he go to jail for?
He got into a fight
defending his friend Lin Kai
and left the other man
with a second-degree disability.
That's what got him sent in.
[Gender: Male]
Is he at home?
If he were, would I let you in?
How many days has he been gone?
A few days.
Are you here for me,
or for him?
No, no.
Sister-in-law.
You're calling me "sister-in-law" now?
I really have something important.
Half an hour wouldn't hurt, right?
Are you coming in or not?
What are you doing?
Lin Kai isn't at home.
Where...
Where did he go?
How would I know?
Sister-in-law,
can you let me in to talk?
Oh, my.
A man and a woman alone—
how can you even suggest that?
Come out.
Looking for Lin Kai?
Can you stop bringing him up?
I haven't been able to reach him for days.
I'm really worried
something's happened to him.
If others see me like this,
it would be really embarrassing.
What could possibly happen to him?
He's probably off somewhere,
fooling around with some woman.
I have a bad feeling about this.
I need to find him quickly.
Are you still coming over?
Don't be like this, Sister-in-law.
Kai and I are like real brothers.
I know.
[Precise Phone Location]
Isn't this illegal?
Obviously.
You can really track a phone?
What do you think?
Then help me track one.
Tell me your wife's phone number.
It's not my wife.
Just say your wife's number!
Excuse me.
Hello?
Is this Yang Wei?
Yes.
This is
the Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau.
We'd like to ask you about something.
The license plate's been changed
and the car's paint altered.
We've come back again.
Zhou Rong can still slip away from us?
Can he shake us?
He's a rat in a trap!
Hold it in. Don't throw up in the car.
We're almost at the service area.
Hang in there.
[Sandu Service Area]
Water.
-You okay?
-Water.
We're out of water.
Here, have a steamed bun
to settle your stomach.
Here.
Can't you at least buy me a bottle of...
What's wrong?
This isn't the one we bought for that jerk
that day, is it?
When did we buy it?
Yesterday.
Didn't give it to him?
I forgot.
So you haven't checked on him
these past few days,
and he hasn't made a sound either?
Whose phone is ringing?
His.
Find somewhere out of the way
and bury him.
[Calling]
The line is busy.
The phone must be turned off.
Can you still track it then?
I'm a professional.
[September 6, 2012]
The owner of the Land Rover
is this guy, Yang Wei.
By comparing surveillance footage,
we've confirmed
the kidnapped person is Lin Kai.
They're very close—
sworn brothers.
Sworn brothers?
And Liu Bei.
And there's another...
They also have a big brother
named Mei Dong,
who is also a wanted criminal
and has been fleeing abroad.
What a den of crooks.
Quite the crew they've got.
As for
why Lin Kai was driving Yang Wei's car
and why the kidnappers took Lin Kai,
we can only get answers from Yang Wei.
Look at him.
He's clearly a regular here.
Doesn't look like the cooperative type.
So, how should we question him?
Officers,
I really don't know anything.
It's no use asking me.
Lin Kai was kidnapped.
Did you know that?
That's still got nothing to do with me.
Nothing to do with you?
As far as we know,
there is a little conflict
between you
and your sworn brother.
What conflict?
Sit down.
Sworn brothers,
yet you could do such a thing to him.
Did you think
you were being careful enough
that you wouldn't get caught on camera?
Impossible. Well...
Is the video ready?
Do you want us to play it for you?
Play it.
Are we really going to play it?
Okay.
Then let's
enjoy it together.
I've slept with Ying.
State the relationship.
She's Lin Kai's wife.
Except for this, e-e-everything...
everything between us
has been aboveboard. W-We...
We have no conflict.
"Except for this?"
Is that not a big deal?
Officer.
Lin Kai is away all year round. He...
H-He just hires hookers.
For more than a year,
he barely touches Ying.
Well, Ying and I... I...
We are...
We are truly...
Sometimes we'd even...
cover his photo on the wall.
He couldn't possibly know!
And i-it's even more impossible
for me to...
W-Why would I kidnap him?
I'm innocent, officer!
Whether you are innocent or not,
we will investigate thoroughly.
But first,
you need to cooperate.
I'll cooperate.
I definitely will.
[Subject: Yang Wei]
I-I-I can go now?
Don't leave the city for now.
Be available whenever we call.
I'm going now.
Don't go yet.
Wait over there.
Stand outside and wait!
Customs just flagged someone—
possibly Mei Dong.
Come on, Yang Wei. Come in.
Come in.
-You...
The affair
between you and your sister-in-law...
Go home and sort that out.
Handle it properly.
Go.
Aren't you going to question him
about Mei Dong?
Chief,
should we have Customs
detain that person
and verify his identity?
No.
Just let him in.
What if it really is Mei Dong?
If he dares
to take such a huge risk to come back,
he might be related
to this case.
Whether there's a big fish or not,
let's cast the line first.
Now it seems
Lin Kai and the kidnappers
only had a traffic dispute.
The kidnappers
wanted Lin Kai's car,
so they kidnapped him.
[Phone Location Results]
[Location: Sandu Expressway Service Area]
Why would he be
at the Sandu Expressway Service Area?
According to this,
he's at the Sandu Expressway Service Area.
[Phone Location Results]
[Location: Sandu Expressway Service Area]
Thank you.
Well...
Hold on!
Pay up!
How much?
[Precise Phone Tracking: 200 per search]
Two thousand.
Money to burn.
[Precise Phone Tracking: 200 per search]
[Charge only after locating the target]
[200]
Chao,
I swear I didn't kill that jerk.
You even told me
not to kill him.
Every time we stopped,
I even let him go to the bathroom
and gave him food.
I was very attentive to him.
I've never been
that attentive to my own dad.
Chao.
The cuckold choked to death on his own.
So he choked to death.
Then it's not on us, right?
You wish.
Come give me a hand.
He got carsick just like you.
But with a towel stuffed in his mouth,
he couldn't throw up.
Everything in his stomach
surged up through his nose—
he suffocated.
This death is on our hands,
no matter how you look at it.
I was planning to
let him go once the job was done.
After all, we've never
killed anyone before.
If we got caught someday,
the worst we'd done was robbery—
not a death sentence.
But once we have blood on our hands,
everything changes.
Then what do we do now?
Bury him.
Where...
Where should we bury him?
This place may not be exactly scenic,
but it's spacious.
Land prices being what they are,
and the location so convenient—
easy access to anywhere.
We've done right by him.
Chao, aren't you going to help?
I'll keep watch.
[Shengshun Taxi]
Where to?
Sandu Expressway Service Area, going?
No, it's too late!
[Shengshun Taxi]
No!
It's not late, not late at all!
I'm not going that way.
I'm off shift!
It's too late.
It's not too late...
Driver,
Sandu Service Area, going?
It's too far. Not going.
[Vacant]
Why is no one hailing a cab?
You call this a cab?
It's literally like a tractor.
[Vacant]
That guy's hailing.
That guy's flagging one down.
Sir, need a ride?
Licensed taxi.
[Vacant]
Metered fare.
Right.
Out in the suburbs,
we always go two to a cab.
You're still willing to
head to the suburbs this late?
Yeah.
Exactly. It's...
It's late, so there are two of us.
Safer this way.
Where are you going?
Sandu Service Area.
Perfect!
Perfect. Hop in.
I'm telling you,
you're lucky you ran into us.
Otherwise...
There aren't many cabs on this road.
You could be waiting till tomorrow morning
and still not get a ride.
Exactly.
Get in.
Okay.
Let's go.
You done?
Yeah.
Where's the body?
Right here.
You really treat him like your dad?
Hey, I worked hard on this.
Don't just come here
and mock me.
No, I...
I told you to dig a hole and bury him,
but why did you build a grave
right in the middle of the road?
Chao, you can't blame me for this.
I barely dug a few times,
and it was all rock underneath.
I shoveled... Well...
How big was the rock?
The entire city underground
is solid rock.
Well...
Well, I just want to ask you—
since it's all rock down there,
where did this soil come from?
I dug a hole over there
and shoveled the soil over here
one scoop at a time.
I went back and forth...
You knew enough to dig a hole over there
and move the dirt here to bury the guy,
but it didn't occur to you
to just bury the body there?
Dig the body up.
Well, Chao!
I just made his grave,
and now y-you want to move it?
Well, Chao,
I can't bring myself to dig up graves!
Shut up!
I don't trust you anymore!
You go keep watch.
Well, Chao.
Let me do it!
Chao, let me do it!
Get lost!
Chao,
you really are the pro here.
It can fit another body.
Why don't you lie in there then?
Bury him.
You won't move the grave,
but you can't even fill the pit properly?
Is this okay?
Let's go.
Wait a minute.
[Cables Below; Do Not Dig]
Is it okay, Chao?
Classic
"no silver buried here," huh?
Really subtle.
I'll put it back then.
It's fine.
Let's just leave it at that.
Where are we going next?
Back to the city.
We need to hurry up with this job.
In a bit,
I'll pull over.
You grab the hammer
and go to the back
to get the money from that dude.
If he won't hand it over,
cave his head in.
Why don't you go?
I'm driving, aren't I?
You started this mess.
You go.
It's just killing someone.
You do it.
You got it.
"Just killing someone?"
You make it sound
like buying groceries.
You go.
Tinggang, you go.
You take it.
You go. You...
I just...
Crap...
He ran away.
My fault now?
I didn't even say anything.
You were saying it in your head.
I wasn't even thinking it.
Well then, d-d-do
we chase him?
Chase what? We're exposed.
Let's go.
[Cables Below; Do Not Dig]
Take the body away.
-Chen.
Chief, Captain Wang.
Who reported this?
It was an anonymous call.
We traced it.
It was from a public phone booth.
An anonymous tip?
Have we verified the victim's identity?
The victim is Lin Kai.
Time of death
was over 48 hours ago.
So did the kidnappers
kill him
before leaving Sanjiangkou,
or did they come back and do it?
We've been monitoring
all the highway exits.
No sign of them returning.
Let's wait for Chen's
autopsy results.
If the time of death
is over 72 hours ago,
it means
they killed him before leaving.
If the time of death
is within 72 hours,
they must have come back
and likely switched vehicles.
[Police]
Chief.
Captain Wang.
We can basically rule out
robbery as a motive.
The phone and wallet are both on the body,
and there's still a lot of cash
in the wallet.
[Jinshuiting]
What does this say?
This is the suspect's backpack.
There are only a few clothes inside.
It's written in cursive.
Hegegao.
Jinshuiting.
It should be pronounced Jinshuiting.
[Jinshuiting]
Hegegao.
[Police]
What?
It's "Jinshuiting."
Same as the character
on Liu Bei's backpack.
Summon Yang Wei.
[Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau
Personal Information Form]
Li Feng has confessed it all.
He is a Class-A wanted criminal.
This time,
you finally caught him.
Lin Kai is really gone?
Can you still hold it together?
We called you in today
to talk about Jinshuiting.
How much do you know
about this gang?
Jinshuiting...
was, you could say,
our first pot of gold.
At that time, our big brother,
Mei Dong, handled the channels.
Liu Bei managed the supply.
Well, Liu Bei robbed the tombs,
and Dong fenced the stolen items.
Lin Kai and I
handled market expansion.
Later on,
the business got better.
We all had money.
The first time I ever had abalone
was at that...
The company was started by Mei Dong?
And after that?
And after that,
Jinshuiting's business
just kept growing.
Then...
D-Dong and Liu Bei started thinking about
how to take the business
to the next level.
Then they decided to
crowdfund—
to rob
the Mausoleum of the First Qin Emperor.
I heard.
You guys really dared to dream big.
If you were in Egypt,
would you have gone to
dig up the pyramids?
We surveyed it.
The pyramids in Egypt,
the ancient city of Pompeii in Italy,
and the Mayan temples in Honduras—
Dong checked them all out.
That's why they say
you need to get out and see the world.
The more places you see,
the more you realize
how good things are back home.
Those places—
t-there's nothing left underground.
It's still our country
that has the good stuff.
-So much treasure is buried...
-Stick to the point.
And then what?
And then... Well...
The crowdfunded tomb-robbing scheme
got discovered.
The two of them killed someone over it
and e-ended up on the wanted list.
So Dong fled to Southeast Asia.
That's when we
went our separate ways.
Mei Dong has a murder charge on him, huh?
So what was he doing in Southeast Asia?
Started a new business.
What kind of business?
Financial derivatives.
Just l-loan sharking.
He provided capital from overseas,
while Lin Kai and I handled
debt collection and lending here.
Just loan sharking?
A-And money laundering.
Tell us about Liu Bei.
I-I really don't know about him.
We haven't been in touch for a long time.
I-I just heard that he...
he might still be doing his old trade.
Besides tomb raiding,
has Liu Bei been
negotiating some big deal recently?
About...
some big artifact?
Well...
I really... really...
really don't know.
Mei Dong is back, you know?
Impossible.
Absolutely impossible.
He's a wanted criminal.
He wouldn't dare come back
even if his own mother died.
Doesn't he value your bonds?
Your good buddy Lin Kai died.
Wouldn't he come back for that?
He is a loyal friend.
There's real brotherhood between us.
I'm telling you,
Mei Dong is back.
Help me get him to come out.
That's impossible.
No, officer.
I-It's not that I don't want to help you.
H-He really wouldn't dare come back.
He...
[Dong]
It's M-Mei Dong.
You know what to say, eh?
Don't stutter.
[Dong]
D-Dong.
Wei,
I'm back in Sanjiangkou.
Do you have time tonight?
I-I do.
Why did you come back?
W-W-Why did you
come back so suddenly?
There's a big deal in Sanjiangkou.
I came back to negotiate personally.
If it goes through,
we won't need to work
for three to five years.
Then let's say 7 PM,
in the Guanlan Hotel lobby.
I'll wait for you.
You...
Didn't you say
he wouldn't come back
even if his mother died?
You haven't been straight with us.
[Investigation Area]
Chief,
what does catching Mei Dong
have to do with
us investigating Zhou Rong and his men?
It has nothing to do with it.
If it doesn't,
why are we catching Mei Dong?
Mei Dong has a big deal to negotiate.
Liu Bei has a big business to conduct.
And they both end up in this city.
I have a feeling there's something bigger
going on here.
Chief Zhang.
Lin Kai's time of death
was within the last 72 hours.
It must have been those two kidnappers
returning.
Report it to Director Gao.
It should satisfy him, right?
I-I also have some news.
Mei Dong called.
He's arranged to meet Yang Wei
tonight at 7 PM
at the Guanlan Hotel.
It really was him.
What is he doing back here?
Trying to get himself caught?
Mei Dong said he came back
to negotiate a deal.
After all his years
laundering money in Southeast Asia,
for him to show up in person,
the amount must be enormous.
They think they can come and go
whenever they want?
Not a chance.
In their dreams.
Then, let's move quickly
and arrange an arrest.
Okay.
Sit out the operation tonight.
I have an even more important task
for you.
Organize the materials
for the provincial task force first,
and send them to Director Gao.
There's one thing
that needs to be made absolutely clear:
request that jurisdiction
be formally assigned to us
so we can lead the investigation.
We will report
all developments in real time
and hand over the suspects
according to regulations afterward.
Be clear about it,
but keep the wording tactful.
After all, they're from
the Provincial Department.
Organizing materials again?
I'm fully recovered.
I know you're fully recovered.
But can I trust others to do this?
Wang Ruijun?
Song Xing?
Understood. Consider it done.