EMILY BRONTË THE COMPLETE POEMS
Noah, are you ready?
My Fault
What are you reading?
JANE AUSTEN PRIDE AND PREJUDICE
Just tell me. I'm not
wearing my glasses.
You're not going to talk to me?
This isn't easy for me either.
You spend your life trying
to get to the next level,
but the same monster keeps
getting in your way.
But one day, when you've
run out of hit points,
you're given an extra chance
at life, just like that.
Mom, enough video game metaphors.
I'm not ten.
Well, it's like opening a new book
and a new story begins. Better?
Damn it, Noah. Now we'll be the
main characters of our own lives.
Your life. Mine's 1,000 km away.
Now I'm all by myself
just for a fucking whim.
- Will and I love each other.
- Don't want to hear it.
Well, we love each other.
I love somebody too
and you didn't care.
I didn't want to keep you
from Dan and your friends.
Noah, you're 17.
I'm sure you'll make
friends being this nice.
I'm not in the mood.
Honey, St. Marie
is a good school.
It has a great volleyball team.
- You'll be the captain in no time.
- Don't you get it?
I don't wanna go to a fancy
school a stranger is paying for.
He's not a stranger,
he's my husband.
So get used to it.
Hi, Manuel!
Will, honey!
Hi.
How was the trip?
I'll tell you later.
Please, miss.
- I can do it, thanks.
- It is my duty.
- Allow me. Allow me, miss.
- No.
- I can do it! - Allow me.
Let Martín help you.
Let me take the suitcase!
You win, Mortimer.
- I'm so happy to see you, Noah.
- I can't say the same, I'm sorry.
Well, I just want you to feel at home
and for you to consider me your family.
At some point.
Why don't we show you around?
Take it easy.
- Good morning. - Ma'am.
All right, sir.
This is the hallway, that's the
kitchen, the bedrooms are upstairs.
- This is the spa.
- And the gym.
This saves you quite
a few maneuvers!
Don't you have a library?
Or a guest room where I can be
alone and rest for a while?
Your favorite colors.
A decorator helped me,
but I chose most of it.
I don't know what to say.
I wanted you to have what you always
wanted but I couldn't give you.
It's amazing.
- Thanks.
- You deserve it, sweetie.
Okay, Mom.
And it's not a guest room.
I'm sorry.
In fact, Nicholas'
room is next door.
Oh, right, Nick. Daddy's boy,
the perfect son... How cool.
Listen to me.
As perfect as he may be,
he's your stepbrother now.
You have the same right
to be in this house.
You know I'll never
see it like that.
And I won't stop until you
see this as it is, our home.
Now unpack.
This is obscene.
Very funny.
The ringtone you
had was so dull.
- How do I change it? - Don't!
I want you to hate me.
Hate you?
I don't want you to bug
me about how you miss me.
Well, suck it up, because
I miss you already.
Well, I hate you. I'm so jealous.
That dressing room!
I'm not going to wear
any of those dresses.
Are you crazy? Enjoy it!
I can't stand all
this extravagance.
The house smells
like poodle perfume.
Can you picture me in the spa cuddling
up to one of those pompoms on legs?
So I have to feel sorry
for you for being rich?
Today it's family dinner
at the sailing club.
I'll puke overboard.
Look, his great-grandfather
was an English admiral.
Enough to make you puke again.
- Post millions of photos, please.
- Yes, I will.
I didn't eat anything
and I'm starving.
Why don't you ask your butler?
I bet these people don't
even have a lousy sandwich.
Just as I expected, not
one goddamn sandwich.
Shit!
You must be my dad's
new wife's daughter.
How about an Angus ragout? Some ramen?
An apple strudel?
Don't know what you eat in Yokel-land,
but if you're gonna throw it up...
- Nicholas, right?
- That's right. And you are?
- Seriously?
- Are you still there?
- Noah? - Noah?
Isn't that a boy's name?
Your limited vocabulary doesn't
include the word "unisex"?
Do you know what Thor's favorite
word from my vocabulary is?
It starts with "a,"
then "tta,"
and ends with "ck."
- It's not funny.
- He doesn't like you.
He must think you snuck
in without permission.
But that's not true, is it?
That's enough, Nicholas!
He's like a poodle, but smarter.
Did you hit your head
as a baby, you jerk?
Thor hates it when
people insult me.
- Relax!
- Say something, damn it!
Thor, stop.
- What are you doing?
- Seriously, or I'll hit you.
If he senses a threat,
he'll rip you to shreds.
- You'll still get a pan in the head.
- Thor, sit!
You're crazy, aren't you?
By the way, from a distance, I
couldn't see your freckles, sis.
I'm not your sister
nor anything like it.
Hey! I see you've already met.
Oh, yes, Nick is very nice.
But I like Thor best.
Right, cutie? Come here.
Come here, little guy! Hey!
I don't know what's wrong.
I must scare him.
That was awesome!
Betty?
- You're still there?
- My God, your stepbrother!
Was that the sweet boy
your mom mentioned?
You see? A total dick.
Is he hot, though?
So you're a gossip
and a pervert.
So he's a total hottie, then?
I don't know. I didn't
really look at him.
I don't mind the lack of punctuality,
but this dinner is bad timing.
I'm sorry, it's not negotiable.
She must be choosing a dress.
We went overboard in the store.
Right, sweetie?
You look stunning, Noah.
Let's go.
Why don't you take a picture?
Next time, you're driving.
Should I change the music? Maybe
she likes something more... Right?
You're riding
shotgun, you choose.
Texting: Hey. THIS IS WORSE THAN I IMAGINED. I
WISH YOU WERE HERE. CALL ME WHEN YOU GET THIS
- Is the temperature okay?
- Yes, don't turn it up.
No? You like it cool?
- Hands on the wheel. - No...
On the wheel, please!
Texting: I'LL CALL YOU LATER.
GOTTA GO. LOVE YOU
- It's a straight road.
- You smell great.
- 7654. Nick. - There's Nick.
Noah, your membership card
will arrive next week.
Meanwhile, you can
use my surname.
- Won't that be confusing?
- Why would it be?
Hello, Mr. Leister.
Hi. I'm Mrs. Leister.
Noah Leister.
Congratulations, sir.
I did hear rumors.
No, Antonio, no. I'm
not that kind of guy.
This is Mrs. Leister.
- I'm sorry, how silly of me.
- Don't worry. It wasn't your fault.
Come on.
Summer has never been my favorite season,
but with this sea, the sunsets, you...
This city amazes me.
Ranked as one of the most charming places
in the world by National Geographic.
Thanks to our lobbying.
Are there a lot of forest
fires around here?
Yes, Noah, unfortunately,
it's a blight on our city.
There have been two
already this summer.
I don't get people who throw
cigarette butts out the window.
Ever had points deducted
from your license?
For doing that? Impossible.
Nick doesn't smoke.
He's an athlete. Surfing
champion, right?
- Yes. - Surfing?
Is there a problem?
No, I just prefer team
and strategic sports.
Where you have to use
your intelligence.
If you'll excuse me, I
have to go to work.
- At Mikel's? - Yes.
- Your first case? - I wish.
His dad asked us to take
care of the paperwork.
He studies law, and
gets great grades.
But it's all strength of
mind, no intelligence.
Don't worry, if you're fired
from Mikel's dad's firm,
you'll still have your dad's.
There'll always be a Leister
Enterprises subsidiary to milk.
- Right, Nick? - Noah, please.
It's fine.
My evening was going
to be dull...
Now we'll have something
to laugh about.
See you later, sis.
- I'm leaving too.
- You're staying.
No, wait. Nick.
Can you take her home?
Isn't it on the way?
Not really, it's
quite the detour.
- I'd rather take a taxi.
- That's enough.
We won't tolerate this attitude.
- It's best if you get along.
- Will's right.
Go with Nick, don't worry.
He's a careful driver.
- What are you doing?
- What's your problem now?
I don't want to die because
of a lunatic who can't drive.
- You think you could do better?
- Wanna bet?
You're in my house, in my
city, and my car, so shut up.
Just because you own things
you think you're gods.
Well, you're in my personal space, my
comfort zone, and my sight, so go away!
Your mom must love you a
lot to put up with you.
What would you know
about a mother's love?
- What are you doing? - Get out.
- Why? What did I say?
- Get out or I'll get you out myself.
You wouldn't dare.
Nick!
What is he doing?
No way, no.
Nicholas!
Nick, let go of me!
- What are you doing?
- Call that taxi.
- No taxi will pick me up here.
- Uber, then.
Nick!
Nick, seriously? You're not even
going to give me a safety vest?
This can't be happening to me.
And now I'm out of battery. God damn...
Fuck! That asshole!
Fuck.
Come on...
Fine, don't stop. I bet
you're a serial killer.
I dodged a bullet there.
Shit.
- Hey, are you okay? - Yeah.
Some jerk left me stranded here.
All alone, in the
middle of nowhere?
Yes, all alone, in the
middle of nowhere.
- All right, bye. - No, hey!
Wait. Okay, I know
that sounded bad.
But it's true. I can't leave you all
alone in the middle of nowhere.
Okay, that sounds better.
Do you have an iPhone charger?
What a day. I couldn't even take
my charger out of my suitcase.
So...
- Where am I taking you?
- Where are you headed?
To some random party
at a villa out here.
I'd invite you, but if
what I said sounded bad,
you'll think I'm
gonna dismember you.
The surprise guest, right?
- Where do you live?
- Know where the Leisters live?
Of course. Do you
live near there?
- I live there. - What?
You live in Nicholas' house?
Worse. He's my stepbrother.
- And the one who left me stranded.
- Nick?
What an asshole.
Well, now I get it. He didn't
have time to drop you home.
- What do you mean?
- He wanted to get there early.
- Get where?
- To the party I just told you about.
Hold on, Nick is there?
There's no party without Nick.
Noah, listen.
It's a gang get-together,
so be careful.
That's the most dangerous
one over there.
That guy in white is Ronnie.
Got out of prison yesterday. To give
you an idea of what the deal is.
What's up?
- How are you? - Yo, Ronnie.
- Good to see you.
- You good? How are you?
Listen. You've got the
purples, the greens,
the blues, and then
there's our gang.
And that's our leader.
Let's go!
How's it going, man?
Drink!
Yeah!
- What are you doing here?
- Surprised I made it on foot?
- Who'd you come with?
- Shithead.
Freckles, just go back
to where you came from.
I'm staying here until
I want to leave.
- I won't repeat it.
- You're in no position to order me.
- I'm not?
- What if your dad finds out about this?
- You wouldn't dare.
- The perfect boy, huh?
Damn. You've really
fooled everyone.
- I'm perfect in many ways, honey.
- Modesty isn't one of them.
The other girls are not
concerned about that.
I'm not like most other girls.
You're not? I'd say you are.
Ordinary lips...
An empty gaze...
A neck...
- What's that? - A knot.
To show how twisted you are?
- To show how strong I am.
- Strong.
A figure-of-eight knot,
the hardest to undo.
There's no knot too hard for me.
Just by kissing their
tattoos, girls loosen up.
- How can you be sure everyone likes you?
- Small details.
- Such as?
- You haven't asked me to let go of you.
Obviously I want you to let go!
Never mind. I like women,
not girls with braids.
- I never wear braids.
- Look, sis,
you have no idea what
you're getting into.
So stay out of my way, and I'll
stay out of yours. Got it?
Asshole.
Can I help you?
- Shit, sorry. Is this your Jeep?
- No.
Just some creep's who
snuck into the party.
Wreck it, if you want.
You're Noah, right?
If Nick sent you to watch
over me, I don't need it.
I'm not here for him. Mario
told me what he did.
- Are you his girlfriend?
- Mario's? No.
No, Nick's. He's got his tongue
down every girl's throat.
Nick and I go way back.
- I feel sorry for you, he's a jerk.
- He has his days.
Hey, what's up? Cheers!
What's up, dog?
How are you? Sorry
for the trouble.
If I'd taken the sports car, I
wouldn't have had an excuse.
No worries, I'll take the 4x4.
- Fuck. - What is it?
I can't see my boyfriend's and
my best friend's stories.
So you need a new boyfriend
and a new best friend.
- I'm Jenna. - Nice to meet you.
- I must've just pressed something.
- Look at me.
Forget about that, girl. Take
off your bra, get drunk,
and make out with the hottest guy.
In that order.
I'm not really into all that,
regardless of the order.
Who's that hottie
talking to Jenna?
Hottie? You're tripping, dude.
Go on, get out of here.
Put this on so Ronnie's gang
members don't bother you.
Anything I can put on
to keep Nick away?
Hey! Hello, ladies.
- Hi, man. - Hi.
Hey! Hey, shoo!
No, this is Lion, my boyfriend.
- He's one of ours.
- Welcome to the club, then.
Okay.
Hi.
So you're Nick's sister.
Damn, news sure
travels fast, Ronnie.
Yeah.
What's up?
Coke or mojito?
- Coke. - Here.
- Shit, this has rum in it.
- Just a little.
- No, thanks.
- Drink, it's good.
- No, thank you.
- Drink, don't be silly.
- What the hell?
- Last time you crash my party.
Get your Jeep and scram
before I kill you.
Why do guys solve
everything with violence?
Right. I'm still hurting
from your punch.
We agreed to stay out
of each other's way.
What are you doing?
That asshole goes around
spiking girls' drinks.
What? Shit.
- I'm taking you home.
- No, I'm going with Mario.
Mario! Mario?
I'm fine, I just feel
a little hot, okay?
Hey, leave me alone. I'm
just cold, damn it.
No, man, not again.
No, let me drive.
- I've always wanted to drive one of these.
- My baby? Never.
- You're drugged and don't have a license.
- I'm just dizzy.
You did drink, though.
Just one shot.
Yeah, but off of
someone's boobs.
Nice and salty tequila mixed with sweat.
Tasty, huh?
What would Freud say about pouring liquids
and sucking them all up like that?
Freud isn't some trap
singer, just so you know.
He'd say that it's like shedding
tears, or something worse,
on your mother's breasts.
So suck on that!
Leave my mom alone.
Sweetie, where's the
Bohemian glass?
What's the matter?
Your mom never taught you that there's a
thing called a glass to pour liquids in?
Hey, Darcy, my friend! This
is your great-grandson.
But don't be fooled, he's
no English dandy like you,
even with a damsel in his arms.
Oh, my!
What's this?
I bet you drink your steroids
out of a glass though, right?
Well, you know what?
Glass is a liquid.
A liquid that holds another liquid.
Neat, right?
If you were capable of having
emotions, you'd appreciate it.
Glass flows so slowly
that it appears solid.
That's why it's so fragile.
Hard, but fragile.
No, not the light!
Don't touch me.
Asshole.
Noah.
Sweetheart, wake up.
- Sweetheart. - Rafaella!
Come, honey.
Come on.
Get in here.
- Here. - What's going on?
Open the fucking door!
Don't come out, okay?
Open it or I'll break it!
- Working at Mikel's house, were you?
- Yes.
- Ibuprofen? - Thanks, Martín.
- Coffee, miss?
- Thanks, Mortimer, I'll get it myself.
- What happened last night?
- You really don't remember?
- This'll be fun.
- When your dad walks through that door.
- We'll see who ends up worse off.
- Tell me.
I put you into bed and
lots of things happened.
You didn't touch me.
That's what a psychopath would do.
You're more twisted, Nick Leister.
- Really?
- I know you did something.
- Did you record me? - No.
I should have, you
were very funny.
Good morning.
- Good morning. - Hi.
- Hi. - How was last night?
Last night?
- You know where I was last night?
- Yes, at Jenna's.
You texted me to say you were
staying there to watch La La Land.
- I did?
- Jenna is from a very wealthy family.
Well, that's besides the point.
Her boyfriend is a mechanic.
You're going to get
on just great.
Yeah, I'm sure.
Thanks for introducing
her to your friends.
You're welcome, anything
I can do to help.
You're so sweet.
And I'm glad you've
settled your differences.
MOM, I WAS WRONG ABOUT NICK.
HE'S WONDERFUL
Were there any boys your age?
I don't need friends.
You separated me from Dan,
but I won't forget him.
- Sweetie...
- He's much better than all these snobs.
Dan?
Her boyfriend. She misses him,
she must've had a bad night.
More pancakes?
I'm good. Thanks, Petra.
- Right here's fine.
- I'll get sunburned.
UNKNOWN NUMBER
Hello?
Yes?
- Watch out, Lion. - So cool.
I almost hit you.
Hey, sis.
Don't ever touch my phone again.
Don't ruin one of
my parties again.
- La La Land? - It suits you.
I hate chick flicks.
You're more into porn, right?
With that face...
Leave her alone.
- Just ignore them.
- It's fine. I can stick up for myself.
Bro, you missed out on the
best part of the party.
I know, man. I crashed.
I stayed up reading.
Hey, did you know that
glass is a liquid?
Crazy, right?
- Are you shitting me?
- I'm serious.
I swear. The windshields
you replace in the garage?
Pure liquid. How about that?
- What are you smoking, bro?
- Crystal.
Mikel, tonight we do need
to do that paperwork.
- What time should we meet?
- 9:00 at my place?
Book: ROMEO AND JULIET 9:00?
Okay.
- We can order some pizza.
- Okay. Cool.
Come help me with this.
Nice ass, right?
And now, like flies to honey...
- Nick. - What?
- You didn't invite us to your party.
- I saw you there.
Please, can we come
to the race tonight?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
The weather is nice
today, isn't it?
HEATS
Nick! Nick! Nick!
Good luck, baby.
Careful on the sixth
turn, it's tricky.
- Okay? - Don't worry.
That's it. Go, Nick!
What's the matter?
Are you afraid you won't
make it to the final?
Don't worry, I'll beat you
like I do every year.
Sure.
Ready?
Come on, Nick!
Come on, that's it! Step on it!
Noah!
- Hey! - What a surprise!
Come on! Go!
Come on!
I don't know what's wrong.
He's not focused.
Let's go!
Come on, Nick!
Problem's the sixth turn.
He has to turn through the wide
side and hold off braking.
How do you know that?
No!
Let's go!
Yeah! Come on, dog!
Come on!
Nick! Nick! Nick! Nick!
She's back for more.
Is she his girlfriend?
Anna? His only girlfriend
is that machine.
Yeah!
Fuck this shit.
Amazing!
IMAGE RECEIVED NOW USER87911124_
What is this crap?
No, I can't believe this.
- Your boyfriend?
- And my best friend!
She's sucking his
face right off.
Fucking leech! God
fucking damn it!
- I can't believe this.
- Hey, come here.
- Cry it out. - No way.
"Get drunk and make out with some guy"?
Or the other way around?
Depends on how hot he is.
Motherfucker.
Come on!
HEATS
IMAGE RECEIVED
FINAL RACE
No, not like that.
Look at the camera, okay?
Now kiss me.
Leonardo Daniel Ponce de la
Rosa, your ass is on my car.
- Sorry, Nick. - Beat it.
Stop scaring away everyone
who comes near me.
You're still drinking
everything people give you.
So what?
I won't take you home.
Especially if you're pregnant.
- I just wanted a picture.
- A picture?
- Yes. Kissing someone.
- Right. Trying to make Dan jealous?
- What happened?
- None of your business.
So that's what you've
been doing all night.
Sorry I'm not as complicated as you,
racing cars to prove who has a bigger one.
If I get you your picture,
will you go home already?
Maybe.
Maybe?
Tongue?
Okay.
There's your picture.
Come on.
Wait here. I'll go get
Jenna to take you home.
Anyway, I'm going
back to the party.
Where have you been? I
haven't seen you all night.
What are you doing? Do we
have time before the finale?
Just a quick one.
ONLY TOOK ME HALF AN HOUR TO FIND A
GUY MORE EXCITING THAN YOU. WE'RE DONE.
There.
So cool.
Hi. It's clear you
know a lot about cars.
I've raced once or twice.
- I thought it was your first time.
- I wish. But I'm not racing.
No? Then why are you
at the starting line?
Already? So soon?
No, hey, I... You don't get
it, I'm not racing, Nick is.
So why the fuck isn't he here?
Shit.
Whoa, baby! Where are you going?
If no one races, we win.
I can tell you want to.
Since you're a woman, I'll give
you a five-second head start.
- What do you say?
- Five seconds?
What's up, Nick?
- What are you doing here?
- Ready?
- Didn't you get my text?
- What text?
Ready?
But if you're here, then...
You're shitting me.
What? Why aren't they going?
Hey! What are you doing? I
just gave you a head start.
I know, I'm using it.
When we reach the finish line, I want
people to know a woman beat you.
What the fuck?
Hey!
What are you doing?
What the hell, asshole?
I like this girl.
Come on!
The sixth turn.
She's not braking. She'll
run off the track.
Yes! Take that!
Fuck!
What's he doing?
What's he doing? He's crazy!
Yeah!
Yes! Yes!
- Have you lost your mind?
- But I won.
- You don't know what you've done.
- Damn cheaters!
What happened, Leister?
The finale was
between you and me.
You've totally
disregarded the rules.
- So we win.
- That's ridiculous.
She's not in the gang.
We'll race again.
She is. She's wearing
the bandana.
You're the one who cheated
by ramming into me.
And I still beat you, asshole.
A woman.
Look at me. A woman.
- Shut up, will you?
- Sorry, Nick.
Rules are rules. So pay up.
I'm transferring the 15,000.
- Nick, that's crazy.
- You just couldn't help yourself. Move.
I'll pay you back, even if it
takes me years to save up.
And the other thing?
I know it's hard to part
ways with that beauty,
but you don't have a choice.
Nick? You can't give it to him.
Are you crazy?
Don't worry, I'll take
you for a ride anytime.
You're not going to enjoy it.
You know why?
- No. - Because I beat you good.
Everyone'll remember that when
you're showing off in it.
Nick.
Please.
Next time, don't let that
bitch out of the house.
What are they doing?
Rafaella!
Push forward! Come on!
What's wrong, girl? Let's go.
Get in the car. Come on.
Let's go, brother!
Move!
Drive!
You.
- Are they following us?
- I don't think so.
Jenna, are you okay?
- Answer me.
- Stop pestering me. I'm in shock.
I worry if you don't talk.
- Because you love me?
- Don't start.
- Not even a little?
- Girl, quit nagging me.
- God, you're lame.
- "You're lame."
- Come on! Get up, you've slept enough.
- I don't feel well today either.
Today is Will's company
gala and I need your help.
UNKNOWN: SHOULD'VE KEPT
YOUR MOUTH SHUT, BITCH.
Is that Dan?
I didn't know that you were so
close to him and Betty. I'm sorry.
- That doesn't matter now.
- It does.
I don't want to see
you like this.
You'll end up mummified with
all that Egyptian cotton.
Here's the plan: breakfast at the
beach club and then the hair salon.
Which one? Will and Nick
will wear a tuxedo.
Nick's here?
He's been missing for 4 days,
but he knows this gala's important
to his dad. He'll show.
That hater again?
It's got to be Ronnie, right?
Just block him.
Yeah... I just got here and
everyone hates me already.
Which one are you wearing?
Hey, Will! Which one?
Both are beautiful.
I'll tell the designers, but
which one should I wear?
We'll be late for rehearsal.
I don't know. The black one.
Important people will be there.
Judges, lawyers...
- We can't leave this to chance.
- Relax, you'll look gorgeous.
That's not the point.
What's the matter?
What are you worried about?
Not being good enough?
Is that it?
Look at me.
You've been through more
important tests in your life.
This will be child's play.
I don't know what you saw in me.
I remember you walking
through that cathedral,
and describing its altarpieces
and its dome with such passion
that it seemed like you'd
built it yourself.
I'll have to show it to you again
because you never looked up.
Tonight's going to be the same.
I'm only going to
have eyes for you.
Hey. Listen to me.
This family and all of its companies,
think of them as a huge cathedral.
And you'll be the perfect
tour guide. Okay?
- I love you. - I love you too.
Hurry up.
I think I'll wear the pink one.
Hey, you know Rodrigo
wants to be my boyfriend?
The blond? What
will you tell him?
- No. - Good girl!
You'll only get heartbroken.
Do what I do, sis, run
away before it's too late.
I have two boyfriends already.
Why would I want three?
My blood sugar.
Come here, sweetie. There we go.
Mommy's going traveling
again, will you come see me?
I don't know.
- When will she be back?
- She didn't say.
What if she doesn't come back?
What do you mean?
What if she divorces my
daddy and abandons me?
- That will never happen, honey.
- She did it to you.
That was different, sweetie.
I was a disastrous son, an
intolerable little devil.
Unlike you. You're a little angel.
You're growing wings and everything.
Hey, Maggie...
I have to leave early today.
No, why? Please don't go!
Ma'am.
Sir.
Honey. Everything went great.
Hello, Noah.
STATUSES - NICK
Thor.
Those turns are impossible.
They can be done.
You just have to pull
on the handbrake,
and turn the steering wheel 20 degrees
to the right and 60 to the left.
Twenty, sixty. Like a passcode.
That's right.
You stood Anna up at the gala.
Where were you?
With someone who needed me.
I thought I was
your only sister.
- I'm sorry about...
- It doesn't matter.
No, it does matter.
- That car must be worth over...
- That doesn't matter.
This isn't right.
- No, it isn't right at all.
- No.
You're my stepsister
and you're 17.
Then kiss me until I turn 18.
Don't let me do this again.
Wait, you get close to me
and I have to prevent it?
I don't know what's
happening to me.
Nick, is that you?
You think what you
did today was okay?
It wasn't just a gala, we were
introducing ourselves as a family.
We can't give that impression.
Your dad is upstairs.
You should talk to him.
I'll go right now.
And you? You didn't
say a word all night.
What am I going to do with you?
- From racing driver to car washer.
- And tomorrow, waitress.
- Want one?
- You shouldn't kill your last brain cell.
Hey! Don't.
We agreed you couldn't come near me.
Remember?
But you can watch.
Tequila?
- Hi, sweetie. - Hi.
Why are you washing that beater?
I have a surprise for you.
- What, the car?
- No. The car's mine.
Hi, Noah.
Dan.
What are you doing here?
You can kiss, don't mind me.
It's good to see you.
I need to finish washing
the car, I was...
Okay.
- Come, I'll show you to your bedroom.
- Okay. See you in a bit.
No! No, please, no.
No!
Nick! We've got a problem.
- You're the one getting close now.
- No, it's just...
- My boyfriend... I mean, my ex is here.
- You're the one with the problem then.
- I sent him the picture of us kissing.
- Oh, right! That picture. Yes.
So what?
- If he recognizes you, he'll tell my mom.
- Noah?
Noah.
Excuse me.
Can't believe you had
the cheek to come here.
I came to say I'm sorry.
- Sorry? - Sorry.
Betty didn't mean anything. I missed
you and she reminded me of you.
You remind me of an orangutan,
but I didn't kiss one.
Noah, I know. I know
I've been a real jerk.
I deserve everything
I have coming.
Sorry, dude.
- Pack your bags and leave, today.
- Fine.
- But there are no flights until tomorrow.
- God damn you, Dan!
Well, brother!
You're soaked! No worries,
dude, come with me.
- Are you stupid?
- That was fun, wasn't it?
No.
I'll help you dry off.
Okay? Look.
Asshole!
What are you doing?
Dan could see us.
If our parents catch us,
it'll be game over.
Is that what you want?
No. You?
No.
Right... Let's see.
Oh, God.
It's fine, we'll dry you
off, we'll help you...
- Sorry, who is that guy with Noah?
- That's her neighbor, Cayetano.
Nicholas!
Coming!
That's right, Nicholas.
Hey, wasn't that the
guy from the picture?
- Surprise! - Damn, Mom.
Look what came for you.
I'd say these flowers
smell like a reunion.
Thanks.
- Honey, did something happen with Dan?
- No.
I just didn't expect
to see him so soon.
It was some sort of emotional jet lag.
I'll be fine.
Have you met someone
else, maybe?
No, not at all. Who
would I have met?
Right.
Well, he'll be on
the same floor.
Who?
Dan. I trust you'll behave
responsibly and show restraint.
- All right, Mom. Get out of here.
- Okay, okay...
YOU'RE GOING TO PAY
FOR WHAT YOU DID
What the hell?
Why are you doing this?
- That's not mine. - Please.
I'm persistent, but not violent.
Is it from Betty? Does
she know you're here?
Forget about Betty.
Does your mom not
suspect any of this?
- I don't know what you mean.
- Sure.
Can we talk tonight
over a drink?
Mallows? Who would send
mallows as a gift?
I found you a cheap
hotel nearby.
You gave that Leister a
good beating, right?
Don't worry, the car won't be
the only thing I take from him.
So what are you waiting for?
Go get her.
I thought you'd want
to be here to see it.
Call your buddies and
let the party begin.
- Bye, Nick. It's your loss.
- Some other time, girls.
Hey, Nick!
What are you doing here?
Did your car break down?
If you need a ride
someplace, really, I...
I want you to deliver a
message to your sister.
Noah?
Nick!
- Are you okay?
- Just what I needed.
I'm sorry. I thought
you were Dan.
I still would've hit you
if I'd thought it was you.
- Did I do that to you?
- No, but you could've if you wanted to.
No. Your nose is bleeding,
don't tilt your head backward.
You need a cold compress.
Do you have painkillers?
You know about beatings
as well as cars?
I'm perfect in many ways, honey.
- Who did this?
- Never mind that.
I swear that from now on,
I'm not fighting anymore.
- It was Ronnie, wasn't it?
- That guy is crazy.
He's after you. You have
to stop going out alone.
- So do you. - I'm serious.
- So am I.
- Well, let's stop going out alone.
Both of us.
Not the most romantic way to say you
want to spend more time with me.
Do you want to spend
more time with me?
I can't. Dan's still here.
Do you still have
feelings for him?
Does it hurt?
Quite a lot.
What about here?
Or here?
What are you doing?
I need to check your sensitivity.
You could have a damaged nerve.
The heat of your hands won't
help with the swelling.
I can feel you're more swollen.
- We're being bad again, Freckles.
- Do you want me to stop?
Are you sure you can resist?
Why do we girls always get
hooked on the bad boys?
You're cocky,
liars,
and you're violent.
You're wrong. I'm not like that.
Noah?
Are you okay? I
heard a bang and...
I heard a bang too, but I
got them all in the face.
I'm fine, thanks.
You wanted me to forgive you.
Well, if you could keep
this to yourself, please...
Do it for me.
- Come on, Petra. - Hush!
- A little higher.
- Good morning.
I cleaned the leaves
out of the pool.
- I'm sorry you slipped.
- It's not your fault, Morti.
Martín.
All done. Dan is on the plane.
- You got a letter from school.
- Thanks.
Looks like he didn't
say anything.
Yeah.
I'M GOING TO REALLY
MAKE YOU SUFFER
No spots left on the volleyball team?
That's too bad.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
- I'll move.
- No, we're in a rush.
Hi, Anna.
All here?
Noah, the race the
other day was awesome.
- Where'd you learn to drive?
- I'd rather forget that night.
Her dad was a rally driver.
She has a photo on Insta.
Was he good? Is he
still competing?
He died.
He stepped too hard on the gas.
- I'm sorry.
- What about you, Nick?
How did you get into
this gang culture?
- I don't wanna talk about the past.
- Grew up without a mother
and ran away. He
wanted to be a rebel.
- Enough, Anna.
- Daddy canceled his credit cards,
and in Mexico, he met Lion, who
taught him how to live dangerously.
Then he hooked up
with his bestie.
You don't have a
dark past, Anna?
No way. My life has been very boring.
Maybe if I'd met you sooner...
- She was the classic school bully.
- Screw you.
Did you send anonymous notes
to the girls you didn't like?
She ripped their
eyes straight out.
So I need to get to
know you better, right?
- That was a long time ago.
- Wait.
I have something for you.
I owed you a car, right?
It's perfect. You can't
sneak into this one.
But seeing you in that
uniform was the best gift.
I was going to get you a poetry book,
but I see that's not your thing.
No! I don't want Anna
to rip my eyeballs out.
This had never happened to
me with Anna or anyone else.
It's the first time I
can't control myself.
Mario is waiting for me.
What does he want from you?
I just know he smiles
when he sees me.
Are you going to
settle for a smile?
Until our faces hurt.
That guy has no blood in his veins.
He can't give you what you need.
What do I need?
You don't need kisses, you need
volcanic eruptions in your mouth.
You don't need caresses,
you need furrows burying in
deeply until you shiver.
Vertigo-inducing
whispers in your ear.
You don't need pleasure,
you need shivers.
We didn't see a thing.
Well? Was that poetic enough?
We now have a car for the races.
Added 100 horsepower
to Jenna's car.
You can borrow it anytime.
Dude, are you crazy? Isn't
she your stepsister?
- So? - Isn't that like incest?
After that beating and what
you were doing to him,
he won't have any
strength left to fight.
Fight?
You guys don't settle on going for
a coffee or watching a movie.
Hit him, Bruno!
Nick!
- Don't do this.
- It's okay. He won't even touch me.
This is nonsense.
- Isn't it exciting?
- Getting hurt excites you?
- Pain doesn't bother me.
- And your opponent?
Do you enjoy hurting others?
No, I just like to fight.
Well, I don't get it.
- It's a way to blow off steam.
- From what?
What trauma do you have
that's making you do this?
Leave him alone.
I'm sick of you!
What the hell is this
idiot's problem?
Are you going to let her soften you up?
Come on.
Go, Nick!
Hey, Nick is fighting!
What is this shit? Did you
know it would be like this?
- Kind of.
- Just for fun. This is obscene.
What if they beat up a
homeless person tomorrow?
Forget about all that, okay?
Because it's not worth it.
- Go on, show him!
- You got him!
- Go on! - Come on!
Nick! Nick! Nick!
I wanted to thank you for asking
me to come with you today.
It made me very happy.
Sorry it was such
short notice...
I don't want this jerk putting
his hands on you again!
Who the fuck do you
think you are?
- Mario, I'm sorry.
- It's fine. I'm okay.
Of course, I guessed
something was going on.
Mario, you can't walk home.
What the fuck do you
think you're doing?
I don't know.
I've never felt jealous
of anyone before.
You drive me crazy.
So this is all you can offer me?
This can't ever happen again.
- I swear I won't do it again.
- No, nothing can happen between us.
Ever again.
What? Why? What's wrong?
- You're hurting me.
- Stop messing with my head.
- What's wrong with you?
- Don't you see?
- I'm scared. - Scared of what?
Besides the dark,
like a little girl.
Of you.
I can't have a violent
person in my life again.
Everything okay, Noah?
Need a ride home?
Mario! Jenna's taking us home.
Pick me up on the way!
I taught her the basics.
The brake, the gas
pedal, the gear shift...
I'M VERY CLOSE NOW. CAN YOU
FEEL THE PAIN OF MY PRESENCE?
I need to tell you
something about Noah.
Did you know her dad
tried to kill her?
- What? - With a knife.
He'd never touched her before.
Only Rafaella.
- He hit Rafaella?
- That's right, son.
There are people like that.
Violence is their way
of blowing off steam.
Why are you telling me this?
Rafaella is scared he'll come
back to try and hurt Noah.
- Come back from the grave?
- The grave?
He was sent to prison.
- Wasn't he dead? - No. If only.
His sentence was reduced. He
was released two weeks ago.
We've asked Esteban
to accompany Noah.
But you know her.
Noah with a driver...
So we thought that
you could do it.
Why do you think he
wants to hurt her?
Because Noah's testimony
was key in convicting him.
It's all here, take a look.
That man is dangerous, Nick.
- Does she know he's out? - No.
- Rafaella didn't want to worry her.
- Why?
She's terrified of her father.
Drink.
Okay, ready?
That guy's all bark but no bite.
Where are all the cool guys
who whisper you sweet things?
NICK - DECLINE
- Those guys don't exist.
- Yeah.
I like you, girl.
See? Why can't they
say "I love you"?
They say "I love you"
before sleeping with you,
- but what they mean is "I want you."
- Exactly!
Of course, then they cum and go quiet.
Mistake!
You have to say it after!
That's when it means
something, not before.
That's so deep.
Thanks.
Not even one?
Bro, liven up this party.
It's depressing.
Leave it to me. What's up?
This looks like a funeral.
Let's party like
there's no tomorrow!
- What's up, bro?
- Lion, is Noah with you?
What's that? Hold on. Hey! Turn
the music down a notch! No...
Lion!
No...
Fuck!
You have to turn up in a pimped-out
car, but the party is indoors?
That's absurd.
Since Nick isn't here,
the fun is over.
Shall we get out of here?
Such pretty flowers!
You see how you can't drive?
NICK - CALLING
Hey, Nick, can you come to
Mikel's to get Noah's car?
It's best if we take a taxi.
Yeah, she's wasted.
There's no way she's driving.
All right.
Shit, brother, you're
going to kill me!
Don't sneak up on me like that.
You scared me.
You too?
- Are you okay, Freckles?
- I'm perfectly okay to drive.
You don't need a license
to drive these.
All this bullshit she's
pulling is because of you.
Where's the handle?
I forgot my blazer.
- I'll be right back.
- She's been out of control for two weeks.
Don't you think it's
time you apologized?
- You're a good friend.
- She's a snitch!
- What are you looking for?
- My blazer.
It's in the closet.
Anna!
Anna, no! Open the door, please!
Are you looking for
the light switch?
Please, it's not fucking funny!
The door is jammed.
Anna! Help, please!
Anna! Anna, open
the door, please!
Nobody is going to let you out.
What's the matter? Did
you see a monster?
Where's your mother?
Where is your mother?
Anna, open up! Open up!
- What happened?
- He's in there.
- There's no one there.
- You're the fucking monster!
Come on. Let's go.
It was just a joke.
Why did you tell me
your dad was dead?
Because he is to me. I
hope he rots in jail.
Please, don't go.
Why do you make it so
hard for me to hate you?
I would do everything to
you, Noah, you know that.
But we won't do anything until
there's no fear left in your eyes.
That's so sweet. So cute.
Hey, about your dad, I wanted...
Good morning, Freckles.
Are you okay?
I thought you couldn't control
yourself when you're by my side.
I should go before
everyone wakes up.
Yeah.
Noah, have you seen...
Dad...
Listen, I... She
just couldn't...
It's Maggie. She's
in the hospital.
Maggie? What happened?
I think you should go.
Maggie!
Nick!
- How are you, honey?
- Much better.
- You gave us a real scare.
- I wanted to scare the nurse.
I hid behind the drapes and
turned off the cell phone alarm.
That alarm is horrible, right?
Don't ever do that again, okay?
Okay. Where is Mommy?
She'll be here
soon, don't worry.
Is that Noah? She
doesn't look that rude.
No, she's not. She's amazing
once you get to know her.
Good morning.
Hello.
Isn't he the best brother ever?
He is.
Once you get to know him.
But you'll always
be his favorite.
The shock was critical, but
she's out of danger now.
Thank God. Thank you, Doctor.
Lucky the nurse was at home.
She doesn't need a nurse.
She needs a mother.
For now, she should
get some rest.
We'll be home soon.
What are you doing?
Are you kicking me out again?
All of this was my fault.
Instead of leaving you stranded
that day, I should've kissed you.
If I'd known earlier
about your dad...
It hurts me to see you're scared of me.
It hurts so much.
But you know I'd never hurt you.
You know that.
They know about us. There's
no time for apologies.
If loving each other is a
sin, then yes, we're guilty.
The guiltiest people in the world.
But your mom has to understand.
No. I don't want to hurt her.
What she's found with
your dad is amazing.
She deserves to have that.
We can't ruin it.
No. I couldn't bear it if
these were our last kisses.
These kisses will last forever.
If this is going to
be the last time,
why don't we make
it our first, too?
Wait.
You're not sure?
- I am. - Yeah?
Just promise me we
will never forget it.
How could you doubt it?
No!
- So he had no teeth?
- We were eight.
What about your first kiss?
It was much later. I was nine.
Yeah, playing with Jenna.
A chain game.
I kissed someone who then kissed
her, and then she kissed me.
Who was that someone?
- Her hamster. - No...
- Yes... - That's awful.
Yeah.
This was amazing.
This was wonderful.
The sun will rise in
less than an hour.
Let's run away. Let's
escape together.
That never works.
Look how the Montagues
and Capulets ended up.
- It worked for Casanova.
- He didn't run away for love.
He escaped from prison.
And didn't Blood
Wedding end well?
- What are you doing?
- Making the most of our time.
You're bad. So bad.
- Why?
- Because I'm out of condoms.
10.50 euros.
I just texted you.
That was fast.
- See how I'm the fastest?
- Nick!
Nick!
NOAH: I'M STILL ON FIRE
- Transaction denied. - What?
Try this one.
Quickly, please, she's
waiting for me.
Nick!
Bastard!
Now I'm going to give you
that ride in my car.
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
Noah!
Fuck!
NATIONAL POLICE CORPS
Impossible. They're
not distinguishable.
That's Ronnie.
I'd recognize that bastard's
shadow in a dark well.
Are you sure?
Very well. We'll
request a warrant.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Detective.
You're welcome.
- I'm sorry. I should've told you...
- Leave me be, please. Just go.
Nicholas.
If Noah gets out of this,
don't ever touch her again.
The fights, the races...
I should've realized when
you missed the gala.
You promised me that was over.
Are you really my son?
I don't recognize you.
They'll find her.
Fuck.
Fuck, Ronnie! You
perverted motherfucker!
I'll give you a five-second
head start to run away!
All this because I beat you in a car race.
You're crazy!
You beat him in a race?
- Dad. - What a bastard, Ronnie.
He didn't tell me.
Well done.
That's my girl.
How was it?
Well, it doesn't matter.
I'm just glad I taught
you something useful.
I wasn't such a bad
father after all.
Did you like the
letters I sent you?
I'd never written to you before.
I don't know, I felt
like I owed it to you.
We found letters in her room.
They seem to be anonymous.
- Unknown number. - Answer it.
Hello?
- Mom! - Noah!
Mom!
I'm so disappointed
in you, Rafaella.
Jonás, don't you dare hurt Noah.
In all these years, you
never visited me once.
Not once.
Oh, Rafaella...
In jail, everyone dreams of
being a gold digger like you.
Don't talk to my wife that way!
"My wife," he says.
- What do you want?
- I don't know.
I see you all enjoying the things
that money can buy and I think,
"Shit, but I'm also
part of the family."
- How much? - A million.
- To which account number?
- By Bizum. Would that be okay?
Cash, non-sequential bills,
in a black, waterproof bag.
At the statue on the
promenade, at 4:00 p.m.
The two of you, and
no police, of course.
Noah! Are you okay?
Nick!
Oh, brotherly love...
We've got something.
Your ex-husband and Ronnie
were in jail together.
They shared a cell.
If I don't call you in two
hours, something's wrong.
Are you sure about this?
She's your daughter.
She beat you in a race?
- Yeah, well, she cheated.
- Right...
You'd like to get back at her?
- That's not on my mind right now.
- It's not on your mind. Right.
Why is he taking so long?
Unbelievable!
You think this is one
of your illegal races?
I'm not going to stand
by and do nothing.
Don't worry, honey. Everything
is going to be okay.
He won't show up.
Why do you say that?
He couldn't care less about the money.
He just wants to see Noah and me suffer.
Don't worry.
I don't like this.
Is it true you lost one
of those in a bet?
The idea wasn't to
lose it, ma'am.
Ronnie cheated. It still pisses
me off seeing him show off in it.
Especially because I'm still
paying for the insurance.
That's it!
The insurance! The
insurance's tracker!
Attention all units!
They found them.
This is it.
LÓPEZ'S GARAGE
Okay.
Noah.
Be informed, he's on the
run in a red sports car.
Unit two!
Okay. The roundabout.
No! Stop!
Get the fuck off me.
- Are you okay? Noah! - You?
Why do this? Just take
the money and go.
You're engaging the clutch too soon. Don't
release until it starts to struggle.
Come on, faster!
That's it, good.
Good job.
Why did you do it?
Why weren't you like you always
were when we drove together?
Like now, right?
- We were a team, I was happy.
- Shit, so was I.
What a great year, remember?
Coming first overall... Two races
away from being world champion.
Two easy races, and
you both ruined it.
World champion, Noah.
But no, to hell with the
championship, my career, everything.
Do you have any idea what it's
like to go for years, years
without laying my hands
on a steering wheel?
Without a car, my favorite
thing in the world!
It's like not living, Noah!
Your lives should've
ended too, like mine!
You shouldn't have come.
You killed us back then.
Doesn't look like it. You seem
happy, living the sweet life.
Get down!
No!
Shit.
End of the race.
What are you doing?
Are you trying to kill us?
Does it matter?
We're already dead.
Noah.
Thank you.
Mom!
Noah!
Sweetie!
Are you all right?
Did he do anything to you?
Thank you.
Ma'am.
Come on in, Petra.
Thank you for coming.
I couldn't be alone.
No one will ever hurt you again.
Ever.
I love you.
Wait, what did you say?
I said I love you.
- I can't believe it. Did Jenna tell you?
- What?
- About saying "I love you" in this moment.
- No.
Okay, it was Lion.
- But I would've told you anyway.
- I doubt it.
Well, believe it.
Because it's true.
So how long do we have to stay
in each other's arms now?
For a long time, I hope.
Because this is where
our story begins.
Will, we need to do something.
Anything, but this has to stop.
Now.