(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
♪Wandering alone♪
♪Walking far by dusk-lit streets♪
♪Your eyes are as cold as clouds♪
♪Faintly coming into view♪
♪The city lights♪
♪Lit up that single moment♪
♪I can't hide or stop missing you♪
♪I can't forget those moments♪
♪Losing you♪
♪Like the seasons in my memory♪
♪Without winter♪
♪Walking down the long, dark street♪
♪Snow will never fall again♪
♪Our old story was torn♪
♪Into scattered pieces♪
♪Replaying every single scene♪
♪After you left♪
♪As if our documentary♪
♪Lost winter♪
♪The breeze speaks of good times♪
♪Pure white devotion♪
♪Send out a letter♪
♪Carrying my longing♪
=The Double Game=
=Episode 1=
(Self-media blogger Wen Yan,
3 hours ago)
Qing,
I'm in.
No wonder you became a mega influencer.
You even got
into a tight Luzhou Group gala.
Stay safe.
Don't worry.
I've got the target.
Once I get the evidence
of their illegal fundraising,
I'll be
the top influencer.
Ladies and gentlemen,
(Lu Jianchuan, Chairman)
tonight isn't just a celebration
about the launch
of the Lianxin Island project,
one of our key projects.
I'd also like to welcome my eldest son,
Lu Tingxiao.
He's back after years overseas.
Today, he'll officially take over
as CEO.
(CEO of Luzhou Group, Lu Tingxiao)
He's taking over the family business.
It looks like my target
is Lu Tingxiao now.
Lin Zhi'er,
where were you?
(Lin Zhi'er?)
Tingxiao's out of wine.
(Xu Shulin, stepmother)
Get him a fresh glass.
What a talented young man.
Be smart about this.
Go propose a toast to him.
(A toast?)
(Isn't this my chance?)
Okay.
(Lu Tingxiao,)
(you're my target today.)
(Those drinks were tampered with.)
(That woman drugged us.)
Where's my brooch?
Are you looking for this?
A hidden camera.
Secret recording.
Did Xu Shulin send you?
Setting me up.
Turning it into a scandal.
That's exactly her style.
I don't know any Xu Shulin.
Give it back to me.
What's wrong with you?
How much did Xu Shulin pay you?
I'll pay double.
You won't be doing this for nothing.
Watch your mouth. I didn't film you.
I...
Hello?
Are you the owner
of the yellow motorcycle?
Please come down and move it.
Sure, on my way.
There isn't a single car here.
Who called me?
(Where am I?)
(This is...)
(the Lu residence.)
(It's her.)
(She knocked me out.)
(She looks so much like me.)
(So,)
(she's a daughter-in-law here.)
(The mother-in-law drugged the wine)
(to set up the elder son
and his sister-in-law?)
Last night,
someone drugged me.
You must be behind it.
Tingxiao,
you can't say that without proof.
Don't pin that on me.
So, you won't admit it.
What do I need to admit?
I never did anything like that.
Zhi'er,
tell Tingxiao.
How could I ever hurt him?
You won't even answer me now?
Do I need Tingxiao to call you?
Tingxiao,
this is Tingyu's wife,
Lin Zhi'er.
(They really think I'm Lin Zhi'er now.)
(Should I play along?)
Greet him.
(Greet him?)
(This is so awkward.)
Go on.
Hurry up.
Tingxiao.
(Oh, my god.)
(She's...)
(my sister-in-law?)
(Xu Shulin,)
(for your son,)
(you'd do anything shameful.)
(And Lin Zhi'er too.)
Mr. Lu,
we found Xu Wangzu, Xu Shulin's brother,
lining his own pockets.
He used Luzhou Group funds for futures.
Find a major media outlet.
Get this story out.
Xu Shulin's had it too easy
all these years.
It's time to end it.
You're back.
Aunt Hui.
Have you eaten yet?
Not yet.
I'll cook for you.
Alright.
(Jin Chanchan Studio)
Sis, you're finally back.
Come take a look.
This month,
that pool hall video blew up again.
Today, you're the target.
If I'm calling you out,
why wait?
(Coaching or a trap?)
The Feis' Billiards Club
looks like coaching.
But it's hiding a mess.
Look at these views.
(Qing, assistant)
Look.
Our KPI is solid again this month.
Not bad.
One more good deed.
But I've heard
(Very deep)
the boss, Fei Yifan,
(Wear a dive suit)
is mad.
That's the point.
The more mad he is,
the more it shows we hit his sore spot.
Enough about that.
Let's handle
the Lianxin Island deal first.
I'm going to meet a tipster.
He has inside info on Luzhou Group.
(Why is he here?)
You think a mask hides you from me?
You're everywhere, Zhi'er.
Tingxiao,
what a coincidence.
Coincidence?
Didn't you follow me here?
Me? Following you?
I got here first.
What did Xu Shulin tell you
to do to set me up?
I came on my own.
I've got things to do.
Did you
follow me here?
This is too coincidental.
I'm meeting someone here.
You're meeting someone?
At a bar?
A woman?
Do I need to report that to you?
What do you want?
You're here to have fun.
I'm here to work.
That makes me above you.
Work?
Here?
So what?
My work is flexible.
I can do it anywhere.
I'm not picky at all.
I never complain.
Top-notch skills, great attitude.
I'm a top star in the business.
Top star?
So, this is what you do in secret.
So what?
I love what I do.
I get it right
every single time.
A lot of people come to me.
But my energy is limited.
I only take
the intense
and thrilling ones.
Intense
and thrilling?
After all, I care about depth.
You really have no sense of shame.
Shame?
I'm a little angel for justice.
How am I shameless?
(Quite the top star,)
(Lin Zhi'er.)
Where's Jin Chanchan?
She should be there.
I'll contact her again.
Send me her phone number.
Yes.
Who? Spit it out.
Do you know how late you are?
Jin Chanchan,
is this your work standard?
I'm informing you now:
This deal is off.
What is your problem?
You stood me up.
How can you say that?
I'm telling you.
I don't even want this deal anymore.
You...
Say that again.
What's wrong with you?
I'll say this once more.
I don't want your deal anymore.
How interesting,
Lin Zhi'er.
Tingxiao.
♪This door♪
♪Lets in the sky outside♪
♪With a voice even lighter♪
♪Than how you just greeted me♪
♪I know now♪
♪What the chill in my body means♪
♪The moment salt hits the wound♪
♪My heart still beats so naively♪
♪To complete♪
♪A joy that needs no brave pretense♪
♪How cruel sincerity can be♪
♪Like a door with no key♪
♪Maybe you just passed by♪
♪The tears in my eyes♪
♪You looked like you had nothing to say♪
♪Then got so good at being cold♪
♪That's why a smile feels so precious♪
♪Maybe you just passed by♪
♪The tears burned into my heart♪
♪Let's say silence was just for show♪
♪Even if I've grown another year♪