Otherwise, you being you,
who would ever take you in?
Fine.
- It's no big deal.
- Wait.
My Lord,
do you plan to use the Marquis's power
to bear the Liu family down?
Since I gave you my word,
I will see it through.
You don't get to
tell me how to do my job.
What if I have a way
to keep you out of this?
What is it?
This is my foster-charm.
Since I was a child,
I've been under Priest Qingxu's protection.
One word from this man
and my Father
sent me away to Tongzhou.
I was still in swaddling clothes.
If he is willing to step in,
Father is ours.
However, Xuanmiao Temple
is a royal sanctuary.
Without your help
I wouldn't be able to access.
In that case, you should
hate this Priest Qingxu
to your very core.
Why turn to him?
A liar is detestable, no doubt about that,
but being gullible
is no less a crime.
That priest is after none other than money.
And money I have plenty of.
If Father can use him,
so can I.
Wait.
What happened to your hand?
What's all this about?
W... Why do you care?
Hands off me.
You didn't
get yourself beaten, did you?
By whom?
Who else could it be?
Whoever you've been
so desperate to please.
Mr. Chen?
How...
Stop being a busybody.
I'm leaving.
When I have news,
I'll send Li Xianhuai here.
Foster-charm, seriously?
Are you smart or reckless?
Ye Xian,
are you here to see Jinzhao?
I heard you were
just chosen as the Prince's study partner.
How do you have time to be out?
I'm attending the palace,
not doing time.
You seem troubled, Miss.
Tell me,
do you think Ye Xian
might have feelings
for Jinzhao?
I'm not sure I follow.
He was supposed to be
in the palace.
Yet for Jinzhao's sake,
he cared to
show up himself.
I mean,
what is he trying to imply?
Miss Jinzhao has only been back
for a month and a half.
I doubt his Lordship
has much of a history with her.
It's only been a month,
yet how many times have they met?
They met at Jinzhao's
coming-of-age ceremony.
They shared a carriage home.
Then again at the Lin family banquet,
and now today.
What are the odds?
I only get to see him
once a year when we return
to the ancestral home for New Year's.
This time,
Xuanqing ranked first in the exam,
following in your footsteps.
Come to think of his biological father,
this is going to be tricky.
Xuanqing is his own man,
not his father's.
Sir,
the Ji family's here with gifts.
The Mid-Autumn has passed.
What kind of gifts?
Speaking of opulence.
This set of jade paperweights alone
must be worth a fortune.
She's still uneasy.
Oh?
Is there a message in these?
The driver we planted at the Gu Manor
has been withdrawn,
but she's still wary.
So you see,
she sent this
jade carving of a carriage
to test the waters.
And as for
these jade paperweights...
Two turquoise, two opalescent.
It's her way of saying she's innocent.
And these motifs—
plum, orchid, bamboo, and chrysanthemum.
Symbols of virtue.
She hopes I'll act with integrity.
It's also a thank-you
for helping Ye Xian leave the palace.
Miss Gu...
She's quite the clever one.
She's just a young girl after all,
living in constant fear.
It truly breaks one's heart.
Greetings, my Lord.
Priest Qingxu?
I assume you recognize
this foster-charm?
This is...
Today, Priest Qingxu came to
Yongding Manor for a ritual
and specifically asked to see me.
So, I had him look over
Jinzhao's and Liu Xiancheng's birth charts
and asked him for his insight.
And?
Jinzhao's chart is fine now.
He once said she'd hinder my career.
Now that she's of age,
that particular curse
seems to have lifted.
However, Liu Xiancheng's chart
is quite unfavorable.
It suggests...
he brings misfortune to his kin.
While "kin" doesn't
include his in-laws,
his destiny is simply
too harsh.
In my opinion,
we should probably
ditch the marriage.
Well,
fortunately,
Jinzhao's betrothal card
hasn't been delivered yet.
If we were to back out later,
it would ruin Jinzhao's reputation.
We can't tell them the truth.
Let them know that
Jinzhao's Grandmother
can't bear to see her wed so soon.
That way,
we give the Lius an explanation
while protecting Jinzhao's name.
All of a sudden,
my reputation matters, Father?
What a pity.
My reputation...
is likely beyond saving.
In that case,
strive to mend your ways.
It's not up to me.
There's someone bribing their ways,
hell-bent on smearing mud on me.
Wait...
What?
Song Miaohua!
How ungrateful of you!
Ma'am!
I've never broken
any of this to her.
Ma'am,
I warned her long ago
the Liu family's son is a lecher.
He's got
bed-warming maids
and a secret mistress
for over a year now.
He's...
What?
He's got...
I've been meaning to report this to you, Ma'am.
But...
It was Nanny Zhou.
She...
She blocked me at every turn.
She said master’s countenanced on this matter,
and it wasn't for me to poke my nose into it.
Absolutely outrageous!
Every word I've said is true.
If I've told a single lie,
may my tongue rot away,
and let me die a wretched death.
Song Miaohua!
The nerve of you!
How dare you keep me in the dark about this?
A family like that...
If Jinzhao were to marry into that house,
what kind of future would she have?
Nanny Zhao!
I want the two of them
out of my sight.
Fifty strokes each.
Pack them off to the country.
Make them gone for good.
Yes, Ma'am.
Ma'am, please... I...
Ma'am!
Master!
Say something, I beg you!
Well...
You have truly
crossed the line here.
You are not getting away with this.
Again...
Taking her away from Lan seems too much.
She doesn't deserve
banishment.
But the strokes are no goner.
Twenty each.
It's not fair!
You told me to
to match her with that Liu boy!
You knew every bit of
the filth about his family.
Nanny Zhou and I
were only doing your bidding.
Why should I take the fall?
What are you talking about?
How dare you pin this on me?
I told you to arrange a match,
not to make a laughingstock of us!
But... I...
My Lady!
Please, don't.
Master, Ma'am,
this is all my doing.
She was completely
in the dark.
Nanny Zhou,
nice try covering
for your lady.
But I don't think you'd
have taken the risk
if she hadn't nodded.
That's not true!
I've been framed!
I...
Gu Dezhao!
When you asked me
to find a match for Jinzhao,
I knew it was a bad idea.
I knew this would be
a thankless task,
but you insisted I handle it.
I was raised as a
proper lady myself.
What do I know of such schemes?
If I were that cunning
about the ways of the world,
would I ever have
defied my parents' wishes,
refused every penny of dowry,
and fought to be your concubine?
You...
No, I mean...
I...
Damn you!
Ungrateful scum!
I'm the pearl on my family's crown!
Solely for this marriage,
my parents disowned me.
It's been a decade and they never paid me a visit.
I've born your children,
run your household.
And yet, while you all dine in comfort,
I must stand and wait on you.
And now, you want to beat me?
Look at me!
Alright, alright.
- I know you've had it hard.
- Mother!
Lan!
Don't you dare bully my mother!
You...
And you!
Ma'am!
Ma'am! Ma'am!
Quickly, someone!
Ma'am!
Get her back to her room!
Go and fetch the physician!
Hurry!
Careful, now. Move gently.
Miaohua...
Woe is me!
Don't cry. It's alright.
There, there...
Everything is fine.
I know it's been unfair for you.
Stop crying now.
Did you hear the Master?
Drag her out!
Make sure she feels every stroke!
- Dezhao!
- Father!
Master!
Take her away!
Don't you touch my mother!
Get your hands off her!
Hands off her!
Let her go!
Move!
Get a move on!
At a time like this,
how can you even have an appetite?
Why shouldn't I?
It wasn't me who caused the mess.
How come you
got caught red-handed?
Nanny Zhou
was too desperate for revenge.
She thought the marriage
was set in stone,
so she had the matchmaker stir the pot.
Who knew it would all blow up?
Of course it fell through.
You've all misjudged Jinzhao.
She has her sights set much higher.
She'd never settle for the likes of him.
What do you mean?
My Lady...
What's up?
Master is staying with Ma'am tonight.
The lights are already out.
Fine, let him stay away.
I'm sick of him anyway.
But what about Nanny Zhou?
It's getting chilly outside,
and that woodshed is freezing.
She'll catch her death in there.
My people are under watch.
Take Ziling with you
and bring her a blanket.
Yes.
I'm not going.
You wild girl!
Any idea
how many times she used to
clean up after you?
Show some gratitude.
So you won't go?
Fine.
I'll just force my way out then.
Don't venture!
It took everything
to placate Father.
Don't give him
another excuse to throw you out.
Bless you, Lan.
How is my lady?
She's miserable.
Your mess has ruined her.
I have failed her.
Did Master go to see her?
Hardly.
Ma'am fainted.
Where else
is Father going to be?
So, he's in Ma'am's room...
Good.
Very good.
Lan,
can I ask you to
take a message to my lady?
What stupidity this time?
It's not stupid.
It's to help her
win back the favor.
My Lady, the Master's orders were
for you to stay in your quarters.
What brings you here?
I've come to beg the Ma'am's forgiveness.
Here are the household tallies
and the keys to the storehouse.
Now that I am overwhelmed by shame.
I'm not in the position to run this household.
So I am here to return
all of this to Ma'am.
I await Ma'am's punishment.
Well...
I beg Ma'am for mercy.
Song Miaohua and Nanny Zhou
paid off the matchmaker.
This wasn't just aimed at
ruining my reputation for life,
but at dragging our
family through the mud.
How can you
tolerate them?
How would I
not see it all?
But I know your father.
If I were to insist on
driving out Nanny Zhou
and punishing Song Miaohua,
I'm afraid
that the marital bond
would end then and there.
But why must you and I
swallow the bitter pill?
That makes no sense.
You're still too young
to understand.
Between a husband and wife,
reason was never meant to rule.
It's only...
I've made you suffer, sweetheart.
Sir. Sir.
Sir.
Then we hire an opera troupe
and have them perform
for three days straight.
Sir has arrived.
- Uncle.
- Brother.
You're all here.
Mother.
Here you are.
Have a seat.
Alright.
We were just discussing
holding a banquet for Xuanqing
and your brother.
Mother,
I was just about
to discuss this matter with you.
Right now,
there's a storm looming large at court.
We should keep a low profile.
Better
forget about the banquet for now.
Why?
It's only
a little gathering.
Since when was that illegal?
Exactly.
A glory like this deserves a feast.
Think about it, Brother.
If my passing the exam isn't
reason to celebrate,
Xuanqing's made it to the top!
Grandmother.
Uncle, your kindness
fills me with gratitude.
I'm sure Uncle
has his reasons.
Uncle is
single-handedly pushing the tax reforms.
He's at the center of the storm.
He must be
under countless pairs of eyes.
Holding a feast now
invites attacks from his enemies.
That would likely
reflect poorly on the entire family.
Turns out I am the
unreasonable one all along.
It's not like that, Mother.
If that was all
you've got to say to me,
you can excuse yourself.
So accustomed now is Yanyun to power.
Nobody under this roof
could keep him in check now.
Mother,
you are the head of this household.
Surely you have a say
on a little banquet?
I don't care.
I'm throwing it,
no matter what.
But...
But what?
Xuanqing.
Let's not forget,
even though your surname is Chen,
you're in no position
to speak your mind.
Watch your mouth.
Xuanqing is your little brother's heir.
In my opinion,
we needn't make it a lavish affair.
Let's just invite some close family and friends over.
We won't even break
that it is a celebration at all.
Rather,
the chrysanthemums in the courtyard are in full bloom
and we're inviting everyone to come admire them.
I don't expect Yanyun
will further object.
We'll do as Mother wishes.
You.
Deliver those invites
without delay.
Make sure every single one
of those former classmates of mine
who didn't pass the exam.
Sir.
Is that wise?
Sir Yanyun was reluctant to host a banquet,
and Madam
- suggested a modest...
- What was that?
Bastard.
Mrs. Chen invited
Jinzhao and me over,
saying the chrysanthemums at hers are in full bloom.
In my sickly state,
I'd only be an unwelcome sight.
I suspect
Jinzhao isn't keen either.
Let's just decline.
Do you have any idea
how many people in the court
would kill to receive
an invitation from the Chen family
to become a guest at Chen Yanyun's table?
They all say the Lord Chief Councilor is insinuating
Lord Chen into the cabinet sooner or later.
At his age?
A cabinet minister?
Just think how my mother-in-law
got into Lord Chen's favor from the start.
Such a merchant's trick.
Prying open doors and connections with coins.
I could never pull it off.
Ministry of Revenue wouldn't have set eyes on you
if not for your mother.
That's why I say she commands my respect.
Why hasn't Jinzhao come to eat?
She's growing more and more unruly.
The Chen manor
is a most lofty household.
Why let such a rare opportunity
go down the drain?
If only Rong were here.
He could accompany his sister.
In that case,
Lan
can also accompany her sister.
Fine.
Lan can go, then.
The two of them
can keep each other company.
Why do you have to
put on that sulky face?
Your coming-of-age is near.
Now is the time to get out and be seen.
And the Chen family?
They only associate with people of substance.
Their fourth
may be claimed,
but that top scholar isn't!
At this feast,
there's got to be plenty of young gentlemen.
A perfect chance to
see and to be seen.
What are you talking about?
All this looking and being looked at.
You can't embroider the wings like that.
Didn't you ask me the other day
why they took away that
ebony Taiyin zither of yours?
It's because that zither
was part of the Madam's dowry.
See?
I've only just stepped down,
and already you're targeted.
I must have been blind back then,
to insist on marrying down,
making you,
my poor sweetheart,
second-class in every way.
Now I've come to see the truth.
For me, this life is as good as it gets.
But you still have a chance.
The Chens may hold a superior rank,
but that prize scholar...
he was taken in from the outside.
Not being the heiress, you're still
more than a match for him.
If you could only
secure him as your husband,
I could go to my grave in peace.
Oh, Mother...
Never mind whether he
finds me to his liking.
He might not necessarily
be to my taste.
You? Looking down your nose at a scholar?
The vanity of it!
Then pray tell, who has won your heart?
I...
I never said I had a preference for anyone.
His Highness the Crown Prince!
Greetings, Your Highness.
Sit, sit.
You're back at last.
Tomorrow,
Mr. Wang is off, no lectures today.
Tell me,
where should we go for some fun outside?
What's on your mind?
Anywhere, if
outside these walls,
Oh, no, no!
Have you forgotten, Your Highness?
Last month when we ventured out,
it was less than a quarter
before Lord Chen found out.
We all took a thrashing for it.
I still ache just thinking about it.
Then, we'll go somewhere
where he
won't find us.
Your Highness,
I hate to be a spoilsport,
but your safety is paramount.
If anything were to go wrong
while we are out,
our heads
would be on the block!
I think I know a place,
where even if he found out,
he'd flinch to fly into a rage.
Do tell.
Lord Chen's own estate.
Are you playing me for a fool?
Peace, Your Highness.
Think about it:
Lord Chen is your tutor.
What could be more natural
than visiting his place?
Besides, in front of his guests,
he could hardly scold you.
And while you are under his roof,
he'd be responsible
for whatever happens.
He might even have to cover for you!
You're right!
This would really
back him into a corner.
It's settled. To the Chen estate we go!
When the former Lord Chief Councilor, Song Chong,
was the examiner for Hubei,
a candidate wrote the line:
"Yan toiled at the loftiness of Confucius."
Lord Song had never seen it before,
so he dismissed it as a fabrication.
Later, the candidate came to protest,
saying the source was in Yangzi's
"Model Sayings."
Lord Song checked the text himself,
and realized he had indeed wronged the man.
He granted him his degree on the spot.
Does your stepmother still treat you this way?
She hasn't changed.
That woman...
she is so petty.
Without a daughter of her own,
she should thank heavens
your good match
reflects well on her?
Don't be offended, Sister.
I only stared,
for you've got that
radiant smile.
You're gorgeous yourself.
Stop teasing me.
When I was small, I loved soy sauce so much
that I ended up as dark as a bottle of it.
My grandma never lets me hear the end of it!
My mother is here.
We'd better go.
Let's go.
Come.
To have two top scholars in one family is rare,
but the prospect of
having three by next year's finals?
That's a blessing
beyond one's wildest dreams.
Is this little Wanxue?
Madam.
It's been two years since I saw you,
and you've blossomed into quite the young lady.
Today,
you and Ying shall be our hostesses.
Take the young
ladies and gentlemen
for a stroll in the garden.
No formalities.
Come back here when the banquet begins.
Yes, Ma'am.
Let's go.
This way, please.
Sir Yanyun.
What's happening?
What's all that commotion?
Madam is hosting a garden party.
The guests are admiring the blossoms.
Who are the guests?
Lady Yu,
and her children.
Mr. Mu.
Two of Xuanqing's classmates.
And also...
the two Misses from the Gu family.
Were
Yi's friends invited?
They were, originally.
But after Yuzhu was beaten to death,
Madam, in rage, forbade him
from hosting anyone.
Yuzhu was beaten to death?
What do you mean?
Sir Yi ordered him to send out invitations,
specifically to his classmates
who failed the exams.
Every one of them.
Yuzhu felt it improper
tried to speak up,
and was thrashed to death.
Bring him here right now.
Death by suffocation.
Mud under his fingernails.
Must've struggled to reach the shore.
"Yuzhu felt it improper,
tried to speak up,
and was thrashed to death."
I had intended to
deal with you after the
Tongzhou business,
but your depravity knows no bounds.
Yuzhu was so faithful.
How could you be so cruel?
I'm not cruel!
And what of our little brother?
Did you kill him, too?
It wasn't me!
Don't you dare lie to me.
I didn't do it!
The pond was newly dredged back then.
It was seven feet deep.
Before you killed him,
you asked the steward
how depth is measured.
This was outright murder.
You have two choices.
Either you write
to the Ministry of Rites and claim that
a chronic illness
prevents you from
continuing your studies,
or I
go to the Prefecture
and tell them exactly how you
killed our brother,
and suggest a proper investigation.
Which will it be?
Chen Yi!
Brother...
I was but eight years old!
Eight, and
already a fratricide!
Fifth brother was always the quiet, shy one.
Just because a word from the tutor,
saying his talent outshines yours,
you took his life.
If a man like you
enters public service,
how many innocent lives
will be lost at your hands?
Mother will never
allow you to do this!
You'd have Mother know about this?
No.
Brother.
Brother, I was wrong.
Don't let her
know about this.
Brother.
I swear I'll change.
I know I was wrong.
We are family, aren't we?
And Fifth brother was my family too!
He was a concubine's, way below us.
Brother.
You're truly set on this path, aren't you?
How can you do this to me?
Yes.
I killed him.
So what?
Along your way,
haven't you taken lives as well?
Latching onto
the Lord Chief Chancellor, huh?
Good for you!
But I know your secrets.
About you and the canal gangs.
This is not a negotiation.
Chen Yi.
Escort Sir Yi back to rest properly.
Damn you, Chen Yanyun!
You will rot in hell!
Uncle.
The young Lord Changxing is here.
He's waiting in the front hall.
Is he alone?
He came with
a young gentleman as well.
Lord Ye.
- Your humble servant...
- S...
Lord Chen, no formalities.
I...
I came out today with my cousin
to have a look around.
Cousin?
This cousin of yours
has quite some nerve.
If anything were to go wrong,
could you bear the responsibility?
That's precisely why we
came to Lord Chen's home.
Surely, with Lord Chen here,
nothing can possibly go wrong, can it?
If you want absolute safety,
it would be best to go back.
Not gonna happen.
I've only just managed to get out.
There's no way I'm going back.
A man of status
does not court danger.
As Crown Prince,
your life is beyond price.
Guards!
Lord Chen, why go to such lengths?
We're already here.
I'm sure you won't plunge
all of us in a faux pas?
Exactly!
I'm not going back.
If you insist,
I'll announce my identity,
and summon the Imperial City Guard.
I'm afraid I'll have to throw
this place into turmoil...
Were these words
taught to you by this cousin of yours?
My cousin is gifted and clever.
Of course he's self-taught.
Indeed.
Very well said.
Then, at the Royal Lectures the day after tomorrow,
you can say it all again to the Lord Chief Chancellor.
Sir, please.
I've only just managed to get out.
Go fetch Xuanqing.
He can keep Lord Ye and...
Wang by surname. Wang Zhang.
I'm Ye Xian's cousin.
Good.
Ask Xuanqing to keep Lord Ye and Mr. Wang company
Wonderful.
We are in your debt, Lord Chen.
It's my duty.
I must ask Lord Ye
to watch carefully over
Mr. Wang.
Mark this:
Do not let your guard down for a sec.
Of course.
Lord Chen, rest assured.
We've only had
close friends
and relatives over.
Gu Jinzhao?
Oh, right.
I almost forgot.
Lord Ye and Miss Gu
were acquainted.
More than just acquainted, I'd say.
This way, please.
Xian!
What brings you here too?
This is my cousin, Wang Zhang.
Already on first name terms.
Now the curtsy's gone too?
Greetings, Lord Ye. Greetings, Mr. Wang.
What's this?
Let's play together.
Alright, alright.
Let's play.
Xian,
what would you like to play?
Anything.
But with winners and losers.
It's all about the thrill.
I have an idea.
Riddles?
We each come up with one riddle,
and put up a prize as stakes.
Whoever guesses it...
"I bet on Lord Ye."
...wins the other's prize.
"I follow."
I just know
Xian
will take first place.
You're right.
Let's wait and see.
You just can't stop
flaunting your wealth, huh?
A willow-leaf vase for a game?
It's not even an antique.
Besides,
I couldn't think of anything else.
A Lumi musket.
This...
Xian,
how come you
carry a weapon on your person?
It's rather frightening.
Frightening?
Isn't being out and about weapon-free
even more so?
What are you doing?
Are you alright?
Lord Ye.
That musket...
Better not point it at people.
What's there to fear?
This musket isn't even loaded.
But once you make
a habit of fiddling with it,
sooner or later,
it would lead to
some serious trouble.
Who are you to lecture me?
Lord Ye.
What?
You hear me out.
Wanxue.
Are you alright?
We were just having fun.
Can you just grow up?
Then why are you siding with Chen Xuanqing?
Funny. Did I?
Today's hostess
is Mrs. Chen.
Go ahead and have issues
with Chen Xuanqing.
But you're now
rubbing Mrs. Chen in the face.
You do have a point there.
I'll let him off this once.
Are you afraid?
Of what?
Of dying.
Who's really afraid of dying here?
Someone who's never at ease,
pulling out a dagger one moment,
and a musket the next.
Isn't that the definition of cowardice?
Miss.
The definition of cowardice...
Baoling.
Sir.
Everyone's been notified.
The Criminal Investigation Bureau
has sent additional men.
We've also set up covert defenses.
With the Crown Prince outside the palace,
won't it alert our enemies
and ruin our plan?
His Majesty is gravely ill,
and Prince Glorian is getting restless.
Didn't we set this trap precisely to
draw the snake out of its hole?
On the contrary, I feel
the Crown Prince's visit this time
makes our plan
all the more credible.
Sir.
Baoling here with something
to report.
What is it?
Sir.
Miss and the other young ladies and gentlemen
are playing riddles.
Miss Gu Jinzhao and Lord Ye
have put up precious prizes.
Miss says Sir Xuanqing
has never been one
for such amusements.
Worried he'll be put in a spot,
she'd like to ask you for something.
What did they put up?
Lord Ye
brought out a Lumi musket.
Miss Gu
offered a willow-leaf vase.
She says it's worth a hundred taels.
This Lord Ye
is a real dandy.
And Miss Gu?
She's flush with money too.
Lord Ye is no surprise.
He's always like this.
But Miss Gu is probably
leveraging this chance to
cozy up to us again.
Take this.
Give it to Xuanqing.
Yes, Sir.
Xuanqing.
"Pure and innocent."
Sister, what does it mean?