If I really looked good,
someone would like me.
But no one does.
How do you know that?
Where have you been?
Do you know that you shouldn't do this?
I just wanted us all to be together.
We are together right now.
Do you think I'm mean?
Why would I love you if you were?
I like you, Shane.
And I want to be your boyfriend.
I like you too.
(If I had to compare my nearly-finished
high school life to a time of day,
(I'd say it's like this golden hour.)
(It's a sad moment
because time is slipping away,
(but there's no denying
how beautiful it is.)
I like you, Shane.
And I want to be your boyfriend.
Mm.
Me too.
I like you too.
And I want to…
Be your boyfriend too.
But we can't be together.
I'm about to move away.
In the end, we'll be apart.
But it hasn't even happened yet.
It's not easy.
Being together only to be separated.
What if I followed you to Germany?
You wouldn't be against
me studying abroad too, right?
Are you really going to study in Germany?
If that's what it takes to
make everything work.
If that day comes,
we could finally be together
without any worries, right?
Time to get in the water!
Shoes off!
What are you doing?
You're so finished!
Ugh, you got water in my mouth!
(Looking back,
I realized I didn't know
what the future held
(or how much time I had
left to enjoy life like this.)
(Luckily, my friends didn't let me
spend too long overthinking it.)
(Thanks to them, really.)
(I'm grateful to have them in my life.)
Thank you guys so much for today.
No problem.
Shane's little sister is
like my own little sister.
Earlier, you called her Shawn, though.
Hey, Kit.
Are you sure I can take the car?
Yes, I'm sure.
I'll ask someone at home
to come get us tomorrow.
Okay. Let's do that then.
Shane, look after your friends.
Mhm. You guys take care.
Let me know when you get home.
Mm.
Come on, let's head home.
Bye-bye.
Thanks again, everyone.
See you.
You wicked thing!
So why aren't we going home now?
The van service is still running.
It's already late. Let's not head back now.
It's not safe.
But we get home
even later than this on school days.
Tar just wants to hang around.
He won't go back no matter what you say,
so give it up.
You think you know everything, huh?
You live in my head now?
More like in your heart, jackass.
Ew! Stop it. I'm gonna puke.
Let's find a place to crash.
It will get harder the later it gets.
No need.
I've already booked a place
my sister's friend owns.
It's not far. We can walk.
You're seriously cool, my friend Kit.
How come we just became close, huh?
I'm cool, aren't I?
Come on, let's get to our place.
Wow!
WISH YOU WERE HERE WITH ME.
Hello, Mr. Nut.
Why did you lie to your mom,
saying it was a Literature Club outing
when you just wanted to
travel with your friends?
I didn't lie.
Traveling together counts
as a bonding activity.
But don't worry, sir.
You won't have to take care of
the students all by yourself.
I got you some backup.
Backup?
There he is.
Right on time.
Hold on! Wait!
This way, sir.
I'm coming.
I'm coming. Wait up!
I'm here.
I'll be helping you, Mr. Nut.
Think of it as payback for helping
me out during the school field trip.
Oh, I forgot.
I'll just run back and put away the helmet.
Actually, we can just go.
Guys, get in the van.
Chop chop!
I'm hopping in too.
Thanks, Mon.
One more kid for me to take care of.
It's like this every time.
They said it smelled like lime.
Hello, sir.
Hi, guys.
I missed you so bad, Mon.
We were apart for hours.
I missed you too.
Let's take some photos and post them.
My boyfriend came
all the way to Pattaya to see me.
Wait, Kim.
No couple photos today.
Why not?
I told my mom I was coming here with
Literature Club friends, not to see you.
If she finds out, we'll be in trouble.
So no couple photos.
Come on.
Even without the social media updates,
it's still our trip, right?
Aren't you happy?
I am.
Just having you here makes me really happy.
Kim and Mon must be thinking
they're the only two people in the world.
Yeah, I guess so.
I'm kind of jealous of them, honestly.
Shane.
Since you're leaving for Germany,
why not make this your farewell trip?
How do you know I'm going to Germany?
Ah, Mon told me.
I told Mon.
Everyone's going to find out eventually,
so I just told people for you.
Good thing I convinced you all to stay.
Now we get to have
this farewell trip together.
Let's have the most fun on this trip. Yeah?
Right.
So, where do you guys want to go?
Koh Larn, sir.
Everyone, share your ideas
on where you'd like to visit.
Let's brainstorm.
So where is it?
Koh Larn.
Right.
So, where does everyone want to go?
Koh Larn.
Aquarium?
Aquarium!
Mr. Nut?
Yes?
I think we should visit the aquarium.
Seems like that's what everyone wants.
Aquarium, yeah?
Aquarium!
Guys, don't touch everything you see.
There are signs that say
what you can and can't touch.
Show some maturity.
Whoa!
Mr. Nut.
That thing's huge. Let's go check it out!
♪ Feels like everything's
turned pink-it's true ♪
♪ Like my heart is
yelling out, "I love you" ♪
♪ Like I fell into a flower
field and there's you ♪
♪ Never felt like this with anyone before ♪
♪ One look from you
and I'm weak to the core ♪
♪ No fronts, no form,
wanna give you my all ♪
♪ Your eyes are sparkling so bright ♪
♪ Maybe…can I call you mine? ♪
♪ 'Cause every star is shining
on you—I'm losing my mind ♪
♪ Shot, shot, shot ♪
♪ Hob, hob, hob ♪
♪ Stops, stops, stops ♪
Look!
Hey.
It looks just like you.
♪ I wonder if you feel the same as me ♪
This one.
♪ Or am I the only one
deep in this fantasy? ♪
♪ I beg you, please tell me ♪
♪ That this isn't a
one-sided dream, not reality ♪
Per, Tar, can you take some photos for us?
That angle's too low.
Three, two, one.
Hey!
I asked you to take our photo, not yours!
♪ No clue what it is
I'm feeling right now ♪
♪ Just one look and I am shot, shot, shot ♪
♪ My heart's about to blow up—pop! ♪
♪ Hob, hob, hob ♪
♪ Trying to keep cool, but I'm gonna drop ♪
♪ 'Cause your cuteness is a lot ♪
♪ I don't think anyone else could top ♪
♪ The whole world stops, stops, stops ♪
♪ Like someone pauses the ticking clock ♪
♪ Hob, hob, hob ♪
♪ Can't believe this isn't a dream ♪
♪ You're standing right here beside me ♪
♪ I can barely hold it in ♪
♪ Can barely hold it in ♪
TRIP MODE: ON
Guys, do you wanna take a group shot?
Sure.
Come on.
Gather up.
Say it together.
Aquarium!
It's nice seeing the students
spending time together like this.
I thought you said you hated
going on school trips with students.
Aquarium!
Yeah!
MRS. PAAN
Hello.
Mr. Nut, you need to bring
the students back immediately.
What's the matter, ma'am?
You said it was a Literature Club outing.
So why are Kim and his friends there too?
But Kim is also a member of the club.
Mon didn't say Kim would be there too.
I think there's just been
a misunderstanding
I said, bring the students back right away.
I promised them
I'd look after them until the trip ends.
I'll inform you as soon as
we return to school, ma'am.
Goodbye.
Mr. Nut—!
MRS. PAAN
Hello.
Mr. Tan,
may I speak with Mr. Nut, please?
Uh…
If Mr. Nut doesn't take this call,
your evaluation this semester
will be in serious trouble, Mr. Tan.
Sorry, Mr. Nut.
Mrs. Paan wants to speak with you.
Sorry, guys.
We came all this way,
but we only got a little time to travel
before we have to head back.
It's okay, Mon.
Going back early isn't so bad.
Come on.
Don't worry, Mon.
I will help talk to Mrs. Paan.
I was kind of expecting this.
It's just how my mom is.
Are you coming back with us?
We've got some spots left in the van.
Okay, sir.
Let's go.
Wait a minute!
Where are Per and Tar?
Weren't they with you, Shane?
No, they weren't.
I haven't seen them for a while.
I thought they were with you.
They weren't!
If we want to go, we go.
Let's go to Koh Larn, baby!
- Yes, sir.
Let's go!
Go!
They're not picking up, sir.
What do we do, Mr. Nut?
What if something happened to them?
What am I supposed to do?
Stay calm, Mr. Tan.
MRS. PAAN THE POWER-MAD
Yes, Mrs. Paan?
If Mon isn't back within the hour,
I'll seize the parcel storage room.
You can share your office with the janitor.
Shit.
Mr. Nut,
take the students back to school right now.
What about Per and Tar?
I'll deal with them.
Just get Mon back.
Everyone, into the van!
Get in.
Don't worry.
You're finally back.
We need to talk.
Please don't scold Mon, Mrs. Paan.
It's not his fault.
I was the one who asked him to come see me.
This doesn't concern you, Kim.
You may leave now. It's late.
Go home.
All right, then.
Goodbye, ma'am.
Why did you lie to me?
Mon, don't you walk away from me.
We need to talk this through.
Mon!
We need to talk.
Mon, come out and talk to me.
Mon, open the door.
Don't pull this on me.
Mon, open the door now.
Mon.
Mon!
Uh
I was just about to leave, ma'am.
It's true.
Goodbye, ma'am.
Please don't be upset with Mon, Mrs. Paan.
He saw me enjoying the trip
and wanted to join too.
And I was the one who asked him to go,
so…
This isn't your fault, Kim.
You should go home.
Good night, ma'am.
Finally ready to talk?
I'm sorry
for lying to you.
Why did you choose to lie?
Because I thought if you knew,
you wouldn't let me go see Kim.
That's just what you assumed.
Just admit it, Mom.
If you knew I was going to see Kim,
you wouldn't be pleased.
You'd interrogate me
or find a way to stop me from going.
You don't want me to be with him, do you?
It's not that.
I just don't want you
to rush into anything.
You just knew Kim.
If one day he hurts you or lets you down,
have you even thought
about how you'll deal with that?
In the end, I have to
take responsibility for my choices,
whether they turn out good or bad.
That's easier said than done.
Reality hits harder than that.
I know you're worried,
but I'm strong enough to handle it.
I learned that from you.
You're strong
and I'm strong too.
Just don't lie to me again.
Whatever it is, say it.
Talk to me.
I will.
Next time I want to go
on a trip with my boyfriend,
I'll tell you.
This is all your fault, Per.
You got carried away.
Look. It's already dark now.
And my phone's dead.
How are we supposed to
contact Kim and Shane?
So, it's my fault again?
Weren't you the one who wanted to go?
I just came along to keep you company.
Keep me company, huh?
You had way more fun than I did.
How many times
did you ride that banana boat?
Hi.
You two jackasses.
You're finally back, huh?
You're so getting it!
I told you so many times
I wanted to go to Koh Larn.
You just never listened.
Are you blaming this on me?
Don't we have a school rule
about not hitting students?
We're not at school now,
so rules don't apply.
Yes, Mr. Nut.
I found Tar and Per.
Turns out Shane was right.
They went to Koh Larn.
We're heading back to Bangkok now,
but it's going to take a while.
Got it.
Travel safe.
I'll be waiting for you in the storage room.
It's okay.
You can go home first, Mr. Nut.
No.
We're a team.
We went together, so we go home together.
I mean,
we leave for home at the same time.
Okay then.
See you soon.
Sure.
I TOLD MOM I WAS SORRY.
WILL YOU TALK TO ME NOW?
GOOD WORK!
Are you absolutely sure, sweetheart?
Why do you suddenly want to study abroad?
Don't tell me you watched
some movie and got inspired.
I'm sure.
I wouldn't be standing here
talking to you if I weren't.
You told me to think about my future,
so here I am, thinking.
Do you even speak German?
The study part is hard enough as it is,
and you don't even know
the basics of the language.
Why don't you give it some more thought?
You can take a gap year
and spend time thinking.
We're not pressuring you.
But I don't have time.
Shane is leaving for Germany soon.
So that's what this is about.
You just want to follow Shane?
Then I'd say we're right not to let you go.
You just want to follow your friend there.
Shane isn't just a friend.
He is more than that.
Shane, dear.
Have you made up your mind
about moving to Germany with me?
As for Cheese,
your dad will never let her live with me.
But that's all right.
Having just you come with me
is more than enough.
Jin and Name are already grown.
Cheese can stay with her father.
I love you the most anyway.
You love me too, don't you?
Is it because we don't see each other often
that you love me less?
I love you just the same.
Not less.
But if you could stop fighting with Dad,
I'd be really grateful.
Your dad and I are just too different.
That's why we fight, as you've seen.
But you're like me.
You know how to take care of yourself,
and you're always
ambitious about your future.
Studying abroad has
always been your dream, hasn't it?
CAN YOU COME TALK TO ME?
I'll BE QUICK.
But if you stay here,
you'll wear yourself out.
You have to take care of yourself,
your older siblings, and your little sister.
If you come with me, I'll take care of you.
And you can finally
focus on chasing your dream.
KIT
Come with me, Shane.
Let's chase your dream together.
Can you not go, Shane?
We just started this.
I don't want it to end like this.
I like you, Shane.
And I want to be… your boyfriend.
I'm not going, Mom.
- Shane, but I—
- I already have responsibilities.
I have a cat to look after.
Aw, Kaiju.
We were too loud, huh?
What happened?
Why did Dad look so mad?
Of course, he's mad.
I told him to leave.
I said if he sold this condo,
I'd make all of us change our last name.
So, bottom line,
the four of us are staying put.
Okay?
I've got a meeting soon,
so no loud noises,
or I'm giving everyone noogies.
Name, don't steal my snack.
Give it back.
Can't I just have a little taste?
I told you, no loud noises!
- Please.
- No.
No!
Will you stop stealing her snacks?
I don't have anything.
Then buy your own.
Can I just have some for now?
(Hello, Shane.)
Sorry, I was talking to my mom.
Can we meet?
- I have something to tell you.
You go first.
I've decided not to move to Germany.
Hey!
Seriously?
Yeah.
I talked to my mom.
Told her I'm staying here.
I'm not going anywhere.
Good.
That's great.
So, what did you want to tell me?
You seemed really excited just now.
Ah…
Nothing.
I wanted to say that,
on second thought,
I don't want to go to Germany anymore.
You changed your mind pretty fast.
I thought you'd already
started planning for schools there.
Plans change with my heart.
Wherever my heart is, that's where I'll be.
I didn't just come to talk
about my family plans.
I also came to give you
the answer you've been asking for.
Well…
I
I'm actually okay with it.
Okay?
With what?
What thing?
That thing.
That thing!
What thing?
Okay!
I'll be your boyfriend.
From now on, we're boyfriends.
Is that clear enough?
Crystal clear, boyfriend.
You already knew that.
Why'd you keep pushing?
Because I wanted to
hear it straight from you.
Kit.
Yes, Dad?
I think I judged you too quickly.
I felt like.
I wasn't being a good dad.
So, if you really want to study in Germany,
I'll support...
Ah!
I've changed my mind.
I'm not going anymore.
What?
Come again?
I'm not going anymore, Dad.
Thank you.
Exams are over!
(Time flies, the first
semester's almost up.)
(Next up, Kit and I are going
on a double date with Kim and Mon.)
This party is straight
out of a Hollywood movie!
(Let's see which couple
turns out to be sweeter.)
See? Nobody's paying attention to us.
(Or maybe… a surprise is headed your way.)