=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 19=
Next one.
Yes.
This outfit is splendid
and quite light.
It won't hinder movement at all.
It is good,
but the design is too ornate.
How wise of you.
I think the same way.
Allow me to trim it.
How is it now?
This one will do.
Yes.
Simu,
you want a new outfit?
Sir, do you know
the Void Tournament is near?
I came
to take Her Grace's measure.
What is that?
Every hundred years,
Her Grace holds
a Void Tournament.
On that day,
any spirit can challenge her.
If they win,
Her Grace yields
the throne to them.
And if they lose?
If they lose,
they wait for the next century
and try again.
I see.
No wonder
the city feels different.
Simu,
why hold this tournament?
The desires of spirits
can never be erased.
Rather than curb them,
better let them stir up some trouble.
I can't let them
keep trying to kill me.
But your power
has weakened.
How will you face them?
You can sense
my power change?
I can sense
that you've grown
a little weaker.
It is nothing.
The Fusang Tree is restored.
Next, I need only breath regulation.
I can handle it.
If they find out about that
during the contest,
what will your ambitious courtiers
do then?
Even together, they're no match for me.
But if I don't show up,
they'll immediately figure out
what's going on.
By then,
over half of the spirits
will be after my life.
So,
you have to show up?
That's right.
What would make you not go?
Nothing could stop me.
I'm your spell bearer.
And I can't stop you?
What does that have to do with that?
As for you,
these past few days,
you've been running out every day.
Is the Void that enticing to you?
You're not used
to my absence, right?
Watch your tongue.
I should have let you
keep suffering from cold poison.
Please calm your anger.
I was only joking just now.
I've been going out
for this very thing.
I've troubled you for days,
so I wanted to get you something.
I made this for you.
♪Spring comes; ice and snow thaw♪
♪All things wake, with the east wind♪
I don't want
such a pointless thing.
♪In the season at its fullest♪
I worked very hard on it.
Please accept it, Your Grace.
♪The old night♪
♪Borrow mortal warmth to ease the cold♪
♪Warm winds bring fragrant blooms♪
♪Let me love with all my heart
in youthful grace♪
♪With light, carefree words♪
♪Still shining bright♪
You're recovering quite well.
Soon,
your cold poison will heal.
♪A brief life dares seek eternity♪
But I can sense
you've spent much spirit power again.
♪Borrow one lovely dream♪
Do not probe into me.
I can't do that.
My life depends on you.
If anything happens at the tournament,
I'll lose my shelter,
and the Right Hand will end me first.
At least you know your place.
(Zhaomu Pavilion)
♪I see a ray♪
♪To what home shall I return♪
How boring.
(Gao Xuande, Ji Youming, Xiao Yuan)
(Jun Lin, Yin Lang, Gu Cangwu)
(Yin Lang)
(Jiling Temple)
- Your Ladyship.
- Move.
Move.
Let me go.
Let me go!
Move.
Let me go.
I want...
I want to gamble.
Move.
Let me go.
Stop right there.
Don't run.
What is it?
Where did Father go?
I looked everywhere for him.
Your father is the Sovereign.
He has duties to bear.
Once he is done,
he'll come to see you.
Why must Father be the Sovereign?
Every time he returns to the Void,
he never has time to play with me.
Your father never wished for this role.
He wants to stay with us.
But
these spirits are driven by desire.
If we let those
with selfish desires
rule the Spirit World,
it would surely throw
the Mortal and Spirit Worlds
into ruin and suffering.
Being the Sovereign is no fun.
I don't want to be the Sovereign.
When you become the Sovereign one day,
you will understand.
(I still don't like)
(to be the Sovereign.)
Come on, fight.
Fight.
Fight!
Hurry up.
Simu lifted
the curfew on the day
of the Void Tournament
and set the matches
under the full moon,
so these spirits
would unleash their full strength.
Tonight, it's only just begun.
No more. I quit.
Before these spirits came,
they all signed death waivers.
They'll fight
to the death.
Where is Simu?
Aren't these spirits here
to challenge her?
There are so many spirits
vying for her seat.
If Simu faces them one by one,
she'll be worn out.
The preliminaries
started this morning.
The martial contestants
fight through a melee
and face off in pairs.
Only the final ten pairs
will earn the right
to face Simu directly.
Everyone,
the preliminaries end now.
What is that smell?
The time is about right.
Simu should be here.
Look.
Quick.
It's Her Grace.
Her Grace is here.
Her Grace.
Let's not waste time.
Come at me together.
Your Grace,
impressive!
Whoever defeats me today
will claim the seat
of the Sovereign.
I'm Wu Kui.
Greetings, Your Grace.
Wu Kui. He's making his move.
Right now, only he
can match Her Grace.
Wu Kui.
Wu Kui is formidable.
- Exactly.
- Indeed.
Watch closely.
That is Wu Kui.
It's been 100 years.
You've grown a little stronger.
Thanks, Your Grace.
Then,
forgive me.
This spirit is strong,
different from the rivals before.
Of course.
He was once the Lord
of Zhuangling Temple.
The spirits of Zhuangling Temple
all crave power, especially Wu Kui.
After Simu became the Sovereign,
he came to challenge her
countless times.
After each defeat,
he resigned and went
to the North Sea to train.
He's not challenging Simu
for the position of the Sovereign,
but to become the strongest.
In these 300 years,
you are the first
to make it this far.
You flatter me.
You can't beat me.
Come back in the next century.
Your Grace,
will I be able to win
in the next century?
Why must you act on impulse?
Your Grace,
after my last defeat, I resolved
that this time,
I'd either prevail
or perish.
Spirits live long.
Why would you do this?
I see things differently, Your Grace.
If I don't give it my all,
it is no different from death.
Kui.
Kui!
If that is your choice,
I will grant your wish.
Simu's Kunwu Blade.
Your Grace, well done!
Your Grace!
You're incredible!
Indeed.
- Your Grace!
I knew Simu was good,
but not this good.
Within ten generations,
she is the strongest Sovereign.
Her power is terrifying.
You never saw it then.
When the former Sovereign fell,
the Spirits Lantern had no master,
and the Void fell into chaos.
In the end,
Simu slew over half the rebels
in the Void.
Of the 24 Temples,
over 30% of the Lords
were annihilated by Simu.
From that day on,
no spirits in the Void
dared tell Simu no.
Of course,
it includes that one.
Greetings, Your Grace.
Only you are left now.
The Chiling Secret Technique
hasn't appeared
for over 1,000 years.
The stronger the spirit power,
the harder this move hits back.
The cruel part of this technique
is that it drains spirit power
and turns it on its owner.
How generous of you.
We will gladly accept it.
Do you think I haven't seen
this power-stealing trick?
You can't withstand
such overwhelming power.
You're seeking death.
Two annoying flies.
That scent is gone.
It was coming from them.
♪Yet I can't♪
Your Grace, you possess
supreme authority
and boundless might.
Your Grace, you possess
supreme authority
and boundless might.
Your Grace, you possess
supreme authority
and boundless might.
Your Grace, you possess
supreme authority
and boundless might.
Your Grace!
(That scent again.)
Yes.
Truly astounding.
This tournament now comes to an end.
The Crown of the Victor
still rests in the hands
of the current Sovereign.
All unconvinced heroes
may gather
in the arena
and fight for the throne
in another century.
Enough. I know.
Over here.
Come, a reward.
Does this feel good?
It has been a while.
Your touch has improved.
(The scent is lost in cosmetics.)
What is your name?
Yes, yes.
Is my touch okay?
Each time you come here,
you always catch me off guard.
Let us have a look.
You do the same to me
by appearing
right behind me.
Yan Zhang.
We are closed today.
Please pardon
the discourtesy.
Very well.
All right, all right.
Lord Yan,
an honored guest came.
Why weren't you with him?
If the ladies here get the wrong idea,
can you bear that blame?
I failed to notice in time
that Mr. Duan was here.
A grave mishap was nearly caused.
Qifeng House serves ladies only.
If you wish to stay and look around,
please allow me to accompany you.
This time,
I did not come for pleasure.
Then what did you come for?
Young man,
Qifeng House
is not a place for you.
But you invited me.
Me?
During the archery match, you said
that at Xuling Temple,
I could look around as I pleased.
So, it seems I was in the wrong
for spoiling your mood.
I'm glad you remember.
I almost thought
I couldn't tour
Xuling Temple today.
After all, the tournament just ended.
You must have
much to handle in the aftermath.
Her Grace was ambushed
in the Void Valley.
There is no need to worry.
The Right Hand was with her.
Nothing would happen.
They have already returned.
Simu is already
resting in her bedchamber.
Simu.
Coming in without permission,
you've grown far too bold.
For the coming days,
I need quiet seclusion.
Go stay in the side chamber.
Sir!
Sir,
I've been looking…
for you.
Her Grace…
Her Grace asked me
to settle you in the side chamber.
Don't be too downhearted.
You're so handsome.
Her Grace still likes you.
She just finished the tournament.
So much awaits.
In a few days…
In a few days,
she will surely summon you again.
I am telling you.
The side chamber is not bad.
It is filled with jeweled adornments.
You may go now.
Yes.
(Memorial)
Simu,
the spirits that attacked you today
are all listed here.
You're in charge of the placement
and ascension
of the Void's spirits.
Why would spirits
marked as ascended on the register
suddenly appear and ambush me
in the Void Valley?
Had you not arrived in time
and fought with your life,
I would not have
broken free so quickly.
No need for formality
between us.
I will look into this.
If it were just the ascension
that had gone awry,
we'd simply deal with them by the law.
But from what I saw today,
those spirits were controlled.
To control spirits,
one must hold a fierce obsession
and immense power.
Someone with such an obsession
and spirit power may only be the one
in Nine-Square Maze Prison.
It's been centuries.
He was annihilated long ago.
Other than him,
I can think of no one else.
Keep this matter quiet.
Conduct the inquiry in secret.
Yes.
Yan,
you've spent much spirit power today.
Go back and get some proper rest.
You should rest well too.
I'll come see you tomorrow.
Stop standing here in my way.
Simu is in no mood
to toy with you.
Have some sense.
Go back where you came from.
Where I stay or go
is not your concern.
You're only her passing amusement.
She already drove you out,
yet you still cling to her.
How shameless.
You've clung to her for centuries.
You are
far more shameless than I am.
Besides, Simu hasn't told me to leave.
Who do you think you are?
Who am I?
I'm the Right Hand of the Void.
I helped her put down the rebellion,
enforced the laws,
and governed the Void.
I can stay by her side
forever.
You're just
a self-righteous mortal,
a shameless outsider,
a useless man
who only brings Simu trouble.
What can you give her?
A self-righteous mortal,
a shameless outsider,
a useless man
who only brings Simu trouble.
What can you give her?
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪