=Eight Hundred=
Boss, is there any new stock?
It's here.
I've saved some for you.
Let me know when the new stock arrives.
Of course.
We're old friends, after all.
I'm heading out.
Hey buddy, want some discs?
Western, Japanese, Korean,
I have them all.
I've got a business here
that's much more
profitable than selling discs.
Are you interested?
What's that?
Selling this.
(Peidun Cough Syrup)
It keeps the miners alert.
It makes way more than selling discs.
Can you really make money with this?
You'll know once you try it.
=Episode 3=
(The Honey Trap)
Everyone, get inside.
Police inspection!
Turn on the lights, turn off the music.
Everyone, stop.
Over here.
Men in one line, women in the other.
Stand straight.
Li, come here.
Take him.
Get him sorted.
Line up.
Quickly!
Men in one line, women in the other.
Spot check.
Take a paper cup.
We're doing urine tests in a moment.
Step aside.
Can you just give me two bottles?
Just two bottles.
I really can't take it anymore.
You're addicted.
I just couldn't resist
having one bottle.
Men in one line, women in the other.
Move it.
- Get over here.
- It's all the same.
- Police spot check.
- Line up.
- Form two lines.
Go to the restroom.
Men in one line, women in the other.
Take a paper cup.
We're doing urine tests in a moment.
Hurry up.
Dad,
- what's going on?
- Move it.
It's a spot check.
Why didn't you give us a heads-up?
A heads-up?
That would defeat the whole purpose, no?
Stop arguing.
I can't handle this all by myself.
I'll go help out.
Go ahead.
Master, I'm going over.
Alright.
Come on, line up here. Over this way.
He hasn't paid yet.
I've got it.
Here's your money.
Next.
(Men's Restroom)
Whose were those size 36 shoes just now?
Mine.
Head upstairs. Come on.
- Why did she faint?
- Songge.
Someone fainted!
What happened to her?
She fainted.
Songge.
What's wrong?
Songge,
what's wrong with you?
Mr. Chen, I think my blood sugar is a bit low.
From exhaustion?
Lin,
come here.
Take her to rest.
She can do the test after resting.
Easy now.
Take it slow.
Dad,
why don't I go first?
That way, I can look after Songge.
Fine.
Limin.
Test Hui first.
- Alright.
- Go on then.
- Come on.
- Move forward.
You, come out first.
(Men's Restroom)
Officer Lin, I have low blood sugar,
and I haven't had dinner yet.
Could you help me heat up my food?
Sure.
Just lie back down.
Thank you.
Hui.
Hui!
You brat, what are you doing?
I couldn't pee earlier,
but now I have.
Fine, hurry up.
Come on, next.
Chen Hui.
All set.
Over there.
What's wrong with you?
Urine test. Move it.
Hurry up, now.
How are you feeling?
Much better.
Songge, go get in line first.
Go.
Name?
Wang Dali.
Do you have ID?
Let me see it.
I was just passing by
when you guys brought me in.
I don't have it.
Do you remember your ID number?
It's so long,
who could remember that?
I never need it anyway.
Wang Dali.
No. 33.
Noted.
Go wait over there.
There are only a few left.
I'll notify you all
once the testing is done.
When your name is called,
you're coming back
to the station with us.
Zhang Mingyuan.
Li Xiaojun.
Zhang Hai.
Zhao Qiang.
Li Zhijun.
Present.
Hurry up.
Take him away.
Listen up.
This
spot check
is over.
Thank you
for your cooperation.
The roller skating rink
can resume business.
Strange.
Where did my lens case go?
Why did he faint?
- Songge, are you okay?
- Someone fainted!
- This woman passed out.
- Songge.
Songge.
(Water Tank)
Page me,
23768.
Leave a message,
water tank.
(Water Tank)
Come here, miss.
Come over for a moment.
Your friend's name is Wang Sui?
Yes.
It's just as you said.
She is indeed a college student,
and she has no prior criminal record.
Tell her,
once the fine is paid tomorrow,
she can go home.
How much is the fine?
Three thousand.
Three thousand...
Have a good talk with her.
Tell her to focus on her studies
and stay away from places like that.
Understand?
Yes, thank you.
What are you looking for?
My contact lens case is missing.
It's a tiny little case
with my contacts inside.
Have you seen it?
Contact lenses?
I think I just saw it.
Let me check for you.
Thanks.
Is it this one?
Yeah.
Where did you find it?
I just finished cleaning the restroom.
I reckon someone probably threw it
in there by mistake.
How could it be there?
(Vienna Cabaret)
Yu.
Mr. Yang.
Are you looking for me?
Mr. Yang, here's the thing.
I've run into some trouble lately,
and I wanted to ask
to borrow some money.
I thought it was something serious.
How much?
Three thousand yuan will do.
Well,
how about after work,
we go book a room
and have a good chat?
Why book a room?
We're both adults.
What else would we do in a room?
Forget it. I'm not borrowing.
- Get lost!
- Hey, wait.
Get lost!
Yu, if you don't want to, fine.
I'll still lend it to you.
Yu.
Get lost, you creep!
What are you looking at?
Hurry up.
- Take it over there.
- Move faster.
(Victim, murder weapon, glass shards)
Director Tong.
Chief Liu.
Well?
Did you find anything
in this night raid?
This night raid covered
eight entertainment venues
in Fengyang.
We found six people
positive for ketamine
and twelve positive for Kejianin.
It's just a pity
that they were all buyers.
We didn't catch a single seller.
This group is organized
extremely tightly.
This is quite strange.
The whole thing is strange.
The trail goes cold here again.
I always feel like these people
are always one step ahead of us.
Don't be discouraged.
It's because our work
isn't thorough enough.
Understood?
(Yingxiong Roller Skating Rink)
Today was really dangerous.
Lu Yuan is the only one right now
who has seen our faces.
With him roaming outside,
he's a ticking time bomb for us.
I've been thinking.
Actually, he can't produce
any evidence against us.
Even if he calls the police
or gets caught,
the police won't just believe
everything he says, right?
Besides, didn't you tell me once
that a single witness isn't proof?
That's true.
But if he identifies us,
the police will get involved.
No matter how well we hide,
the police will keep
an eye on us for a while.
Then we won't be able
to move any stock for a long time.
Your illness can't wait any longer.
So, what do you want to do?
Take a gamble.
Have Lu Yuan come over tomorrow.
Director Chen,
you have a call.
Okay.
Hello?
What?
Chief Liu.
Chief, stop knocking.
I've been knocking for 20 minutes.
It's no use.
Maybe she went out?
No, she goes downstairs
to eat every day.
I haven't seen her go down today.
Chief Liu.
Chief Liu!
Look, I have the key.
Why don't you go in and check?
You have a keycard?
Why didn't you say so sooner?
Well, she's a police officer,
and a lady on top of that.
- How would I dare...
- Hurry up and open it.
Alright, I'm opening it.
Are you kidding me?
Chief Liu.
Don't you know how
to knock before entering?
Chief Liu.
Are
you okay?
I'm fine.
What's the big hurry?
Right.
It's my fault.
Carry on then.
Chief Liu,
so
you found something new?
I don't think this is working.
Ever since we discovered
someone was selling
Peidun Cough Syrup in Fengyang,
Lu Yuan took off immediately.
They're spooked now.
They've been in hiding for a while.
So, what do you think
we should do?
Back to the old approach.
Find a way to identify the victim,
and then screen their social circle.
The body was burnt to nothing.
How do we investigate?
Tang sent me
an autopsy report last night.
It mentioned
the victim's right heel bone
was more worn down than the left.
(Bone wear on the right heel)
The high-heeled shoe heel
found at the scene back then
(Sole)
also proved this.
This lump of material
is the plastic sole from the shoe.
This is a heel.
That's the issue.
Why did she
only attach a sole to one shoe?
It can only mean
she consistently put
more weight on
her right foot than her left.
That's why the right heel
was worn down so badly.
A limp.
Someone with a limp
wouldn't wear high heels.
Normal daily life
wouldn't cause wear like this.
It must have been caused
by her work environment.
Director Chen,
with your knowledge of Fengyang,
any ideas where to look?
(Right-foot high heel from the scene)
In Fengyang,
there actually is such a place.
The people working there
only wear out their right heels.
(Huabo Art Products Processing Factory)
A processing factory?
Three years ago, this man
opened a factory here.
He said
he was using jet
to make jewelry.
Making jewelry?
Jet.
In the past,
when it was dug out of the mine,
it was all treated as waste
and thrown away.
I didn't understand it then.
I thought these guys
were just using it as a cover
to do something illegal.
So I watched them for a while.
I eventually noticed
the workers there
had very heavy wear
on their right heels.
If it weren't for this case,
I would've forgotten all about it.
Let's go.
Who is it?
Police.
Chi Huabo, right?
We're from the police station.
I know.
You're Director Chen.
You don't remember me?
My dad was in the ventilation zone
of Mine No. 3.
Right.
Back then,
you got into
the city's normal college, didn't you?
That was over ten years ago.
Director Chen,
is there something you need?
We'd like to
ask you a few questions.
Can we come in?
Sure.
This business pays pretty well,
doesn't it?
Not bad.
Better than digging coal in the mines.
This is carborundum, right?
Yes.
We use it to polish the jet.
Why are there no workers here today?
They're on break.
I'm planning to close up for a while.
Why?
I need to go do some market research,
see if there are
any new styles out there.
When are you leaving?
Tonight's train.
I'm heading to the city
with some samples.
How many workers
do you usually have here?
(Piecework: Tan Wen, Anita Mui, Jiang Xue)
Seven or eight, I'd say.
Men or women?
All women.
This kind of work is too tedious for men.
Director Chen.
What is this?
Some people like the vintage style.
They like the texture.
We use this to distress the items.
Why is the water this color?
What's in here?
It contains lime,
caustic soda,
and potassium permanganate.
Sir and madam,
is there anything else?
I'm in a hurry to catch a train.
I won't make it if I don't leave now.
Chi Huabo,
I'm afraid that today,
you really can't leave.
(Confess for leniency,
resist for severity)
Did you register the IDs
of these female workers you hired?
No.
You hire people
without even checking IDs?
This work is dirty and exhausting.
No locals are willing to do it.
They're mostly the families of those
at the illegal coal pits.
Director Chen, you know those people.
Many of them don't have IDs.
You should at least know their names.
There are names
on the piecework sheet in my office.
But whether they're real or fake,
it's hard to say.
Do you have their contact info?
No.
Then, when you
come back from out of town,
how do you tell them to start work?
I pay by the piece,
settled daily.
When it's time to work,
I just hang
a hiring sign on the front gate.
Those who want to work
will show up on their own.
Alright.
It seems you don't know anything at all.
It's not that,
I really don't know, Director Chen.
Not knowing stuff
is not against the law, right?
You're here.
Come.
Hui,
playing ball?
Where's the stuff?
You're a man of great wealth, Boss.
This is just
a drop in the bucket for you...
You want it?
Let's get things straight first.
Go ahead.
You broke the rules.
The rules were set
before the deal.
We won't be supplying you anymore.
Don't do that.
You're cutting off my lifeline, Hui.
You brought it on yourself.
Just give me one bottle first, okay?
I'm begging you.
Just give me one bottle.
I haven't touched that stuff in so long.
I want it... I...
Just one bottle, Hui.
I'll do anything you want, please.
Your words.
The heat is on out there now.
The goods can't be moved for sure.
But you have a choice.
What choice?
Leave Fengyang.
There are 50,000
and ten bottles of drugs in this bag.
We'll give it all to you.
But you must guarantee
that from now on,
you'll act like you never met us.
Fine.
I...
I'll leave.
I'll never come back.
How can we trust you?
Hui,
I, Lu Yuan, am a man of my word.
I won't come back.
If I do, I'm a dog.
Listen,
this is the only time
and the last time.
If you dare come back,
I will never let you off.
Boss.
I'm never coming back.
Don't worry.
Regarding yesterday's drug test,
someone faked it.
Master.
Chief Liu.
Chi Huabo's drug test results are out.
It's negative.
And at that coal gangue dump,
they didn't find
any Peidun Cough Syrup.
Did you check
the piecework sheets?
Yes. No one was at the station
applying for a residence permit.
How many of them are there?
There are only
piecework sheets from last month.
Thirteen people in total.
The longest stayed for a month,
while the shortest stayed
for only a day or two.
Fengyang isn't that big.
If we can find two or three,
we should be able
to find out about the others.
That's going to be hard.
Take a look.
This list even has Anita Mui
and Yang Yuying on it.
Why would these people
use aliases just for a manual job?
The people coming to work
from the illegal coal pits
all have very complicated backgrounds.
Some are running from marriages,
some are dodging debts,
and some have
criminal records or priors.
Every year, we catch
quite a few of them here.
Potassium permanganate,
carborundum abrasives,
and wear on the right heel.
All three conditions match.
Chi Huabo still wants to leave town.
He must have a problem.
But the problem now is
we have too little information.
It's hard to get him to talk.
In Fengyang,
I don't believe
he can hide anything from me.
Yesterday, when I put
my contact lens case on the front desk,
you were right there.
You must have taken it.
Are you okay?
There were so many people there.
You're saying
I was the only one near you?
Don't you just want my dad's help?
That's no way to ask for a favor.
I've already solved the problem.
I don't need your help.
And you don't need
to put on an act for me.
I see people like you all the time.
If you want me to pretend
I don't know anything, that's fine.
Lend me 3,000 yuan.
I'll pay you back in two months.
Are we even that close?
Why should I lend you money?
So you don't want
to settle this quietly?
Then I'll go
to the police station right now
and tell them everything.
Go ahead.
Let the police come and check again.
I gave you a chance.
Just you wait.
Xin Yu.
You're Han Ning's friend, right?
Why are you borrowing money?
Did something happen?
My friend tested positive.
The police caught her.
She needs to pay
the fine to be released.
I've asked everyone,
but I can't find the money.
I see.
Xin Yu,
we really didn't know
about what you just said.
But if you go to the station
and they come to investigate,
tell me,
how are we supposed to do business?
Customers have been sparse lately.
We're all neighbors here.
We should look out
for each other, right?
Yes.
I'm not that kind of person.
I just have no other choice.
Alright.
As long as we're clear.
We can lend you this money.
But
I have one condition.
What condition?
Three thousand yuan
isn't a small amount.
We'll give you the money,
but you have to sing here
for free for two weeks.
This money will count
as your performance fee.
Business lately
hasn't been as good as before.
These past couple of days,
Chen Hui and I have been discussing
what we should do.
If you come sing for us,
on one hand,
it'll solve your financial problems,
and on the other hand,
it'll help us attract more customers.
It's a win-win.
What do you think?
I need to get the money today.
No problem.
Right, Chen Hui?
It's up to you.
Then, let me get ready.
I'll give you the money tonight.
This contact lens case
is already worn out.
Later, Chen Hui and I
will buy a new one for you.
No, that's okay.
I can buy one myself.
I'm sorry.
I was just in a rush.
I didn't come here to cause trouble.
It's fine.
I understand.
If it were my friend,
I'd also be trying
everywhere to borrow money.
Okay.
See you tonight.
(Fengyang Coal Mine Guesthouse)
Let me ask you something.
Do you know Chi Huabo?
Yes, I do.
The guy who does those jet carvings.
Has he come here
with any women?
Be honest.
Well, we have a woman here...
Just speak.
He has.
But he hasn't successfully landed many.
You know better than he does?
If he had landed them,
he'd have taken them
upstairs for a room.
Lately, when he comes here,
what kind of woman has he brought?
The recent one was the most clingy.
Southern accent.
Slender.
Fair-skinned.
Are there
any more distinct features?
I didn't really notice that.
What's wrong?
Is it hard to say?
No, let me think.
Right.
She liked wearing high heels.
But with those heels, you know,
only one of them was soled.
Are you sure?
Only one of her shoes was soled?
Positive.
When she walked down the hall at night,
you could hear the rhythm.
What is her name?
I heard him call her Susu.
Susu?
I have a photo.
You took these secretly, didn't you?
How is it a secret?
Why did you take
so many of these?
These people all get rooms by the hour.
In case something happens,
maybe I can
be of help to you guys.
Yang Baichun,
I've found that you are
not just annoying,
but also very disgusting.
Find it.
Whether it's disgusting or not,
just say if it helped you or not.
This is the one.
Director Chen,
(Liusan Mutton Restaurant)
how did you know Chi Huabo
would take women to the guesthouse?
In Fengyang,
it's only an 800-meter radius area.
Look at Chi Huabo,
he smokes a pipe
and wears a tie.
Why?
Because he likes it.
Like it, my foot!
He likes...
I'm sorry.
My language is a bit crude.
It's not that he likes it,
so what was the reason?
He's just
pretending
to be important.
I'm telling you, Chief Liu,
when a boss
and a female employee
have something shady going on,
then it's definitely
some kind of affair.
For guys like that,
besides the wining and dining,
they have to go shopping
and book a room.
But in a place like Fengyang,
most businesses
basically cater to the miners.
This place doesn't appeal to them.
So there is really only one place
they would like to visit.
The guesthouse?
Exactly. This guesthouse
is where the leaders host guests.
In terms of the general vibe,
it's a high-class place.
Chi Huabo has been
a child of the mine since he was little.
Never mind how much
of the world he's seen,
his petty mindset
will never change,
and it can't be hidden.
I'm full.
Let's go back
and continue the interrogation.
Chief Liu,
I suggest waiting until tomorrow
to question Chi Huabo again.
Why?
Look at him. Since he got here,
he's been acting all tough and arrogant.
Just ignore him.
Lock him up for the night.
The more you ignore him,
the more nervous he'll get.
By tomorrow,
he'll have
scared himself to death.
Recognize her?
She was blackmailing me.
From the beginning.
What's this woman's name?
How do you know her?
Her name is Yu Susu.
She's a worker at my factory.
And then?
And then we slept together.
She was willing.
I never forced her.
How did she blackmail you?
She said she'd sue me for rape.
She said she had evidence
and wanted 200,000 yuan.
I don't have that kind of money.
When did this happen?
October 2.
The specific time?
It was almost noon that day.
She came to see me.
Bo,
I'm leaving Fengyang next week.
I won't be coming back.
Not coming back?
Then what about us?
Didn't I say it that day?
The elders at home are sick,
so I have to go back
and look after them.
But, you know,
I've been a bit short on cash lately.
If you're doing well,
could you lend me a few thousand first?
With our relationship,
why even talk about "lending"?
This is all the cash I have on me now.
Take it all.
What kind of person do you take me for?
I've been with you for half a year.
How many meals did you take me out for?
You only bought me two pairs of shoes.
Even if I were a girl
at a massage parlor,
it wouldn't be that cheap.
Susu,
what are you saying?
Don't we have love between us?
What love?
One price.
Twenty thousand yuan.
Give me the money,
and I won't make things
hard for you anymore.
Otherwise,
believe it or not,
I'll go to the police station right now
and say you raped me.
Did you have any contact after that?
No contact.
Is it that there is no contact,
or that there's
no need to contact anymore?
What do you mean?
She threatened you.
So,
you killed her.
What?
Yu Susu is dead?
Sit down.
It wasn't me.
I didn't kill anyone.
Listen!
Yu Susu is dead.
Regarding the Beimianling murder case,
right now,
you are the prime suspect.
It really wasn't me.
I didn't kill anyone.
How can you prove you didn't do it?
I really didn't kill anyone.
Have you seen this before?
Never.
Then,
you must have seen this.
I haven't seen that either.
No?
Then why did you want to leave Fengyang?
I couldn't explain my way out of this.
Besides, her husband
digs coal at an illegal coal pit.
I was afraid he'd come beat me up.
Why were you so certain
that Yu Susu's husband
would come after you?
They are a bunch of desperate thugs
who'd do anything for money.
She definitely would have
come back to me for money.
The more I thought about it these
last few days, the more scared I got.
I had no other choice, so I thought
I'd go away to hide for a bit.
Where does Yu Susu's husband dig coal?
In Liugou.
The pit entrance is halfway up the hill
at the west end of the village.
I'd dropped her off there a few times.
Three 3s, three 4s.
Do you have them?
No, right?
What are you playing? I'm higher.
Don't move!
- Police!
- Don't move!
- Grab him!
- Get him down from there!
- Don't move!
- Get down!
Come here!
Who is the mine owner?
Speak up!
Are you the mine owner?
Are you?
Then why aren't you saying anything?
What's going on?
This man has gone crazy.
He knocked down
all the support pillars in the shaft.
We are conducting
safety production education.
I think you're the one
who needs education.
Let me ask you,
do you have someone here
named Zhu Qiang?
That's him.
Is he Zhu Qiang?
Look at me.
Is your name Zhu Qiang?
Are you Zhu Qiang?
Do you recognize this woman?
Zhu Qiang's wife,
Yu Susu.
Susu!
- Hold him down!
- Susu!
Susu!
What's his deal?
I don't know.
He's been acting crazy lately.
Like he's possessed.
He ruined his brain by drinking a drug.
Drinking what drug?
His wife got it for him,
something called
cough syrup.
Cough syrup?
Where is Zhu Qiang's dorm?
Over there.
Which bed is Zhu Qiang's?
That one.
Chief Liu,
look.
So many bottles.
Did Zhu Qiang drink all these himself?
I don't know.
Anyway, this bag is his.
Take it.
Get out.
Director Chen, this pair of shoes
also has the right heel soled.
The victim is Yu Susu.
(Sole)
There's no doubt about it now.
Chief Liu,
next,
interrogate Zhu Qiang.
Okay.
(Fengyang Mine Workers' Hospital)
Have you seen this before?
No.
When was the last time
you saw Yu Susu?
I think...
October 2.
She went out early this morning.
Have you contacted her since?
No.
I was working at the coal pit.
It's been so many days.
Why didn't you report it?
Susu can't bathe at the coal pit,
so every few days,
she goes to a hotel in town.
Sometimes she stays
for a day or two before coming back.
This time,
it has been a bit long.
I was thinking about calling the police,
but the mine owner wouldn't let me.
He's afraid the police
will find the illegal coal pit
and shut it down.
Do you know where Yu Susu's
household registration is?
I only know she's from around Yunchuan.
I don't know the specifics.
Do you have her family's number?
No.
She's your wife,
and you never asked her?
Susu said she ran away from a marriage.
Her family sold her
to a bachelor in his fifties.
She didn't dare
let them know where she was,
so she didn't contact them.
Where did these bottles
of cough syrup under your bed
come from?
Susu brought them back.
She said she
bought them at Fengyang Pharmacy.
Does Yu Susu have
any relatives or friends here?
Susu doesn't seem to
know many people around here.
Other than her colleagues
at the factory,
there's the owner of the lottery shop,
Cai.
Susu and I met there
while buying lottery tickets.
Chief Liu,
I think Yu Susu
is a bit suspicious.
Tell me your thoughts.
Look at
those people we caught
drinking cough syrup
in Fengyang last time.
We've only seen it sold loose,
put into tube popsicles.
I just don't understand
where Yu Susu
managed to get
the whole bottles.
So, does it mean Yu Susu
is a seller,
just like Lu Yuan?
She doesn't seem like a seller.
We didn't find any bottling tools.
She must have gotten the cough syrup
directly from the source.
That seems unlikely, right?
Why unlikely?
Although we haven't
caught the dealer yet,
from the information we have
on these lower-level sellers,
they all share a common trait.
They're male,
over forty,
unmarried,
and have no bad habits.
The impression they give
is that they're honest, simple,
and hardworking.
I see what you mean.
This drug trafficker
is very selective
when choosing downline sellers.
Since this group of sellers
is very low-profile,
it's been very hard for us
to discover this.
But this Yu Susu
is not the same
as those people.
Don't you find it very strange?
(China Welfare Lottery)
Good luck to you.
Thanks, boss.
Here.
Your change.
You're Cai, right?
We're from the police station.
We'd like to ask you some questions.
Director Chen,
I recognize you.
What would you like to know?
You know Yu Susu?
I do.
You're quite close?
Not really.
We're both from Yunchuan.
She likes to play Happy Poker.
When she comes by,
we just chat for a bit.
What is "Happy Poker"?
This is it.
(Happy Poker, Face Value 2 Yuan)
Scratch it to win a prize.
When was the last time
you saw Yu Susu?
I think
it was last month.
I was wondering
why she hasn't come by lately.
What happened to her?
Does Yu Susu have
any other acquaintances in Fengyang?
Well,
I don't really know.
(Fengyang Bus Station)
11:45 PM.
Thanks, bro.
Don't mention it.
Take this.
Thanks, Dali.
Dali,
once you leave,
you're really not coming back?
A man of his word
never goes back on it.
I don't want to go on about it with him.
You're a real man.
Well, I'm off.
Safe travels.
Keep in touch.
Hey, mister.
Want to have some fun?
How much?
For the whole night,
one hundred and twenty.
My bus leaves in a bit at 11:30 PM.
Make it cheaper.
Mister, are we really haggling over this?
I'm fast,
really fast.
Make it cheaper.
Fine, I'll take the loss.
I'll let you go
at 11:30 PM.
Eighty.
Deal.
Where to?
I have a place.
Mister,
don't be in such a hurry.
Let me give you a massage first.
Mister, don't be in such a hurry.
Mister, go wash up first.
Go wash up first.
Wash what? No need for that.
You dare to sleep with my wife?
Kill him!
Hit him hard!
Beat him to death.
What took you so long?
I was afraid
you hadn't reeled him in yet.
Once they're in this room,
is there anyone I can't handle?
This one today is a big customer.
Yeah, that's quite a lot of cash.
Alright.
Stop hitting him.
Leave him some breath.
Let's go.