=No Doubt In Us=
(Adapted from the Manman comic No Doubt in Us)
=Episode 6=
Your Majesty, I know this man.
He is the leader of killers secretly
groomed by Marquis of Zhenbei.
The Marquis of Zhenbei
wants to use the hunt's unpredictability
to secretly assassinate Your Majesty.
Then, he can completely
deny any involvement.
I want to see who will be the real prey
in this autumn hunt.
No.
After careful consideration,
I cannot let you take this risk.
Your Majesty,
I'm currently possessing your body.
You should have faith
in my martial skills.
But...
No buts, Your Majesty.
Duo will protect me.
Xiao Jinyun, rest assured,
I'll hunt a fierce beast for you
and return safely.
♪How I wish to hold your hand tightly♪
(I believe you'll return safely.)
♪Yet I cannot escape fate's tricks♪
♪Until we vanish
from each other's sight♪
Giddy up!
♪Can we stay silent♪
♪Watching the scenery slowly change♪
♪Words have failed me♪
♪Can we stay silent♪
♪Let memories carve themselves silently♪
♪Treasure the most beautiful moment♪
Xu Yu!
Your Majesty,
assassins have been eliminated.
Only one survivor was left.
Your Majesty, I arrived late.
I beg forgiveness.
The Empress...
Xu Yu.
How dare you attempt
to kill Their Majesties!
Your Majesty, this assassin
is a guard of General Xu Jun.
Impossible!
I've never seen this man before.
He can't be my brother's man.
With the plot exposed,
you naturally deny it.
It appears
you were protecting His Majesty,
but in truth,
you were trying to kill him.
Tao Kan,
you mean the Xu family is behind it?
Then why did the Empress
take that arrow for me?
That's precisely their cunning.
If successful,
no one would suspect the Xu family.
Confess! Who sent you?
Confess truthfully,
and I might spare your life.
It was Xu Jun.
The original plan was
to assassinate Your Majesty.
If unsuccessful,
we were to kill the Empress
to clear the Xu family's name
in this way.
What a brilliant scheme.
Should anything happen to Your Majesty,
they would use her to control the court.
Now that the Empress died saving you,
Your Majesty would
naturally favor the Xu family.
Either way, the Xu family wins.
Baseless accusations!
Spit it out!
Xu Duo, are you silencing him
after the plan failed?
Please let me explain.
He had a poison pill.
I tried to stop him
from swallowing the pill.
Master Xu...
I failed the mission.
Your Majesty, we've caught him
with concrete evidence.
The Xu family must be eradicated,
and then a new Empress is appointed.
I'm not dead yet!
A new Empress isn't needed.
Her Grace is fine.
Sorry to disappoint you.
Xu Yu!
Since you insist
that this assassination was planned
by the Xu family,
we'll have the Ministry of Justice
and Supreme Court jointly investigate
this to find the person behind it.
What do you say?
Today, we deliberately set this trap
to lure out those assassins.
We'll follow the lead to the truth.
Tao Kan, you've tried to protect me.
I will reward you handsomely.
I don't deserve it.
Sure, you don't deserve it.
Xu Yu!
Xu Yu.
What are you doing?
I'm checking if you're injured.
Though you wear soft armor,
it can't block every arrow.
Rest assured,
I won't let your body get hurt.
Who said I'm only worried about my body?
Then you're worried about me?
Of course!
You actually conspired with Duo
and kept me in the dark.
Only after Duo and I
eliminated the ambush in the forest,
he revealed your plan to me.
You'd already anticipated
that if the assassination failed,
Tao Kan would try to get out of it.
And you
faked your death
to make Tao Kan fall for it
to accuse my family
of using a self-sacrifice ploy.
I wanted him to blame your family.
That way,
relevant authorities could intervene,
putting pressure on Tao Kan.
His impulsive nature
makes him prone to mistakes.
Eventually, his backer would be exposed.
Who is it?
Prince Ning.
Your Highness,
the poison in the assassin
is too common to trace.
I knew it.
Tao Kan has schemed for so long.
How could it be so easy to find clues?
Jiang Tang, do you know
why Jinyun assigned
such a tedious task to me?
I need to help
the Grand Preceptor find the book.
Your Highness,
why didn't you refuse?
Tao Kan wants to frame the Xu family.
I must help Jinyun investigate this.
Did you find something?
It smells somewhat familiar.
Take a whiff.
It's face powder.
True. That's why it smells familiar.
That's it.
Xu Yu.
Could you help me put on this robe?
Your Majesty.
Your uncle targets you at every turn.
My father gave me soft armor,
and my eldest brother suddenly returned.
After the assassination,
do you truly not suspect my family?
In the past, I might have suspected.
But after meeting your two brothers,
I realized how terrifying rumors can be.
From now on,
I only trust what I see and what I feel.
Xu Yu, I will never suspect your family.
Your Majesty.
Jinyun, I've found evidence.
Why are your faces so red?
What were you doing just now?
What evidence did you find?
I found the perfume on the assassin
was from the northern royalty.
Those who once
accessed the northern royalty
are the Marquis of Zhenbei,
who invaded Dada's heartland,
and
Your Grace's father and brothers
guarding the northern frontier.
The Xu family is innocent.
I certainly know that.
But the Marquis of Zhenbei
is hard to deal with.
We need solid evidence.
Now this mask is our only clue.
What do you plan to do?
Then I need your help.
Jinyun.
Jinyun, she is copying you again.
I'm teaching you propriety.
Mind your manners. Why stand so close?
Isn't it good
that I'm close to my own brother?
Your Grace, why do you keep stopping me?
Let me guess.
I guess you're jealous
of Jinyun and me being close.
That's all. I'm leaving now.
I can't believe him.
Listen, I've flipped through them
a million times.
But I haven't found a single clue.
Your Highness.
Do you want my help?
Any clues?
You know which type of people
wear much face powder,
don't you?
Face powder?
♪Parting clouds to get the waxing moon♪
♪Brewing a pot of bygone years♪
♪Chill flame, window shade,
console my grieving soul♪
♪Drunk through lifetimes
with no dreams returned♪
♪If not for letting go, how could I
bear to shatter this dream♪
♪Returning to drift
through the mortal world♪
♪Like her, like me, like you♪
♪Hairpins carved
with endless sighs and regrets♪
♪Fate laid bare my deepest thoughts♪
♪Like vows, like remorse, like love♪
♪Loving, hurting,
and regretting our late meeting♪
♪Tell me, after all this entanglement,
who regrets it more♪