[Fated Hearts]
[Episode 22]
Greetings, Your Majesty.
The two princes have been
accompanying His Majesty this whole time.
I advised them to go back and rest.
Tonight,
I will stay here
to watch over His Majesty.
Leave us.
I already know about
His Majesty's illness.
Please take care of yourself,
Your Majesty.
Let me have a moment alone with him.
Your Majesty...
Get out!
Fifteen years.
You've been terminally ill for 15 years,
and you never
said a word to me about it.
Your Majesty,
you've really been keeping me in the dark.
Never mind.
You must have your reasons
for not telling me.
You're always the one
who makes the most sense.
We've been married for so many years.
When have you ever considered me
in any of your decisions?
Your Majesty,
guess
what I've brought you.
Zongzi.
You didn't expect that, did you?
Those people must think
I've lost my mind.
The Dragon Boat Festival was a month ago,
but today I suddenly feel like
having zongzi.
Your Majesty, you know
I've always loved zongzi.
But...
I haven't had one
in 15 years.
Your Majesty,
zongzi is so delicious.
Smell it.
Doesn't it smell good?
Do you know
why I haven't eaten zongzi
in 15 years?
Of course you do.
On the 5th day of the 5th month
15 years ago,
that woman died right in front of you.
Since then,
you've never celebrated
the Dragon Boat Festival again,
and you've never eaten zongzi.
Your Majesty.
You actually have the leisure today
to tend to plants?
These plants
must have accumulated great fortune
over several lifetimes to receive your...
What brings you here today?
I came to celebrate the festival with you.
Today is the Dragon Boat Festival.
Your Majesty,
you haven't had any zongzi yet, have you?
I made these myself today.
They're just freshly steamed.
Please try some, Your Majesty.
I have no appetite.
Just one bite, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
How dare you!
Get up.
I don't want them.
Take them away
and share them with the kids.
You said you hated her
and forbade anyone
from ever mentioning her.
You erased
every trace of her,
as if
she had never existed.
But she's here.
She's been here all along.
I've spent 15 years
and still haven't been able
to reach your heart.
Is it because
you don't care about me
that you've hidden
your terminal illness from me?
Fine.
From today on,
I don't care whether you like me or not.
I only want what I like.
I've already given you
the first half of my life.
Now I want you to spend the rest of it
with me!
Feng Pingcheng!
Wake up!
Pull the Empress away!
Open your eyes and look at me!
Hurry!
Feng Pingcheng!
Let go of me!
Wake up!
Feng Pingcheng, wake up right now!
Feng Pingcheng!
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty...
What should I do?
What should I do now?
Your Majesty...
Feng Pingcheng!
Let go of me!
I can walk by myself!
[Yifeng Palace]
Get lost! All of you!
-Yes.
All of you, get out!
Mother.
Don't be too sad.
I'm here with you.
Brother said
that Father will surely wake up.
Mother,
please take care of yourself.
Don't cry until your eyes are swollen.
If Father wakes up and sees that,
he'll be upset.
He wouldn't be upset at all.
In his heart and eyes,
there's no place for me,
or for you.
The only one he cares about is that woman.
That woman?
You mean Brother's birth mother?
You see him as your brother,
but has he ever acknowledged you
as his brother?
Remember,
Feng Suige
is your greatest enemy in this lifetime.
You'd better stay away from him.
Do you know
what will happen
if your father doesn't wake up?
Feng Suige will ascend the throne.
By then, he'll kill you
and me.
If he succeeds,
we'll both die.
He's always hated me
for causing his birth mother's death.
That's why he refuses
to acknowledge me as his mother,
or you as his brother.
He's been waiting for this day.
He's waiting for your father to be gone
so he can take his revenge.
And your father, even though
he knows exactly what will happen,
still refuses to name a crown prince.
I know he hates me deep down.
Mother,
please stop.
Don't speak of them that way.
Even you're taking their side now?
Once your father passes away
and Feng Suige takes the throne,
he'll kill you
and all of us.
Our lives are in your hands.
Only you can protect us.
I want you to take the throne
and kill Feng Suige.
That's the only way we'll survive.
[Imperial Hospital]
From today on,
no one is allowed to leave
until we find a way to save His Majesty.
Eating, drinking, and dumping—
you'll do everything here.
Even Lord Ling from Zhengnian Villa
has no solution.
We're at a complete loss as well.
Physician Wei,
that must be very difficult for you.
No, not at all.
Being at a loss
just shows your medical skills
are lacking.
It's better to die
and, in your next life,
study medicine properly from the start.
Don't you all
agree?
What do you say?
I'll take your silence
as agreement.
From now on,
if you find any method in medical books
that could wake His Majesty,
try it on him.
Don't worry about whether he might die.
If he does, I'll get you
another one.
[Murong Residence]
Elder Marquis eats well
and sleeps soundly.
Don't worry.
No need to thank me.
Yixiao.
My Lord,
we chased down 3 streets
but couldn't find the archer.
Pull back all the people
watching Feng Suige's residence!
But if we pull them back now...
My father is in someone else's hands!
What's the point of keeping watch?
Go!
Yes.
Fu Yixiao,
just you wait.
[Wutong Mansion]
Lu Ke.
Miss Yixiao?
Where have you been?
His Highness has long known
that you haven't left Yujing.
I'll explain later.
Where is your master?
He entered the palace last night
and hasn't returned today.
Then please pass on a message for me.
I want to see him at 3 p.m. today.
Tell him to come alone.
Is there anything else
you want me to convey?
Give this to him.
He knows where we should meet.
How does he...
Make sure to tell him.
I have something very important
to tell him.
Don't worry.
I have one more thing to tell you.
Appointing a crown prince
is a major matter.
His Majesty is wise and mighty.
He must have made arrangements already!
Do you really think,
while he's ill,
that you alone
can turn everything upside down?
Give up that idea!
Greetings, Prime Minister Zhuang.
May I ask why
you summoned me?
You don't know why?
It's just the two of us here.
Mr. Ma,
let's just
speak plainly.
You've been serving His Majesty
for so long.
You must be his most trusted person.
His Majesty always plans ahead.
Since he knows
he has a terminal illness,
he must have made preparations.
Has he already drafted
an edict of succession?
I am merely
the head eunuch.
Many things are beyond my knowledge.
Please understand, Prime Minister Zhuang.
You are his most trusted person.
If there is an edict,
it should be in your custody, right?
I truly know nothing.
I'm only asking.
Since you don't know,
I'll trust you.
I will fulfill my duty as Prime Minister
and summon all the key ministers at court
to discuss the matter
of appointing the crown prince.
Mr. Ma,
don't wait until we reach a decision
and then suddenly pull out
some imperial edict—
that would be
impossible to deal with.
Yao.
I heard about what happened
to the Elder Marquis.
How is the situation now?
You've heard that?
Someone actually dared to lay hands
on the Elder Marquis in Yujing City.
They're courting death.
I'll order all the elite soldiers
from the Feng Battalion
to search the entire city.
We'll leave no stone unturned
to find...
No need to trouble the Feng Battalion.
I have the Imperial Guards.
Yao,
The Elder Marquis is like a father to me.
Anyone who dares to kidnap him
is making an enemy of me.
Tell me
what happened
before the Elder Marquis disappeared.
I want to figure out
who might be behind this.
My father spent most of his life
on the battlefield.
He made too many enemies.
Countless people want to harm him.
Forget it.
Don't worry
about it.
I came to see you
because the duty of guarding the palace
has to be temporarily handed over to you.
You must keep watch over
the palace for me.
Alright.
What?
You don't trust me?
Of course I trust you.
You're my best friend.
You seem a bit off today.
What I'm going to do now
is catch the person
who harmed my father,
flay him, pull out his entrails,
grind him into mince
and feed it to the dogs.
I'm not like my father.
I'll collect any debts
owed to the Murong family.
Even if it's my closest friend,
I'll settle the score.
A dancing girl
got beaten to death for no reason.
I know
you wanted to teach the Prince of Zhennan
a lesson,
but you shouldn't have killed her
so recklessly.
If this gets out,
how will it look?
Also,
when I came in just now,
I saw another official's wife
leaving your place.
Tell me,
what's with her clothes?
Mother,
you think it looks good too, right?
I picked it for her.
Absurd!
That's the Princess of Zhennan's outfit.
Don't tell me you have feelings for her.
I didn't think it that way.
But now that you mentioned it…
Don't you dare set your sights on her!
There are plenty of consorts
in the palace,
but you never touch them.
Yet you always scheme after
officials' wives.
I'm tired of lecturing you
about your rotten behavior.
But remember,
you are not
to touch the Princess of Zhennan.
Mother,
you don't actually treat him
as your own son, do you?
If I had a son like him,
would I still be getting angry every day
like this?
You sent him back to the capital
without consulting me.
This is clearly
asking for trouble.
You humiliated him again last night?
He can't stay in the capital anymore.
Send him away immediately.
Send him away?
That's like releasing a tiger
back to the mountain.
Once he reaches Shengjing,
Pingling City will get the news.
Mother, are you really that afraid of him?
What I'm afraid of is political instability
in Jinxiu
and internal strife.
As you said,
his greatest support
is the army in Pingling City.
Now that he's in Shengjing,
he's in danger.
Mother,
how do you think he can communicate
with them in Pingling City?
If he's obedient, it'll be fine.
But if he's not,
he'll definitely make moves in Shengjing.
I want him to reveal
all his cards
in Shengjing.
Just one thing—
you must not set your sights
on the Princess of Susha.
Bai Shouzhuo!
Your Majesty.
The Empress Dowager forbids me
from setting my sights
on the Princess of Susha.
I had no such intention anyway.
But now,
somehow,
I find this very intriguing.
Grandfather.
I heard your mother is ill.
Mother is sleeping.
Last night she went to see Father,
stayed up all night,
and ran a high fever.
The imperial physicians have already come
to check on her this morning.
How are you?
I spent the whole night
copying the Heart Sutra
for Father and Mother,
hoping they'll recover soon.
Let me ask you again—
how are you?
I...
You're 20 now,
a grown man.
Are you ready?
Father was perfectly fine before.
I don't know why
he suddenly became like this.
I truly don't understand.
If Father truly doesn't make it,
then...
That's not what I'm asking.
I'm asking
if you're ready
to become the ruler of the realm.
Once your father passes away
and Feng Suige takes the throne,
he'll kill you
and all of us.
Our lives are in your hands.
Only you can protect us.
I've...
never thought about that.
Don't you even trust your grandfather?
I do.
I...
respect you the most.
Then why aren't you looking at me
when you speak?
Remember,
I always stand by your side.
You, your mother,
and I—
our fates
rise and fall together.
I'll do
whatever you say.
I want you
to become Emperor.
Yes.
To be Emperor, you must act like one.
Louder!
I want to be Emperor.
Your Highness,
Miss Yixiao asked me to give this to you.
What else did she say?
Nothing.
She said that once you see it,
you'll understand.
She was so cautious
about asking me to meet.
There must be a reason.
Did she look well?
She seemed fine.
No illness, no injuries,
nothing unusual—
just a bit mysterious.
Oh, right.
She repeatedly reminded me
to tell you that
you must go see her alone.
It's not safe to talk here.
Follow me.
♪ Lost in the wilderness ♪
♪ I've been looking for you ♪
♪ Even if devastation fills my eyes ♪
♪ The shadows continue to sway ♪
Don't move.
♪ The phoenix going against light ♪
Let me give you a hug first.
♪ Has been looking for a thousand miles ♪
♪ As years pass, dust stirs,
stirring deep longing ♪
♪ All I ask is to be together  forever ♪
I know
that the reason you cautiously
asked to see me
must be that something happened.
I've already caught Wu Ying.
I'll make her
feel the pain
you once suffered a thousandfold.
Aren't you happy
to hear that?
I am.
Really?
On your face,
I can't see
any sign of happiness.
Do you remember that day,
when I helped you save Yun Qing,
you promised me 5 favors?
Now there are 4 left.
Today,
I want to use another one.
No matter
what you hear,
you must promise me
to stay calm.
Alright.
I've discovered Meng Junran's
true identity.
He is Murong Yao.
What are you saying?
How could he possibly be...
You're not joking?
I know it's hard for you to accept.
Before coming to see you,
I considered all possibilities.
I know
Murong Yao is your best friend
and the person you trust most.
I considered
whether I should hide this from you.
I also thought about
who you'd choose to believe
between him and me.
I even thought
you might suspect
that I'm a spy from Jinxiu,
or that I've been sent
by Xia Jingshi
on some secret mission—
that I
came to you
only to help him drive a wedge
between you and your best friend.
Feng Suige,
I've thought through all of it.
Even if you doubt me,
even if my words hurt you,
even if
it means losing you,
I've still decided to tell you.
I don't want to
keep anything from you.
You have the right to know the truth.
Can you tell me again—
who is Meng Junran?
You said it's Yao?
Officail Website : kissasian.be
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Murong Yao?
I know this must be painful for you.
If your chest feels tight
and it's hard to breathe,
just take a few deep breaths
and let it out.
It's okay.
Everything will be fine.
It will all get better.
I'm fine.
I'll go ask him face to face.
You promised me.
You must stay calm.
Don't worry.
I invited you all here today
to discuss
several important matters.
Minister Hou of the Ministry of War
was attacked and injured;
he has requested leave to recover
in his hometown.
The position of Minister
cannot remain vacant.
Let's have Vice Minister Liu Qin
of the Ministry of War
temporarily take over the duties
of the minister.
I will serve with utmost dedication
until my dying breath.
Second,
His Majesty's condition is now critical,
and the position of Crown Prince
remains vacant.
As
both a court official
and a member of the royal family,
I
shouldn't speak pessimistically,
but for the sake of the realm,
we can no longer delay
the matter of succession.
In my opinion,
the Second Prince,
being the Empress's legitimate son
of noble birth
and virtuous character,
is the most suitable choice
for Crown Prince.
But after all, the First Prince
is the eldest legitimate son.
Throughout history,
the tradition has always been
to appoint the eldest legitimate son
as Crown Prince.
Shouldn't the First Prince
be appointed the Crown Prince?
His Majesty is the founding emperor—
there's no fixed rule
for succession in Susha.
Although the First Prince
is the eldest legitimate son,
he has repeatedly defied His Majesty
and acted without restraint.
With such conduct,
how can we entrust Susha's future
to him?
I agree.
Before, during the Ancestral Ceremony,
His Majesty personally appointed
the Second Prince
as the secondary officiant.
Clearly, in His Majesty's eyes,
the Second Prince possesses
both virtue and talent.
Thus, he is the best candidate
for Crown Prince.
I agree.
I understand
what you are suggesting.
Please rest assured.
Appointing an heir
concerns the nation's fate,
and I
will handle it with the utmost care.
Prime Minister Zhuang,
the wise carry heavier burdens.
Thank you for your efforts.
Thank you for your efforts,
Prime Minister.
I heard from others
that you were badly wounded
in the Battle of Pingling.
I came here to
end our brotherhood.
I no longer consider you my brother.
You've been saying that
since we were children.
Don't tell me
you'll miss me.
Get lost!
With you in Yujing City,
I'm annoyed nonstop all day.
Annoyed?
Aren't you happy with me here?
Why are you annoyed?
But then again...
If I were the Commander
of the Imperial Guards,
I could certainly be of help to you.
Don't you do that for me.
I know you.
You hate being tied down the most.
But you have no influence
in the court.
Now that His Majesty has even had
the Second Prince
take your place at the Ancestral Ceremony,
how could I leave you behind
and enjoy freedom alone?
[Murong Residence]
I've been waiting for you.
I knew it.
Fu Yixiao told you everything.
Looks like she really does
mean more to you than I do.
We've been brothers for so many years.
You believe everything she says?
I came here
to hear it from you directly—
are you Meng Junran?
Yes.
Did Zhuang Shen force you?
What leverage does he have on you?
If you weren't being coerced,
if you had no weakness,
you'd never do this.
Yao,
we've been brothers for so many years.
What can't you tell me?
Are you in trouble?
Tell me.
I did it willingly!
No one forced me!
Why?
I can't stand seeing you do so well.
I'm jealous of you.
You still won't tell me the truth?
See?
You don't believe me anyway.
Fine.
Then tell me—
what have I
ever done to wrong you?
Why must it be that
only if you wronged me
could I stand against you?
Am I not worthy to be your rival?
If I want to go against you,
it doesn't have to be
for some hidden reason.
It can simply be my own choice.
Your own choice?
All my life,
I've seen you as my closest brother.
And now you're telling me
you're going against me
of your own choice?
So you colluded with Xia Jingshi
and Zhuang Shen
to take my life?
I could have spared your life.
I could have done everything
I wanted
without you ever knowing.
But you got in my way.
I have no choice.
There's nothing else I can do.
What are you trying to do?
Tell me!
Murong Yao,
what do you want?
When we were 10,
we went with our fathers
to inspect the border.
Do you remember
that time we sneaked off
without permission to play
and ran into assassins?
Don't come any closer!
What are you doing?
Stay back!
If my father hadn't arrived in time,
we would have been doomed.
But there were too many assassins.
My father couldn't handle them all.
I only realized later
that my father at that moment
never thought
he would survive.
The only person
he cared about
was you,
the First Prince.
Kill!
In that life-and-death moment,
the first person he tried to save
was you, not me.
Father!
I was his own son!
Go!
At the time, I couldn't understand
why your life
was more precious than mine.
Later, I realized
it was because you were the First Prince.
If anything had happened to you,
the entire Murong family
would have been executed.
That's why my father
risked everything to save you.
Father!
Yao!
That was the first time
I ever truly faced death.
I remember countless blades
slashing toward my father and me.
My mind went blank,
and all I could do was cry
and beg for someone to save me.
It hurt so much.
The pain was unbearable.
I passed out from the pain.
When I woke up,
they were all dead.
My father was severely wounded,
all from blades.
It was then that his leg was injured
and left with a chronic ailment.
Even now,
it still pains him from time to time.
Father!
Son.
With me here,
you don't need to be afraid of anything.
Suige!
Suige, please come save us!
What happened next?
How did you get out of danger?
I kept waiting,
waiting for His Majesty to send people
to rescue us.
But I waited for a long time,
and no one ever came.
Later I realized,
as long as you,
the First Prince, was safe,
no one would care
whether we lived or died.
The First Prince was ambushed,
and His Majesty flew into a rage.
At that time,
who would have remembered
my father and me?
That road
was only a few miles from the border camp,
yet it was the longest, hardest road
I've ever walked in my life.
Here's His Majesty's verbal decree!
Murong Zhong, heed this command.
From this day on,
the Murong clan
is to guard the northern border of Susha.
You are forbidden to return to the capital
without royal summons.
I
will depart tomorrow.
Better if you leave today.
His Majesty also said
that the Murong family
bears unshirkable responsibility
for what happened
to the First Prince.
But
in recognition of your service
in protecting him,
you will not be punished.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Yao,
my father and I
gave you the chance to live,
yet in the end, we were sent to suffer
in the northern frontier.
Why is your life
worth more than ours?
Why must the Murong family
always be ready
to sacrifice for the Feng family?
Why didn't you send people to get us
after you returned?
Why didn't you send people to save us?
Why didn't you
plead with His Majesty for us?
Aren't we brothers?
Where were you when I needed you?
Where were you?
After I woke up,
the first thing I did was ask
how you and your father were.
But they told me at the time
that you were already out of danger.
When I saw you again,
it was two years later.
So at that time I thought
you...
You thought?
You Fengs
always only care about what you think.
Have you ever considered how others feel?
Yao,
why didn't you
tell me all this sooner?
If I had told you earlier,
could you have given me back
part of my foot?
Could you have made my father's legs
stop hurting so much every night?
Even if I had told you earlier,
what could I have gained—
besides your pity?
Feng Suige,
let me tell you—
the thing I despise most
in this life
Officail Website : kissasian.be
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
is your pity.
I also come from a military family!
I want to be a great general
like you.
But I can't even ride a horse.
Back then, my father and yours
fought side by side
to build Susha together.
Your father became emperor,
while mine is just a marquis
in name only.
Is that fair?
Yao,
stop this.
While you still can.
I've been thinking about this
for over a decade.
How do you expect me to stop?
How can I?
For once, I want to live for myself.
I only want the Murong family
to get what it rightfully deserves.
Is that wrong?
While my father is in Fu Yixiao's hands,
I can't do anything to you.
You can kill me.
What?
Can't bring yourself to do it?
How about now?
Can you bring yourself to do it now?
I have only one condition:
release my father.
He knows nothing about this.
From today on,
we're even.
We're no longer brothers.