Previously on Seducing Drake Palma.
Excuse me.
You’re my girlfriend.
Act like one.
Leave Alys alone.
I don’t want.
You don’t love her, right?
Bye!
Oh.
Why?
Bird brain.
You’re rude!
Alright, fine. I’ll teach you.
Nice!
Finally.
- I really can’t do this alone.
- But...
But what?
Kiss me.
Drake.
Please don’t...
When will you ever
learn to shut up?
Oh, my…
Why is he so handsome?
My heart is having
wild palpitations again.
Oh, my gosh!
I’ve been feeling this
more often.
Why am I so drawn to him?
Oh no!
Shocks!
Is Drake going
to be my first kiss?
Cannot be!
I don’t want!
That’s all for now.
Did he really kiss
me on the neck?
I love you, Drake Palma!
Why don’t I want to
go to the bathroom?
Why don’t I want to shower?
Why don’t I want
to wipe my neck?
Oh no!
What?
Wow! Is answering
really that hard for you?
Isn’t it obvious?
I’m not in the mood.
Let’s talk some other time, Alys.
Gosh.
What’s her problem?
And why is she
taking it out on me?
Maybe she’s having
Kent problems again.
I’m such a KenYa shipper,
they’re so cute together.
They’re so cute and fluffy!
Alys!
Mom?
Sheen is here.
He’s in the garden.
Just meet him there.
- Okay?
- Okay, mom!
Why is Sheen my loves here?
Cute pajamas, check!
Cute slippers, check!
Lip balm…
Check!
Tutti-fruity scent, check!
Absolutely check!
Let’s go to Sheen my loves.
Sheen!
I miss you!
I miss you, too!
So, what are you doing here?
I just wanted to
ask you something.
Yes, Sheen.
Huh?
You’re going to ask me
if I want to be your girlfriend, right?
Yes, of course!
No.
You got it wrong.
- You’re silly.
- Is that so?
I wanted to ask if...
if you really love Drake?
What kind of question
is that, Sheen?
Nothing.
Well, as your best
friend, I just want to know
what’s really going on
between you and Drake.
You got together
because I asked you to, right?
I’m just curious if
you actually love him.
Why do you want to know?
If you don’t love him,
I’ll find a way to break you up.
I don’t want you to end up
with someone like Drake.
Just because.
So, what now?
What does Drake mean to you?
Why is he asking me this?
Is he making sure Kei
has no chance with Drake?
Because we’re together now?
He is my boyfriend.
Come on, Sheen.
We’re about to
celebrate our monthsary.
Come on, Alys Perez.
Keep fooling Sheen and yourself.
Well, don’t you feel
anything for Drake?
It seems you’ve been having
heart palpitations lately.
Mmm, really?
Yes, best friend.
I don’t even know what gift
to get him for our monthsary.
Do you have any
ideas, best friend?
Maybe give him a book.
I don’t think he likes
other things.
Well, if we were together,
then he’s the one
I’d be giving gifts to.
But this is the last time, Alys.
After this, I’m moving
on from my loves.
And why should I move on?
We never became a couple.
Oh, okay.
Thanks, Sheen!
Well, I’ll go ahead now.
Sheen!
Mmm?
What’s this?
Uh, your watch?
I don’t need it.
Drake’s already teaching
me how to read analog.
Thank you.
Alright then. Good.
I’m heading out.
Oh, Sheen.
Letting you go now.
I won’t call you
“loves” anymore.
Maybe we’re just
meant to be friends.
Someday, I’ll find
someone to love.
But no one will ever
love you the way I did.
Thank you!
Oh, my god!
Aya, come on!
Good morning, bestie!
What’s so good about it?
Why are you grumpy?
Shut it!
You were the one
in a mood last night.
I couldn’t talk to you,
and now you’re jump-scaring me?
Come on, Alys, my bestie!
Let’s not be negative
in the morning.
We should always avoid negativity.
Come on.
Where’s Kent?
Oh my, don’t mention
that little pest’s name.
He keeps asking about our monthsary
and I haven’t said yes yet!
Yiiee!
You look good together!
I’m a KenYa shipper!
I’ll back you up, promise!
You are so cute and fluffy!
What’s cute about that?
You mean creepy?
Admit it.
You have a crush on Kent,
don’t you?
Right, bestie? Yiee!
What?
Yiee!
Get it together, Alys!
You’re neighing like a horse, going yeee!
You’re crazy!
Yieeee!
Now what?
You started it!
Oh no!
Yieeee!
- Let’s open it.
What?
Drake!
You scream like a fangirl!
That hurts!
Aya, we’re going to be late!
Stop it!
There’s still time!
Here’s your girlfriend.
I’ll leave you alone.
Go, DraLys!
Tss.
Hey!
Eat.
I’m full already.
I can’t eat that anymore.
So, where’s Kent?
Oh my, don’t mention that
little pest’s name.
He keeps asking about our monthsary
and I haven’t said yes yet!
Come on, Sheen.
We’re almost
celebrating our monthsary.
Hey, Drake.
Do we have a monthsary?
Tss.
This is irritating.
You don’t know either.
What now?
I know!
Let’s just say we got
together on September 31!
So, we’ll celebrate our second
monthsary on November 31, okay?
What are you looking at?
Stupid.
There’s no September 31.
Whatever.
Every 31st will be our monthsary, so we
only have to celebrate seven times a year.
Does he think I’m stupid?
OMG!
For the first time,
I got ahead of Drake!
This is really an achievement!
Besides, you really think
we’ll last a whole year?
Keep dreaming!
We’re graduating
in a few months.
Once we start college,
we’ll go our separate ways.
Who says that I’m
gonna break-up with you?
Hmm?
Bestie, go take
a shower already!
We’re gonna be late!
- Wait…
- You’re heavy!
Come on, Bestie!
That’s not even until later!
Why are you so eager, anyway?
It’s just a wedding rehearsal for
Uncle Steve and Aunt Katrina!
So what?
I miss Uncle Steve!
Gosh, Aya!
Do you have a crush
on Uncle Steve?
What do you think of me?
A fan of May-December
love affair?
Then, why are you so eager to go?
To be honest Bestie,
I’m just really sick of Kent!
He’s always at our house,
trying so hard to court me.
My gosh! My mom is
totally rooting for him already.
She might even
force Kent to marry me.
Is that fair?
- Ouch!
- Well,
if my daughter had a
fluffy and cute suitor,
I wouldn’t complain either!
What if I punch you now?
- Alright! I’ll shower now!
- I’ll hit your head on my biceps!
Let’s eat first!
Let’s go! We’re late!
Geez, you’re making me nervous!
Why?
You might get hungry there and
ask Uncle Steve for breakfast!
So what?
Aya, that’s embarrassing.
- Why?
- People might think we’re poor.
Whatever, let’s just go!
Fine, you go ahead. Go on.
I’ll eat here.
Mommy!
Can you please tell Aya
to have breakfast here?
Aya, come and join us.
Oh Alys, by the way,
on the weekend, you have to
go to your Daddy Cyriel, okay?
This is our set-up.
Sometimes, I spend weekends
at Daddy Cyriel’s.
Yup.
Dad Andy is my stepdad.
But who cares?
I am still his one and only princess!
It’s okay, princess.
He’s your biological dad.
And besides, you’re
there every weekend,
so no need to ask permission.
Okay Mom, sure. I’ll go visit him.
What time will you
be home later?
So I can have Clarence pick you up.
Um, 4:00 PM?
Right, Aya?
We’re supposed
to be home by 4:00 PM?
Yes, we’ll be back by 4:00 PM.
Okay.
You’re going to Drake’s, right?
Um, yes, Dad.
Alright, take care.
Tell him to visit sometime.
We’re full now.
Let’s go!
Hey, I’m still hungry!
Come on, weren’t you in a hurry?
Let’s go, come on!
Bye!
- Take care, bye!
- Love you!
Bye!
- Wow, Uncle has so many guests!
- Exhausting!
Why do we even—
Bestie, hurry up, it’s so hot!
I’m hurrying up!
Do you want me to run?
Faster, it’s hot!
Girl, can’t you see I’m
wearing heels? Take it easy!
I’m running out of energy!
Goodness!
Hi, Aunt Katrina!
Hello!
Alright, head straight in.
Okay.
Uncle Steve!
Alys, Aya!
Uncle, sorry we’re late.
We had breakfast first.
That’s fine.
Head over to the pavilion.
The designers are there for the fitting.
Okay po, Uncle.
Randy!
Oh, wait.
- Hey.
- What?
Aren’t you going to get
your measurements?
Go ahead.
I just need a break.
I’m tired!
I’ll follow you there.
Oh no, I know that creepy smile.
Go on! Go, Bestie!
Go to the fitting already.
Hurry!
- You’ll follow.
- I will.
- You better follow!
- Yes, go ahead!
Uncle Steve!
Aya!
Where’s Drake?
He’s in his room.
He doesn’t want to come down.
He’s hard to talk to.
You know him,
he’s allergic to people.
Uncle Steve, that’s not okay!
What about our plan?
What is this?
Folder within a folder
within a folder?
Huh!
Something’s fishy, Bestie!
I can’t sleep because
I wiped Drake Palma’s body.
From his face, arms, hands, chest—
and my God, all the
way down to his stomach!
I trembled from nervousness.
Uncle Steve…
Uncle Steve, please,
tell Drake to come down.
Alright.
I’ll get him for you, okay?
Yes, please do!
Wow.
You really feel it, Bestie.
Just because your Mom is a designer.
Hey, Uncle Steve.
Let’s go!
Drake...
Drake, they need to get
your measurements.
Oh!
Oh no!
Sorry, I intended—
I mean—I didn’t intend to do it.
Alys is winning.
She can see her boyfriend’s body.
Geez, Aya,
you’re so careless!
I’m trying not to stare at it,
but I can’t resist it!
What now?
Drake needs to get
measured but he’s all wet.
It will be hard for you to change
since your room is upstairs.
And it will be rude to keep
the designer waiting.
The best thing to do
is to take your shirt off
to save time.
OMG!
I knew it.
This is all Aya’s plans.
What kind of torture is this?
Can you still handle the heat, Bestie?
Do you want juice?
Okay.
I know your techniques, Aya!
What?
Oh, he’s here.
Oh, you’re here already.
I just got here, Uncle.
Thanks for filling in.
The photographer
couldn’t make it.
Anytime, Uncle!
And thanks for the gig, too.
Alright everyone, gather up!
Do you know who your partners are?
What are you all
waiting for? Hurry up.
I think the coordinator needs
me. I’ll head over there now.
- Go ahead, Uncle.
- Line up, everybody.
Fix your line.
Tss!
Tss yourself!
Okay, ladies.
Hold onto your gentlemen.
Come on, let’s go.
Hold on.
There, very good!
Hold onto your partners!
Sweetie, hold on.
Very good! There you go!
Now everyone, walk slowly!
Ugh! Why do I have to
hold onto him while walking?
It’s electrifying.
Are the blockings clear to everyone?
Any questions?
None.
Yes?
Can we rehearse the garter part?
Drake and Alys, please.
Hey, Aya!
What is up with you today?
I’m wearing a dress!
So?
Bestie, wearing a dress is better.
Easier to put on!
I’m wearing floral undies.
Hmm?
Floral undies?
Go on, laugh some more, Aya.
You might accidentally
say what I whispered.
Go ahead!
I heard that, Miss Blossom.
Higher!
Miss Blossom.
Entrepreneurship.
Applied Economics.
Business Finance.
Bestie!
Why are you so grumpy?!
Don’t play with me, Aya!
Why?
Because of you, I have
a new pet name from Drake!
Miss Blossom?
Aya, you are so annoying!
Whatever!
Bestie, come on, don’t sulk!
Aren’t you going
out with your mom?
Oh, right!
I can’t be late!
Okay, just text me
when you’re done.
I love you, Bestie!
Bye!
These books are heavy.
But I really need to bring them home.
Alys,
your Dad and I aren’t mad
about your grades right now.
But you need to get
into St. Collete Academy.
If you don’t, I’m afraid we’re
giving you an ultimatum.
What do you want?
Do you want us to send you to the States
with your brother Dane, so you’ll learn?
Is that what you want?
Okay, how about this...
since it’s almost your Christmas break,
and it might motivate you,
let’s make a deal.
What kind of deal?
Well, if you get perfect
scores on your exams,
we’ll spend Christmas
vacation in the States.
We’ll visit your brother, Dane.
Really, Mom?
Oh my gosh! I’m so excited,
I wanna see Dane!
Even if that kid’s naughty,
I miss him so much!
But only if you get perfect scores.
Ah okay, Mom. I promise!
I really need to study hard.
Please be good to me!
Sheen?
Oh.
How have you been?
I haven’t seen you since Monday.
Ah, you’re right.
I’ve been busy.
Just because you have a boyfriend,
you suddenly got busy?
What is Sheen really trying to say?
But it doesn’t matter anymore.
I said I’m moving on.
That’s not true!
Come on!
Just because your monthsary
with Drake is coming up,
you forgot you have a best friend!
Huh? Monthsary?
Yes, didn’t you say your
monthsary’s coming up?
Ah! Right, our monthsary’s
on November 31.
Huh?
- Okay, I’ll go to class.
- But there’s no Novem—
Bye, Sheen!
November 31?
There’s no November 31.
Why did Sheen remind me of my
monthsary with that weird Drake?
I didn’t tell him the actual date.
He’s so annoying!
I’m trying hard to forget about that day,
and he had to bring it up?
That’s why I said 31— so it
only comes seven times a year!
And now he reminded me?
What if Drake Palma remembers, too?
What should I do tomorrow?
A. Sleep all day
and pretend I’m sick?
But I can’t lie to Mom!
Erase!
B.
I’ll just act like I forgot.
My memory’s bad anyway,
so that might work.
Or C...
Should I just greet
Drake a happy monthsary?
Oh no!
Why am I thinking about
Drake instead of studying?
So annoying!
What is wrong with you, Alys?
Good morning, Mom!
Good morning, Dad!
- Good morning!
- Hi!
Good morning.
So, are your things packed?
What?
Wait.
Aya mentioned that you’re gonna
sleepover in their house tonight.
I don’t want to, Mom.
Why not?
I don’t want to go there!
So what now?
Your dad and I are leaving.
You’ll be home alone.
Where are you going?
Uh, secret?
Yuck!
Ew!
You’re so annoying, you playboy!
Just because I took care of you the other
day, it doesn’t mean I’m your girlfriend.
Are you threatening me?
Why don’t you just date the
one who has a crush on you?
Ew!
Stop saying “I love you!”.
That’s not what I mean!
You’re so gross!
You’re so confusing, bye!
Ugh, that guy!
Oh, Bestie — you’re here!
No. This is just my 3D image.
And no, I didn’t hear
you and Kent fighting.
You’re so corny.
- Oh!
- Mm!
Bestie…
are you sick?
- Don’t be so dramatic!
- Why are you studying?
Do you have a fever?
Tsk! I’m changing my
life now, okay?
“I’m changing my life now.”
But why did you tell
Mom I’m sleeping over?
You’re up to
something, aren’t you?
Bestie, you’re so judgmental!
How could I not be suspicious?
You sold me out during our practice.
Bestie, I said sorry!
Come on, let’s go
to the mall instead.
Huh?
Mom’s leaving for Tagaytay.
It’ll be just us at
home— let’s go malling!
Please!
Come on, say yes!
Did you say yes?
I’ll just get ready.
She said yes!
I think it’s best to go out instead,
so I can forget about our monthsary.
What exactly are
you buying here, Aya?
I knew it, Aya!
Oh no, I didn’t know Uncle Steve
and the others would be here too!
Alys, Aya!
You are such a great
liar, Bestie— so annoying!
Uncle!
- Uncle, hi!
- How are you today?
Alys, I’ll ask Uncle Steve
to come with me over there.
We need to check something out.
He’ll accompany me.
We’ll leave you two for now.
Enjoy your special day.
- Happy monthsary!
- Mmm, go on!
Enjoy!
Let’s go, Uncle!
This is a set-up.
Obviously.
I’ll just go home.
Wait.
You can’t just go.
Huh?
Oh!
Where exactly are we going?
Tss.
Oh!
I’m tired!
We’ve been walking around forever.
Where are they, anyway?
Come on, let’s go.
I’m tired,
Drake Sebastian Palma!
My legs are killing
me, isn’t it obvious?
Bird brain.
I heard that.
Which one?
What?
This one?
Is this okay?
Better?
Wear this.
Why is my heart beating so fast?
I’ll give you a ride.
But don’t choke me to death, okay?
Hop on.
I think I’ve already moved on
from Sheen my loves.
It seems this is not a
simple crush anymore.
I think I really this guy.
Drake?!
Shh!
He smells so good.
Why?
Sorry…sorry.
Did you guys have fun?
Alys!
Sheen.
Are you two on a date?
Yes.
Oh, is that so?
If you’ll excuse us.
Come on, let’s go!
The sun is setting.
What?
Isn’t it romantic?
It’s our monthsary.
November 31.
What are you on?
It’s December 1 today.
No.
In our world,
it’s 11/31.
Our second monthsary,
and our first official date.
I should kiss you.
- Are you on drugs?!
- No, I’m not.
Stop it or I’ll kick you!
You really know how to ruin the moment.
Don’t look into his eyes!
Alys, you’ll just fall for him!
Drake?
Don’t.
Why are you laughing at me?
Because you’re funny.
What made you say that?
Is it your first kiss?
- No, of course not!
- Liar.
I’m not lying. I already
had my first kiss.
With who?
With Sheen!
Yes, Sheen!
My first kiss belonged to Sheen.
Sorry, Sheen, my
loves. White lie.
I’ll just treat you tomorrow.
You jerk! You left us here!
It’s getting dark!
So what time are we going home?
Bestie, Uncle Steve and
I are watching a movie.
And you didn’t even invite me!
Wow, what kind of best friend are you?
If you’re not getting me into
trouble, you’re leaving me behind!
Sorry, Bestie!
We just started watching.
And oh… I’ll call you
later, it’s getting to the good part!
Okay, Bestie, bye!
Wait!
What?
I've decided.
Huh?
Sheen was your first kiss,
and I don’t care.
Neither do I.
I’ll be the first one...
here.
Here.
I’m territorial.
She’s surprisingly beautiful.
Even more so when she’s calm and composed.
Drake, it’s time for your fitting.
On the next episode of
Seducing Drake Palma.
Come inside, the
coordinator’s already here.
Ah, thank you, Uncle.
Congrats!
Hurry!
Hi, Miss Beautiful!
Why are you here, gate crasher?
Obviously, I’m here
because of you.
You’re not even good-looking.
I know.
Good, at least you know.
I don’t want to be handsome.
I just want to be loved.
By you, perhaps?
Too bad.
Maybe next time.
Let’s go.
Where?
To the hotel!
Why would I go to
a hotel with you?!
Reception, stupid.