What would you like?
One iced mocha, less sweet.
Sure. Please wait a moment.
Thanks.
Hey there.
Hey.
Oh, P'Phut! Hello!
Sup, man.
I'll have an iced mocha, too.
Got it. Please wait a moment.
Hang on. Have you eaten?
I'll treat you—pick anything.
No thanks, I'm on a diet.
Good, saves my money.
So what will you do next?
Probably back to the same old workroom.
So, has Sorn been rough on you?
All the time.
One hot chocolate, please.
Alright. Please wait a moment.
P'Yo, you're in early today.
I always come at this time. You know that.
How have you been?
I'm good. And you?
I'm good too.
Where are you going next?
Phut!
Hello P'Vee.
Jun, I'm off to work!
Excuse me, your drinks are ready.
I'm heading back to work.
Oh...
Wow, such dedication.
Of course. Hardworking people, you know?
Jun.
Me and Aey walked past the café earlier.
Saw a girl. Know her? Looked
like she had beef with Phut.
Oh, that's Vi. She's Phut's girlfriend.
P'Vee?
Yeah.
Hey Jwin, your wound's
healed? Looking good again, huh?
That day I was so shocked.
I thought my ass was broken.
The wound has healed.
It's good to come back handsome.
I look handsome when I have a wound.
Okay, I think so too.
P'Sorn seems to care about Jun a lot.
If I weren't rooting for P'Penny.
I'd have shipped Sorn
and Jun a long time ago.
What the hell are you talking about?
Uh.
You're just dreaming.
Hey, if we really get
together, we'll give you credit.
Talking nonsense.
Keep working.
Wow, what are you up to?
Putting away snacks.
Why'd you buy so much?
It's for my dog.
Eats a lot.
Some dogs, especially picky
ones, might not even eat that.
How would you know? You a dog or something?
I don't. I guessed. Got it?
Try and see. If it doesn't eat, I'll
stuff it in your mouth.—like last night.
P'Sorn.
I...
Not now, I have to work first.
Really can't?
You're so naughty.
It's your fault, P'Sorn. You're like this.
Why?
Come on.
Jun!
It's very thrilling.
Ahh!!!
Hmm? Who gave you this,
P'Penny? Someone I know?
No idea.
Alright.
I'll just leave it here, then.
Go ahead and leave it.
What's wrong.
Hey, P'Phut?
I know I was wrong, but Vi
didn't have to rub it in like that.
I feel terrible. So bad I don't even know
what's good enough to earn her trust back.
Don't, P'. Don't be like that.
Come here. Don't cry.
Thanks, man.
What happened to your neck?
It's nothing.
Turn around.
I can see it.
How's that “nothing”?
It really is nothing.
Turn around.
Isn't it my personal business!!!
I'm sorry, didn't mean to.
I'm sorry too. I didn't mean to say that.
I get it. It's fine. I'm your
bro, just worried about you.
Whatever, let's eat.
Here he is—my beloved little bro!
Let me walk you through the menu...
Okay.
Whoa! You're eating before I finish!
Tasty.
First, spicy papaya salad with
pickled crab. Second, blue crab salad.
Great taste.
And the best—spicy Vietnamese
pork salad with salted egg yolk.
Whoa, why'd you order so much?
For you, bro. My treat!
Oh really?
Only the best for my favorite bro.
I'm deeply moved!
Is it okay?
Sure.
New Caption
I come here often. Vee likes it too…
Oho, caught ya.
Isn't that P'Phut, Vee's boyfriend?
Yeah, but who's he with?
Try this one.
What now?
Salted egg yolk salad.
I don't really like salted
yolk. It's kinda gross.
That hurts, man. Just try it once—for me.
And as thanks for letting
me cry on your shoulder.
Whoa.
Just a bite, okay?
Nah
I'll feed you train-style!
Fine. Just once.
Alright, here it comes—choo
choo, open wide!
Great taste?
Hey, snap a pic. I'm telling Vi
her boyfriend's cheating again.
Is the angle good? Zoom
in—yeah, right there! Snap it!
Does it feel sinful?
Mmm.
Did it burst in your mouth?
Mmm-hmm.
Damn, how was it?
Tastes good, but I don't like it.
Why not?
This one's better.
Oh, really? Dig in, then!
Give the whole shell.
It doesn't have crab meat.
What is this, Phut!?
It's not what you think,
Vee. You misunderstood.
Misunderstood? You
two were hugging in public!
Why believe others? It's not like that!
It's because I can't trust you.
That's why I get betrayed like this.
Vee, calm down.
Why would you do this, Phut? Huh!?
Just listen to me!
P'Puth, what's going on?
You've been hooking
up with Phut, haven't you?
Wait, no! You've got it all wrong!
Hey, that's enough! Stop it, Vee!
Then call me wrong? How could you!
You hug her like that.
Vee!!
How could you do this?
Vee, stop! Don't hurt him!
Oh, My god!!
It's not what you think, Vee!
P'Sorn, bad news! Jun's in trouble!
Where?
Downstairs! Phut's girlfriend
is slapping him like crazy!
How did she get a mark like that?
Vee!!
Vee, please stop! It's not like that!
What the hell are you doing?
What are you doing to my kid!?
Sorn, I'm sorry. My girlfriend
misunderstood. She thought I was with Jun.
It's not a misunderstanding. That
girl is sneaking around with Phut!
Look at the red mark on her neck! Isn't
that proof enough? Still protecting her?
When would my junior and your boyfriend even have
time to do anything? He's been with me the whole time.
You're so paranoid over your man,
you're turning on everyone. Are you insane?
Praew.
Yeah.
Take Jun back to the office.
Come on, Jun.
Does it hurt a lot?
And you, Phut. You and
your girl—we need to talk.
Sorn, listen. I'm really sorry, but
there's nothing between me and Jun!
I know.
But even I don't know where that mark
on him neck came from. I didn't do it.
It was me.
I was messing around with Jun. I
don't want your girl blaming him.
And how do I know that mark was from you?
Maybe you're just covering for him.
Vee, I told you—there's nothing going on.
And how can I trust you, Phut?
Then what do you want me to do?
Then from now on, stay away
from that kid. Don't even talk to him!
Vee, that's crazy! We work at the same
company. I can't avoid him completely!
I don't know what your solution is…
But what you both need
to do is apologize to Jun.
He's done nothing wrong.
And you, Phut…
Just admit the mark on his neck and end it.
Why is it every time I'm not
around, Jun ends up in trouble?
Guess I need to have a talk with
Phut. Can't let this keep happening.
What happened?
Phut's girlfriend started drama
with Jun. Over who knows what.
Damn, what's going on, Sorn?
Just a small misunderstanding.
It'll be sorted. No big deal.
But what was it even about?
I can't find Jun anywhere!
Phut's girlfriend got jealous—she
thinks Phut and Jun are lovers.
Seriously? What kind of logic is that? Phut
and Jun? Must be blind. See an eye doctor.
And you, stop overworking.
Pack up and go home.
Get home safe.
Where are you?
Home, obviously.
What? You didn't wait for me?
Come on, it's late! Who would wait?
Typical you. Anyway, want
anything? I'm about to head back.
Nah, I just ordered food.
From where? That place near the village?
Nope. I called Je Jom's place.
There it is, the rice has just arrived.
Wait! Turn your camera on.
Why?
I don't trust you.
Ugh, seriously? I'm
getting my food. Bye now.
Don't bother with that food.
Looks like you've got backup.
It's shrimp over rice.
I'm saving it for tomorrow.
You close with Jom or what?
Not really. He's just easy to talk to.
And what about me?
Are we close now?
Why are you asking?
You said you only call
people “hia” if you're close.
You call Jom “hia,” but me? Just “P'”.
Sometimes even “damn P'.”
I don't know if we're close or not.
I just know that.
I like you more than before.
What'd you buy?
Check it out.
Bamboo shoot curry.
Sorry again for scolding
you in that meeting.
Don't worry about it. I messed up
too. Just felt embarrassed, but I'm okay.
Penny.
Can I ask for a chance?
I really care about what we have.
I want us to be something real.
Will you give me that chance?
Actully.
I feel so good with you.
But I still love my freedom.
I'm not ready to commit.
Okay. I get it.
You get what?
I get…
Like this.
I'll go grab a towel.
Wait.
Don't. Just stay with me.
Do you like that?
I like it.
Can it be more than this?
You heading home tonight?
Yeah.
Want me to drop you off?
It's okay, P'. I can go by
myself. Don't want to bother you.
Who said it's a bother?
Sorn, don't go yet. I need to talk to you.
So, want that ride or not?
It's fine, you go talk.
Where are you?
Waiting for the car.
I'll go pick it up.
Jun.
Yeah? What is it?
Want to visit my hometown?
I'll think about it and let you know.
Dad, Sis—can I talk to you for a sec?
What's up?
Can I go visit P'Sorn's place in the South?
Please, Dad?
It's up to Dad. He's grown now anyway.
Fine. Go if you want. But
don't be a burden on Sorn.
Come on, Dad. I'm not a kid!
Oh look, P'Sorn's here.
Talk to him yourself.
Uncle Nueng, hello.
Hello.
Want some iced tea, Sorn?
Thank you.
I'm coming too, Sis!
Jwin said you invited him
to your place in the South.
When are you heading out?
Late this morning. I
already got plane tickets.
Jun, pack your bags.
Don't miss that flight.
Take care of him for me, alright?
Of course.
Hey!
Oh! Hello, P'Thanu!
Just call me Nu.
That Tai little brother?
Doesn't look like him.
Nah, he's Tai younger friend.
Yes.
Cool. Let's go inside.
Sorn, all this yours?
Nah, it's my mom's.
Your mom's loaded.
Wanna be her daughter-in-law?
Hey you—come here.
You and him close or what?
I've known him since he was little.
Dang, raising a sugar baby, huh?
The hell are you even saying?
He's tai fave.
He's staying with me now, so I've
gotta take care of him. Or Tai kill me.
Wow, Ty must mean a lot to
you. You're spoiling this one.
But I've never seen you hang
with a kid more than 5 minutes.
I'm just not used to it.
Yeah yeah, get inside. Jun, let's go.
How's Aunt Noi's deal going?
She bought it. Your mom wasn't gonna
miss it. Still complained at her, though.
I kept following up, but Madam
won't listen to anyone—except you.
What is this hell you, elder brother?
What are you looking at, my little sister?
Your brother's cool.
I like him.
Why'd you do that!?
You're even jealous over
your brother? I just looked!
You just met Nu and already
said he's cool—and you like him?
You fall too fast.
I just said what I thought.
So I'm not cool?
Nope.
I'll make you say I'm
cool—right on my chest, Jun.
Wait here. I'll be back.
Where you going?
To pee. Wanna help me hold it?
Is it? Do you need help carrying it?
Are you serious?
Why do I look so much better in photos?
Ugh, it's burning hot out! Just a short
drive to the market and I'm roasted.
Mom!
Oh my! When did you get
here? Why didn't you tell me?
Why didn't you tell her?
Jun.
This is my mom.
Mom, this is Jun—Tai
beloved friend I told you about.
Hello, Auntie.
Hello, dear. Just call me
Mom like Sorn's friends do.
Yes, mom.
What're you cooking, Mom?
I made “aw-dib” curry. Aunt Noi
brought it, so I made it with fish.
Jun, do you know what aw-dib is?
No, Ma'am.
It's like taro stems but not quite. People
usually make sour curry with it. Pretty bland.
It's kinda crunchy but
has no taste on its own.
The flavor comes from the sour curry seeping
into it. Can you handle spicy food, Jun?
Totally! I can eat spicy.
Go scoop some rice, dear.
Mom, better make a separate bowl.
Last time I made fish kidney
curry, he was panting like a dog.
I'm fine, Mom. No need for that.
Go on, get some rice.
Mom, seriously… has he
always had such a mouth?
That's just how he is, dear.
No wonder y'all don't keep
dogs—his mouth's already full of bark.
Just don't say that around
him. You can tell me, though.
Heh, your face is so sweet,
Mom. I say that and he slaps me!
Whoa!
All this is your mom's?
Yes.
From that corner all the
way down—it's all ours.
Damn. That's rich.
Uncle Nui! Hello!
Oh hey, Sorn.
This is Uncle Nui, Mom's helper.
Uncle, this is Jun, my junior.
Nice to meet you.
Hello there. Good-looking, huh?
Thank you, Sir.
Uncle Nui, how's the palm plantation going?
Oh, that? Gotta keep the workers watering
and fertilizing. Otherwise, it won't make it.
I already talked to Nu about getting someone
to mow. Look at it—it's a jungle out there!
What about the other side?
Oh, that side? Almost ready for sale. With that
much land—hoo boy, I'm gonna be rolling in money!
Time for a photo.
Want me to help? I'm good at taking pics.
Sure, P'Nu. Thanks! Here.
Stand right there.
Okay, one more. Just one more!
Take another picture.
So cool, I'm telling you.
Really.
Whoa, you're amazing at this.
Yeah, I love this one.
New Caption.
Hey Jun.
Just a few meters down—something
fun's happening. Wanna check it out?
Yeah, let's go!
Is that booze? Go for it.
What, no invite for me?
Hey little bro, come
drink! Try some! Come on!
Can I join you guys?
Why are you standing there? Sit, sit!
Come here.
Hello, everyone.
Hey there, kid. Come, have a seat.
Whose is this? Take it, take it.
Whoa, so many snacks today.
Man, they love drinking moonshine
around here. You ever tried it?
Never, bro. I think it's too strong. If I
get drunk, P'Son will scold me again.
What are you so scared of?
Go on, go on. Give it a try, kid.
That's enough, that's enough!
Just a little, please.
Smell good?
That's insanely bitter, bro.
What the hell is this taste?
Hey, bro, wake up!
Hey, Jun.
Bro, wake up.
Jun are you drunk?
Wake up.
Junnn!
Ugh… I can't… I'm wasted.
You made me drink alone…
You drunk or what?
You're looking kinda hot now.
Jun, you're totally drunk.
Oh, Mom. You're so hardworking.
Looks like your boy gets along with my mom.
I've been wondering about something.
Does Jun have a girlfriend?
Hey Jun, wanna go walk
around the temple fair with me?
Yeah, let's go!
You're doing this 'cause you care, right?
Yeah.
Even if you always yell
at me... I still like you.