Do you still remember me?
I'm still the same Jun.
Now I'm officially a full-time
employee at RT Design.
Not long after graduation.
I started working here right away.
Everyone at the company is still the same.
P'Put and P'Wi already broke up.
And things didn't work
out with P'Yo either.
Unlike P'Korn and P'Preaw...
They're still the company's
gossip duo as always.
And what about Hia Tai and Hia Champ?
They ran off abroad for
their honeymoon together.
Oh, and when Hia wasn't around.
P'June got even stricter.
Luckily, I still had
P'Penny to look out for me.
But most importantly.
No one in the company
has any idea that.
Sorn and I…
Are…
Jun.
What is it, Sorn?
Come here for a bit.
What's up?
What are you doing?
Just finishing up some work.
What is it?
You're late.
Did you finish packing my stuff?
What did you pack?
Umm…
Three pairs of socks.
Five pairs of underwear.
Oh, and that pair of socks.
Save it for tomorrow.
All the clothes are packed,
plus toiletries.
And most importantly,
your razor.
Everything's complete, nothing's missing.
I'm only gone for a week.
You packed like I'm moving abroad.
Well,
better be prepared, right?
What if your beard grows
out again like last time?
If a client sees you…
And cancels the deal, what then?
Hia Tai will kill you.
So don't forget to shave.
I don't even want to go.
This time it feels too long.
Don't try to act all clingy now.
Last time you left
you didn't say any of this.
But this time, it's longer than usual.
Can I just not go?
I just want to stay with my baby.
Can James go in my place?
Stop acting spoiled.
Just go do your job.
Earn lots of money
so you can buy me snacks.
I'm not acting spoiled.
But you didn't pack
everything yet, you know.
Belt.
Everything's done.
Nothing's missing.
All set?
Not yet.
Really?
Clothes.
Shoes.
They're all there, Sorn.
What's not complete?
I didn't forget anything.
This piece right here.
Can't I just pack you in my bag?
I'll be gone for so many days.
I'll miss you like crazy.
Feel better now?
No.
I still miss you.
Hm.
That's enough.
Not enough.
Fine, go all out then.
Fold yourself in and pack up.
Can I take you with me?
Double-check everything, okay?
You've got your passport, right?
The tablet's in your bag.
You didn't forget anything, right?
Didn't forget, babe.
We should hurry.
I'll end up missing the flight.
Mm.
While I'm gone.
Don't go acting too flirty.
Why do you always dress up so sharp anyway?
It annoys the hell out of me.
Especially when people scream for you.
“Jun this, Jun that” all the time.
Look who's talking.
When you go out, all the
girls go crazy over you.
Hmph.
Besides, P'Penny says
you've got major charm.
Even more now that you're taken.
Hmph.
Want me to bring you
something back from Japan?
Snacks.
Same as always, huh.
Well, they're tasty.
Give me a kiss.
Didn't you kiss me this morning already?
Can you go now?
Okay.
Hurry back.
I will.
Hey Win,
doesn't your family get mad
about you dyeing your hair like that?
Nah, Dad and Mom don't care.
Only Tai nags me.
Morning and night, nonstop.
Says the color looks
unprofessional when talking to clients.
But I work at the factory, man.
All I see every day are
warehouses and piles of wood.
Like I really need to look formal for that.
And besides...
He's not even here to nag me right now.
You jerk.
He's only gone for two weeks.
On his honeymoon.
How can you talk about him like that?
So what?
He's gone for two whole weeks.
Doesn't he miss his little bro at all?
Oh right, and Sorn went
on a business trip to Japan.
Yeah
but just for a week.
That's still long.
You're not dying of heartbreak?
Normally you two are glued together.
Of course I miss him
but
we talk every day.
What about you? Do you
talk to your brother at all?
Hah. He's just busy with his wife.
Wife.
Fine, you pick up then.
Hello, bro!
Win, you little shit.
Where's my wife?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
First thing you ask is about your wife?
Don't wanna talk to
your little brother first?
Who the hell wants to
talk to a brat like you?
Fine, fine, I'll let you talk to him.
But first,
say it nicely like.
“Win, my dear brother, may I
please talk to my beloved husband?”
You're dead when I see you.
What's he saying?
You're annoying.
Hey, what's up, Sorn?
You with Win right now?
Yeah, we're out grabbing something to eat.
What about you?
What are you doing?
Just finished dinner.
Once you're done, head straight home.
I'll call you tonight.
Okay.
Take care of yourself, Sorn.
Bye.
Told you he calls me all the time.
What does he even call for?
Just random stuff.
Ohh.
What the hell are you grinning at?
I'm not.
Bullshit, Win.
I know exactly what's
going through your head.
Okay.
Hey, what's up, Sorn?
Have you showered?
Mhm, I did.
I was out all day. Win
invited me to play badminton.
I was all sweaty. So I quickly showered.
Good.
At least you had Win to play
with so you wouldn't be lonely.
That's not the same, Sorn.
Aren't you in a hurry to get back?
Why, what's up?
Don't say it like that.
If I'm not supposed to say it to
my wife, then who should I say it to?
How can you say that
when we're far apart like this?
If you were close.
I'd just tackle-hug you
until I stopped missing you.
Please don't say that.
Especially when I'm alone.
You're just too adorable.
How could I not miss you?
Come on, show me what
are you wearing to bed?
No need,
stop being naughty.
Please.
Come on.
I want to sleep having sweet dreams.
Please.
Don't screenshot this, okay?
Damn,
with you that handsome,
how could I not miss you?
Can I kiss the screen?
Sorn,
if you say that again I'll hang up for real.
I'm not teasing.
I really miss you, Jun.
It's just not the same without you.
Everything feels so quiet.
Then hurry back.
Okay.
I'll hurry back to see my wife.
Jun.
Huh?
I want...
Want to sleep?
Want to do it?
Do what, Sorn?
It's because we're not together.
The more I see your face,
the more I miss you.
Let me see your shoulder, Jun.
Can I see yours first?
Already open.
If you were close right now.
I'd nibble those muscles off.
Come on, let me see your shoulder.
Give me a sec to set the camera. (Watch on
www.kisskh.ovh or www.kisskh.la to support Admin)
Take it off.
Please.
I miss you.
You're even more adorable now.
I want to be close to you.
Don't you think I want it?
I want to go back right now.
Wait, Sorn.
Yes?
Sorn.
Ahh, it feels so good!
Sorn, I'm about to come.
I'm about to...
Sorn.
Go wash up.
Turn off the camera and go wash first.
Hello, Piang, what's up?
Hi P'Jun, did you get the package yet?
Yeah, I'm opening it now.
Piang.
So, what do I have to do?
I don't really use lotion though.
Hm, it's not hard.
Just film yourself applying it
and say what I put in the brief.
It's really easy, just follow the brief.
I'm not that confident, Piang. I've
never done a review before. What if.
What if it turns out bad
and the brand complains?
Brands don't always want
someone who's super smooth.
Just try. They picked you
for this, it won't be that hard.
Okay, I'll give it a try
then. Thanks a lot, Piang.
Apply it on the arm.
Hey, Sorn.
You're back.
I missed you so much.
Bet you missed me a lot, huh?
I missed you a lot.
And the souvenirs.
My snacks, Sorn.
Here.
You tease what did you even buy?
Just kidding.
This one's yours.
And this one's for Jie Poi and
Dad. Don't eat it all yourself.
Okay.
Kiss on the cheek to say thank you.”
What did you buy?
It's packed full.
And what's that lotion on your arm?
You got a rash?
No, not that.
Umm
I just took a product review job.
I wanted to make some extra income.
So I can help ease your burden.
Piangrak got me all of these.
Look, the whole table's full.
So, have you filmed any yet?
Hm.
I'm not confident, Sorn.
I'm scared it won't turn out good.
Do whatever you want.
Just be a good person.
But don't push yourself too hard, got it?
Mm.
Then take this upstairs for me.
Why'd you buy this?
You'll see.
Like this, Sorn?
Looks fun.
Yeah.
Ready?
Here, nice shot, right?
Yeah.
Think this would work as content?
Uh-huh.
Wait, is that food?
That way the comments will blow up.
Yeah, people cursing you out.
Just film it, no need to talk.
Skincare.
I see it now.
Jun.
Take these things upstairs.
It's all over the place.
Okay.
Give me a hand.
Can you manage?
Whoa.
Smells so good, Sorn.
Fried chicken.
Hm?
Why is it so salty?
I made it to eat with rice, not as a snack.
Try it.
Hey!
Why'd you bite my finger?
Mmm, Sorn.
How are you so good at cooking?
Teach me how to cook too.
Please?
No need, I'll just cook for you.
Mhm.
But if you're ever not
here, I can cook for myself.
And why wouldn't I be here?
I'll be with you till I die, Jun.
I've taken care of you this much.
I'm not leaving you that easily.
What are you even saying?
You're making me blush, you know.
And you're taking it out on me?
So you really won't teach me?
Nope.
What's with you?
Sorn
I'm washing the dishes.
I can do that later.
I forgot the condoms.
Hold on.
Harder, Hia Sorn.
Can you aim?
Ya.
Jun.
Huh?
Is that message in?
Probably about work… or maybe from Win.
Jun.
I think it's getting too much.
Watch out
maybe your house is on fire already.
Hiiiii~.
Today I'll have an.
Ice Latte
with oat milk,
large size
less sweet
please. Thank you...
Work again…
Win just texted me about it.
All done!
It's nothing
really…
Wanna keep playing?
This story needs to be expanded!
Preaw!
Hey Preaw!
I have an update for you!
This is
super secret, okay?
Guess who I saw today
I saw Sorn and Jun!
But not in a normal way, you know.
I saw them kissing on the cheek!!
Screams.
Ugh, girl!
Why'd you scream like that?
My eardrums are about to burst!
You ruined the mood.
I'm hungry…
Wanna grab something to eat outside?
Maybe they were just joking around,
you sure? And I'm not exaggerating, girl.
I saw it
with my own eyes fresh from my
LASIK surgery with 0.2 sharpness.
Plus, I was wearing
my angle grey contact lens.
No way I missed this.
Oh shit
they're here! Sorn and
Jun are coming gotta go!
Sorn, Jun~.
Hellooo.
Hi, P'Korn.
Hello, Jun.
Did you come to get coffee?
Well,
I was craving coffee,
so I came for some.
By the way.
P'Sorn.
Jun.
What are you two here for?
Play snooker.
Snooker...?
So...
P'Sorn and Jun..
Are you two dating?
Jun and I are dating.
Oopss.
But don't tell anyone, okay?
It wouldn't look good.
Oh, Sorn.
About this.
I'd never spill something like this.
You can trust me.
So…
P'Sorn
and Jun
are officially together now~.
Babe
what are you doing?
Speaks in Korean.
Coffee.
I
I gotta go now.
Byeee~.
Why did you tell him we're dating?
You know exactly what he's like.
What are you smiling for?
Why'd you tell Korn?
By tomorrow the whole company will know.
Exactly.
I know what he's like.
I actually want people to know that
you and I are together.
Didn't you say you don't like kid?
I don't just like you.
I'm crazy in love with you.
Why do you always make me blush?
Can I hit you back.
Nahh, let's grab something to eat.
Hello, Piang.
I'm sorry.
I was the one who introduced
the brand owner to you.
Who would've thought
he'd call you like that?
Hmm, whatever.
It's not your fault.
I already told him to mind his
own business, but he still messages.
What..Really?
Hey Jun
you mustn't
let Sorn find out
he's super jealous.
If he finds out, trust me, it won't end well.
I think the same as you do.
You..
What do you think I should do?
Just reject him.
Be direct
tell him you're taken.
Piang.
I already told him I have a boyfriend.
But he doesn't believe me.
You know I've posted
photos with Sorn on IG.
Why doesn't he just check my feed?
Then post more photos
make it obvious so he'll see.
You know me, I keep my IG aesthetic.
Ugh. Keep your aesthetic or
dump your man? Your choice.
Piang
why are you like that?
Fine, Bye.
My IG aesthetic comes first.
You asleep yet?
I miss you, Jun.
The sun might make your face warm,
but this message will make it blush.
Ugh, help me out here.
I wanted to message you all
cool, but in the end I just miss you.
Come on, back me up a little.
Oh my what is he doing?
I don't mean to bother you, I just
want to be on your mind all day.
What's his deal?
I'm tired of looking at a screen
I'd rather see your face for real.
Why are you sleeping shirtless?
It's hot.
If it's hot, then I can't cuddle you.
That's why I took it off
so we can cuddle.
Wearing a shirt makes it even hotter.
Can I bite you?
Gently.
Mhm.
Ah.
Ouch!
That hurt.
Can I say sorry?
Then let me bite you back.
Go ahead
but gently.
Too soft
you're scared of hurting me, huh?
My wife will get a mark.
I'll go to the bathroom first.
For what?
Can't I take care of something private?
I'll be quick.
Hurry back.
Um.
I miss you.
I'm back.
So...
The thing is…
Honestly,
the brand owner didn't text me about work.
He was..
He was actually flirting with me.
Please don't be mad at me, Sorn.
Please.
So what are you going to do about it?
I
I told him straight up
don't bother me, don't
mess with my personal life.
But.
I never wanted to hide it from you.
I was just scared that
if I told you directly..
You'd get mad like this.
And when were you planning to tell me
huh?
If I hadn't seen it myself,
would I even know?
Sorn..
There's nothing going
on between me and him.
You've read it all.
I clearly told him I wasn't okay with it.
Please don't be mad at me, Sorn.
I'm not mad at you.
Huh?
You already rejected him.
I saw the messages.
Then why'd you raise your voice just now?
I just wanted to tease you.
You're really not mad?
Mhm.
You're the sweetest.
But
what should we do about him?
I've got my own way.
Calling this late… you must miss me, right?
Hello, Jun? Why aren't you saying anything?
What's that sound?
Jun, what are you doing… with someone else?
No…
Why are you doing this to me?
Stop it.
Jun!!
P'Thanu
when did you get here?
Just now, when you saw me.
How many days are you staying this time?
I'll have Jun open up a room for you.
I'll be here a few days.
But I'll head into the city to
meet a new pharma factory
and also take care of some errands for mom.
No need to set up a room for
me. I'll crash at a friend's place.
Why?
What?
How could I sleep here?
You two make too much
noise when you… you know.
P'Thanu!
Wait,
are you really staying at a friend's…
Or with a.
A friend!
Keep your wife in check.
He's my sister-in-law, but he's
younger than me, you know.
Goodboy.
Huh?!
Hey P'Thanu
when you're at your friend's,
don't be too loud, okay?
Jun!
You're lucky Sorn's around.
So what?
I'm with Sorn all the
time. I'm not scared of you.
Yeah.
I'm out.
Too much sickly love here.
Go on then! Bleh!
And you go put your stuff away.