(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
Fuck this.
Did they really think
a newbie can kill me?
Don't you dare touch Matt.
Why do you still trust him?
He betrayed you
and your friends.
I'm begging you
save my mother, please.
Can we try to do something?
Can we try to save them?
Please.
Just this once.
I am still Supremo of this school.
I can choose who I protect.
Mr. President, you must not forget
the only rule of your position.
You must never get
involved with anyone.
You remind me of Lux.
You must know
I am not named Ace
without one.
After you remove the onion's skin,
do you know the next step?
- What?
- You dice it, of course.
Keep the blade away
from your finger then
keep slicing it.
You're so good.
Try it. Here.
It's looks to complicated for me.
Are you sure?
Come, Zein. You'll be fine.
You know.
I never tried to cook before
it's always mom or
Alison doing the cooking.
Me?
I'm the resident food taster and eater.
You'll be fine, Zein.
Come on, try it.
- Are you sure about this?
- Yes, I'll teach you.
If you say so.
How do you do it again?
Keep the blade away from your fingers.
Be careful.
- Like this?
- Yes.
That's it! Keep slicing it.
How did you do it? This is too hard.
You're doing great. Keep going.
- Like this?
- You got it.
There you go!
Tears of joy?
I'm really this happy right now?
Hey
why are you laughing at me?
Tears of joy, really?
Onions are really like
that huh, it's like love?
It makes you cry.
You're so corny!
- So corny!
- Why are you tearing up?
Who's crying?
Go on.
- How do you do it again?
- Just keep the blade away from you.
It's Hoy! Hoy!
Come back here!
I'll tell Vanessa to hit you again.
Hoy!
Hoy, wait for me.
Hoy, where are you?
Hoy!
Hoy...
Hoy?
Hoy!
There you are.
- Celine!
- Let's go!
Celine!
Celine, what's wrong?
- Celine, what's your problem?
- Just be quiet.
Zein, please.
Just be quiet.
Someone might hear us.
Who?
BBG
DGW
I don't know.
You're just wasting my time
if you're not going to make sense
can I go now?
What is it now?
Do you know?
The owner of this cat?
That cat
is owned by Lux.
Former Supreme Student
Government President.
Where's the former Supremo now?
He's dead.
He was killed
by Madam Violet
and Mr. Francisco.
Even Lux' girlfriend, Samantha
was murdered.
Just like Headmaster Valdez
who also happens ot be Lux's father.
He died.
All of them.
They murdered all of them!
You wanted to know the truth, right?
How did they die?
Only a few minutes left
until Bloody Night.
Please.
Please, just tell me the truth.
Let's meet here again at one
o'clock in the afternoon.
I'll tell you everything I know.
Don't do this, Supremo.
You'll just put yourself in danger.
I know.
You know the rules, Supremo.
You should've just punished her.
Ms. Kath is right.
You'll lose your authority.
I can live without this position.
What is your relationship with
Ms. Shion, Supremo?
She's my secretary.
I need to protect her.
And that's understandable.
But your position is on the line here!
We're just concerned, Supremo.
We don't want you in danger.
I don't care.
I can't lose her.
I need her.
We understand, Supremo.
I guess
it's better for now if we just
focus on the Foundation Day.
I don't care.
I can't lose her.
I need her.
Why am I smiling?
Has Celine's craziness
rubbed off on me?
Speaking of Celine...
Are you sure you really want to know
everything?
Remember that formula I
was telling you about?
There's more to it than that.
A lot of people are
interested in the formula
including Mr. Valdez,
Violet, and Francisco.
But Dr. Quizon was steps ahead of them
because he knew they
would eventually betray him.
That's why he stopped the experiment.
But the three got a hold of his plan
and devised a plan to steal the formula.
Mr. Valdez, Violet, and Francisco
murdered the headmaster
so they could steal the formula.
But that's not all of it.
As the second most powerful admin,
Mr. Valdez supported Dr. Quizon
with the aid of Violet and Francisco.
They continued the research
of the missing formula
and searched for the only person
who knows about the secret ingredient
to complete it.
I thought Mr. Valdez was against all of it?
Why was he interested in the formula?
Is it for power?
No!
It's not that!
He wanted to resurrect his
wife from the dead.
Mr. Valdez has a child.
His name was Luxury Valdez
the former SSG President.
Everything was going as they planned
until newbies arrived in this hellhole.
But Samantha charmed
everyone's hearts.
She became a big influence on Lux's.
The former dull Supremo
suddenly became full of life.
She convinced him to
speak with his father
to help them stop the violence
because it only causes everyone pain.
And it worked!
There was finally peace in the
university but it didn't last long
because of Madam Violet
and Mr. Francisco.
They implemented stricter rules
to the point of sealing the
university from the outside world.
After the deaths
of Mr. Valdez...
Lux... Samantha...
Hell University was sealed off again.
Who are you!?
Come back here!
Show yourself!
He went that way!
He ran over there!
Who are you!?
Show yourself to us!
Shit! Shit!
Shit! Shit! Shit!
Again?
Why are we here?
Where is he?
Do you know who that is?
I didn't.
I don't know.
I don't know his name but
I always see him around me.
And he's been following you!
What are you saying?
They're always monitoring us, Zein.
What?
Them?
Who are you talking about?
I don't know!
But I'm so scared.
Zein
if something bad happens to me.
Please
tell Supremo that I'm sorry.
What are you talking about, Celine?
I have to be sure!
This is the most afraid I've ever been.
Celine
Celine!
Wait for me, Celine!
Where are you going?
Celine!
Where am I?
You're at the faculty dorm.
What happened?
I saw you in the woods
unconscious.
Where's Celine?
I was with her in the woods.
But she left me.
Did you see her?
You're the only one there.
There was someone else there.
It wasn't just the two of us.
She left me and disappeared.
Celine!
I was trying to look for her but.
I can't remember.
Everything went dark.
Did you notice anything
different in the woods?
The secret lab?
Or did she say anything about it?
Nothing.
There wasn't a lab.
It was just trees and...
Where are you going?
My friends must be worried.
It's dangerous outside.
Stay here for the night.
Sorry, sir.
If I have no leads with
the hidden laboratory yet.
Don't worry about it.
It's not called secret lab
if it's easy to find.
Get some rest first.
Mia, what's your plan with my hair?
Just trust me
I'm giving you a new hairstyle.
Let me see.
Wow!
You did great!
Of course.
It looks pretty.
Do your makeup next!
You need to hurry so we won't
be late for the activities.
Mia
did you see my cap?
Cap?
Jerome misplaced it after borrowing it.
So careless.
Wow!
Look who's talking!
I'm not the only one who's
careless with my stuff.
I found it.
Here!
I saw it in the lobby.
Store your things properly!
Nice! Thanks, Van!
Hey!
It's too early
why are you in a daze?
Just let him be.
Zein looks beautiful today.
Don't just stare at her, bro.
She won't see your feelings that way.
If you really like her
make a move.
You know.
Dave's right.
Remember, bro.
If you make the first move,
you have the advantage.
Really?
You know what - What?
Stop it with your non-sense
You guys are crazy.
Matt?
Are you okay?
Or do you need something?
You.
You're the only one I need, Zein.
You look beautiful, Zein.
That's Matthew 101!
They look so cute together!
Right!
Zein
can I be your date later?
Um.
- Okay.
- Really?
You're sure?
Really? Yes!
Oh my god!
That looks cool.
Let's go?
- Is this legit?
- That suits you!
- It's looks so good. I want to try it.
- Are you okay, Zein?
Hold on. I need to talk to them.
Excuse me
have you seen Celine?
We haven't.
She's a dead kid, right?
Maybe she's drawing in a corner.
Okay, thanks.
Oh my god
Matt this suits you.
Where did Zein go?
Foundation Day!
Free Bloody Night later.
No weapons. No exemptions.
Hey, Zein!
What are you doing here?
Look at all the booths
you're missing out on.
Let's go!
Come on!
Let's go, bro.
Okay, we'll start with the bonfire first.
Then the fireworks.
I expect everything to be
executed in the right flow.
- Got it?
- Yes, Mr. Vice President.
But don't forget
tonight is free Bloody Night,
with zero tolerance
for weapons in the field.
Oh my gosh
you know
we should take a photo!
Camera! Camera!
Sure! Here is it.
Here you go.
Thanks, Jerome.
- Where should we face?
- Here, here.
One, two, three!
Say cheese!
Cheese!
Yey!
I'm excited to develop this!
It's nice to be in peace, not hell.
I know right?
I hope the gangs won't cause trouble.
The peacefulness of this
night will get ruined.
Speaking of the devils
they're here.
They're so many.
Matt
are you okay?
Why are your hands cold?
I was just tensed.
I was afraid they might cause trouble.
I know, right?
I was tensed too.
That was close.
Attention to all candidates
go to the backstage.
OMG Matt!
Are you ready?
Here he goes.
I hope so! Wish me luck?
- Let's go, bro!
- You can do it!
What is it? Why? What's happening?
- It's a secret!
- It's a surprise.
Are we really keeping secrets tonight?
Just tell me what it is!
- You'll find out later.
- Just let us have this.
You guys are so annoying.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go!
Okay, girls. Move backward a bit.
One step back.
More.
Perfect, next.
Okay, next boys!
- Straight ahead.
- It's starting.
Okay, good.
Keep walking forward.
Let's go, Matt!
- Let's go, Matt!
- Faster, guys! We're about to start.
See, I was right choosing Matt
as the class representative.
It's not his first time right, Zein?
- Zein, she's calling you.
- Mia was talking to you.
What?
Ah, you're right.
Matt's used to these things.
- Go Matt!
- Matt's kind of hot, right?
Huh?
Hot?
Wow!
Look who's being modest.
You can't hide your
giddiness from me, Zein.
So I'm your target tonight, huh?
Because your gaze has been
on Matt the whole time.
No, it's not!
You're getting flustered.
He's just good at this.
Zein's staring at him again!
He's on the stage, isn't he?
- Okay, fine.
- She has a point.
Candidates, we will start in a few minutes.
You can go back now.
Wish me luck.
- Hi Matt!
- Hi!
- Good luck, bro!
- Give it your best shot!
- Thank you, I will.
Good luck, Matt.
Make our section proud!
I'll do my best. I'll make you proud.
This is for you, guys.
Don't you have a good luck kiss for me?
What's that?
Just one kiss.
You don't know the
rules in this competition?
What rules?
I organized the rules for this event.
We're not breaking any rules.
There's actually one.
If you're one of the participants
you can't be kissed by
or kiss anyone.
Especially by your friends.
Okay, I'll just get a hug.
Not even a hug.
Is he sick in the head?
What a buzzkill.
Students of Hell University
the program will start in two minutes.
Thank you for your patience.
Alright
ladies and gentlemen
are you ready for the night?
Welcome to.
Hell University's
Mr. and Ms. Face of the Year!
Let us welcome our first candidates.
We have Rafael Montenegro
and Amara Castillo.
Next up, we have
Elias Navarro and Lucy Dominguez.
For our third candidates
let's give a round of applause for
Jason Villanueva and Serafina Reyes.
In fairness, all of them are hot.
Not really.
Our next candidates
we have Matthew Hart and...
Huh? Where's his partner?
Matthew Hart only!
Matthew! Mathhew! Matthew!
Go Matt!
Matthew!
Matthew! Mathhew! Matthew!
Try to beat that!
Supremo!
Rated SPG
viewer discretion is advised.
Supremo.
What are you doing?
I can't see anything!
Supremo!
I can't see!
Stop it. I'm want to watch.
Give it up for
Matthew Hart!
Matt! Go, Matt!
- Let's go, bro!
- Get out of the way!
Hello, Matthew Hart!
Please greet our students.
Get out of the way!
Move!
Hello everyone!
Good evening.
I'm Matthew Hart.
Go Matt!
Matthew! Matthew! Mattew!
Hold on, why are you alone?
Where's your partner?
Actually.
I have a partner but
she backed out last minute.
That's such a pity, Mr. Hart.
Zein, he needs a partner.
Too bad since you
seemed prepared for this.
Where are you going?
I'll disqualify Matthew Hart.
You can't do that.
He doesn't have a partner.
Me!
I'll be his partner.
Go Zein!
Zein! Matt! Zein! Matt! Zein! Matt!
Wow! What a surprise!
- Let's go, Zein! Let's go, Matt!
- Matthew Hart
and Zein Shion!
I'm Zein Shion.
Matthew's partner.
This competition's getting hotter!
Matthew Hart and Zein Shion!
You look beautiful.
What's he planning?
Announce our names! Now!
It looks like we have new candidates!
Let's give it up for Ace Craige
and Fritzy Saldivar.
What?
Supremo?
Let us all welcome.
Ace Craige and Fritzy Saldivar.
Now
you can look at me as
much as you need.
Eyes on me only.
Don't look at anyone else.
This is an order from the highest
Supreme Student Government.
You can't do anything about it.
To all our candidates,
please go to the backstage.
You may now take the stage again.
Let's give it up for
candidate number 1!
Candidate number 2!
Clap your hands for candidate number 3!
Candidate number 4, let's go!
Why are they together?
What are you doing here?
Why are you here?
Where's Matt?
What happened?
Why are you - I took his place.
I'm more suited standing next to you.
Why?
Do you want to be partners with Matt?
Do you want to see his body?
Pervert.
I prefer him to be my partner
compared to you.
Fine.
I admit it
you guys look good.
But you look better with me.
Last but not the least
candidate number 5!
Huh?
Everyone settle down
we will be announcing our winners
for Mr. and Ms. Face
of the Year momentarily.
Hell University, are you ready?
Things are getting exciting!
I will now announce the winners for
Mr. and Ms. Face of the Year.
For Ms. Face of the Year
we have.
Ms. Fritzy Saldivar!
What?
Freakin' rigged.
Congrats, Fritzy.
Congrats.
Thank you!
Oh my gosh! Thank you!
I didn't expect.
This is a mistake.
Ms. Shion should be the
new Face of the Year.
She's literally the most
gorgeous woman here.
Don't worry, Supremo
because you are
the Mr. Face of the Year!
Shut the fuck up.
I'm not interested.
Supremo, wait. I'm sorry.
Supremo...
Alright everyone.
Let's standby for the next activity.
Zein
are you okay?
I've noticed that you've
been restless since earlier.
Excuse me.
Where are you going?
Do you need me to come with you?
It's okay.
There's no Bloody Night anyway.
I'll be safe.
Where is she going?
Looking for me?
Don't be so full of yourself.
I know you too well.
Really now?
Are you ready to face your punishment?
Aren't you going to beg for your life?
You're willing to beg for
your other people's lives
but when it's your life
you can't do it?
I know you're position will be on the line
if you save me.
So don't save me.
And suddenly my position
matters to you, huh?
Just do the right thing.
What if the right thing for me to do
isn't the right thing for everybody else?
Cause it feels like
the right thing for me to do
is get you out of this university.
I'll get you out of Hell University.
No.
I don't want to.
You don't understand, Zein.
I'm willing to do everything.
I'm this close.
I don't want you harmed.
I've been involved in this from
the moment I entered this place.
If you'll force me to leave this place
you can just kill me now.
I'm not leaving without my friends
and the students.
This administration is fucking up.
I take back what I said.
I won't push through
with your punishment
in one condition.
You must be mine.
So I can protect you
be with me.
I will make you my world.
What's going to happen
if I allow myself to be yours?
As long as you're mine
nothing else matters.
Because
you'll be my everything.
It doesn't matter
nothing else matters.
It doesn't matter where life takes us.
You'll be my everything.
You'll always be my everything.
I have nothing to lose
because you're all I want.
Zein
where have you been?
Isn't that the mark of
the Black Blood Gang?
Why was she killed by the BBG?
Are you involved in Celine's murder?
Answer me, Matt!
This is the new member of BBG?
Where's your toughness now?
Do you think your gang
will be here to save you?
Aren't you afraid, Supremo?
When you lose your position
you can't protect her.
Eat.
I'm not hungry.
And I still have a lot to do.
Eat it.
Or else.
Or else what?
If you're an enemy
you'll probably be dead.
Are you the enemy, Supremo?