I’m now in charge of the MV thing.
Do you want to help me,
so you’ll be hanging around that area?
You're such a liar!
You said you’d have me do the work
so I could stay with Thame.
Bringing up the MV
and pressuring you like this
isn't to get you to meet Thame.
It's all for your own benefit.
Guys,
here comes a big problem.
Would you mind
If I fell for you?
Don’t tell me you all teamed up
just to revive that song
and use it to negotiate with me.
I'll create a new song under MARS.
If my song beats Ice's song,
we'll all get to go there.
I’m sorry.
I rushed there, but still
couldn’t make it to the movie in time.
I told you already
I didn’t want to break our promise,
but here I am, breaking it again.
It’s fine.
I’m actually more surprised that you came,
while such a serious problem
just happened.
How could I forget?
Well…
By the way,
what about the song that got stolen?
I talked to the company already.
We have to make a new song.
What a shame.
All that was left was releasing the MV.
I feel even worse for you.
You worked so hard on the MV.
Hey.
Why are you worrying about me?
You should be worrying about MARS.
Aren’t you already
worrying about that for me?
Hold on.
Where is the storyboard?
I think I left it in front of the cinema.
Oh, where you were sitting, right?
- I’ll go get it for you.
- Hey, don’t.
It’s fine.
How come?
It’s full of great ideas.
I’ll go get it for you.
It’s fine, Thame.
You should head back
and talk to your members.
Just drop me off here.
I don’t want to take up
too much of your time.
You're not taking up my time at all.
Go back, okay?
All right.
But…
let me know when you get home.
Yeah.
What are you doing here?
I should be asking
why you’re here at this hour.
LOVE YOU TO DEBT
Would you mind if I fell for you?
There’s no one next to you?
You’re making me breathless, baby
I'm so damn pissed off.
I went as far as selling my soul
to make this song.
Look at the choreography.
It doesn’t look right at all.
Ours is even better.
Turn it off already,
or it'll get stuck in everyone's head.
We need to clear our minds
and refocus here.
PRODUCE A SONG
Back to square one.
What do we have to even compete with him?
That song is about to top
almost every chart.
I bet it'll hit a perfect all-kill
in no more than a week.
Based on our timeline,
how many days do we have left?
We only have one week left.
Wow. How impressive.
So, does anyone have any ideas?
What are you doing here?
I should be asking
why you’re here at this hour.
Where is Po?
He went back already.
If you have to write a movie review,
then head inside and watch it.
Forget about that for now.
We need to talk.
I’m not available.
I do.
I want to make a love song.
But Ice just made one.
Won't it be too similar?
Let’s just make it different.
- You’re getting on our nerves.
- I’m not.
To play safe, a love song
is the best choice, isn't it?
This style of song is easy to mainstream,
catchy, and people get into it.
Plus, love can take many forms.
We can just make it different.
What kind of love song
do you want to make?
Is it like, "You stepped in
and changed my life?"
Something like that?
That sounds like a good idea.
"Become a better person for you,
instead of that previous guy,
who was good for nothing."
So, you two are still
talking about the song, right?
- Yes.
- No.
I’m not bringing personal stuff into work.
But the idea you just proposed
is your personal matter, isn’t it?
Are you trying to find an idea
for the song,
or start a fight with me?
I’m not trying to start a fight with you.
But I just want to clear things up
with you about…
Who’s here?
I’m enjoying their conversation, you know.
Oh. I guess it’s Po.
- I’ll…
- I’ll go.
Hey, come. Let me help.
Hey, let me carry some myself.
Why are you here?
Do you want me to help
with your full-time job again?
I do.
Well,
Mick assigned me to film
the footage of you all
praising Ice’s song.
Damn. That's such a black comedy.
Turn on the camera now.
I’ll do a diss rap to get him embarrassed.
Calm down, Dylan.
Sit down.
Don’t hurt him.
I bet someone like him
was clueless about the whole thing.
Perhaps the situation was like…
WOULD YOU MIND?
This is such a great song.
It feels like it was written
for my comeback.
Yeah.
We composed it especially for you, Ice.
He’s just a clueless bystander, you know.
We can record it now.
Do you have scripts for us?
Yes.
But we don’t have to rush.
Let’s eat first. I bought a lot of food.
- I’ll help you then.
- I’m good, Thame.
Just continue what you’re working on.
I’ll let Jun help.
He’s free.
- Am I right?
- Yeah.
Let’s go.
I’m free now. I want to help.
All right.
You’re free?
You have to produce a new song
and also a bunch of new stuff.
How could you say you’re free?
Why don’t you work on the MV then?
It’s your job, isn’t it?
I have to wait for the song
to be finished first, don’t I?
Also,
I’m in charge of the welfare service,
you know.
That’s such an intense atmosphere.
When are they going to punch each other?
Dylan!
What?
Jun, go arrange the table.
Thame and I will take care of it here.
Eh?
You asked me to help you, didn’t you?
Come on.
What did you argue with Jun about?
It isn’t a big deal, is it?
It’s a big deal.
Eh?
Do you want me to help clear things up?
It’s all right.
If you get involved,
it’ll get even more serious.
Yeah?
It’s all right. Don’t worry.
- And…
- I’m done arranging the table.
Bring me more plates.
Ask Thame to do it.
He’s standing close to that.
Thanks.
- Who said you can eat first?
- Come on.
It looks yummy.
I’ll take this one.
- I’m hungry already.
- It’s not yours.
Who is this for?
Give it to me.
Hey, give it back to me.
I can’t choose which side to take.
That guy is my friend,
and so is the other.
- True.
- I’m rooting for Thame for sure.
Someone like me
will never take sides with Jun.
No way.
No.
Are you saying this
because you don’t want Jun to date Po?
Eh? Of course.
Someone like Jun
isn’t supposed to date anyone.
Well, then, I’m going to root for Jun.
My sense says there’s chemistry
between them.
Can I take that one?
Give me, okay?
Are you sure there's chemistry?
Uh-huh.
I’m trying to look for it.
Where are you going after this?
- I’m heading home.
- Already?
Do you seriously have no ideas at all?
I don’t have any.
His life is so chaotic.
How could he come up with anything?
Eh? Why?
I’m just reading the atmosphere, you know.
But it’s true, Thame.
If you let it go on like this,
won't it just get worse?
Be careful, or you might end up
losing both your friend and your job.
- And you’ll probably…
- You’ll probably lose Po, too.
Hey?
I didn’t tell these two anything.
But Jun and you are obviously overacting.
I didn’t mean to keep it a secret,
but it’s Jun
who didn’t agree to talk it out.
So, the problem is Jun again, right?
Jun always avoids problems.
Don’t you know that?
Think about it.
When he wanted you to go to Korea,
he didn’t tell you directly,
but ended up causing so much chaos
that everyone turned their back on you.
Are you still going to keep
someone like this as your friend?
So, are you trying to stir things up,
or are you just showing off
that you know Jun best?
I’m stirring things up!
Thame.
What do you think the reason is
that he won't talk to you?
Po.
Oh, I’m done filming
all the footage of MARS.
I’m working on the storyboard now.
I wasn’t going to ask you about that.
I was going to ask
who gave you those snacks.
Yeah?
Those.
Here you are.
Eh?
How could you know it’s my favorite?
I’m someone who cares.
I stalked your IG stories.
I don’t do things half-heartedly, okay?
How annoying.
You’ve just started working here
and already become so popular,
unlike someone here,
who’s been here forever
and still not hot at all.
- Why are you insulting yourself?
- I’m insulting you.
Stop it.
You know what? I'm hot too.
I’ve got some hitting on me,
even if the one doing it sucks a bit.
Ugh.
I’m also curious about
how good-looking that person is.
He’s more good-looking than you,
obviously.
Eat that!
By the way, can you tell us who?
It’s nothing. It’s just…
What do you want to eat?
I’ll buy some for you.
If you don’t reply,
I’ll let you eat trash.
It’s just someone who wants to tease me.
I see.
Are you being arrogant?
You’ll get to eat trash for sure.
Eh? You like sandwiches, don’t you?
I’ll grab some for you.
His favorite sandwich
isn’t from this store.
Why are you avoiding me?
Why don’t we just talk properly?
- We have nothing to talk about.
- We do.
About what? You’ve finished
working on the song, huh?
Not yet.
But I’ve already got an idea.
Why? What’s not good about my idea?
I just want to present
my idea to you first.
Go ahead.
Can we talk somewhere else?
Why do I have to play
this stupid game with you?
It’s because this is going
to be a long conversation,
both about the song
and Po.
(official website: www.kisskh.la www.kisskh.co and www.kisskh.id other than this are fake)
Why did you avoid me?
Me?
- I didn’t.
- Really?
Say whatever you want.
Stop pressuring me already.
If you want to say something, just say it.
See? I’m not avoiding you anymore.
If I did, I wouldn’t be standing here.
- Why did you go to see him at the cinema?
- Because I thought you wouldn’t go.
But I did!
- I saw that.
- This is what you want, huh?
Don’t act like you know me well.
But I do know.
Someone like you
has never done this much
for someone else before.
You helped him with the subtitles
and the idea for our MV concept.
You like him, right?
It doesn’t matter how I feel.
It’s you I should be asking.
What do you even see him as?
You use him without even knowing
what he’s skilled at.
Have you ever even noticed his potential?
You kept asking him to do nonsense stuff.
You wanted to thank him
by just giving a free movie ticket,
and on top of that, you tried to use him
to write a movie review for you.
Stop nitpicking me already.
Someone like you should back off
and stay in your place.
If you can’t take care of him well,
then just don’t do it.
Otherwise, he’ll end up
facing the same thing as before.
You don’t even have feelings for him.
What if I do?
OPPOSITE MAKRO SATHON
I think you’ve already realized that
since you saw me at the cinema.
That’s why you’re acting
this way towards me.
I don’t know what’s more annoying for you.
Me not being the kind of person
you thought I was
or the fact that we both
like the same person.
So, you want to be
this straightforward, right?
Yeah.
Fine.
Come up with some excuses now.
You like him,
but why did you treat him like that?
Why does he have to revolve around you,
your life, and your work
without even caring about what he wants?
I’ve been trying.
You must try harder.
At least you should know what he likes
and what he can do.
You must be able to support him.
Look at you also.
If you like him, stop avoiding me already.
Others are already worried
that we’re having conflict.
But I think I know
you’re not that type of person.
Really?
I think you know that
this isn’t about losing
or winning,
but this is what
makes us realize
whether we’re true friends.
And are we?
What do you think?
We’re standing here,
scolding each other like this.
And what about that song idea
you mentioned?
I just told you, it’s the song.
Huh?
I think it’s a perfect fit for you,
me, and MARS.
How?
Here you are.
Why have you been so quiet this week?
Don’t tell me Mr. A and Mr. B are secretly
dating without letting me know.
Date? Nonsense.
I’ve got so much extra work recently.
Do you want to come and see where I’m now?
Don’t challenge me, okay?
You know I can really go.
By the way, you mentioned before
that you wanted me to help MARS.
So, what is it about?
I’ll send you the brief
but I’m not sure when,
and I’m also not sure
if we’ll still get to do it.
Fine. Just let me know.
I’ll be on standby.
LET'S GO
Po.
Just a few days and MARS managed
to get this much done?
What do you think?
It’s incredible.
It perfectly fits your group.
But…
is this really Thame’s idea?
It’s this great,
but you still don’t believe it’s his idea?
I’m not saying I don’t believe it’s his,
but I’m just surprised.
When it comes to Thame,
I thought he would come up
with a song about friendships,
giving off a heartwarming vibe.
I didn’t expect this style from him.
I want our song to deliver these messages,
"Just do whatever you want to do."
"Be persistent in chasing
what you desire."
"Feel what you truly want to feel."
"Go after what you want…
without worrying about anything else."
If you also have feelings for him,
I think we both stand an equal chance.
Even though we have been friends
for so long,
neither of us has to back down, right?
By the way,
do you think the footage of us
can be used in this song somehow?
Let me see.
Whether he chooses him or me,
it’s not anyone’s fault, is it?
We still remain friends anyway.
So, this is the fairest way
for the whole thing.
You really like him, don’t you?
I know I’m not doing well enough,
but I’ve been trying.
For everything I just scolded you, right?
Yeah.
Otherwise, he’ll choose you.
If you can promise me that,
let me tell you something.
If we film the new line sync,
I think it will work.
But I want to show this to Thame first.
Eh?
I thought you were going to accuse me of
jumping to conclusions about Thame again.
I won’t scold you anymore.
Why?
It’s because I’ve realized
you’re not just imagining it on your own.
What do you mean?
I just talked to him,
so I realized
he does have feelings for you.
I don’t have feelings for him.
All I did is just to let you know that
when you like someone,
don’t be a loser.
It’s nothing much,
but I just don’t want to see you
being a lousy partner.
Honestly,
from spending time with him,
I’ve realized he also likes you.
Congratulations.
You’ve won this game,
even from the start already.
You silly.
Who told you to confess love
on someone else’s behalf?
Eh?
Then why did you both
tell me about it, huh?
Ugh, you’re just…
Tell me where Thame is.
Whoa. Do you have to be
in a rush to see him?
I’ll show him the MV.
Why should you be in a rush?
Seeing him today,
I guess, at most, you’ll just end up
staring at each other.
I’m telling you,
during the first six months of dating him,
even holding hands is an achievement.
And it will take two whole years
before you two get to kiss.
As for going to his room,
I’d say it will definitely
take up to five years.
I told you I’m going to show him the MV.
Tell me where Thame is now.
You’re here?
Yeah.
Well,
I…
I’ve finished… the MV draft.
Do you want to take a look?
Are you sure this is the first thing
you want to talk about?
Well, yeah.
I think if we add a line sync,
it will work just fine.
What do you think?
I really like it.
You’re not just saying that
to please me, right?
I mean it.
It’s amazing.
I can’t believe that
with our limited amount of footage,
it can turn out this well.
You’re talented.
You are.
Your song is good.
That’s why I could edit the MV well.
It’s like you planned ahead
that this song
would fit the footage we have.
Am I right?
Well, let me forward it to my members,
so they will know what to work on next.
Yeah. Go ahead.
I’m going to grab my stuff.
I already talked to Jun.
Well,
I met him already.
You did?
What did he say to you?
So… what did he tell you?
He said
you like…
our new song a lot.
Exactly. I really like it.
I enjoyed it so much when editing it.
So…
What did he tell you?
He said
you like…
our MV a lot.
Yes. I really do.
But…
we watched it together just now,
haven’t we?
That’s right. You just watched it.
So…
What did Jun tell you?
He said…
you might be waiting for me here.
Why here?
I remember that every Monday and Tuesday,
you have to come and help Uncle Joei here.
I also remember our movie date promise.
Here.
I always have them with me.
I’m sorry I’ve been busy recently.
It’s all right.
You don’t have to say sorry.
You already said sorry for this.
But…
I haven’t made it up to you.
It’s totally all right.
Po,
can you not say, "It’s all right"?
From now on,
just make a request.
Tell me what you want
or what you want to do.
I’ll try to make it happen.
If you're angry,
just tell me straight up.
I'll make you stop being mad.
Let’s begin it this way.
Begin what?
What do you want to begin?
Begin…
Let’s begin by watching this movie.
I want to watch the movie today.
Okay.
Let’s go.
Today is the 3rd.
Eh?
I’ll book the tickets then.
It’s all right.
I think it's already out by now.
That's how a special screening works.
Po, I’m sorry.
It’s all right.
I know you’ve been busy.
Po.
I told you to stop saying,
"It’s all right".
I also said
I want us to have a good start.
Hey,
I’m not that serious about it.
Actually,
this movie was shown in a special theater,
but it's also available on streaming.
We can watch it anytime.
But…
I don’t want our beginning
to be these expired movie tickets
or something that disappoints you.
Well,
let’s watch another movie.
No.
I want to watch this movie with you.
You said it’s
on the streaming platform, right?
Yeah.
So…
can I watch this movie
in your room tonight?
Others might see us.
Really?
Yeah.
Since I’m doing this,
nobody will see it, okay?
Anyway,
there aren’t many people around here.
I didn’t expect you
to do something like this.
Well, someone told me
not to treat you badly.
That’s why I want to do everything well.
You… talked to your friend about me?
Yeah.
Well…
We talked a bit.
He told me…
not to disappoint you.
Also,
I don’t want to keep you waiting anymore.
Oh…
I see.
Actually,
there are many things I want to do,
but let’s start with watching this movie.
What do you mean by "many things"?
Well, it’s just many things.
But before we arrive at your place,
let me stop by to buy something.
You can wait here.
- Just one box, right?
- Yes, please.
Just one box, right?
Thank you.
What should we do to make MARS’ song
beat Ice’s on every chart
by the end of this month?
Do everything we can!
Yep, man.
This is just perfect.
Since it’s our first time,
I’d rather see your face clearly.
When I'm outside,
I have to keep my distance from you.
It's really frustrating.
I’ll come to see you again tonight.