This is great.
Public opinion has
shifted from your resignation
to the technical difficulties of
Qingniao and Minghui Groups.
It's triggering deep
reflection across the industry
on basic computing power and
core technological independence.
That's exactly what
we wanted to express.
Now we just have to see if it works
and if everyone agrees to
the mobilization of computing resources.
Shen Gu.
Hello?
Well done,
Producer Song.
You too.
I'm sorry.
I have still made you worry
about the company matters.
You should be proud of me.
I am very proud.
You must not have
rested well last night.
It's my fault.
Then, Mr. Shen,
why don't you write
a long apology to reflect on it?
Fine.
I'll keep reflecting
until you're satisfied.
Let's talk later.
Hello.
Miss Xu.
Your speech just now
was brilliant, Miss Xu.
If Raymond Technology can team up
with other tech companies today
to pressure Yinghai Group,
they will use the same
tactics to suppress us tomorrow.
What we need now
is a stronger resistance against them.
Miss Xu,
you really taught us a lesson today.
We all understand that if one falls,
the rest will follow.
Mr. Fang, I'm sorry
about what happened last time.
We have considered it thoroughly.
We can sign the contract right now.
That's right. As long as we join forces,
I don't believe Yinghai Group will
give up the entire East Asian market
just for Raymond Group.
Thank you for your trust.
Let's show them
the meaning of absolute unity.
Good.
Let's officially launch
the Emergency Mutual Aid Agreement.
Thank you for joining voluntarily.
Let's complete the first batch of
computing power transfers before dawn
to support the Spark system.
- Alright!
=Echoes of Gang City=
Alright.
That's wonderful.
=Episode 24=
(By Your Side in This Life)
Having you all by Wanxin's side
is her good fortune.
Wanxin has been at
our TV station for eight years.
I care for her like my own daughter.
Wanxin, let's get down to business.
Qingniao Group's technical staff
is stranded at the airport.
Mr. Fang has
already gone to resolve that.
But what we need now is
to coordinate and mobilize resources,
equipment, and talent from peers
to handle the emergency for Qingniao.
We need a large amount of capital.
Wanxin, you don't need
to worry about that.
I've already spoken with my mother.
She will provide
enough funds to support us.
Mr. Fang,
we can't let your
family bear all the risks.
I've discussed it with Grandfather.
We've decided to use
group equity as collateral
to complete the formal
loan approval process.
Wanxin, no need for collateral.
The Song Group will also
mobilize all available funds
to help you.
Qionghua,
Wanxin's intention is also mine.
We invited you here today
to convey these decisions to you.
Count me in.
Dad,
I know my elder brother
is better than me
and smarter than me.
But after all, I'm also your son.
It has already come to this point.
I can still tell who is on our side.
If we need equity collateral,
then so be it.
If it's not enough,
you can include my shares as well.
Uncle Zhaohui,
thank you.
No need to thank me.
This is what I should do.
Come, you should sit down too.
I invited you here today
because there is one more thing to say.
I want to introduce someone to you.
Boss,
the first batch of resources
from Miss Xu and Lawyer Fang
has departed from Gang City
and will arrive at headquarters soon.
From the current state
of the computing system,
it's enough to support the continuous
operation of the Spark system.
But
we currently don't have
a suitable technical team.
Expand the search area.
With these allocated
resources as support,
it has already bought us a lot of time.
Raymond Group and Junlin Group
are competing with us for talent
using equity incentive plans.
Raymond Group is
an established tech company.
Judging from the current situation,
whether it's in terms of employment
or future scientific research results,
we are at a disadvantage.
Shen Gu.
Dr. Sun.
This is my husband, Shen Gu.
Hello, Dr. Sun.
I've heard so much about you.
Hello, Shen Gu.
Wanxin told me
everything about your situation.
We are willing to join forces with you
to carry out technical development
alongside Minghui's results.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, everyone.
Li Yan.
Dr. Sun, please come inside.
Wanxin,
thank you.
♪The clouds hide the faint light
behind them♪
♪A lonely bench on the street corner♪
♪Where all feelings come to rest♪
♪In the night sky, the moon's trail♪
♪Stitches up and soothes my sorrow♪
♪The courage to get close to you♪
♪Drives away my hesitation♪
♪Fate turns and brings us together♪
(Qingniao Group)
♪Love is so sudden♪
♪You, in the album♪
♪Shine through my past like starlight♪
♪You fall between light and shadow♪
♪Melting all my fears away♪
♪Those youthful, naive memories
are more than enough to heal♪
♪I'm lost in them♪
♪The world suddenly has meaning♪
♪Through the pouring rain, I found you♪
♪In the space of our embrace♪
♪Stars spill across the sky♪
(Qingniao Group)
♪Stitches up and soothes my sorrow♪
♪The courage to get close to you♪
♪Drives away my hesitation♪
♪Fate turns and brings us together♪
♪I search my memories with all my might♪
♪Love catches me off guard♪
♪You, in the album♪
♪Shine through my past like starlight♪
♪You fall between light and shadow♪
♪Melting all my fears away♪
♪Those youthful, naive memories
are more than enough to heal♪
♪I'm lost in them♪
♪The world suddenly has meaning♪
♪Through the pouring rain, I found you♪
♪In the space of our embrace♪
♪Stars spill across the sky♪
♪You fall between light and shadow♪
♪Melting all my fears away♪
♪Those youthful, naive memories
are more than enough to heal♪
♪I'm lost in them♪
♪The world suddenly has meaning♪
♪Through the pouring rain, I found you♪
♪In the space of our embrace♪
♪Stars spill across the sky♪
Mr. Tingyuan,
what are you worried about?
There has been no news at all
from Shen Gu and his team.
I'm just afraid...
Don't worry.
Right now, all the technical
personnel in the world are in our hands.
Do you know how much
manpower and resources
we spent to build
the technological barrier?
Shen Gu and his team won't be able
to break through it in a short time.
Besides,
we are using
the lawsuit to stall for time.
Yinghai has an excuse to
keep cutting off Qingniao's supply.
We'll wear them down sooner or later.
Good.
Hello everyone.
This is the news scene outside
the headquarters of
Qingniao Group in Shen City.
The facade of the building behind me
is covered with giant dynamic posters
of the Spark supercomputing system.
After experiencing
a unilateral supply suspension,
Qingniao Group today
officially announced to the world
its self-developed
supercomputing solution,
marking a breakthrough
in key technologies
within the field of
high-performance computing.
The Spark system
uses Qingniao's original
quantum-state encryption technology
and deeply integrates Minghui's patents.
The tested computing density can reach
80 percent of Yinghai's capacity.
In other words,
we have successfully broken
through a major technical barrier
in the field of AI computing power.
The cooperation is by no means limited
to Minghui's technology licensing.
(Spark, Minghui Group, Qingniao Group)
Relying on Qingniao's Spark system,
Minghui Group's biotechnology team
has made a breakthrough.
AI pathological identification achieves
digital quantification in 30 seconds.
Promoting the development
of digital pathology
has become a perfect practical case
for Qingniao Group in other fields.
Qingniao and Minghui
have built a deeply
integrated strategic community.
Both parties have formed
a technical closed loop in areas
such as computing
infrastructure and bio-intelligence,
jointly promoting
future intelligent upgrades.
Finally,
I would like to thank you,
Ms. Xu Wanxin,
for the support you
provided to Qingniao.
Today's research results from Qingniao
would not have been
possible without your help.
(Spark, Minghui Group, Qingniao Group)
♪Tonight the rain falls soft and slow♪
♪Blending with letters left unread
drifting through the air♪
♪You turn and look back at me♪
♪In those same eyes familiar tears
quietly appear♪
♪It feels like we have carried so much♪
♪So many questions time itself
could not make clear♪
♪The moment you walked into my life♪
♪Every dream I had became something
I want with you near♪
♪How many letters have I written
just for you?♪
♪If only you could truly hear
what my heart is trying to say♪
♪From this life on
no distance could keep us apart♪
♪The promise we made♪
♪Will find its way to be fulfilled
one day♪
♪But I want more
than just that fleeting gaze♪
♪Still I have not heard your answer♪
♪Can we still rewrite the ending
we face?♪
♪When regrets begin to turn around you
will hear it all♪
♪Everything that leads me back to you♪