(Lee Je Hoon)
(Jang Hyuk Jin, Bae Yoo
Ram, Kim Eui Sung, Pyo Ye Jin)
(Taxi Driver 3)
(This drama is a work of fiction.)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(Children and animals were
filmed under guidelines.)
How long have you been with the unit?
Eight months, sir.
The mission was a failure,
and you died in action
just eight months in?
And you, instructor? How
long have you served?
- Six years.
- And you died after six years too.
Attacking me after
you're dead doesn't count.
I wasn't dead yet.
I stabbed you as I was dying.
Consider it my dying message.
But, sir...
What if I were to say I saw
her stab you before she died?
Am I going to get in trouble?
What's your name?
Sergeant Yoo Sun A,
Counter-Terrorism Team one, sir.
- Everyone, fall in!
- Yes, sir! All right, fall in!
Hey, on your feet.
Did anything about this
operation strike you as odd?
Sergeant Park Jae Won, sir.
Sir, I believe the hostage's
safety wasn't the priority in the plan.
We could've been the
ones who killed the hostage.
That's precisely what blinded you.
One simple feint, and half
of your unit was wiped out.
Any idea why?
Because you all assumed
the hostage you took
was your get-out-of-jail-free card.
You figured if things went south,
you'd use them as a human shield.
But if the hostage dies, the
mission's a failure, right, sir?
If I really intended to rescue them,
I'd have secured them first, not
entered from the opposite side.
I came through the main gate,
blocked your escape and engaged.
My objective for this operation
wasn't to rescue the hostage.
It was to annihilate all of you,
the hostage included.
So, if this were a real combat situation
and you realised the enemy
wasn't protecting the hostage,
but was instead cutting
off your escape routes,
the very first thing you should do
was quickly get out of there.
If you can't run, then
with your last dying breath,
take down at least one more of them
with everything you've got.
Your final stand will
instil fear in the enemy.
And that fear will spread like wildfire,
becoming a coat of armour
for the rest of your team.
- Understood?
- Yes, sir!
On that note,
I want you all to learn from
Sergeant Yoo's final action.
Check your personnel and
gear, then return to base.
We'll cover the rest in the AAR.
- Salute!
- Unity!
Unity.
At ease.
(Seoul 24M 5283)
(Taxi Driver 3)
- How can I help you?
- Hi.
This monstrosity was delivered to my house.
(Military Manpower Administration
Notice of Active Duty Enlistment)
Yes? So?
I was honourably discharged
from the military over a decade ago.
All right, let me just check that for you.
I'm telling you, when I saw this,
I was so shocked, my heart jumped.
- I'm checking. Please have a seat.
- Right, sure.
Mr. Park Jin Eon?
Yes.
(Subject eligible for active duty)
But I see no record of prior service.
(Building a Korea proud
of its military service)
What record?
Your completed service
record. It's not here.
And what happens if there's no record?
You'll have to enlist again.
- Go where?
- The military.
No way!
I'm sorry. Sorry about that.
- I'm telling you, I already served!
- Sir, please calm down.
How am I supposed to stay calm? How?
You're saying I have to enlist
again just because there's no record?
To someone who's already served ages ago?
Wait, your enlistment date was yesterday?
That makes you AWOL. We'll
help you enlist immediately.
What kind of twisted thing is that to say?
What's going on?
You're reporting for duty. Now.
Reporting for duty? No, wait. Hold on!
Hey, wait! I think there's been a mistake.
No personal excuses.
I'm telling you, I already did my time!
(Active-duty enlistment)
Have a good tour of duty.
No! I can't go!
No!
- What do you mean, "no"?
- I'm sorry.
- Why are you screaming?
- I'm sorry. I just...
Go Eun.
Gyeong Gu.
What kind of dream
makes you scream like that?
Hey, look. You're
breaking out in a cold sweat.
It was a dream! It was all just a dream!
Gosh, that was intense.
Goodness. Such a drama queen.
- Did you dream you got drafted?
- Yes.
For real?
I kept saying it was a mistake,
but they dragged me off to the army.
- That must've been terrifying.
- Totally.
- Want to hear an even scarier one?
- Scarier than a draft notice?
Way scarier.
Because this one actually happened to me.
I love scary stories.
Hey, where are you going? Come on.
Do you really have to
set the mood like this?
Spooky.
My senior and I
were on guard duty at the gatehouse
when over in the washroom
at the HQ barracks,
- a soldier was dancing like crazy.
- Dancing?
So my senior
asked me what I was looking at.
What?
I said, "See that guy over
there, dancing his heart out?"
He said he couldn't see anyone.
But I could see him clear as day.
We went back and forth all
shift, and when we were relieved,
we went to the command post to report in.
Right after we reported in,
I told them what happened.
And that's when
the sergeant major
told me that ten years
ago, in that exact spot,
a new recruit had hanged himself.
- What?
The way the body was swaying,
it must have looked like dancing.
Ever since then,
they say anyone who saw the
soldier has either died or gone insane.
But you saw him.
I guess it doesn't count if
you can't see him clearly.
Actually, it was quite far,
so I couldn't see clearly.
- I don't think so.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- That explains it.
- Explains what?
It probably followed you here.
Driver Kim Do Gi! How
long have you been here?
I've been here the whole time.
I had no chance to slip away.
- Gosh.
- You scared the life out of me.
You were?
Why lie about being
followed? That's creepy.
But it is true.
It's probably following us now.
- Are you serious?
- Okay, never mind. It isn't scary.
Gosh, that's not funny.
It's not funny at all.
Gosh.
- What?
- What's this?
Do ghosts really exist?
Captain Kim Do Gi.
It's been a while. Have you been well, sir?
Park Jae Won.
- Have you been well?
- Yes, sir.
- Have you been well, sir?
- Yes.
I've never seen you take
the afternoon off, Driver Kim.
Mr. Jang is out, so I couldn't tell him.
I'll let him know for you.
All right, enjoy your time
off. See you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow.
Jae Won.
I told you to wait in the
car. Why did you get out?
I'm perfectly fine, sir.
- You haven't eaten yet, have you?
- No, sir.
I know a few great restaurants,
so let's pick one on the way.
I'm good with anything, sir.
Has Driver Kim Do Gi ever
had a visitor here before?
No, never.
His rank is Master
Sergeant. Gosh, that's so cool.
- Driver Kim Do Gi looks so happy.
- Yes.
He must've been really happy to see him.
Master Sergeant Park,
what are you in the mood for?
You still like ginseng chicken soup?
- You even remember that, sir?
- Of course.
You and Master Sergeant Yoo
insisted we go for ginseng chicken soup.
What about Master Sergeant Yoo?
How's she doing?
You should've brought her with
you. I haven't seen her in ages.
I assumed you hadn't heard the news, sir.
Master Sergeant Yoo Sun A
is dead, sir.
The thing is...
That's why I came to see you. I
need your signature on a petition.
(Petition)
Master Sergeant Yoo Sun A...
Where is she now?
(The Late Yoo Sun A)
Mom!
Will you be returning, sir?
No.
Please come back when this is over, sir.
Even if I did come back,
there's nothing left for me to teach you.
Even if you have no more to teach,
I still have much to learn from you, sir.
I'll be waiting for your return, sir.
I will
also be waiting, sir.
- Salute. Unity!
- Unity!
Requesting to return to duty.
Oh, this place has great coffee.
- I thought our coffee was the best.
- It's in a class of its own!
Gosh, look at the shine on this car.
Driver Kim is going to love this.
- The number you dialled is off...
- Why is his phone off again?
(2 weeks later)
Is this it?
Yes, this is the taxi
Driver Kim was driving.
For him to just abandon his taxi,
something serious must've happened.
Exactly. And his phone's
been off this whole time.
For now, could you two take the taxi back?
I'll grab the nearby CCTV
footage and then head back.
It looks like he's paying
his respect, doesn't it?
Sergeant Yoo Sun A. She
served with Driver Kim Do Gi.
Sergeant?
But she's a Master Sergeant in that photo.
The records say she went
AWOL from a training site,
and died in an explosion while fleeing.
She was posthumously disciplined
and discharged as a private.
Wait, that's a little strange.
No matter how severe
the disciplinary action,
to demote someone that many
ranks is highly unusual, isn't it?
Seriously, what could
she have possibly done?
Either way, it seems Do Gi
disappeared because of this,
but I'm just wondering
if looking for him now
is the right thing to do.
That's been weighing on my mind too.
From the way he even ditched his phone,
Driver Kim didn't go
missing. He chose to leave.
It's almost like he's telling
us not to look for him.
Have a safe trip. See you tomorrow.
Yes, see you tomorrow.
He said he'd see me tomorrow.
Mr. Jang, did you send this page?
No, I just got the page
and rushed down here.
Go Eun, was it you?
If none of us sent it,
then this message must
have come from Do Gi.
But why send a page
instead of just showing up?
Maybe so we wouldn't worry?
Then he would've called, not sent a page.
Something must've happened to Driver Kim.
We have to go find him right now.
I agree. We have to.
We absolutely have to go!
Of course I want to go. But
we don't know where he is.
I did some more digging.
Master Sergeant Yoo's last
unit was a temp one, Unit 280.
And there's one more thing.
This is the exact spot
where Driver Kim sent a page.
But there's nothing there.
That's right. The area's
blurred out on Street View.
It has to be a military base.
In that case, that's most
likely where Do Gi is right now.
CEO, you once said that there are victims,
but no perpetrators in two
places. Hospitals and the military.
We have to find Driver Kim now.
But how do we get onto a military base?
Civilians can't just go waltzing in there.
It's a problem. What on
earth are we going to do?
Hey, Go Eun. Any bright ideas?
The military? I know nothing.
What would...
Driver Kim do if he were here right now?
If Driver Kim were here
I think I know what he would've done.
What?
Chief Park.
I'll let you punch me 100 times.
What?
- Go Eun.
- No, wait, make that 200.
An Go Eun!
- No way. I refuse to go.
- Why refuse without knowing?
I don't have to. I already
know what she's about to say.
You're going to ask me
to re-enlist, aren't you?
No.
Whenever you feel like it,
you can hit me for the rest of your life.
No way. I can't. I won't. Absolutely not!
Please just hit me!
I'm not going. I can't go!
Over my dead body!
(Warning: Failure to
comply will be met with fire.)
(For our country and our people)
We've filled personnel shortages.
We got transfers for supply and mess,
and one of them is a new recruit.
- Private First Class Park Jin Su.
Put your bag down.
Run in place.
Run.
- Gosh, this is the last one.
- Is this the army or a summer camp?
You've all been through a lot getting here.
From now on, this is your home.
- Take them to their barracks.
- Right this way.
Yes, sir.
That's right.
I came here to find Driver Kim Do Gi.
Once I find him, this will all be over.
What's with that guy?
I heard he just re-enlisted.
Excuse me. I'm actually
looking for someone.
- Is there a Captain Kim Do Gi here?
- Has this guy gone mad?
What? Is the captain your buddy?
That's right.
We're the same age, so I act
casual, but he keeps things formal.
I think there's been a misunderstanding.
I know the army pretty well.
My service number starts with 11.
What about you two?
What do yours start with?
What's the status?
Still no word from him?
Yes, his comms are still off.
- I bet it's still in his bag.
- Don't worry.
Jin Eon will be doing just fine.
This isn't his first rodeo.
I was wrong, sir!
I forgot I was in the army!
I was wrong!
What? You "forgot"?
Hey, this jerk...
When he's done with his
punishment, throw him in the brig.
I'm sorry!
I was wrong! I'm sorry!
So I guess facing the military
alone is impossible after all?
Looks like I'll have to go in myself.
You, sir?
Security's going to be tight there.
How do you plan on getting in?
When you get to be
my age, it's not that hard.
Halt.
(For our country and our people)
Sir. May I ask what brings you here?
What kind of question is that?
I'm here to see you do your job.
What is it? Who's that?
- And you are, sir?
- Me?
General...
Unity!
What are you gawking at? Are
you opening this gate or what?
Hey, you want me to just leave?
- What is it? Who is he?
- He's a general!
My apologies, sir!
What are you doing?
Open the gate for him, now!
- Salute!
- Unity!
All right. Carry on.
(For our country and our people)
- Guard post, com sec.
- What is it?
- A VIP's on base.
- On the ground!
- Sir!
- On your feet!
(Special mission code of conduct)
(Garrison)
(Rear supply unit)
(Operational plan)
Getting some screenshots.
(Executive meeting,
senior staff meeting minutes)
- Unity!
- As you were.
The commander...
The commander has stepped out, sir.
I see.
So, you're not going to ask why I'm here?
First Lieutenant Lee Hyung In.
With all due respect, sir, may
I ask what brings you here?
What do you think? I'm here to see my son.
You have a new recruit here
named Park Jin Eon, don't you?
Park Jin Eon?
I'll go myself,
and bring him here.
- Go ahead.
- Unity.
Unity.
(Sgt. Yoo Sun A and seven others)
Looks like there's
something useful for us here.
There's no information
here besides Area B24.
It's nearing the Demarcation
Line. This is unsettling.
Anyway, I'll do everything
I can to find Driver Kim.
But I bet Mr. Jang has no
idea where to even begin.
Instead of just sitting around here,
we should go in and help find him.
Into the military base? Us?
And how are we supposed to get in?
We'll just waltz right in, of course.
What?
And get a warm welcome while we're at it.
(Special Mission Unit Rules of Conduct)
(Special Mission Code of Conduct)
Unity.
Unity!
- You little punk!
- Mr. Jang?
It's your old man.
My dad?
Let me get a good look at you.
You little punk. You've gotten all chubby.
Looks like the army life
suits you, you little rascal.
Stand up straight. Lead the way.
Show your old man
around the base, will you?
- Then I can escort you...
- No. If I asked for that,
- I'd be pulling rank.
- Lieutenant...
Lead the way. Go on, you little punk.
- Unity.
- Hurry up, punk. Keep it up.
One, two.
Let's get a move on.
Unity. This is First
Lieutenant Lee Hyung In.
It appears a general officer just arrived.
A general? Why would one come to our unit?
- He said he's here to see his son.
- What are you talking about?
If a general's son were in
our unit, I'd know about it.
He insists that it's his son
- I'll look into it. Hang up.
- Unity.
He did call him a little punk, though.
Corporal Ma, do you listen to Elements?
They're awesome.
Elements? They're sick.
They're my all-time favourite.
(Armed Forces Welfare Agency)
(Unity Club)
(For our country and our people)
How did a convenience
store get all the way out here?
I never thought we'd see
one at a temporary post.
Come on. Let's check it out.
(Temporary Post: Unit
for a specific mission)
(Stop)
- Hello, sir.
- Yes, sir.
- I'll go check over here.
- All right.
Driver Kim, are you in there?
Hey, form a line! One at a time.
You're going to hit it with your
rifle. Gosh, look at these guys.
- Get out of the way.
- Let's go.
- Thanks.
- I'll take this one.
Go Eun, now!
(Armed Forces Welfare Agency, Unity Club)
(Special Mission Code of Conduct)
Unity, sir.
You're a new face.
- What's your unit?
- I'm from the Intel Division.
I'm here for a system check.
I see.
- First Lieutenant?
- Yes, sir.
And I'm a Captain.
First Lieutenant An Go Eun.
Appreciate all your hard work.
- What do you think you're doing?
- Is something wrong, sir?
I said, what are you doing?
I thought it was the
right greeting for this unit.
I was just following your lead.
- Did that bother you?
- Has she lost her darn mind?
If you don't like it,
then don't treat people like that.
Got it?
Unity.
Darn it.
- Unity. Yes, Commander.
- Unity.
Captain Kim Do Gi should
have reported here recently.
Let me check for you, ma'am.
Driver Kim Do Gi.
Driver Kim, you in there?
Do Gi, are you there?
- I don't think he's here.
- Let's check the next floor up.
- Okay.
- Yes.
Yes, I understand. Unity.
Hey.
HQ says no general's
son was sent to our unit.
So who did you just let in?
Sir?
(Soldier's Personnel File)
You punk, where is your head at?
Go catch that darn impostor now!
Yes, sir. Unity!
Darn it.
Now what is that? Darn it.
Unity.
Go Eun.
- How did you get in here?
- I just waltzed right in.
And...
What?
These are the keys to the Deluxe Taxi.
Driver Kim was here.
All right, anyone seen
our Driver Kim Do Gi
I mean, Captain Kim Do Gi?
Raise your hand if you've seen him.
You'll get a free box of soy milk.
Me, sir!
- I have.
- You've seen Captain Kim Do Gi?
- I'm the one who cleans his room.
- Come out and get your free case.
(Vegemil High-Protein Soy Milk)
(Armed Forces Welfare Agency, Unity Club)
Unity.
Take us to Captain Kim Do Gi's
room, and I'll give you another free box.
- Everyone, stand back!
- Move!
- Out of the way!
- Move it!
- Hey, what's going on?
- Move aside! Get out!
Don't shoot!
I'll tell you anything! Ask
one thing, I'll tell you two!
Just don't shoot!
(Establishing Military
Discipline, The 2802nd Unit)
Mr. Jang! Jin Eon, Go Eun!
Are you guys here to rescue me?
We got captured too!
Right.
Please don't shoot!
So these jerks are all in on it together.
Who are you people?
I'm only going to ask
you this one more time.
Who are you people?
(Unity Club)
(Welcome)
What took you all so long?
Do Gi.
Glad you could all make it.
(2 weeks earlier)
It's in the Civilian Control Zone,
so I'll need military credentials.
A company-grade officer
can only re-enlist within
three years of leaving.
But you're well past that deadline.
Even if we get you in, it'll
be flagged immediately.
So forget the two weeks you asked for.
You won't even last two
days before it's voided.
Here.
An endangered Black Eagle's
nest was found in the border region.
(Eagle Nest Found, Border
Region Emergency Survey)
So we need someone to spend three weeks
identifying and surveying the habitat.
How about it?
Think you can handle it?
Thank you. I won't burden you any further.
Burden? Not at all. I'm
the one asking for a favour.
Okay. Take that car back there.
Everything you need is in there.
Yes, sir.
Halt!
Lights off.
Engine off.
Driver, exit the vehicle.
Turtle.
- Ladder.
- Who goes there?
Captain Kim Do Gi.
State your business.
On assignment. I've spoken
with the duty commander.
- Captain Kim Do Gi has arrived.
- Yes, let him through.
Yes, sir.
- Copy that.
- Identity confirmed. Unity.
Unity.
We weren't expecting you
today, so your room isn't ready yet.
We were told you'd be arriving tomorrow.
Don't worry about it. I can sleep anywhere.
So, what mission are you here for?
I'll brief the unit commander
on the details tomorrow.
Is the office all set up?
Yes, sir.
You of all people know what
Sergeant Yoo Sun A was like.
(Petition)
(Victim: The late Sgt. Yoo Sun A)
I'll be in touch.
I'd like you to come back then.
Understood.
- He came last night?
- Yes, sir.
So where is he now?
He wanted his own room, so I
gave him one of the empty ones.
He said he'd introduce
himself this morning.
He should just do his job and leave.
What's the point of an introduction?
Unity. Apologies for the late introduction.
Yes. You had a long trip.
- I hear you arrived last night.
- Yes, sir.
The room's great, by the
way. It gets a good breeze.
Right.
And the reason for your assignment is?
(Colonel Kim Tae Hyun)
(Eagle Nest Found, Border
Region Emergency Survey)
(Urgent Survey Team to the Border Region)
Surveying birds?
Yes, sir.
What kind of bird?
- Black Eagle, sir.
- It's an eagle?
They were thought to be extinct,
but a nest was recently found.
But
- why send you for a bird survey?
- I may not know about birds,
but I know the border ecosystem very well.
So what happens if you find this bird here?
It's an endangered species,
so we'd have to protect it.
So if it becomes a protected
area, we can't fire our weapons?
That's highly likely.
We're better off if it's not
here, even if it is, right?
Anyway, if you need
anything, let me know, okay?
This is my house,
so don't go wandering
around like you own the place.
Thanks for your consideration.
Right. Do you need anything?
Do you want me to assign a soldier to you?
That's all right. I've
already called someone in.
Unity!
Speak of the devil.
He'll be rooming with me,
so you don't have to worry about a thing.
(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
Yes, sir.
I haven't eaten yet,
so if you haven't either,
would you care to join me?
I'm good.
There's a jjamppong place
near the entrance. It's really good.
You should go try it.
Thanks for the tip.
Unity.
(Advanced barracks, elite special forces)
(Establishing discipline,
accomplishing the mission)
Captain, I knew you'd call on me,
but I never imagined it would
be for something like this.
- Let's get food first.
- Yes, sir.
- You drive.
Hey.
What do you think they're really here for?
He said he was here for the
protected species research.
"Protected species," my foot.
You don't think so?
He was a Special Warfare
instructor, he's led operations,
and he quit after years of overseas intel.
You think he's here for
birds? Give me a break.
Tail those jerks and find
out what they're really up to.
- Dig in.
- Yes, sir. You too.
This jjamppong is pretty good.
It is, sir.
I looked over the internal report
on Master Sergeant Yoo's charges.
During a training exercise,
Master Sergeant Yoo abandoned her squad,
and drove a truck full of
weapons into North Korea.
No way...
That's impossible.
Going AWOL from the
training site, theft of weapons,
and attempting to contact
North Korean officials.
She was demoted three
ranks, one for each charge.
Captain, do you
really believe Master Sergeant
Yoo would do something like that?
Could you do it, Master Sergeant Park?
Commandeering a truck,
stealing strategic weapons,
and coordinating a time and
date with a North Korean operative.
All in less than a week
of being deployed here?
I don't think even I could pull that off.
Quietly meet with the squad members
who were with Master Sergeant Yoo.
All eyes will be on me for a while,
so you shouldn't have any trouble.
Yes, sir.
One more thing. Do senior
officers get temp posts?
No, sir.
Actually, I thought that was strange too.
A colonel living in the barracks
instead of his own quarters...
Isn't that pretty unprecedented?
Exactly.
So do we really have to look for this bird?
Well, it's not like they're
going to believe us anyway.
Gosh, this jjamppong is really good.
It's so good, sir.
- Was that good?
- Yes. Gosh, I'm stuffed.
Good.
Captain, where are you going?
Looks like he's from my unit.
Why is he taking my picture?
I'm not a bird.
Go tell your commanding officer.
Unity! You called for me, sir?
We got a message from Captain Kim Do Gi.
We did?
Hey, read it again.
Your jjamppong suggestion was great.
Please recommend more great spots.
Also, I need a bird-watching
camera, so I'll borrow this and return it.
Thank you for being so thoughtful.
No matter how you slice it,
it looks like that jerk, Kim
Do Gi, has an ulterior motive.
- I'm sure of it.
- I'll see what he's up to, sir.
Report the second you find
anything, even if it's at dawn.
Yes, sir. Unity!
- Unity!
(Investigation Team)
All the squad members' statements match.
They said on the way to the op zone,
Master Sergeant Yoo Sun
A told them all to get out.
Get out.
- Get out now!
- Yes, ma'am! Understood!
Everyone, dismount the truck.
Move it! Out!
- Yes, ma'am!
Effective immediately,
you will all return to base.
- We must have misheard you, ma'am.
- You heard me, didn't you?
Everyone, return to base!
- Yes, ma'am! Understood!
They didn't seem to be lying, sir.
Could Master Sergeant Yoo
Sun A really have done that?
(Results: Explosion in Operation Area B-24)
Those reasons listed for her demotion...
Could they really be true?
The answer to that
is one you've already
given, Master Sergeant Park.
Yes, you're right, sir.
Master Sergeant Yoo
Sun A would never do that.
I'm absolutely sure of it.
I agree.
Unity.
Who's in charge of the
vehicle movement logs?
The transportation unit co-manages them.
What's the logging
interval? Every five minutes?
Yes, sir, that's correct.
And the reporting cycle to command?
It's automatically updated
every three weeks, sir.
That's perfect.
Get me a copy for this date.
- Right now.
- Right now, sir?
You must be busy betting
your pay in the barracks.
Master Sergeant Park, why don't you get it?
Yes, sir.
Gambling on duty?
He seems busy. I'll get it myself, sir.
No, sir! I'll go get it right this second!
Really? Then you'd
better be quick about it.
Yes, sir!
- Unity!
- About-face!
On the double!
By the way, Captain,
how do you know all that?
Know what?
That vehicle movements are
logged in five-minute intervals.
They're mostly logged to
evaluate training performance.
- But isn't that data classified?
- It is.
But I'm the one who used to
grade the performance evaluations.
I reviewed those logs and
gave you the best score.
You did?
Unity!
These are the vehicle movement
logs for the date you requested, sir.
- Thanks. Good work.
- Unity!
- Unity.
- Save your pay and be a good son.
Unity!
Let's use this to retrace her
steps on the day of the incident.
And see what she was trying to do.
So that's why you asked for the
logs from the day of the incident.
You never know.
Her route might tell us
what happened that day.
Right.
Unity!
You'd think people studying
birds would have at least one photo.
Is there a problem, Colonel?
If you're here to investigate birds,
you should be focused on them.
So why are you digging into
a dead woman's business?
Why are you snooping on a
traitor who betrayed her country?
Since you've asked, allow
me to ask you something.
How did you know she
was dealing with the North?
- What?
- You couldn't have met either side,
- and you weren't there, were you?
- Hey.
Do you need to be next to
a fire to know it's burning?
You can tell there's a fire
by the smoke from a distance.
Aborting the mission on her own,
disobeying orders, sending men back,
then loading weapons into a truck
and heading North. It's obvious.
Just seeing that smoke,
it's clear she was playing
with fire, don't you think?
I see your point.
Hey, Kim Do Gi.
- Yes, sir.
- I'm sure I made myself clear.
Don't come into my house
and act like you own the place.
What's your real reason for being here?
Who sent you?
I believe I already told you. A
Black Eagle nest was discovered...
Cut the nonsense, you jerk!
Black Eagle, my foot!
I have to get back to the
nest, so if you'll excuse me.
Unity!
(Bird investigation)
But I guess a bird's nest is
someone else's home too.
This is awkward.
And by the way,
people don't really put photos up on walls.
Not when you have one of these.
Unity!
That arrogant jerk...
A measly Captain has the nerve...
Sir, what should we do?
He must have someone backing
him up to be so cocky, don't you think?
I'm going to go see the General.
(Special Warfare School)
Stop here for a second.
Yes, sir.
What is it, Captain?
On the day of the incident,
Master Sergeant Yoo had
her team exit the truck here.
Everyone, dismount the truck.
Move it! Out!
- Yes, ma'am!
She took the right fork.
What? But this is Sector B24.
Why? Is there a problem with that?
On the day of Master
Sergeant Yoo's accident,
my team was also scheduled
with an artillery unit for a live-fire drill.
And the target for that drill
was right here, in Sector B24.
(Military Demarcation Line,
Special Mission Unit's Area of Ops)
- Let's go.
- Yes, sir.
Sector B24 starts here.
(Military Demarcation Line,
Special Mission Unit's Area of Ops)
(Special mission code of conduct)
Master Sergeant Yoo
was here for ten minutes.
Only this spot right here is empty.
It looks like she couldn't move
everything on the shelf at once.
Instead of going to the base,
Master Sergeant Yoo went
up this path to the north.
Yes, that's what the report said.
That she took the weapons north.
Master Sergeant Yoo didn't
go north to sell the weapons.
Her original route back was blocked,
so she couldn't get through.
What?
Darn it.
Back off, you jerks! Are you
disobeying a direct order?
Since her escape route was blocked,
she tried to find an alternate route.
If she sought a new route, like you said,
she had to be panicking.
This path is a dead end at
the Military Demarcation Line.
And there's no way Master
Sergeant Yoo didn't know that.
Or did she head that way
knowing it was a dead end?
With her escape route blocked,
Master Sergeant Yoo would
have done the only thing she could.
The only thing she could?
Captain Kim Do Gi!
I have a question.
There are times in the field
when our mission objective
is to acquire certain intelligence, right?
There'll be plenty of those in the future.
Let's say we've acquired
critical intelligence,
but on our way back to base, we
run into an unavoidable problem.
What do we do with the intel?
Your safety comes before the intel.
If your safety isn't guaranteed,
you abandon the critical intelligence.
But if, despite all that,
you find yourself in a
life-or-death situation,
you pass on the intel
using our team's protocol.
(Landmine)
Captain, you should watch your step.
Master Sergeant Park, search this area.
Yes, sir.
What is that protocol?
Find the bird's nest in
the closest tree due west,
and secure the intel inside it.
A bird's nest?
They're sturdy, they have good drainage,
and they're hard to see from the ground.
I see.
Master Sergeant Park!
Sir!
I'll check it out.
I found it.
(Landmine)
If anything should happen to me,
I'm trusting you to find this.
Captain Kim Do Gi.
Master Sergeant Yoo
Sun A sacrificed herself
to save her comrades.
(Special thanks to Jeon So
Nee for her guest appearance)