I heard you're talking to someone, Sun.
Is it the guy named Earth?
Why are you doing this, human?
I also like what you like.
MORNING.
Ongsa, are you Earth?
How should I feel about you, Ongsa?
I must admit that I'm not sure.
That's why I'd like to
get to know you again.
Hi. I'm Sun.
I'm Ongsa.
It's nice to meet you, Sun.
Hi, Ongsa.
Hi, Sun.
Dear Lord! Can Thailand be any hotter?
It's a fact of life.
Where are you heading?
The library.
Where are you heading, Ongsa?
I'm going that way to buy some Kanom Krok.
Okay. I'll see you later then.
Okay.
You go this way.
I'm gonna go this way.
Okay. I'll go this way.
-Bye-bye.
-Bye.
What was that? What's up with those two?
We were standing here together.
How would I know?
Damn it. Why is it so hot today?
It's like it's preparing me for hell.
I think because the weather is scorching,
people are going insane.
Screw it. It's hot out here.
Let's go to class and get some air-con.
Ongsa? Can I sit with you?
Of course. Why wouldn't you be able to?
What's going on? Are you blushing?
No, I'm not.
Yeah? Then why are you afraid
to look at me?
I'm not afraid.
If you aren't, look at me.
Why are you smiling?
Because you're cute, Ongsa.
Don't smile. You're making me flustered.
Why would you be flustered?
You're pretty smooth in the chat,
but super shy in person.
Honestly, this is quite new for us.
Sun.
What's up?
Sorry, I'm not as chill in person
as I am online.
Don't be. You're also cute this way.
I'll try to be more chill like this
when we're chatting.
Can I have your phone?
What's the passcode?
2-2-0-6.
We're using the same passcode.
Really?
What a coincidence.
Totally not a coincidence.
I set your birthday as my passcode.
Sun, wait a minute!
This is
my photo.
Do you like me that much?
Yes.
But I'm afraid you'll feel uncomfortable.
Just tell me if you feel uncomfortable.
I don't.
Should we take it slow?
I…
I don't want you to feel uneasy
around me either.
Here.
Do you want some Kanam Krok?
Is it Kanom Krok-Sun?
Charoen.
Charoen, you devil.
Cha-roen. Charoen!
I'm talking to you, Charoen.
Why are you not talking to me?
Charoen, Charoen, Charoen.
Charoen.
Yes, Ongsa?
Can we please switch seats?
Why?
Is it a bad feng shui there?
It's not like that.
I just want to have a different vision.
I could use a different vision too.
Thank you.
Here I am. Your new vision.
It's all right.
I'm ready to take down a demon.
Did you just imply I'm a demon?
-Yes.
-Take me down if you can.
Have you eaten?
Class.
I have an update on our Sports Day.
You're looking forward to it, right?
-Yes!
-We are.
This year, our class will be on Team…
Team…?
Team…
Blue.
Yeah!
Our main duties are making the props
and decorating the bleachers.
-Class president, please look into it.
-Yes, ma'am.
Does anyone want to be a cheerleader
or a drum major for Team Blue?
-I do.
-Me too.
Okay. Dear and Vi, stop by the recreation
department and write down your names.
That will be all from me.
Thank you, ma'am.
Hey.
Don't you want to audition
for cheerleader?
Are you nuts? Me?
Why not?
I don't dance.
And I don't have guts.
I'm also not pretty.
I'll just help with all the shit jobs.
That's right. I agree.
I'll just do nothing but look at hot guys.
What a dirty soul.
All you care about is men.
Stop talking. Don't let me catch
you also eying someone up.
-You're sinful.
-What do you want to do?
-No, you're sinful.
-I'm not. You are.
-You're shameless.
-What? You did not just say that.
You're foul-mouthed. That's sinful.
What are you smiling at?
Smiling? I'm not.
-You're not?
-No.
"No"?
Lying is a sin.
I saw you smile just now.
No, I wasn't.
Thank you for taking me home.
Ongsa, will you help?
Step on it.
One, two, three.
You don't want to go home just yet?
No, I don't.
But it's dark.
I don't want you to get home late.
It's unsafe and inconvenient for you.
Whatever.
I will take you home no matter what.
But…
No buts.
Especially when it's late like this,
I must take you home.
And my house is just over there.
But I'm afraid
you might get into an accident.
Well then,
why don't you let me spend the night?
What?
What about your clothes?
I can just wash them.
And while you wait for them to dry?
Well,
I can wear your clothes.
I'm blushing for my shirt.
I'm kidding.
I'm blushing too, you know.
So,
can I crash here?
Luna, where are you going?
Can you please let me spend
a few nights at your house?
My house?
This annoying human senior
likes to make me do things her way.
I'm helping Aylin
with Sports Day stuff for her team.
I want Aylin to help her classmates,
but I don't trust her to do it on her own.
So, I'm here to keep watch.
And you two humans…
Are you girlfriends now?
Hey! No. It's not like that.
What's this assembly in front of my house?
Hey, Luna.
-Good evening, sir, ma'am.
-Hi there.
-We're talking about…
-Hey!
It's nothing.
Luna is spending the night here
to make sure Aylin takes part in
the Sports Day prep.
See?
Aylin participates
in human activities now.
What? What was that?
Yes. We must celebrate. For Aylin.
Then I will throw you guys
a feast tonight.
I'm gonna go help my mom cook.
Hold on.
Come here.
Not so fast, little sis.
I heard something.
Are you two…
girlfriends?
Uh, well…
About that, you can ask Ongsa.
I'm gonna leave now. Bye.
Ride safe, Sun.
Now. Tell me everything.
It's…
What's that?
This kid.
Come on in.
Ongsa!
So that's what it's all about.
You were depressed
and disappeared because of Sun.
Alpha, I'm sorry
for not telling you anything.
Next time, fill me in, okay?
I'm actually annoyed
that my friend knows more
about my sister than I do.
Hey. Ongsa told me not to say anything.
Right. I asked Luna not to tell.
I was afraid you'd yell at me.
I'd yell because
you didn't tell me things.
You're lucky nothing bad happened.
So, what's up with you and Sun?
Exactly.
You like each other.
You have feelings for each other.
But you're not girlfriends.
Are you guys in a talking stage?
I think we're beyond a talking stage.
Are you, like, seeing each other?
Not yet.
So, what kind of
relationship status is it?
Then let's just call it a "question-mark"
relationship status, human.
I don't get why
you two are being unclear about it.
If you like or love each other,
put it out in the open.
Why are you hiding it?
I'm afraid people will badmouth Sun.
Besides, Sun has never dated girls before.
Are you saying that you're afraid
that people will have a low opinion of Sun
if she dates a girl?
And I'm not sure
that I'm good enough for her.
Sometimes I even think
Sun doesn't tell anyone
because I'm not good enough.
Don't say things like that.
Why wouldn't you be good enough?
Right. And Sun would never have
that kind of thought.
You're the one who knows her best.
Then what should I do?
Why did you take me here?
Ongsa.
-Come.
-Sit down.
I heard from my pals that you,
my ex-girlfriend,
feel unconfident about your looks.
What?
I…
I will boost your self-confidence,
self-assurance,
self-esteem,
and self-love.
Huh?
So, what's your plan?
-I'll get her on the palanquin.
-What?
What palanquin?
Team Blue is still looking for
a pretty girl
who will wear Thai traditional dress
and sit on the palanquin.
I'm gonna be your mentor
on your road to being the school star
on Sports Day, sweetheart.
Ton, no. Let's not do that.
I can't do it, Ton.
But I can.
Ta-da!
Are you going to war, Ongsa?
We aren't stationed
at a historical war outpost.
Change the outfit, honey.
Now. Go.
Damn it.
Lift her hair on that side.
-What?
-You're burning me.
Luna, don't you burn my sister.
-It was you.
Here we go.
Damn.
She looks like a banana tree ghost.
We're all set.
Luna!
-You said straight hair.
-I said curls.
You said straight hair.
-What are you talking about? I said curls.
-No, we had an agreement.
"Curl it" is what I said.
We're in the theme "Colorful" this time.
Every color is here.
Blue, yellow, green, and red.
But Ongsa is on Team Blue.
Go change.
-This is blue right here.
-And what is this color?
Go change. Change.
Okay. Let's start on this side.
Ongsa.
Ton, what are you doing?
I'm training Ongsa to be a school star.
You know how to do makeup?
Don't worry, Sun.
For Ongsa, I can do just about anything.
All right, Ton. I brought clothes
of every color from the art room.
You can choose.
Goodness! None of these colors is pretty.
-Go change.
-None of them are pretty?
No. Go change.
-Damn it.
-Why don't you go get what you want?
Hey, Sun.
What's wrong?
You seem kind of mad.
No.
I'm not mad.
Good then.
Can you help us pick the costume
for Ongsa?
Come on.
-Come.
-Sure.
Which one should we go with?
Sun, is something wrong?
You look stressed.
No, nothing is wrong.
I'm fine.
CLASS 6: NIDA'S MINIONS
IS THAT TON AND ONGSA?
-YES!
-ARE THEY GETTING BACK TOGETHER?
WAIT A MINUTE!
Goodness gracious!
Sun, what's going on?
Nothing.
There was a mosquito. So I hit it.
It was annoying.
You hit it so hard
even its soul must have been squished.
The Sun is burning strangely hot today,
don't you think?
Hot weather today.
Do you think?
Yeah? More like hot-headed.
What?
I mean
the weather is so hot that
my head feels hot too.
Right?
It's hot.
Ongsa, let me see the brows
Ton drew for you.
I think they look weird.
Next time, let me do your brows for you.
And from now on,
don't let anyone draw your brows for you
except me.
Got it?
Do you think
I can be the one on the palanquin
on Sports Day?
I don't feel confident anymore.
Of course you can.
You're beautiful and cool.
You will kill
in a Thai traditional costume.
Ongsa, sweetheart.
Oops.
Sorry, Sun.
Can you please make room for me?
Scoot over.
Scoot over now.
Thank you.
All right. Ongsa.
Trust me.
Team Blue is going the win
the Best Parade award.
You're exaggerating.
So?
My heart truly believes that
you're the most beautiful girl.
Ongsa!
Crash at my place tonight.
Ongsa.
Let's get to class.
Come.
What do I do?
I'm freaking nervous!
Ongsa.
Here. Let me try putting makeup on you.
All right.
What makeup tones do you like?
Orangish or pinkish?
Crap.
What are orangish and pinkish?
I don't know.
You pick.
Okay. I'll do what I feel like.
I want you to be confident.
About what?
About yourself.
I don't want you
to feel inferior to anyone.
You're a beautiful,
cute,
and very good person.
But I don't know
if I'm good enough for you.
You are who you are
and that's more than enough for me.
Let's add more.
This is my favorite lipstick.
Yeah?
Nice color.
Let me put it on you.
I…
I haven't fed Latte yet.
I don't think I can crash here tonight.
I should go home.
Ongsa.
Here, take it.
It's okay. It's yours.
But it looks better
on your lips than mine.
Thank you.
Should I take you home?
Oh, no, it's fine.
It's just nearby.
I can manage.
Oh, I forgot.
Bye.
Goodnight.
Bye-bye.
Let's get on TikTok.
Sun One Day Vlog.
Swoosh!
-Does Dear look kind of different today?
-What are you doing?
Shit. Ongsa's got a new look.
Wow, Ongsa.
What happened?
Is something wrong, guys?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Ongsa.
You look drop-dead gorgeous today, girl.
-What an overstatement.
-It's true.
What's your lipstick? It's so pretty.
Well…
Sun gave it to me.
-Ton.
-Hi, Ton.
How are you, Ton?
Ongsa, sweetheart.
The bougainvilleas are blooming.
So, I took some for you.
Ton, can I ask you something?
Of course, Dear.
Are you really hitting on Ongsa?
Please give me time to think.
Let's just say that
Ongsa is special to me.
Ton, people might get the wrong idea.
How can they get the wrong idea?
You really are special to me.
Thank you very much, Ton.
Charoen.
Are you leaving?
Are you going to your class now?
That's right.
Come on, Tinh.
I'll see you later then.
-Ton, I love you.
-Ton!
See you, guys.
-Bye, Ton.
-Bye.
Ton!
What do you want to eat?
I should grab something to eat
after all my gaming.
Charoen, you're supposed to
make them even.
How about you do it yourself?
My duty is to make the pom poms.
Yours is to cut, so cut.
Do your job.
Ongsa? Are you okay?
Sun's been acting weird all day.
Do you know why, human?
-I think I know.
-Know what?
Sun doesn't like my new look.
I did it the way she taught me.
I wore the lipstick.
I did my hair.
Ongsa. Where are you going?
The bathroom.
So, she still has no clue Sun is jealous?
Damn. It's so obvious.
Even someone living on Mars could tell.
True.
The jealousy is brighter than xenon light.
Exactly.
It's clearer than the facts of life.
Humans are the cleverest
sentients on earth.
But sometimes,
they can be unbelievably stupid.
Hey, Aylin.
Aren't you on Team Green?
Why don't you go help your team?
Tinh.
I like this team.
Me too.
Mawin, where are Ton and Alpha?
They're rehearsing
their Sports Day opening speech.
Where is Ongsa?
She isn't here yet?
Human Aunt dropped her off
at four in the morning.
Guys.
-Ongsa.
-Whoa.
Is it not okay?
No!
It's not okay?
No one is more beautiful than you today.
You're killing it, girl.
Let's take some photos.
Hold on, Tinh.
Sure. Come on. Everyone, gather round.
Okay.
One, two, three.
Change your pose. One, two, three.
-Wow.
-You're stunning and charming.
You're so graceful, my lady.
Thank you.
Ongsa, you look good
in Thai traditional costume.
That's true. Trust me.
With you on the palanquin,
Team Blue is going to win.
In this Thai costume,
you look prettier than usual, human.
Thank you, Aylin.
You look gorgeous today, Ongsa.
Does it suit me?
It does.
So pretty.
Good luck today.
Hello, Ongsa.
Can I snap your photo for the school page?
Are you sure?
Please do. Snap all the photos you need
and pick the nice ones to post.
-You do it, Tong.
-Sure.
Excuse me. Can you just…
-Let's move, guys.
-Move.
Look at the camera, Ongsa. Okay.
One, two, three.
-Can I get one more from the side?
-Let us help with that.
-You can start.
-This side, okay?
Turn a bit to the side.
Look at the camera. Okay.
Smile. Okay.
Thank you, Ongsa.
And since I'm from the PR team,
I'd like to announce
that I'm single.
-See you.
-Okay.
Sun, are you okay?
Sun.
What's the matter?
Nothing. I'm all right.
I'm fine.
Can I get a photo with you, Ongsa?
Yes.
One, two, three.
Thank you.
Ongsa, you look stunning.
A photo with us, please.
Do you have an IG account?
I'd like to follow you.
-Ah, sure.
-Our friend is famous.
-Here.
-Ongsa!
Come on. Time to form the parade.
You look gorgeous today.
Like, lethally gorgeous.
-Come on. Time to go.
-Guys, don't forget to dance your ass off.
-You can do it.
-Don't embarrass our class.
I'll see you later.
-Let's go, Ongsa.
-See you.
Get it, girl.
Sun.
Easy there, okay?
You're ruining your Kanom Krok.
Let them be ruined.
Take a deep breath.
It'll help calm you down, Sun.
What's the problem, human Sun?
You seem frustrated.
I don't like Ongsa like this.
Like what?
Too pretty.
Too gorgeous to handle.
Isn't it good?
It's not like it's bad.
But when she turns pretty,
other people want to get to know her.
They want to approach her.
They want to hit on her.
And then there's Ton.
Are you afraid Ton and Ongsa
will get back together?
But it's not wrong, is it?
He has the right.
Ton is single.
Ongsa is single too, right?
-Yeah?
-Right.
That's right.
It's not against the precepts.
We won because we danced
our asses off, for sure.
Team Yellow danced pretty well,
but we were better.
Agree.
Ongsa.
Guys.
-Hello, Alpha.
-Hi.
That's my little sister. Good job.
I watched you the whole time.
I told you Team Blue would win.
Ongsa, you're the best. Congratulations.
No. I didn't do anything.
We should thank those
who designed the parade.
To me, you're the best no matter what.
Should we take photos together
just to capture the memory?
-Every one of us.
-Let's do it.
Nack! Can you help take pictures for us?
Here.
Let's pose.
One, two…
Hold on one second!
Ton is coming.
Stop. Just stop.
Move.
Hey!
Sorry.
I just want to stand next to Ongsa.
Ready?
One, two, three.
One more.
Cool. Thanks a lot.
How'd it turn out?
Ongsa, can we steal the trophy for a bit?
This background is nice.
Again?
I'm gonna go change.
You can go home.
I don't know how long it will take.
It's all good. I can wait.
I'll take you home.
-Go.
-Thank you.
-And then we…
-Ongsa.
Should we celebrate with BBQ Pork tonight?
My treat.
Sure. Who else is going?
Just the two of us.
Why just us?
Because I want to spend time
with someone I love.
Ton.
I don't like it
when you get close to Ongsa.
She is taken.
What?
Ongsa, are you taken?
Since when?
Since now.
She is mine.
Remember this, Ton.
Ongsa belongs to Sun
and Sun only.
Excuse me.
Come on.
Sun.
What did you just…?
How do you feel toward Ton?
What?
I asked how you feel toward Ton.
Well…
He's a good big brother
who always helps me.
Are you getting back together with him?
-What?
-Well, you're single.
Are you going back to him?
What about me?
Sun, I think you're misunderstanding…
I don't know what you think of him.
But I like you.
I like you so, so much.
I don't think I can like you more.
I want to be your girlfriend.
I don't like when other people
get close to you.
I don't like it
when other people touch you.
I want the right to be possessive.
To be jealous.
And I want you for my own.
I already spoke my mind.
What do you want to do?
Do you want to be my girlfriend?
Ongsa.
I like you, Sun.
I like you so much.
I've liked you
since before we knew each other.
And I'm not sure
I'm good enough to be with you.
But I want to be your girlfriend.
And I want you to be my girlfriend.
Will you be my girlfriend?
I asked you first.
You can't just ask me back.
What's your answer?
I will.
Of course I will.
Finally.
Sun and Ongsa like each other?
Yes.
I'll fill you in later. Okay?
My plan has been completed.
My sweetheart
has finally found her happy ending.
Please. You can't call her
your sweetheart anymore.
-Respect her girlfriend, will you?
-Yeah.
Yeah, that's true.
From now on,
she should be called Sun's sweetheart.
Ongsa, my sweetheart.
Hey!
Sun's sweetheart.
She's all grown up.
So, we're girlfriends now?
-Great job!
-Good job!
Well done!
This Friday night,
I'm hosting a meteor shower watch party
at the school.
Any couple who watches meteor showers
together at school
will be lucky in love.
When people are in a relationship,
they go on dates.
The first date is mostly watching a movie,
and it should be a romantic movie.
Yes! Shoot him! Aim and kill!
Well, that was unexpected.
So, this is how aliens ask someone
to watch stars with them?
It's cute.
It's almost time.
Why are the kids not here yet?
We can just watch the stars together then.
Luangpu, can you enlighten us on
how people in a relationship should act?
Do you think I'm a love guru or what?
Why did you come to me
regarding love issues?