I'm sorry.
I just want to be friend with you.
From now on, you can follow
your dream and do it well.
I still want to be your friend.
And ignore them all.
Therefore both of us…
Will create even better memories.
Please continue to support us.
Pure is here.
I'm at Siam already,
tell me when you're done.
I'm done. Meet me at the same spot.
The shopping mall will be
closed in the next 30 minutes.
You didn't wear a mask earlier?
I looked around and there
was nobody around. Don't worry.
It's not like that. We've talked about this.
You need to wear the mask every time we meet.
I said I looked already.
Why are you so upsetting?
What's going on?
Well, you can't follow our deal.
Don't you forget what we had to deal with?
It was a mess because of this, remember?
We discussed it and we'll continue
to be like this until the contract ends.
You said that you understood
me and you'd support me.
You called this supportive? You're asking for
troubles. I Isn't it what I've been doing all along?
You told me that you'd try
to find time for us to meet.
When I came to see you, and you
yelled at me, you were mad at me.
I already explained everything
about what I needed to carry
and what decision I had to make.
If you're only thinking about
yourself, then there's nothing I can do.
Me? I only think about myself?
It's not the other way around?
You!
You only care about someone else.
You told me to understand
you about everything.
It's me, right? I have to
change everything for you?
Why haven't I been in your thoughts?
You never asked me
if I was exhausted or how my school was.
You wanted me to understand
you about everything.
I needed to change
everything for you, didn't I?
If you feel exhausted that much,
I think we should call it off.
You want to break up with me?
I don't know.
I know that you're exhausted, keep it up!
I see that you've taken your
son to the events quite often.
Do you expect him to follow
your footsteps in politics?
I think it's too soon
because he's still a teenager.
I don't want to force him or rush him.
But I can't say that I didn't expect him
to be like me.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have
dedicated all of this for him.
What about you? Diesel?
After hearing what you
Dad said, what do you think?
Do you want to follow his path?
No, I don't.
I want to find my own path.
I don't know what it looks like.
But people can choose, right?
He totally embarrassed
his Dad by saying that.
Thara had great education.
But why didn't his son
take after him? I Puppies don't turn
out to be exactly like their parents.
Why does a son turn
out to be like his father?
Kids these days are all the same,
they are manipulated.
Dream? You're done?
Let me help you with
that. I I can clean it up.
Why don't you have some milk?
Come on, I'll go with you.
What's up Little Boss? You learned
to disagree with your Dad now?
Yeah? You watched it?
I like that, did you get kicked out already?
What do you think?
Aloha Hawaii. You like it?
Stop messing with me, I'm super mad today.
Fine, I'll stop.
I'll go. I What?
Why did you invite me then?
Come on, let me beat
you for at least one match.
Let's go.
What did your Dad say after the show?
I don't know. I walked out after it's done.
Oh my goodness! You're such a brave guy.
What's on your mind when you said that?
I thought about you.
What's wrong? Your home is not a safe zone?
I moved back home, but.
I don't think my dad can change.
I feel bad for Mom,
she must have wanted everyone
to stay under the same roof.
I don't know what to do.
What defines your safe zone?
It's a place
where I feel safe and I can say anything.
Nobody judged me.
You're my safe zone.
What about you? Am I your safe zone?
Saved me from what?
Look? I'm dying in this game.
What the hell is wrong with
you? Why did you keep calling?
I just wanted to see your face.
You want to have dinner? Same spot?
Sure, I'm craving some clams.
Look at you and your new boobs.
Tokyo, your boy's here.
New hair color? I That's right.
Nice, I like it.
Besides the color of my hair,
you wanna guess the color of my bra?
What color?
When you said you traveled
with your family, you meant this?
I know.
I thought you'd like it.
It's not that I don't like it.
But it…
We didn't talk about this first.
Do you feel like you
can't talk to me about this?
What do you think I would feel
when you said that
you liked to play with boobs and
you looked at someone's boobs?
What do you think?
Well, I like them.
But it doesn't mean
that I want you to change.
And I don't want you to.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I think
we need to communicate more.
Hey! I Yeah?
I love you the same,
you know that right?
You know that, right?
Of course, I do.
Hey, teaser of Paint Your Dream
season 2 is so cute, did you watch it?
Here.
Teaser of Paint Your Dream season 2
reached one million views in 12 hours.
That's more like it.
Yeah?
Hi, will you go to DEVI's party?
I saw you reposted it. I Sure.
You're coming too?
But they're also coming.
Do you have one more invitation left?
How do you feel about the second season?
We're just done shooting and…
What is it?
You're still hurt?
Not anymore.
Mint, hello.
Hello. I Hello.
Let me introduce you to our DEVI's girls.
Your mom is here.
Is that Lukjan?
Shit!
I heard that they
organized this party because.
Kimia refused to renew the contract.
So they need to find a new brand's muse.
Who'd have thought that they
selected four persons for this?
Four? They reserved a
spot for Lukjan since the start.
She nepo-babied her way in, don't you see?
All of this
will be traded with business
connection of Lukjan's family.
Lukjan?
I think I will stay
with a friend in the country for a while.
I thought that me going home
would make everything better.
I know that my Dad loves me.
But I can only listen
and I can't share one f... king opinion.
I don't feel like a human.
The only place where I can say anything is
when I am Anyone.
Well,
we're like characters in games.
They are players and we are avatars.
They'd choose our jobs and items,
and this and that that
they thought good enough.
But…
They never asked the characters
if they wanted any of them.
You're talking nonsense when you're drunk.
But I like it. It's good.
Just because they were born first doesn't
mean that they're right about everything.
Why do they think that
their opinions are better than ours.
You're just an amateur.
Amateurs.
Ouch! I You deserved it. You're weak!
How can a weak guy
like me can get better?
People can change.
You never had spicy stir-fried
clams and now you have it.
It's not that easy, you know?
You can do it.
I believe in you.
Wanna go with me?
Take a train with me?
Are you crazy? It's late.
How can I go? I don't
have any clothes, nothing.
Why're you so obsessed with
these thing? You don't need them.
You can wear my clothes, okay?
Let's go.
Don't think, just go.
Come on, tough it up.
What are you doing?
Can I join you?
Sure.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, I didn't know.
Damn it!
Please wait.
I need to talk to Ms.Duangtawan.
You can't get in if you're
not on the guest list.
She knows me, please. Just a minute.
It will be just a minute.
You can't get in if you're
not on the guest list.
Please take her to see Tong.
Please meet Tong and
I'll catch up with you.
Sure.
This way.
I know that it's my
fault for rejecting the job.
Please give me another chance. Please.
A chance?
I think I was so clear with you.
You can go now.
I just heard that you're looking
for a new muse to replace Kimia.
Are you sure of appointing
a person to be a muse
because of the business?
Do you have a problem of my choice?
I just think that
being a muse means that
you can inspire someone, right?
Why?
You think that you should be that person?
I'm just an ordinary girl
who've been trying to prove myself.
I did the wrong things.
I traded everything to be where I am now.
You should see that, right?
Lukjan didn't even sweat a single thing.
Why did everything look so easy for her?
This is not different than devalue
your own art pieces.
There's so much for
you to learn in this world.
What you said was right.
Lukjan may not reach the criteria
to be exactly what I needed.
But she got connections, with so
many businesses that benefit my brand.
These things are what.
I am willing to trade for.
What about you?
What do you have to offer?
Bambi,
why do you look so upset?
You're sad that I was selected
to be a muse and you weren't?
Honey, you look so
desperate. It's making me sad.
Let me ask you something,
why do you want to be a muse?
You have everything.
Bambi,
I've never thought
that I needed to compete with you.
I didn't even want to be a muse.
But my parents urged me to.
They wanted me to be
recognized in the society.
A social climber like you should get it. I
You ended up using your family's connection.
You should be proud of yourself.
Bambi,
I admire you.
I see that you're so good
to be where you are now.
You're so lucky to have met
someone like us, you know that?
What did you have before this?
What school are you going to?
A no name school?
For example,
when you hit an old man,
can I ask you something?
You think your parents could help you
out? I What the hell is wrong with you?
You think that old man died?
If you didn't have us to save you,
you could end up in jail already.
It's okay. Today is my day.
I think I should go back to the party.
Do you want to join me at my table?
And you should stop
thinking about being a muse.
I don't think you can be one, you know why?
Your digital footprint is all over the place
and it could show up any time.
Unlike me, I'm super clean.
To heal my stress.
You could die if you take it all.
Take home?
You can't, officers are
lining up on the way home.
Want to sniff some?
I can't believe it, cool!
Keep the pouch, okay? I Thanks.
What did you do? Why do you look like this?
When you ask me,
do you really want to know or just asking?
Is it that important to you?
I think so if I had a mom.
There's a thin line crossing
between our relationship.
If you were my product like Dana,
I would have so many
opinions to share with you.
But you're your Dad and your Mom's product.
As a human being,
when you feel sad, I feel sad too.
This is so you.
No wonder why you can stay with Dad.
Wanna call her?
Call your mom?
I think right now
you need someone.
Even if I feel your pain,
you wouldn't feel great about it.
You better find it from someone
who'd make you feel good.
Are you okay?
I saw Lukjan followed you inside,
she didn't do anything, did she?
It's none of your business.
You didn't seem to care about me before.
Why?
You want to be a good guy now? I My
company ordered me to stay away from you.
They're worried that
something bad would happen.
I saw you like this and
I'm worried about you.
I really can help you.
My company is about to
launch a new project of series.
I can introduce you to them easily.
It will turn out great.
I don't want you to live like this.
Live like what?
You're all talk,
you've never done anything.
You said that if I needed
something, I needed to trade it, right?
See? I traded it with everything.
What about you?
You told me that you'd
quit starring in BL series.
It's my fault.
I'm sorry.
But can you trust me just one more time?
It's gonna turn out great this time.
Trust me.
You saw how I live my life, right?
I talked to Joe about it.
I used all of my connection for you.
I planned this because I worried about you.
You can't compete with Lukjan with DEVI.
She got connections with
lots of money, you know it.
Trust me, if you don't
want to struggle like this.
Don't forget that
you're just an ordinary girl.
I don't want to see you
live your life like this.
If it troubles you that much,
then you can enjoy fake
happiness that you choose.
Can I sniff some? I Are you sure.
I don't think you can be the muse,
because your digital
footprint is all over the place.
Unlike me, I'm super clean.
Watch out!
Hey! You!
Can I help you?
Here, hold her clutch.
How are you heading back?
I drove here, I think I
need to drive it back.
Hey, can you help me look
if there're any officers on the way back?
Lukjan, the car is here. Come on.
Come on.
Thank you.
Easy there.
Get in, okay?
Oh my!
Bambi!
Any officers on the way back?
All clear.
You sure? Alright, I'm
leaving. I You should go.
Name, hey!
Her clutch.
Right, thank you. See you.
Bye / Get home safe. See you later.
Drive safe.
Can I have a look inside?
Stay still, sir!
Look for what? I have a
lawyer, officer. This is not right.
To be a special someone in this day and age
comes with many privileges.
Many people want to be
special persons by many ways,
either to have good taste
or being tasteless.
Hello,
you're calling me in?
Do you know
how people
can inspire artists to create art pieces.
Their individualities.
That person has something
that others don't have
or they can't find it from anyone else.
Kimia is that person.
I saw her
and I saw so many possibilities
happened with her body.
When I selected a muse,
it can't be just anyone.
What about Lukjan?
You already know what she has to offer.
DEVI's girls
aren't perfect.
But they believed me.
They believed that I would
create a better version of themselves.
Unlike you,
you didn't believe me,
you didn't accept any
chance that I gave you.
Also, you destroyed me.
To ensure that they would be a person
that I wanted them to be,
I followed them all the time.
Of course, I knew whose
drug's pouch in Lukjan's purse belong to.
The main investors weren't
quite happy of what happened to Lukjan.
I'll dismiss Lukjan because of the scandal.
I'm not happy to lose
the deal but what can I do.
Deep down,
I admired your boldness
for deciding to do something like that.
This is how the world is.
People who wanted to climb to the top,
if they don't already have great start,
then they need to step on someone's head.
But pictures of Lukjan
spreading around showed that
she wore DEVI's dress.
I won't tolerate it that
the pictures will last forever.
Everything that happened is all
because of you.
You're a person who tainted my brand.
I'm sorry.
But it's fine.
I called you here
because I found a solution.
You want to be a muse so bad
so I will give you this position.
Today, you have what no one else doesn't.
I don't think I could find any model
who can represent ambition
as better as you can.
This is exciting.
Clothing which is inspired
by someone like you
must be so different from Kimiya.
But I think it must be
a tough job for me bring back
the reputation,
from what you have done.
Work hard.
This is not a request
but it's an order.
I didn't hold any better cards in the past.
But this time,
you need to remember
what you have done.
Glad to be working with you.
People can inspire
artists to create art pieces
- because of their individualities.
- Duangtawan