[Fate Chooses You]
[Episode 17]
Eat it while it's hot.
That one's burnt.
Don't eat it.
It's fine.
I like it like this.
Senior,
I went to a nearby village just now
and paid them
to have them draw a map of North Xiang.
There are 3 roads to North Xiang.
There is only 1 official road
for traveling merchants—
that is this road on the south.
But it's a bit further
and passes through 2 cliffs.
The north road is shorter,
but it's all sandy paths—
hard to travel.
There is also a west road.
It's longer than the north road,
but connects to half of the official road,
making it relatively easier to travel.
Okay.
Then let's head west.
Senior,
do you know
where the person you're looking for
exactly is?
North Xiang is vast with many cities.
If we search one by one,
I'm afraid it'll take
more than half a year.
Master is still waiting for us
at the sect.
I know.
But I have to find him.
I can't remember
anything now.
That darn official said
I married him in Wei County
and killed someone for him in the capital.
But I don't remember anything.
So,
he must have done something
to me in the dark.
When we met last time,
I felt he wasn't a good person.
Seeing how beautiful you are,
he must've tricked you into marrying him
and decided to use you
after taking advantage of you.
He deserves to die.
He's terrible.
Well...
That might not be the case.
I can kinda guess
why I married him.
When I left the sect,
I had the thought
of finding a death row prisoner
to marry.
Do you remember—
I have the destiny
of bringing death to my husbands.
I am destined
to bring death to 3 husbands.
So I wanted to find
a heinous death row prisoner to marry
to break this destiny.
I guess
I found him,
and after marrying him,
I found out he was a good person,
so I went to the capital to avenge him.
Oh, right.
Didn't Emperor Zong Ding
exonerate him?
It shows
he was wronged.
And the Landlady also said
I was brought back to the inn
after he saved me.
With my skills,
it would be impossible
to retreat unscathed
under the siege of various immortal sects
in the capital.
He must have saved me.
So?
So—
that's where the problem lies.
Since he is so capable,
why would he willingly
suffer
and endure death by a thousand cuts?
And why did he erase my memory?
He is obviously very capable.
Even if I knew the truth
and turned against him,
I couldn't have beaten him.
I guess he just didn't want to hurt me.
And in Chongling Valley,
he saved my life several times.
He was the one
who gave me my Gongshan Jade Tablet.
He was an honest official,
cared for the people,
and has powerful skills,
yet he doesn't seek immortality.
I really can't figure out
what a person like him
could possibly want
from me.
Didn't you just say
you wanted an explanation from him?
Yes.
You want to settle scores with him?
But look at
the words you just used to describe him.
Calling him an honest official
not seeking fame—
a hidden master
with powerful skills.
Senior,
are you really trying to
settle scores with him?
Good people do bad things too.
Besides...
Besides, I need to get
my memory back.
[Qinghong Sect Headquarters]
Master summoned
us Dharma Kings for a meeting.
Why is a Vajra like you here?
He is no ordinary Vajra.
She serves day and night
by the Master's side.
[Qinghong Sect, Dharma King Niankong]
[Qinghong Sect, Dharma King Wenyin]
Thoughtfulness like this
isn't something everyone can learn.
Fortunately
our sect ranks by
the strength of our magic.
If we ranked by anything else,
I'm afraid we'd both fall behind.
If Dharma King Wenyin would like to learn
some of "anything else,"
I can teach you.
[Qinghong Sect, Lord Tiling]
Master told you to come in.
[Qinghong Sect, Lord Baori]
The Phoenix God's power is unmatched;
long live, Master!
[Qinghong Sect, Futian]
Rise, everyone.
Thank you, Master.
Bishui Branch suffered heavy losses
this time.
Hewabu and many cultists
died because they were controlled by
the Spell of Utterance.
I invited you here today
for that—
Master.
Over the years, Hewabu
has been loyal
and protected thousands of
our sect members.
Now that he is dead,
we must avenge him.
Xunmu.
You speak first.
Master.
When I went to the capital,
I saw the cultivator
who killed Mr. Gui.
I exchanged a few moves with her
and she ran away.
You couldn't even stop
a mere Qi Refining cultivator?
You have no idea, Dharma King.
There is nothing special
about this cultivator.
It's just that
she's aided by a master.
With just a few moves,
he could make the Heavenly Talents
of major immortal sects back off.
I suspect
it was also him who wiped out
Bishui Branch.
Killing a few Heavenly Talents is nothing.
Master.
I volunteer to go to Bishui Branch
to look for this cultivator.
I will use her blood
as a sacrifice to our Phoenix God.
If so,
you may go.
You may all leave.
Vajra Xunmu.
Master.
Go along with Wenyin.
Keep an eye on him.
Don't let him cause trouble.
Yes.
The Bishui Branch is a trivial matter.
Our business is what's important.
The Central Plains replied,
saying the person has arrived.
Master,
you must be prepared.
Once I get the money in Xutuo City,
I will leave here immediately.
I won't stay here for even another moment!
This place is no good.
It's too dry.
It's not a place for humans to live in.
They owe me a lot of money.
I have to get it all back.
They'd better not think they can get
even a single cent from me.
On the way back,
as soon as we leave this desert
and reach a place
where I can hire a carriage,
I'll hire one immediately.
I won't walk back no matter what.
I'll go to Zuixian Restaurant first.
It's for nothing else
but those soy-braised pork trotters.
Then I'll go to the Textile Pavilion
to get a new pair of boots made.
Lu.
Are you going to stay in North Xiang
or go back to the Central Plains?
Lu?
Did he fall asleep?
You can sleep even when it's this bumpy?
Stop, stop!
Slowly.
Come on.
Okay.
Gosh, my back.
Let's rest a bit.
Yeah.
Help massage me.
He's asleep.
No wonder he wasn't answering.
This coffin lid is so thick.
I'll leave a crack open for you
So you can cool down.
Sir,
what song are you singing?
The Boat Song.
You are from North Xiang—
have you ever seen a boat?
Yet you sing a song about boats?
How ignorant.
Boats don't just sail on the water.
There are also boats in the desert.
Boats in the desert?
Flying boats.
Those boats
are over 30 feet tall,
with dozens of rooms
and can hold hundreds of people.
From a distance,
it looks like a pavilion in the air.
It's much bigger
than your Zuixian Restaurant.
I don't believe it.
Me neither.
You're talking nonsense.
What's that?
What's going on?
There's a large group of people on horses
300 feet away.
They're after us.
Who?
Who's after us?
Mounted bandits?
They're coming fast.
It's them.
They're just some mounted bandits.
We can just fight them off.
My divine sword
finally has a use.
There are too many of them. We can't win.
Let's go!
-Let's go.
Hurry up.
Come.
Master!
Didn't you hire me
to protect you?
Why run from some mere mounted bandits?
Wait for me.
Where are they?
Old man.
My parents died
over 50 years ago.
Here you are
saying there's going to be a disaster.
What disaster?
What?
Are you going to move the graves?
What's going on?
Exactly.
How about this?
See if you can read my fortune.
If you can,
[Shi Wen]
I'll admit you're good.
[Tai Shiqian]
Okay.
If I'm right,
you can't go back on your words.
And what if you're wrong?
I'll smash your darn stall today.
Deal.
Your forehead is dark—
it's a sign of impending disaster.
Have you done anything bad
recently?
Your disaster is coming soon.
Wh-What are you talking about?
He can tell that?
Your bloody disaster
is coming soon!
Bah!
I'll smash your darn stall
today—
It's close.
I...
I'll smash it!
It's getting closer.
[Zhu Taijian]
Shi Wen!
Give my money back!
I'll smack you to death!
They really came.
See, wasn't I right?
Give back my money!
Give it back!
I have no money!
You haven't paid yet!
Okay, okay.
Don't rush!
One by one!
Come, line up!
You are here.
I thought you had
run back to the Central Plains.
Why did you run?
I'm asking you why you ran.
Are the mounted bandits that formidable?
You've got me.
You're fast, Lu.
You got them before I did.
Wh-What's going on?
We need to find a place
for him to rest up.
He's been poisoned by a scorpion.
D-Don't kill me!
I'm just a commoner.
I'm penniless
and my life is short.
I-I just bought a coffin.
I really don't know anything.
Heroes,
please,
spare my life.
No one wants to kill you.
I ask you,
was there a group of
Central Plains people with you earlier?
Central Plains people?
No.
Think again.
Yes, yes.
It's those
Central Plains laborers.
Right.
They helped me carry the coffin.
But when they heard
your horses,
everyone scattered.
I don't know
where they went.
Boss,
are you hot?
Just say what you want.
With the sun so bright,
no one will come out.
Shall we close up?
You brat.
Look at
what time it is.
And you want me to close?
Are you intentionally preventing me
from making money?
The problem is no one's coming.
You won't make money
even if you stay open.
You bastard!
If there's no work,
can't you wipe the tables,
mop the floor,
or find something to do?
Fine.
I'll listen to you.
Boss!
There are customers!
There are customers?
Quick, count—
how many there are.
One, two, three...
Do dead ones count?
Is the hot water ready?
Almost.
Let me do it.
Give it to me.
Thank you.
It's quite cool and shady ahead.
Senior.
Go sit and rest for a while.
I'll go fetch some water.
Then I'll go start a fire
and heat up some flatbreads.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Senior, did you make this yourself?
Yes.
I am Xin Mei from Xin Xie Manor.
May I know your name, Senior?
It's Lu Qianqiao.
♪ Honor and disgrace;
rumors and prejudice ♪
Qian as in millions
and Qiao as in arbor trees.
Since you consider me your senior,
♪ Everyone has their own take ♪
I will not let you die.
I don't need you to go through any danger.
♪ Fingers coated in blood
and disasters brought about ♪
It'll save me a lot of trouble
if you could
master the Fish Drinking Technique soon.
♪ Were never what I wanted ♪
Lu Qianqiao.
What kind of person are you?
It's mine!
It's mine.
Here you go.
Hairbands are like threads,
connecting karma.
Since it fell into your hands,
it means we are destined to meet.
Let me read your fortune for you.
No need.
I don't believe in this.
Whether you believe it or not
is your business,
but whether I read it or not
is my business.
I don't have money for you.
We disciples of the Crazy Daoist
from Dongting Mountain
only talk about destiny,
not money.
What are you doing?
Physiognomy.
You can do that just by looking.
It's physiognomy—
not just reading faces.
Physiognomy covers a lot,
including...
looks,
facial features,
bones, and palm lines.
They are all things
I have to observe for physiognomy.
Reading faces
can reveal good and bad luck,
but Miss, your Hongluan Star is active.
The Hongluan Star falls on your brow bone
and the radiance can be seen in your eyes.
If I am guessing it right,
there is a tree shadow
in your Hongluan Star.
This person must
be related to arbor trees.
Your brow bone is cool
with a slight bulge in the middle.
You are missing someone.
And this person
has countless ties with you.
Your feelings for him
are quite complicated.
Moreover, this person
also has a deep destiny with me.
It will be very difficult
for you to find him.
However,
rest assured.
You are blessed by the Hongluan Star.
As long as you have him on your mind
you will definitely meet
who you want to see.
Senior.
Senior!
Sheng...
What happened?
Confusion Powder?
Oh no. We've been tricked.
Sir, Sir.
Sir.
Please hold up.
Sir,
please come with me for a moment.
Come over.
What's wrong?
Sir,
you can't put a coffin
in the lobby of my inn.
It's an empty coffin.
Even an empty one won't do.
Look, it's such a large coffin—
so big and heavy.
It's an inauspicious sight
in the lobby.
How am I supposed to do business?
You don't have any other guests
in this inn anyway.
How about this?
Could you put this coffin
in the backyard?
Master!
You can move it there then.
How can I move it?
-Master!
-Sir.
Don't hold things back.
We have a life to save.
The hot water is ready.
I...
Hey...
What's their problem?
I've sealed
his arms' meridians.
But this
can only delay the spread of the poison.
To detoxify him completely,
we need medication.
What medicine do you need?
The Dragon Subduing Grass.
In the middle of nowhere,
where are we supposed to find that?
Dragon Subduing Grass
usually grows in
dark places in the desert.
It's most commonly found
in places under stone walls
that haven't seen sun for a long time.
What does it look like?
The water is boiled.
-Give it to me.
-Where should I put it?
I'll go right now.
Wait a minute.
It's too dangerous for you to go alone.
I'll go with you.
Let me go with you.
After all, I know more herbs
than you do.
Huh!
That's like telling me
to take up this job.
I'll go.
You all are clumsy.
If you get bitten by another scorpion,
there won't be a second coffin for you.
If you're going, I'll go too.
Stay here and don't cause trouble.
Let's go.
Sir,
are you going out on a long journey?
The coffin has already been put
in the backyard for you.
Shouldn't you settle
the bill?
Don't ask me.
I'm just a laborer.
Go find those nerds in there.
You...
Filthy poor
but has quite the temper.
Exactly.
What are you looking at?
Are you blind?
Don't you know to close the door?
You want to eat sand?
Go!
Quick!
Innkeeper!
More guests are here.
More guests?
No coffins this time, right?
Please come in.
Please.
This way.
Have a seat.
What are you staring at?
Hurry up and clean it for the guests.
Hurry!
Shoo!
This chair is definitely clean.
Please sit.
Master.
Ever since my master
moved into the new house,
he has nightmares every night.
Sometimes we also hear
a woman crying.
We suspect we've encountered
something from the underworld.
You've found
the right person.
Our Master Qian
learned from
the Crazy Taoist of Dongting Mountain.
He's best
at eliminating demons
and turning bad luck into good.
Do you see that person behind?
He looks like a human,
but actually,
he's not.
He is
a pig demon from Heifeng Mountain.
He eats humans.
Influenced by our Master Qian,
he volunteered to follow him and practice—
and now, he has taken human form.
Pardon my disrespect.
He is harmless.
So,
your master's matter—
just leave it to our Master Qian.
All right.
Besides eliminating demons,
we can also help you
look at the feng shui
to ensure your master's
3...
no, 5 generations of peace.
Thank you so much.
No problem.
Run!
It's over.
I miscalculated.
How could the person she's traveling with
be from the immortal sect?
Where's the money?
Here.
This is mine.
In the future,
don't let me
catch you swindling people again.
I didn't miscalculate.
She is a noble person.
Fortunately
she's not from the Tianyuan Sect.
This poison is fierce.
I don't know if he can hold on
until they return with the medicine.
Lyu
won't die, right?
Well...
it's hard to say.
You...
You guys—
can't you wish me well?
-He's awake.
Master Lu,
your medical skills are truly brilliant.
Come, let me have a look.
Okay.
The poison
is only temporarily suppressed.
But to completely detoxify it,
we still need the Dragon Subduing Grass.
Before that,
you can't feed him
anything.
You can only give him a little water.
I'll remember that.
Enjoy your meal.
Are you
just eating or staying the night?
We're staying the night.
Clear out
all the superior rooms here.
How unfortunate.
Our small inn
only has 2 superior rooms.
One of them
is...
is already occupied.
Then tell them to get lost.
I'm afraid that's not appropriate.
Don't be afraid.
Our Dharma King
is a reasonable person.
Try discussing it with them.
What if they're willing?
Then...
Then I'll go up and ask.
I'll go ask.
Guests in the room,
please open the door.
Guests—
I have a small matter
I'd like to discuss with you.
What is it?
So, here's the thing.
There are some
distinguished guests downstairs
who would like to switch rooms
with you.
Would you be...
They're asking for the moon.
In their dreams.
Dream on.
We are not switching.
Miss,
don't be so angry.
To show their sincerity,
they specifically
brought out this money
as a
compensation for you all.
It's not about compensation.
We were here first.
And one of us is severely injured
and has difficulty moving.
That's such a small amount of money—
how stingy.
If it were me,
I would be embarrassed
to take that out.
You all should listen to my advice.
Sure.
Well—
Sure?
This gentleman
is quite generous.
Thank you, Sir.
Prepare
another room for us.
Of course.
Your room
has already been prepared.
It's on the first floor.
Okay.
Allow us to pack up.
If there's nothing else,
I'll take my leave.
Leave the money.
The money?
Look at my memory.
Here you go.
Even a little bit helps.
Come take a look.
We've got good stuff.
-I'm off.
-Take care.
Come, eat.
Have some meat.
Thank you.
Enjoy your meal.
This place is worth coming to.
Senior.
Here.
Let's just eat it.
Sirs,
are you eating or staying?
Do you have plain water?
I'd like a bowl.
Plain water?
It's 5 wen a bowl.
So expensive?
What about egg noodles?
Also 5 wen.
How can you...
Are you three
eating or not?
Yes!
Bring us one bowl.
One bowl?
There are no seats left.
Let's share a table.
It tastes really good.
Eat more.
Ladies,
which sect are you from?
What are you doing in North Xiang?
Seeking refuge with your relatives?
Are you here on business
or for vacation?
I'm guessing
you are here looking for someone.
Since you're not speaking,
I'll take that as a yes.
To be honest,
I'm familiar with
the 36 regions of North Xiang.
If you want to find someone,
you have to go to Phoenix City.
It's the most bustling place.
Highly accessible,
it's also the hub of North Xiang.
If you are going to Phoenix City,
we might as well travel together.
Do you know why,
even though you tricked me,
I didn't make it difficult for you?
I had so much money in my bag,
but when you knocked me out,
you only took 2 taels.
You still have a conscience.
It seems we are destined to meet, Miss.
A liar with a conscience is still a liar.
Whatever your purpose is,
stop following us.
Sheng,
let's go.
Why are you looking at me?
Eat up.
Come.
I don't think
they are here after us.
Those two ladies are fierce.
But it doesn't look like
they want to kill us.
What if it's a stalling tactic?
That they make us drop our guard first
then go back for reinforcements?
That makes sense.
What sense does that make?
Who are the reinforcements?
You?
Or me?
That girl carrying dual swords
could take on 10 of us.
Does she really need
to play tricks on us?
That also makes sense.
So what do we do?
Keep going?
Yes.
Let's go.
Oh no.
They are here.
Why did you stop?
We are still 20 li away
from Xutuo City.
Let's take a break.
Dismount and rest.
We'll set off in an incense stick of time.
Rest on the spot.
-Yes.
Don't worry too much, Senior.
This time, not only our Tianyuan Sect,
Lingji Mountain and Sun Moon Cavern
have also sent
many immortal sect disciples
to intercept them.
These few demonic cultivators
cannot cause any big troubles.
We are catching a bunch of ordinary people
with such a large scale?
They are not ordinary people.
They are really good
at manipulating people's minds.
They're just like the plague.
They spread wherever they go.
I heard that Wushuang Society
only had over 10 people at first.
Now it has gradually grown stronger.
There are people who believe in them
in various states and counties.
Not only do they preach secretly,
but they also gather to make trouble.
Local governments are having a headache
because of them.
This Goddess Wushuang—
isn't she the Goddess of Craftsmanship?
They are
rotten demonic hearts
with
deity skin.
Over the years,
they scatter throughout the world,
causing many commoners
to lose their minds
and enter the demonic path.
They are utterly lawless.
So,
we cannot be soft on them.
It's for the commoners of the world
and for our immortal sect.
There's news.
Let's go.
Here.
Thank you.
Miss!
Quick!
Ladies!
Help! Help!
Please help. Let us on the boat.
You still dare to chase us.
You're really seeking death.
Miss, Miss.
We are being hunted by enemies.
Saving a life brings infinite merit.
Saving 3 lives brings merit
equal to building...
16, 17, 18...
Anyway, thank you, Miss.
There's no time. Quick!
-Get on the boat quickly!
-Thank you!
Hurry!
Tell us. Who exactly are you?
We are just
poor wanderers making a living.
Still lying?
Okay, okay.
I'll tell the truth.
What kind of grudge
do you have with the Tianyuan Sect?
You know the people
from the Tianyuan Sect too?
Is it weird
for us cultivators to know
people from the Tianyuan Sect?
But what did you 3 ordinary people do
that is attracting
so many people from the Tianyuan Sect
to hunt you down?
We didn't really do anything.
We just
took a book from Lingji Mountain before.
Took?
You mean stole.
How can you put it that way?
Knowledge belongs
to everyone in the world.
There's no distinction
between yours and mine.
No distinction.
It's just a book.
We originally wanted to copy it.
But we didn't have time.
We were planning
to return that book.
If you stole a book from Lingji Mountain,
why is the Tianyuan Sect hunting you?
We don't know either.
Maybe they are just
sticking their noses
into other people's business.
Anyway, no matter
what kind of grudge you have,
stop following us
from now on.
Let's go.
I...
Why would
this ship appear in
the arid and waterless North Xiang?
The hull of this ship
is made of teak from Piao State.
This kind of wood
is solid, durable,
and highly anti-corrosive.
When we humans build ships,
we use century-old teak.
Looking at this ship,
it has been abandoned here
for probably hundreds of years.
When this ship was built,
the teak used
must have been a thousand years old.
Forgive us, immortal lady.
There is only one way
to the hinterland of North Xiang.
We won't bother you.
Why would
this ship appear in the desert?
The nearest sea is
a 2-month journey from here.
How was such a big ship
transported here?
You may not know this, immortal lady.
This is not a sea ship.
This is
a tower ship that can fly in the sky.
It wasn't
transported from anywhere else.
It fell from the sky.
Ships can't fly.
Only immortals have that ability.
Thousands of years ago,
with the exquisite craftsmanship
of our human ancestors,
let alone building flying ships,
even indestructible
automatons,
cannons with a range of over 100 zhang,
and super-capacity spatial bags
were a piece of cake.
What are you laughing at?
Spatial bags?
Those are legendary treasures
of the immortals.
Who said spatial bags are...
Spatial bags
were made by our human ancestors.
It was a highly skilled
female artisan.
She ascended to godhood
through her craftsmanship.
She was titled Goddess Wushuang.
That was a thousand years ago.
Of course,
you can't say
she wasn't human just because
she became a god later.
When she created
these miraculous inventions,
she was still human—
a mortal.
Please forgive us.
[Qianyan Cavern]
[Soul Lantern Hall]
Congratulations on emerging
from seclusion, Father!
Gui is dead.