-Surprise!
-Dad! Mom!
-Mikoy!
My son!
How about the one I asked
you to investigate?
Here it is, sir.
He hasn't achieved anything in life.
He's very simple.
Chiara, sorry.
I just don't want you to think
that I'm taking advantage of your family.
That's why I accepted your dad's offer.
Hurry!
-Chiara's parents are here!
-What?!
Mr. and Mrs. Valtrovi?
Oh!
Tell Mikoy what we decided.
Well, we finally got the blessing
of your mom and dad.
-Oh!
-This weekend!
Yes, sweetheart.
Yay!
Yes, sweetheart!
We're getting married!
We'll be Mr. and Mrs. Pinagpala!
Son! Mikoy!
He really loves pulling pranks.
Whether in Prague or the Philippines,
he's always up to something!
Oh my, come here! Let's eat!
I really love this… What do you call it?
Sweet cake!
-Come on!
-The sweet cake.
Oh, this is his fault.
He arrived late.
-Come on.
Let's eat first.
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
It was Papa's idea.
It was also your Dad Mario's idea!
If I love joking around,
your dad is even worse!
Hey, in-law!
No flopping around.
I thought we were besties!
Look at you calling him "in-law"!
But what is "balae"?
"Balae",
in English, means we are family.
So then, allow me to be your "in-law",
Daddy Mario and Mommy Tess!
Mikoy,
have you told them why
you came back to the Philippines?
Wait.
Aren't you here just for a vacation?
You and Chiara.
Just relaxing from work.
Something like that, right?
I've just been looking
for the right moment to tell you.
Dad, Mom.
I'm sick, Mom.
I've been given a limited time to live.
I only have a few days left, Mom.
What illness are you talking about?
Mikoy, what? What happened?
Mikoy!
Because…
They said, Mom…
Just kidding!
Mikoy!
Oh my, this kid!
Our asset, Mikoy, confirmed
that the Valtrovi's are here,
in the Philippines.
Why would they come to the Philippines?
Away from their influence
in the European Union?
What they're doing is dangerous.
They're not protected here.
That's what I find strange, too.
The truth is,
Mikoy has grown close to us.
And in such a short time,
we realized how hardworking he is.
Very hardworking.
And very kind, too.
Like you said, in-law,
we are now one family.
So, who else should I trust but family?
I know he can run my business.
And he won't have to be far away
from his own family.
-That's Tagalog, huh.
-Well, in-law.
If that's the case,
we should have another party!
-Right!
-Wow!
-I love it! I like that!
-Okay.
-Oh yeah!
-Party! Party!
-In-law!
-Yes!
Betchay!
Hold on. Stop hitting…
My parents are clearly
enjoying their stay.
Yeah, right!
Uncle Vik is really showing off his moves,
like John Travolta!
-Where's your Mom and Dad?
-Huh?
They're probably upstairs,
getting some food ready
for your mom and dad.
-Well, there's a sudden party!
-Can we just do videoke?
It's embarrassing
that they had to do that.
No, it's fine.
They are enjoying it.
I'll help them.
Huh?
You sure? Okay.
-It's fine.
-I'll come with you.
-Mikoy! Mikoy! Join us!
-Huh?
But…
Okay, you take care of it.
-You can handle it!
-Come on. Dance with us.
-Huh?
-Dance with us!
-You can do it!
-Dance with us.
Okay.
Move like this.
You know, darling,
I'm thankful to Viktor.
But does Mikoy really need
to work at his girlfriend's dad's company?
What is the problem?
First, he'll probably get a good salary.
Second, Mikoy no longer needs
to go back to Prague.
He will stay close to us.
You know, you're right.
But this is just what I'm thinking.
The truth is,
they can't accept Mikoy for who he is.
That's why they want to change him.
You know,
I would think the same
if I were in their position.
I also wouldn't want
my daughter's boyfriend
to be just a waiter.
Of course, what I'd do
is give him a better job,
something more acceptable,
right?
So, what's wrong with that?
Tess, don't think that way.
I want to believe
that Viktor and Donabel are sincere
in wanting to help Mikoy.
They want to give him a better job.
I don't know.
I can't explain the reason for this,
but I'm really scared for our son.
Scared of what?
I don't even know.
But I'm really anxious
that something might happen to our child
if he accepts that job.
Boss, here's our delivery for this month.
It's all complete.
Just always be on the lookout.
Okay, Boss.
But do we really need to bring that
Michael Pinagpala into the company?
He might ruin all our plans.
We don't have a choice.
This is his daughter's fault
for falling for that nobody.
So you'll just allow it, Boss?
That he would take over your position?
I won't let that bastard
take everything I worked hard for.
So what's our plan now?
We will have to find a way
to eliminate him
before he ruins our plans.
I will kill him
before he interferes.
-What was that?
-Someone's there!
Go after him!
-There she is.
-She's pretty, right?
-Nice!
-There she is! Chiara!
Chiara, come on. Join us.
Your mom and dad have great moves.
They're really killing it.
Come on! Join us! Look! It's so fun!
My dear. Are you okay?
Yes, Papa.
It feels like something has changed.
What happened? What is that?
I just remembered something.
My dear, do not overthink.
You're right! I agree.
No! Of course not, dear.
There's no problem at all.
If you like, you can stay here tonight.
Yes. Don't think about that,
because we're glad that you're here.
And it's even better
because we got to meet you.
Thank you, Uncle and Auntie,
but we've already caused
too much trouble for you.
We'll just stay at a hotel.
Okay, sure.
-I'll accompany you--
-No, it's fine!
We'll handle it ourselves.
Alright. Okay.
-Mikoy…
-Take care.
Thank you so much for having us here.
See you soon, in-law.
In-law, thank you so much!
Oh, sorry about that.
But we'll definitely come back.
Because my husband enjoyed it,
not just me.
Right.
-Ouch.
-You're welcome, in-law.
-Take care.
-We'll come back.
You go ahead.
Go ahead!
Dear.
You think Chiara's okay?
Her mood suddenly changed, right?
It's like you said.
It's worse than having a monthly period.
I was shocked with her reaction.
You're right.
I was shocked, too.
Is she really like that?
Her mood suddenly changes?
Yes.
What do you call that?
She has mood swings?
Not really, Dad.
Usually,
she's just having fun.
You know, just always chilling.
She has no major hang-ups in life.
Maybe she heard something bad
about her and her family.
I can't recall anything I said
that could offend her.
Actually,
we were enjoying
talking to each other earlier.
Then suddenly that happened.
Maybe it's not you, Mikoy.
Maybe she heard it from other people.
Who?
From Mom and Dad?
Oh! I don't know.
But who else?
Is there anyone else here in the house?
Stop with your mumbling!
Tell us. Be straightforward.
Do you know why there's a sudden change
-and why Chiara's mood changed?
-Right.
Alright. I'll be the one to speak,
because I'm the only one
who knows the truth
Wow! No more beating around the bush!
Just say it!
You're impatient!
This is what happened.
Earlier, I saw her.
I don't know why,
but I am really worried about our child.
What are you worried about?
Because I know something bad
might happen if he accepts that job.
Mom?
Dad?
Why did you say that?
I already told your mom earlier.
She shouldn't speak like that.
She shouldn't say something bad
about Chiara's family.
Wow!
You're letting me take the fall.
It's true, right?
Mikoy.
I didn't mean for Chiara to hear that.
But you can't stop me from worrying.
Of course,
I was also shocked by what happened.
Think about it.
You went to Prague for work.
Then you suddenly came back with Chiara.
Then, surprisingly,
her mom and dad came, too.
Of course, it got me thinking.
What's happening?
Feels like something's wrong.
Maybe you're just surprised
by your own decisions.
Mom, Dad.
I know it feels like everything is sudden.
But believe me,
this is for everyone's good.
Promise.
I know that, son.
But it's my duty to overthink
and worry about my child, right?
Of course.
But I promise you, dear.
I'll visit Chiara tomorrow
and explain everything to her.
And I'll apologize to her
if I hurt her feelings
because of what I said earlier.
Please forgive your mom.
Because everything she does
and thinks is what's best for you.
Even if she acts that way,
she's still your mom.
-I don't know about you!
-Sir…
-Come here. You!
-Ouch. That hurts.
-That was hard.
-And you…
You're always throwing me under the bus.
You were talking too much.
But earlier, you sold me out!
That hurts.
Is there anything wrong, dear?
Did we say anything wrong?
Did we do something wrong?
Mikoy! Mikoy!
Pinagpala!
Darling!
PINAGPALA
SPECIAL BAKESHOP
Oh, wait. Did you have breakfast?
-Badong!
-Don't bother, ma'am.
I'm fine, ma'am.
Thank you!
Where's Uncle Vik?
Oh, that fool.
He went back to Manila.
He has business, as usual, to attend to.
But wait a minute.
Are you looking for Viktor or Chiara?
I'm looking for…
Chiara, ma'am.
I shouldn't ask, right? Isn't it obvious?
Kind of.
You know, my daughter seems worried.
I noticed she seems to be deep in thought.
She even mentioned
she wants to go back to Prague.
What is this? Wait, did you have a fight?
No, ma'am.
Actually, I wanted to talk to her.
She probably heard something bad.
That's why she's acting that way.
You know what? You can make it up to her.
Well, you can use your charm now!
Convince her, so we can stay here.
I haven't been to the beach yet!
Oh, wait a minute!
Is that it?
-You didn't bring anything?
-What?
Oh my! Well, my daughter,
aside from the fact that we look alike,
our habits are also similar.
What you need to do when you woo her,
is to bring something like…
Flowers!
You didn't bring any?
-Nothing.
-Wait, here!
Badong, please clean this up.
Here, let's get three.
There you go. It means "I…
am sorry."
Go straight to her!
That's her room.
-Oh, okay.
-Come on, lover boy.
-There!
-Thank you!
-Wait a minute!
Don't try to woo me.
That was a close kiss on the lips.
Be thankful…
Okay, hurry!
I'll call you. Just be ready!
Mikoy?
What are you doing?
Why would you do that?
I don't like being startled.
This was actually your mom's idea.
That I should make it up to you.
I didn't know that
you're a jōnin of Konoha!
I took karate lessons
since I was four years old,
so I know how to defend myself.
Isn't it obvious?
I can see that you're in a bad mood.
Even if you don't say anything,
it's written all over your face
that something
was bothering you last night.
Chiara.
Can we talk?
Please?
Heart to heart.
So I can know what the problem is.
Are you sure about
the complications you're getting into?
Do you know what gives me courage?
-What?
-You.
I believe you now have eyes and ears
inside their organization.
You just have to believe in yourself.