(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
ALL FIGURES,
INCIDENTS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS,
AND OTHERS ARE FICTITIOUS.
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
WERE FILMED SAFELY
IN ACCORDANCE WITH GUIDELINES.
Long time no see.
SO-HYUN
THE LATE HAN SO-HYUN
WE LOVE OUR BRIGHT
AND RIGHTEOUS SO-HYUN
You wanted to handle it yourself,
and you handed over
crucial evidence to the police?
I won't make excuses.
You better not.
Han Na-hyun must not make excuses.
Actually,
she must not do anything
to make excuses in the first place.
Since she works for me.
I'll pull out of all the cases
I've been in charge of
and take some time to reflect on myself.
You'll be moved to a different office too.
You're dismissed.
Sir, you have a video call
from the States.
I'll be there soon.
How are you feeling?
I heard you got crushed
by a solo practitioner at that.
Father, that's--
Who was in charge from our side?
I was in charge of it myself.
It takes many years to reach the top,
but you can topple in an instant.
I apologize.
I won't let you down again.
Please trust me, Father--
The surgery went successfully.
I can be discharged in a month or two.
That's great news, Father.
I hope you come back soon…
DISCONNECTED
Hello.
I'm here to meet Attorney Han Na-hyun.
Attorney Han Na-hyun?
Did you make a prior appointment?
No, she wouldn't answer my calls.
Her office is at the end of that hallway.
What brings you here?
Is this
because of that evidence?
Because the prosecution got the evidence
against the defendant?
Why are you asking this question?
What's so wrong
about an attorney losing a case?
This is a bit harsh.
What does it have to do with you, though?
Do you pity me?
Absolutely not.
This case…
I only won because you chose to lose.
- What?
- You could've
destroyed the hard disk back there.
You knew that evidence
would work against you.
The police arrived before I could do it.
I'm busy, so please leave.
Thank you.
You…
saved Ji-woo.
I may be mistaken
or unaware of your true intentions,
but it doesn't change the fact
that you saved her.
I'm here to tell you that.
Mother,
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
I-rang is a little weird.
What are you saying?
Since a few days ago…
A secret space?
What? What did you say?
I'm the gangster attorney, Lee Gang-pung!
You darn dog-hole ghost!
Darn dog hole?
He mumbles to himself.
And he acts like a gangster
who speaks in a dialect.
I think he's a little--
Enough.
Mother, I get that you want to deny it.
But playing dumb won't solve his illness.
I'm not playing dumb.
Bong-su, the truth is…
Mister.
Mister?
Come on, mister.
That's so distracting.
Will you stop already?
CLIENT: VERBALLY AGREED
ATTORNEY: SHIN I…
What are you doing?
I beg you.
Can you please act like a human being?
So, what are you doing right now?
I'm writing a contract.
Do we even need it?
Now that I'm bound to deal with ghosts,
I might as well write a contract
to prevent future trouble.
You really are an attorney after all.
I'd make it big in this field
if not for ghosts.
"I, Shin I-rang,
shall fulfill my duties as an attorney
for the amnesic ghost."
"But the contract will be
terminated immediately
if the ghost puts the attorney in danger."
I can't risk my life
to help a ghost, you know.
"If the attorney is hired
by a living client,
he will put a stop to the ghost's case
and focus on the living client."
This isn't fair for me at all.
Even if you don't like it, cope with it.
I'm the only one who can help you anyway.
Are you sure that I'm dead, though?
If you can't believe it, why don't you
go outside and try to slap someone?
I've tried that already.
I guess
this is a bit heartless.
…PUTS THE ATTORNEY IN DANGER…
I'll take a risk if it's not too big.
Fair enough.
Hold on.
What about being possessed?
That's an absolute no.
What, possession?
You mean, I could possess your body?
No, that's never going to happen.
Don't overreact.
I'm the one who suffers damage
from being possessed.
I tumble, trip,
bump into stuff, and throw up.
It's a total mess.
And frustratingly enough,
I can't even remember what happened.
You're really like the Hulk.
Then, how do I possess you? When?
Do I recite a spell or something?
Like "Abracadabra"?
Well, I'm not so sure.
The ghost before you possessed me
when he saw the food he liked
or heard the song he hated.
The key is…
human desire.
The most basic and sheerest forms
of human desire--
Or rage must be triggered
for a ghost to possess someone.
You already told me before.
Did I?
So, who is it this time?
I'm not sure yet.
But she's in a school uniform.
I checked nearby schools,
and her uniform didn't match anywhere.
What about her talisman?
I found it over there.
Where?
No, wait. Please don't touch it.
There are so many attached to it.
I took her talisman off. Here it is.
Did you check surveillance footage
with the super?
Yes, I did.
But Min-ju was the last visitor,
and the footage before her
was all deleted.
Who is this?
None of your concern.
Then what about him over there?
I-rang.
Who were you talking to just now?
Oh…
I was talking to the priest.
R-Right, Father?
The priest…
Ghosts?
I know it's flabbergasting.
But it's true.
I-rang can see ghosts.
Mother, I'm a huge fan of sci-fi movies,
and I watch movies about superheroes,
supernatural powers,
and even time travel except ghosts.
Guess why?
Because it's way too unrealistic.
I know I won't be able to convince you.
Go and see for yourself.
How scarily realistic.
It's almost like a movie set.
How may I help you?
I'm here for a divorce consultation.
Who is the attorney here?
That's me. I'm Attorney Shin I-rang.
Oh, I see…
You know what?
I don't think I need a divorce.
What on earth?
Why did she just leave?
Gosh, my neck hurts.
Was I perhaps possessed?
Nice dance moves.
Geez.
Be gone, Satan!
Wait, no.
- Bong-su.
- No.
Are you feeling better?
Yes, sir.
It's me right now.
Your brother-in-law, I-rang.
Oh.
Then, where is she right now?
She's behind me.
Oh, I see.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Yoon Bong-su.
Bong-su, she's a high schooler.
Anyway,
it's a bit frustrating
since you can't see her face.
Why don't you try sketching her face?
You might need it
to find out who she is anyway.
That won't be easy.
I-rang had the lowest grade in art.
I forgot that.
Thanks for the reminder.
Mister.
It might work.
What do you mean?
All right.
Great.
It actually worked.
Wow.
SHINSEONG MIDDLE SCHOOL
You saved Ji-woo.
I may be mistaken
or unaware of your true intentions,
but it doesn't change the fact
that you saved her.
If I keep on enduring…
- Ji-woo!
- Hey, guys.
May I be happy?
I want to smile every day
I want to be free of concerns
Anyone, please tell me what I should do
So help me
I want to flop down…
…I cannot sing a song that ended again
Even if that's what everyone wants
Please don't
Make me any more miserable
If you're pretending to stop me
This is enough
Please don't make me keep looking at you
Because I get butterflies…
Dear God, please help my brother-in-law.
At least for the sake of my mother-in-law,
my wife, and my family, please--
M-Mother? Minister!
Mother.
What should we do about I-rang?
He's all right.
It didn't seem too dangerous.
- But--
- She's right.
The ghosts aren't evil,
so don't be afraid.
- But--
- We won't completely let our guards down.
Speaking of which, Bong-su…
Can you take care of I-rang for me?
Me?
It won't be too hard.
Just keep by his side
and tell me what happens
from time to time.
But I'm scared of ghosts.
That's actually why
I don't watch ghost movies.
Oh, dear Lord.
Can't you reconsider?
You're the only one I can count on.
That's why.
Amen.
Mother, please.
Okay.
I'll do my best
to take care of my sweet brother-in-law.
Thank you.
Oh, right.
Keep it from I-rang
that I'm aware of the situation.
Why?
- Mister.
- Geez!
Can we listen to some music on our way?
No, absolutely not.
Are you chicken?
No, I'm not!
Then, why so sensitive?
Wouldn't you be in my situation?
Now that Bong-su knows, it'll be
a matter of time before my mom hears it.
So what if she does?
Then,
I'd feel bad for her.
Think about it. Her husband died early,
and now, her son's possessed.
It's so sad.
Are you crying?
No, I'm not…
Anyway, who is it this time?
I hear it's a high school girl.
Mother,
I-rang even drew a sketch of her.
PITTER-PATTER BUTCHER-STYLE BBQ
SHIN I-RANG LAW OFFICE
So…
where are we headed?
Where we can find out who you are.
Where is that?
A place
full of cool teenagers
who are good at dancing.
This is where I was?
Excuse me.
Have you perhaps
seen this girl?
No, I haven't.
HIP FLOW ACADEMY
LIST OF STUDENTS
I think your guess is way off.
Maybe it's somewhere
more open and unrestricted.
HONGIK UNIVERSITY STATION
This is better.
Have you perhaps seen this girl?
I don't think so.
- I'm not sure.
- No.
- I don't know.
- I don't know her.
Go for it!
She's not bad.
You were great.
Let's go now.
What's wrong?
So what if we find out who I am?
It won't bring me back to life.
PITTER-PATTER BUTCHER-STYLE BBQ
I'm back.
Why do you look so sour this time?
It's nothing.
There's just something that bothers me.
Hi, I-rang. You're back early today.
Welcome back.
Sa-rang.
Back when you were in high school,
what did you do
when you felt sad or gloomy?
- What?
- That's random.
I… ate.
- You ate?
- Goodness.
Food is her mood booster.
Oh, right. Tteokbokki.
I'd have some real spicy tteokbokki
until I was drenched in sweat.
Then, all my concerns were gone.
That still applies for me, right?
Mom, what are you up to?
To celebrate I-rang's new business
and stuff,
let's make something delicious.
Sounds good.
Sounds good indeed!
Then, I'll make tteokbokki.
- What? All of a sudden?
- Tteokbokki?
Goodness.
Let's give it a try.
Gosh, it stings.
Okay.
Some green onions too.
Why…
Why is it so red?
All right.
It looks so good.
- Here comes your grandma's food.
- Looks delicious.
And some braised galbi too.
Doesn't it look good?
Oh, my.
I-rang, your cheeks…
Mom, his cheeks…
Come along. Let's sit down and eat.
- Come and sit down here.
- Mom?
Let me.
Eat up now.
Enjoy.
Wait. Hey, you're going to have that?
Is it good?
Yes.
But you can't have spicy food.
Are you okay?
No, I love spicy food.
Uncle, why do you laugh like this
with your mouth covered?
It's so weird.
Da-bong, it's a new meme.
- Well, Bong-su.
- Yes?
The meat was delivered.
Why don't you bring it in?
- Well…
- Sa-rang, help him out.
Sure.
Honey, come on. The meat might go bad.
Oh, silly me. I forgot to bring water.
Show some respect, twirp.
Or do you have a death wish?
Grandma! Uncle called me names.
No way.
Yes, he did!
He said, "Do you have a death wish?"
I didn't call you names.
I rather called you cute.
Mom! Uncle pinched me. He pinched me hard!
I hate you, Uncle.
Don't eat.
I will.
Hands off.
Thank you.
What for? Don't mention it.
I enjoy those dishes
on the regular anyway.
I know you did it for me.
But all I do is complain ungratefully.
I guess I can't seem to admit
that I'm dead when I'm already dead.
Don't admit it.
What?
You looked so cool
when you were dancing earlier.
What I mean is,
your body may be dead,
but your soul isn't.
Gosh, it was spicy.
Deliciously spicy.
- Uncle.
- Yes?
Her face looks exactly like this drawing.
Da-bong,
can you see her too?
What? No.
There isn't anyone here.
I'm talking about her there.
Why are you on TV?
Yes.
I understand.
Thank you. Bye.
What did they say?
It's a popular audition TV show
called Tomorrow Idol.
They have female trainees compete,
and the final seven
will get to debut as an idol group.
So, did they tell you her name and age?
Loanne, and she's 19 years old.
Do you recall anything?
- Is she behind me?
- Loanne?
No, nothing.
Is it because it's a stage name?
W-What else?
D-Didn't you hear anything else?
Loanne dropped out
due to personal reasons.
But she was on TV earlier.
It was a rerun.
I might be able to hear more tomorrow
at the entertainment agency.
Who wants ice cream?
I do.
Mom, what's with him?
TAEBAEK
What is it?
It's about the company
of your case this time.
He says to ask the company yourself
for more information.
I understand.
I don't think
they allow just anyone inside.
Did you give them a call?
I did.
But they hung up
as soon as they heard the name "Loanne."
Then, how will you get in?
If there isn't a way, I'll make one.
How may I help you?
Hello, I'm Principal Attorney Shin I-rang
of Shin I-rang Law Office.
I'm here for the human rights survey
on idol groups
which is being conducted in collaboration
with the National Human Rights Commission.
Please wait here
until the person in charge comes.
Sure.
Excuse me. Where is the bathroom?
Oh, go around that corner
and you'll find it next to the elevator.
I see. Thank you.
The doors are closing.
2-3F TRAINING ROOMS
I'm here for an appointment with CEO Park.
I see.
This is like Inkigayo or something.
Let's hurry up.
We have lots of work to do.
Oh, right.
Excuse me.
Do you perhaps know who Loanne is?
Why do you ask?
I have a question to ask.
Who are you? A reporter?
No.
I'm a lawyer.
I'd like to hear some things about Loanne.
Do you have time?
Just a moment.
This is about the IP-related case.
And this lists
the stalkers of our artists.
I see.
I saw some chrysanthemums
by the entrance on my way here.
Did something happen?
Oh, that.
Loanne, Abel, Ji-on, and I joined
that audition show from our agency.
Loanne was pretty
and the best dancer among us.
I knew it.
Be quiet.
- Excuse me?
- Oh.
I meant to ask if she was a quiet girl.
She wasn't.
She had a rather loud voice.
She was more of the leader type.
Hey!
Move to the left,
to the right, and again to the left!
Must I keep repeating myself?
Are you an idiot?
Loanne was always competitive
and never let things go easily, so…
It's okay. Feel free to tell me.
The girls found it hard to deal with her.
I got confused. Sorry.
Don't make excuses.
I'll try it again.
You're confusing us all.
How will you become an idol when you can't
memorize this one easy move?
You know countless people
can't even make it to debut.
That's enough.
Abel says she'll try.
You may not know,
but my life depends on this chance.
This means everything to me.
Hey, if you're not that desperate,
stop causing harm to others
and just go home.
What is it?
Tearing up again?
I'm sick and tired of this.
You piss me off.
Still, I think
it was all thanks to Loanne
that Abel and I got to this point.
I was truly grateful to her.
I had no idea she'd end up like that.
You mean, she dropped out of the show?
No.
She killed herself.
I killed myself?
A trainee committed suicide
and the fans are going wild.
They make protests
and even write online petitions.
I'd like to sue the trolls and set
an example before it gets more serious.
Is it possible?
Several conditions are
required to sue someone
such as defamation, slander, and insult.
Let me look into it.
THE LATE KIM SU-A
"Kim Su-a,
born June 20, 2007."
- Su-a.
- Mom.
I'M ON YOUR SIDE, LOANNE
I-rang!
Hey! What's going on, I-rang?
Why are you so drained?
Are you okay?
Still, I've made progress.
What?
Her name is Kim Su-a.
She was born in 2007 in Suwon.
Su-a's mom was a young single mom.
She neither had the ability
nor leisure to raise a child.
Repeat after me.
Three-zero-one.
Once you see Grandma,
hand this to her first. Okay?
Now, go.
What about you? Aren't you coming with me?
I told you.
I have to go far away to make money.
Go.
Three-zero-one.
Three-zero…
Mom!
Where are you?
Who is it at this hour?
Grandma.
Please help me find my mom.
There, there. Come on inside.
Bong-su, are you crying?
It suddenly reminded me of my daughter.
Sorry about that. Continue.
Fortunately, her grandma
took her in warmly.
She got an unexpected family member
added to her lonely life.
And Su-a got a reliable guardian.
At that time, her grandma worked
at a diner by a construction site.
Su-a was so mature for her age
that she felt sorry for her grandmother.
Grandma.
Wait. Grandma!
So she started working part-time
as soon as she was of legal working age.
Even if she was tired from work,
she'd dance in front of her grandmother
because her grandmother enjoyed
watching her dance.
One day, she happened to dance in Hongdae
on the way to her part-time work.
A producer from Glory Entertainment
happened to see her.
That was how she became a trainee
at Glory Entertainment.
She even got to perform on stage
in her dream audition show.
WHAT KIND OF PERFORMANCE
DID THE GLORY TRAINEES PREPARE?
That Grade-A girl is so good.
Loanne definitely deserves an A.
THE TRAINERS UNANIMOUSLY GIVE
LOANNE OF GLORY ENTERTAINMENT AN "A"
She also became hopeful
that she could support her grandmother.
But in the midst of the audition show,
Su-a had to keep working part-time.
She was an acting child breadwinner
due to her grandmother's back injury.
But not all her teammates
were as desperate as her.
One, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
- One, two, three, four.
- And Su-a was too young to understand.
Hey!
Move to the left.
To the left, not to the right!
Must I keep repeating myself?
Are you an idiot?
I got confused. Sorry.
Don't make excuses.
I'll try it again.
- You're confusing us all.
- In the end,
her teammates stood up
and said they'd withdraw if Su-a didn't.
Stop causing harm to others
and just go home.
This is as far as you can go this time.
You'll have another chance.
The CEO of Glory Entertainment
pressed her to withdraw
so that he could prevent bigger losses.
The agency announced
that it was due to personal reasons,
but in fact,
she was forced to drop out.
Even so,
she shouldn't have killed herself.
She didn't.
Su-a wasn't weak.
She was brave and optimistic.
Besides, that day,
she could never have wanted to die.
I better just hurry home to see Grandma.
Hello?
It was my mom.
She said she saw me in the audition show.
But…
can you guess the first thing
she said on the phone
after more than ten years?
What did she say?
She called me pretty.
She has to be crazy.
Why did she call you?
She wanted to meet.
And?
I agreed to meet her.
I wanted to meet her too.
She abandoned her little child
to survive alone.
I was meaning to swear right to her face
when I met her again.
So, when you went to the rooftop,
it wasn't to jump off?
Me?
Absolutely not.
SAVE
MOM
That day, I had to drop out
of the audition,
but I thought I learned a big lesson.
MY STORY
ADD TO MY STORY
I AM HAPPY
But then,
there was someone else on the rooftop.
It was too dark to see their face, though.
I heard a phone ring.
I never heard that ringtone before.
PLEASE LOOK FORWARD
TO SEEING MORE OF LOANNE!
D-Does this mean
she was murdered?
The victim herself made a clear testimony.
And this is crucial evidence.
But can we catch the culprit with it?
It's hard to solve a case
with just a dead person's testimony.
We learned that from Lee Gang-pung's case.
Still, we ended up revealing the truth
behind his resentful death.
But you're an attorney.
This is a murder case.
A murder case is for the police to handle.
But all cases are bound
to reach an attorney in the end.
Besides,
Su-a was kind enough
to live her life to the fullest
without resenting her mom
despite her tough circumstances.
I can't turn a blind eye to her.
Right?
O-Of course.
That's for sure.
My mom.
What is it?
I was supposed to call my mom.
I forgot.
Her number's saved on my phone.
She must be waiting for me. What do I do?
KIM SU-A (LOANNE)
TRAINEE INFORMATION
ADDITIONAL DETAILS:
LIVES JUST WITH HER GRANDMA
ARTIST HAS DIED (AGE 19)
WHO COMMITS SUICIDE
MINUTES AFTER POSTING
THAT THEY'RE HAPPY?
Can you make some time for me?
Aren't you angry at me for stealing a look
at the investigation info?
No need. I found the evidence
and resolved the case thanks to you.
Is that so?
Then, I'll ask you for a favor at ease.
What is it?
My new client is an entertainment agency.
Let me hear you out
before giving you an answer.
A female idol trainee
died of a fall from the company rooftop.
The CEO claims that she killed herself.
But her phone disappeared from the scene.
Is it plausible that her phone
wasn't with her when she died?
No.
She wrote on her social media account
right before she died.
Someone irrelevant to the case
may have picked it up.
Or maybe the culprit.
You think she was murdered?
I'm open to the possibility.
Speaking of which,
can you check the criminal records
of the company employees
and whoever is related?
And if anyone is undergoing a lawsuit.
Why go to such lengths, though?
It's not like you.
Did you find it?
The detective in charge said that
they didn't find any phone on site.
So, the culprit took it.
But I don't get it.
They should've left the phone there
if they wanted to stage it as suicide.
Maybe there was something
they wanted to hide saved on her phone.
Where are they with the investigation?
They already closed it.
They found no traces or motives of murder.
Thank you, Bong-su.
Let's go.
Go where?
Let's go catch the culprit.
We need to find the culprit
to find your phone
and your mom's number.
First, let's look into who was left
in the building at the time.
Oh, Emma might help out.
Okay. I better start with her, then.
Wait for me.
- Ms. Park.
- Oh, my goodness!
Are you okay?
I mistook you for a ghost.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing here, Father?
I'm here to find something.
Find what?
The reason why I-rang is seeing ghosts.
Is there a reason?
Probably.
Every outcome has a cause, you know.
What brings you here?
Oh.
The truth is,
I'm here to find something too.
But then,
come to think of it,
you might have an answer for me.
Me?
A long time ago,
I-rang's dad was a prosecutor.
He was honest and steadfast.
In other words,
he was an inflexible prosecutor
who was stubborn as a mule.
One day, he got into a car accident.
His body tested positive for drugs.
What dumbfounded me more was
that they found
so much evidence of bribery
- from his computer and desk.
- I found it.
- Did you find it?
- Yes, sir.
Along with his colleague's testimony,
my husband turned
into a corrupt prosecutor in an instant.
I was so angry and resentful.
Grasping at straws,
I even visited a shaman.
And that was right here,
Unit 501 of Okcheon Building.
Could I be to blame
for what's happening to I-rang?
Because I visited a shaman?
Well…
That, I can't be sure.
But one thing is for sure.
Your son has been a good influence
to the people around him,
whether it be the dead or the living.
Aren't you going in?
What? Hold on.
What should I tell them this time?
Tax audit? National intelligence?
Let's just go.
There's a secret door only for artists
to avoid fans.
I know the passcode and where the girls
might be right now. Come on.
Why didn't you…
It's nine-four-one-two.
If they took your phone,
it means something important
was saved on it.
Does anything ring a bell?
It could be a picture
or a voice recording.
Nothing.
Except for the lyrics and songs
I wrote in my spare time,
there's nothing.
What? Lyrics and songs?
Yes.
PROCEDURAL HISTORY
CHARGE:
COPYRIGHT INFRINGEMENT
Every time he was sued, he countersued
and got acquitted each time.
Is he innocent or is he just that good?
They're probably
in that training room over there.
That's strange.
They practice here all the time.
What day is it today?
Today? It's Thursday.
Are you serious?
What is it?
It's nothing.
- Let's go again.
- Okay.
You don't have to hide.
They can't see you anyway.
Oh, right.
Do you…
have a crush on that guy?
What are you saying?
Even Da-bong would be able to tell.
Well, he's handsome. I give him that.
Hold on.
Remember what the priest said.
Being possessed manifests
when their desires reach a peak.
This doesn't feel good.
Let's hurry out of here.
Who are you?
Excuse me?
I asked who you are.
Not anyone can come in here.
May I see your entrance pass?
Please don't come close to me.
What?
Darn, it's too late.
Hello.
Is Songwriter Ko Jong-seok here today?
Just a moment, please.
He should be in the vocal training room.
Please take the elevator
to the second floor.
Thank you.
Mr. Ko.
Long time no see.
Wait. Will you stand still there and talk?
What's wrong, Mr. Ko?
- It's me.
- Don't come any closer!
Are you a reporter? A stalker fan?
It's me, Loanne.
What? Loanne?
Mr. Ko.
- Have you been well?
- Over here!
Get this man out.
- How did you get in? Let's go.
- Mr. Ko.
Don't touch me!
What is he saying? Hey, grab him.
- Let's go.
- Ouch!
All fans get criticized
because of scum like you.
Send him straight to the police station.
Mr. Ko!
Hello? What is it?
Right now?
Okay, I'll be there.
Mr. Ko! Wait!
Will you let go?
Mr. Ko!
Ma'am, he's the songwriter.
Excuse me. Wait!
Wait!
Na-hyun!
One thing is for sure.
Your son has been a good influence
to the people around him,
whether it be the dead
or the living.
Are you okay?
SPECIAL THANKS TO LAYONE
I better look more into Ko Jong-seok.
You were in the building
the day Loanne died.
- Did you perhaps meet her?
- No.
I didn't even see her that day.
Something smells fishy for sure.
She saw me write songs.
My phone.
I can't use any of Su-a's songs
if someone else knows about them.
She's in danger.
- He's trying to kill you too.
- It can't be.
Give it back to me now.
Mister, watch out!
Subtitle translation by: Eunjin Erica Kim