I don't know. I’m scared, Via.
I don’t know if it’s still worth it for us to try again.
Just use our time here in Boracay to think, Luna.
Hello, Kalix.
Hey! I just arrived here in Malaysia.
Enjoy your stay in Boracay.
I guess it’s good that
we’re on separate trips so that we can think clearly.
Again, I’m not pressuring you to give me an answer right away.
I’m willing to wait for it and work hard for it.
I know he already knows what he lost after you broke up.
But, let’s show him more.
Let’s show him what he missed out on.
You look great.
You just reminded me of our time in Boracay.
If you give me another chance,
I will never let go of you ever,
ever again.
Maybe we should go back inside?
Hey,
I know everything I said is a lot to process.
Don’t worry about it.
Take as much time as you need to process everything, okay?
Thank you, Kalix.
- Let’s go? - Yes.
Okay.
Come on.
Were you cockblocked by the rain?
Yanna…
Stop it.
I just said that the moment was ruined because it started raining.
But you felt bad that nothing happened, right? Admit it already.
Yes.
Look at her smile.
But, I’m actually glad that it suddenly rained.
How come?
The tension was quite high for both of us.
In a way,
the rain stopped us from doing something that we might regret.
Wow! You’re so levelheaded.
I really admire your self-control.
My cousin is so mature now.
And she even flirted responsibly.
I should have learned by now with all of the honest-to-goodness opinions you gave me.
So, thank you.
You’re welcome.
You did a good job, too.
Smile for the camera! Move a bit. One, two, three, smile!
This is the life!
Can we, like, extend our vacation, please?
I’m still not ready to face the stressful work.
Just let it all out later during our yacht party.
Yes, my god! I’m so excited to go party with you, girls.
I even made sure my dress was a stunner.
Oh my god, it’s Kalix!
Come on, girls. Let’s go.
You’re leaving me?
You’ll manage.
- Keep it up. - Let’s go.
Good morning!
- Hi Kalix! - Hi!
- Bye, Kalix. - Bye!
Let’s go, Yanna, hurry!
Hey!
Hi.
How’s your morning?
I didn’t get enough sleep
but it’s still a good morning.
Have you eaten yet?
My treat.
No need,
your company is already a treat.
I insist.
I know what you went through last night.
You came here to Boracay from Malaysia.
That’s definitely a tiring trip.
It wasn’t.
I wanted to be here.
Answer it.
I’m sure it’s important.
I’ll make this quick.
One order of breakfast, please.
I’m so sorry, Luna.
It seems like I can’t join you for breakfast.
I forgot I have a video call meeting with my client.
It’s okay, I know that’s important.
I’m so sorry.
Make up for it later, we’ll have a yacht party.
But if you can’t go, don’t worry about it. No pressure.
I understand.
No,
I’ll be there.
Okay.
See you.
This is the life!
Hey, this view is amazing!
Hi!
- How are you? - Hey!
- Hi! - It’s nice to see you again.
Looking good.
You too. How are you guys?
We’ve been pretty busy.
We’re so glad to be here even if it’s just a short vacation.
I feel you. I had to change my flight to tomorrow.
I wanted to enjoy Boracay a little bit.
And Luna.
What’s that?
Nothing— You’ll be leaving tomorrow?
Yes, I have a court hearing tomorrow, so…
So you really just came here for Luna, huh?
So sweet!
Speaking of— here comes Luna.
She really took her time in the ladies room.
Hey!
Hey.
I was waiting for you.
Well, I’m here.
It’s party time! Come on, come on.
Let’s go!
Excuse me.
Guys, more drinks!
Let’s keep drinking!
¡Muchas gracias!
Are you Spanish now?
Hey, that’s my drink.
Huh? Oh, sorry. I thought that was mine.
You can just have this.
- Sorry. - It’s okay. I’ll just order another one.
What do you call this thing when we were young
when you accidentally drink a glass that’s not yours?
Indirect—
kiss.
What’s that? How— How do you do it?
Can we play a game so that we’re not just drinking?
What game?
Body shot!
I’m in!
Join in, you two.
- Don’t be a killjoy. - You heard that, Kalix Jace.
Killjoys aren’t welcome here.
- What are the game mechanics? - Nothing.
You just choose the person you want to do a body shot with.
Should I go first?
- I’ll do it. - Okay!
Everyone’s joining, okay?
Pour a lot.
Let’s go, Yanna.
- I’ll take a full shot. - Full shot!
Full shot! Full shot!
Don’t you dare me.
Just kidding.
- Let’s go! - They don’t have to be too naughty.
So, I’m your first victim, huh?
Your turn!
Why me?
Because we said so.
Come on.
You don’t have to think about it,
we all know that you want to do a body shot with Luna.
Hey, stop putting pressure on him.
Come on, girls…
Oh, come on. Please?
No killjoys, right?
All right, take the shot.
No turning back now.
Go, Luna!
Hurry up!
Really? That’s so lame.
Couldn’t you make it more intense?
- Yes! Ours was– - Right here, see?
- Right here. - I know right.
Luna, show Kalix how it’s done.
Huh?
What? Why me?
- Go girl! - We’re all doing it.
And this is me talking.
Can’t I do it with Via?
Seriously? He’s right there. Go for Kalix.
Hurry up and do a body shot with Kalix!
- Do it with Kalix. - Do it, Luna.
Go girl!
Body shot with Kalix, hurry!
Okay, fine! Fine.
Okay, another drink.
That’s it?
How boring. Let’s just go dance, guys.
Let’s go, hurry! Let’s dance.
- Come on. - Let’s go, let’s go!
Okay, we’re just gonna dance.
What time is your flight tomorrow?
11 AM. I have to be there after lunch.
So, does that mean that you can’t sleep late tonight?
I can.
This is my only chance to enjoy Boracay with you.
Okay. Let’s make it worth it.
You wanna dance?
- Come on! - I don’t know how to dance.
Come on! I’ll teach you.
Come on.
Let’s dance, let’s dance.
So, just feel the vibe and listen to the music.
You look great today.
You look hot.
Just a minute, I’ll get us some drinks.
Okay.
Hey, hold on.
You dropped this.
I’m sorry.
Turn around.
Can I?
Are you cold?
A bit. The air is getting quite chilly.
I have a jacket
in my bedroom.
I can pick it up before going to the after party.
No, it’s okay.
I insist.
You might get sick.
Fine. I’ll go with you to keep you company.
Okay.
Your jacket.
Thanks.
I’ll help you.
What’s wrong?
Nothing.
Let’s go.
Okay.
I love you, Luna.
Stand up.
What?
Good morning.
You’re leaving?
Yes, love.
Have to catch a flight.
It’s okay.
I’m sorry.
You weren’t able to sleep last night.
There’s nothing to be sorry about.
Come here.
Closer.
Good?
Luna?
Yes?
What are your thoughts about marrying me?
Are you proposing right now?
I’m just asking you a question.
I haven’t thought about it yet.
Don’t worry.
No pressure.
I just wanna let you know that those thoughts cross my mind.
We can talk about it more when we both get back.
I’m just handling a big case right now so I’ll be busy.
But after that,
can I take you out?
Of course.
Thank you for this short trip but sweet.
I’ll never forget this.
Take care.
I will.
- Bye. - See you.
Hey!
You girls really had fun in Boracay, huh? I saw the social posts.
Where’s Luna, by the way? What’s taking so long?
She texted me that she’s just parking. She’ll be on her way.
Excuse me, sir. Your meals are ready. Should I serve it now?
Sure, please have this table ready first then serve it.
Oh, wait a minute!
It’s so good. Thank you!
I miss hanging out here. Do you remember, back in college?
You’re right. I miss it too.
And the view–
Oh, there she is.
Hey, guys!
My god, I was swamped with work and the traffic was so bad.
So…
What’s up with you and Kalix?
Have you seen him recently?
Really, Sevi, that’s your first question?
Not even a “How are you? Are you okay?”
But no.
We haven’t even talked to each other yet.
Huh?
It’s been almost two weeks since the Boracay trip.
How come you two haven’t spoken yet?
Is he still busy?
I figured. He hasn’t been visiting the site, too.
That’s because he’s handling a pretty big case right now.
Besides, he’s been updating me anyway.
I’m not even his girlfriend. So who am I to demand?
Why aren’t you though?
They had the chance to actually talk about their status when they were in Boracay.
But they did something else.
- Because they— - Nope, nope.
- I don’t want to hear the details. - Listen.
We're conservative here.
- Tell him. - I don’t want to hear it.
You need to.
- You need to. - I don’t.
- Tell him. - So this is what happened—
We just enjoyed ourselves.
Come on.
Wasn’t your status already confirmed after what happened?
I mean, that wasn’t just a hookup, right?
Of course not.
And he even talked about marriage.
That’s a whole other level, Luna.
You’re right.
But I still want us to talk things through on what our status really is.
I also want to hear it from him directly.
Like what Ke said, we don’t need to rush.
So, I’m willing to wait for Kalix.
There really is a miracle!
The Luna Valeria,
is now willing to wait?
She’s not jumping to conclusions now
and she’s willing to listen first before reacting.
She also trusts him.
Wow! Major upgrade, girl.
Come on, guys, nothing new here.
It’s just me, Luna.
A very patient, Luna.
She knows how to wait now.
It’s Kalix.
And she’s quick, too.
Can we meet tomorrow…
Can we meet tomorrow?
I have a meeting tomorrow.
A meeting?
Oh, I can have it cleared up. I can clear it up.
I don’t think she’s talking to us.
She just said that she can wait.
- But she quickly cancelled— - So quick…
- Amazing. - Did I say, upgrade?
- No, I said you’re pretty! So pretty. - Nothing, nothing at all.
- Awesome, right? - So pretty.
Why are we here?
Is this where our date will be?
I bought this land before.
I wanted to show it to you.
So, you brought me here to get my opinion as an architect.
Maybe.
I’m just kidding.
I’m gonna bring you to Tagaytay.
But, before that,
I wanted to show you this lot
and know your opinion about it.
You’re getting spoiled.
You should’ve set a meeting with me.
Everything I do as an architect is paid, you know.
I’m willing to pay.
Is that so? Well then, okay.
I like the location
and the lot is pretty big.
What do you plan to do here?
I don’t know… yet.
Just sell it to me.
I’ve been looking for a lot for my dream house.
This is perfect.
Sure.
Really?
For how much?
60 million.
60 million?
Isn’t that too much?
Don’t you have any…
discounts?
An ex-girlfriend discount or something.
I know an easier way and cheaper way too for you to get this lot.
Okay then, let’s negotiate.
Well,
you can marry me.
Stop joking around.
The price for an ex-girlfriend is 60 million
but if you'll be my wife, it's free.
This is the second time you did this.
The next time you propose, I’m just gonna think that it’s a joke.
Hold on, wait.
I have to get this.
Hello?
What’s up?
What?
Okay. Yes, sure.
Just text me the address.
I’ll be there. Bye.
- I have to go, sorry— - What happened?
Amy was rushed to the hospital
and Leo doesn’t want to give me the full details yet.
I’m worried.
Let’s go then. Let’s go to the hospital.
You’re okay with that?
Come on, Kalix.
You’re friends with Amy and I know you’re worried.
- Let’s go? - Yes, let’s go.
How’s Amy?
Amy was shot.
How is she?
Don’t worry, the bullet wasn’t too deep
so they were able to get it out.
She was conscious earlier.
Maybe she just fell asleep.
Why was she shot?
Do you have a suspect in mind?
She’s been receiving death threats ever since
she lost Miguel’s case and he went to jail.
Kalix, there’s paperwork I have to do.
You take care of Amy for now.
Her family is on the way.
Sorry. Excuse me.
You wanna go in?
Do you want to check up on Amy?
I don’t know if I can, Luna.
I feel bad.
It’s my fault.
I was the one to ask her
to take on Miguel’s case.
Why would you do that?
I asked Amy to play dirty.
Since the people that she was going to defend
were already playing dirty in the first place.
She was making Miguel’s camp believe that
she was preparing to win the case
when actually she was just digging his grave.
I’m surprised that Amy accepted the case.
She asked for my forgiveness.
Those were my condition.
She had to accept the case and lose it.
But—
How could she do that?
Wasn’t that against your oath?
Amy did her job.
She defended Miguel in court.
She just didn’t do it well on purpose
and trust me it takes a lot of skills for a lawyer to intentionally lose a case.
Besides, Miguel’s family wanted Amy to pin the crime
on someone else just to win the case.
An innocent person, Luna.
They’ve even tried to pay the first prosecutor.
They tried to play with the justice system.
Amy never played dirty before but I told her that if she’s going to,
to do it with someone like Miguel.
He deserved it.
I can be professional with Attorney Martinez.
But I don’t wanna work with him.
I’ve heard he protected an abuser, Dad.
I did my research and I didn’t really see Kalix's name
in the list of the Villaflors’ legal representatives.
I did see Amethyst’s name, though.
Kalix asked her to take it.
That was also Amy’s first loss.
If I had taken that case,
you would have hated me forever.
You would have never talked to me again.
I can't ever live with that.
I’m really sorry if I disappointed you.
I just—
didn’t know that things would turn out the way they did.
Kalix,
don’t be too hard on yourself.
At the end of the day, the intention was to send a bad guy to jail.
Amy will be okay.
She’s a strong person.
How are you feeling?
I’m fine. It’s not severe.
I told you to tighten your security.
Kalix, I’ve been a criminal lawyer for years now.
I get death threats all the time. It’s just—
Just so happens that this pushed through.
He’s a crazy, damn politician.
You should have known better.
What? So it’s my fault now?
Kalix.
Maybe you should go out and buy our food.
I’ll stay here with Amy.
Fine.
Are you gonna scold me too?
Why would I?
I’m glad you’re alive.
I won’t die that easily.
Luna?
I almost died today.
And that changes a person’s perspective.
So let me be direct.
I’m so sorry.
I’m so sorry for everything that I’ve done to you and Kalix.
I’ve ruined your relationship.
I fucked up.
I know that the damage has been done
and this apology is years too late but—
Still, I’m sorry.
I guess I was scared to talk to you?
Because Kalix was so ruthless with me and I just couldn’t
handle another tirade,
even if I knew I deserved it.
To be honest,
I was really upset with you.
My life changed because of what you did.
I lost years with Kalix.
I even questioned my own worth.
That’s the kind of pain I wish you would never experience.
It’s so hard to build yourself up again.
I’m not gonna make excuses for my behavior.
And I begged Kalix for forgiveness years ago so now I just—
I just wanna beg for yours.
You don’t have to beg.
If Kalix forgave you, why wouldn’t I?
Besides, it’s not good to hold on to grudges.
I forgive you, Amy.
Thank you, Luna.
I’ve been ridden of guilt all these years
and I’m just so happy I get to do this in person.
Just promise me, you’ve changed.
Yes.
I believe in karma.
Maybe this is my karma.
Just trying to be a better person now.
Wow! You really prepared.
Wine?
Cheers.
Luna…
I know I mentioned it before as a joke.
And right now I just want to be clear.
I want us to get back together
with the intention of marrying you.
I know
I had a lot of shortcomings before.
But this time I’ll do better.
I wanna be braver,
more protective of us,
to the extent that I won’t let anything
or anyone ruin our relationship again.
So many things have happened in our lives
but my love for you only grew stronger.
It’s been almost ten years,
but it’s still you.
And it will always be you.
That was an amazing speech.
I feel a bit pressured.
You’re not the only one with shortcomings, Kalix.
So do I.
I want to be better too.
Let’s grow old together?
Yes,
I want us to be together.
I still love you, Kalix.
I love you, Luna.
So,
let’s do the boyfriend-girlfriend thing?
Did you plan this, too?
I guess the world also wants to celebrate us.
I love you.
Ate Luna!
Hi. Hi Kio.
Hello!
Luna, this is Kelsey, my sister.
Hi Luna! It’s nice to finally meet you.
I feel the same way too, Doc.
Please, just Kelsey is fine.
I can’t believe I was just in med school when you guys first got together.
And now we’re here.
Where’s Mom and Dad?
Oh yeah, we’re just waiting for the reservation.
Come on, let’s go see them.
- Okay. - Kio, let’s go.
Mom, Dad, look who’s here.
Luna…
I’m glad you can join us today.
It’s nice to see you two together.
Thank you, Doc.
Mom,
Luna wants to say hi.
Hi, Doc.
Architect Valeria,
so good to see you.
Thank you for inviting me and you can call me Luna.
Sir Martinez, table’s ready.
Okay, let’s go.
Kalix, can I talk to Luna privately?
- Go ahead. - Okay.
Sure.
Luna,
I’ve never seen Kalix smile this much.
Not even when he topped the bar.
So,
I think you’re really making him happy.
I try my best to be there for him.
You know what Luna,
Kalix and I did not have the best relationship.
We had issues, we still argue every now and then.
But I love my son, dearly.
And I’m glad he—
He found someone to love and care about.
Luna, you promise me you’ll continue being there for Kalix?
Because you’re good for him.
Yes and thank you.
I’ll support Kalix no matter what.
- Really? - Yes.
Thank you.
Thank you, Luna.
Luna,
am I making you nervous?
Your hand’s cold.
Don’t be, okay?
I’m just like this but I don’t bite.
You know how mothers are.
- Mom. - Yes?
Luna.
Everything all right?
Yes!
We were talking about you.
Okay. Let’s go.
Let’s go.
Cheers everyone!
Cheers!
Let’s party tonight!
It’s good.
Hey, where’s Luna?
I don’t know. I’ve been texting her but she hasn’t responded.
Where could she be?
Text her again. She must’ve fallen asleep.
Guys, try the food.
- She’s here! - It’s delicious.
Hey!
Are you two back together?
Oh my god!
I never doubted you two.
Glad you got back together with him, Luna.
I’m so happy for the two of you.
So, why were you two late?
But what happened? Tell us everything!
Tell us!
Bro, you better take care of my best friend.
I’ve grown so tired of her.
Wow! Seriously, Sevi.
No, just kidding.
Just make sure to love each other, bro.
Hey Kalix, I know where you live.
If you ever make Luna cry, you’ll be dealing with us.
Heard that? That was a threat so you better watch out.
Yes, ma’am.
Such a princess!
Guys, before anything else.
Drink… Here you go, Kalix.
Cheers to Luna and Kalix. LuKal forever!
Cheers!
I saw that!
How is it?
Show me the pregnancy test.
Two lines.
- Two lines! - Oh my god! Oh my god!
Luna, it’s positive! It's positive!
OMG!
Avi finally has a playmate!
I’m so glad I had my stay extended!
I wouldn’t miss this for anything!
Why are you crying?
I’m just so happy.
I—
I can’t believe Kalix and I are gonna have a baby.
I’m just not sure if he’s ready to start a family.
Come on… Seriously?
He’s even more excited than you.
It’ll be fine, Luna.
You can do this!
Right, he’s going to be so happy, Luna.
Trust us.
Really? You really think so?
You think he’s ready to start a family?
Of course, you’re the only one he’s waiting for.
Besides, we’re sure that you two will be the best parents.
And you guys will be the best godmothers.
Congratulations!
- Thank you! - Careful now.
It’s a little bit cloudy right now,
but it’s going to be a full moon tonight.
Hope we see it.
Are you okay?
Yes, I’m more than okay.
I have a gift for you.
A gift?
What’s the occasion?
That’s so sweet of you.
Thank you, Love.
Just open it.
Luna…
I’m going to be a dad?
You’re not kidding me?
Are you happy?
Yes!
Fuck, yes!
Of course!
Are you happy?
Of course, I’m happy.
We’re going to be a family.
Luna,
I have a gift for you, too.
I’ve been meaning to ask you for the longest time.
Please.
Marry me,
Architect Luna Valeria?
Please?
What’s wrong?
Love, you’re crying and laughing at the same time.
I know, I’m just— I’m just so happy.
And it’s because of you.
It’s all because of you.
I love you so much,
Attorney Kalix Jace Martinez.
Yes, of course I’ll marry you.
Let’s do the husband-wife thing?
Yeah.
I love you, Luna.
I love you, Kalix.
We love you, too, little one.
- We love you, too. - We love you, too.
Oh my god!
Hi.
I can’t imagine myself enjoying this life
with anyone else but Luna.
With her, I have the moon… and the stars.
I couldn’t ask for more.
Action!
Sorry.
Marco! Cut.
I didn't do anything.
Don't you laugh.
Ready. Okay.
You're really not helping.
And...
I didn't do anything.
Ready, and action!
Let's feast!
My parents are already on the way.
Come on, let's go.
Direk, Marco is not helping.
Luna.
What is that?
Behind Marco?
Stop that, stop that!
It hurts.
Sorry.
Sorry! Are you okay?
Now look at the underwears.
Cut! Good!
Action!
Sorry!
Shake it off.
Heaven!