( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
I think I know who did it.
P’Oh-Lin… your friend.
Is Do still around?
Show yourself.
Direk, remember Do, the one who got killed?
He’s still lingering around.
Do you think Mom is still around?
Emma’s gone.
Emma, stop nagging.
I heard that kid next door who can talk to ghosts
I heard him talking to Emma, Direk.
Emma’s still here, Direk.
Mom’s still here.
What are you doing, sir?
You can’t go in.
Why not?
No entry without a pass.
-I’m going up to see Direk.
-You can’t.
-No outsiders allowed.
-I’m going to see Direk.
Staff only.
You don’t know who I am?
No, I don’t.
Little sperm.
What?
Hello, Direk.
Your security won’t let me in.
What? Why?
He says he doesn’t know me.
Is he new or something?
Ok, hang on. I’ll handle it.
Please check on this, my son can’t get into the company. He’s stuck outside.
Damn, what the hell are you wearing?
Just grabbed whatever I could find.
If I were the guard, I wouldn’t let you in either.
Did you get any sleep?
I couldn’t sleep.
About Emma?
Emma, stop nagging.
Since when did you become such a nag?
I’m not talking to you anymore.
Are you hallucinating or something?
Your mom can’t even speak Thai.
Oh… right.
Well…
I didn’t think about that.
I was just shocked the name was the same.
Emma’s such a common name anyway.
Who would think it’d be that much of a coincidence?
By the way—
which Emma?
Since living in that condo,
I’ve never heard of a ghost named Emma.
Do you really think this is about ghosts?
That kid can talk to ghosts.
He can see and communicate with spirits.
You don’t believe me, do you?
Honestly, I wouldn’t either
if I hadn’t seen it myself.
What kind of crazy person talks to ghosts?
What are you even talking about?
Just listen first.
The one who helped find Do’s killer
it was him.
He talked to the ghost for us.
Shit.
You’re thinking of asking him to find Emma, right?
Wow, I’m really lucky today, got someone to drive me home.
Maybe I should buy a lottery ticket.
After you, Mr. President.
Direk!
Why’d you hit me? That hurts.
You’re asking for it.
Since I’m sitting here, drive properly.
This isn’t a racetrack, got it?
Yes, sir.
Hey, you idiot—
Direk,
don’t forget to pay me for the ride.
I didn’t drive you for free.
How much?
Four hundred thousand.
Go ask your dad for it.
I’m asking him right now.
Hey, I’m serious.
I need it to fix my car, Direk.
I’ll pay you back after the next race.
No more racing.
Focus on your rotations. Focus on your studies.
I’ve seen your grades—I’m seriously disappointed.
What the hell?
Look at your friends, especially Tonfah.
You’re the last person who deserves to be friends with him.
Wow.
No shame and you’re laughing?
-Ow!
-Then what’s the difference between me and Fah?
That’s the dumbest question I’ve ever heard.
Seriously,
can you handle med school?
Why would you ask that?
Because I know you’re studying medicine for your mom.
You promised Emma you’d become a doctor to treat her.
But now she’s gone.
If you want to change your mind now… no one’s gonna blame you.
Mom must be really disappointed then.
Emma’s not disappointed in you.
Same here.
’Cause I never expected anything from you anyway.
You just got back from class and you're working again?
Aren’t you pushing yourself too hard, Michael?
I just wanna keep myself busy.
So I don’t overthink.
I thought you said you don’t miss him anymore.
Khun Kim said he likes the cover we made.
Just need to tweak the lighting a bit.
Khun Kim’s easy to work with.
He could totally become our regular client.
He’s hired us quite a few times already.
"Of course, dear client.
I’ll adjust the lighting a bit.
and send it over ASAP."
Open the door.
Open up.
Hey!
Who’s Emma?
-You heard that?
-Yeah.
When?
Last night.
Shit.
What? What do you mean “shit”?
It’s nothing.
Hey.
You still haven’t answered me.
Who’s Emma?
A wandering spirit or something?
A friend.
A friend or a ghost?
Be honest.
A friend.
An imaginary friend or what?
Mm.
What kind of guy is named Daotok? Sounds like a girl’s name.
I heard he can see ghosts too.
Creepy. I’ve seen him talking to himself.
My mom said to stay away from him if possible.
Hi.
Can I sit with you?
Sure.
What’s your name?
I’m Michael.
Hi, Michael.
Hi.
Emma.
Why Emma?
Emma Watson.
I used to love Harry Potter as a kid.
Whatever.
Call them whatever the hell you want.
But can you use another name?
Don’t use Emma.
Emma is Emma.
I’ve been using it for ages.
I’m not changing it.
You—
Then...
Do me a favor.
-No.
-Hey, what the hell is wrong with you?
You keep slamming the door on me.
Are you gonna help me or not?
If you won’t,
I’ll have North talk to you anyway.
That’s cheating.
So what’s it gonna be?
Help with what?
Talk to Emma for me.
Emma… my mom.
Talk to my mom for me.
In the bush—go, go!
Yeah, finish it!
Nice!
Nice, take the tower—nice!
That’s clean.
-Waiting for Jo?
-Yeah, P’.
All done.
Oh.
What happened to you?
Are you the doctor or the patient?
Pick up your meds at counter two.
I’m not in the mood to mess with you today.
Don’t have the energy to argue either.
Hey, North.
Can I get your friend’s Line?
Which friend? I’ve got tons of friends.
The guy next door.
Oh, Daotok?
Yeah.
Are you trying to hit on my friend?
Hell no.
What a relief.
I thought you were hitting on him.
If you were,
I’d be the first to stop you no matter what.
No.
I just need his help with something.
It’s important.
Important?
He’s right next door. Why not ask him yourself?
Man...
We keep missing each other.
When I’m in my room,
he’s not.
When he’s in,
I’ve gotta drag myself up early for rounds.
Life...
Alright, I’ll send it to you.
Hey, North.
Your friend...
I don’t know if I should say this, but—
he—
What about him?
He’s got an imaginary friend.
What?
Named Emma.
- Same name as my mom.
- Hey!
Emma.
- Emma!
- Asshole, how old are you? Still making fun of parents’ names, Nid?
Hey, Nid is my mom.
Oh, really?
So this “imaginary friend” thing—
is it real?
I don’t know.
But I’ve seen him talking like someone’s there.
Like really talking?
That’s creepy.
Should he see a doctor?
Is it dangerous?
A doctor?
No idea.
Maybe.
Mm.
I’ll talk to him.
Yeah, thanks.
Alright, I’m off.
See you, P’.
See you, Nid.
Hey, that’s my mom!
What’s with him?
Hey.
Where’d you get my Line?
North.
Where?
Where are you?
Mm.
Is she still around?
I don’t know.
What?
Well—
that’s why I’m asking for your help.
What if she’s not around anymore?
Then I can finally move on.
Can you give me more details?
Mm.
Go ahead.
What did she pass away from?
Cancer.
How long has it been?
Seven years.
So… can you actually see if she’s with me?
Let me finish my work first. I need to send this today.
Yeah.
Hold on.
Do you have a photo of your mom?
Yeah.
So?
No.
What do you mean?
There's no
your mom.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
I checked everywhere.
If you wear that necklace, you won’t see ghosts?
I still do.
Then?
So why wear it?
It only blocks weaker spirits.
Some spirits—you need to take it off and focus to see them.
Are you okay?
You look pale as hell.
Hey—
What if Emma isn’t following me?
She could be with my dad or somewhere else, right?
Right?
It could be somewhere familiar—
or with someone she had a bond with.
Anything’s possible.
Hey.
Since you’ve helped me already,
can you help me a bit more?
Can I say no?
No.
Has he texted you again?
We’ll see each other soon. I miss you.
Why is he doing this?
Why would he come back?
Right?
What should we do, Emma?
Should we just run away?
Yeah.
Run far away from him.
How far is “far”?
Where are you going?
I don’t know.
That’s worrying.
When Michael overthinks, you tend to do weird things.
I’m not gonna do anything weird.
Why’d you dye your hair that color?
Is it weird?
Well…
Not really.
Just… not used to it.
Hey.
Why are you so quiet?
Why?
Usually when people ride with me,
they complain that I drive too fast.
Mm.
You do drive fast.
Aren’t you scared?
No.
Hello there.
Hello.
Are you sure about this?
Yeah.
Do whatever you want.
Make yourself at home.
Thit, so?
Yeah, wait a sec.
Emma liked this room.
Even though she’s not here anymore,
we’ve kept everything of hers the same.
What kind of husband are you? Your wife doesn’t even follow you.
Hey.
You…
Direk.
She’s not here either.
Hey.
Are you sure this guy is reliable?
Yeah, he is.
He helped solve Do’s case last time.
But what if this time
we don’t find her?
Then we’ll just have to let it go.
Mm.
Yeah.
We’ve come this far already.
Why don’t we try going to her house?
California, you mean?
Yeah.
When Emma was with us,
she mostly lived there.
She only came to Thailand occasionally.
If she’s still alive, she’d probably be there,
not here.
You mean…
my mom might still be there?
She likes it here.
Huh?
Your mom—
she likes it here, right?
Yeah.
How do you know?
I don’t know.
I can’t explain it.
Maybe it’s just a feeling.
So only the feeling remains.
But she’s gone.
She’s not here anymore.
There’s one more place.
My mom’s house.
Where?
California.
Let’s wait until the semester ends.
So that’s a yes?
Deal.
What’s wrong?
Hey.
Hey—
You—
What’s wrong with you?
So what’s going on?
You suddenly started crying.
P’…
Yeah?
It’s because of you.
What?
I’m sorry.
When I take off the necklace, I can’t really control my power.
Wait—
What the hell do you mean?
I accidentally read your feelings.
Who told you to mess with my feelings?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
Then why are you crying?
What?
Why are you such a sad person?
Do I really look that sad?
But I'm not someone who cries easily.
Are you stupid or what?
Crying for someone else?
What?
You're looking at me like you're insulting me.
Yeah.
I am.
Shit.
P'.
I'm sorry.
For accidentally reading your feelings.
Yeah.
Whatever.
Thanks, man.
For helping with my mom.
Hey, what's up with P'Thit hair?
That's just how he is. He woke up late and didn’t fix his hair.
I'll see you at the hospital.
Okay. I miss you.
Hey.
New hair?
Damn, that looks cool as hell.
Where are Ter and Maew?
Those two are studying all day.
I just found out,
vet and photo majors are insanely demanding.
Who can I even report this to?
My friends are gone all day.
But engineering’s probably just as tough, right?
Hey, Daotok.
I’ve got something to ask you.
Yeah.
About Emma.
P'Arthit told me,
but he didn’t mean any harm.
I talked to him, and I think
he’s worried about you.
That’s why I had to talk to you.
North.
Hm?
Aren’t you scared?
Scared of what?
Aren’t you scared of me?
What are you talking about?
Emma’s been with me since I was a kid.
Hey, seriously?
She didn’t disappear when you grew up?
Whoa.
So,
what kind of person is Emma?
She’s kind.
She understands everyone.
I can talk to her about anything.
Hey, you can talk to me about anything too.
Yeah, yeah.
She's a good person. That's enough
I’m just worried about you.
Hey, I’ve got one more thing.
About…
P'Arthit.
- Let’s not talk about him.
- Why?
What’s going on?
- He made me cry.
- What?
He made someone as numb as you cry?
Sorry, I didn’t mean to call you numb.
Sometimes you just seem like it.
Hey, talk to me first.
- I’m not talking to North anymore.
- Hey.
You’re really sulking at me?
I already said sorry.
Have you been waiting long?
Not long.
Just got back from club activities.
I heard you made my friend cry.
Huh?
What did you do to him?
What the hell? My friend’s tough as hell, look at him now.
You must’ve done something serious.
Tell me right now, P'Thit.
Hey, hey—I didn’t do shit.
What the hell?
Yo, Jo, I’m heading out.
-Hey.
-Yeah, see you.
P'Thit, get back here and tell me now!
Hey! P’Thit! Thit!
-Damn it.
-If you wanna know, go ask him yourself.
Calm down.
Shit.
What the hell is this?
Hello?
Yeah.
Wanna play a game?
-No.
-What the hell?
Guess your junior don’t matter anymore, huh?
I’ve got an early morning tomorrow.
Your husband, huh?
Go to sleep.
Yeah, right.
He’s got an early ward shift with us tomorrow.
I told you, you came later.
You think you can cut into me and Jo?
Not a chance.
So I really am just the backup, huh?
One day P'Jo’s gonna dump me, right?
Damn you.
Who are you talking to?
I need to learn to be on my own.
You’re so full of shit.
Be on your own? What's that?
It' not gonna happen.
This dumbass again.
Jo, you idiot—
The hell? You’re the idiot, Thit.
How’d you hear that?
-Hey, North.
-Yeah, P'?
Let me ask you something.
If someone cried for you,
how would you feel?
Who?
Daotok?
My friend.
Your friend? Who?
Daeng.
Daeng. His name’s Daeng.
My friend’s name is Daeng.
That fake name sounds stupid, P’.
Then why cry for him? Why doesn’t he cry himself?
How the hell would I know? I’m not Daeng.
Then let me guess.
Daeng’s the type who doesn’t like crying, keeps everything in.
Never tells anyone, just bottles it up.
What an idiot. Thinks that makes him cool or something?
In the end, the one who gets hurt is you, dumbass.
You’ve got people to talk to, yet you keep it all to yourself.
Why act so tough?
I feel bad for Daeng.
What’s your problem?
P'Jo asked me to tell you this.
Jo, you idiot.
-Tell him yourself. I’m not saying it.
-So?
Is this really about Daeng or someone else?
Daeng.
He told me to say it.
Oh.
P'Jo.
Hmm?
P'Thit
says, “I’m not telling you, dumbass.”
That’s from Daeng.
You’re so dead, asshole.
- Oh, you mean Daeng?
- No, I mean you, Thit.
Savage.
Hey, son.
Hello, Khun John.
I missed you.
You din't miss me, right?
Of course I do.
I missed you and Dad the most.
Missed you too.
Khun John,
how was your trip?
The outside is so nice.
Um.
But the rent so cheap, right.
Yes.
I thought it’d be an abandoned condo.
Yes, I thought that too.
This is the only place around here that allows pets.
I see.
That's why.
Let’s go inside.
Sounds good.
Mr.John gained about one kilo.
Which one of you made him gain weight?
Oh, it was definitely Phai.
Excuse me?
Just kidding.
How have you been?
Khram’s coming back to Thailand.
Do you still miss him?
Not at all.
I don’t miss him.
I don’t want to go back either.
But every time I think of him,
it still hurts.
I’ll be in Chicago for three years.
Aren’t you really coming to see me off?
No.
Dao.
Are you okay?
Are you mad at me for having to be apart?
But it’s okay.
I’ll come back to see you often, Dao.
Okay?
From now on,
you don’t have to come back anymore.
Dao.
I’ve been trying to look pass it all this time,
because I believed people make mistakes.
But sneaking around with my friend?
Isn’t that going too far?
Dao, I can explain this.
Since you’re going abroad anyway,
please get out of my life too.
Let’s not see each other again.
It still hurts.
But the reason it still lingers
is there something left unresolved?
When you broke up, you never really cleared things up.
There must be
a lot left in your heart.
About yourself and about him.
Do you want me to go talk to Kram, Dad?
Just a suggestion.
Whichever path you choose,
I’ll support you.
But running away for years like this hasn’t helped at all.
It’s better to be honest and talk about why it happened,
what caused it, and what’s still unresolved between you.
So you can finally settle it.
And I also think
he couldn’t take care of you.
So I want you to talk it out,
so you can move on,
and not end up back here again.
You understand what I mean, right?
Okay.
If he comes back,
I’ll find a chance to talk to him.
That’s good.
And don’t go alone.
Bring someone with you.
Someone.
Hey.
What can I do for you?
Dad, who’s that?
What is it?
Uh…
Just wanted to ask when you’re free.
Whenever you are.
I’ve only got a few exams left before break.
Mm.
Okay.
I won’t bother you then.
Dad?
“Daddy” not meaning father?
Damn, this kid’s got guts.
Not bad.
A friend?
My neighbor.
Knocking that loudly?
No manners at all.
Exactly.
Actually,
I’m going to California
during the break.
On vacation?
Not quite.
I have something to take care of.
Your friend?
The guy who just knocked the door.
Long story.
Mr. John’s here.
- So cute.
- I wanna play with him.
You’re obsessed.
Where are you going?
Getting coffee.
On a motorcycle?
Yeah.
I’ll take you.
It’s late.
Come on.
Aren’t you bringing work?
I need to get back to Mr. John.
The one in your room?
Mr. John is a cat.
Oh.
It wasn’t easy clearing my schedule for California.
I even got Direk to pay for my ticket.
You’re not gonna ditch me, right?
Hey.
Why so quiet?
In return for helping you,
I’ve got a condition.
What condition?
Help me deal with my ex.
Huh?
So what’s going on with your ex?
Did he stop bothering you?
Then let P’Arthit help you.
What do you mean?
Have P’Arthit deal with your ex for you.
- Is that a good idea?
- It is.
An ex like yours who keeps harassing you—
-Kram.
-Kam? Who the hell’s named Kam?
Kram.
Yeah, that asshole Kram—
he needs to deal with someone like my brother.
Hey.
Trust me.
Let P’Thit help you.
He already owes you one anyway.
And besides,
P’Thit isn’t useful for much,
but this is one of them.
He can be your guard dog.
Honestly, I wanna help you too,
but if you get back with your ex, I’ll look like an idiot.
So I’ll send P’Arthit to bark in my place.
Woof.
My ex…
Help me.
Alright.
Who is it?
What’s your problem, asshole?
So?
If you miss someone,
does that mean you still love them?
Dao, thanks for helping me.
Don’t you ever think about opening your heart?
If you’re still around, come see our son sometimes.