[birds chirping]
[solemn music rises]
[braying]
[braying loudly]
[gasps]
[snorting, huffing]
[coins rattling]
It's the Musso farm.
Bella's not well. Yes. Please hurry!
[braying continues]
[light upbeat music playing]
It's a good thing you heard her braying.
If you hadn't called when you did,
they probably would've died.
It was a breech birth.
How many times a day
do we give the antibiotic?
- I'll write it all down.
- Thank you, Doctor.
Hello… Have you thought of a name?
[in Sign Language] Topsy-Turvy.
"Topsy-Turvy?"
What, are you trying to be funny?
I told you yesterday
Bella felt like she had a fever.
But you don't listen to me.
You're so hard-headed.
We're both hard-headed.
So glad we moved here
to become mule breeders.
[music fades]
[faint music in headphones]
It's your first day at school,
and that's what you're wearing? Go change!
Mama! Mama! Don't be a pain!
To Topsy-Turvy!
- [clinking]
- [sighs]
[water running]
[sighs]
[sloshing]
[clattering]
[spoon clanking]
[whisking]
- [bells clink]
- [saw buzzes]
[swishing loudly]
[scattered clamor continues]
[clinking]
- [slurps]
- [slams]
[burps loudly]
What the hell, guys?!
Try making an effort?
[loud clanking, banging]
- [notes pinging]
- Boo!
No music when we're at the table!
See ya! I'm leaving. Gonna be late.
See ya, bitch.
Right back at you!
Mama, please! I'm not 4 anymore.
I'll see you at the clinic. Bye-bye!
[sighs]
[chickens clucking in distance]
["Dal giorno in cui sei NATO tu"
by Andrea Laszlo De Simone plays]
[song playing in headphones]
FEEL MY VOICE
[sings in Italian]
♪ …the most beautiful in the world  ♪
♪ And your eyes are the most sincere  ♪
♪ And in my heart lies a true love  ♪
♪ Since the day you were born  ♪
[ringtone playing]
[in English] Yes, Mrs. Bocchio?
- [indistinct chatter]
- [girl] I hear we're having a quiz today!
Yes, I'm afraid we have to
cancel the order, Mr. Bocchio.
A 20% increase is just too much.
Our donkeys will never notice
the difference between your feed
and Mr. Marzarin's, I assure you.
Unless you're willing to meet us halfway?
We appreciate that.
All the best to your wife.
[school bell ringing]
We can't move towards something
unless we know where we came from.
Now, these tests are designed to help us
assess where each of you stands
before you begin these last three years.
[class laughing]
[teacher] I assess that
this young lady is still in dreamland.
- Am I right?
- Yes.
[teacher] Well,
aren't we off to a good start…
So, what will our educational goals be
for these next three years?
One… to deepen our self-knowledge.
Two… to strengthen
our confidence in our abilities.
- How are ya? Martina.
- And three…
- To learn to face our mistakes.
- Eletta.
Eletta?
Really?
[soft pop song playing]
That's Gregorio. [Chuckles]
He's totally obsessed with me.
First, I gave him a little kiss
in grade school,
then we made out more in middle school,
and finally, I let him
explore a bit up top.
[laughs] I blame it all on my parents.
They're both shrinks.
They told me I needed
to work on my empathy.
So, that's what I did. And your parents?
They're donkey breeders.
Tell me you're joking.
- Eletta, who breeds donkeys?
- We do, on our farm.
Tell me more…
Besides the donkeys we have geese,
some sheep and chickens.
No, I mean do you have any other
weird stuff to tell me about yourself?
Nope. Nothing else "weird."
So! What's left to choose from?
Ceramics, photography, singing, theater…
Do you think, "Singing?"
Shit, no. I'm tone-deaf.
[music fades]
[Eletta] You know him?
A douche bag from fifth year.
Nickname's "Marco the Giant."
A fighter in the MMA.
You know it?
[soft pop music resumes]
[yelling]
[friend] Look at that.
Naked men beating each other up!
- [chuckles]
- Let's pick this course.
- Hi.
- Name?
Marco… Traversato.
- [woman] Course pick?
- Singing.
- Singing…
- Maybe not as tough as he seems to be.
Really?
Eletta Musso. Singing.
[man] Alright. Sign here, please.
- Do you know what you're doing?
- [chuckles]
- Singing. [Sighs]
- [man] Um, name, please?
- Whose?
- [man] Uh, yours?
Martina.
- Tell me the course.
- Put your hands down, dumb-dumb.
[laughs] He'll take Singing, please.
[laughs]
♪ Outside my quiet rooms… ♪
- That blonde bitch wants The Giant.
- Stop it! [Chuckles]
[cheering]
[sighs]
[heavy metal blasting over speakers]
What are you doing?!
Dad! Dad! Go, go!
C'mon, Dad! Stop. Get in!
- [music stops]
- [booing]
We're supposed to meet
at the doctor's, not here!
- [booing]
- Mama, drive!
Wanted to do you a favor.
You didn't sleep last night.
[Eletta] You had the music at full blast!
Mom, drive! Mom, drive! Drive!
- [horn blaring]
- Mom, drive!
Drive, damn it! Hurry!
[blaring horn fades]
So it's the same results as the last time.
There's no improvement at all.
Are they applying the cream?
Are you applying the cream?
Yes. I rub the cream
into my vagina every night.
Yet somehow your mother's mycosis
has gotten worse.
But your father is applying the cream
I prescribed for him too, right?
Papa, are you applying the cream?
Are you using the cream?!
I used to, but not anymore.
It really greases up…
It greases up my underwear.
And the donkeys like it.
The other day,
Osvaldo tried to nip my balls.
[blows raspberry]
That's enough!
Excuse them.
Your father has to apply the cream.
Otherwise, it simply won't work.
Papa, you have to apply the cream!
It's important!
And no more sexual intercourse.
And sex must stop.
For how long?
Three weeks minimum.
Mama!
Forget it!
Mama, what do you mean
you don't agree with the treatment?
You suddenly a doctor?
You've got to listen!
I am so sorry, Doctor.
- [indistinct chatter]
- [piano tune playing]
[girl] I took the bus this morning.
It was god-awful!
I didn't want to do this.
My mother made me.
If he's worth a shot…
- Then you gotta take it.
- No, no! Please!
[professor] Good morning!
[students] Good morning!
I am Professor Giuliana Palumbo.
First off, thank you for wanting
to take my singing course,
but there are too many of you.
I'm gonna have to weed some of you out.
You! Come over here.
Name?
- Elena.
- Ah.
- [chord playing]
- Say it again but sing it.
♪ Elena-ah-ha-ah-haa ♪
Soprano. Great. Go over there.
♪ Luuu-caaaa ♪
A beautiful bass.
Men can stand over there. Very good.
You. Tall one.
Marco.
[piano plays notes]
♪ Marco ♪
Why are you shy?
Why? Again. Sing it.
[piano plays notes]
[fuller] ♪ Marco ♪
Much better.
Stand over there with the others.
[ambient melancholy music rises]
You. You're next.
♪ Enrico  ♪
♪ Federica  ♪
Better? [Laughs]
[airy vocalizations lilting]
[off-key] ♪ Senna ♪
Oh my God, this is difficult.
♪ Lorenzo  ♪
[chuckling quietly]
Do you find something funny?
Uh, you there. Laughing Girl.
C'mere and sing for me.
[ambient music fades]
♪ Martina… ♪
No. Martina, no. Thank you for your time.
- But you didn't let me finish!
- Uh, it's better this way.
I'm sure that you have other talents.
- Believe me, I have many. See you, Eletta.
- Uh, yeah… I have no doubt.
No. Where are you going? One second.
- [Eletta] I'm leaving. Thanks.
- No, I haven't heard you sing. C'mere.
Come on back here.
Go on, Eletta.
[chord sounds on piano]
♪ Eletta ♪
Well, you-you can sing, but…
You can sing even better than that.
Don't be shy.
Try one more time, okay?
♪ Eh-letta ♪
Another soprano.
You should stay.
Please.
Thank you.
♪ Gem ♪
The passion is there, for sure.
But, I'm sorry, you didn't make it.
[laughs]
You're going too fast! Too fast!
Oh! Whoa!
[laughing]
What did I say?!
- [Martina] What are these?
- [Eletta] They're the Giseldes.
[laughs] Where is their mother?
Someone wrung their mother's neck
a while back.
- So now, they think they're donkeys.
- Huh!
Everything's so simple for animals.
[sniffs] I actually have
a lot of respect for them.
I don't eat anything that has a heart.
FYI, I'm vegan.
Hm!
Look at you!
Aren't you a sweetheart?
He's Topsy-Turvy.
[Martina] Aw…
This is our kitchen.
[liquid trickling]
Sorry, everyone lives
in their own little world here.
[Martina chuckles]
What the fuck? Why did you close the door?
Martina…
- Hm!
- You're disgusting.
Pleasure to meet you.
Tell her she's very pretty.
He says your hair looks stupid.
Hm…
Why didn't you tell me
you had a hot brother?
What did she say?
That's none of your business,
and go wash your hands like a human.
- [snarls]
- [sighs]
[Martina chuckles]
- C'mon.
- Hey!
- Do not hit on my brother, okay?
- Why? Why not!
How do you say,
"I like you a lot" in Sign Language?
- "I."
- "You."
"Like you."
"A lot."
- "A lot."
- [both chuckle]
- [rhythmic thumping]
- [panting, moaning]
[laughs] What the hell?
Is your brother watching porn?
No. It's my parents.
- Are they doing it?
- Yes.
[upbeat folksy music playing]
[bed frame thumping and clattering]
Mama! Papa!
The gynecologist told you not to do that!
And I have company.
Is your boyfriend here?
No.
Then turn the light off!
[sighs]
Again?
- You sure you're ready to meet my parents?
- Oh, I can't wait!
Good evening! Nice to meet you.
And they're ignoring me…
That's because they're totally deaf.
And if you sign without them watching,
they won't "hear" you. Just do this…
Hello!
Good evening.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm, uh…
Mar…
Tina!
- Howdy, Marti.
- [Martina] Howdy, Francesco.
At last, you brought a friend!
Why did she say I'm a wanker?
[laughs]
"Eat?"
He's asking if you'd like
to stay for dinner.
Yes! I'd love it.
Your family's so sweet.
[pleasant music playing]
FYI, my mom's created a new cheese.
She's gonna want you to try it.
Yes. I'll try it.
Aren't you a vegan?
Yeah, but then again,
I'm a lot of things. [Laughs]
So?
Fucking good. [Chuckles]
My brother has an idea.
He says he's come up
with your "Name Sign."
My "Name Sign?"
- Martina, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
- Is it because he's saying "yes"?
[chuckles]
[sniffles]
[sobs] Fuck, I am so moved.
[music fades]
Good night. Thank you for dinner.
[upbeat folksy music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[man] Ah! Here they are!
The Musso family! [Chuckles]
I have to say,
your husband is the luckiest man here.
[chuckles] Mwah!
- [chuckles]
- Good morning, Mr. Mayor.
- [mayor] Good morning.
- Care to try some homemade cheese?
No, no, thank you. The elections
are coming up soon, as you know, and…
Um, actually, there are some
important issues on the table.
Especially, hm, for uh… for them.
- Who's "them?"
- Please, what I mean is…
Oh, my! Are my eyes deceiving me?
[mayor] Here he is!
Our very own Giacinto! [Chuckles]
[shouting] I was just, literally,
talking about you people!
What people?
And, actually, I was, uh,
just telling the Musso family here,
that we…
[Giacinto laughs]
…your friends, want to support
our handicapped voters
with new programs
developed by my council, okay?
If that's what you're going to do,
then I'll see you voting day!
Thanks! Thanks a million.
Tell them to fuck off!
Mayor?
My father says that
you are now obstructing access
to the table where we do business.
Ah, certainly, yes. Uh…
I'm always around,
so if you ever need anything. [Chuckles]
- Don't get upset and smile!
- [mayor] Well, goodbye. And thank you!
Yes, Mama.
[students] ♪ Oh yeah! ♪
[Giuliana] Good!
But sing it like you mean it!
- [bluesy piano tune playing]
- ♪ Che blues!  ♪
[Giuliana] Giorgia? Get ready.
It's time for a solo.
[students] ♪ Oh yeah! ♪
[vocalizing] ♪ Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Che blues!  ♪
[Giorgia vocalizes]
Luca, you feelin' it?
Attack and chase it!
♪ Oh yeah ♪
- [vocalizing]
- [Giuliana] Whoo!
- ♪ Che blues!  ♪
- [Giuliana] Yeah!
[Luca vocalizes]
Elena, now play with the tempo.
♪ Oh yeah!  ♪
[scatting vocals]
♪ Che blues!  ♪
[vocalizing]
- Eletta, your turn! Jump in.
- ♪ Oh yeah!  ♪
Go on! Jump in!!
♪ Che blues!  ♪
Jump in! You got it!
♪ Oh yeah!  ♪
Stop! Stop. Just hold up for a minute.
[piano stops]
Come over here.
Okay, now.
Let's say you won the lottery.
Yoo-hoo!
Try that.
[weakly] Yoo-hoo.
You realize you should be happy
that you won? Let's help her out.
Let's start with some blues.
Gianfra, hit it.
[bluesy piano tune playing]
[class snapping in rhythm]
♪ Oh yeah! ♪
You.
♪ Oh yeah!  ♪
I can't hear you. Louder.
Let them hear you!
♪ Oh yeah! ♪
[Giuliana] Ah! That's more like it.
Keep going.
[Eletta] ♪ Oh yeah! ♪
Now, to a seventh in the chord…
[piano scale ascends]
[higher] ♪ Ooh! Oh yeah!  ♪
Can you sing that high?
Do you think you can sing that note? Try.
[Eletta] ♪ Oh yeah! ♪
Ah, now where's the energy?
No, don't stop. You're almost there. High!
♪ Oh yeah! ♪
Up! Sing up! Let your voice
rise to the clouds. You've got it.
Do it! Sing!
♪ Oh yeah! ♪
Good! Now make that last note very long!
Until you're almost out of breath!
Go on now.
♪ Oh yeah! ♪
[silence]
[somber acoustic music plays]
[indistinct chatter]
[Giuliana] Why sign up for Singing
if you're not gonna sing?
[music fades]
I'm not sure if I even like singing.
I just don't know.
Hm…
But you like music, don't you?
- Yes.
- Eletta, are you okay?
[Eletta] Mm-hmm…
Wait, I have an idea. I'm gonna suggest
a duet for the end of year showcase.
- Me and him?
- [Marco] Me and her?
Yes.
You're both a bit shy
and a bit stuck right now.
Spend some time together.
It'll do you both good.
Let's see…
Both of you learn this song together.
It's by Ron.
If you don't know him,
believe me you'll love him.
But, please, listen to it
before you try to sing it.
And I mean really listen to it.
I'll send you a link
with the backup track.
Enjoy it, guys!
["Non abbiam bisogno di parole" playing]
[in Italian] ♪ Now come here… ♪
What were you doing?
Nothing.
Studying history.
The mayor is live. It's a TV special.
For your second term as mayor,
you chose to prioritize the construction
of a state-of-the-art
logistics center. Why, sir?
[mayor] Because we must not give
the impression that cultivating the land
or raising donkeys is prosperous enough
to keep our young people in the region.
So, the logistics center
will have benefits. Any examples?
[mayor] Well, for Camagna,
we're talking about over 100 new jobs.
So, there will be
economic benefits as well…
[grunting angrily]
That asshole!
Dad, how can we stop it?
- I'll run in the election.
- You wanna run? Are you crazy?!
We'll all work together!
I'm in.
[lavish rock music playing]
[shouts]
No, no. I don't want…
[sighs]
- [bleating]
- [quacking]
I couldn't sleep last night.
Why?
It's the election.
I don't think it's a good idea.
Because I'm Deaf?
Yes, because you're deaf.
[sighs]
You know very well that being Deaf
means having an identity and a culture.
[sighs] I know that it's not a handicap
but a culture with its own language.
You've told me a thousand times.
Do you want me to let that idiot
destroy everything?
I didn't say that.
[soft music playing]
Being the mayor and speaking
a language that no one understands
may seem presumptuous.
You know the farm is our life.
Yes, I know.
Everyone wants money.
But not us. We take care of animals.
Even if they speak a different language
than ours, they understand us.
You're right. But you can't be known
as "The Mayor of Donkeys."
Papa, the problem is your hearing.
So, what about Elon Musk?
What does Elon Musk have to…
He has Asperger's Syndrome.
And yet, he's headed to Mars!
And he's the richest man in the world!
Remember. Changing things
requires thinking differently.
That's important!
[kisses]
[music fades]
I love you, Papa.
Me, more.
Even if you are flawed.
[upbeat folksy music playing]
You're too serious!
Not in this one right here, no.
[clucking, squawking]
[shouts]
- Good morning, Mayor.
- Ah, good morning, all of you, Mussos!
Hey! What are you doing in there?
I DON'T HEAR EXCUSES
- It works.
- I like it. [Chuckles]
I CAN'T HEAR YOU, BUT I SEE YOU
"I can't hear bullshit." [laughs]
Vote for me!
#ILISTENTOYOU
Nice!
- [chuckles]
- Whoo!
[music fades]
Marco, Eletta? You two, stay, please.
Let's try the duet.
Have you studied it?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
Let's do it.
["Non abbiam bisogno di parole" playing]
♪ Now come here  ♪
♪ And gently close your eyes  ♪
♪ You'll see that
The sadness will go away  ♪
♪ And as for the rest, who knows?  ♪
♪ It will come tomorrow  ♪
♪ I want to be with you ♪
What are you doing? This is brutal.
- Sing it while dancing.
- Dancing?
Yes, dancing, Marco. Or would you
rather sing it while you're fighting.
[chuckles]
C'mon. Hold each other.
From the top.
- From the top.
- [piano continues]
♪ Now come here  ♪
♪ And gently close your eyes  ♪
♪ You'll see that
The sadness will go away  ♪
♪ And as for the rest, who knows?  ♪
♪ It will come tomorrow  ♪
♪ I want to be with you ♪
♪ Kiss your lips and tell you that  ♪
♪ In a time when everything passes  ♪
♪ Where everything changes  ♪
♪ We are still here  ♪
[Giuliana] No!
We're not there, Eletta.
We're nowhere if I can be perfectly blunt.
What is going on here?
I mean, don't you care about the showcase?
Do either of you even know
what this song is all about?
Singing is far more
than just a vocal exercise.
[playing notes]
It's not enough to just hit F-sharp
or G-sharp when you sing a song.
Passion and souls come out,
and you're telling a story.
This is a wonderful
and heartbreaking love song.
This is more like a love poem!
A love that is not bound by time,
that overcomes all obstacles…
"In a time where everything passes,
where everything changes,
we are still in love."
You can't sing that song
the way you two are singing it!
I mean, look at each other!
You're looking over there.
You're scratching your leg. What the hell?
What kind of shit is that?!
It is disrespectful to the music!
You have to sing this song together.
It belongs to both of you.
It's not yours and not yours!
From now on,
you'll rehearse this song together!
Do you two hear me?
Looking at each other,
touching each other,
feeling these wonderful words.
That's it for today. You can both leave.
I'm wasting my time
and getting pissed off!
Come back tomorrow.
Give me your address, and I'll come by.
To Shanghai Village?
[sighs]
Give me your number.
I'll come to you.
Okay…
[phones chiming]
[phone clicks]
Alright.
That went well.
No, no. My parents aren't home.
They're in town trying to get votes
for my dad's election campaign.
No way. I don't want him to meet them.
'Cause my parents don't know I sing!
Okay, I gotta go.
I'll call you later. Bye.
- [phone clicks]
- [animals bellowing]
They're our doorbell
and burglar alarm. [Chuckles]
Hi.
So this is my bedroom.
So, should we start?
Yeah.
Do we have to dance?
No, I don't really want to. Dancing sucks.
Yeah, totally agree.
What do you think if we stood
with our backs to each other?
["Non abbiam bisogno di parole" playing]
[in Italian] ♪ Now come here ♪
♪ And gently close your eyes ♪
♪ You'll see that
The sadness will go away ♪
♪ And as for the rest, who knows? ♪
♪ It will come tomorrow ♪
♪ I want to be with you ♪
♪ Kiss your lips and tell you that ♪
♪ In a time when everything passes ♪
♪ Where everything changes ♪
♪ We are still here ♪
[both] ♪ And we don't need words ♪
♪ To explain what is hidden
Deep in our hearts ♪
♪ But I will lift you up
Every time you fall ♪
♪ And I will pick up your flowers… ♪
[sighs]
[music stops]
- [exhales]
- Everything okay?
Yeah.
What's the matter?
The phone's dead.
- [sniffs]
- Um, what should we do, then?
Listen, we'll do the song…
But let's do it while we move, okay?
Without the music?
Without the music.
- Like how?
- [chuckling] I don't know. I don't know.
[inhales deeply]
[exhales]
♪ Now come here  ♪
♪ And gently close your eyes  ♪
♪ You'll see that
The sadness will go away ♪
♪ And as for the rest, who knows? ♪
♪ It will come tomorrow ♪
♪ I want to be with you ♪
♪ Kiss your lips and tell you that ♪
♪ In a time when everything passes ♪
♪ Where everything changes ♪
♪ We are still here ♪
[farting loudly]
What the hell?
[upbeat folksy music playing]
It was a joke! I thought you were alone.
You usually laugh!
You brought your boyfriend.
He's really hot! I'm happy!
He's not my boyfriend!
Earlier, upstairs, I heard some noises…
What the…? [Grunts]
He's muscular. Perfect for farming!
Did you fuck my sister? I'm watching you!
Huh?
If you get her pregnant, I'll take it,
and slice it into pieces!
Enough! Stop it, all of you! Stop!
Okay! I'm outta here.
I'm so sorry.
Are they always this crazy?
No, uh…
I don't know what to say. I'm embarrassed.
I'll see you tomorrow, okay?
- See ya.
- Yeah. Bye.
What's wrong with you?!
I hate you!
[Eletta] It would've been my first kiss.
[chuckles] Look at it this way.
If it wasn't for your father,
today you'd be nothing more than
a notch on the bedpost of Mark the Giant.
[girl] Speak of the devil!
Hey, Eletta… [imitates fart noise]
[girls laughing]
Remind you of anyone?
[laughs]
- Fuck yourself, bitch!
- [girl] Charming…
Skanks!
[school bell ringing]
[students gasping]
Fucking asshole.
[students vocalizing]
[gentle piano tune playing]
♪ Ever wonder 'bout what he's doin'? ♪
♪ How it all turned to lies? ♪
♪ Sometimes, I think that it's better ♪
♪ To never ask why ♪
♪ Where there is desire
There is gonna be a flame ♪
♪ Where there is a flame
Someone's bound to get burned ♪
♪ But just because it burns
Doesn't mean you're gonna die ♪
♪ You've gotta get up
And try, and try, and try ♪
♪ You've gotta get up and try, try, try ♪
♪ Try ♪
Oh!
♪ Where there is desire
There is gonna be a flame ♪
♪ Where there is a flame
Someone's bound to get burned ♪
♪ But just because it burns
Doesn't mean you're gonna die  ♪
♪ You've gotta get up
And try, and try, and try ♪
And try, and try, and try!  ♪
[silence]
[Giuliana] Eletta, you have a gift.
And that urgency…
That's in your voice.
[inhales shakily]
[exhales shakily]
You should try to get into the
International Singing Academy in Turin.
I believe you have what it takes.
- What?
- Yes.
Impossible.
What do you mean impossible?
It is possible.
You just have to believe it is.
The audition is the day after the recital
for the end of year showcase.
There isn't much time to prepare.
There's almost no time to prepare.
But you can get in.
I have no doubt.
There's definitely work
to be done, of course, but…
And if I'm accepted?
Then, it'd be a miracle!
You'd go to Turin.
In Turin, you'll study with the best!
You were born to sing, Eletta.
What do you think?
No.
It's not for me.
[overlapping chattering]
[man] Excuse me, excuse me.
Alessandro, excuse me.
If I may. Look, we all know
that Deregibus is a huge asshole,
but, unlike you, he is guaranteeing us
jobs if he's re-elected.
He also guarantees
wider distribution of our products.
That means we can make more money.
[Eletta] More money?
I alone distribute my product.
That way, I can respect nature,
the animals, and above all else, myself.
Alessandro, we all love you here,
but if you're suggesting
that we give up profit, I'm afraid
you're going to lose this election.
If you tell him something's impossible,
it motivates him even more.
Eletta is right. When Alessandro told me
that he was going to take over
my uncle's farm, no one here believed it.
But, when my husband
gets an idea in his head,
it's better to be behind him
than in front of him.
- Or he will…
- He'll shove it up your ass!
[laughing]
…crush your bum.
- [man] You got my vote, "Bum-Crusher!"
- I vote for Caterina!
[group laughing]
Alessandro, I don't want those big-box
warehouses popping up everywhere.
That said, I support you.
But I predict that Deregibus will win it.
- [man 1] Come on… Who wants that?
- [man 2] You got your work cut out.
[Eletta] Look here, everyone.
Even if my chances are one-in-a-million,
I have to try.
I have the ability,
and I believe in myself!
It's my destiny.
And I have to follow my own path.
- Bravo! This is how we move forward.
- Well said! Well said!
You've got my vote too! Nice, Alessandro.
Yes! Bravo! Bravo, bravo!
Great!
Together, we can do this.
[music fades]
That's great news! Why the frown?
How will I tend to Mama, Papa,
the farm and the market?
And now a candidacy for mayor?!
Stop it! We're Deaf, not stupid.
Before you were born, we got by just fine.
You were only 2 at the time
So?
If you weren't always in the way,
I'd have already completed my project!
[exhales deeply]
Meaning?
I have a dream.
To turn this place
into an educational farm
and rent out rooms!
Sounds good.
But it's a dream.
Because you underestimate me!
I studied agriculture for a reason.
But do you truly want to sing?
Yeah… Maybe.
Not, maybe. It's either yes or no!
I do like singing…
Then do it! And don't bust my balls!
[sighs]
It's a gift, you know?
Do you even realize
that you have it? [Chuckles]
- Hmm…
- Damn, girl!
I have a friend who has a gift!
I have an idea!
What's that?
Martina can replace you at the market.
I'll teach her sign language!
You want her to replace me at the market?
[laughs, gasps]
Cool idea!
[chuckles] I mean, why the hell not?
My father always says
that I could sell ice to polar bears.
[laughs quietly]
[Martina chuckles]
[chuckles] It's a deal!
[Martina laughs]
Come here, you!
Mwah!
[laughing]
- [Giuliana] Yes?
- Miss… may I?
Eletta, hi.
Come in. Come in.
I thought about the audition.
I wanna do it. I'll try out.
[chuckles]
I'm so glad.
Really pleased.
Have you asked your parents?
Yes, ma'am. They're very happy.
Because you won't have time
to do anything else.
We'll always be rehearsing.
Days, nights, weekends.
We'll start tonight.
You'll come to my place.
At six o'clock this evening.
I'll let Marco know.
On time, you understand?
Thank you.
[chuckles]
[indistinct chatter]
See you at the teacher's?
[Martina] My God, he is so annoying.
I'll see you there.
Forget about it. Blondes are out!
[laughs]
["Madama Butterfly, Act 2:
Un bel dì vedremo" playing]
[woman singing opera]
That box belongs to my ex-husband.
He played the cello.
And I took care of all the rest.
What happened?
Well, he wanted…
to call the end a "break."
There were nine "breaks" in all.
And I couldn't do it anymore.
So, I told him, "Call it what you'd like,
'a Break' if you want…
But for me, the song is finished."
And I left him.
But I have always liked teaching,
so… here I am.
In Alessandria?
Let's just say I needed to put
a few hundred kilometers
between me and his ego.
And between me and my mother.
But that's another chapter
in my disastrously complicated life.
We won't go there…
She taught me one thing
that I'm forever grateful for.
She taught me all about music.
And how you should appreciate it.
[chuckles]
It's time, let's start.
What about Marco?
Aren't we waiting for him?
No. Marco quit.
He's not coming.
Because of me?
[Martina] Hey!
A post about
an underground fight of his just dropped.
It's tonight.
- [shouting]
- Come on! Let's go!
Bring it on!
[dog growls]
[barking]
Don't be nervous.
They bark, but they don't bite.
Okay, that one bites. [Laughs]
[dog barking]
[crowd clamoring]
[ambient melancholy music rises]
You fuckin' pushin' me?
- Hey! Calm down!
- Oh…
- What the fuck you doin'?
- Come here.
[airy vocalizations lilting]
Back the fuck off!
- What do you want?
- We need to talk.
So talk, then.
- Aren't you afraid to go in there?
- Of course, I'm afraid.
I feel like an idiot, but… something
happened when we were practicing.
- Eletta, I gotta go in there and prepare.
- At my place…
- "At your place," what?
- Something happened at practice.
[sighs]
I've never sung like that.
And?
And come back and sing.
[scoffs]
Mark, it's time. Come on!
Listen, singing is your path to follow.
Don't waste time following me.
[woman] Mark! Come on! Let's get going!
Okay?
Now, get outta here.
No.
Eletta, go.
Get outta here!
- You're a fucking asshole!
- Yeah, fuck you too!
[music fades]
Mama, I'm going.
Where are you going?
I'll be back for dinner.
The TV people are about to arrive.
What do you mean, "TV people?"
No one ever told me that?
I thought Dad had told you.
[sighs] Can you reschedule for tomorrow?
Impossible!
I have to meet my boyfriend soon.
Ah, your boyfriend!
Get him to come here!
He's part of the family, now.
Mama, I would,
but we have work we can't do here.
You can do them here.
He'll be proud to see
his father-in-law become mayor!
[rooster crowing]
Okay, they're here.
Go on downstairs.
[upbeat folksy music playing]
[braying]
[horn beeps]
Hello!
Who is she?
It's beautiful here.
Oh, that's too much.
It's a beautiful farm.
And the lighting is just perfect.
Her look is completely wrong, though.
Does she have something rustic?
Something that says, "donkey farm?"
And, lose the makeup.
She says you're not going
to a beauty contest.
She wants to shoot us working the farm.
Let's go change.
Sorry, but is she from the TV?
Stop! Come on!
[music fades]
Mr. Musso, you're running
in the local municipal elections.
Can you tell us why you would want to?
[cell phone pings]
Camagna is a town of 500 residents.
So far, we've farmed the land
and raised animals.
[thunder rumbling]
Today, someone wants to intervene.
I WILL BE AT THE LESSON THIS AFTERNOON
They say our produce isn't sufficient.
That we can produce more
to reach the global market.
I'M SORRY, I'll BE LATE TONIGHT…
You can already feel the smog,
and everything is moving faster.
I want to bring a new energy to Camagna.
Hm. Mm.
Uh… You're deaf, sir.
Don't you think that could be
a handicap as the town's mayor?
Handicap? How dare you?
[pinging]
And you, with that setup?
You think you're a journalist?
- Is he angry now?
- No-no.
- You sure about that?
- Yeah.
If you're a journalist, I can be mayor!
So, he doesn't believe it's a handicap?
No.
GET HERE IN HALF AN HOUR
OR STAY WHERE YOU ARE
IT'S NOT UP TO ME
Ah! A new boyfriend! I got that part.
Did you translate?
I'm translating like always!
Are you sure you translated?
You've got your face in your phone…
Who are you texting?
[stomping]
Your behavior's not appropriate.
I missed my date with my boyfriend.
Everything always
has to revolve around you!
And you don't care about my life.
What's that got to do with anything?
[stomping]
[ambient melancholy music rises]
Can we go on?
Translate properly now, word for word.
Translate!
Look at me.
I will sign…
- Francesco will write my answers.
- Ah, hm…
[distant thunder rumbling]
You will subtitle what I say.
Okay.
And if you speak slowly,
I can easily read your lips.
Okay. Mm.
If we don't understand each other,
we'll write it down.
Perfect! I got it.
Now then, what do you want
to do for Cama… No?
Okay.
[shouting] And what do you want…
[cell phone vibrating]
[buzzing]
[quick piano tune playing]
- [door buzzes]
- [playing stops]
[Eletta] Professor?!
It's me, Eletta!
Please! It wasn't my fault!
[buzzing repetitively]
[piano continues playing]
[rhythmic thumping]
[loud thumping]
You were terrible!
Apologize to your father.
Apologize to my father?
For what exactly? For wanting a life?
You're not the only girl
in the world with a boyfriend.
There are lots like you. But remember
that you have responsibilities.
Your boyfriend comes after them.
Apologize!
Mama, I don't have a boyfriend.
And if we keep this up, I never will.
[thunder rumbling]
I have something to tell you
that's really important.
Are you pregnant?
No! I don't have a boyfriend, I told you.
Okay, here it is. I'm training to get
into a school for professional singers.
If I'm accepted,
I'll finish my studies there.
My teacher says that I have talent,
that I can make it.
I go to her place every night.
She's helping me prepare.
If I pass the audition,
I'll move to Turin.
You really want to move to Turin?
[thunder rumbling]
So you won't be at home with us anymore?
If I'm accepted.
How long have you been singing?
More than three months.
I'm also in the school choir.
[smacking table]
What's this teacher's name?
Giuliana.
And her last name?
Her last name is Dickhead!
She's brainwashed you!
Don't you have anything to say?
Mama!
I like singing,
and Giuliana says I'm very good.
Ah, I get it.
What do you think you get?
You set it all up.
You figured it all out in secret.
No, Mom. It's not like that.
She wanted to tell you sooner.
You are the problem.
So, that means we're the problem?
Papa, it's all of it.
All of it. It's the farm,
the market, now the election…
I'm here too!
You've always told me
we Deaf people are better than others.
But actually you two
have never had faith in me!
You should be ashamed!
He has a point.
I can stand up for myself!
[Alessandro sighs]
Say something to her!
I'm beat. I'm going to bed.
Going to bed? Already?
Papa!
[Alessandro exhales deeply]
Are you happy? See what you've done?
No, Mama, I'm not happy at all!
I'd have to leave here to be happy!
[ambient melancholy music plays softly]
[grunting gently]
HOW TO BE A LEADER
Our daughter wants to be a singer,
and you're just standing there!
If she wants to be a singer,
we should let her.
So she can show her ass
to the whole world.
Since when have you been such a bigot?
Don't you understand, she's in danger?
And you're just there…
You have to tell her to stay here.
What if she doesn't have
a beautiful voice?
It's that Giuliana
who put that idea in her head.
Stop being silly. Enough!
Stop talking nonsense!
Our daughter isn't stupid.
You're the one with issues.
Okay. Let's say she gets in.
How do we manage here?
Oh, so the problem isn't that
our daughter is going to Turin.
But that the two of us will be here alone.
Come here.
Look at me!
I'm sure that Eletta will miss us…
And come back.
Please, tell her to stay.
Of course.
[sighs]
[bright tranquil music plays]
[car engine starts]
[bright vocalizations lilting]
[Martina] I'm here! Sorry I'm late!
Fuck.
[music fades]
[Giuliana] Good morning.
Thank you for being on time.
Please, relax and make yourself at home.
You're all good.
- I wasn't on time yesterday because…
- Did I ask you to explain?
I apologize.
Come over here.
["Un'emozione da poco" plays on phone]
Anna Oxa. You know her?
No.
What is the matter with kids these days?
It was 1978. She was 16.
She went to the Sanremo Festival,
briefcase in hand, dressed as a man,
and she walked on stage,
put the case on the ground,
turned her back to the audience,
and sang like this!
[in Italian] ♪ There is a reason
Growing in me ♪
Perfect start.
[power chord]
[mouthing Italian lyrics]
♪ And my naivety's fading ♪
- [power chords]
- ♪ And like a journey… ♪
- [music stops]
- Hey, what are you doing?
- You said I have a gift. Are you sure?
- You can doubt everything in this world.
Except for me.
[in Italian] ♪ …in the night, it ends ♪
♪ Tell me, tell me, tell me
What sense it makes ♪
♪ To give love to a man who has no mercy ♪
- [power chords]
- [both laugh]
♪ One who never felt defeated  ♪
- Then she danced. Here comes the chorus…
- ♪ Who never lost, never  ♪
♪ For you, for you… ♪
[indistinct chatter]
Good morning.
What's so special about this donkey milk
that it costs €20 a liter?
- Why aren't all cars the same price?
- It depends on their features.
A donkey isn't a cow. It produces a small
amount of milk, but it's high quality.
To me, it seems like a gimmick
to steal people's money.
Did you wake up this morning and say,
"Today, I'm gonna be an asshole?"
He's a fucking asshole!
I can try it?
Like I said.
Hm.It's just a gimmick.
[upbeat folksy music plays]
- Bumpkins…
- What the hell are you looking at?!
[straining]
[groans]
[music fades]
So, tell me, how'd it go at the market?
Zero!
You didn't sell anything?
I don't sell anymore, don't fuck anymore,
and I beat people up.
You don't sell or fuck anymore,
but you attack people? What happened?
It's your fault!
Me?!
Martina's a disaster.
And you're gonna blame that on me?
She has to be kind. She's not polite!
But that's normal. She just started.
Mama! She just needs some time.
If she doesn't work out,
then it's your fault.
You keep people at arm's length.
You make no effort to accept
those that you call "The Others."
[sighs]
[sweet plucky music playing]
[Martina] What do you wanna do?
[softly] Kiss?
[Martina speaking quietly]
[sighs]
[laughing] You're crazy…
Sorry again for yesterday, but that
market's like a magnet for assholes.
Forget about it.
[clamoring in hallway]
[Martina] What's going on?
That guy's been involved
in some illegal fights.
Who is it?
[indistinct chattering]
-[girl] They want information
-[boy] Figures… It's Marco.
Police wanna question him about some
underground fights he's involved with.
They're arresting him?
What do you think?
[gentle piano melody playing]
[in Italian] ♪ I'd like ♪
♪ To give you my word
To tell you I can't wait  ♪
♪ To forget everything ♪
- ♪ I would like…  ♪
- [music stops]
Eletta, you're not singing.
You're whining. You're not thinking about
what you're singing, you're not breathing…
I've been practicing all week, Miss.
You didn't focus like this on Marco.
What?
If Marco had kept singing,
he might have avoided the trouble he's in.
He's not why you're here.
Or why I'm here.
Why don't you just leave?
Do me a favor and just leave.
Today is ruined.
It's ruined. And you know what?
Think carefully about
whether you want this.
[quietly] I don't believe this.
Okay, yes, I'll be back
to see you tomorrow. Eh…
You good?
What was Giacinto doing here?
Tomorrow at 6 p.m.,
we have a meeting with the voters.
Mom's asked Giacinto to give us a hand.
But you always said the Oralists
were a disgrace to the non-hearing.
We need to get by on our own from now on.
You serious now?
Of course.
[ambient melancholy music playing]
HOW LONG WILL YOU BE AWAY FROM SCHOOL?
MARCO: TWO MONTHS I THINK.
IF I BEHAVE MAYBE LESS
[keys clacking]
THEN BEHAVE. SO YOU CAN KEEP SINGING
YOU'RE OBSESSED WITH SINGING
[keys clacking]
YES. SINGING MAKES ME FEEL GOOD.
I DISCOVERED THAT WITH YOU.
THEN SING AS MUCH AS YOU CAN
[exhales heavily]
[music fades]
[Eletta in Italian]
♪ There is a reason growing in me ♪
- ♪ And my naivety's fading ♪
- [power chords playing]
♪ And like a journey in the night
It ends  ♪
♪ Tell me, tell me, tell me
What sense it makes ♪
More!
♪ To give love to a man who has no mercy  ♪
[accompanying piano continues]
- ♪ One who never felt defeated ♪
- Yes!
- ♪ Who never lost, never ♪
- Now, softly!
♪ For you, for you…  ♪
Oh! Red! [Chuckles]
♪ A song ♪
♪ Never a cheap illusion
A banal thought  ♪
♪ Something that remains ♪
♪ Instead, for me  ♪
- ♪ For me  ♪
- Francesco?
- ♪ It's more than normal ♪
- He went to get Martina. He'll be here.
♪ That such a slight emotion  ♪
♪ Can make me feel this bad ♪
- Slowly! Just like that!
- ♪ One softly-spoken word is enough ♪
♪ And I can no longer see reality ♪
[Giuliana] Breathe…
[both] ♪ I don't know
Where it is anymore  ♪
♪ The clear difference  ♪
♪ Between the blindest love
And the stupidest patience ♪
♪ No, I can no longer see reality ♪
♪ Nor how much tenderness it gives you ♪
♪ My incoherence ♪
♪ Thinking that you would live
Just fine without ♪
[music stops]
Concretely, uh, what do you plan
to do about our young people?
Without any employment
development in the area,
many of them are packing up and leaving.
Everyone is leaving.
Let them go sing, the young people!
[man] What's that gotta do with it?
Our small world is part of a bigger world
that's moving very fast!
- We have to keep up with it!
- [clamoring]
What do you think?
It's a problem.
[crowd clamoring]
[chuckles]
"What are ya? Papa and Mama ducks?"
What did you call me?
[gasps] Holy shit, you almost spilled it!
[overlapping shouts]
You scared me.
You want to see me dead?
Is it somehow my fault
that they had an accident?
Who introduced him to Martina?
It's your fault!
And you, what are you doing
while you're driving?
[stifling laughter]
[laughing]
So? What were you doing?
You're a little girl…
Come on! C'mon, tell me!
- [groans]
- Oh, God. Sorry. Sorry.
[laughs] Come on, I'm sorry.
Please? Forgive me.
- [Francesco] No.
- [laughs] Come on!
All traitors!
You can't call them that
They're your voters.
No. I'm talking about you.
You left me there on my own.
Francesco had a car accident,
and we had to go and get him.
It's not serious.
He sprained his wrist.
He's in his room resting.
And Mom?
I don't know.
[soft tones rising gently]
Mama!
Mama?
Mama, sit up.
[grunts]
Leave me alone. Don't touch me.
Leave me alone! Here, with the cheese.
Mama get up, you can't stay here.
I want to stay here!
Let me help you, please.
Help me? But I'm a terrible mother.
Because I'm Deaf,
and I couldn't find
the right words with you!
You're not a bad mother.
In fact, you're the mom
everyone wishes they had.
When you were born, and they told me
that you could hear, I cried.
Those like you,
I could never stand them!
But he calmed me down, saying
he would have raised you Deaf inside.
But, instead, you can hear.
And you want to go away to sing.
So that's it?
Am I condemned to a life
of serving the two of you forever?
Is that what you see
when you look at my future?
And you?
You say nothing.
There is no problem.
It's better if you go.
Follow your own path. You're free.
We'll get by on our own.
- Eletta? What are you doing here…
- I'm quitting.
- You're quitting?
- I'm not going to Turin.
I'm not doing the recital, audition,
and I'm not singing anymore.
Calm down. Calm down.
- Maybe...
- It's just not for me.
- I can't do it.
- It's normal to be nervous.
Completely normal.
Happens to every artist.
But I'm not an artist.
Of course you're not.
You're just someone who breeds donkeys.
Yep. Apparently.
Wait.
Why won't you tell me what happened?
[gentle acoustic music playing]
[airy vocalizations lilting]
Shall we go to the hair salon?
[shopkeeper bell rings]
But I like my hair straight.
Why not give it a try like that for once?
[music fades]
[sighs] alright, I'll try it.
But if I don't like it,
I'm washing it out at home.
Eletta.
Good morning, Professor.
- Hello.
- [Eletta] This is my mother.
Oh, I'm very pleased to meet you.
You know, you are very lucky.
Your daughter possesses
an extraordinary talent. A gift.
This is Giuliana, my teacher.
This woman is a nightmare!
Mama, she just wants to meet you.
I'd like to slap her!
Stay away from my daughter!
- What did I say?
- Stop it, Mama!
I wanted her to know
what I thought about you.
- Let's calm down.
- She's telling you what she thinks of me.
What she thinks of you?
You don't know my daughter at all.
I raised her.
She says she's the one who knows me best.
Because she's my mother.
It's okay.
My mother would say the same thing too.
All parents say that to each other.
It's not always the case.
What do you know?
You've never had children.
Mama!
What'd she say?
- Nothing.
- No, translate. What'd she say there?
She said, uh, that's 'cause
you don't have any children.
That's a fact!
Okay, I have no children.
Unfortunately, I have none.
That's true!
But I have a mother, and you're alike!
And she forced me to marry a man
who she said was perfect for me.
Except he cheated on me constantly.
So I know perfectly well
what it means to be manipulated.
Translate this, Eletta.
Eletta…
It's your life.
It's your life, sweetheart!
Don't let anyone decide
how you should live it.
Not me, not your parents. Understand?
Then she put her hands on her head
and messed up her hair.
- Liar.
- No.
- I would've paid to be there.
- I don't know.
He got out?
If he doesn't wanna go back in,
he'd better smarten up.
Maybe he'll sing again.
Hm!
[sighs softly]
[indistinct chatter]
If you're afraid of me, you can walk away.
You've turned and run before.
If you do, I'll understand.
You know the duet is quite challenging.
Can you do it?
Do you accept the challenge?
- Eletta.
- [indistinct chatter]
Are you nervous?
[breathes deeply]
Got another question?
Hey, it's gonna be fine.
How can you be so sure?
Because I showed up.
I like you.
I like you too.
♪ I get knocked down but I get up again
You're never gonna keep me down ♪
♪ I get knocked down! ♪
[song ends]
[cheering]
["Non abbiam bisogno di parole"
playing on piano]
♪ Now come here ♪
♪ And gently close your eyes ♪
♪ You'll see that
The sadness will go away  ♪
♪ And the rest, who knows
It will come tomorrow ♪
♪ I want to be with you ♪
♪ Kiss your lips and tell you that ♪
♪ In a time when everything passes ♪
[both] ♪ Where everything changes ♪
♪ We are still here  ♪
♪ And we don't need words  ♪
[fading out] ♪ To explain what is… ♪
- [high-pitched tone]
- [soundscape fades]
[fading in] ♪ I will follow your flight
Without ever interfering  ♪
[soundscape returns]
♪ Because all I want is to be with you  ♪
♪ Without chains  ♪
♪ To be with… ♪
-You
[kisses]
[cheering and whistling]
You were incredible.
[screams] Oh, you were amazing!
- [laughs]
- Mwah!
- [chuckles] I'm so proud!
- [Eletta laughs]
Eletta. [Sighs deeply]
- Oh my God, you're amazing!
- [Eletta laughs]
[inhales deeply] I'm so proud.
Fantastic! It was magical!
Magical! [Shaky breaths]
Listen…
I never canceled tomorrow's audition.
You can still go and do it.
It's at ten in the morning in Turin…
- No, Professor.
- And I can take you.
- It's not possible.
- Uh…
Good evening.
[pants]
[pants] It's nice to meet you.
It is very nice to meet all of you.
Um…
And now that you know
the talent that is within your daughter,
I know you'll encourage her
to follow her own true path.
Right?
She learned our language.
Eletta… Eletta has a voice
that's extraordinary!
It's a wonderful voice. A gift.
Why would you silence it
instead of nurturing it?
Why would you stop her
instead of helping her? Why?
Why?
The show was fantastic.
Eletta moved everybody. My compliments.
My father… congratulates you
on the wonderful concert.
The staging was great,
and Eletta was well-dressed.
And my mother appreciated
the costumes and staging.
Eletta, you have to tell them your voice…
your voice is extraordinary.
- We're going. Uh, good… Goodbye.
- Tell her, though.
Eletta, tell her, please!
- [insects chirring]
- [donkey brays softly]
[footsteps approaching]
What is it?
It describes a love
that doesn't need to be spoken.
If you want.
[in Italian] ♪ Now come here ♪
♪ And gently close your eyes ♪
♪ You'll see that
The sadness will go away ♪
♪ And the rest, who knows
It will come tomorrow ♪
♪ I want to be with you ♪
♪ Kiss your lips and tell you that ♪
♪ In a time when everything passes ♪
♪ Where everything changes ♪
♪ We are still here ♪
♪ And we don't need words ♪
♪ To explain what is hidden
Deep in our hearts ♪
♪ But I will lift you up
Every time you fall ♪
♪ And I will pick up your flowers
That you'll lose on the street ♪
♪ And I will follow your flight
Without ever interfering ♪
♪ Because all I want is to be with you ♪
♪ Without chains ♪
♪ To be with you ♪
What's the matter?
Get dressed.
Get dressed? Why?
Turin?
- [farts]
- Papa! [Laughs]
[line ringing]
[engine revving]
Professor. Professor!
Professor!
Holy fuck.
Miss!
Marco! What are you doing here so early?
Is that your car parked over there?
- It's the neighbors.' Why, what's up?
- Ask if we can borrow it.
You wanna borrow it to go where?
C'mon Papa. Please, go faster.
We're already running late!
- Haven't you read our messages?
- Marco, I didn't read them. I was asleep.
- Now if you don't tell me what's going on…
- Eletta's going to the audition!
Papa! Stop doing that! [Laughs]
Good morning. I'm here for the audition?
- Yes.
- Eletta Musso.
- Eletta Musso? But you're late.
- Sorry.
Alright, go up those stairs over there.
And your family should wait there.
- Thanks a lot.
- Thank you!
[woman singing in operatic soprano]
["Lascia ch'io pianga" playing on piano]
- Nicely done.
- [singer] Thank you.
Break a leg.
Thanks.
[breathes shakily]
Good morning. And your name is?
Eletta Musso.
One more minute of that music,
and I'd have slit my wrists.
One more minute of whining,
and I'd've let you.
What song have you chosen?
"Atlantis."
Do you have the sheet music?
- Excuse me, the auditions?
- [man] Up that way.
Thanks. Up that way…
Claudio, do you know
the music for this song?
No. I don't know this song.
Regrettably, you'll have to sing
the song a cappella, Miss Musso.
We're ready when you are.
[indistinct chatter]
Screw this, we're going up.
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
But I've never sung a cappella.
Sorry to say it,
but you have no choice today.
Sorry! I'm here!
I'm here! I'm her teacher, I prepared her.
Good morning.
I'm sorry I'm late, but the car was...
Hurry and come down.
We've wasted enough time already.
Yes, you're right. You're right. Thanks.
[panting] Your time is valuable.
It should not be wasted.
[breathes deeply]
I can do it. Thank you.
[gentle piano melody playing]
[in Italian] ♪ I would like  ♪
♪ To give you my word  ♪
Oh! I played the wrong chord.
Excuse me for that. Um… I'm sorry.
Give me one second, please?
[chuckles]
Wait.
Take a deep breath.
[inhales deeply]
[exhales deeply]
Sing for yourself.
Thank you. Excuse me.
[gentle piano melody playing]
[Eletta breathes deeply]
♪ I would like ♪
♪ To give you my word
To tell you, I can't wait ♪
♪ To forget everything ♪
♪ I would like to tell you
That I have no voice ♪
♪ So I don't have to talk
That I can't choose anymore ♪
♪ I used to go out
With broken bones ♪
♪ My mind was in love
But with abstract things ♪
♪ Now I don't know what to do
I don't know where to go anymore ♪
♪ I have to get used to it ♪
♪ I was lost in a vortex
As if trapped at the edge ♪
♪ I asked you for fairytales
Like the sea of Atlantis ♪
♪ I'm scared and I admit it ♪
♪ I've been waiting for months  ♪
♪ Now I change direction
But I don't change my intention ♪
♪ I have nothing to say
I want to break free from the edge ♪
♪ At least I try to understand
How much it hurts to leave ♪
♪ I'll be there waiting for you
Somewhere else in the world ♪
♪ Now I change direction
But I don't change my intention ♪
♪ I'm just in a bigger hurry
With my hands in my pockets ♪
♪ And your keys always in my purse
Come on ♪
♪ Don't turn your back this time either  ♪
♪ I see everything in your eyes
I need nothing more  ♪
♪ I keep asking myself
If I'm the one who's wrong  ♪
♪ If I wasted time
And didn't give you my all  ♪
♪ But now I know what to do
I know where to go ♪
♪ I have to get used to it ♪
♪ I was lost in a vortex
As if trapped at the edge ♪
♪ I asked you for fairytales
Like the sea of Atlantis ♪
♪ I'm scared and I admit it ♪
♪ I've been waiting for months ♪
♪ Now I change direction
But I don't change my intention ♪
♪ I have nothing to say
I want to break free from the edge ♪
♪ At least I try to understand
How much it hurts to leave ♪
♪ I'll be there waiting for you
Somewhere else in the world ♪
♪ Now I change direction
But I don't change the emotion ♪
[ambient melancholy music plays]
[laughs softly]
[airy vocalizations lilting]
[smacking on wall]
Giuliana is here.
[donkey braying]
[Eletta] Good morning!
Ah! Let's go, Eletta. It's getting late.
Thanks, big brother.
What's up, why are you crying?
No, it's because I'm happy.
You're leaving,
and I can rent out your room!
[laughs] You're an asshole.
I know you're joking!
No, I'm serious!
Converting the farm into a farmhouse,
renting rooms is a nice dream. We'll see!
And when I come back?
I'll offer you a fair price!
[both chuckle]
Now come on, give me a hand.
[ambient melancholy music rises]
[airy vocalizations lilting]
You're my precious love.
I just put on my makeup, come on!
She meant to say she'll miss you.
[mouthing] I love you.
[music fades]
Go now, before I change my mind.
- [laughs]
- [Giuliana] What's he saying?
- To leave before he changes his mind.
- Oh, I'd love to get going but [chuckles]
[chuckles]
- [Giuliana] Oh!
- [huffs]
- [whines]
Donkey, please, be gentle.
[car engine starts]
["Atlantide" by Sarah Toscano playing]
♪ Io vorrei ♪
♪ Darti la mia parola
Dirti non vedo I'ora ♪
♪ Dimenticarmi tutto quanto ♪
♪ Io vorrei
Dirti che non ho voce… ♪
Stop. Stop the car.
♪ Non Dover parlare ♪
♪ Che non so scegliere più ♪
♪ Uscivo fuori casa
Con le ossa distrutte ♪
♪ La mente innamorata
Ma di cose astratte ♪
♪ Ora non so che fare
Non so più dove an dare ♪
♪ Mi devo abituare ♪
♪ Ero persa in un vortice
Come chiusa in un margine ♪
♪ Ti chiedevo le favole
Come il mare di Atlantide ♪
♪ Ho paura e lo am met to ♪
♪ Sono mesi che as pet to ♪
♪ Adesso cam bio direzione
Ma non cam bio I'intenzione ♪
♪ Non ho niente da dire
Voglio uscire dal margine ♪
♪ Almeno provo a capire
Quanto male fa andarsene ♪
♪ Sarò lì che ti as pet to
Da un'altra parte del mondo ♪
♪ Adesso cam bio direzione
Ma non cam bio I'intenzione ♪
[gentle piano melody continues]
FEEL MY VOICE
- [folksy music playing]
- A big "hello" to all!
This is Francesco, and I am Martina.
We'd both like to welcome you
to our educational farm.
We look forward to seeing you here
with your families and with your children.
We know you'll have
a wonderful time with them.
And with our animal friends.
[donkey huffs]
[indistinct chatter]
[upbeat folksy music playing]
[cheering]
[indistinct chatter continues]
[upbeat folksy music continues]
[music ends]
[soft pop song playing]
♪ The silence is loud there ♪
♪ The ceiling too low from my side ♪
♪ That I stay awake ♪
♪ Things I feel inside ♪
♪ Life keep moving ♪
♪ Keeps my heaven feeling alive  ♪
♪ Just feeling alive  ♪
♪ They laugh, they shout ♪
♪ They talk, they cry  ♪
♪ Inside my quiet rooms ♪
♪ Outside my quiet rooms ♪
♪ The morning is quiet  ♪
♪ The coffee's still warm with my hand  ♪
♪ And lets my with out to lose me ♪
♪ Some days start with hope ♪
♪ Let it keep moving  ♪
♪ Keeps my heaven feeling alive ♪
♪ They laugh, they shout  ♪
♪ They talk, they cry ♪
♪ Inside my quiet rooms ♪
♪ Outside my quiet rooms ♪
♪ The silence is louder  ♪
♪ The ceiling's too low ♪
♪ The silence is loud there ♪
[instrumental guitar continues]
[song fades out]