FILING FOR LOVE
REPORTING MS. JOO IN-A
Joo In-a's
having an affair?
HEAD OF AUDIT JOO IN-A
Will you hear me out?
It's really a misunderstanding,
Ms. Joo.
I said no, but the supplier said
it's customary.
Ms. Joo... Come on, Ms. Joo.
Please, listen to me.
Let me off just this once.
My kids are young, and my wife
quit her job to care for them.
I'm all they have right now.
Please, just this one time.
You should've thought of your wife
and kids before taking the kickback.
Don't use them
as a sentimental excuse.
What was that?
Hey, you.
Know your limits.
A cornered mouse can bite the cat.
Darn it!
What are you staring at?
You weren't hoping
I'd get slapped, were you?
She's such a freak.
Joo In-a couldn't possibly be
having an affair.
- It can't be.
- Mr. Noh.
Yes?
I thought you wanted to talk to me.
Oh, well...
All right, for now...
Let's backtrack strategically
until I've grasped the situation.
I wanted to apologize.
I was rude at karaoke yesterday.
I'm really sorry, Ms. Joo.
I get it.
I was a bit indifferent
and insensitive.
I put someone like you
in charge of very limited duties.
You must've been frustrated.
Well...
I'll give you more work.
Sure.
Wait, Mr. Noh.
Why are you doing this?
Oh, dear.
Why did you have to go and...
Why did you take her on?
You really need to be careful.
Seeing how she handled Mr. Seo
made me realize
how she got called "JJCC."
"Jeer Joo, Chaos Comes."
That spells JJCC.
JEER JOO, CHAOS COMES
Gosh, just thinking about it...
Mr. Noh.
I'll leave this here.
Since you're at it.
You know I'm rooting for you, right?
Stay strong.
Jeez...
My gosh.
What the heck?
Darn it all.
JJCC, my foot.
She's just an employee
like everyone else.
REPORTING MS. JOO IN-A
MS. JOO IN-A IS INVOLVED
IN AN INAPPROPRIATE
WORKPLACE RELATIONSHIP
Yes.
If that report turns out to be true
that means I'll have what I need
to take Joo In-a down.
This could be
my opportunity.
Fine, Joo In-a.
I'll take you on.
Let's see who comes to a grizzly end.
EPISODE 3:
A WOMAN WITH A TWIST
A workplace is a battlefield.
Every single day,
we fight hard to survive and win.
The fundamental rule of war is IFF.
Identifying friend or foe.
However...
Good morning.
Ma'am, you colored your hair.
You look 20 years younger.
Hello.
Sang-hyeon, you drank too much.
Soothe yourself or you'll get sick.
Identifying friend and foe at work
is not at all easy.
Some foes look like friends.
I never see you around.
We should meet up soon.
Your team and mine
could exchange info.
Yes, sure. That would be nice.
Let's meet for a drink another time.
Sounds good.
Yes, take care.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Today's friend
could become tomorrow's foe.
Why are you pushing this on your own?
You just clocked in?
I do this every day.
Even so.
Be careful. You might hurt your back.
Don't you worry about my back.
Pushing this cart takes know-how,
not brute strength.
- You do this.
- Oh, my gosh.
This is almost scientific.
It's nice to have some help.
TEAM LEADER MOO KWANG-IL
But one thing is clear.
The moment you identify a foe
that is exactly what they become.
As of now
I will sharpen my blade quietly
for my archenemy.
NEW FOLDER: NONAME
And plan a critical blow to Joo In-a.
Ms. Joo In-a.
You asked to be excluded
from the executive staff meeting.
Yes, Haemu's Audit Team
is an audit team only in name.
Our tasks are not independent.
We need to renew
our chain of command.
We are fully under the control
of management for now.
That almost hurts to hear.
I can't approve your request.
I would like for you
to be under my control.
Please reconsider my request.
Well, I have a lot of work
to catch up on.
I will excuse myself.
She's as independent
as she needs to be.
Shall I hear from HR next?
Okay, so...
President Jeon wants to reinstate
Managing Director Jeon Sung-yeol
to the head office.
He called me himself this morning.
Yes, I'm aware of that.
You are, right?
I knew you'd be aware
of the situation.
You are the vice president.
Still, you should've run it by me
before bringing this to the meeting.
It's a sensitive matter.
I apologize. That was careless of me.
To be honest, personally
the risk of reinstating
Managing Director Jeon
right after the end
of his probation period
is quite concerning.
Is it the President?
PRESIDENT JEON
Hello, Father. It's Jae-yeol.
Did I call the wrong person?
I apologize. We were in a meeting,
so I answered her phone.
Sign the form.
The thing is...
HR voiced their concern.
It's still a bit early.
Some will criticize us
for putting on a show...
Haven't you seen
Haemu Construction's stocks?
You must acknowledge what's due.
Don't make me repeat myself.
Thanks for working hard today.
See you tomorrow.
- Goodbye.
- Take care.
Who wants to have dinner with me?
My wife wants me to eat out.
No one?
- See you tomorrow.
- Yes, bye.
- Goodbye.
- There's no one.
Are you all trying to lose weight?
Yes, sure. Got it.
RECORDING, REFRAIN FROM TOUCHING
Project No Name,
following the target.
Is she going straight home?
One triangle gimbap, a can of beer
and a box of digestive medicine?
My gosh.
What are you, mister?
Are you a stalker? A beggar?
Did you hear the news?
The VP's stepbrother
Managing Director Jeon Sung-yeol
is coming back here.
They say the president
favors him over the VP.
Is it because
he's the current wife's son?
This is top secret.
The VP's birth mother.
She was basically thrown out
because of a mental illness.
They called her
a disgrace to the family.
There's even talk
that they think it's hereditary.
- Then the VP...
- Come on, now.
Aren't you two too young
to have a prejudice like that?
If Director Jeon does come back
all we have to do
is decide whose side to take.
Wouldn't it be better
to side with the managing director?
The current VP is in charge
only in title.
He doesn't have a stake in Haemu.
Hey, guys.
It's not like that.
You never know.
The VP has an influential wife.
His father-in-law owns Sesan Group.
The President arranged that marriage
because he needed something.
He has to be wary of them.
You're right.
Then we really don't know
what'll happen.
What I can say for sure is
our company is about to see
the biggest storm in history.
You should be careful.
- Hey, Mr. Moo.
- What?
- Come see me.
- What for?
- Follow me.
- Why?
I packed this for you.
- What is this?
- We made them
for the executives,
and there were a lot of leftovers.
Your wife is looking after twins.
She won't have the time
to cook for herself.
Take some home for her.
Gosh, she's going to taste
some fancy food, thanks to you.
My word.
There's one more thing.
It's not much.
Buy your kids some clothes.
My kids have enough clothes.
You gave too much money
when you attended
my father's funeral.
I didn't get to thank you then.
Take the money.
- It's fine. It wasn't much.
- No.
- You don't need to.
- Take it.
- I don't want it.
- Don't say no.
- You need to stop, ma'am.
- Take it.
Don't do that.
- No.
- What's this?
Can you not do this?
What kind of scene is this?
This is insane.
What are they doing out here?
A triangle gimbap and a can of beer.
That's all she buys every time?
Yes, I thought the lady
just had a small appetite.
I see.
Does she not like eating?
Did she ever
come here with a man?
No, I never even saw her
with a woman.
- She's always on her own.
- Is she?
You must be really smart, Rhena.
You remember all the customers.
No, I only remember because it's her.
Because it's her? How come?
She's pretty.
What? She's pretty?
Joo... That woman?
Yes.
Well, I guess.
We all have
different beauty standards.
She must be what you consider pretty.
Hey, do you want another ice cream?
No, buy me wine.
- Rhena, I drove...
- To share with my boyfriend.
Where would the princesses
like to go?
Where shall we go?
- That way.
- That way?
Here we go.
We've reached the ocean.
Where do we go now?
Backward?
Where shall we go now? Which way?
- This way?
- Girls.
It's past your bedtime.
Go and brush your teeth.
Mommy Monster's angry. Get away.
Run away.
Gosh. I feel so hot.
Oh, dear. It's hard work
raising young kids at my age.
Save your energy.
You need to work
until they finish university.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, dear. My poor knees.
- Honey.
- Yes?
Your cafeteria food is delicious.
Large companies are the best.
- Do you like it?
- Yes.
It tastes even better
because someone else made it.
Take your time.
Can you bring food home
every now and then?
I'll do that.
It's great to see you enjoy it.
Here's some water.
You're home.
You're late. Did you meet someone?
No, I worked late.
Why did you spend so much
at a convenience store?
Oh, that?
The part-timer
bullied me into paying.
Gosh.
Gosh, ten condoms?
What?
Jeez, that kid...
I wonder if her parents know
what she's up to instead of studying.
If they heard, they'd be relieved
that she knows enough
to take precautions.
They must be really in love
if they need ten boxes.
Hey, ten boxes is nothing.
You know... Back in my day...
Is that what you're eating
for dinner?
Why didn't you order takeout?
I had dinner.
This is a late-night snack.
Do you want one?
It was buy one, get one free.
KIMCHI AND SPICY PORK TRIANGLE GIMBAP
Hey.
I know someone
who eats just one triangle gimbap
for dinner every day.
What kind of person would do that?
They must be poor.
No, it's not that.
They make a decent amount.
Then maybe
they just eat to survive.
Some people eat the bare minimum
so they don't die.
They might look like they have a lot
but they feel empty inside.
That's why
they don't feel full
even though they eat.
They don't feel energized
even though they sleep.
Who are you talking about?
It can't be you, seeing you're eating
a late-night snack.
- Hey, Seung-hee.
- A-jeong.
Sorry for calling late at night.
Did you check out
the anonymous bulletin board?
There are endless posts
about the VP and his stepbrother.
GET SOME POPCORN READY
SO DO THEY HAVE DIFFERENT MOMS?
A LEGENDARY SITUATION AT HAEMU
GOODBYE TO J'S SUPPORTERS
Information Team!
Do something about it!
Take down the posts
as soon as they come up.
Or block certain keywords.
Can't you block posts
that say "birth mom"?
That won't stop people
from using other terms.
If we block every post on this topic
they'll complain that HR
is censoring public opinion.
And work.com
can't be controlled or censored.
Be reasonable.
I'm not asking you
to censor anything.
That can't be the only solution.
We each have just one mouth.
Can't you
come up with an idea?
This is driving me insane.
- Sir.
- What?
Can you take a look at this?
What is it?
Someone posted it yesterday.
How about we use this
to our advantage?
It could gain some interest.
"Middle-aged romance"?
Hang on.
I know this jawline from somewhere.
Team Leader Moo?
Hey, Moo...
Good find, Ms. Oh. Can you move over?
Yes, let's put this to good use.
Let's see.
A middle-aged woman. Madam...
How does "Madam Killer" sound?
Well...
- That's a bit...
- Then...
"An audit team leader's affair."
Is that more provocative?
Isn't it a bit much
to reveal his identity?
Revealing his identity
will increase the impact.
You don't have to worry.
This guy's a PNU.
"PNU"?
Yes, it's a term HR uses.
It refers to someone who is useless.
What? That's so mean.
When a printed report has many pages
you can fold the corner like this
so the big bosses can flip easily.
Don't you think they'd appreciate it?
You're so thoughtful.
Are you serious?
- What?
- Never mind.
This is how I became a team leader.
Must be why I'm still a manager.
I think it looks great.
SEARCH HAEMU GROUP: JOO IN-A
JOO IN-A'S PERSONNEL FILE
SEARCH REQUEST FOR LEISURE STIPEND
NO REQUEST FOR LEISURE STIPEND
NO APPROVED REQUEST FOR LEAVE
NO RECORD OF COMPANY CARD USE
She doesn't go on leave
or claim any benefits.
And she doesn't eat much.
What does she live for?
Did I get you?
You almost fell onto your backside.
Is this what gives her joy?
I scored.
Wait, were you the one
looking after this plant?
Oh, yes.
I water it whenever I think of it.
You're surprisingly thoughtful,
Mr. Noh.
It's quite pretty.
It smells, too.
She's pretty.
Well, I guess you can't say
she isn't pretty.
What was that?
I think you just smiled at me.
That's because...
Do I look funny to you, Mr. Noh?
No, it's not that.
I found your prank hilarious.
When you jump-scared me.
The more I think about it,
the funnier it is.
The more I get to know you,
the more I see your humor.
You caught on?
I knew it. You have the wit.
I don't get
why people are afraid of me.
I'm hilarious, aren't I?
You are.
You get my wit.
Oh, my gosh.
My blood sugar must be going low.
Where was Ms. Yoon's snack box?
What's going on?
Ms. Yoon,
The snack box is in here, right?
Your box of snacks
full of candies and chocolates.
The drawer's locked.
Ms. Yoon.
Did you not like
my getting into your snack box?
You should've told me so.
Locking it away is harsh on your part
and embarrassing for me.
I kept dropping hints
that I didn't like it.
You failed to pick up on them.
Oh, dear. I feel bad.
- My gosh.
- What's wrong?
Mr. Moo,
I think you need to see this.
IF THEY DO THIS IN PUBLIC,
THEN IN PRIVATE...
OH, MY GOSH! SPARE ME!
Wow, you're the talk of the town.
MADAM KILLER IS HILARIOUS
"The Madam Killer"? Goodness.
You're a killer, too, Mr. Moo?
I had a nickname similar to that.
It's not at all like that.
Why would I go around killing ladies?
The photo was taken at an angle
that made us look suspicious.
We were...
That lady and I don't have
any kind of relationship.
I can't believe that smoke
sometimes does appear without a fire.
This isn't just some smoke.
The blaze could take us all down.
Assistant Manager Ahn Min-su.
Yes, Ms. Joo?
I need you to look into this.
Mr. Noh usually takes the PM cases
but that would be inappropriate
as they're teammates.
Pardon? Whose case am I taking on?
Mr. Moo's case.
- Gosh...
- Wait.
Are you going to investigate this?
Of course, I must.
The case is big enough
that everyone's talking about it.
Ms. Joo. It's just a random incident.
It can't even be called a case.
I'm innocent. You know what I'm like.
Yes, Mr. Moo.
That's all you have to say
when you're interviewed.
Drop everything you were working on
until the case is concluded.
If anything needs to be approved...
Manager Cha Sung-tae,
that's your duty now.
That's all.
Why are you still here?
You're dismissed.
Oh, dear. It really isn't anything.
It's really nothing.
My goodness...
WRITTEN STATEMENT
I'm home.
Is everyone in bed?
Are the girls asleep?
OUR AUDIT TEAM LEADER'S CHEATING
They say this is you.
Yes.
The food
you brought me last night.
Did she give it to you?
- Did she?
- No, it's not like that.
How should I explain?
Based on how she treated Mr. Moo
she wouldn't do anything.
wrong or immoral
Am I wasting my time?
Hang on. She's not going home?
Darn it.
Okay. This is it.
SEON DRAWING CLASS,
RECREATIONAL CLASS FOR ADULTS
"Recreational art"?
Excuse me.
Are you going inside?
No, sorry.
Was drawing her hobby?
- Hello.
- Morning.
Oh, my goodness!
Mr. Moo!
Oh, dear. My bad.
My gosh.
Goodness me.
Oh, dear.
Did you spend the night here?
Did you argue
with your wife last night?
Why sleep here
when we have a night duty room?
What are you doing here, Mr. Moo?
Good morning, Ms. Joo.
Something came up,
and I couldn't go home last night.
I couldn't think
of anywhere else to go.
So you decided to come to the office?
You don't seem to know
where to draw the line.
You take cafeteria food home
and come here to sleep at night.
Please leave
immediately.
- Sorry?
- The subject of investigation
does not have free access
to the office while it's ongoing.
This was far too careless of you
as the head of an audit team.
Ms. Pyun.
Request a restriction of his access
to General Affairs.
- Do we have to go that far...
- Going that far is our ground rule.
And Audit Teams are here
to strictly abide by the rules.
Yes, of course.
I should've thought this through.
I'll leave right away.
Goodness, I'm sorry.
Please let me just get my shoes.
Sorry.
Ms. Pyun, here's my employee ID.
Mr. Baek, can you put the box away?
Goodness. I'm sorry. I apologize.
I'm so sorry.
Mister, you're Moo Kwang-il,
aren't you?
- Yes, who are you?
- Don't you know me?
We met at my grandfather's funeral.
Yes, you're Ms. Eom's eldest son.
It's nice to see you.
I should've known
when you were acting nosy.
Work colleague, my foot.
Who would care
about an outsourced worker's family?
You were coming onto her!
There must be
a huge misunderstanding.
A misunderstanding?
That's easy for you to say.
My mom lost her job
and can't make a living anymore!
You'll probably be fine
because you're a big corporate guy
but my mom is an expendable! Get it?
Let go of me!
- Sir.
- Goodness!
Did she seem that easy to you,
you punk?
- Hey, goodness. Wait a second.
- Let go of me!
Let go!
- You can't do this here.
- Let go!
You went around acting nosy
like you were my dad. This is great.
You can now be my dad
and make a living for me, okay?
Dad... Father...
- Sir.
- Darn it.
Will you let go of me?
Just let go!
Please calm down.
Let go of me!
How dare you hit on my poor mother?
How can you be so vulgar
at your age? Darn it!
I knew he was like that
when he acted too nice.
It was a temporary reaction
due to stress
so please get a good rest.
Would you like anything to eat?
Come on, let's leave.
Get a good rest.
I've never seen Mr. Moo
look so disheartened before.
He must feel awful.
People took his act of kindness
and called it an affair and whatnot.
They all blamed him
like they were hunting him down.
It is too petty a matter
to even make excuses for.
Jeez, this is awful.
The bulletin has become crazier
in the meantime.
"No one is kind enough to visit
the cafeteria lady's dad's funeral."
They say it's 100 percent an affair.
Man, that's just too much.
Why are people like this? Why?
- Hello.
Is Mr. Moo inside?
- Is he all right?
- What do you think?
- Do you have the result?
- Yes.
It doesn't seem like
they were having an affair
but Mr. Moo will be reprimanded...
If he didn't have an affair,
why should he be?
After all, there was a commotion
within the company
and our reputation fell
when the word got out, so...
How is that his fault?
- He's the victim of a witch hunt!
- Yes.
I agree with you, but it's Ms. Joo.
- Excuse me.
- Wait a second.
Mr. Moo can't afford
to be shocked anymore right now.
Also, we cannot accept
this disciplinary action.
How will that change anything?
Let's go and ask Ms. Joo
to withdraw this as a team.
Yes, it's time to protest.
Well, the thing is...
It's embarrassing to bring this up.
I lost my fortune in crypto before
and couldn't pay my credit card bill
but Mr. Moo helped me out.
And she should do her part as a boss
to cover for her team in these times.
I wonder if she'd do that
when I do something wrong
- so it feels very personal.
- You're right.
This isn't just Mr. Moo's business.
This is everyone's problem.
Things seem
a bit heated up right now.
Why don't we calm down
and use our common sense to think...
Do you want to stay out of this?
Why? Do you not want to take part
because you're the Audit Team's ace?
COME TO THE ROOFTOP! PLEASE
FROM AUDIT TEAM 3
It was a phrase
I haven't heard for a while.
"Come to the rooftop."
So are you ganging up on me?
It's kind of cheap
to outnumber me like this.
Why don't a few of you cross over?
Ms. Joo.
We would like to speak to you
as a team
regarding Mr. Moo.
Withdraw the disciplinary action
against him, please.
- Please do that!
He's already suffering
from all kinds of malicious rumors.
The notice of his disciplinary action
will only make matters worse.
He wasn't at fault to begin with.
It was a misunderstanding.
Oh, my gosh!
Never mind.
My legs were hurting.
Now, where were we?
Yes, that Mr. Moo
didn't do anything wrong.
You're right.
There was no infidelity between them.
But he took cafeteria food out,
which is considered company property
and exchanged
a considerable amount of money
with an outsourced staff member
causing a controversy
inside and outside the office.
I think
reprimanding him sounds adequate.
Will anyone care
about the whole story?
They'll brand him for infidelity,
thinking the suspicions are right
because of the disciplinary action.
Then will glossing over this matter
put everything to its rest?
"The Audit Team nitpicks over
every little detail with us
but they cover for their own."
Wouldn't people insult
the entire team?
You're our boss
before you're the Head of Audit.
And shouldn't you draw the line
and protect us in times like these
if you truly are our boss?
How can we have faith in this company
if you treat us like this?
You don't need to have faith to work.
We aren't a church.
You come to work
because you get paid to be here!
And because we are paid,
I will fulfill my responsibility
and Mr. Moo must fulfill his own.
"Draw the line"?
That line is there
because you are not to step over it.
White Blood Cell, you're something.
Never mind. Go ahead.
I think we stepped off the deep end.
We can't end it like this.
The negotiation is off
so we must act as a group.
There's no talking to her,
so we must show her with our action.
Excuse me.
Ms. Joo, the entire team
took the rest of the day off.
They called it a kind of a strike.
They want you to retract
Mr. Moo's disciplinary action.
Goodness. There's a fly in here.
It's a dung fly.
Is the office not tidy enough?
Sorry?
Yes.
That was it?
All right. Bye.
Why? What did Ms. Joo say?
Nothing.
She caught a fly and turned around.
- That's it?
- Yes.
She must think we're a huge joke.
How can she not respond in any way
even after our group strike?
That's why she's Joo In-a.
I expected this, but how could she
not be bothered at all?
Whatever. Let's keep it going.
Take tomorrow off, too.
Wait a minute.
If Ms. Joo doesn't approve
our leave request
it'll be considered
unauthorized absence.
Wait, in that case...
Is there a possibility
that we'll also get punishment?
Come on.
Ms. Joo can't be that inconsiderate.
Isn't that why we're here now?
In that case
why don't one of us go upstairs
and do a quick vibe check?
And check how Ms. Joo is doing.
Do you want to go, Mr. Noh?
Me?
DOES ANYBODY KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED TO THE MADAM KILLER?
Lastly
Managing Director Jeon Sung-yeol
will return to the headquarters.
I expect you to show him support.
Now it's official.
It must be what the president wants.
Of course, it is.
Jeez, there are two suns
radiating up in our sky.
It'll happen, anyway.
Ms. Boo.
It's Se-young.
Se-young.
Isn't it about time
that you took a measure for Mr. Moo?
HR and Information Office
is in charge of the intranet.
I already shared the result
of our investigation
that the infidelity was groundless.
But the bulletin
is still going strong.
People are like that.
No one cares about the truth.
Exactly.
So I'm asking HR
to delete those posts accordingly.
We've been a little busy.
I'll look into it, though.
It's because of Mr. Jeon, isn't it?
The bulletin always has
posts about him
so you're diverting people
and manipulating opinions.
I've noticed it a while ago
but HR was doing what HR does
so I was going to observe.
But you know
I've had enough of your nonsense.
Nonsense?
Hey. Do you think HR is a joke?
Anyway.
But in the end,
I guess I have to thank him.
You always cover up a rumor
with another rumor.
Right?
You cover up a rumor
with another rumor, right?
What are you doing?
Hey. Let go of me. Hey!
You!
Have you lost your mind?
Get over here.
Let go of me!
Let go! Hey!
Let go! Let go of my hair!
Have you lost your mind?
Hey! Let go of me!
Let go of my hair!
'22 RECRUITS GROUP CHAT
1 NEW MESSAGE
AUDIT TEAM 3 GROUP CHAT
You. Let go of me.
Let go!
What kind of person
is Joo In-a?
- No way.
- This is the craziest ever.
- People made so many clips.
- Why did they fight?
They've always been enemies.
Everyone knew.
In the end, did everything go
according to her plan?
Right?
You cover up a rumor
with another rumor, right?
Know your limits.
A cornered mouse can bite the cat.
Ms. Joo.
I need to talk to you.
Unfortunately, I'm done for the day.
Please come to my office tomorrow.
What the heck is this complaint?
Wasn't the disciplinary action
more than enough?
Are you trying
to end someone's life?
Let's talk.
Anyway, Ms. Joo.
Do you have to keep
the rest of your fingers folded in?
I wanted to make it easier for you.
Right.
Goodness. Of all those fingers,
you hurt this one.
All done.
I only gave you first aid,
so please see a doctor tomorrow.
Okay. You're my savior today, so...
Please enjoy, sir.
Is this what your life is worth?
It's not for my life.
It's for my finger.
I look stylish and powerful.
I like this one.
"This one"?
Does this happen to you often?
This is kind of cute, actually.
Back in the day,
someone destroyed my computer
and another employee fled after
splashing my seat with superglue.
And a CEO of a corrupt business
struck my head with a golf club.
I probably have a scar here.
Right here. Can you see it?
It's from my surgery back then.
While I was working abroad
the local gang
even threatened me with a knife.
So I
picked up a gun.
That's why you're Joo-niper.
So that rumor was true?
Did you really shoot a person?
What do you think?
No, I don't want to know.
Ms. Joo.
About your fight with the Head of HR.
No, never mind.
Are you perverted?
- What?
- Do you get off on getting hated?
I know it's hard not to make enemies
when you're working
but you can try to make less.
But it seems like
you want to get hated
even more than you actually want.
No one wants to be hated.
However, there are times
when I must position myself.
I must either be a saint
or a villain.
If I stay in the middle,
I get no work done
lose my popularity,
and nothing works out.
Do you know who your worst boss is?
A non-committal jerk.
Yes.
You definitely are committed to one.
But it must be lonely
to have your sincerity misunderstood.
Did you misunderstand me?
How so?
That you were a cold-hearted person
who don't care about others' feelings
to accomplish your goals.
Well, I thought so.
But you seem to be someone
who does things your own way
when you do something
you believe is right.
People may misunderstand you
because of that
and you put yourself
in a hard position
but you do not back out
or make excuses.
I doubt it's easy
to always live like that.
Wow.
You know how to talk, Mr. Noh.
I was a bit moved just now.
Anyway, don't you think
the misunderstanding was harsh?
You practically thought
I was a psychopath.
You do come across that way.
Me?
But I love people.
Even personality tests say
I'm an extrovert
- like a cute little puppy.
- Cute little puppy?
People are intimidated by you!
You can't have this.
Look at this.
This is why you come off like that.
Give it back.
I'm a big psychopath,
so I can't do that.
It's even better
because I took it back from you.
Don't finish it. It's mine...
You skipped dinner today.
You should eat,
even if you don't want to.
Okay. Leave it there and go.
It's the key to the studio apartment.
Thank you for everything.
While moving out
I stole a bottle of your hard liquor
as a souvenir.
Is that okay?
I don't mind.
But why the sudden change?
Has your family matter been resolved?
No.
I just
don't want to stay there anymore.
Then where are you staying?
- Is it safe?
- I'm not telling.
I want you to be concerned
about me.
He wrapped it up so neatly.
Jae-yeol!
I'll see you more often now.
Jae-yeol.
Sure.
It's been a while
since I've written an apology
and I found the fun in it.
- Mr. Moo.
- Yes?
You're a special man who have worked
in 12 teams, 5 branches,
and 3 different subsidiaries.
You're highly interested
in every aspect of the company
so you have information and network.
It makes you a perfect candidate
to take up Audit Team Three
a team that receives
dozens of complains a day.
Above all
you're a good leader
to your team members
who each have a big personality.
Goodness, I appreciate
your words of consolation.
However
that's a double-edged sword.
Your sound personality
sometimes doesn't fit
to be the leader of the Audit Team.
Members of other departments are
the subjects of our investigation.
Make use of them as your intel
but please try to keep them
in a proper distance.
How can I make use of people
as my intel?
I'm not a spy.
Goodness.
Well, Ms. Joo.
I crunched some numbers
and realized that during weekdays,
I can only play with my daughters
two hours a day at most.
But I must sit here
and work with my colleagues
for nine hours a day.
And in those hours
if I do not keep
a friendly relationship
with my colleagues
it would make my life
too meaningless.
In the future
I will do my best to help out
if I find another colleague in need
and gladly take any food they bring
if they decide to do that.
I'll write up another apology
when that happens.
I'm sorry.
Anyway, I will do my job
without a big ambition
but for a long time
while enjoying my time here.
If you have nothing more to say,
then please excuse me.
All right.
Oh, Ms. Joo.
By any chance,
did you pull out Ms. Boo's hair
for my sake?
Is that important?
No. Please excuse me.
Perhaps
distinguishing between
your friend and foe at work
is not that important.
I don't work here anymore.
I got a better job elsewhere,
so don't worry about me.
Goodness,
you're such a talented person.
Good for you.
Please give me a call
when your twins get married.
I may not give you as much
but I want to show you
my token of sincerity.
Of course.
- Stay healthy.
- Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
What's more important is...
HEAD OF AUDIT
Gosh, the air in this office
is way too dry.
I should tidy this up a little.
Are you done?
Ms. Joo, here's your coffee.
Goodness.
Let me dry that off.
Shoo!
Shoo.
Excuse us.
...the discretion
not to turn your friend into a foe.
By any chance, do you feel hot?
Should I fan you?
- Stronger.
- Stronger wind.
Does that feel better?
And the determination to gladly
become my colleague's friend.
Perhaps those are more important.
RECREATIONAL ART CLASS
TONIGHT AT 9 P.M.
Even someone who has
a great reputation like Mr. Moo
got cornered
because of a single photo.
Joo In-a has enemies all around her.
That report.
REPORTING MS. JOO IN-A
It's probably
an attempt to entrap her.
All right. I need to stop here.
Wait. Excuse me.
Do you need that
to take a class here?
Oh, yes.
The club members must bring it.
I see. Thank you.
What's going on?
She wasn't carrying that thing.
FILING FOR LOVE
GUEST APPEARANCE BY LEE JUNG-EUN
How can I act like nothing happened?
It's just not the same.
This is driving me crazy.
Babe, come here. Hurry.
- Bravo!
- There's
definitely more to this incident.
Who did you mess with
to become their target?
If this backfires
due to a careless move
you could be in serious trouble.
I'll make sure it doesn't backfire.
Room 1306, please.
I'm staying the night.
Why are you hesitating now?
You've already seen it.
- Could you stop staring at my body?
- Sorry?
Subtitles by Eunsook Youn
and Jennifer Lim