(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
(All characters, places,
and organizations are fictional.)
(Children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
(Episode 14)
I stopped by to say hello,
but the lights were off.
So I figured you hadn't
come back from Germany yet.
I got back a few days ago.
The elderly woman you're looking after,
is she able to get around?
Yes. She just has some minor heart
and blood pressure issues,
but she's very good about
taking all her medication.
I'm really just there to keep her company,
so I feel a little guilty
getting paid for such an easy job.
I'm sure her family is relieved, though.
Knowing she's being cared for...
by a kind person like you
and not a total stranger.
I'd say I'm more lukewarm than kind.
Honestly, it feels more like
she's taking care of me.
She tells me great stories,
and she's someone I can really lean on.
When I go back this time,
I might be gone for a while.
I want to stay by his side
until his treatment is finished.
He used to have a girlfriend,
but she left him.
Since you're nearby,
could you check on this place
once in a while?
Bring in the mail and things like that.
Of course. When are you leaving?
I have some things to finish up.
I'll leave this week, once I get a ticket.
You get regular checkups, don't you?
I got one when I came back last year.
They said nothing was wrong.
You should get one every year.
Reporter Geum, how are your parents?
Yes, Grandma.
I'll be there in a minute. I'm close by.
Okay.
She said she can't find
the pain relief patches.
I'll let you go then.
Right.
- No, don't worry about it.
- I'll just leave it there for you.
- I'm glad I got to see you, though.
- Me too.
I sometimes worry
since it's a detached house.
By the way, my number changed.
I'll text it to you.
- Okay.
- I know it's tough with a sick person,
but have a safe trip.
- Thanks. I'll walk you out.
- It's only a ten-minute walk.
- Still, she's waiting...
- Hey, your phone is ringing.
Okay, just text me then.
Okay, I will.
(Kim Young Jun:
The door passcode is 8-8-3-2.)
The car will just go to waste here,
so feel free to use it.
The insurance covers any driver.
The freezer is full of
ingredients people have sent me.
Please help yourself to anything you need.
I'd really appreciate it.
I'm sure you need some time
to yourself as well.
Come by whenever
and make yourself at home.
Listen to some music or read a book.
I suddenly got a craving for the sea bream
and seaweed soup my mom used to make,
so I tried making it from memory
for the first time.
I think it tastes pretty similar,
to me at least.
But I made way too much.
I put a container in the fridge,
so give it a try.
You can always try again.
I guess this is her punishment
for throwing away such a blessing.
Now she came in
and snatched up my precious brother...
Yong Joong must be devastated
when even I feel this bad.
And Reporter Geum...
It's like she vanished into thin air
or was swallowed by the earth.
I miss her so much.
What if she's despairing
over her situation...
No, I shouldn't even think about that.
A part of me thinks it's for the best.
I'd rather have a son anyway.
We'll have a son next time.
Just focus on recovering for now.
And no swimming for a while.
What did your brother say?
What do you think?
What did he say?
He said we can always try again.
And he wasn't worried about me?
It was a quick call.
- Of course he was.
- I bet he was secretly thrilled.
He was more excited than anyone
about having a niece or nephew.
I'm telling you, his feelings toward me
changed the minute we got married.
Don't jump to conclusions.
You're just clueless about these things.
Do we have any soy milk?
- I'll go get some.
- No, don't.
I don't want to be alone.
Have you heard from Ba Ra?
Are you worried about her?
She's on my mind.
That's why she disappeared.
She wants everyone
to miss her and worry about her.
I bet she's doing just fine somewhere.
Doing what?
Maybe a part-time job in the south,
at a cram school or something.
That'd be a relief if it's true.
Don't make me worried.
We won't be able to have a baby
if I'm stressed out.
(Pregnancy Test)
Come over for brunch tomorrow.
Yong Joong will be here.
- You know it's your birthday, right?
- It's my birthday?
Gosh, you don't even
know your own birthday?
I'm fine.
You're busy, so don't trouble yourself.
But I want to.
Is it so hard to have one meal together?
- Besides, it's been so long since we met.
- Then let's eat out.
The birthday boy is supposed to treat,
you know.
I'm so sick of eating out.
(Call Log)
(Chairman Park, Reporter Yoon Oh Cheol...)
(Unread messages)
(Team Leader Yoon Young Chan...)
(Development Team's Manager Kim...)
(Park Il Joon,
Operations Team's Manager Choi...)
It's opened up perfectly.
First time eating here, right?
- Yes.
- Happy birthday.
To our personal physician.
I feel like I'm always taking from you.
What are you talking about?
I loved the abalone you sent last time.
That was just something I got
and passed along.
Tossed or whatever, it was delicious.
You could have passed it to someone else.
Eat before your soup gets cold.
I wonder if the seasoning
is to your liking.
It might be a bit bland for you,
Director Shin.
A doctor should practice what he preaches.
- What's this?
- Cazuela.
I enjoyed it in Madrid.
Scoop some out and put it on the bread.
You always make way too much.
Don't worry.
I just freeze the leftovers
and eat them all myself.
A birthday calls
for a proper feast like this.
I'm starting to wonder if
Reporter Geum joined a monastery.
How else could she have vanished
without a trace?
I doubt it.
It's been over six months with no word,
not just a month or two.
Should I check with
the Jogye Order office at Jogyesa?
Manager Yoon. What is it?
Park Sun Woo said she just saw
Reporter Geum at a rest stop.
- Reporter Geum Ba Ra?
- Yes.
- Which rest stop?
- Let me ask her.
No, wait. Hold on.
Who was with her?
And she's sure it was Reporter Geum?
Park Sun Woo wouldn't be mistaken.
She was with an elderly woman.
An elderly woman?
- But...
- But what?
She said she looked different.
Looked different?
Her belly was showing.
- You mean she's pregnant?
- Yes.
How far along did she look?
No. She must be mistaken.
She says she's positive.
I didn't believe it at first, either.
And she didn't say anything to her?
She saw her helping the elderly woman
into a car,
but Park Sun Woo's husband had to rush
to the restroom, so she couldn't get out.
Right as they were pulling
into the rest stop...
Ask them which rest stop it was.
Ask how far along she looked...
- and if Reporter Geum saw Sun Woo.
- Okay.
What is going on?
You haven't heard?
(Manager Yoon)
- Yes.
- It was the Meeting Plaza.
She looked six or seven months along.
Maybe five?
Did she say she looked happy?
- Did she seem to be doing well?
- She said she seemed fine.
What about inside the car?
Who else was there?
She couldn't see that.
But she said it was definitely Geum Ba Ra.
She has such a unique face.
There's no way they were mistaken.
But if her husband was in a rush,
she could've grabbed her phone and left.
Park Sun Woo was driving.
Then she could've told him to get out
and run for it.
It's a busy rest stop.
Cars are always coming in.
- All right.
- Maybe she's with a regular guy?
- You can go now.
- Okay.
Could Manager Yoon be right?
If she's six or seven months along,
that means she got pregnant
after she disappeared.
It's crazy, but she's sure she saw her,
so we have no choice but to believe her.
If she were at Meeting Plaza,
does she live
in Seoul or just passing through?
Is she on a trip?
You have a beautiful baby.
How many months is she?
She's nine months.
Do you live here at the painter's house?
No. He's abroad at the moment,
so I just check on the house now and then.
When are you due?
Are you about six months along?
The 12th of next month.
Goodness. Is it your first baby?
- Yes.
- I was huge when I was pregnant.
My mother-in-law wants another already.
Gosh, already?
Her health isn't great.
Hyun Ran Hee visited today.
Momo's mom, CEO Hyun?
Even though my face has changed,
how could she not even remember my voice?
Even if she'd forgotten me,
how could she completely forget
the child she gave birth to...
and go on living as if nothing happened?
I just can't understand it.
She's a mother, after all.
She asked about the child
so mechanically...
and then left without a word.
As for me,
any old feelings I had for Hyun Ran Hee
are completely gone.
All I want is to find our daughter.
"Our daughter?"
Hyun Ran Hee is dead.
She took her own life.
If only I had answered her call
that night,
she might not have made that decision.
She might still be alive.
I'm worried about Momo.
How will she cope?
And how will she go on living?
Momo?
Momo left, asking me to let her know
if I found her sister.
I'm the one who's desperate to find her.
My baby's eyes, nose, and mouth.
I can still see them so clearly,
but why didn't I think to take a picture?
Even in all the chaos,
I should have taken one.
I don't deserve to be a father.
How will I ever live with this guilt?
I'm so sad,
and it hurts so much.
It can't be true.
When I heard from Mr. Park
that he'd found Kim Jin Ju,
the whole world felt like paradise.
But it wasn't her.
Where in the world could my daughter,
Kim Jin Ju, be?
Please, just be alive.
I pray the sky is watching over her...
again today.
Congratulations. This is such a surprise.
It feels like a dream.
I really hope he's my dad.
Are the results not a match?
Not a match.
I'm just giving it a shot.
So I won't have any what-ifs.
And no regrets.
I have something to say.
My wife isn't home yet.
You know I got fired, right?
I was fired.
I hadn't even been here one month.
This is ridiculous.
Why?
(Hospital Director, Shin Ju Shin)
The housekeeper stopped by.
What did she say?
Why can't you cut people some slack?
You fired the last one
just for not answering her phone promptly.
She deserved it.
Reusing disposable gloves
is a fireable offense?
You think that was the only thing?
She barely rinsed the cutting board
and never wiped the windowsills.
The windowsills are spotless.
Yong Joong.
Are you taking the housekeeper's side
over mine?
I'm not taking sides.
It's just a fact that...
If you keep this up,
what if someone posts about it online?
You'll get slammed
for being on a power trip.
Then I'll sue them for defamation.
You're going to fight them on it?
That's not the way to handle it.
Nobody's perfect, you know?
I expect to get what I pay for.
It's not like she works for free.
Just stay out of household matters.
You think I want to be involved?
She came here to complain,
but you were at your get-together,
so who else was going to deal with her?
I had to sit here and take it all.
The nerve of her.
You need to treat people better.
Why not start with me?
When have I ever treated you poorly?
The wife of Hyunsong Pharma's CEO...
replaces people
until she finds the right one.
All right, that's enough.
You started this,
and now you want to stop?
You shouldn't have brought it up,
or you should've put her in her place.
Why should we have to get upset
over the housekeeper?
This is so irritating.
Clothes fill every single room.
Stop buying so much stuff.
- They're taking up all the space.
- I buy them with my own credit card.
I don't care whose card it is.
There's no room to walk
with your clothes, bags, and shoes.
I'm an actress.
But you wear sponsored outfits to events,
don't you?
There are dozens of outfits
hanging in there with the tags still on.
Have you been going through my things?
This can't go on.
If you want to buy more,
you have to get rid of some first.
Then let's move into a house,
or build a 670m² one.
Or if the apartment upstairs or downstairs
goes on the market, we can buy it.
I already checked.
The one upstairs is just a rental.
You can't be so reckless with money.
People with money should spend it.
It helps the economy.
If you want to spend money,
why don't you donate it to the needy?
You already donate.
Are you taking this out on me?
You fire someone for being disrespectful.
You fire them if the food is too salty...
If it's too salty, just ask them
to use less salt next time.
It's one thing after another.
Now you're ruining their livelihood
over some gloves.
It's driving me crazy,
having new staff in here every other day.
It doesn't feel like home,
and I can never relax.
What do you mean, "every few days?"
Why are you so obsessed with clothes?
Don't you know the difference
between elegance and excess?
What does that even mean?
Fine, I'll get out of your hair.
Darn it.
Momo.
(Paternity Test)
(Paternity DNA Test)
(Sekyul DNA Test Center,
Helixnova Gene Analysis Center)
(Unigen Prism Center)
(Nexergene Bio Center)
(Paternity DNA test,
real-time and confidential)
(Domestic, International Standard,
International Express, EMS)
I thought I would get pregnant right away.
But the doctors say there's nothing wrong.
Just try to relax and be patient.
Shopping is the easiest way
to feel better, you know?
Mr. Ha...
You, of all people,
should understand, right?
But still,
there's a limit.
I was floored
when I stopped by the other day.
Every room is just stuffed with clothes.
I just haven't been myself lately.
This is my way of coping.
It's better than taking antidepressants
or seeing a shrink, isn't it?
This too shall pass.
It's not about it passing.
I need to get pregnant.
You're both perfectly healthy.
It'll happen.
They say kids are a gift from the sky.
Who says that?
- Where is that written?
- Fine, don't believe it then.
You can't just pack your bags
and storm out of the house.
He hurt my pride. What else could I do?
You think you can live on pride alone?
Look...
I'm Momo.
He sent two texts, and that was it.
Is this really what I got married for?
I'm not going back until he gives me
a proper apology.
He wasn't wrong, though.
Don't take his side just
because he's your brother.
A couple's business is their own.
All right.
Have you heard anything about Geum Ba Ra?
Have you?
I don't know. It's not certain.
They probably just imagined it.
What was it? Come on, tell me.
Oh, boy.
Momo.
Hey.
I'm worried she's trembling somewhere.
If they really saw her at Meeting Plaza,
then she must be with someone.
Did you really like Ba Ra?
It was more than just
a simple crush on a girl.
I was just drawn to her.
Just me.
(James)
- Hey, James.
- You changed the door code again?
Yes, it's 2-3-5-3, star.
She changed it so I wouldn't
waltz in anymore.
Remember that rainy day?
The jajangmyeon Ba Ra made for us
was so good.
She makes great gimbap, too.
Do you think Ba Ra...
ever thinks about us?
She probably doesn't think of me.
You?
She could.
She didn't want you to see her
as a little sister.
She wanted you to see her as a woman.
You couldn't tell?
Seriously?
You kept treating her like a kid,
so she couldn't tell you how she felt.
You know how proud she is.
She said her pride is all she ever had.
She really told you that?
That's why...
you two spent the night together.
When?
- Then why are you just telling me now?
- And what if I had?
You were about to get married.
And when I asked if you'd call yours off
if I called off mine,
you couldn't answer.
- Do you feel differently now?
- I don't know.
I try not to think about it.
You need to really look at your feelings.
See if she's still just
little Ba Ra to you.
But if you slept with her,
how can she be a kid?
Exactly.
I told her I needed some time.
I know this is kind of personal,
but how is it living with Momo?
I just feel pathetic.
Your feelings for someone
aren't supposed to change.
If they didn't, you'd be a robot.
To be honest,
Momo isn't the person I imagined.
And Ba Ra isn't
who I thought she was either.
So what are you going to do?
What can I do?
There's no way to find Ba Ra.
I'm married. I have to be responsible.
You should have realized it sooner.
Seriously?
I'm not making excuses,
but I thought Ba Ra...
had feelings for you.
It was just gratitude for my position,
nothing more, nothing less.
She was good to me when we were together.
She'd put so much care
into cooking for me.
She'd even send food
to the operating room.
Things like that just
keep popping into my head.
I can't stop thinking about them.
The thing I don't get is,
am I just unable to forget that one night,
or have I actually fallen
for her as a woman?
It's probably a bit of both.
They say life never goes the way you plan.
For all we know, Ba Ra...
might not care about either of us anymore.
And here we are, still doing this.
We hear rain and run out,
hoping she's there.
There is no way she hasn't forgotten.
Ba Ra was even hospitalized.
She wasn't in any condition to fly,
so I had her stay at my place.
If you hadn't shown up that day,
Ba Ra would've left for Boston.
And I would've had to just let her go.
I asked her what she liked
so much about you.
She said her whole life was just for you.
At first, when she was young,
her only goal was to be successful
so she could see you again.
But then it turned into something more.
Of course she would.
But you only had eyes for Momo.
It must have been so hard for her,
just watching.
She figured if you knew how she felt,
you'd decide to marry her.
She said that, out of a sense of duty,
forcing your feelings
would be meaningless.
When did you get here?
You should've just gone home.
I already dropped Momo off there.
This is my home too.
Unless you're planning on leaving her,
go easy on her.
After all, you two got married
because you were in love.
She lost the baby, and she's anxious
about having trouble conceiving.
Has Ba Ra...
ever said anything to you about me?
No. She would not have.
- Why?
- Is there really no way to find her?
She obviously left for a personal reason.
What good would finding her do?
The best way to help her
is to leave her be.
All of us...
ever really knew Ba Ra at all.
You can never truly know
what's in someone's heart.
Sometimes I don't even know my own mind.
There's no point in dwelling on it.
Just focus on Momo.
I'll make you some soup.
You treat Momo better than me.
I was jealous and upset.
She told me exactly how she felt,
and I had no idea.
Where are you, Geum Ba Ra?
(Test Results)
(DNA match test results:
99.9 percent match)
(Paternity is established
between Kim Young Jun and Geum Ba Ra)
Could Artist Kim Young Jun really be...
my dad?
(Could Artist Kim Young Jun
really be my father?)
You're gorgeous!
- Can you look over here, please?
- Thank you.
Momo, could I get a picture with you, too?
- Sure.
- Thank you.
- Okay, ready?
- One, two, three.
You're so, so pretty.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- You're even prettier in person.
- Can I get one too?
- I'm sorry, but we have to get going now.
Get home safe.
Take care!
I know, right?
Of all the photos taken of me in Korea,
this is my favorite.
(Artist Kim Young Jun)
What's this?
I went to the hospital today,
and the doctor suggested
a fertility clinic,
even if nothing's technically wrong.
You can make time on Friday, can't you?
It won't take long.
No. Why would we do that?
I'm anxious, okay?
You have nothing to be anxious about.
You want a baby too, don't you?
Let's just let nature take its course.
It's not hard.
All we have to do is show up.
If you want to be a father,
then cooperate.
- Watch your tone.
- I'm the one who'd bear your child.
I'm the one who has to go through it all
if we start treatments.
Exactly. So who's asking you to do it?
Have we been trying for five years?
Or ten?
It's not like we have parents pushing us,
so why are you so obsessed with this?
Obsessed?
It's about our child, not an obsession.
The child isn't even born yet.
And you're too busy
with your games to care.
You think I'm just playing around?
I need something too!
What's so hard about one doctor's visit?
Just do this for me once.
I've done everything you've ever wanted.
I buy you everything you ask for.
It's easy for you
to just throw money at things.
Money and time.
I shop with you for hours when you want.
- What more do you want from me?
- And me?
What have you done?
- I'm Momo.
- So what...
if you're Momo?
You want a medal
for doing the bare minimum?
- A medal?
- What else would you call it?
I'm saying I did my best as your husband.
So as your wife,
I'm offering to have your baby.
Maybe we can think about it in a few years
if it doesn't happen.
At least Shin Ju Shin
had some paternal instinct.
Is it wrong to want a baby
so we can finally be a happy family?
Then you should've stayed with Ju Shin
and been happy.
Don't you dare compare me to him!
You're so two-faced.
Then go find your precious, pregnant Ba Ra
and live together.
I heard James's employee saw her.
Let's just end it!
Geum Ba Ra tried to have it all
and ended up with nothing.
I bet she shacked up with some nobody
and is having his kid somewhere.
Too embarrassed to show her face,
just hiding away.
Darn it.
If you're not coming back,
then pack your bags.
I said it's over. I'll sign the papers.
Are you sure you won't regret this?
You bastard.
It could just be false labor.
Your due date isn't for another ten days.
Thank you.
Especially on a Sunday.
It wouldn't matter if it were
the middle of the night.
Is your doctor coming in?
Yes.
Well, the baby's dropped,
so it could be time.
(Solpyeong Women's Clinic)
Okay, take a big deep breath in,
and exhale.
Okay, bear down and give a big push.
Take a breath and push!
Yes, good. Keep pushing.
Yes, just like that.
It's impossible without
a formal police investigation.
Personal privacy laws are
so much stricter these days.
Even my police contacts are lying low.
Well, I appreciate the effort.
I'm sorry.
It is what it is.
My baby...
You're not alone.
Mommy's here, and so is your grandfather.
You're doing great.
Okay, one more.
Last one.
A little more.
Just a little bit more.
Okay, you're almost there!
There we go.
You did great, Mom.
I want to hold my baby.
Here you go.
The father must be very handsome.
He's absolutely gorgeous.
Could you take...
a picture for us?
Stop drinking that ice water.
I'm fine.
So, what are you going to do?
She stormed out like that.
She's probably filing for divorce.
What good will a divorce do her?
It's her own loss.
First a broken engagement, now a divorce.
An actress lives and dies
by her public image.
I made a mistake I can't take back.
You hit Momo?
To Ba Ra.
What did you do to her?
I have to find Ba Ra.
How are you going to find someone
who's determined to stay hidden?
Momo's probably right.
She got lonely and ended up
with some loser.
Don't you know Ba Ra?
She even pushed Ju Shin away and left.
- What could possibly...
- It might be my baby.
But if she's six or seven months along,
the timeline doesn't add up.
Exactly.
So, you're saying, you and Reporter Geum?
Oh my gosh.
- I'm heading in.
- Okay.
- Could you look after Grandmother?
- Don't worry.
When she saw the baby's picture,
she said he was very handsome.
(Test Results)
(Paternity is established
between Kim Young Jun and Geum Ba Ra)
(Match)
Yes, sir.
When Reporter Geum Ba Ra was
at Meeting Plaza, was she at full term,
or six or seven months pregnant?
- Try to remember exactly.
- She wasn't full-term.
Didn't you see her from far away?
About ten meters away.
I could tell she was pregnant right away,
so I was surprised,
so I stared for a few seconds.
You're sure it was six or seven months?
Yes. Or maybe even five months?
- All right.
- Yes, sir.
Is this a love story
or some crazy soap opera?
It's not a total soap opera.
Then who on earth did she meet?
She has the worst luck.
So what are you going to do?
Should I get the papers ready?
How much are you offering?
For alimony.
Shouldn't I be the one getting paid?
Since I'm the one being divorced here.
- How much do you want?
- Half.
Are you serious?
Dead serious.
I don't resent you.
I'm grateful.
If it weren't for you, I would've spent
my whole life as an orphan.
Because of you, I have my baby,
and I even found my birth father.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
I'm having the birthday soup...
that my father made...
Maybe I should've just
married the director.
He seemed cold,
but he had a warm side to him.
(Momo. Born: February 14, 2002.
Occupation: Actress)
(Momo: No Comment on Separation Rumors)
(Is Momo Getting Divorced?
Confirmed Living in Her Old Villa)
(Momo Remains Silent on Separation...
Divorce Rumors Resurface)
(Is Momo Getting Divorced?
Confirmed Living in Her Old Villa)
(Momo Remains Silent on Separation...
Divorce Rumors Resurface)
This is so pathetic.
I look so pathetic.
Seriously.
Should I just admit I was wrong?
Then that softy Ha Yong Joong
would just let it all go.
Internal medicine specialists and interns,
please report to the third floor
immediately.
(International Call)
- Hello?
- Reporter Geum, I see you called.
I did.
Is everything okay at the house?
Yes, it's nothing.
A shelf on the bookcase fell off.
When are you coming back?
How's the patient doing?
The doctor says
he won't last another three months.
I'm the daughter...
(I'm the daughter...)
you've been...
(I'm the daughter you've been...)
searching for.
Hello?
Yes, Mr. Kim.
Do you have a cold?
Yes, a little...
Thanks anyway.
Do you need anything?
I can grab it on my way.
No, I'm good.
Wait. For a baby...
Baby?
Never mind.
A friend of mine just had a baby,
so I was wondering, maybe a baby toy?
Got it. A baby toy.
I'll let you go then, Mr. Kim.
Okay, yes. It's a bit noisy here.
Okay.
Father.
Dad.
Don't bite your nails.
Those are my sister's nails.
(Those are my sister's nails)
What happened?
Say something.
I went down to the countryside
to get some rest.
(Brother-in-law)
Honey, I was wrong.
Please forgive me.
I just wanted you to baby me.
I won't stress over having a baby anymore.
I'll leave it to fate.
From now on, I'll live only for you.
Can I get you something cold? A beer?
No.
- Champagne?
- I'm not in the mood.
I'm a man of my word.
I made myself clear.
I said to pack your bags
if you weren't coming home.
I said I'm sorry!
You take everything too lightly.
- You only think about yourself.
- That's not true.
I promise I'll do better from now on.
I'll never upset you again.
I won't be harsh on the housekeepers.
It's all part of
learning to live together.
I feel like I finally understand you now.
I really do.
The feeling's mutual.
We're not compatible.
There's nothing more to say.
Honey, in life...
Sure, couples can bicker
from time to time.
But what did I do that was so wrong?
Now that we're ending things,
I don't want to list every single thing.
"Ending things?"
I'll get the papers ready.
How much alimony are you going to give me?
I'll discuss it with my lawyer.
I'm Momo.
First a broken engagement, now a divorce?
- I'll take the fall.
- And what becomes of my life?
You brought this on yourself.
Don't take what I say as a joke.
Don't you love me?
You did.
I've thought about it.
It was closer to fascination than love,
but whether it's love or fascination,
it's still a feeling.
But I'll be honest about how I feel now.
I'm completely over you.
That bastard.
That bastard!
How can you be so cruel?
- I had my own complaints, you know.
- Like what?
You were always thinking about Geum Ba Ra,
weren't you?
I know.
Right?
I was the one who had to
put up with it all!
In any case,
I did my best as your husband.
You did your best acting the part.
The point is, we're both over each other.
Fine, I'll give you a divorce
after I have a baby.
I'll have a baby and devote my life to it.
You can do that much, can't you?
I'm so done with men.
No! I won't break up with you! I can't!
I refuse to be humiliated again.
How pathetic would that make me look?
My mom died, my engagement was broken,
and now a divorce?
I might as well be dead.
Hey!
Hey, what's all this?
Calm down and talk it out.
I'll give you two some space.
Put on your coat.
Why?
Please talk to her.
He wants a divorce!
Oh, not like that.
Hurry up and put the side dishes
in the fridge.
Whatever happens, happens.
(Ju Shin)
- Hello?
- Ba Ra is in the hospital.
- Ba Ra?
- Yes, today.
What happened? Is she sick?
It's nothing serious,
but we're going to run some tests.
(Doctor Shin)
Do you really think you can be happy,
Ha Yong Joong, after making me cry?
I'm going to make your life
a living torment.
I'll have ten kids
if that's what it takes.
As many as we can have.
- Did you get married?
- Were you seeing someone?
Her hemoglobin is low,
so I'm thinking of an MRI this weekend,
just in case.
Did she say anything else?
Like how she's been?
I'll become you and live as Geum Ba Ra.
Living as Momo can't be that bad.
Why do you want to become me?
With that face and that body,
there's no reason to cling to them.
Think of all the tears you've shed.
Thank you.
And don't forget what I told you.
I'm never letting you go again,
Geum Ba Ra.
Can you accept...
my child too?
It's only the first step that's hard.
You're just asleep for a few hours,
and then you wake up.
It's no big deal.
- You scream, and you'll regret it!
- Dad!
It's me, Jin Ju.
I'm Momo now! We swapped brains!
Don't give me that crap.
Ma'am!
Are you all right?
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)