[SUZUKI] Thanks to our
super romantical class trip...
[gasps] Oh, Tani!
...Tani and I are closer
than we've ever been before.
Hola!
You recharge your batteries
after the trip?
Yeah.
How are you, Suzuki?
[SUZUKI] Just kidding,
things are the same as always.
Huh? What is it?
Is something wrong?
[muttering]
Still plain ol' "Suzuki."
OH.
Miyu.
[groans nervously]
Wait a second,
but you just called me Tani
instead of Yuusuke.
[SUZUKI]
Really? I didn't notice.
Then again, we are at school,
so gotta keep things
a little profesh.
[TANI] Yeah, you're right.
Wait, so you wouldn't
be profesh if we were,
you know, alone?
You know, are you saying
that if the mood was just right,
you'd, you know...
No, I really don't think I do.
[SUZUKI] To ze common eye,
this romance has made
few large developments.
But the improvements
are incremental.
Who are you talking to?
I'm just out here chroniclin'
the small imperfections o' life.
It's called wabi-sabi.
Satou, your handwriting.
Pretty, right?
How come you're the one
acting proud?
[laughing]
Yeah, wait a sec.
I MIGHT
JUST BE IMAGINING IT, BUT.
[SUZUKI] Am I crazy,
or did Azuma
totally shake her storm cloud?
Where's her negative aura?
AFTER SCHOOL
Hey, Tani, did you already
order some class trip pics?
Not yet.
[SUZUKI]
Tani's social circle is growing.
It's like whenever
I take my eyes off him,
he's made a new friend.
You at least
have to order this one.
You're moggin' us all.
I don't know what that means,
but it sounds like a lie.
THEY WERE IN THE BIG ROOM
WITH HIM
STARE
[Saotome gasps]
Suzuki's staring into my soul!
Show me my man's glamour shots,
or else.
[laughs] What the heck's
going on here?
Some guy walked in and we
asked him to take a pic for us.
[laughs]
-And here's the hot one.
-[Suzuki laughs]
This is so dumb!
Aww, if you won't order these,
I totally will.
[TANI] You should
save your money.
[grumbles] There are so many
to choose from.
You should just
pick out a few faves.
These prices are
highway robbery.
This reminds me
of when Gapacho ordered
a bunch of photos
from our middle-school trip,
and not a single one of them
had him in it.
Apparently his folks were
super pissed off about it.
[SUZUKI]
So he just got the landscapes?
Gapacho's an artiste!
[TAIRA] I'd do the same.
HE DOESN'T WANT
PHOTOS OF HIMSELF
HE WANTS A RECORD OF THE TRIP.
Boom, bought 'em.
I'm not in too many,
so that was easy.
What? There's a lot of you. See?
[exclaims] You know better than
to fall for deepfakes, girl!
[Honda sighs]
Finally, a day
where I'm not bogged down
by student council work.
Ever since our classmates
picked me to be class rep
while I was out sick,
I've hated their guts.
That being said, don't you think
the class trip was super sweet?
[Nishi gasps]
Uh, yeah, it was nice.
[students chattering]
Mm?
[Nishi gasps]
[AZUMA] No, don't.
I like that one.
[whimpers]
[gasps]
So, have you two
set up your date?
[NISHI] What?
Oh, well, um...
[♪ opening theme song playing]
YOU AND I ARE POLAR OPPOSITES
[NISHI] What do I do?
Wanna hang out later?
After the class trip?
[NISHI] It's out
of character for me,
but maybe just this once,
I'll try to dress up.
The last time I dressed fancy...
Oh my. Well, don't you look
like a cute little cupcake.
[NISHI]
Ever since Mom said that,
I've been embarrassed
to wear this stuff!
I've barely
ever worn this dress.
Should I wear it now?
Will it be okay?
Or is it too weird
for a casual meet up?
I'm usually a function-
over-fashion kind of girl.
You should always wear
what you want to.
It doesn't matter
what people think.
If you wanna be a cupcake,
lay on the frosting.
[NISHI] All right,
fancy dress it is!
This is my chance.
I've bought lots of random
accessories over the years,
but I've never
actually worn them.
Huh?
What's going on?
What is this feeling?
My heart is racing,
and it just won't stop!
-[birds chirping]
-[door opens]
I'm heading out.
[NISHI'S MOM] What? This early?
[NISHI] That was close.
I managed to leave
without my family seeing me!
ALL DECKED OUT
WHEW.
I'm probably
realizing a little late,
but nothing in my outfit
actually goes well together.
I bought each item
because it was cute on its own
and didn't even think
about coordinating it
with the rest of my wardrobe.
[indistinct chatter]
[NISHI] It's funny.
THE STATION
WHERE THEY'RE MEETING
I never really
noticed it before today,
but all the girls
walking down the street
look so fashionable!
SHOWY
I gotta take these off!
-[cell phone buzzes]
-[gasps]
I'M HERE!
WHERE ARE YOU RIGHT NOW?
[NISHI]
Um, I'm already here too.
I'm near the top
of the back escalator,
over on the platform.
[whimpering]
[cell phone buzzing]
NISHI-SAN
INCOMING CALL
Yellow, Nishi.
You good?
Are you lost?
[NISHI] No, I'm already here.
Whoa, where at?
[NISHI] Um, if you go up
the escalator, there's, uh,
I suppose it's a plaza.
[YAMADA] Hmm.
She'll never see me like that.
I'm standing
next to the ticket gates.
-[YAMADA] Heya.
-What?
Reception isn't so--
[gasps] Forgive me, sir.
-So formal.
-[squeals]
And intense.
Oh, I apologize.
I didn't realize it was you.
[YAMADA] You sounded all shaky
on the phone, too.
Sorry.
Wait, are you nervous?
[NISHI]
Are you really asking that?!
[whimpers] Yeah, I am.
-[YAMADA] Me too.
-[Nishi gasps]
[NISHI] Wait, now that
I've got a closer look,
did Yamada style his hair
a little differently than usual?
Smooth as ice.
[NISHI] Now I can't remember.
What does it normally look like?
Come to think of it,
I never look Yamada in the eye
or even at his face
when we talk.
SHE LOOKS AT THIS AREA
CHINATOWN
Going to a place
I've never been.
Wearing something
besides my uniform.
Walking together, just us two.
It's hard to believe
that we're even part
of each other's worlds.
Of all the girls out there,
how am I the one
walking next to him?
-Wanna eat something?
-[gasps]
I am kinda peckry.
Wait, I mean hungry.
You know,
I'm kinda peckry myself.
[whimpers]
[NISHI]
I was gonna say "peckish"
and switched words
halfway through.
That's normalry.
[Nishi whimpering]
Whoa, looks good.
I should've
asked this earlier,
but is it cool with you
that I chose the restaurant?
Mm-hm.
I've got no idea why,
but I was like mega craving
a warm meat bun.
Yeah, the weather did cool down.
-It did.
-It's nice.
AWARD WINNING XIAO LONG BAO
ULTIMATE
[YAMADA]
I usually stop by Taira's work
whenever I wanna get
some steamies,
but then I caught a whiff
of some
delicious-smelling meat buns
on my way home the other day.
And I thought, "I gotta
chow down in Chinatown."
Oh, there's this new
convenience store I go to,
that's where my boy Taira works.
[NISHI] Taira,
the boy with brown hair.
[YAMADA] It was hilarious.
Mini had Morimo
dying of laughter.
[NISHI] I'm learning
more and more names,
thanks to Yamada's stories.
[YAMADA]
So I went to ask Gapacho
if he wanted to go when, uh...
Oh, God, have I been
talking this whole time?
-Your go.
-Oh!
Uh...
-Back in the line, you lost me.
-What?
You used a strange word.
I didn't know what
you were talking about
when you said "steamies."
It's what I call store-bought
meat and pizza buns.
I see.
STARE.
What else were you lost on?
You said you "caught a whiff
of meat buns."
Curry would make sense,
but meat buns don't
have a strong smell.
Oh, come on, they totally do!
You know, on the train,
when someone's got
a takeout box full of 'em,
it invades your brain.
-It's like stank psyops!
-[laughs]
-"Chow down in Chinatown."
-Whoa.
Talk about a delayed reaction.
I can't even remember
why I made that joke.
How come you didn't laugh
when I said it?
[NISHI] I'm sorry.
It was funny,
but you were talking,
and I didn't wanna
interrupt your story.
Interrupt away, girl.
Don't remind me
I made a cringe joke
-way after the fact.
-[laughs]
"It's like stank psyops."
Now what did I just tell you?
[laughs]
What'd you end up doing
on the class trip
in your free time?
Um, well,
-I went to a comedy show.
-Mm-hmm.
And I took a lot
of scenic photos,
and saw
the electronics district.
[YAMADA] Sick.
Most of my class just went
to Ultra Super Jumbo Land.
[NISHI] The photo you sent me
of you guys
in the puppy hats was so funny.
[YAMADA] Yeah, but now
I can't wear it anymore.
Can't recycle the fit.
It's too iconic.
[both laughing]
[NISHI] Just this morning,
I was nervous about meeting
outside of school,
but my anxiety's fading away.
Spending the day with him,
around nobody else
that I know,
it's weirdly comfortable.
It'd be nice
if he felt the same way.
Hey. Come on, let's walk
over to that bridge.
[♪ tender music playing]
Whoa, check it.
This place is so sick,
it makes the view extra pretty.
[NISHI] What do I do?
It's too much.
I think my heart's
going to explode!
CAN'T PAY ATTENTION
TO SCENERY RIGHT NOW
I can't look at his face.
[Yamada shivers]
Man, that's chilly.
The ocean breeze
really hits ya.
[NISHI]
Yamada's still acting normal.
Am I the only one
who feels all giddy inside?
Like my emotions
are going crazy?
[gasps]
Huh?
Over there.
Hmm?
[both gasp]
[both exclaim]
-[YAMADA] Abort!
-[NISHI] Yes, sir!
[YAMADA] So fast! Wait!
Nishi, your bag's open!
-[panting]
-That was close.
Yeesh, I would've preferred
a less chaotic ending,
but that's life.
[Nishi panting]
Sorry, my curfew's so early.
Hey, don't worry. It's cool.
You just focus on breathing.
Oh, yeah.
When we were making our getaway,
you dropped all sorts of stuff.
[Nishi gasps]
[YAMADA] I don't think I've ever
seen you wear these.
Do you usually
carry them around?
Um, not really.
Well, you should put
some of 'em on.
-Huh?
-It'll look cute.
[NISHI] Cute?
[YAMADA] I like this fluffy one.
[NISHI]
Oh, he means the clip is cute.
-[exclaims]
-[YAMADA] Just a sec.
This is tough.
Girls have mad skills.
Oops. Sorry, it looks weird.
[NISHI] Mm.
Then again,
now you can look me
in the eye more.
I noticed you don't do
very much of that.
[NISHI] Unfortunately,
that's not a problem
with my bangs.
It's a problem with me.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Okay, I'll start looking.
Now!
You say that,
but your eyes are still closed.
From now on.
Oh, how 'bout now?
Let's hang out again.
Just us.
Mm.
[both gasp]
[both exclaim]
[YAMADA] Abort!
[tape rewinding]
EXPLANATION
While Yamada and Nishi
were about to get
their snow on the road,
that very same day,
about an hour earlier.
Wow!
This rules!
A blue sky,
the fresh ocean air,
and a popping place
for sightseeing.
Is it just me,
or is this like...
an extra date-y date?
What do I do?
My heart's already
pounding like crazy!
On the class trip, we had
a couple of romantic momos,
but most of the time,
we were busy hanging
with-slash-near
the rest of the crew.
GLOMP.
This is my chance to indulge
and get supes snuggly!
He won't mind, right?
I know I won't!
NO REACTION.
Whatever!
Today, I don't give a flip!
SNUGGLE.
Because today is special.
Hey, that looks delish!
We're a ways away
from where we live.
We're alone.
I'm gonna need
like ten of those.
Pick your poison, Yuusuke.
I gotta enjoy this vacay
from everyday life.
Peak choice!
I think I'm gonna get a...
Wha...
-[gasps]
-[TANI] Great.
Should we go inside, then?
PERFECT VISION
Let's go.
FWIP
-Uh, is--
-Hush!
Don't speak, don't turn around.
No sudden moves,
stay low, stay frosty.
[TANI] Frosty? What?
[Suzuki whispering] Step inside
if you know what's good for you.
[TANI] What's going on?
[Yamada, Nishi
talking indistinctly]
[SUZUKI] Why?!
Why did he have to show up
and burst my lovey-dovey
vacay bubble?
-[TANI] Uh?
- Wait a minute!
Are those two an official item?
Or are they floating
in situationship limbo?
Either way,
if they're on a date,
things must be going
pretty well so far, eh?
Smooth moves, Yamada.
You got this, bud!
I'm gonna explode when they
make the big announcement.
[snickering]
Don't you just love a clear,
sunny day?
[TANI] Yeah.
JUST RECENTLY
GLOMP
Yo! Can you dig it?
Uh, dig it?
'Cause it's underground, get it?
I guess so.
[laughing excitedly]
You know,
date night next to the bay
has a major
grown-up sort of aura,
like we're super mature adults.
[TANI] Admitting it
makes us sound like kids.
It really does, though.
I like to think
I've grown up a little bit.
Yeah, but it's
lowkey embarrassing
when a date is pulled
straight out of a chick flick.
[TANI] Mm.
[chuckles]
[SUZUKI] I wonder
if Yamada and Nish
will make it out here later.
If he whisked her away
to a fancy spot like this,
she'd melt into his arms
and be over the moon.
OMG, they could totally
be on their way now.
Eh, probs not.
[TANI] Beautiful.
Huh?
-The view.
-Oh! Uh, yeah.
If you want, Miyu,
we could go over there
for a little while.
[♪ sparkly music playing]
[SUZUKI] Really?!
Wow! This is peak existence!
Nice skyline.
I've always quietly hoped
I'd get to ride a Ferris wheel
with someone
who's extra special to me.
Quietly?
-Loudly, very loudly.
-[laughs]
-Of course it was.
-[chuckles]
THAT GOT A LAUGH.
When they turn girly
romance novels into movies,
there's always
a cute Ferris wheel scene.
[TANI]
Are they in the books, too?
[laughs] I wouldn't know.
Just me and the person I love,
riding a Ferris wheel
alone together.
Can I sit over by you?
Huh?
A moment straight
from my bucket list!
STARE.
[TANI] They are staring
right at us.
[SUZUKI] They really oughta
tint these windows.
Selfie time!
[camera clicks]
Ahh, what a fun-filled day!
TBH, I wish
things got a bit mushier,
but I didn't wanna
alert the PDA police.
All the cool lights
got me so hyped!
Christmas came early for us!
[TANI] It really did.
Speaking of Christmas,
the best thing about it
is all the cozy, festive vibes
leading up
to the actual holiday!
The most wonderful time
of the year!
♪ Jingle bells, jingle bells ♪
[humming]
For this Christmas,
do you have any plans
in mind yet?
Wha?!
Uh, mm, mm...
I'm not sure.
I would be fine with anything
if it's with you.
What about you, Yuusuke?
Same here.
[SUZUKI] It's so quiet.
'Bout time.
We finally got
a little bit of privacy.
[car approaching]
[both gasp]
WHOOM
STOPPED.
[SUZUKI] Ugh, stupid car!
Of course.
[SUZUKI'S DAD]
Oh, look who it is!
Hi, Miyu!
Hi, Yuusuke!
[SUZUKI] Dad?!
No, we were so close!
[SUZUKI'S MOM] When you said
you wouldn't need dinner,
Dad and I took advantage
and went on a little date
of our own.
Hey, Yuusuke.
Your house
is just over here, right?
Yes, sir.
Thank you for the ride.
THUMP
[both groaning nervously]
Wow, you two rode
the Ferris wheel?
The view was absolutely gorge!
A high-speed,
unhinged Ferris wheel
would be a totally killer ride!
Spill the tea, Suze.
What happened?
Well, not to brag,
but your girl's
living the rom-com dream
with extra rom.
[HONDA] Aww,
that pin looks cute on you.
[gasps] Yeah?
Thank you, Hon.
So...
Did you and Yamada
have a good time?
[whimpers]
What? You went to Chinatown?
-That's rad.
-Yeah.
Convenience store steamies
can't compare.
[TANI] Huh. Yamada went
to Chinatown, too.
[TAIRA] Who did he go with?
No, stay nonchalant.
Don't engage.
[SUZUKI] Ooh!
It's already starting
to get dark out so early,
[chuckles]
You've got ice cube fingies.
Yours are hot.
How are you so warm, Miyu?
[gasps]
-Yuusuke, Yuusuke, lookie here!
-Hmm?
[SUZUKI] They added the "warm
and cozy" winter drinks
to the vending machine.
COCOA WITH CREAM - CORN POTAGE
CONSOMME SOUP - BEEF FLAVOR
Huzzah!
When the vending machines say
the seasons are changing,
then it's real.
You look forward
to this every year?
-Oh, you can snow bank on it.
-[laughs]
You gotta shake 'em vigorously
like a chemistry project
for your mouth
you don't wanna fail!
Looks intense.
[SUZUKI] Just like I cherish
the changing of the seasons,
I wanna cherish the little
changes between us, too.
Could you, uh, stick to "Miyu"?
I like it when you're
more casual with me.
[TANI] Hmm?
-[Suzuki giggles]
SO IT DIDN'T SEEM CASUAL
AFTER ALL.
[TANI] So, you like Miyu better?
[SUZUKI] Uh-huh.
When I hear Miyu,
it means Yuusuke's
all cute and embarrassed.
Mm.
That's a messed-up reason.
[laughs]
Miyu.
[Suzuki giggling] Hey, he's not
as embarrassed as before.
Little by little,
things are changing.
SQUIGGLE
[laughs]
[laughing]
[SUZUKI] I'm doing it.
I'm bringing the poles together.
Wait, you're what?
HEH HEH.
[♪ closing theme song playing]