[Team Leader Baek Su Jeong]
[Moon Ga Young]
[Director Ban Ju Yeon]
[Choi Hyeon Wook]
[Yongseong's successor. The new chaebol director?]
[Im Se Mi]
[Kwak Shi Yang]
[My Dearest Enemy]
[This series is fictional.]
[Characters and settings are fictional.]
[The child actors were filmed in a safe environment.]
I've never met you before.
You know me, right?
No? You're my chaebol'sun?
Yes, I am a chaebol.
If you're lonely, would you like to hang out with me?
Then I am also a customer of your company.
Why are you being so friendly with me?
As a chaebol, shouldn't you be polite to your customers?
This bitch is funny.
I knew you weren't one of us the first time I saw you.
So you were a customer, huh?
Okay.
I will treat you like a queen.
In bed.
Let go. I said let go!
I liked your rebellious spirit.
I know people like you well.
Stop being coy. Come here.
What's going on?
Did he really kick her?
How embarrassing.
Have you lost your mind?
What's wrong with them?
Anyway.
Baby, let's go.
What's going on?
What?
Sir?
What did you say?
Am I a baby?
I wasn't talking to you.
It was something like, "Let's go, baby."
"Let's go into the water, baby." Something like that.
It is known for being sensitive to heat.
How do you feel? Do you feel cooler now?
Are you mad?
Who is this slut?
Who does he think he is to do this to me?
I am an employee.
Actually, he's a very important employee at the company.
Let's go, Team Leader Baek.
It's going to rain soon.
It's raining heavily. [Chapter 3]
How did you know it was going to rain?
It was said.
By whom?
He tells me the weather forecast every morning.
A handy little thing.
Sometimes they're better than humans.
Did you meet with the important client?
I don't think they're here.
If I had known there was going to be a party, I wouldn't have come.
I'm free to go home now, aren't I?
Not yet.
Hey, are you kidding me?
You may have offered job security.
But you don't respect my fundamental rights.
If you're not going to abandon me, at least feed me.
I haven't even had lunch.
I'm hungry!
I have no energy left.
You look full of energy.
See? I told you.
Why are you being so friendly with me...?
What?
[Egg Drop]
Does this count as a meal?
Why not? It has all the major food groups.
Didn't you like what I ordered?
Are you asking after I've ordered what I want?
You're the one following me.
Don't eat it if you don't want to.
I have to eat it because you ordered it.
Since we're among the people, there are no chocolate drinks.
You only drink espresso.
I'm very thirsty.
What will you do next?
It's too late now. How will you keep track of me?
Are you going to stay awake?
Or will you sleep with me?
I signed the contract.
Even if I wanted to, I couldn't reveal his private life.
If you sue me, I won't be able to pay you.
I have nothing but debt.
Why would I want to be fired from the highest-paying company?
Hooray!
It's so cute. Do you like it?
What a shame.
They are handing out plush toys.
It's a favorite, isn't it? [Pirate King Special]
Why would you want a plush toy?
Sweet and free.
Sweet? That thing?
Yes. Right?
Go home.
- Excuse me? - I said, finish this and go home.
You can't get it back.
I'll have this packaged.
Baek Su Jeong's danger level has been lowered.
He has better taste than I thought.
How much is this already?
I can sell it for at least three million.
I still have to return it.
Why isn't this working? Oh no.
What difference does it make if it's expensive?
It's not mine and it's not coming out.
It worked!
Oh my God, seriously.
I'm already tired enough.
What? Did the light go out?
Yes.
We should have waited for me.
I could have handled it.
I can easily do this on my own.
At work.
Wow, you can take over now.
That's why I learned it, in the first place.
I also obtained an electrician's license.
You know I work on this every day after work, right?
I say this because you're my daughter, but... you're proud of me, aren't you?
It's child's play.
It's a bit too empty for a bar, isn't it?
It should be crowded and noisy.
I like it when it's quiet.
I promoted it on Instagram, but it didn't work.
But it worked.
I'm here now.
I even liked your post.
Did you come after seeing my posts?
You have a fun and clear concept.
By chance, did you write the descriptions yourself?
I can't imagine you writing them.
I wrote it myself.
I used to be interested in online novels.
I understand.
If you allow me, the photos could have been better.
The food needs to look delicious.
Doesn't this look more impressive?
Get a loan...
Composition is important in photographs.
You either emphasize the entire opening or you do a close-up.
Really?
You can't show anything else alongside it.
Like this.
- Like this? - Do something like this.
I am sorry.
Do you want to sleep with me?
Shall we do it?
[Grace]
[Purchasing and Shipping Service in China - TAPL]
[RGB leisure]
[Added to cart]
I'm alive now.
What time is it now?
It's only 5:00. Go back to sleep.
Where are you going at 5:00 in the morning?
To go fishing.
Thank you.
You didn't have to bring me here.
I have some time before I go to work. Can I watch you?
I've never been here before.
I'm going to my family's shop. Can you handle it?
Why couldn't I handle it? Old people like me.
This is worse.
They want me to remarry any man.
- Are you divorced? - Why?
Does this excite you even more?
I think I should stop.
I need to go to work.
Go on then.
I had fun last night thanks to you.
See you later.
Anne!
How long did it take you to get here?
Huh? I'm not late. I arrived right on time.
That's too late.
Buying the goods at their original prices...
...if you want, you need to come early and help us.
Have you ever seen a thief with a conscience?
Seriously. Don't be so proud.
Okay, how's your shop?
Ha Jeong says she doesn't have any customers.
If it fails, there's nothing you can do.
Really.
I told you to save up the child support money and find a job.
Why did you start a business?
You quit your job to get married, but you got divorced within a year.
You're about to close the shop within a year.
Why can't you commit to anything?
Why are you such a nuisance?
I dated a guy for 10 years and then I married him. Have you forgotten?
Dad, what are the good deals today?
Coral.
Coral. Okay.
Director.
The dress from last night is here.
Did you give it to the dry cleaner?
I don't think you have time.
I only wore it for a moment last night.
The clothes you're wearing need to be cleaned.
Isn't this a rule?
It rained last night too.
I didn't even want to wear it.
I thought this was just common sense, but my expectations were way too high.
The staff needs etiquette training.
Someone was speaking loudly in the elevator too.
Are you saying I'm that ill-mannered?
It could be your voice.
Okay, I'll do it.
You need to pay him back.
What was that little head shake?
I told you. This isn't my style.
It doesn't suit me, does it?
Didn't it suit her?
Is this etiquette training?
He should learn manners first.
He always acts the way he wants...
You weren't talking about me, were you?
You're too sensitive.
Me. I was talking about myself.
I act too much the way I want to.
Objectifying oneself.
At least you're good at this.
Let's begin the meeting.
You must understand the importance of the renovation project.
It will start in Seoul and spread nationwide.
The beginning will be the most important thing.
That's why we chose the Gangnam store.
[Renovation Candidate No. 1, Gangnam Store]
Is it the Admiral store or the Gangnam store?
Gangnam is the center of commerce.
But our store's sales were lower than the others.
We need a refresh right now.
Failure would be very risky.
If we succeed, the reward will be great.
Once we open the way, sales are guaranteed.
The next candidate is a safer option.
No problem. I was thinking of the Gangnam store too.
We all agree. Why waste time?
Let's go to the Gangnam store.
Okay.
Where are you going?
To the Gangnam store. That's the selected store.
I need to assess the region properly.
- Um... - What?
They didn't plan this together beforehand, did they?
I know. They completely agreed.
[Grace]
Do you want to sleep with me?
Shall we do it?
Damn it.
I am good.
You've probably heard about the renovation project.
Yes, I heard that our store might be the first.
It will start today.
Ah, I understand.
Let's work hard, Branch Manager.
Yes, of course.
We will research customers and measure demand.
Will this be enough?
Sir?
The main goal of the renovation is to acquire new customers.
Conduct a survey beyond existing customers.
The brands, products, services, and facilities they want.
How can we ask about non-customers?
Make them willing to participate.
Spend money or overindulge.
There's no need to be conservative.
Understood. We'll start immediately.
Okay. You can go.
Excuse me? Is that all?
If I were with you, they would realize that a high-ranking official was here.
I want to evaluate the store as it is.
Alright then. Feel free to explore.
We will stay in touch.
This...
You recognized it. That's the brand I use.
I only use their products.
The lead singer of my favorite band is like that too.
Ah, I understand.
I noticed the slanted letter on the sign.
You're observant.
But you didn't notice the brand of my sunglasses.
I will inform the employee.
These sunglasses cost one million won.
But how can the repair cost 800,000?
Feet and screws...
It was designed by a craftsman.
The repair needs to be done at the center in Italy and then sent back to you.
Still. You're not doing it again.
800,000 won is no joke.
They basically need to be rebuilt.
Who are you?
If you don't understand their value, you have no right to wear them.
Who are you? Why are you deciding whether I have a right or not?
What is it?
Someone who understands the value of the product.
Whatever. Whatever. I don't care.
If you came here to shop, buy yourself a pair and leave.
You're getting on my nerves.
Trying to annoy you? Are you serious...? Excuse me.
How are things?
It looked better on you than it used to.
Are you telling me to buy a new pair now?
Are you trying to annoy me even more?
It doesn't deserve any of this... You have to wait a long time for repairs.
If it's going to cost the same price, shouldn't you buy a pair that suits you better?
I work at Yongseong.
I can give you a discount.
Then they would be worth 650,000 won.
Say what?
Try it briefly.
Just hold it over your face.
Let me show you the mirror.
Let me see.
Great.
I think I'll buy a new pair.
- Would you like to? - Of course.
Give her a new pair.
Wow, that's great.
It wasn't that he didn't understand its value.
He couldn't afford the fee.
Still, we shouldn't have paid that much attention to him.
That was too much, even for you.
I know.
I was about to make an unforgivable mistake.
It might have been one of the few mistakes I've made in my life.
But you stopped me.
Thank you, but this is a bit...
I've never seen his naked face.
I didn't recognize him.
Sir?
Kim?
The singer at the concert? Is that right?
Great. You should have said something.
You're a fan.
True, it was a secret.
Are you just going to leave him like that?
Shall I get your autograph?
No problem.
Just wait.
Ben...
A pen. I don't have a pen.
Al.
Excuse me!
Excuse me.
One second.
I watched your show once.
I'm a huge fan of yours.
Can I get an autograph?
Certainly.
I didn't recognize you.
You're so cool.
Thank you.
Photograph?
One second.
I told the director that I admired him, and he offered to take a photo with me.
A photo?
It would be nice if you could be inside, but you can't tell anyone.
I'll take one for you. Be satisfied with me.
I'll take the picture now.
One two three.
What's this?
Only my hair is visible.
Because I'm not a fan.
Message me the photo.
Maybe I won't throw it away.
I got your autograph and a photo.
But you treated me like this.
I know.
I got an autograph and a photo.
You don't need to thank me.
I admire him for a reason.
Not only is he a great singer, but he's also a wonderful person.
Do you love him that much?
Are you kidding me?
I'm jealous.
To feel passionate about something.
I think it's something valuable.
Finding what you love is hard.
It's hard to love something for a long time.
For that reason...
Enjoy it as much as you want.
No matter what others think, enjoy your hobby...
...I don't think receiving it makes you a bad heir.
The heir chooses the president, not you.
Do you think I don't know this?
Is this how you answer...?
Anyway.
Be careful. You'll get wet.
Get a loan!
Rainbow.
I hadn't seen him in a while.
Beautiful.
I'm enjoying it...
That's enough already.
Or...
I'll try to enjoy myself more freely...
At least in front of you.
He's not bad at his job.
That is, Bayan Baek Su Jeong.
You said it wasn't important...
And that it must be destroyed.
Not anymore. It doesn't look bad anymore.
You said it was a talent I would appreciate.
Isn't it?
I knew I understood your type.
He's not bad at his job.
- Who? - Director Ban Ju Yeon.
He makes decisions quickly, is highly motivated, and has a good intuition.
I think you called him a rebel this morning.
I think we have two directors now.
I thought you didn't like him, Team Leader.
I thought so too.
There's nothing to like or dislike.
He/She just needs to be good at his/her job.
[Curved]
It makes you wake up immediately.
This is best when working late hours.
Do you work late?
Well, yes.
After working in the field, I had work to do.
I wanted to finish it before I left.
If I work late due to a sudden schedule change, how will that show me?
Don't work late and leave without a reason.
Well...
Who would tell someone to quit their job so rudely?
Besides, it was too late to take the dress to the dry cleaner.
You should keep it safe.
Excuse me? Why?
I don't need it...
And it was beautiful.
A dress. I mean, a dress.
So, the dress.
Peace.
Comic.
You're coming to my sanctuary.
- Who is this? - Bbanjju! Sweetheart!
My face blushes when I see you.
He doesn't really resemble her.
Please thank your mother for me.
What are you smiling at? How annoying.
What is it?
Did I smile?
How stupid do you have to be not to notice?
I've never experienced this before.
Hey, do you think fate is a real thing?
We were made for each other.
My destiny.
Your existence.
His very existence disgusts me.
Stay sealed forever, you little cow!
You're in a dangerous situation. Be careful.
Falling dangerously in love with someone will cause you unbearable pain.
You just...
You were thinking about your first love, weren't you?
I will relieve you of your pain now.
Hey, tough!
Is it nice?
I would never wear it, and it doesn't even suit me.
I'm busy because I opened a shop.
What kind of shop?
[What kind of shop?]
[Shipping notification]
[Hello, Black Dragon. Your order has just been shipped.]
Finally.
As you instructed, I cleaned everything except the study.
Okay, thank you. You can go.
That point should be good.
Okay. A new friend...
Shall we get ready to welcome them?
I'm jealous.
To feel passionate about something.
I think it's something valuable.
Finding what you love is hard.
It's hard to love something for a long time.
So, enjoy it as much as you want.
[Very delicious, Sulo]
[Grace]
Please sign here to confirm delivery.
Who sent all this?
Black... Dragon?
Ah, I understand.
Okay.
- Go ahead. - Okay.
Thanks.
Have a nice day.
- Thank you. - Of course.
Older sister.
What were those flowers in the front?
Oh my, what is this?
Why is it so cold here?
What is this now?
What did he bring here without telling anyone?
I won't tell you anything.
I asked you what it was.
I bought it as an opening gift.
Who would send you a gift like this?
He looks like he came from a chaebol.
I know.
Sit down for now.
Let's turn off the air conditioner, sister.
The air conditioner won't prevent it from melting.
Should I do it?
So, who is this?
- A friend of mine. - Which friend?
Do you have a friend I don't know about?
That scared me!
Who sent you a service robot when you didn't have any customers?
[Congratulations on your opening, Sister]
'Older sister'?
From a man?
[Wishing you endless success - Black Dragon]
'Black Dragon'?
I'm not going to throw away the trash and come back.
Black Dragon?
Sister, were you in contact with him?
From where?
You were angry too, because he had deceived us.
I was angry, but...
You know. He's a good player.
I swear we...
We only spoke briefly during team fights.
I understand.
Now I understand.
I'm leaving. We need to keep our distance for a while.
Strawberry. Su Jeong.
Should I throw them all away?
I'll throw them all away.
[Excessive drinking can cause the owner to smile.]
Nevermind.
Isn't it?
Gifts. I shouldn't throw them away, should I?
Altars Market village.
I can't stand them, but it's a waste.
Okay.
[Yongsung]
You arrived early.
You arrived early, Director.
I'm just hardworking.
Did you check today's weather forecast?
Yes.
It will be open today. The level of fine dust is low.
UV level: medium. Humidity level: 46%.
The wind speed is 2 meters per second.
I understand. It seems really useful.
Yes like that.
But the letters are very small. Can you read them?
I can read.
Can you read?
Meanwhile,
How long are you going to do this?
Sir?
Director, are you alright?
Well, I'm sorry...
I didn't want to do that.
A-Are you alright?
He has a strange watch.
My stress levels are high.
Me too.
Should I report what you requested last week?
Let's listen right away.
What's this?
Huh? This...
The capsule looks like a toy.
My son's favorite character.
Does anyone in the office have children?
No. Whose is this?
I forgot something in the car.
Okay.
It can't be mine.
Impossible.
You're late.
Where have you been, looking like this?
B-Grandmother.
Who is your grandmother?
I don't have a grandchild like you.
Do you want to take my son's place?
You're not just embarrassing.
Am I lost again now?
That's not true.
[Pirate King]
My son...
He was killed because of you.
My only son...
He died that day because of that stupid thing.
I am sad.
It's all my fault, Grandma.
Forgive me. Forgive me.
I said...
I don't have a grandchild like you.
I knew he had been unreliable lately.
But again, this thing...
All this trash.
Get it out of my sight immediately!
I'm sorry, Grandma.
Please don't. N-No...
I am sad.
Grandmother.
It's my fault.
I'll never do that again, Grandma.
Grandmother!
Just forgive me this once.
Grandmother.
M-Grandma! Not her, Grandma.
Grandma, please. Grandma.
Just forgive me this once, Grandma.
Don't do that, Grandma.
Grandma! Grandma!
Don't throw it away, Grandma.
Grandmother...
I am sad.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
According to Chef Kwon, this is really expensive.
It's something rare.
Who brought this child's stuff to work?
Be honest. It's you, isn't it, Na Na?
What is it?
You are the youngest among us.
It's not mine.
Is that you, Assistant?
Are you mad?
It's noticeable that a man likes such things.
- Really? - Of course.
One of my classmates is collecting these things.
A grown man. Seriously...
I really don't understand.
Do you understand, Na Na?
Well, I don't understand, but—I know. It's definitely not me.
Ok then.
However, we must return it to its owner.
How ignorant and narrow-minded.
Should we put it on the company bulletin board?
Yes, it will work.
That's been taken care of too.
How much progress have you made with the report?
Oh, let me bring mine.
Ah, that's right.
The file you mentioned last time...
One second.
Oh no?
I just found it.
I asked around, but no one claimed it.
I'll carry it with me until I find its owner.
Why don't you ask me?
It can be mine.
Are you interested in such things?
I'm not interested in such things.
Bayan Baek Su Jeong,
That dress. Give it back to me.
You told me to hide it.
Are you changing your mind now?
Why not?
You do it too.
Thinking about it, I'm not a philanthropist.
No, there's no need to hand them out.
I never wanted that. What does donation mean?
Do I look like I'm begging you for it?
What gives you the right to do that?
Since you never wanted it, give it back.
You said you had a lot of debt.
Did you sell it because it was valuable?
So I really did help you then.
I'm the one who helped you.
Your private life that you want to hide.
I'm pretending I don't know.
Everyone needs to know each other's secrets, right?
Are you mad?
Not yet.
I'll bring the dress on Monday.
[High C]
Okay. See you tomorrow.
[New High-C dress for sale urgently - Sold]
Hi. I'm sorry, but there's a small issue.
Can I get the dress back?
I will pay you in full.
It's fine if you've worn it once.
The deal is complete.
I don't like being contacted in this way.
[You have been blocked]
Do I have to spend millions to satisfy his whims?
Should I expose him and sink with him?
No, calm down.
People learning doesn't change anything.
I will be sued for breach of contract.
[Director Ban Ju Yeon]
So, enjoy it as much as you want.
What was I expecting?
[Dear Black Dragon, your order has been processed.]
Yes.
All people are the same.
Let's not worry.
I knew they trusted me, Ban Ju Yeon.
Yes. That's all.
That's enough.
In the section below, one...
inside one.
This is the key to the problem.
So, for example...
I have no idea.
Was I really such a useless person?
This is not good.
Experience and skills.
I'll call in a reliable expert.
Someone who doesn't know this is my place.
From a further distance, [Hardware store]
but within the service area.
Too many reviews are also bad.
Because they're probably fakes.
[No. 1 Hardware]
Baba.
Hey.
Hello?
Is this No. 1 Hardware Store?
Yes, this is it.
I'm looking for a faulty electrical outlet.
I'm in Yeonghae-dong. Can you come now?
Yeonghae-dong?
It's a bit far from here.
Oh dear, can't you come?
N-Never mind. I can come.
Very far.
I'll be there. It's a short bike ride away.
Instead, we'll give you five times as much...
I will pay your normal rate.
Can you come now?
Now?
I have appointments in the neighborhood... We can do it.
I'm going.
A-Who was that just now?
Well, my daughter.
Shall we leave now?
I'll give you the address.
No, I'll give you our phone number.
Send the address as a message.
Okay.
It was perfect.
You're already busy. Take a break.
Why are you doing this?
He said he would pay five times the tariff.
I'll drive there right away.
Really.
You should have rested at home.
Why did you come here?
I wanted to have dinner with you, like we used to.
I am sad.
Then let's get something really delicious for dinner.
And be careful, even in small tasks. Be cautious.
Don't help people with random things.
Just focus on the job, okay?
Okay.
Is this Yongsung Palace?
Wow, chaebols really do live differently.
I'm just informing you that you will be recorded on CCTV.
Activities unrelated to repairs, especially...
...taking photographs or filming is prohibited.
Look at the picture to find the faulty socket.
Why is it so strict?
Wow, this is amazing.
Here it is.
I'm here now. I'm going to go inside.
A woman?
- Hello? - What is this...?
What is this?
The person on the phone was a man.
I am the owner's daughter.
Don't worry. I'm just as good as the owner.
So, when you press the button next to the painting, the room will appear, right?
Meanwhile, your voice sounds familiar.
Shall I get your autograph?
Director Ban Ju Yeon?
[My Dearest Enemy]
[Thanks to Crack Shot for the special look by Vincent]
You've decorated the room beautifully.
Go. I only work with top-level experts.
It doesn't match the image you've created.
A hospital?
I would be surprised if I were alone.
How do you lift your spirits?
Director? Are you flirting?
He didn't look like that kind of person.
How unexpected.
Black Dragon.
Our relationship may have reached a point of no return.
Fate plays tricks on us. It's like magic.