(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
Whoa!
What's going on?
Hey...
Look.
You were such a cute kid.
Are these...your parents?
Mm.
Why haven't you told me about your family?
It was a long time ago.
Just help me pack.
Though...
You looked so happy as a child, didn't you?
Your smile,
your parents' smiles,
and the birthday cake.
The happiness in their eyes truly doesn't lie.
Ugh!
What kind of girlfriend am I?
What now?
I don't even know your birthday.
Ugh! It's not a big deal at all.
So when were you born?
I'm not telling you.
What?
It's just a birthday, so why aren't you telling me?
It's just another day.
Plus, I haven't had a birthday party for so many years now.
It's nothing important.
Now, please help me pack.
You...
On this slideshow,
you'll see the names of the shareholders
the number of shares from last year,
and the adjustment of the shareholding ratios.
May I ask you a question?
The anonymous shareholder,
who are they?
Right now, they are the ones with the most shares at hand.
Their decisions will affect W Empire's management direction.
That's why I'm curious.
No need to worry.
This shareholder
won't interfere with management.
The authority in decision-making
is still mine.
Understood.
If the decisions are yours,
I'm relieved.
From now on,
Ms. Arisa is officially part of our organization.
W Empire and Alist
are now family.
As the CEO,
I would like everyone to welcome her with a round of applause.
Why don't you ask my boss yourself, Ms. Lalin?
It's just a small question.
You don't have to ask me.
Well, that boss of yours keeps dancing around it.
When is she ever going to tell me?
Ooh...
If she refuses to tell you,
I wouldn't dare answer.
So...
why do you need her birthday, Ms. Lalin?
Is it for fortune-telling?
She's not superstitious, though.
It's not!
I just wanna plan a surprise for her.
I happened to see the photos of her younger self blowing candles with her parents.
She seemed so happy.
I want her to be able to experience it again. It's gonna be really nice.
Excuse me.
I wouldn't dare tell you since she's gonna tell me off.
Besides...
she doesn't like surprises.
Is she gatekeeping her birthdate as some kind of lucky number?
Please, Ms. Aiy. Please?
I just wanna be a good partner.
Don't you feel bad that she'd have to spend her birthday alone?
Please?
Please help me out.
I just wanna be a good partner.
Would you please help me?
Please help me!
Even though I'm single,
I'd like to cherish these kinds of moments for once.
And even though she's gonna tell me off,
I'll help you, Ms. Lalin.
You will?
Thank you, Ms. Aiy. Thank you.
Here.
Cheers.
Good luck.
Good luck to me, too.
I've brought you your favorite white flowers.
My birthday arrives in two weeks.
I wish you and Dad were here to wish me a happy birthday.
No matter how tired I may be,
I will bring back our family's dignity.
I don't know if another life exists,
but if it does...
I'd like to meet you guys again.
But if not,
please appear in my dreams once in a while.
I promise
that I will make sure to put those who tore us apart
in the deepest agony,
just the same way they did to me.
What is it?
It's the person we're looking for.
The anonymous shareholder.
Her name is Ruwajee,
the older sister of Thana, Weiling's husband,
who was also Lalin's father.
She received the shares from a transfer her brother made in his will,
and ever since he passed away,
she distanced herself from W Empire
to live a life on her own
with no husband or family,
and barely any contact with Weiling.
Partly because
she has a gambling problem.
Miss,
care for some cookies?
Here you go.
Wow, that looks appetizing.
I was just craving desserts.
Please get up.
Huh?
Please.
Now, please sit.
What's going on?
It just happened...
that we offer a delivery service
straight to your lips.
Since when did you become such a teaser?
Are you interested in our service?
So where is it?
Is it good?
It is.
Dear customer,
you got it on your lips.
All clean.
Jeez, you...
If I can have something as delicious as this every day,
I don't think I'd ever have to go out.
You know,
the pros of us working together are that
you can charge your battery with me whenever you want
and however much you want.
Then I'll charge it to the brim.
Ow! Dear...
Refreshing!
Enough, enough, enough, enough, enough.
- You... - That's full battery for me.
What do you think?
How do you find my service?
I like it.
This is tasty.
- Right, dear. - Hm?
Another one of the shareholders
who remains anonymous,
who...are they?
Mm,
it's Auntie Ruwajee.
And who is she?
She is my father's older sister,
but she and Mom never really got along,
so she gave Mom the company's management authority.
Speaking of which, I kinda miss her.
It's been a while since I've seen her.
How about this?
I'll take you to see her to fix that. How does that sound?
Nice!
I think that
Auntie's gonna like you,
just like how everyone does.
Ooh! That's gratifying.
Let me hug and kiss you until I'm satisfied.
It's been years.
You've grown into such a beautiful woman.
I miss you, too, Auntie.
I see that you still enjoy flower arranging.
t's what I do to cure my loneliness.
I'm all by myself, not with a partner like you are.
So, you two,
have you been together for long? Fill me in.
It's been some time, Auntie.
It was after Mom took me in.
I heard that you were also in real estate?
That's correct.
Lalin said in a phone call that Weiling isn't particularly fond of you.
Right.
I guess I'll have to try more
and approach her with sincerity
to prove that I truly love her daughter.
She wants genuineness, huh?
Was she ever genuine toward my little brother?
What do you mean, Auntie?
Ugh, pay it no mind. It's all in the past.
I don't want anything to do with her.
She's done something in the past,
and now, her daughter's paying for it.
She's anxious about everything
when she should be giving you freedom.
Don't give in to her, Arisa.
You're the only hope
for my niece's happiness
and freedom from her mother.
I can tell
who Lalin gets her assertiveness from.
Stay for a meal with me.
Sure.
Auntie seems to like you.
Approaching the elders
is my strong suit.
Except for my mom.
Dear...
Here you go. I'm just kidding.
Here's to you.
Thank you.
My judgment was right.
I knew this woman couldn't be trusted.
But what does she need?
How should we get this sorted, ma'am?
Should we inform Ms. Lalin?
Not yet.
Lalin is absolutely obsessed with her.
She wouldn't believe us if we told her.
We need to figure out what her plan is.
Don't let that woman find out.
I would never let her have the last laugh.
That's it. I fold.
Oh?
What about you?
I'm going all in.
Then, I fold.
Let me see your cards.
Goodness, I just got tricked by this girl!
I didn't trick you.
I just got a read on you.
Sometimes when you play cards,
you need to know your rivals
and what direction they might take
so that you can turn the tables in time.
I'm starting to like you!
Look, seeing as how your girlfriend's this good at cards
you need to come visit often.
Of course, I'll bring her to visit often.
But let's do it just for fun, alright?
No gambling.
Oh!
This is all for fun. It's nothing serious.
It's an old lady's hobby.
Let's hope that was true.
Then, please excuse me while I use the restroom.
Hurry back.
Lalin doesn't really like it when I gamble.
She knows I'm generous
and not one to back down.
I could go all in just to win.
Truthfully, it's not all that bad.
I know my own limits.
But I do understand that.
Sometimes, betting
makes the games much more interesting.
There, you get me.
Though,
I know Lalin is just worried about me.
She's concerned that I would fall apart because of this.
She's such a gentle soul.
She never means anyone harm.
She deserves to be loved by a nice person.
You can be that person, right, Arisa?
Please don't worry.
Meeting Lalin
is the best thing that's ever happened to me.
Don't worry about Weiling.
Just tell me if something happens.
For my niece's happiness,
I will handle it for you.
Cheers.
Thank you.
How do you feel? Has that longing gone away?
It is, but I do wanna see her again.
She seems to like you.
I'll take you to visit her again.
Where have you been?
You're home late.
I took Arisa to see Auntie Ruwajee.
Ruwajee?
What for?
Well, I miss her,
so Arisa took me to visit her.
I also wanted to introduce them to each other.
How is this any of your business?
Mom!
Be nice to her.
It's just a visit. I don't see what's strange about it.
It's fine, dear.
I just took her to visit her beloved relatives whom she respects, that's all.
It's nice to visit senior relatives,
but I hope that's all there is to it.
- Dear. - Hm?
About Auntie Ruwajee,
hasn't she been married?
No.
My dad used to tell me
that she was in a relationship,
and they met in Las Vegas.
I suppose you can guess what kind of person they were.
The family didn't accept it,
and after that, I've never seen her with anyone again.
She's been alone half her life.
That must have been so lonely.
It sure is.
With how she lives alone,
it must be really hard to do things.
I don't even wanna imagine if I could make it on my own.
Why do you even have to imagine that?
You already have me!
What's there to imagine?
Then, promise me that we'll grow old together
to apply my skincare like this every day.
I promise.
I'm not even done applying your skincare.
Let me do it for you.
- Hello, ma'am. - Oh?
Lalin is not with you?
No.
She has a meeting to attend,
but I'm available today.
I recall a game you used to like, and wanted to play it with you.
What do you mean?
It's a game of chance.
But this is not something Lalin is good at.
I think I'd better have you join me.
Will it be okay?
- If Lalin finds this out... - Don't worry about it.
This will be kept between...two of us.
This...
is my lucky spot.
I used to come here pretty often.
But now...
I don't have much money to keep it up.
Shall we try?
Go ahead.
Please place your bets.
Time's up.
Banker wins.
See?
I told you it's my lucky spot!
I believed you.
Player.
Oh!
Wow!
- Oh! -Whoa!
Cheers!
Let's do it.
- You're thrilled. - Yes, I am.
Banker.
It's okay, kid.
Learn from it.
- One more time. - Let's do it one more time.
Wow!
See?
Place your bets.
I'll bet a large amount this round.
No more bets.
Player wins.
It's totally fine.
My luck will come in the next round.
Damn it!
Wait...I...
Here you go.
I'm afraid I can't repay you...
It's alright.
Let's say, I'm here to have fun with you.
Win or lose, it doesn't matter to me.
No one is unfortunate their entire life.
You're right about that.
Then...
I'll take it.
Alright.
I've been with my boss for years,
but I have no idea she likes strawberry cake!
Actually, she doesn't like any sweets.
Really?
Your boss...
seems easy to open up, but not actually.
I see one door,
then I see the second and third doors.
Like I really know her, but I don't.
So mysterious.
She is not that mysterious.
You see, she looks tough, but is so soft inside.
Since she met you, she's even softer now!
It surprised me to see that side of her.
Are you serious?
What do you think?
Will it look good?
The beauty of it doesn't matter,
what matters is the dedication.
- My boss will definitely love it. - I hope so.
But I think...
a cake isn't enough,
you might need to impress her more with something more special.
A special venue.
A special item, or something that can't be found elsewhere.
I think I've figured it out!
It's gonna be a special night at the place where we first met!
Thank you, Aiy.
A romantic person like you should find someone!
Help me find one then, Miss Lalin.
Alright. Like this?
What are you up to, dear?
How...long have you been in here?
Why didn't I hear your car engine or anything?
I just arrived.
I heard something in the kitchen, so I walked in.
So...what were you doing?
Umm, well...
I'm hungry.
I'm here to find something to eat.
- Are you? - Umm, yes.
What's on your cheek?
What a mess.
I wanna eat some pancakes,
so I was practicing to make one.
You can simply let the maids do it for you.
Well, I don't want to bother them.
You're acting weird, though.
Why did you keep looking away?
What's the matter?
I didn't!
No, I am staring at you now!
You're the problem!
You've been away the whole day,
working and working.
Where do I stand as your girlfriend?
What are you mad about?
I was just asking.
- So what can I help you with? - No!
Nothing!
Hey, I've not hugged you or anything yet.
- Just a hug. - Keep that for later. I'm hungry now!
No hug, straight to the shower!
Go! Go!!
- You're good? - Sure!
For the Cornerstone, the architect's approved in the first round.
And the Singapore team just sent us the adjustment drafts yesterday.
If there's nothing to change,
we can proceed with the building permission by next month.
Did Petra learn about this?
Yes.
Who's here?
Is that Uncle Mek?
He won't ring a bell.
I'll check on that for you.
Hello.
We want to see Ms. Arisa Kulnavee.
What is your matter, officers?
We have a summons.
I'm Arisa. What can I help you?
Ms. Arisa, please present yourself at the police station.
Ms. Arisa, do you know this person?
Ms. Michelle, you are under arrest.
Hold on...
What the heck is this?
I do know her.
What is your relation with her?
She used to be an investor for my company.
After the financial investigation,
we found many transactions made to your account,
involving hundreds of millions.
And what is that money for?
The invested money is used as the company's cash flow,
in hospitality and real estate businesses.
Do you know that part of Ms. Michelle's money
was from the scammer network?
I have no clue, sir.
Have you never wondered how she had that much money?
Excuse me.
My client
has run her entire business, legally.
The investigation on money source
is the responsibility of the relevant authorities, not my client.
And the way you asked that question
was too leading.
We're now in the process of investigating all her financial trails.
If your transactions
are involved in money laundering or scammer networking,
I'll summon you here for another statement.
I'm fine with that.
Ms. Arisa,
you have known Ms. Michelle was involved with the scammer thing, right?
The invested money's part of the money laundering, isn't it?
Please give us a way.
Wait a minute.
Will your Cornerstone project with Petra proceed?
Is your company involved in the money laundering scam?
Everything is under the investigation.
I will fully cooperate with the officers.
So are you denying this?
Yeah, is this true?
- Please give us a way. - What are you gonna say?
Please! Tell us!
Dear...
I've seen the news.
What happened?
No need to care about it that much.
I have no clue where they learned about this.
They all got the same brief.
Just tell me what happened.
You know what, people are gossiping
that you have this much money because of the scamming business.
I know Michelle, that's true.
But I have no clue she was running an illegal business.
She helped me build this company.
But I never knew...
that all the money
was from a scam scheme.
That's okay.
You didn't know that, you're good.
If you're not involved,
no one can place the blame on you.
Thanks, Lalin.
You got many past stories, though.
Anything else I need to know?
Many more.
Are you sure you can handle me?
Love is about embracing one another's mistakes in the past.
Everyone has a second chance, always.
Oh, are you a life coach by any chance?
I'm doing great, right?
You cheered me up so well.
Wait a sec.
Hello.
Oops! Sorry, I'm gonna be there right now.
I have a meeting to attend.
Are you leaving now?
Yeah, I've been called in. See you later!
What big news.
How did you explain yourself?
Why did I have to do that?
The truth remains.
Besides, I haven't done anything wrong.
I've already told the officers everything.
But it already happened.
Being involved with someone who has done an illegal business
is not a minor issue.
Not only you will be affected,
but also the companies you hold shares in
will be investigated, too.
More importantly,
what about Lalin?
Her reputation might also be ruined by this.
Don't worry too much about that,
I won't let this damage her reputation.
I hope that's true.
Soon,
Lalin will finally see
who the real
Arisa is.
It's true, though.
When it comes to a scammer thing,
people are ready to judge you.
It takes ages for the result to come,
and by that time, the news will have spread widely.
The truth comes too late, no one waits to hear it.
I see.
We tend to believe what we want to believe.
You're right.
But at least, you still got Lalin by your side.
When life's ruined,
having someone by your side is so important.
Lalin is just as great as her dad, Thana.
When I was a teenager,
I went to study in the States.
And I fell in love with a foreign guy.
My family really looked down on him.
Eventually, we couldn't make it.
I was told to fly back to Thailand.
My parents did everything so that I couldn't communicate with him.
But there was only Thana,
who said goodbye on my behalf.
He consoled me and everything.
I felt so lucky to have him as a young brother.
But on the day he passed away for good,
I learned that...
life isn't always that kind to us.
From that day onwards,
I had no one else on my side,
no family or friends,
only me.
Have you talked to Weiling?
She's still your sister-in-law, isn't she?
You still can't tell I hate that bitch?
The whole time she was dating my brother,
I knew she was secretly dating someone else.
Acting like a perfect queen.
Scolding me, saying I was a compulsive gambler.
She was no better than me.
Did Mr. Thana know about this?
Just like you said,
we all wanted to believe in what we felt like.
Don't tell Lalin about this.
Let this die with someone old like me.
OK.
Hey...
Is the shop closed?
No, you can come!
♫Happy birthday to you♫
♫Happy birthday to you!♫
♫Happy birthday, happy birthday♫
♫Happy birthday to you♫
Make a wish.
What did you wish?
I wished...
us...
Better not say it.
I'm afraid it won't come true.
I don't think I need to guess
how you found out when my birthday was.
Only Aiy knew about this.
Don't blame her,
I just wanted to surprise you.
I told you,
I'm not into birthdays.
And I don't like surprises either.
I don't know what you've been through in the past.
But it's time...
to recreate good memories.
I hope you can leave bad things behind.
If you can't leave some,
share them with me.
I want to laugh and cry with you.
But the surprise isn't just that.
You got more?
Umm! Follow me.
Can I be your new memory?
A memory that will make you smile forever.
Thanks.
Next week, my mom is holding a violence-against-women charity.
Sometimes,
it's the time we have to open our relationship to public.
For Arisa,
I already got something to attack her.
What is it?
Hey, Kee!
Who is that, dear?
Why do you seem close to her?
An old friend of mine.
How did you know that woman?
Tell me about it.
I'll pay you for that.
So Lalin will know what Arisa hides from her.
No matter how severe your past is,
I want you to know you will always have me by your side.