I wanna break up.
I don’t.
Enough.
I’m done.
I’m tired of all this.
During the times I was so down with what you did to me,
Sevi has always been by my side.
What are you doing?
Sorry. I just got curious.
I’ll just come back next time when you’re not busy.
Sorry!
- Sorry, sorry! - No, no…
Those are very important client files.
I’ll do anything to make it up to you. I’m really sorry.
Anything?
Yes, anything.
Do my house in Tagaytay.
Attorney!
Here’s a package for you.
What package?
Who sent that?
There’s no name attached to it actually,
but it’s from Valeria Construction.
That’s cute.
Yes!
Return those to Architect Luna Valeria.
Huh?
Okay, sir.
Thank you.
He is so annoying!
Hey! What happened?
Look at this.
Kalix is so annoying.
Why, what did he do?
I sent him a gift package.
But he gave it back to me. What the heck does that mean?
- Your apology was not accepted. - Huh?
Who does he think he is?
Maybe he just didn’t like what you sent him.
What is this anyway? What’s this? Humi–
Humidifier, Luna?
- Are you an old lady? - Why?
He definitely needs something to help him relax
while he fixes all the documents I ruined.
See? I’m quite thoughtful.
Sure you are. You do seem worried.
You even thought it through.
But you do know the apology Kalix is willing to accept, right?
Since he lost a job because of the documents you ruined,
it just makes sense that he demands to get something job-related in return.
Ke, you know why I didn’t accept the project, right?
I know and I heard the rumor that
Kalix was part of Mi-Miguel’s legal team.
But…
I did my research
And I didn’t really see his name in the list
of the Villaflors’ legal representatives.
I did see Amethyst’s name, though.
What?
Are you serious?
But it’s fine if you don’t want to talk about it.
No, I’m okay. He’s behind bars now.
I can talk about him.
Just make sure to clear it up with Kalix, okay?
We shouldn’t take this project for granted.
You should just stay strictly professional.
Unless there’s some other reason as to why you keep rejecting him.
Don’t be silly!
You’re overthinking.
Seriously, Luna, do you still have feelings for him?
Huh?
No. Of course not. What are you talking about?
It’s been years. No.
Okay. Sure.
Sure. If there’s any other reason, I get it.
We, architects, have certain preferences with the projects we work with.
But you still need to apologize.
Instead of just giving him this nonsense.
Do what’s right.
- Come in. - Welcome.
Are you here to stare at me?
No.
I’m here to give my formal apology.
Can you forgive me now?
I’m really sorry for spilling water over your documents.
I’m willing to pay for all the damages that I’ve cost.
That’s how sorry I am.
I appreciate the written apology and the gifts.
But I had to return it because people might think
that those are bribes from the clients.
I clearly do not want that.
I would rather have you repay me through
your professional service, Architect Valeria.
You already know what I’m talking about.
I already sent you the proposal and the contracts.
I know you already rejected the project, twice.
But maybe this time, you’ll accept it.
Can I ask you a personal question?
Depends on the question.
Did you represent Miguel Villaflor in court?
Who said I did?
Some rumors.
Well, I didn’t.
I value my morals, Luna.
Do you have anything else to say?
I’m busy.
Actually, I do.
May I sit?
I’m interested to talk about the proposal.
This contract is flawless, I can’t find any loopholes.
Duh, your client is a lawyer.
Sorry, I came from the site.
What’s with the meeting?
Sevi,
will you be my engineer for Kalix’s house project in Tagaytay?
Wait a minute,
you’ll accept the project?
What made you change your mind?
I came from his office earlier and we were able to talk.
You’re right Ke. He wasn’t one of the lawyers of the Villaflors.
I just needed to confirm it once and for all.
So, you accepted it just because you had the wrong idea?
Of course I wanted to make sure
he wasn’t one of the lawyers of that jerk who hurt Kierra.
I won’t have it any other way.
I value my principles.
And no one can pay me to do otherwise.
I appreciate it, Luna.
You even made my feelings your priority.
Of course, Ke.
What about my feelings?
Is Kalix okay with me being the engineer of his house?
In case you forgot, you made me the
third party of your break up, remember?
Oh, come on!
Are we still going to bring that up?
Besides, I already told Kalix that you’ll be my engineer.
That’s part of the deal.
Okay, then.
Just remember Luna,
this is strictly professional. Don’t take anything personally.
Of course. I’m professional.
I’ve worked with difficult clients
and Kalix is just my ex.
I can easily handle him.
So professional… Okay.
Easily, huh?
Just remember Luna, this is strictly professional.
Don’t take anything personally.
Get a hold of yourself, Luna.
Architect Valeria.
Attorney Martinez.
Thank you for meeting me this early.
It’s fine.
I hope you have good news
for me to meet you this early in the morning.
I’m accepting the project.
That’s great.
I’m glad you changed your mind.
Well, I have to admit,
it’s hard to reject a project this good.
And renovating residences is my specialty.
Besides,
you even accepted all of my conditions.
Of course.
Anything to get the best architect to say yes.
So, let’s get to work?
I’m really looking forward to working with you, Architect Valeria.
Be professional, Luna.
You’re early.
There’s no traffic.
I see.
Do you still remember the house?
Not really.
Okay.
I’ll tour you around.
After you.
As you can see, the house is not in great condition.
Haven’t been here since I got my own condo.
I brought you here,
because I wanna show you every side of me.
Even the most vulnerable parts.
What I’m trying to say is—
I like you, Luna.
Are you okay?
Yes.
It’s just dusty.
Should we see the living room?
Okay.
Sorry, I didn’t hire a cleaner since
construction is gonna start soon.
Obviously looks rundown.
What’s that again?
Nothing.
It’s obvious that no one has been coming here
based on the house’s condition.
Seems like you took your time with having this fixed.
Yes.
I couldn’t find the perfect architect to remodel the house.
Hold on.
Hello?
Alright.
I'll have it checked when I get to the office.
Sure, bye.
Luna– it means moon.
Now you’ll remember me everytime you look at the moon.
Like a curse.
More like a tattoo in my brain.
A beautiful one.
One that I’m never gonna forget.
Luna?
The telescope isn’t there anymore.
Yes, I kept it so it won’t break.
I didn’t expect you would still remember it.
Luna?
Sevi, come in. I’m in here–
We’re in here.
Engineer Camero,
so nice to see you.
How you doing?
Doing well, Attorney.
I’m so excited to renovate your house.
It’s in such a good spot.
I’m glad you accepted the project.
You were Architect Valeria’s special request.
Excuse me.
I have to take this.
I’ll leave you two for a while.
Feel free to do whatever you have to do, okay?
What took you so long?
Traffic was bad. I can’t help it.
Fine! Come on, let’s just do this quickly so we can go.
- Do your measuring. - Okay.
This house is really nice.
It just needs a lot of fixing.
What’s his plan with this house anyway?
He said we’ll discuss the floor plan later.
Hey, Luna!
You were staring so hard.
What? I was not staring.
Okay.
If you say so…
What’s with the face?
Did something happen earlier?
I don’t know.
It just feels awkward coming here after all these years.
While he was giving me a tour of the house,
the memories just came rushing in.
Like–
I couldn’t breathe.
So,
it still hurts when you remember the past?
I don’t think there’s a break up that isn’t sad, Sevi.
Can you still turn back now?
No, I already signed the contract.
And I don’t want to seem unprofessional.
Honestly,
this house is special to me.
It’s actually really sad to see it in this state.
That’s why
I really want to have it fixed.
Make it a bright
and happy place again.
Well,
that’s a really good motivation, Luna.
I know that all of the projects you accept
have an important reason behind it.
I’m sure it would be awkward at first, but–
I know you’ll be able to handle it, right?
You always give me the best moral support, Sevi.
That’s why I wanted you to be my engineer.
Just don’t introduce me as your boyfriend ever again.
So disgusting.
I already apologized to you.
You jerk. Stop reminding me.
We have dinner tonight, okay?
You’re my mascot, my moral support.
You have to be there.
I can’t go.
I have to be somewhere.
I thought you were my mascot?
Sorry.
Fine.
Send my regards to the person you’ll be with.
Hey, it’s not like that.
Don’t worry about tonight.
You know how to act like you’re okay, right?
You think that's funny?
What are you having?
I’m getting beef soup.
Maybe we shouldn’t eat out next time.
Some people might get the wrong idea.
Why?
Your boyfriend might get mad?
Boyfriend?
Who?
Engineer Camero.
Huh?
What are you talking about? We’re just friends.
But
even if we were together,
it’s none of your business.
I did not say I care.
Let’s just talk about the house.
No. Let’s eat first.
Sir?
Can we also have the menu for the dessert?
Thank you.
He’s even having dessert.
So, about the house, how do you want it?
Is it just going to be two floors or do you prefer three?
What do you think?
I need to know how many residents will be living in the house
so that I can design accordingly.
It would be just me–
and my future family.
O-okay.
Are you good with having one master bedroom
and two normal ones
or do you prefer three normal bedrooms?
You decide.
Huh?
Who’s going to live there, you or me?
Like what I promised,
I’m giving you full creative freedom.
Architect Valeria, design it like your dream house.
I want to be impressed.
Of course, I still need to know the non-negotiables.
- Stuff I shouldn’t– - Attorney Martinez?
Attorney!
- Claire. - Attorney!
How are you? I missed you.
I was looking for you at your old firm but they said that you already left.
Yes.
Sorry! Girlfriend?
No, she’s not.
A client?
No, she’s just someone I know.
I see.
Oh well! It’s so nice to see you.
I really missed you.
If you need anything, just go to my condo.
You know where it is.
- Yes. - Bye!
Who was that?
Your fuck buddy?
She was a client.
Okay.
Whatever it is that you’re thinking—
stop it.
You’re always so quick to judge.
We should probably just have dessert next time?
It’s getting late.
Let’s just talk about this next week.
Enjoy the weekend with whoever it is you’re with.
Sure.
Sir? Excuse me.
Sorry, we don’t need the menu.
Can we just have the bill, please? Thank you.
Excuse me.
Amy?
Hey,
what’s up?
Hey, the boracay trip is set in stone, okay?
I already declined two photoshoots for this.
Don’t worry, Via even came home for this vacation.
I’m just glad that Arkin had free time.
Besides, Sam has been texting me nonstop
to come home so that we can all go on this trip.
My god, yes. They’re always so busy!
I’m sorry, too.
I’ve been swamped with projects lately.
If you only knew how much I’ve been dying to go for a drink.
Is Luna making you do all the hard work?
- Exactly! She’s so bossy. - Hey!
Excuse me, I am not.
- I’m a cool boss. - Even for getting a drink.
Hey! Hey, I think that’s Yanna.
- Wait a sec. - Here she is.
Hold on.
Hello!
It is her.
Move over ladies…
- Your goddess– - Wow!
- has arrived. - Wow!
- Damn, girl! - You’re late.
- Look at you! - I’m sorry,
the flight was delayed. But look, I even made sure–
- Ouch! - Oh, it hit her eyes!
Sorry…
- Stunning outfit. - Damn, Yanna!
- I followed the dress code. - So flirty.
Sorry, baby.
- I’m just glad you’re here. - I know.
Hey, what did your husband say?
I just told him
that we’re having a girls night out,
so he’s in charge with our daughter.
Come on.
- Let’s drink? - Cheers!
I love weekends like these, you know?
No work, no clients,
just rest and relaxation.
Why?
Is Kalix a stressful client?
I thought you’re free to design whatever you want?
- Isn’t that the dream? - It is!
Only if the client is cooperative.
Of course I still need directives.
Kalix is the one who’s going to live in that house, not me.
But as expected, he gave nothing. All he said was “I want to be impressed.”
Didn’t you talk about it during the meeting?
We should have!
But some client of his came and flirted with him.
So we weren’t able to discuss anything about the project.
Really, flirting?
Would Kalix even do that?
Well,
the girl did say
that if Kalix needs anything, he could just go to her condo.
That just means
that Kalix knows where she lives.
She’s probably his fuck buddy.
It was just so surprising.
He’s still flirting like that even while he’s together with Amy.
Did he not change at all?
- He’s still with Amy? - Yes!
- Really? - And you know–
- I even heard their conversation. - Well?
He just looked really happy and in love while talking to her.
That’s still not enough proof that they’re still together.
And it’s the same with the female client.
There wasn’t any concrete proof that she’s Kalix’s fuck buddy.
Let’s not jump into conclusions.
Jeez, I know what I saw.
No, wait–
we all know that you no longer see Kalix the same way you did before, right?
But maybe…
Just maybe– it wasn’t what you think it was.
Maybe it’s all just an assumption.
No.
I’m sure, I saw how he was acting.
Hold on.
Why do you look so affected with all this?
Are you actually affected?
Of course not!
I’m not,
I’m just telling you about what happened.
Whatever he does is none of my business.
- Hmm… - Hmm…
Are you sure?
They do say
that if you still have feelings for your ex even after all these years–
it just means that you’ve always loved him.
You’re so funny, Yanna.
No, I just can’t relate to that idea.
I don’t have any feelings towards Kalix at all.
You really don’t care anymore?
She’s not affected by him.
I am not affected by him.
Even if he is my client, we just have a working relationship,
I’ll still do my best, of course.
But I’m not gonna impress him.
If that’s what you say.
Okay.
If you say so. She doesn’t care.
No, she doesn’t.
Hey!
Go sleep inside.
- Huh? - Sleep inside.
- They’re all in there. - Where are they?
They’re sleeping inside the room.
Be careful.
Aren’t you going to sleep?
No, I have something to finish.
Okay.
Architect Valeria, design it like your dream house.
I want to be impressed.
So you wanna be impressed.
Architecture is not an easy course.
You will have many sleepless nights,
finishing multiple plates,
while juggling other subjects and student responsibilities.
You might get too tired and break down
thinking, “why did I even choose this course?”
That’s a true story, by the way.
But, it’s very rewarding.
There aren’t many professions where you get to see your
creativity and vision come to life–
as a building or a house that will last a lifetime.
Whenever I pass by a house I designed,
I feel so proud knowing that I was the architect who did it.
So just keep your eyes on your goals
and always remember the reason why you’re taking this course.
- Yes? - Hi, Architect Valeria.
May I ask,
what was your motivation in becoming an architect?
My parents are architects, too.
Ever since I was young,
it has always been my dream.
To see clients filled with joy after seeing their home,
their dream house, turn into reality with my help.
Have you done your own dream house, Architect?
Not yet.
I don’t have anyone to share it with.
But maybe, someday.
At least, I still have something to look forward to.
Architect,
I’m just curious.
How were you able to balance your personal life
and your studies when you were still a student?
It’s just so amazing that you graduated as a Summa Cum Laude.
Did you even have a social life back then?
Of course!
Of course. I think
I was drunk every weekend.
I’m sorry, ma’am.
But just remember to be responsible.
You have to know your priorities.
Finish your deadlines on time.
Start your plates early so that you can go to parties after.
May I ask, Architect?
Did you ever have a boyfriend when you were still studying?
Hey, your questions are getting too personal.
Yes,
but it wasn’t easy.
So, don’t get too serious with your relationships.
Just enjoy your youth.
And yes, it’s okay to have a lovelife.
She said it’s okay, ma’am.
Luna?
You’re Luna, right?
I’m Kio,
Kio Martinez.
Oh my god, Kio?
- Yes. - Kio!
How are you?
I’m okay.
You’re all grown up now.
You were still young the last time I saw you.
I thought you forgot about me.
I’m the one surprised since you were basically a baby back then.
No, I recognized you from the pictures.
You’re hard to forget, Ate Luna.
I mean, you were my brother’s ex after all.
Kio!
Mom’s looking for you.
Wait Kuya, I’m still talking to your ex.
Isn’t Luna still very pretty?
Yes.
Luna always looks nice.
And you look disheveled.
Kuya, stop treating me like a kid. I’m fourteen now.
Why don’t you get your own child?
Luna, you’re single, right?
Huh?
Ma-Maybe.
Yes! Perfect.
Bro, break up with that girl so you can settle down and stop bothering me.
Kio, watch your words.
You don’t just say that to people.
Mom’s looking for you at the hospital,
come on. Go!
Okay, fine.
- Bye, sis. - Bye, Kio.
It was nice seeing you again.
Sorry about that.
No problem.
What are you doing here, by the way?
I was invited for a career talk.
But I’m about to go now. Gotta go to Tagaytay.
Is that so?
I’m going there, too.
What are you going to do there?
I forgot some client files the last time I was there.
Should we go together?
No need! Besides,
Sevi’s picking me up.
Perfect timing, Sevi’s calling me.
Hold on.
Hello, Sevi.
Sorry, Luna. I can’t pick you up.
Looks like I have to stay onsite a bit longer.
Huh? I didn't bring my car today.
How will I get to Tagaytay?
I’m really sorry. Maybe someone else is going the same way?
Maybe you can ride with them?
Sorry.
I didn’t know you liked that genre.
That’s Kio’s playlist. I’m–
He usually play his songs when-whenever I’m driving him to school.
I usually don’t play music when I drive
so I didn’t notice.
Okay. Too defensive.
By the way,
I was surprised that
Kio still remembers me.
He said he was reminded because he saw pictures of me.
What pictures?
Well…
maybe he saw you from my socials?
Huh?
Didn’t you delete all of my photos in your socials?
Are you stalking my account?
Anyways—
About the floor plan, any feedback on that? Is it okay?
I actually have been meaning to talk to you about that.
It’s good, Luna.
I like the open plan layout
from the living room and to the dining and the kitchen.
The house will definitely look more spacious.
I also like the south-facing windows in the master bedroom.
I love waking up to the natural sunlight.
It’s like you read what’s on my mind.
I hired the right architect.
Does this mean that the floor plan is now approved?
Yes.
Why don’t you answer?
Your girl might have something important to say.
Girl?
I’m single
and Amy is not my girlfriend.
Really?
- Kio did say– - Well, Kio’s wrong.
You know how teenagers can be.
You got the telescope back?
I thought you kept it since it wasn’t being used?
Yes, I passed here the other day and decided to bring it.
I missed looking at the moon.
Let me check it.
I think it’s not set properly.
I can’t see the moon.
Let me help you.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Yes, got it.
Okay.
I can see it! The moon looks so beautiful.
Yes,
beautiful.
Huh?
You said something?
I didn’t hear it.
No.
I just said it’s getting late.
Okay.
Let's go.
Yeah. After you.
Let’s cheers, girls!
Cheers!
I like this music.
Hey, Sam, I thought you were going to close the club when we’re here?
I’m sorry, it’s the weekend, cash is pouring.
Also, I seated you at the VIP table.
Are you still complaining?
There are a lot of guests.
Your business is really doing well.
- Congrats! - Of course.
What if we look for someone Luna and Kierra can flirt with tonight?
So that we can end your dry season, girl.
Hard pass.
How about you?
Oh, she’s not answering.
Why?
Are you saving yourself for Kalix?
Bitch, of course not!
This is taking too long.
I thought you guys would immediately make out in the office or something.
Isn’t Kalix making a move on you?
Anything to get the best architect to say yes.
Seems like you took your time with having this fixed.
I couldn’t find the perfect architect to remodel the house.
I can see it! The moon looks so beautiful.
Yes,
beautiful.
What’s with that smile?
You remembered something.
She remembered something.
- Hey, you’re blushing hard! - Damn, girl!
Drink a little more and you’ll spill the beans.
The past is in the past.
I am not going back to my ex. Never!
Come on, Luna, I know you.
You always hide your feelings whenever you act that way.
- So what is it? - No, I just wanted–
You know what, let’s just enjoy this evening.
The night is young and so are we.
And so are we with rosy cheeks.
Yes!
Luna, your past just walked in.
Hey!
Hello to him, then.
Let’s just stop with this Kalix topic.
Get up, let’s enjoy!
Come on! We should all dance!
- Let’s go! - Yes!
Sam–
Hello, Sam?
I went to the bathroom. What’s up?
We’re in the private room upstairs.
We’re just freshening up.
Yanna’s going home soon since Avi called her
and Arkin just called Via.
Huh?
Why are you all in the private room?
You guys are too weak, I still wanna have fun!
Okay then. Bye.
Sir!
One more shot.
One more.
There you go.
Attorney… Attorney Perez!
- Luna. - I knew it.
You okay?
Are you single?
- Huh? - Huh?
You’re drunk.
Where are your friends?
Why aren’t you answering my questions?
Yes, I’m single.
- Why? - Then let’s kiss.
- Come here. - Luna, Luna!
I– Luna! Luna!
I don’t wanna die yet.
Adi!
Is my kiss gonna kill him?
He’s such a killjoy.
Hello…
Hi.
Wanna kiss?
- Sure. - Okay.
Let’s kiss.
I’m sorry, she’s with me.
What are you doing?
Why are you butting in my business?
Luna, you’re drunk.
Where are your friends?
Why do you care? I just wanna dance.
If you’re gonna bother me, I’m gonna stop dancing. I’ll just go.
Luna!
What?
Are you hitting on me?
If yes…
so what?
Do you like the designs?
I told you to design it the way you want it.
Not the way you think I want it.
Do you have any specific type?
Someone loyal and honest.
Great.
I think I can vouch for my nephew.
I think you guys would be perfect together.
This minimalist design that you got going here
it’s just not working for me.
I have to disagree with you, Mom.
The design is perfect.
It’s a huge improvement from the previous design of this house.
This feels more homey.
I don’t want too big of a house and closed off
where family members can’t even see each other anymore.
Like ours.
I heard you resigned
because of Miguel’s case.
Why?
For you, Luna.
I knew it was important to you and Kierra.
I didn’t want to disappoint you.