Did you see the leaked news about MARS?
LEAKED! FAMOUS IDOL SPOTTED
BRINGING HIS SPECIAL SOMEONE TO HIS CONDO!
I had to exchange
the other member’s news to save you.
Gam!
Right now, she and I…
are no longer involved with each other.
You might be different from me, Po.
And I hope Thame and you
could do better than me.
I love you.
Now, it’s time for the good news
from the music industry.
Congratulations, MARS,
the first Thai boy group
who successfully hit PAK
with their latest single,
which has been a big hit
all over the country,
titled "Who Says".
Let’s listen and watch their MV.
Please transfer my call
to Mr. Lee Sang Hoon.
I would like to discuss my business plan
about MARS with him.
It’s amazing.
You guys really swept
the #1 spot on every music chart.
I still can’t believe it either.
Why wouldn’t you believe it?
You guys devoted yourselves to doing
everything to achieve this, didn’t you?
Well, looking back at the moment
when we almost
couldn’t become a group again
until now,
I think it’s completely unbelievable.
Actually, you should be spending time
with your members.
But because of you,
the five of us could get to make
a song together again.
That’s why they asked me
to give so much stuff to you.
Actually,
it’s because you all wanted
to be together from the start.
Pepper cares about you a lot.
He doesn’t want you to think
we succeeded
just because he broke up with Gam.
I see.
I don’t want you to think
that way, either.
I believe that
if even they didn’t break up,
the result would be the same.
Everything would be the same.
It might take time,
but it would certainly be like this.
I want you to believe it that way.
Can you?
Yeah.
Tonight, I can’t go to your room.
I have to do the live stream
with my members,
and tomorrow, I have to discuss
my contract with the company.
Well, then, we’ll probably meet
at the company.
Yeah.
By the way…
Well…
It’s a bit cold tonight,
and I can’t hug you.
If you want to hug me,
put your hands in your pockets, okay?
Do this.
Here.
You should…
Just go already.
All right.
Good night.
FOR PO FROM MARS
YOU FILMED US A LOT
SO WE SECRETLY FILMED YOU, TOO - THAME
THE MV TURNED OUT AMAZING
I TOLD YOU YOU CAN DO IT - JUN
DON’T OVERTHINK IT, BRO :) - PEPPER
That MV is your work, right?
Thanks a lot, buddy,
for sending my sons to the top.
Now, they have gone super viral.
Check out the link.
TODAY’S ENTERTAINMENT NEWS
SILENCING THE SCANDAL
MARS SUCCESSFULLY COMPLETES PAK!!
THE FIRST PAK OF THE T-POP INDUSTRY!
MARS SHUTS DOWN ALL CRITICISM
PAK BREAKS THROUGH!
- MARS BRINGS GLORY TO T-POP!
- WHO SAYS SWEPT #1 ON EVERY CHART
UNSTOPPABLE! FAMOUS T-POP GROUP MARS
ACHIEVES PAK SUCCESS
FIVE MEMBERS OF MARS CAUSE A STIR
SHAKING UP THE T-POP INDUSTRY!
ICE SHARES CONGRATULATORY CLIP
AS MARS SMASHES PAK! #MARSPAK
Congratulations, MARS and Sphere.
You guys are genuinely the real deal.
THEY FINALLY ACHIEVED THE ALL-KILL!
#MARSPAK
FINALLY, OUR FANDOM COULD CELEBRATE
THIS MOMENT #MARSPAK
- I’M OVERWHELMED. MARS IS AMAZING #MARSPAK
- SEE YOU AT THEIR BIG CONCERT #MARSPAK
I’M GLAD THAT MARS HAS COME THIS FAR
#MARSPAK
I’M ABOUT TO CRY
EVERYONE, YOU DID A GREAT JOB #MARSPAK
WILL THEY GO LIVE? I’M EXCITED #MARSPAK
PLEASE DO A LIVE STREAM #MARSPAK
I WANT TO SEE YOUR FACES
PLEASE GO LIVE #MARSPAK
Yay!
Hello, everyone. We’re MARS.
Today, MARS would like to thank our Sphere
for helping us to achieve PAK!
Yay!
I love you, Sphere.
I don’t know how to express
my thank you message.
Come on. Just do this and say,
"Thank you so much for helping me
avoid selling fried chicken
with my mom at home."
Whose bias is this?
Check on him, okay?
He’s so sharp-tongued.
All right.
Thank you, our Sphere,
for making us reach PAK.
Without you all,
we wouldn’t have come this far.
Anyway, to thank everyone,
we’ll play this song
in an acoustic version for you all.
- Everyone, are you ready?
- Let’s get it.
Here we go. MARS, let’s do it!
One, two, three!
Play deaf da dub dub da dub
Da dub dub da dub
Don’t care what they say, I play deaf
CONGRATULATIONS, BUT I WON’T FORGET THAT
ONE MEMBER BETRAYED US AND DATED SOMEONE
- DO YOU REALLY FEEL NOTHING?
- I LOVE EVERYONE, EXCEPT PEPPER
Da dub dub da dub
Don’t care what they say, I play deaf
Yes, Mick?
Tomorrow morning,
meet Miss Pemika in her office.
She wants to talk to you.
Mick said you asked for me.
Take a seat.
Yes.
You directed this MV, right?
Well,
yes.
It seems you wasted most of your time
on tasks Oner didn’t assign to you.
I’m sorry.
But I don’t doubt the reason.
Did Thame tell you
that Leak It has these photos,
not Pepper’s photos?
But I decided to leak
Pepper’s photos to save Thame.
I bet you don’t know that,
actually, you’re the cause
of this whole situation.
Why are you telling me this, Miss Pemika?
MARS made a deal with me.
The whole group would go to Korea together
if they achieved PAK.
I guess you’re well aware of this.
I proposed this deal to the Korean team,
but there was a bit of a problem.
I don’t know if you know or not,
but the Korean team
is really serious about it.
They can’t let their idol groups
be involved in a scandal.
I also can’t hand MARS over to them
while hiding this either
because it will affect other conditions
between them and Oner in the future.
So, I’m not left with many choices.
I think it’s time for you to decide.
Will you let MARS
go to Korea as a full team,
or will you stay, harming them,
and make everything
they’ve done be in vain?
Whether MARS will get this or not
depends on whether
you’ll walk away from his life.
It’s your choice.
Eh?
You guys came to talk
with Miss Pemika already?
Yeah. But Jun is hungry,
so he took everyone with him.
But I guess Dylan felt annoyed,
so he asked me to go away with him.
But Thame said they’re discussing
this with the Korean team.
It sounds possible.
It’s nice, isn't it?
Yeah.
And how about you?
How are you feeling
about the whole thing that happened?
I’m just going with the flow.
My members never leave me by myself.
I don’t have time to feel sad.
I’m sorry.
Eh?
Sorry about what?
- Well…
- Per.
They’re here. Let’s go.
AFTER WORK, LET’S MEET AT THE ROOFTOP
Our first conversation began here, right?
Yeah.
Back then, it was empty.
But look at it now.
I have MARS
and you.
I think… this is
the happiest moment of my life.
How about your discussion
with her earlier today?
She said it’s possible.
After we left the meeting,
they all started looking up
information about Korea,
but it’s all nonsense, you know?
Jun keeps looking up tourist attractions.
I’ll look up tourist attractions for you.
- What are you searching for?
- Yeah. Just continue.
I’m looking up food.
Dylan is obsessed with food.
Nano wants to wear a Hanbok.
It seemed like Pepper
couldn’t take notes fast enough.
How about you?
I looked up the company we’re signing with
to see if their internet speed
is good enough for me to call you.
Anyway, we’re all excited.
I want to make it come true,
though we know
that it won't be as easy as expected,
and it might take a lot of discussion.
And even if we make it there,
it still won't be easy.
What if you guys can really get to go?
If we can, I won't be afraid
because no matter what happens,
we’ll definitely get through it together.
That’s because…
we’ve already been through
the toughest moments in life,
like right now.
The five of us will stick together
like we used to.
We’ll make music together
and give each other feedback.
I bet Dylan must be more strict
with the song than he was before.
I think Jun will just remain indifferent,
like he always does.
Pepper and Nano
will be managing this and that.
Nano will get to showcase
what he’s got for more people to see.
I’m sure all of us will be so happy there.
I’m so proud
that we’ve come this far.
As for us,
I’ll call you as often as possible.
But if I can’t do that,
I’ll keep texting you instead.
Every day after work,
I’ll give you a video call.
I’ll work hard and earn money
to buy you plane tickets,
so you can visit me as often as possible.
We’ll keep moving forward together, Po.
You don’t like my plan?
It’s not that I don’t like it.
Actually, I think
I should really be happy about it,
seeing you standing there
and listening to your daily updates.
Just imagining it
already makes me feel like
I must be really happy.
Is something wrong?
But everything that involves me
won’t happen
because we must break up, Thame.
Po, what are you talking about?
Why?
Thame, you guys can’t go
if they know we are dating.
She said that to you, right?
- I’ll talk to her.
- Thame!
You don’t need to do that anymore.
You’re aware that
Pepper is like this
because of our relationship.
I’ve made everything worse enough.
This is what you
have been fighting for all this time.
I won't be dragging you down again.
I told you this has nothing
to do with that.
Are you sure, Thame?
Ask yourself carefully.
During the scandal,
what happened to your song charts?
In the end,
if idols want to become successful,
they can only choose one thing.
And what you’ve been doing all this time
is for your members,
not for me.
But throughout the journey,
I’ve always had you with me.
I know
you want everything to work out,
but reality is telling us
that they just won't.
Can you just not give a shit about it?!
How can I do that,
since it’s about your future
and also all your members’ future?
I’ve been with you since the first day
you decided to reunite the group.
I’ve seen the dreams
Jun, Dylan, Pepper, and Nana have,
and I know how much they mean to you.
I know how important this deal is.
I can’t allow myself to stand in your way.
Hey,
don’t do this.
Just focus on yourself, okay?
Don’t make such a decision just for me.
Please?
Just answer yourself,
on whether you want to be with me or not.
I’ll deal with the rest on my own.
Let me handle it.
Let me feel tired.
Thame,
aren't you tired?
I’m not.
I’m not tired at all.
Please, okay?
Just focus on yourself for now.
Decide whether
you still want to be with me or not.
Do you remember
when we kept walking each other home?
Do you know that I can remember
every single digit of your phone number?
We left the line on,
even though we didn’t have
anything left to talk about.
I will work everything out,
no matter how tired I will be.
Just answer me,
whether you want me to do that or not.
If you still want that,
give me another chance
to fight for you again.
I’m sorry,
but I don’t want that anymore.
Hello.
It seems like everything
is settled now, Miss Pemika.
Where is Po?
Apart from singing,
you also have a movie coming up, right?
That’s right.
I’m really excited about it.
It’s a horror movie.
Have you ever seen
something mysterious on set?
Well, I want to give
a brief introduction first.
Actually, I have…
I heard about that from Mick already.
Anyway, thanks a lot.
They’re going to Korea, right?
Yes.
We’ll make sure
everything is properly managed.
Each member found out
that they’re going to Korea.
They’re all so happy.
I plan to announce this on the live show.
There’s one more thing I want to tell you.
MARS’ song achieving PAK
didn’t only earn them
an opportunity to go to Korea,
but the MV that you directed was so great
that I want to promote you
as the main director.
Pardon?
PAWAT NEUNGANAN CREATIVE DIRECTOR
Sometimes, a crisis shows us
someone’s potential,
like the way I saw it in you,
as did every MARS member.
WHO SAYS
ARTIST: MARS
Play deaf da dub dub da dub
Da dub dub da dub
Don’t care what they say, I play deaf
Who says what?
I’m not listening, my heart’s too loud
Sorry, I can’t hear you now
Sorry, I’m not listening
My heart’s too loud
Sorry, I can’t hear you now
And this is MARS!
Please give them a round of applause.
Here we go.
Welcome Jun, Thame,
Pepper, Nano, and Dylan.
This is MARS,
who just finished performing
their latest single, titled "Who Says".
Please take your seats,
relax, and let's start chatting.
I’d say MARS
is the hottest boy group right now.
Thank you.
Right. I have to admit
that it’s such a surprise to me
because you haven’t released
a song for some time, right?
This song is also different
from your previous style.
The initial idea for this song came from
wanting to tell everyone
not to listen to what others say
or worry about how people see them.
Just do what you love most.
That's all that matters.
Wow. That’s impressive.
But apart from producing
this song yourselves,
you also choreographed it, right?
That’s right.
We choreographed it ourselves.
I wanted the choreography for this song
to be different from
any other song from MARS.
That’s why we added a fierce
and playful vibe to it.
That’s amazing. It’s no surprise
that when scrolling through the feed,
all I see are dance moves
from the song "Who Says".
But now, I have to say
that MARS came to our show today
with a surprise.
This surprise is so grand
that the CEO of Oner
has to announce it herself.
Please welcome
the CEO of Oner, Miss Pemika.
Hello.
Please give her a round of applause.
- Hello.
Please take a seat.
Apart from having MARS with us,
the CEO is also here,
so I bet the surprise they’re going
to announce must be grand.
As we already know,
MARS is going to have a big concert
called Dream to MARS,
and also, we have
a surprise reserved for you.
Whoa. Another surprise?
The fans can no longer wait.
Can you not keep it a secret anymore?
Please reveal it now.
This concert not only confirms
the group's future,
that we won't stop here,
but our success
has also attracted interest
from Korea to sign a contract with us.
Wow.
Does that mean
the group will debut in Korea?
We were contacted before,
but we haven’t received
official confirmation
until MARS was able to secure
the number 1 spot on all the charts.
Whoa.
So, the whole group will make
their debut in Korea.
Awesome! Let's give them
a round of applause.
Like I said,
going as a whole group
like this is a phenomenon!
No, not the whole group, just one person.
Korea has always been interested
in signing Thame,
and this single reassured them
that they made the right choice.
So, that means Thame is the only one
going international, right?
- Yes.
- He will make his debut in Korea, right?
Congratulations!
Let's give a big round of applause
to Thame from MARS,
who is going to make his debut in Korea!
Please give him a round of applause!
What does this mean?
Huh?
This is not what we agreed on.
I think I've already made it clear to you
that if we achieve PAK,
the whole team will go to Korea.
I proposed it to them,
but they didn’t accept it.
That's why we had to revert
to the original contract,
which is what I just mentioned.
But everything we’ve done is to change it.
Go ask others to confirm
that I already discussed it with them.
I gave you a chance to prove yourselves,
but you didn’t do it well enough.
Then, why did you tell us
that the whole group would get to go?
That’s because I wanted to speak
the truth in front of the media
so that you all couldn’t complain.
I can’t let what happened
behind the scenes before happen again.
I admit that what you’ve done is amazing,
so I will keep MARS going,
but I’ll send Thame to Korea
as originally planned.
The four of you can stay
as a group if you still want to.
I’m not going.
So what?
Are you going to break the contract
and pay off your friends' debt again?
What do you mean?
I bet you guys don’t know this,
but Thame tried to help you all once
by paying off all the debts.
Are you really going to hold him back
and let him keep doing
the same thing for you all again?
This is my business.
They have nothing to do with this.
But I think they should also know
that you shouldn't be doing things
for just anyone like he once did.
You have no right to say this
to my members.
I’m saying this to you, then.
This decision, in reality,
was something you willingly made before.
And the company shouldn't have to suffer
just because you don't want to disband
or because one day you suddenly walked in
and asked for some ridiculous agreement,
when the company has already had talks
with a multinational corporation.
I've let you all
stay together long enough.
It's time for you all
to grow and look ahead.
Staying together won't help
your friend move forward.
Letting him go to make a name for himself
is what will help to achieve
many things in the industry.
If the four of you can't go,
then you shouldn't hold
your friend back from going.
Mick, handle everything
according to the original plan
and separate Thame from the group.
Asshole.
Shit.
You lied to me.
You said I had to break up with him,
so MARS could go there.
My job is to protect
the company's interests,
so whatever brings
the company the most benefit,
I have to do it.
Even if I didn’t discuss this
with you today,
you’d still have to break up with him
because I need to make sure
he’s as clear and pure as possible
before sending him off.
You’re talking as if he has no heart,
no feelings at all.
You’re hurting him right now.
Do you realize that?
I’ve always thought of you
as a CEO who loves and understands them.
Everyone talks about you like that.
In the end, you helped build them up
just to tear them down like this?
I didn’t build them up to destroy them,
but to help them grow stronger.
In your eyes, I might seem like
a cruel person,
but I want you to think about
what’s truly the most important thing
in everyone’s dreams.
What is it, really?
At first, they might have just come in
as trainees,
but everyone wrote on their applications
that they wanted to succeed.
REASON FOR INTEREST AND FUTURE GOALS
TO BE AN ARTIST AND HAVE SONGS
THAT PEOPLE CAN SING ALONG TO
I WANT TO BE REALLY SUCCESSFUL
As the person who helped shape him
and seeing that his success
is right in front of him today…
Don’t I have the right to make
that dream come true for him?
Of course.
Right now, everyone may have gone
through some changes,
but I believe, deep down,
everyone knows that the reason
they entered this industry
was for what they wanted.
You’re no different.
I want you to think back and ask yourself
why you came to work at Oner
and whether what I gave you,
the title of director
on your employee card,
is truly what you wanted from me.
On the other hand,
with everything you’ve done,
what Thame’s done,
what the group has done to me,
and what I’m doing today…
Do I still look cruel to you?
Today, everyone might still hurt
because this isn’t what they expected.
But just wait.
In the days to come,
what will come to them,
what will come to you,
will make them realize that’s exactly
what they’ve been searching for.
I see. MARS’ BA, right?
Sure.
- I’ll send their rate card to you.
- The sponsor list for the concert is full…
- I’ll also check their schedule for you.
- …but I’ll forward it to Miss Pemika.
Okay. What would you like
to support at the concert?
Dylan,
Miss Pemika asked me to tell you
that you’ll get to produce
MARS’ new song with Mr. Henry.
Have Pepper learn how to produce it too.
Seriously?
Pepper! Mr. Henry?
Mr. Henry, for real?
Jun, the casting results are out.
You got the lead role.
Seriously, bro?
Jun!
The lead role!
You got the lead role.
Nano, Miss Pemika asked for you.
Eh?
This is Coach Ton,
who will coach you on singing and rapping,
so your skills will be improved.
Hello.
Whoa. You’ve been working
for such a short time
and already got promoted ahead of Tae!
Main director, don’t forget
to put us to work too, all right?
If I’ve ever said anything harsh to you,
just forget about it, all right?
Guys, say this together.
Congratulations!
The documentary you made…
I never thought it would be
the one that sent Thame to Korea.
I didn’t know how to explain this to you.
Fine.
It’s okay.
If it were me, I probably wouldn’t know
what to say either.
You’re sad, aren’t you,
that the group won’t be the same anymore?
Yeah, I’m sad.
I cried for days.
I always thought that MARS
would always have five members.
But in reality,
when the opportunity came,
you couldn’t just let it slip away
or complain, asking him not to go.
I can’t be the kind of fan
who doesn't want
the artist I love to succeed, right?
When we love someone,
we want the best for them,
no matter what form that takes, right?
You’re right.
But I hope that
Thame’s success will shine on MARS
and that MARS’ success
will shine on Thame as well.
As for my job as a fan,
it’s to support and surround them
the best I can.
- That’s the meaning of Sphere, right?
- Yeah.
What do you think? Deep, isn’t it?
Super.
But what makes me the happiest is that
you did this work and became a director!!
I’m so proud of you, you know?
I’ve been bragging to everyone about it.
Now, the whole class knows,
and even that jerk Earn knows about it.
I’m telling you,
I’ll make that jerk feel like
without him, you’d still do great.
Fine.
It seems you’re enjoying this, huh?
Certainly.
- Do you want a sandwich?
- Yeah.
I'll have…
a ham and cheese sandwich.
No tomatoes, please.
You?
Oh, I know his regular order. He’ll get…
I’ll take just one BLT, please.
Just one, please. I mean it.
Sure.
So, Mr. B and you…
I’m fine on my own now.
- Here you are.
- Thank you.
Give me that.
By the way, today,
my staff really messed up.
Oh, the boss messed up,
and so did the staff?
Excuse me. When I’m at work,
I never mess up.
You see me like this, but at work,
I’m composed, you know?
And how about you?
How’s your work going?
I’m about to direct the new MV.
The new MV?
But I can’t tell you. You’re an outsider.
Now, you have a secret, huh?
You owe me one, okay?
Come on.
I’m the one who got you this job.
Don’t forget your gratitude, kiddo.
Come on. You forced me to.
LIST OF THINGS TO BUY:
DISHWASHING LIQUID
TOOTHPASTE
FACE WASH FOAM
SHAMPOO
BODY WASH
Hello?
Can you please write a note for me?
For these essentials?
Yes.
What do you want me to write?
LET US BE A PART
OF EACH OTHER'S EVERYDAY LIFE - THAME
I’m surprised at myself too.
Even though I got the job I wanted
and can stand on my own,
I don’t feel like
I’ve won anything at all.
Have you ever sat quietly
and asked yourself why?
Why are you trying to find Thame?
I have something important
to talk to him about.
Po,
I’ve written all of this to thank you
and to beg you for something.