- [guards grunting]
- [Daredevil grunting, yelling]
[Matt] That boat was full of weapons,
launchers and rifles.
He's using the Freeport to smuggle arms.
[Sheila] The wreck's
blocking the entrance.
Nothing is landing till
the Northern Star's cleared.
This is a terrorist attack.
The hunt for Daredevil,
Karen Page. Intensify it.
The people I work for
are grateful for the use of your port.
But this has gone into,
like, eight kinds of wrong.
There's an email on this card.
Not everything I write is under my name.
[Fisk] I imagine that you know
who in my staff is loyal and who is not.
- [gun cocks and fires]
- [people screaming]
Achilleo and Christofi
are in a lot of trouble.
Task Force took him.
Where's Christofi?
[Achilleo] I don't know.
- [gun fires]
- [groans]
- [man] Sorry about your client, Murdock.
- [Matt] Me too.
They killed him. The police.
- I'm sorry.
- I hate them, Mister Murdock.
[grunting]
[shallow breathing]
[gasps, breathing heavily]
[spray paint can rattles]
[sirens wailing in distance]
[sirens wailing]
Can I help you?
[Dex] There a nun who works here?
Sister Maggie, I think.
[man] Yes, she's on a sabbatical year
in Rome.
[Dex] Father, I--
I need absolution.
I've betrayed people.
I've betrayed myself.
[man] Oh, uh...
I'm not technically a priest yet.
I can't administer
the sacrament of Penance, but...
I'm not too picky.
One. One-two. One-two.
One-two. One-two, slip.
- Body.
- [both grunting]
Time!
[Fisk panting]
Sir, I need to talk to you.
What happened?
The cop in Hell's Kitchen.
Daredevil was there.
Thirty-second break. No more.
Gotta get you ready for fight night.
The cop's in hospital.
- Good.
- Well, he had a heart attack.
Four Task Force, dead.
Daredevil got away.
Apparently, someone is helping him.
Someone with very good aim.
Poindexter.
[trainer] You giving up?
Not like you, man.
Not like you at all.
I thought you were tougher than that.
- [Fisk yelling]
- [trainer groans]
[♪ theme music playing]
[vehicle horns blaring]
Okay. Thank you.
Cherry's stable at Metro General.
But the Task Force
can still get to him there.
Yeah, I'll get eyes on him.
Why was Bullseye even there?
I don't know.
He could have killed me.
- Like the Task Force.
- But he didn't.
So, what is that?
Is he just crazy,
or does he have a reason?
Well, killing Task Force
only helps Fisk. Right?
He's saying I'm a terrorist.
So, each body Poindexter drops
is just another hung on me.
Yeah. And it pisses off Fisk.
So that's like two birds, one bullet.
Right. But he doesn't want me dead.
I don't give a shit. He killed Foggy.
I hope those Task Force psychos
put a bullet in his head.
- Karen, that's not helping.
- Yeah? Well, I imagine you feel the same.
Thank you.
Poindexter aside, I want to take down Fisk
before there's any more collateral damage.
Okay, um...
- We prove the Mayor was smuggling guns.
- Right.
- Try and get the feds to file a case.
- Mmm-hmm.
- That at least gets him out of City Hall.
- We can hope.
The Task Force shook down Cherry
once they found Northern Star's captain,
which means
the First Mate's still out there.
- We need to get to Ariana.
- Hell yeah.
So, which one of us is going to Astoria?
How about both?
[people chattering]
[officer 1] Boots on the ground! Now!
[officer 2] Suspect! Hands up!
- [man 1] They're takin' her.
- [woman] Seriously?
[man 2] Yo, what'd she do?
Hey, what'd she do?
- What y'all doin'?
- [officer 3] In the truck.
- Now!
- [woman] Don't do that to her.
- [man 3] Come on.
- [chatter continues]
[Buck] If I may...
[clicks tongue]
...add a thought...
about Daredevil.
You know, you would have
much more influence over the situation
if you let it be known that he
and Matt Murdock...
are one and the same.
No.
I want to quash this idiocy, not stoke it.
Daredevil, he's an easy sell
as enemy of the people,
but Matt Murdock? No, I--
A blind man who saved my life?
I don't think so.
He saved my life.
[cameraman] Slating.
Take... Set.
And... whenever you're ready,
Mister Mayor.
As you know, months ago,
there was an attempt on my life
by the masked vigilante known as Bullseye.
We have reason to believe
that Matt Murdock,
the lawyer from Hell's Kitchen,
survived the attack on his apartment.
This is important...
because Matt Murdock is...
a hero.
[cell phone vibrating]
He risked his life to save mine...
only to be targeted by the same vigilantes
that threaten our way of life.
He could be hurt.
He may not know who he is.
We need to get you out of here. Now.
Help find Matt Murdock, New York.
Let's bring this hero home.
[BB Urich] What do you think
of the Northern Star?
[woman] That boat capsized in the river?
What a mess. How do they fix that?
I don't know.
If you ask me, Daredevil did it.
Or one of those other crazies.
This resistance with the graffiti.
What are they resisting?
New York's never been
this good in 30 years.
[♪ jaunty music playing on tablet]
[Kingpin] Uh-oh!
Looks like I spoke too soon.
Someone caught me.
Spoiled again by that dastardly do-gooder.
I'll get him in the end.
- [Sheila] Has the Mayor seen this?
- I don't know.
I mean, it's pretty underground, you know.
But these drops, they show up on socials,
then they disappear.
It's like guerrilla shit.
Let me rephrase that.
Are you going to show it to the Mayor?
Yeah, I probably should,
but he's not gonna like that mask.
No, he's not.
These blips, they're unsubstantiated.
They're only rumor, right?
The Bulletin, the other majors,
they're not picking it up.
We shouldn't give it any oxygen.
Who else had access to this footage?
Buck, you, Fisk.
Probably Powell.
- You?
- Yeah, me.
Is it on your laptop?
Hell no.
I wouldn't do that, Sheila.
- Come on.
- Show it to him.
He's not a fan of surprises.
But let's be honest,
this is not just bad PR,
and it's coming from inside this building.
Tracked the "at." Dark web.
It's just a leak.
Find it, plug it, and we move on.
It's gonna be okay.
Thanks. Sheila?
Look, I-- I know I can be an ass.
I know we've had our differences, but...
- I really do respect your advice.
- I appreciate that, bubba.
Just try and take it once in a while?
[indistinct chatter outside]
[exhales heavily]
Fuck me.
[Matt] Kind of brilliant, right?
Fisk not outing me?
This way,
he gets all the people
who support vigilantes
searching for Matt Murdock
and their haters
searching for Daredevil.
[Karen] Yeah, well... [breathing heavily]
You're wanted by both sides now.
[chuckles softly] Huh...
[Powell] So we tripled the security
personnel here and at Gracie.
Not my call to tell you to lay low,
even with that fight next week.
But when you or Mrs. Fisk are on the move,
you're gonna have two full,
close protection details,
and I'll volunteer
for one of them personally.
I have Buck to augment my usual detail.
Sure, no flies on Mr. Cashman.
But, listen, Poindexter's no joke.
He fired at you with 30 of us right there.
You're only here
because of that prick lawyer.
You're not much of
a politician, are you, Powell?
I say it like I see it, sir.
Well, here's to that.
[glasses clink]
Murdock's an asshole.
You want him
treated like gold, you got it.
Bullseye, if he tried once,
he'll try again.
My guys know not to fuck around.
They see him, they kill him.
Same with Daredevil.
Your dedication is impressive.
No, I owe that red piece of shit
for what he did to my guys.
You just want to know,
if you go down like that,
whether someone's
gonna get payback for you.
That's just how it works, sir.
Yes, it is.
Murdock's friend, the ex-cop.
Cherry, yeah.
Yeah. I understand he's at Metro General.
Yeah, I'm on it.
I got a couple other things, too.
I'll put Matt Murdock in this office,
and I'll put Daredevil's head
on a fuckin' spike.
Either of those would be sufficient.
Well, I like to shoot the moon, sir.
[radio beeping]
[indistinct radio chatter]
I just, uh...
Cole.
Hey, what's going on?
What are you doing here?
I want back in, man.
I need to be back on the Task Force.
Yeah.
Okay. Uh...
I mean... [chuckles softly]
you gotta heal, man.
This is as good as it's gonna get
for me, man.
- Look, after what they've done?
- Yeah.
- Not just to me.
Fuck the vigilantes.
I'm owed some get-back, brother.
How many people died
in that asshole lawyer's place?
- Seven. Yeah, seven.
- Seven. Exactly.
I'm fucking sure, man.
I'm ready.
Okay. Yeah.
- Okay? Yeah?
- Yeah.
Yeah, welcome back, brother.
- Thanks. Let's get to work.
- All right.
- [indistinct radio chatter]
- [radio beeping]
[Bob] You guys can call it a day.
Yeah,
- but we were told to--
- Look, I'm telling you to get lost.
It's okay. Don't do anything
and get yourself in trouble.
Oh! [chuckles]
What the fuck is this? Jurassic Park?
Just visiting an old friend.
[McDaniel] Nice vests.
You gonna wear
your underwear outside, too?
Get out.
[indistinct announcements over PA]
[monitors beeping]
- We need backup.
- [McDaniel] Yeah, Danny said he'd stop in.
- [Angie] Roxanne, too.
- Have her bring some Lombardi's.
You know how bored these guys are?
You know how many more of them
are out there?
- [Bob] We'll be back.
- We'll be here.
You bringing the pizza?
Or should we still have Roxanne do it?
[Bob] Fuckin' hump.
Dick.
God, I hate those little dickheads.
[chuckles softly]
Remember McDaniel?
Oh, yeah, I remember McDaniel.
Word is, he was North's TO.
- You're kidding me?
- Nope.
- That explains a lot, man.
- Yeah?
Hey, but don't sweat it--
[elevator bell dings]
[elevator bell dinging]
[Powell] Fuck.
Did Cherry nose-blast the two?
Fuck.
You gotta be fucking-- Unbelievable.
Stay.
[exhales]
[chuckling]
[sniffles, sighs]
He's fuckin' gone.
[Fisk] It seems this is turning into
guerrilla warfare.
[Powell] So, what is this?
Is Poindexter freelancing?
Or is he in this Resistance mess?
Without vigilantes,
there is no Resistance.
Destroy one and you destroy the other.
And, Powell? Vanessa is hosting a dinner
at the mansion tonight.
Yeah. Copy that, sir.
I already sent over four more units.
Thank you, I appreciate that.
- Yeah.
- [cell phone beeps]
[Fisk] You know, they say that
driving is most dangerous after it rains.
The collected oil, bits of rubber.
More slippery than ice.
You're not ready for it,
and you spin out of control.
The things that can damage us most...
are the ones
we're least prepared for, aren't they?
[sighs] Shit. I-- Look, I--
I should've told you sooner. I just--
You know, I--
I wanted to get more information
- before coming to you because I--
- Daniel, this...
person is mocking me.
Yes, sir. I'm sorry, sir.
They found this
on Commissioner Gallo's body.
Fuckin' A.
Do you remember
when I told you if you ever betray me...
it'll be the last thing you ever did?
Yeah, I do.
I wouldn't. I swear, Mayor Fisk.
Daniel, you are
the Deputy Mayor of Communications.
- Yeah.
- Finding out how
inside information is ending up in here
- is your responsibility.
- Yes.
- [loudly] Do we understand each other?
- Absolutely, sir.
A hundred percent.
It's completely my fault--
Good. I have two questions.
Do you have any idea
where the leak came from?
No. Honestly, sir, I don't. I--
Is there anyone in this building
you need to protect?
Yeah.
You.
Good answer.
[Buck] You don't need it.
You got me.
And, of course, the finest security
New York taxpayers can afford.
[gun cocking]
Have you ever been in the same room
with Benjamin Poindexter?
Not a ballroom.
Up close, personal?
No, ma'am.
I have.
[gun clicking]
I wouldn't call this a need,
more like a well-thought-out...
want.
[Buck] Hmm.
[gun cocks]
[gun clicks]
Good choice.
[Vanessa] Thank you...
Buck.
- [reporters speaking indistinctly]
- [people clamoring]
[man] Need my help?
Hey. Grab the rope.
[indistinct chatter]
Grab the rope, make sure to go
when they park and they dock. Come on.
[chatter continues]
- [woman] I don't know.
- [man] Hurry up.
Hurry up, lotta cargo here.
Clear out the space, too.
Come here.
- [reporters continue indistinctly]
- [chatter continues]
[man] Hey, Bobby.
[sighs] It's diapers.
[chuckles] Yeah,
they weren't on the ship with me.
- It's just a show.
- It's a good one.
It's local salvage company. Union workers.
It'd be a good headline. It's very, uh...
voter-friendly.
So, what happens
when they think no one's watching?
[man 2] Hey, Drew, get 'em on that crane.
[chatter continues]
I still don't understand
why would you take such a risk
on the Northern Star.
I believe that I can do...
more good than just New York.
You have built an empire
that will be remembered.
Will it? New Yorkers have a short memory.
But, yes, it...
It's true we have built
something generational here, Vanessa.
- But--
- Without an heir.
We've always been enough for each other.
Yes.
Have you ever considered
that with all that we have
and what we've done,
that we're obligated to make
a global impact?
[Vanessa] Hmm.
How many more worlds
do you need to conquer?
Hmm?
How many are there?
[loud chatter]
But those are definitely not diapers.
Shit.
There's Task Force everywhere.
[Matt] Place is a black hole.
If Fisk moves those guns
into Red Hook, they vanish.
I don't think we have a choice anymore.
I gotta get into the port.
No.
No, Matt, it's suicide.
It's our only shot at Fisk.
We might not get another.
Shit.
I hope they find him.
Me, too.
He's...
He's a good man.
He tried.
Sometimes I wonder if...
If your Tío Hector would have never put on
that White Tiger mask,
maybe it'd all be different.
No, he had to.
- It was who he was.
- [speaking Spanish]
[in English] If everyone was too scared
to be a hero,
we'd have none.
And I'd be dead.
Hey, let's get a snack.
[doorbell chimes]
[indistinct chatter]
Hola, Berto.
[boy] Sucks you gotta say that.
- Come on.
- [Javi] A'ight, come on. Come on.
Angela,
why are you so boring?
[boys laughing]
Look at his shoes.
Crocodile shoes.
I could hear you squeaking from outside.
- Nah.
- I didn't even talk.
Shut up with your
three-musketeers-from-Dollar-Tree ass.
Hey, hey, put that back.
[in Spanish]
[chuckles]
- [in English] Mind your business.
- [in English] Put that back already.
[all chattering in Spanish]
[glass shatters]
Berto...
[in Spanish]
[Berto in Spanish]
[in English] Just put that down, okay?
Berto.
[in Spanish]
[officer grunts]
[boy grunts]
- [Soledad] Stop. He's a kid.
- [officer] They're thieves.
He's taking the law into his own hands.
- Mind your business.
- Our neighborhood is our business.
- [officer] Hey!
- Hey! No. Don't...
[man] Come on, man!
[officer 2] Hold him down.
That's assaulting an officer.
You're coming with me.
No! Get off of her! Son of a bitch!
- Get off of her! No!
- Don't be stupid, kid.
- [man 2] What are you doing?
- [man 3] Hey! Let her go!
[people clamoring]
Screw these guys!
[man 2] Hey, what are you doing, man?
- [clamoring intensifies]
- [glass shattering]
[Soledad] Get home, get home,
get home, get home!
It's gonna be okay. Get home!
Get home, okay?
No! No!
Get home, please! Get home safely.
- [screaming]
- No!
No!
[clamoring continues]
[Javi] Get out of our neighborhood!
Get the fuck out of our neighborhood!
[Heather] A lot is said about
a person's mental health,
but what about a city's?
The randomness of a horrific crime.
A stranger pushing another
in front of a train,
a self-proclaimed artist
murdering innocent people.
How do we collectively heal
from these horrors?
You know, you don't have to
go solo to these things.
- [♪ soft music playing]
- [indistinct chatter]
If I may,
how did you and Mr. Murdock leave things?
Not well.
Matt was in a...
place...
before he got shot.
He has very strong feelings
about your husband.
Mr. Murdock
always was the champion of the vigilantes.
My husband...
- not so much.
- [chuckles softly]
Do you think
Frank Castle or...
Daredevil killed Matt?
No, I don't.
- Is my husband overworking you?
- No.
Not really.
- Vigilante trials are coming up, so...
- Hmm.
Must be hard to get into the head of...
those people?
Sometimes it's a little too easy.
That's the scary part.
Is something wrong?
No...
That thing, right?
That... sudden cold feeling.
My gram used to say,
"That's a goose walking over your grave."
- [laughs]
- [chuckles]
[imperceptible]
[exhales heavily]
[thudding on door]
[door opens]
Hello?
Hey.
If anybody's there, I'm not playing!
Angela?
How did you get in here?
Hey, hey, what happened?
- What happened?
- They took her.
They took my tía.
Oh, my God. [sighs]
Oh, come here, honey. I'm so--
[sighs]
- I'll start checking the jails, okay?
- No, that won't work.
The Task Force took her,
- and people usually disappear.
- Shit.
- [kisses]
- [sniffles]
[Kirsten sighs]
That's it, isn't it?
[Kirsten] Angela...
Can I see it?
[latch clicks]
[Kirsten] Soledad didn't want it.
Yeah. I'm not surprised.
Hard to be a hero these days, huh?
[♪ mellow music playing]
I thought we were editing The BB Report.
It's a working dinner.
Coq au vin, pommes du moutard,
and haricots vert.
- Oh! Where from?
- Me.
- And Julia Child.
- [scoffs]
- Bullshit.
- Oh, truth.
Yeah, it's a thank-you,
you know,
for gettin' the place cleaned, and...
a bunch of other shit.
I mean, we both know
I wouldn't have made Deputy Mayor
- if it wasn't for your help.
- We helped each other.
Yeah.
I didn't know you could cook.
I can't.
But I just read the directions,
did what they said.
Hopefully, it's all right.
I got no clue about the wine, but it was--
It was expensive, so, hopefully it's good.
[chuckles softly]
Shit.
Daniel, this is great.
- Wow.
- Good.
- I'm... I'm glad you like it.
- [chuckles softly]
'Cause we got some things to figure out.
- [knocking on door]
- Mayor Fisk?
Were you looking for me?
You know what that is?
Yeah.
Some crazy shit.
A weird mask with Daredevil on the boat?
That video, it came
from inside the Mayor's office.
Maybe even off my laptop.
Okay.
What's your question?
- Don't fuck with me, BB.
- [chuckles softly]
You burned me bad
with that Mayor Garbage leak.
Okay. That was then, and this is now.
It's not me, seriously.
I get it. You're a journalist,
I'm a schmuck from Staten.
- Fuck me or whatever.
- Okay.
But if you are leaking stuff,
anything, stop.
It's no game.
You could get hurt.
We could get hurt.
You're scared of him, aren't you?
Politics is a brutal business, isn't it?
Gallo...
was a good man.
We didn't always see eye-to-eye, but...
I'll miss him.
I'm just being smart.
I wouldn't blame you if you were.
[exhales sharply]
I mean, you had to have asked yourself,
what if the rumors are true?
About Gallo?
- About my uncle?
- [exhales deeply]
Come on, BB. I mean, look, look at this.
Life is good.
I don't know, like,
integrity can cost.
Sometimes, it's better
not to know, or to ask.
You did the right thing, Miss Sheila.
Can I walk you out?
Yeah.
If you are leaking stuff,
just stop.
Please.
[glasses clink]
This place was alive for a long time,
and you three were the heart of it.
I'm sorry.
Shit.
Maybe you're right.
- [car honks in distance]
- [brakes squealing]
[whispers] Josie...
[car doors opening, closing]
[knocking on door]
- Angie?
- Josie.
What's goin' on?
I wanted to check up on you.
Make sure everything's all right.
Maybe some people
are worried about Cherry.
Don't be.
He's safe.
Take care.
Lock your doors.
Fisk is hunting.
Resist. Rebel.
[tape rewinding sound effect playing]
- [♪ fanfare plays]
- [Mayor Kingpin] It's me again,
Mayor Kingpin,
here to give you a better,
more beautiful New York,
without all the riffraff
messin' up our city.
[people screaming]
[man on speaker] You must leave.
[Mayor Kingpin]
I promised you a safer city,
and look at how safe I'm making it!
Rounding up all the...
[echoing] ...vigilantes.
[maniacal laughter]
Hiding in plain sight,
as random people I just don't like.
Don't worry,
all these people are safe
with all your childhood dogs
in a farm upstate.
And for all you rebels,
the more you resist, the more you rebel,
it hurts my feelings.
[baby crying]
There's nothing to worry about.
I'm keeping you safe.
Because, remember, I love you, New York.
I'm Mayor Fisk, and I approve this lie--
I mean, message.
[heavy breathing]
I know why you're hunting me.
- [gun fires]
- [gasping]
You okay?
Are you okay?
- I'm here.
- [breathing heavily]
I can't get you into Red Hook.
You were right. It's a...
It's a black hole.
There has to be a way.
Well...
I'd prefer one where you get out alive.
Yeah, me, too.
[Fisk] It's okay.
It's going to be okay, my love.
What's on your mind?
[Vanessa] I hope that one day,
we find everything we want.
Someplace peaceful.
And where would that place be?
New York is our home.
No.
You are my home.
[Karen] You ever think we'd end up here?
There are worse places.
Like Brooklyn?
[both laughing]
That's--
- I liked Brooklyn.
- Oh, yeah?
My place was nice.
[Vanessa] We still own the island.
Yes.
When was the last time we were there?
I hate the feeling of sand
between my toes.
[laughing]
I did like it there, though.
Anywhere with you.
[Vanessa] Mmm.
Do you really think that
we could live-- Thrive...
outside of all this?
I do.
I have to.
[softly] I have to.
[Matt] I do miss my records, though.
Hold that thought.
No-- Wait. Oh!
- [Karen] Mmm-mmm.
- [sighs]
[♪ R&B music playing on speakers]
What are you doing?
Oh!
[laughs] No way!
Vive le resistance.
[laughs]
♪ In the fire ♪
♪ It was burning ♪
♪ Sweetheart, I know... ♪
- [vehicles approaching]
- [distant thudding]
Hold on.
[officer on speakers] On my mark.
- [high-pitched ringing]
- [Matt groaning]
- This is the Anti-Vigilante Task Force.
- Hey.
We have you surrounded.
Come out or we'll be forced to remove you.
- [officer 2] Go!
- [officer 3] Hands up!
[Josie] Get off of me!
[Matt] They have Josie. Stay here.
- Stay low!
- [Karen] Yeah, go.
[sirens wailing]
[officer 1] Vigilantism will not
be tolerated in this city.
- This is the Anti-Vigilante Task Force.
- [Josie] All right.
We have you surrounded.
Come out or we'll be forced to remove you.
[Daredevil grunting]
- Any and all resistance will be--
- [high-pitched ringing]
Go somewhere safe.
[officer 4] Clear every floor!
- [Karen] Hey.
- Hey, hey, hey.
[grunting]
[all grunting]
[♪ music continues playing]
- [Daredevil yelling]
- [all grunting]
[panting]
[sirens wailing]
Karen!
[continues panting]
[Karen sighs]
- [Daredevil] Where were you?
- I know. I know. Just...
- Come on.
- What happened?
I have something to show you.
What did you do?
They're hunting us.
Maybe it's time we started hunting them.
[Daredevil breathing heavily]