[Fated Hearts]
[Episode 11]
Hurry!
Emperor.
[Xia Jingyan, Emperor of Jinxiu]
Fill it up.
Everyone leave!
You two, stop right there!
Raise your heads.
I recognize you.
Last year during the Dragon Boat Festival
at the ceremony by the Qingjiang River,
you two were there too.
One is the wife of
Dai Quan, the Vice Minister of Works.
The other is
the niece of the Marquis of Bao'an.
Why are these two here with you?
Aren't you the wife of
Wang Encheng,
the Vice Minister of Revenue?
How did you become
the Marquis of Bao'an's niece?
Take them away right now!
Yes, Your Majesty.
Let's go. Hurry up.
There're so many concubines
and beauties in the palace.
Aren't they enough for your debauchery?
You even have to touch
the niece of an official?
How could the concubines and beauties
in the palace
compare to the peerless beauties outside?
But the Marquis of Bao'an's family...
Mother!
I didn't force them!
They were all willing.
Look at you now.
Do you have any bearing of a ruler?
I've been like this since I was a kid.
Xia Jingshi has the bearing of a ruler,
but do you know where he is now?
I heard there's a letter from Susha.
What did it say?
That Feng Suige is quite interesting.
He wants to keep Xia Jingshi
to stay in Susha permanently,
saying he loves and cherishes him
even more than his own flesh and blood.
This is just an excuse
to keep Xia Jingshi in Susha
as a son-in-law married into their family.
We absolutely cannot agree to this.
I already agreed.
Nonsense!
How can he, a first-rank prince of Jinxiu,
become a live-in son-in-law
to those barbarians in Susha?
If Xia Jingshi stays in Susha,
wouldn't Pingling City
naturally return to imperial control?
Or do you think that border stronghold
is better controlled
by powerful ministers, Mother?
If he doesn't return,
I can legitimately
take back his
military and political power
over the Zhennan Army.
That First Prince of Susha
is quite clever indeed.
He could even predict
that I would certainly agree.
Xia Jingshi won't just sit around
and wait for his doom.
How can he possibly
be trapped in Susha forever?
He's bound to come back sooner or later.
By the time he returns,
Pingling City will
no longer belong to him,
the Prince of Zhennan.
Your Highness,
so you had a backup plan all along.
Having him marrying into our kingdom
is brilliant.
Keeping Xia Jingshi in our Susha means
our princess won't have to marry far away.
This way,
we can preserve the sibling bond
between you and Her Highness,
while also keeping Xia Jingshi
firmly under our control.
I'm afraid Xia Jingshi
never expected that
Your Highness would have
such a brilliant plan.
Since arriving in Susha, Xia Jingshi
has been acting like he has
everything under control.
I'm going to strip away
that hypocrite's
fake facade.
That's right.
As long as he stays in Susha,
no matter what
he intends to do next,
it's all in vain.
I'm telling you,
His Highness is just one move ahead,
you know?
I truly admire you.
I-I admire you too.
Completely impressed.
So you guys think
victory is assured?
Why don't we set up a celebration feast?
That's a great idea!
Well...
Yun Fang and I
will go prepare the wine and meat
right away.
Why are you stepping on my foot?
Alright, stop it.
We'll have a proper celebration
after we capture him.
Remember,
when people are backed into a corner,
they'll take desperate risks.
Your Highness, you mean
Xia Jingshi would risk
meeting with that traitor of Susha?
That's right.
By the time Jinxiu sends a reply,
it'll be too late to change anything.
Even if Xia Jingshi wants to escape,
it'll be too late.
And for such an important matter,
he wouldn't
trust his subordinates
to deliver messages.
He'll have to meet in person.
Keep a close eye on Zhengnian Hall.
[Zhengnian Hall]
By the way, Ning Fei,
tell me about
what happened after
the Battle of Pingling.
Why are you asking about this again?
As for past events,
I need to recall it slowly,
piece by piece.
Please, just help me.
The cliff fall happened
after the Battle of Pingling ended.
I really want to know
what exactly happened then.
At least tell me
what happened on the day
I fell off the cliff.
All right.
Officer Ning.
Have you seen Commander Fu?
Haven't seen her.
Hey, guys.
Have any of you seen Yixiao?
No, no.
Hey, fellows.
Have you seen Yixiao?
No, haven't seen her.
We were drinking and
couldn't find you anywhere.
Hey, guys,
have you seen Commander Fu?
Commander Fu?
I think she went toward
His Highness's military tent.
Okay.
Don't worry.
Come on, let's drink!
Someone said
you went toward
His Highness's military tent.
Weiran and I thought
you must have had something to discuss
with His Highness,
so we didn't go look for you.
What happened next?
Next...
After that, we drank too much
and returned to our own tents.
When I sobered up,
you had already disappeared.
Why are you being so evasive?
That night I got excited from drinking
and got into a fight with someone.
Weiran helped settle the matter
and forced me to go to bed.
Ning Fei,
you're my best friend.
I don't remember anything now.
You mustn't lie to me.
When have I, Ning Fei,
ever lied to you?
Yixiao,
even if you don't remember,
you can't distrust me.
Look,
I swear,
if I speak even one word of lie,
may lightning strike me down!
Stop it.
Do you believe me now?
[You, Xiao Weiran and Ning Fei
are all orphans.]
[The three of you grew up together.]
Do you think what Ning Fei said
is true?
Judging by his demeanor,
he was probably not lying.
But I still need to verify it.
Xia Jingshi is almost recovered
and should return to the inn soon.
What do you plan to do next?
Are you going to ask him directly?
Feng Suige told me
that memories recalled with others' help
may not be true.
Only what I remember by myself
cannot be falsified.
Even if
I put a knife
to Xia Jingshi's throat now,
he might still not tell the truth.
So you plan to continue pretending?
I need to make him believe
that I've completely returned
to being that Fu Yixiao
who was completely obedient
and loyal to him.
But since he intends to harm you,
he must have prepared
all kinds of lies.
How do you plan to test him?
Don't worry.
Even a goose leaves a trace
when it files by.
There will be flaws.
It's just that
every single moment spent with him
feels painful and repulsive
to me.
What about Ning Fei
and Xiao Weiran?
Could they be part of Xia Jingshi's...
If those two
were also involved in
the attempt to kill me,
I absolutely won't let them off.
But I'm not sure yet.
That fool Ning Fei.
His feelings are written
all over his face.
What evil intentions
could he possibly have?
Prime Minister.
Minister Shen has arrived.
Prime Minister Zhuang.
What does His Majesty think?
His Majesty kept
the First Prince behind alone.
I think
His Majesty just wants to discipline
his son in private.
It also spares
the First Prince some face.
It's good, actually. Let His Majesty
give the First Prince a proper scolding,
so that brat won't
get more foolish ideas.
I didn't mean to say "that brat."
I meant,
His Highness the First Prince.
I misspoke.
I'll...
Slap myself.
You don't even know what you said wrong.
Let me tell you.
His Majesty will agree.
Agree to what?
I know.
His Majesty must have agreed to support me
and make the First Prince
hand over that Fu Yixiao.
Thank you, Your Majesty!
His Majesty will surely agree to
the marriage into the family.
From what I know of His Majesty,
the First Prince's proposal
aligns perfectly with his wishes.
He won't decline it.
So you mean
the Prince of Zhennan will really
marry into our imperial family?
It still depends on Jinxiu's response.
This marriage arrangement
isn't up to the First Prince.
Whether the Prince of Zhennan is willing
doesn't matter either.
Only His Majesty
and the Emperor of Jinxiu's attitudes
will determine the outcome.
However,
the First Prince took it upon himself
to write to the Emperor of Jinxiu.
This matter can be made into
a serious issue.
Do you understand what I mean?
So Xia Jingshi's
future child with Princess Xiyang
will not bear the surname Xia,
but will take the surname Feng instead.
Do you understand what I said?
I understand.
I understand completely.
I'll contact my colleagues right away.
We'll make sure to submit a harsh memorial
against the First Prince tomorrow.
Your Highness,
news just arrived:
our wedding procession
has reached the Susha border.
They will arrive in Yujing City tomorrow.
Using the wedding procession
as an opportunity,
we can urge Susha
to exchange prisoners soon.
This way, we can also take
Yixiao away from here as soon as possible.
Feng Suige is someone
who's hard to read.
I'm afraid if we stay too long,
something unexpected might happen.
Understood.
You've been in Yujing for many days now.
Have you secretly observed
the market of Yujing?
Thriving businesses,
shops everywhere,
with abundant goods.
The Susha Kingdom is much stronger
than I thought.
I've been stationed in
the southern frontier for over 10 years,
fought seven major battles
and countless minor skirmishes
against Susha.
Of the southern frontier's annual taxes,
70% goes to military expenses.
Pingling City, with its modest population
and small garrison,
is nothing compared to
the splendor of Yujing.
Though they were defeated
in the Battle of Pingling,
for Susha, it was merely
a minor irritation
that caused no real damage.
Feng Pingcheng
is a great ruler of his generation.
Your Highness.
In my opinion,
Feng Suige is actually
not at all like
what others describe him to be,
just a bloodthirsty warrior.
On the contrary,
he's impossible to read or figure out.
In fact,
he's more difficult to deal with
than Feng Pingcheng.
Therefore,
Feng Suige absolutely cannot become
the future ruler of Susha.
If he takes the throne,
our Jinxiu
will have no chance of victory.
Your Highness, are you feeling better?
Much better.
Then please drink this bowl of medicine
while it's still warm.
This medicine was personally prepared
by Xueying.
It can help relieve your pain
when the poison flares up.
Ning Fei also
personally brewed it by the stove.
Thank you, Miss Ling.
Your Highness.
Tomorrow, our wedding procession
will arrive.
By then,
your antidote will also be delivered.
In my opinion, perhaps we should wait
and not take any other medicine for now
to avoid conflicts with the antidote.
I've already tested it.
The temperature is just right,
not too hot.
Ning Fei says you never eat breakfast,
but Xueying says
your body is weakened by the poison
and you should eat more nourishing food.
So should I listen to Ning Fei
or to Xueying?
I'll listen to you.
I'll make the call then.
I'll have breakfast prepared.
See you in the dining hall.
Your Highness.
Don't you think...
Enough.
The prescription was written by Miss Ling,
and the medicine was prepared by Ning Fei.
Yixiao just brought it here.
What could be wrong?
I've already failed
Yixiao once before.
Now I'm about to marry
the Princess of Susha.
It will break her heart again.
The fact that she can put aside
past grievances
and return to my side
is already remarkable.
So don't overthink it.
Yes.
Yixiao.
I don't remember what
Your Highness likes to eat.
These are all
what Shunzi and others enjoy eating.
I suppose
they suit the taste of us Jinxiu people.
These are all my favorites.
Officail Website : 📺 dramacool.club
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Before,
did we also dine
together with Your Highness?
Yixiao,
between us,
we never cared about rank or status.
Please sit.
Yixiao,
do you remember
the first time His Highness
hit you?
His Highness hit me?
You've always been one to hold grudges.
You mentioned it quite often afterwards.
I don't remember at all.
Yixiao,
Weiran is just joking.
At that time,
you had just joined the Zhennan Army,
and you didn't know my temperament yet.
Once, I took you out,
and there was a shop
displaying all kinds of earrings.
You kept staring at those earrings.
So I asked you
if you liked them
and wanted them.
Interested in these earrings?
In the death camp,
the instructor said
I was a lower-class person.
He told me to always remember
my lower-class status.
I shouldn't dare to dream
of possessing things
that shouldn't belong to me.
Whether commoner or prince,
since we're all born human,
you should know
the value of your own life.
What does it matter if our origins differ?
Aren't we all ordinary people?
Don't we all experience
birth, aging, sickness, death,
joy, anger, sorrow, and happiness?
How can you say
you're a lower-class person?
From now on,
if anyone dares to say
such things to your face,
just take this whip and lash them good.
This is my imperial decree.
Do you understand?
I understand.
Don't be afraid.
Even if one day
you punch a hole in the sky,
I'll always be your support.
Go ahead,
pick a few things you like.
And then I struck you once
with my horsewhip
because I wanted you to remember...
You want me to remember
that I'm not some lower-class person.
Now that Your Highness mentioned it,
I remember now.
What else do you remember?
Xueying said
my memory only comes back
with help from others.
If I rely entirely on myself,
I won't be able to remember anything
at all.
Your Highness.
Why don't you tell me about
what happened
after the Battle of Pingling?
Your Highness, let me.
That day,
you shot Feng Suige with an arrow,
and our army won a great victory.
That night, you were discussing with me
how your arrow
missed by just a hair
and didn't hit him right in the chest.
You were
so regretful about it.
We were drinking,
but we couldn't find you anywhere.
Someone said you
went toward His Highness's tent.
Weiran and I
thought you and Your Highness
had something to discuss,
so we didn't go look for you.
He's lying.
Why would he lie?
When we were arguing,
was His Highness there too?
Of course he was.
That day, you were drunk and
insisted on pursuing
Feng Suige's troops.
His Highness advised you
not to pursue a fleeing enemy.
But you wouldn't listen.
You said the chance to kill Feng Suige
was once in a lifetime
and couldn't be missed.
You knew I was drunk,
so why didn't you stop me?
Of course we tried to stop you.
But you promised us
you wouldn't act rashly.
But later,
you left the camp without telling us
and went after Feng Suige all alone.
About what happened after that,
nobody knows.
Ning Fei mentioned
that some soldiers
saw me fall off the cliff by accident?
That's right.
We all thought
you had accidentally fallen off the cliff.
But only after seeing you again this time
did we learn
that you were also shot by an arrow.
Yixiao, don't worry.
As soon as you remember
what happened that day
and who shot you with that arrow,
we won't let them get away with it.
Of course.
If I find this person,
I definitely won't spare them either.
Your Highness,
don't you agree?
Certainly.
Let's eat first. The food is getting cold.
His Highness still needs to return to
the inn today
to handle some
important official business.
What's so important?
Official business is never-ending.
It's nothing but
some trivial matters
about the marriage alliance.
What's so urgent about that?
His Highness's health
is what matters most.
Your Highness,
please eat well first.
I'll have Xueying
prepare some medicinal food
to help you recover your strength.
Okay.
Why did you lie to her just now?
I needed to confirm
how much she actually remembers.
Now it seems
she truly doesn't remember anything.
How many times have I asked you
to stop being so suspicious?
Please rest assured, Your Highness.
This is the last time.
Once confirmed, I won't worry anymore.
From now on, Your Highness
can interact with Yixiao
more naturally and at ease.
Your Highness is already
breathtakingly beautiful.
With these earrings,
it's truly perfection.
I remember
last year, Father gave me a pair of
white jade earrings.
Where are they?
You want to wear the white jade earrings,
Your Highness?
But these ones
were sent by Empress Zhuang.
They're priceless
and better match your wedding attire.
On my wedding day,
I want to wear the ones Father bestowed.
It's not about
how valuable they are,
but about
Father's sentiment behind them.
That's what makes them truly precious.
Your Highness is right.
I'll go get them right away.
Your Highness, I found them.
Sister.
How did it go?
What Xiao Weiran and Ning Fei said
doesn't match.
One of them
is lying.
Who do you think it is?
I'll go ask Ning Fei again.
Okay.
Ning Fei.
Yixiao.
How's His Highness doing?
Don't worry.
His Highness took Xueying's medicine
and is much better now.
That's good.
You must be hungry.
Xueying prepared this for you.
I don't know if you'll like it.
From now on, whatever you want to eat,
just ask Xueying to make it for you.
Later,
when the wedding procession arrives,
we should select some generous gifts
to properly thank Miss Ling.
This is good.
By the way, Ning Fei.
There's something I want to ask you.
Please help me recall—
did anything special happen
on the night of the Battle of Pingling?
Anything special?
I really
can't remember anything at all,
so please help me jog my memory.
If you tell me more,
perhaps I might
remember something.
For example,
was there anyone
who saw His Highness in the camp?
But since you ask,
I do remember something.
That night,
there was a merchant who visited the camp,
and I believe he went to see His Highness.
What merchant?
He said he was trading medicinal herbs.
That's right.
For something as trivial as trading herbs,
why would His Highness need to
handle it personally?
Couldn't Weiran have taken care of it?
I remember
that merchant's carriage
looked quite luxurious.
His status must have been significant.
I didn't think much about it though.
Ning Fei, come have a drink!
Coming!
How many people were there?
I remember there was just one.
I never saw them anyway.
What's wrong?
Are you thinking...
I'm not thinking anything.
I just hope you can
tell me more details
so I can remember everything sooner.
I really want to return to
being the old Yixiao,
able to help you and His Highness more.
Wouldn't that be great?
I thought there was something wrong
with that merchant.
What could be wrong with a merchant?
I was just asking.
By the way,
don't tell anyone about this,
especially His Highness and Weiran.
I don't want them to worry about me.
Got it.
Why would Xiao Weiran
help Xia Jingshi lie?
Could he be involved too?
Were the assassins
at the bottom of the cliff
sent by him?
Who was that merchant really?
What were he and Xia Jingshi
plotting together?
Whatever it was,
perhaps
that was the real reason why
Xia Jingshi shot me with an arrow
and sent me falling off the cliff.
Were you waiting for me?
Since we met,
we've never had time to be alone together.
There are some things I don't know
whether I should say or not.
Go ahead.
We're not strangers.
I want to ask you,
what do you think about
the marriage alliance
between His Highness and Susha's Princess?
Does what I think
matter?
I see.
You must know
His Highness once promised to marry me.
That's right.
There are things His Highness cannot ask
or say,
but I
have to be the bad guy here.
Although right now
you can't remember anything,
someday
you'll remember everything.
Since I lost my memory,
I've met many people.
Whether it's Xueying,
Feng Suige,
His Highness,
or even myself,
we've always been
looking at things
from our own perspective.
It seems only you
completely consider things
from His Highness's perspective.
I'm simply doing
my duty in my position.
If you were me,
from my perspective,
what would you think about
this marriage alliance?
Rather than being entangled,
it's better to forget each other.
If I say
I never had any intention of entanglement,
would you believe me?
Rest assured.
Even if someday
I remember everything,
I will absolutely not have
any entanglement with His Highness.
There's a type of person in this world
who's naturally
as radiant as stars and the moon.
But loving such a person
is too painful.
I'm a lazy person,
too lazy to bring suffering upon myself.
It's good that you're willing to let go.
I'm quite curious—
are you more concerned that
I might entangle myself with His Highness,
or that I might end up
in pain in the future?
I get it.
Actually, you care about both.
Stop frowning all the time.
Everything will pass
eventually.
Nine.
Your Highness, I've missed you so much!
I've missed you too!
I've missed you too, Your Highness.
I think about you all every day, too.
After a while,
let's go home together with Master,
alright?
Sure.
Xia Jingshi.
Why exactly did you want to kill me?
Alright,
go play over there for a while.
Okay.
Let's go.
Xueying asked me to give you this.
Miss Ling didn't ask you
to give me this.
You made this yourself.
You've read the book
I gave you carefully, right?
Before, whenever the poison flared up,
even after taking the antidote,
I would still feel pain
throughout my body for the first two days.
The military doctor said I should carry
this kind of herbal sachet with me.
The herbal scent helps relieve the pain.
Later,
before each poison attack,
you always prepared these for me.
Your Highness.
To be honest,
I once suspected
maybe you were the one
who wanted to kill me.
When you first came to Susha to see me,
I deliberately kept my distance from you.
It was because Xueying told me
that the person who wanted to kill me
must have been someone
closest and most familiar to me.
Others wouldn't have had the opportunity
to shoot me down with an arrow
at such a close range.
Only after reading the book you gave me
in the last few days
did I understand that
you were the last person
I should have suspected, Your Highness.
It's all right.
I know
that you don't understand me now.
You will understand in the future.
Everything I've done
is for our future.
Everything you've done
is for our future?
Then at this very moment,
I'll act on behalf of my future self
and stop you!
Yixiao,
I hope you never remember
everything that happened that day.
Let all that pain
become the past.
From now on,
I will protect you
with my life.
Are you sure
no one has delivered him messages?
We've been watching everyone
who enters and leaves the pharmacy.
I heard that Prime Minister Zhuang
has recently been gathering support
from senior officials.
He wants to submit
a joint petition at court,
making His Majesty punish you
for your private correspondence
with Jinxiu.
So in my opinion,
Prime Minister Zhuang has not
told Xia Jingshi about this.
Then keep calm
and continue watching.
Yes.
However, Your Highness,
hasn't Miss Yixiao
been staying
with Xia Jingshi for a bit too long?
I-I don't mean anything else.
I just wanted to say,
could Miss Yixiao possibly...
Of course she won't!
Kindness must be repaid;
enemies must be avenged a hundredfold—
that's what the Red-Clad General is like.
If an ordinary person suffered
such injustice,
they would have gone mad
and confronted him with a knife.
But Fu Yixiao
could swallow
all her hatred whole.
She knows exactly what she needs to do.
Her composure and decisiveness
are probably beyond even
what you guys are capable of.
Only a fool
like Xia Jingshi
would fail to cherish her.
What?
Are you upset that
I said a few good things about her?
Not at all.
I'll just learn from her strengths
to improve my weaknesses.
Please rest assured, Your Highness.
I will be humble
and seek guidance from Miss Yixiao,
striving to impress you
one day as well, Your Highness.
Why is Zhengnian Hall suddenly
filled with so many patients?
I heard
there's a real estate broker
who's been boasting around
that he knows the Young Mistress
of Zhengnian Villa.
These days,
many people have come because of that.
I'll get to work now.
[Zhengnian Hall]
Miss Yixiao.
Where is His Highness?
Please get in the carriage.
His Highness is not far from here.
What do you want from me?
This tea is a tribute from the South.
The water used for brewing
is plum-blossom snowwater
collected last December,
freshly taken from the ice cellar.
Such fine tea
gulped down by you like that
is truly a waste of treasure.
What do you want to ask?
Yesterday,
did you learn anything?
No.
You spent a whole night
with Xia Jingshi.
How could you have learned nothing?
What nonsense are you talking about?
Right, you didn't spend
the night together.
You merely spent one night
under the same roof.
Yet you learned nothing?
Were you simply
lost in pleasure?
When did you know?
What?
When did you know
that Xia Jingshi was the one who shot me?
Your previous efforts to stop me
were probably for this reason too, right?
So you already know.
Don't worry.
I didn't learn it much earlier than you.
I just never had the chance
to tell you.
I have no reason to hide this from you.
I'd prefer you knew sooner
so I could enjoy watching your reaction.
You really are
incapable of saying anything nice.
Tell me,
since you were
Xia Jingshi's most trusted general
and a hero in the Battle of Pingling,
why did he want to kill you?
I didn't expect you
to care so much about me.
I'd like to know too.
Why don't you ask him yourself?
I'm guessing you discovered something,
something you weren't supposed to know.
He must have been forced
to take such drastic action against you.
Since you're a partner
I can trust,
I might as well tell you.
The day before Susha attacked
Pingling City,
Xia Jingshi suddenly changed
his battle plan.
Before changing the plan,
he received a secret military report.
Didn't you say before
that someone in Susha
was colluding with the enemy?
It must've been around that time.
Very well.
I'll go investigate the military report.
The night the Battle of Pingling ended,
a merchant
met with Xia Jingshi in his tent.
I should have been
in the tent as well.
However,
as for what they discussed,
I cannot remember.
But I suspect
that what that merchant discussed
with Xia Jingshi
was exactly the reason
he wanted to kill me.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm not hiding anything from you.
I truly don't remember
who that person was
or what they discussed.
I'm staying by Xia Jingshi's side
just to uncover the truth.
As you know,
forcing a confession won't work.
And Xia Jingshi
definitely won't say anything.
So,
this might be our
only chance.
Stay safe.
I'll have people protect you from afar.
That won't be necessary.
I'm telling you all this
because I want you to know that
since I've agreed to cooperate with you,
I absolutely won't go back on my word.
Whatever I should do,
I'll definitely see it through.
As for you...
I'll also do what needs to be done.
That's good.
I can't stay out too long.
Xia Jingshi will get suspicious.
Wait.
Take this with you.
What's this?
It's my heart of mercy.
Yun Fang!
Escort her back.
No need.
For safety's sake,
for the next few days,
you'd better not come to see me.
Your Highness.
Why do I feel
you care quite a lot about
Miss Yixiao?
I care about her?
So what if I care about her?
She's a member of my household.
Shouldn't I care about her?
Your Highness,
His Majesty summons you.
Miss. Miss.
What's wrong?
Where are you feeling unwell?
My throat hurts badly.
[Zhengnian Hall]
Take it easy.
This way, this way.
Your Highness.
The carriage sent by the inn has arrived.
Where is Yixiao?
I only heard someone was looking for her.
In Yujing City,
she has no family or friends.
Who would want to see her?
Your Highness.
There're many patients
at the clinic today,
and we're really short-staffed,
so I sent Yixiao to the medicine merchant
to fetch some herbs for me.
Then please, Miss Ling,
tell Yixiao when she comes back
to take good care of herself.
Thank you for taking care of me
these past few days, Miss Ling.
Your Highness is too kind.
It's simply my duty as a physician.
I'll take my leave now.
His Majesty has arrived!
Greetings, Your Majesty!
You may rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Censor Wang.
Yes, Your Majesty.
In your Censorate,
excluding those on official leave, sick,
or in mourning,
how many people remain in the office?
Officail Website : 📺 dramacool.club
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Your Majesty.
The Censorate
has 12 officials of fifth rank or higher.
Excluding two
who cannot perform their duties,
there are 10 working daily.
10 people, huh?
Do you know
how many memorials I've received
in just a few hours?
18!
10 people from the Censorate
submitted 18 memorials to me.
Is your Censorate
so idle that you have nothing else to do?
Stop exchanging glances!
Since you cannot answer, Censor Wang,
I presume Prime Minister Zhuang,
you can explain this clearly?
Your Majesty,
I've heard something about this matter.
It was all because the First Prince
privately wrote a letter
to the Emperor of Jinxiu.
This action is absurdly inappropriate
and unbecoming of a prince.
The court officials are indignant
and have submitted numerous memorials
impeaching the First Prince.
His Highness the First Prince has arrived!
I
pay my respects to Your Majesty.
Rise.
I summoned you here
so you could hear for yourself
how these people
are impeaching you.
Your Majesty.
As Your Majesty's eldest son,
the First Prince should
set an example for all officials.
Such rash actions
offend royal dignity.
This matter must be strictly investigated
and punished;
otherwise, the people will not accept it,
nor will us court officials.