ADAPTED FROM THE NOVEL
HIDDEN LOVE BY ZHU YI
I am telling you
the secret I wanted to seal away forever.
Can you…
Can you believe
that you are a great person?
Seeing how much
I like you,
can you ignore what people say about you?
Can you be with me forever?
MAKE A LOT OF MONEY
AND HELP HIM PAY OFF HIS DEBTS
Please?
How do you fold this star?
I can't fold it back after unfolding it.
After unfolding it, I…
These stars
will be in my safekeeping.
What should I do now?
Counting it now,
I've made you cry so many times.
Yet you deny that you're a crybaby.
Give me a hug.
All right.
I know it all now.
Why did you suddenly tell me this?
I just wanted you to know.
But this time,
I don't have that rumored girlfriend
that your brother mentioned.
I have an official girlfriend now.
So did you come back to Yihe
just to tell me this?
It's because you said
you were considering something.
That's why…
I was afraid that if I called you,
you would…
I thought that
if I talked to you in person,
it should be hard for you to bring it up.
Bring what up?
What were you thinking?
If your parents hadn't disapproved,
I would snatch you
to get our marriage certificate now.
I'm serious.
Why would you have to snatch me?
I'm afraid you will run away.
When I said I was considering something,
it was whether I should stay with you
in Yihe for two years
and go back with you after you graduate
or if I should go to Nanwu first
to get everything settled
and wait for you to return.
What were you thinking?
Is that it?
Actually,
I could stay in Yihe too.
We can talk about it.
You don't always have to give in to me.
I really don't want to stay here.
Besides, who else would I give in to?
Young lady,
what you need to do is simple.
Stay here and study hard.
Don't worry about anything else.
The most important thing
is to spend more time with your boyfriend.
Understand?
As for your parents,
don't worry about it.
I'll find time to talk to them.
Smile.
Give me a smile.
CHAPTER 24, SET OFF
SO NEAR AND YET SO FAR
There is someone
that I really like.
But
he just doesn't like me.
But I will grow up.
Then let's wait until you grow up.
But when I grow up,
he'll fall for someone else.
That's fine.
Sang Zhi, when you grow up,
you will meet someone better.
Why have you been drinking?
What's wrong?
I'll bring you some hot water.
Why did you get up?
Are you in a bad mood?
I think
that I've treated you badly.
When did you treat me badly?
Is it because of what I said to you
at the airport today?
I told you that
because I just wanted you to know.
You didn't know it before.
That's why I wanted to tell you.
But I didn't want you to feel…
You treat me very well.
Be it in the past or the present,
you treat me well.
It's true.
Sang Zhi.
I love you.
I'm sorry, Zhizhi.
I said these words so late.
Over the years,
I know
I've made you sad.
It was your unwavering dedication
that made me realize I'm not good enough.
Whether it's my imperceptiveness
or indecisiveness,
I haven't been good enough.
But for these shortcomings,
I'll try my best to make it up to you
every day that we are together.
Zhizhi.
I won't let you regret
the choice you made.
I love you, Sang Zhi.
Sangsang, what are you drawing?
I found my theme for the competition.
What did I tell you?
You can't force ideas to come.
You need to clear your mind
for inspiration to come.
So what is your theme?
Why are you being secretive?
Come in.
Siyun.
Perfect timing. Come here quickly.
Help me take a look.
I have trouble deciding.
Which one of these two is better?
I think
this one is the best.
-What is this?
-Open it.
You've been working late nights lately,
so I bought you a gift.
Restorative honey?
Xiaoduan recommended it.
He sure knows what to pick.
This kid knows a lot of things.
It smells quite nice.
Come in.
Actually, I wanted to talk
to both of you about something today.
What is it?
I was thinking
that after completing the upgrade
of the Celestial Progression System,
I might have to resign.
Resign?
Why do you suddenly want to resign?
Is another company trying to poach you?
No.
I'm thinking of going back to Nanwu
to start my own business.
Nanwu?
Is it for Sang Zhi?
If I'm not mistaken,
isn't she only a college sophomore?
When she graduates in two years,
you can still go back there with her.
The Dream Games studio
has a very promising next few years.
Are you sure about leaving now?
I have carefully considered it
before telling you.
Some things have happened recently.
It made me realize
I may not have been good enough
to Sang Zhi.
I haven't done enough for her either.
No, Jiaxu, you're worrying too much.
Siyun and I both think
that you treat her really well.
Actually, the main reason
is that her parents
may have some concerns about me.
Sang Zhi is also upset
because of this.
However,
she turned around and comforted me.
She was worried
that this might hurt my self-esteem.
In truth, I understand
her parents' concerns.
But I'm older than her.
So I should be the one
resolving these concerns.
I just want to go
to Nanwu as soon as possible.
After I've settled everything,
I'll give myself more time
and chances to prove myself.
He's all grown up now.
A man should have
a sense of responsibility.
Since you've already made up your mind,
Li Xun and I can't stop you.
We wish you all the best.
Thank you.
However,
today's economy isn't easy
for young entrepreneurs.
Given your qualifications,
there aren't many
reputable companies in Nanwu
that can hire you.
How about this?
You can apply to our headquarters
to open your own studio.
They can provide some technical support
and follow-up expansion,
which would be relatively easier for you.
Look at that.
Siyun thinks of everything.
Our company does have this policy.
If you need it,
Siyun and I will put in a word.
It would be great if that could happen.
Thank you, Li Xun.
Thank you, Siyun.
You're welcome.
If you create a successful game
in the future,
I'll get to boast about it.
I can say that I mentored this guy.
You were still an intern
when you first came.
Look at you now.
So many years have passed.
Now that you're leaving,
I'm actually quite reluctant.
You can do it.
-Good luck.
-LI Xun and I support you.
-You can do it.
-I'll do my best.
Hello?
The patient's condition isn't optimistic.
Cherish the time and talk to him.
Thank you, doctor.
It has been a long time
since I thought about the past.
I didn't want to
and I didn't dare to.
But I think
today should be the day that I face it.
I should get some closure.
It happened such a long time ago.
Now that I think about it,
you would have been released by now
if you hadn't jumped.
There are many things
that I've never told you.
I've finished paying off
the compensation you owed
and those debts of yours.
My mom
passed away several years ago.
Because of you.
Because we didn't have money.
At that time,
she knew she was sick
from cancer.
She refused to get treatment
because she didn't want to spend money.
When she finally went to the hospital,
the doctor said
it was too late for treatment.
I used to wish so badly
that you could see it all.
I wished you would wake up,
so you could see everything
that happened to us.
I wanted to see you feel guilt and pain.
I just wanted you to understand.
If you hadn't
run away
and had chosen to face punishment,
our lives would have been so different.
But actually,
I should thank you too.
Because of you,
I never dared to drink.
It was also because of you
that I learned what responsibility
and taking on responsibility means.
Now,
I can say
that I'm a decent person.
At least I now have the ability
to protect the people I love.
I really wish you could see it.
All right then.
If you see Mom
on the other side,
sincerely apologize to her.
Be at peace,
Dad.
Why are you here?
What's with this expression?
I knew
this day would come eventually.
I know.
I know you're very sad.
I know that.
Okay, it's all right.
Am I really getting old now?
Why are my parents no longer here?
GRACE UPON DESCENDANTS
IN MEMORY OF BELOVED MOTHER,
XU RUOSHU
Mom, you haven't met her yet.
This is Sang Zhi.
I've told you about her before.
Now,
she is my girlfriend.
Mom.
I might settle down in Nanwu later.
But don't worry.
I'll come and visit you every year.
I came today mainly to tell you
that Dad has also passed away.
He passed away
quite peacefully.
Don't worry.
I fulfilled his wish
and found a serene place for him.
I wonder
if you two will meet over there.
If you do…
Never mind.
As long as both of you
are happy and content.
Hello, Mrs. Duan.
I'm Sang Zhi.
You don't have to worry.
Duan Jiaxu is now
a very kind and outstanding person.
He treats people well
and is very sincere.
He excelled in his studies
and performs well at work.
To me,
my parents,
and everyone,
he is a wonderful person.
Although some bad things
had happened in the past,
he never gave up on himself.
Instead, he worked hard
and endured everything
with a lot of hardship.
If only
you could see how excellent he is now.
I'm sure you would have some regrets
and worries too, right?
But don't worry.
I'll take good care of him.
I'll make it up to him.
I'll make sure
he is happy every day.
So I'll also give you my promise.
As long as I am here,
I won't let anyone bully Duan Jiaxu again.
He'll have his own family in the future.
He has me
and many others who love him.
We all love you.
So
you will never be alone anymore.
Okay?
Don't cry.
If you cry,
your mom will think I'm bullying you.
The smoke is stinging my eyes.
You promised.
You promised in front of my mom
that you'll protect me.
Yes, I'll protect you.
Come here.
Let me protect you for a bit.
Hey.
Come and get me.
Come after me.
I can even stand up.
That little girl
who used to sit in my back seat
suddenly grew up one day.
She can always accompany me
and walk side by side with me.
She helped me overcome
my longest and darkest hour.
She even took the lead
and waited for me
in the sunlight.
Come on!
I'm coming!
I've submitted my resignation to Siyun.
Why?
Didn't I tell you before?
You don't have to go back to Nanwu.
I want to go back.
I want
to go in advance and get things settled.
When you graduate and return to Nanwu,
you can immediately start a good life.
Besides, your family is there.
I can start my business anywhere, right?
My home is where you are.
Didn't you say
that after all the bad things are over,
all that is left are the good things?
So we just need to focus on the future.
Our future.
Okay?
How long will it be before leaving?
After completing the handover procedures,
about a month later.
A month?
That's so soon.
Are you feeling reluctant?
No.
But I feel reluctant.
Don't worry.
We'll have many opportunities to meet up.
I'm making supper for you.
Supper?
Glutinous rice balls.
How about six?
Is that okay?
Okay, that's enough.
That's too much water.
Really?
Let me do it.
That's about it.
I'm going to miss you after I leave.
What am I going to do?
If you miss me,
you can eat the candy I gave you.
Okay?
Or you can bring the polar bear with you.
What will you do if you miss me?
I'll leave the polar bear with you.
If you miss me,
you can look at it.
It will be just like I'm right beside you.
Okay?
It's not done yet.
Do you want…
What are you thinking about?
Why don't you go and get some rest?
I'll be done soon.
How about…
All right.
I've called a car for you.
Text me after you get in the car.
The airport is so far.
I shouldn't have let you see me off.
How could I not come to see you off?
I don't want you to leave.
I know.
Don't worry.
After I get there,
I'll visit you whenever I have time.
I won't make you wait too long. Okay?
Listen.
Once you're back in Nanwu,
you need to eat regularly.
You must have
three meals a day.
But I'll remind you.
And also,
don't think
about other things.
Don't be concerned about them.
Just focus on your work
and work hard.
You can work hard,
but don't stress yourself too much.
I mean,
if your start-up does fail,
it's okay.
After all, I can…
You can what?
I'll provide for you.
After I graduate, I can provide for you.
You always say you'll provide for me.
Then I'll just wait.
All right.
Well,
I'm going to go now.
Don't stay any longer.
Okay?
Text me after you get in the car.
I'm going now.
Be good.
Text me when you get in the car.
Head back now.
Bye.
Let me send you off.
Okay.
Then send me off.
This is far enough.
I really have to go now.
Head back now.
Text me when you get in the car.
Make sure to text me.
What is it?
I have a feeling
that you have something to tell me.
After you go to Nanwu,
can we have video calls every day?
Of course we can.
You won't find it burdensome, will you?
Will you find it burdensome?
-No.
-Me neither.
You try it first.
Okay.
One more thing.
We'll be in a long-distance relationship,
so we should
make an extra effort.
For example, on anniversaries or holidays,
I can visit you in Nanwu
or you can visit me in Yihe.
Of course.
Then I shall go and visit you.
Hold on. What do you mean by that?
Are you saying
that I usually don't make an effort?
That's not it.
So do you agree with it?
Of course.
Good.
And also,
if we have an argument…
We won't argue.
But if we do,
we must make up on the same day.
No silent treatment. No disappearing.
-Got it?
-We make up on the same day we quarrel.
Well said.
Trust.
We trust each other.
Actually…
If…
-What are you reading?
-Wait. No.
"Guide to maintaining
a long-distance relationship"?
As you know,
many problems come up
in long-distance relationships.
So I summarized them in advance
and developed a guide.
So you don't trust me
and are worried about me.
No.
I'm pretty worried about you.
I think your guide
is done very well.
You should strictly follow it
in the future.
Me?
Quickly send me a copy.
You can make your own.
I'm serious.
What you wrote is really good.
Wait.
"We can have arguments,
but not in front of other people."
Yes, because it's a matter
of saving our face.
"You don't have to reply
to messages instantly.
But if you see them, you must reply."
-That's right.
-If you see them, you must reply.
Yes, you have to reply if you see it.
Got it?