=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 8=
(Chong Camp)
Get out of the way!
Are you faking all this
or did you lose the bet?
It's not over yet.
It's too early to call it.
Your Grace,
were you satisfied with the first half?
To sell the act,
you got yourself into danger.
This is truly unexpected.
Since when did you suspect him?
From the very start,
I smelled it in him,
the scent of my own kind.
Of your kind?
Then he's definitely no good.
Of course.
Only members
of the Chong royal family
or the All-Knowing
know about this duel.
All-Knowing?
A secret organization
under the royal clan.
It trains loyal assassins.
The Blindfolded Trial
is the graduation rite
for all the disciples.
Royal family members
watch the blindfolded duels.
The winner
gets a name and graduates.
Fifteen is the code name
of the fake Lin Jun.
Disciples from different batches
never meet.
Han Lingqiu was disfigured.
So Fifteen didn't recognize him.
Then, Your Grace,
since when did you notice Lin Jun?
At first sight.
Anyone who always wears
a human skin mask
is no good anyway.
This place is heavily guarded.
You can't escape.
Will you make a wish
and let me grant it?
Your Grace, are you not
taking advantage of my plight?
I don't think so.
Believe it or not,
even though I'm here,
I can still break free on my own.
The best part is yet to come.
Be patient and wait.
(Liang)
Wait.
What's wrong? Shouldn't we go?
Are you saying
these are the General's orders?
Exactly.
These are his plans.
Who on earth are you?
A little torture like this
won't get a single word
out of your prisoner.
Are you so immersed
in your role as Lin Jun
that you'd forget your training
at the All-Knowing?
Master Fifteen.
How can you be sure that I'm Fifteen?
Judging by age,
you're Fifteen, Sixteen, or Seventeen.
Sixteen was crippled in an accident.
Seventeen has been missing for ages.
So, you must be Fifteen.
Who are you really?
Who do you think
was present at the Trial?
You probably sneaked
into Shuozhou to investigate
the red bird thing.
The High Priest
is particularly sensitive
to any insult to Aphorisms of Cangshen.
You can't figure out who I am
and you've sensed
Han Lingqiu isn't ordinary.
So you have to stay in Shuozhou
and pass information to Awo'erqi too.
Now, you've captured me,
the commander of Shuozhou.
If his rival Fenglai knows about it,
what will he think?
There's no need to show off
how much you know about North Chong.
Once you're brought to the court,
everything shall be revealed.
How did it feel
to be "Mr. Lin"?
You've spent your entire life
playing all kinds of roles.
I doubt you've ever lived
as a warm and honest man, have you?
Mr. Fifteen,
when you watched Lin Huaide
meet his end beneath the city walls,
did you waver even for a moment?
You deceived so many people.
Was there ever a moment
when you even deceived yourself?
Get more guards here.
Watch him closely.
Yes.
So long as he lives,
he can't use his own name.
What difference does it make if he dies?
Am I right,
Your Grace?
If you keep thinking of him,
you may die too.
General Duan,
you're in the enemy camp.
They will take you
to North Chong.
Right now, Shuozhou
is also in turmoil.
My offer still stands.
Will you state your wish?
I promised to show you a good show.
So, I won't have you
lift a finger.
No shackles in this world
can ever hold me.
I think they'll regret
not having pinned
your shoulder blades.
Night is falling.
It's time to end this show.
Well, as a front-row spectator,
I'll just wait and see.
- Bravo!
- Nice!
Now,
Tabai's commander has been taken alive.
Tomorrow,
we'll seize Shuozhou!
Cangshen, grant us victory
and safe return.
Victory and safe return!
Come on. Drink.
Let's drink.
Sneak attack!
We're under attack!
What's going on?
Here.
He's here.
The Liang intruder!
Catch him!
Take him alive.
And you'll be rewarded.
Yes!
- Where?
- Where's he?
Where's the intruder?
South!
The Liang intruder.
He's to the south.
- South.
- He's to the south.
He's to the south.
Catch him!
He's to the east!
- East.
Search every corner!
You must find that intruder!
Yes.
- No.
- He's not here.
What's he looking for?
Go look over there!
Yes.
Not in the east.
Not in the south, either.
Go search the north.
Yes.
The horse bolted!
Get out of the way!
Fire! Fire!
Put out the fire! Go get water!
- Hurry.
- Fire! Fire!
Put out the fire!
Go get some water!
The tents are on fire. Put it out.
Oh no. The wind is picking up.
It's spreading too fast.
It's too late.
The fire is growing!
Go put it out!
Miss He,
when will the east wind come?
In three days.
That's why he asked me about the wind.
Oh, Foxy.
Get out of the way.
Fire! Put it out!
Get some water! Put it out!
Go get water!
Water.
Give it to me.
Hurry.
General,
our armory is on fire.
The intruder set it.
Darn it!
General,
the Liang man burned our armory.
We haven't found him yet.
General.
Kill him!
Kill!
Put out the fire.
Put it out. Come on.
Water.
Get us some water!
Go put out the fire.
You really didn't see anything?
I saw something.
I saw him enter
the third tent on the left.
However,
he wasn't holding a letter,
but a few goldfish.
Oh, I see.
Arrogant young man.
Duan Xu,
who on earth are you?
Someone from the All-Knowing
can fight a hundred alone
and slay the enemy general
in the heart of their army.
What's so strange about that?
Fifteen,
you got the wrong man.
Han Lingqiu isn't Seventeen.
He should have been dead.
Because he lost to me
in the Trial.
I am
the real Seventeen.
No more waiting.
Otherwise, he will die.
Hey, rally the army.
But...
Look.
It's Xu's signal.
Commandant Wu.
Repel the enemies out there
to at least 50 li further away.
- Yes.
- Captain Meng.
We'll flank the Chong camp
and catch them off guard.
Captain Han,
stay for city defense.
(Oh, I see.)
I graduated at the age of 18
and followed Mentor to meet seniors.
I had just won the Trial,
injured all over.
I almost stumbled
when serving tea to Mentor.
You steadied me.
That was the only time we had ever met.
Am I right,
my senior?
I've always wanted to challenge you.
You deserve punishment
for betraying our mentor!
I've never betrayed anyone.
Because I've never believed in them.
Not even for one single moment.
How ironic.
Someone like you
who abandons his beliefs should die!
Senior,
you wavered in the end.
Otherwise,
how could you make
such a stupid mistake?
Wake up.
You're frantic.
My final mission
was to kill a family of three.
The baby was so young
that I didn't want to kill it.
Mentor found out.
I stabbed out his eyes.
Then, I ran away.
I found a good family
for that baby.
And I...
I then drifted aimlessly
like a rootless duckweed.
♪Cross your legs for three years♪
Kill!
Let's charge in and get the General.
♪Tether horse and ape♪
♪Mind still as water♪
General!
Where's the General?
Find him!
- Yes.
General.
General!
- General.
Did you tell Meng Wan
to come get you?
I told her.
Not to get me,
but to raid the camp.
There's still a long way to go.
We have to keep going.
Yeah.
There's still such a long road ahead.
But I'm...
I'm exhausted.
Someone who lives
a life of torment
finally gets tired.
The deal we talked about...
Could we do it now?
Never mind.
Forget this deal.
Unless you go back
to Shuozhou and see a doctor,
you will die here.
You want to make a deal with me.
You want my five senses
and promise to return them.
Because you've never experienced
the five senses.
Once you experience colors, flavors,
and temperature changes,
will you still wish to lose them?
Is there going to be a day
when you take away all my senses,
keep me alive
at the brink of death,
and turn me into a living corpse?
Even so,
will you still withstand my spell?
Give me your hand.
Give me your hand
and I'll do it.
Seventeen.
Call me Duan Xu.
Duan Xu,
are you still conscious?
Perfectly conscious.
Isn't this fun?
I wager that when that day comes,
you won't wish to do it.
Deal.
Witnessed by the Pearl,
and bonded by blood,
we make this vow.
The stars blaze.
The Fire Star decrees.
- Your senses
- My senses
- are mine.
- are yours.
Bound in heart,
pledged in soul.
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
Kill!
(Liang)
What's wrong?
Is something wrong with me?
Does a killing frenzy
mean something wrong?
Before Fifteen died, he said,
"You're also a monster.
You won't get away."
Sometimes I don't know
whether I'm a normal man
pretending to be mad
or a madman pretending to be normal.
Don't be ridiculous
when you're leaning
on the most abnormal person.
That makes sense.
Don't push it.
Let me go.
You want to know who I am, don't you?
I'm Duan Xu.
My grandfather was a famous scholar.
When I was born,
he was watching a play
by Chunsheng Troupe.
Inspired by the lines,
he gave me this name,
which means "military honor".
When I was twelve,
I was abducted by Chong soldiers.
They threatened my father
to hand over intelligence.
My father not only refused,
but also told them,
"You've got the wrong boy.
This isn't Duan Xu,
my third son.
My real son
has been sent to Daizhou
for his grandmother."
The boy who was sent
to Daizhou
was actually an impostor.
Father, help me!
I prayed countless times
Father would save me.
- Father!
- I won't.
Climb out yourself.
But he never came.
The kidnappers were misled.
I seized the chance to escape
and ended up homeless.
Later,
I was chosen by my mentor,
Chief of the All-Knowing,
who was recruiting disciples.
I joined the All-Knowing.
I am Duan Xu,
Duan Shunxi.
I've never lied to you.
See?
I escaped safely again.
Your Grace,
what is your name?
♪Joys and sorrows of the mortal world♪
He Simu.
H-E, He.
S-I, Si. M-U, Mu.
♪Lingering for a fleeting moment♪
♪Was once touched by laughing tears♪
He Simu.
♪If I could live a simple life♪
Happy new year.
♪I'd be a guest in a sweet dream♪
May you always be safe.
♪Dawn and dusk rise and set♪
♪Longing to meet, yet parted by destiny♪
♪Let me wander through♪
Foxy,
may you survive every crisis.
May you live a long life.
♪Moments may last♪
♪Love and hate will fade away♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪