=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 37=
Great Ancestor,
are you alright?
I know I was wrong.
I was too careless.
I fell for Yan Ke's
diversion stratagem.
From now on,
stay by Duan Xu's side at all times.
Don't let Yan Ke exploit a chance.
Yes.
But
we can't track
Yan Ke again.
The elixir
I gave Duan Xu just now
can only temporarily ease
his blood vomiting.
But his five organs
are damaged.
I can't stop
his body's decline.
I'll return to the Void.
The Spirits Lantern
had become one with you.
If you kill me now,
you will only destroy
the Spirits Lantern and me.
Then your place as the Sovereign
and the woman you can't have
will be buried with me.
I hold the Spirits Lantern's power.
I can help you.
Do I need help
from a mere mortal?
You can't control
the power of the Spirits Lantern.
I need not kill you.
Sooner or later,
you'll face annihilation.
The war is deadlocked for now.
If you can't use the Spirits Lantern,
you can't defeat He Simu.
Teach me to use spirit power;
I'll use the Spirits Lantern for you.
We'll bring down He Simu
and kill Duan Xu.
I'll only teach you
this cultivation method once.
Memorize it.
(Liang)
At the time,
the vanguard squad led by Chenying
was split down the middle
by Chong forces.
Chenying drew the enemy onto himself
to buy time for the main force
to meet the attack.
But every man he took with him
fell in battle,
and not one returned.
This is
the Liang's banner
Chenying died to keep.
This is all my fault.
I should never
have agreed to Chenying
serving as the vanguard.
I brought this upon Chenying.
Xu.
Xu, are you alright?
(Zhaomu Pavilion)
How are things in the Void now?
Bai Sanxing led men through the Void
and seized
nearly all the puppet spirits.
Bai Sanxing has been obedient lately.
Thanks to you controlling him.
He longs to tear Yan Ke apart.
So, he spares no effort
in catching puppet spirits.
The Spirits Lantern
is still with Yan Ke.
Luckily, he can't use it.
There was an accident.
He's found a way
to use the Spirits Lantern indirectly.
How could this happen?
What do we do if this goes on?
No need to worry.
For Yan Ke to use
the Spirits Lantern,
it will still take some time.
Send some Spirit Officials
to the Mortal World
and report back.
The Void's affairs
are in your charge.
I need to enter seclusion.
Enter seclusion?
Why at a time like this?
Gather the medicines
on this list.
(Calculus Bovis, Borneol, Musk)
How strange.
I can't feel anything,
yet in my chest,
it seems to ache.
(Liang)
Xu.
Xiaoxiao just taught me
how to make a sugar figurine.
Taste if it's sweet.
Oh, right.
I'll let Meng try some too.
Han,
I can never get this move right.
Show me again, will you?
It has to reach this spot.
This strike needs force.
Like this.
Xu,
Xiaoxiao is back.
Let's get wine and meat pies.
She loves meat pies.
After she eats, she'll calm down.
Come on.
Come on, Xu.
(Foxy,)
(I won't let you die like this.)
Your Majesty,
Mr. Fang seeks an audience.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Only Duan Xu didn't return to save me.
By now, he should have arrived.
Fang,
why hasn't he returned?
I know little of warfare.
I don't know.
Perhaps some mishap
delayed him.
Duan Shunxi is the Marshal
of the Three Armies,
yet only he did not return.
I know your talent.
But, Fang,
this world never lacks clever men.
What it lacks is the right moment.
You helped Jin save me.
So,
I shall grant you
that moment.
I will prepare an edict for you.
You protected me,
so you are titled Marquis of Zhonghe
and promoted
to Vice Military Commissioner
and Vice Chancellor.
You can decide when this edict
is revealed.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Fang,
do you truly want
to live as Duan Xu's shadow?
(Duan Xu led Great Liang's elite)
(and marched to Youzhou.)
(Liang)
(After months of hard battle,)
(now,)
(of the 17 Prefectures,)
(11 are retaken.)
(Only Youzhou, Fengzhou, Huanzhou,)
(Jingzhou, Yizhou, and Guizhou)
(Liang)
(are held by North Chong.)
On the day I took command
of the Three Armies,
I made it clear to you.
What we seek
is to win battles,
but to safeguard
our people.
The Chong cavalry is fierce.
They once relied
on their cavalry to sweep
all the way south.
They harmed our people,
seized the 17 Prefectures,
and slaughtered our kin.
Now that we stand on this land,
we must not take one step back.
Our army stands here
to defend our own land
and honor the fallen souls.
This is the Liang's banner
Chenying died to keep.
General,
(Liang)
I want to fight on the field
and defend our nation
like you.
Fight for our land!
We must win!
Fight for our land! We must win!
(Liang)
Your Majesty, you cherish the people.
You've raised
pillars of the realm.
Now, policies grace the court;
the Chong forces are quelled.
Prince Jin
will surely not fail
your hopes.
Leave me alone for a while.
Father,
your most timid son
has done all he could.
In this lifetime,
I could not live to see Great Liang
reclaim all lost lands.
I can only die
with regret.
(Three days
after the order returned to Nandu,)
(the Emperor of Liang passed away.)
(The New Emperor ascends the throne.)
(At this time,)
(on the north bank, Duan Xu)
(led the Great Liang Army past Youzhou)
(and smoothly retook)
(Fengzhou, Huanzhou, Jingzhou,
Yizhou and Guizhou.)
Long live Your Majesty.
Young Master, bad news!
Bad news!
Young Master,
thieves broke into the house.
None of the valuables were taken,
but the study was turned upside down.
(The Analects)
I will prepare an edict for you.
You protected me,
so you are titled Marquis of Zhonghe
and promoted
to Vice Military Commissioner
and Vice Chancellor.
You can decide when this edict
is revealed.
(The late emperor's edict)
(is gone.)
You've been
the youngest Top Scholar of all
since Great Liang was founded.
Ever fearful, yet caring for the people,
you bear the virtue of Yan Hui.
Duan Xu
has a noble family behind him
and countless shadows.
Your chance
comes but this once.
This decree of mine
will raise you high
to fulfill your aims.
After Jin ascends the throne,
you will become
his most capable minister.
But to this decree,
I must add one more clause:
Duan Xu failed to arrive in time,
harboring negligence
and treasonous intent.
Upon his return to Nandu,
he must be stripped of his command
and executed.
In all of Great Liang,
he is
the most exceptional general.
But this blade
must stay in my hand.
From this day on,
it must rest with the new emperor.
Mr. Fang.
Miss Duan.
Mr. Fang,
we made extra dumplings at home.
Since you have no family in Nandu,
I wanted
to send some to your place.
- Great.
- Good.
(Yueran Fragrance)
When unrest broke out in Nandu,
I received an anonymous letter.
Thanks to the warning in it,
the Duan clan avoided the turmoil.
Was that letter
from you?
I...
I recognized your handwriting.
So, Miss Duan,
that's why you brought me dumplings.
Actually,
you and Xu must be
quite close, right?
In this world,
others are the ones who owe Xu.
He has never owed anyone.
However,
soon, he will owe me.
Then I'll thank you for him,
Fang Xianye.
Xu.
What is it?
I can't tie this.
In that case,
could you call me brother?
You have not joined my family.
I...
You are
taking advantage of me.
You are not my brother.
Brother.
Your essays
are the finest in the realm.
One day, you'll be the Top Scholar.
(Duan Shunxi)
Prince Ji and Prince Su
raised troops for treason.
Behind them stood
Duke Pei
and Chancellor Du.
As officials of the court,
they should serve the realm,
yet they turned to treason.
Bring up the guilty Yao Jianhe.
The late emperor's edict is here.
(Decree)
This edict represents
the late emperor.
(Decree to Fang Ji and Duan Xu)
The late emperor's edict:
Fang Ji earned merit
protecting the Emperor.
He is made Vice Military Commissioner
and Vice Chancellor.
Duan Xu failed
in protecting the Emperor.
He harbored treasonous intent.
He must be put to death.
It bears the late emperor's seal.
It's absolutely true.
How dare you!
Marshal Duan commands the Three Armies.
He is still fighting
for us at the front.
Your Majesty,
you should execute
such a treasonous rebel
at once.
How dare you!
This is the late emperor's edict.
Do you want
to defy the imperial edict?
Xianye,
if you had such an edict
to aid the rightful ruler
and strike rebels,
why not present it
to His Majesty sooner?
This was your perfect chance
to rise to power.
Mentor,
why are you doing this to me?
Your Majesty,
I'd like to report a matter.
Please punish me.
Yao Jianhe ordered me
to forge
this edict.
Fang Xianye!
Yao Jianhe was my honored teacher.
I could not bear to see him suffer,
so I had no choice but to obey.
What utter nonsense.
Fang Xianye!
You...
You held the late emperor's edict
yet refused to hand it over,
joining Duan Xu in defying
the imperial edict.
I am guilty.
I shouldn't have followed
vile courtiers into treason
just because of the mentorial bond.
Since the late emperor passed away,
he has visited my dreams nightly,
fiercely rebuking me
for framing loyal officials.
I was consumed by dread
and resolved to destroy
the forged edict,
yet it was stolen by the rebel faction.
Your Majesty,
I dare not deceive you.
Nor can I face my honored teacher.
Your Majesty,
please purge the conspirators
and restore the order of the court.
You insolent fool!
Fang Xianye!
Have you lost your mind?
I have committed high treason
by trying to ruin a loyal subject.
My crime is beyond pardon.
Before the late emperor's spirit,
I am too ashamed.
Only death remains for me.
Fang Ji!
This...
Xianye!
(If I make this edict a forged one,)
(Duan Xu may be spared.)
(If I die,)
(there will be no witnesses left.)
(Duan Shunxi,)
(you still owe me in the end.)
Drag this rebel out
for the ultimate punishment.
Yes.
Put it here.
Careful.
These are
Xu's favorite books.
Don't damage any of them.
Yes.
Jingyuan.
Come in.
Keep tidying up.
All right.
Father,
what did you want with me?
What has pleased you so today?
Nandu has been stable lately.
Xu fought at the frontier.
He'll return
with illustrious military merit.
Now, even his greatest rival,
Fang Xianye, is dead.
Someone who should've died long ago
somehow clung to life till now.
My wish is fulfilled.
Now, it is time to settle your future.
Come.
On this list
are eligible noble scions of Nandu,
such as the Grand Master's son
and the Duke of Lu's son.
Though I have retired,
with your Xu in Nandu,
the Duan clan
is still of illustrious standing.
You are my legitimate daughter.
You must marry into a great house
to carry on the Duan clan's honor.
Look over these young men first.
If one suits you,
I'll arrange a marriage proposal.
I don't like them.
You have not even looked yet.
How can you dislike them?
I said it already.
I don't like them.
Was taking over Xu's life
not enough for you?
Now, you want to take over
my life as well?
You...
Suddenly, I miss my younger sister.
You are very much like her.
Me?
♪In silence, I gaze at you♪
♪My hand hangs and then falls♪
♪Let what stays unsaid pass♪
♪Why torture each other like this?♪
♪My wish might be♪
♪Scattering like ripples♪
♪With a gust of wind,
they fade like a dream♪
♪Daylight fades into ash♪
(Yueran Fragrance)
♪For the rest of my life♪
Jingyuan.
May you find a worthy husband,
be blessed with many children,
and live a happy life.
♪Collapse piece by piece♪
Promise me,
all right?
♪And did not dare draw near again♪
♪Leaving all behind♪
♪The sudden pause of words unsaid♪
♪How I long
to hold that silhouette close♪
♪After waking up, we walk back-to-back♪
Milady,
why are you crying?
(Yueran Fragrance)
♪How I long
to hold that silhouette close♪
♪After waking up, we walk back-to-back♪
♪Watching all that is unfinished♪
♪Fade away♪
I have met him
fewer than five times.
Why?
♪In the end,
love is the hardest to resist♪
Why does he grieve me so deeply?
♪Alone, I gather them up♪
♪Like petals in the spring sun♪
♪Till the past falls still again♪
(Yueran Fragrance)
♪The wind returns with my dreams♪
(Liang)
Unexpectedly,
our long-held wish is near.
So many years have passed.
Back then, I drew you into this cause,
yet in the end,
I asked you instead,
"In this world,"
"can things truly go as we hoped?"
You said,
"It doesn't matter."
"We need only try first."
"The deepest night"
"heralds the dawn."
It feels like yesterday.
Xianye.
I spent a lifetime alone.
I lost my parents young.
I had only one confidant
and a girl that I loved for years
and never let her know.
I'll leave the future dawn
for you to see.
I shall
leave first.
Fang Ji.
Fang Ji!
Marshal, urgent word from Nandu.
Marshal,
a message from Nandu.
Prince Jin has taken the throne.
Mr. Fang is dead.
(The forerunner met his end
in the wild.)
Chaos broke out in Nandu.
Prince Su and Prince Ji rebelled.
The late emperor called for aid.
But the court messenger
never reached here.
Now, His Majesty has learned
that the Pei faction
framed you on purpose.
(To Shunxi, From Xianye)
Fang Xianye, Vice Minister of Revenue,
drafted a fake edict to accuse you.
After it was exposed,
he died by striking a pillar.
(Shunxi,)
(Nandu is now at peace.)
(No need to worry.)
(I have not seen you in many years.)
(How brief a life is.)
(We've parted for so long.)
(Our paths differ with the same aim.)
(Now, my task is done.)
(Death is enough for me.)
(It concerns no one else.)
(Life is full of uncertainties.)
(When you reclaim the land,)
(please pour wine to tell me.)
Marshal.
Marshal!
Physician!
(I lived a lonely life.)
(You are)
(my only kin,)
(my dearest friend,)
(and my true confidant.)
(From: Xianye)
This time, I can do no more.
I've sent word to Great Ancestor.
I only hope she can
bring the medicine back asap.
Great Ancestor.
You nearly died.
Simu.
Simu,
Fang Xianye...
Fang Xianye took his own life.
Take me to him.
I need to see him.
Duan Shunxi.
When I was taken to North Chong,
my father forced Fang Xianye back
to stand in for me.
After I returned,
my father nearly silenced him.
He had every reason
to hate the Duan clan,
but he never once
mentioned it to me.
If we had not shared the same cause,
Fang Xianye and I
should have been enemies.
I had always thought
that once the war was over,
I would place everything
in his hands.
Yet he left before I could.
Now that I think on it,
how can I be sure
that what I set out to do
will never come to nothing?
Flesh and blood
can't withstand fate's turns.
Duan Shunxi,
your light will also fade one day.
Fang Xianye
only went before you.
You're just a mortal.
Look at me.
I haven't learned to accept parting
for 400 years.
Fang Xianye died with no regrets
but a clear conscience.
He would not blame you.
He'd be glad that he met you,
so he could become himself again.
Just remember him.
(Fang Ji,)
(in your next life, don't meet)
(someone as troublesome as me.)
(Live more lightly,)
(and go find your own joy.)
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪