( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(Previously) P'Toh is such a magnet.
Did you see those customers today?
The guy who bumped into him this morning.
He was top-tier.
The guy talking to the owner is Freeze.
You can see it from
Mars—he's hitting on him.
Someone's hitting on your Mama today.
He's a dentist, no less.
Can you please tell your brother?
Since I've broken up with him,
I've always missed him.
I've never seen him this broken before.
When he wakes up, tell him to leave.
I don't want to see his face.
P'Toh, P'Toh, P'Toh, P'Toh!
P'Toh, my ass! It's me!
Thanks for bringing me home.
I didn't bring you home.
I woke up and you were gone.
You didn't pick up your phone.
I was worried you'd died from
a car crash, so I had to come check.
Lucky for you the door was unlocked.
That's why your "saint" of a friend
is here making you food.
So...
how exactly did I get back here?
Okay, what do you remember?
I remember...
going out.
And then... a bunch of
guys were hitting on me.
Skip that part, please.
I don't want to hear it.
That's pretty much it.
Unbelievable…
You don't remember me
risking my life to save you?
Breaking my back
carrying you to my house?
I went to your house?
I thought you were still mad at me.
I'm just a "good friend." End of story.
Eat this here or somewhere else?
(There.)
Was I so wasted... that I
blacked out completely?
Thanks.
Next time, don't drink
yourself into a coma.
You won't get this lucky every night.
Wait...
how did you know I was there?
I have my spies.
They told me you were drinking alone
like you were trying to buy the whole bar.
They asked me to come pick up your "corpse."
Teh…
Please help me get back with your brother.
You don't call this "helping" already?
What do you mean by that?
You're getting stupider by the day, moron.
If I was still mad at you, I wouldn't
have taken you to my house
or looked after you like this.
Me not standing in your way
is already a huge help. Get it?
I get it, friend.
Now, it's all up to you how
you're going to win him back.
And most importantly...
What?
Telling P'Toh you love
him through me is useless.
If you truly love him, you
need to say it to his face.
And prove it.
That's all I can say.
I'm out.
"Love Alert"
(Episode 8)
Thank you so much, P'Freeze.
For taking me to the
exhibition and driving me home.
It's my pleasure. I'm
just glad you enjoyed it.
So, are you heading back now?
Or would you like to stay for dinner?
I'd love to stay and try your cooking.
Give me a few minutes then.
Please, make yourself at home.
Do you want some help?
It'll be faster that way.
Sure.
This brand…
P'Toh?!
P'Freeze!
Oh, you can tell I rarely cook.
Well, you're a doctor, not a chef.
You're ucky it's just a small cut.
I told you to just sit and wait.
I just really wanted to help you.
I'll help you.
All done.
I really like you.
Would you like to try dating me?
What did you answer?
What did you tell Dr. Freeze?
I told him...
I need some time to think.
Good move. If you say yes too fast,
he might think you're an easy catch.
Stop being so overprotective.
They're not kids anymore. There's no
need to play hard to get.
I just...
I don't want to see him heartbroken again.
No way.
Please don't compare
the doctor to your "trashy" friend.
P'Toh, I'm rooting for
this guy with all I've got.
He's got the personality and the profile.
Don't let him slip away.
You're hyping him up too much.
You haven't even talked to him yet.
From what I've heard, he
checks every single box.
Usually, guys like that invite you to clubs,
get you wasted, or look for a one-night stand.
But him? He visits the café
every day, morning and evening.
He takes you to art galleries you love
and even helps with the cooking.
Why aren't you picking up? Who is it?
It's Jimmy.
Don't you dare pick up. It's obvious
he's calling to beg for you back.
But he hasn't contacted me
in ages. This is the first time.
P'Toh.
I'll just take it.
I want to know what's going on.
If he starts with the
same old excuses, I'll just hang up.
Hello?
What?! Saensee is sick?!
Saensee, baby.
Are you sick? Does it hurt?
What's wrong, hm?
Let Mama see.
P'Toh,
he really wasn't okay a moment ago.
Maybe he just missed his "Mama."
Now that you're here, he's much better.
P'Toh.
Why do we have to wait out here?
Why can't we go in?
P'Toh is just checking on the cat.
You don't even like
cats, why bother going in?
I don't mind that.
I'm just worried P'Toh will give in!
Whoa!
Where are you going?!
To get P'Toh. Jimmy
will start acting clingy.
You know that I'm rooting for Dr. Freeze.
You don't have to go. Stay here.
Give him some time. He's got a chance.
What chance?
You're acting suspicious.
Spill it now, or tell me through tears.
I know.
The one who brought me home…
was you.
P'Toh…
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Please forgive me.
P'Toh…
I'm so sorry, P'Toh…
Do you miss me, Saensee?
I brought you some treats.
Let's leave your "Dad" to sleep, shall we?
You were worried about me, right?
That's why you brought me home.
I brought you here
because I didn't want to wake up
and see you in my house.
And I'm here today
because you lied about Saensee.
I care about the cat,
not you.
This will be the only time I believe you.
Don't ever use Saensee to lie to me again.
I hate it.
P'Toh!
I'm so sorry.
I messed up.
Please give me one more chance.
Time's up, Jimmy.
When it's over, it's over.
“Once we're done, never show your face
to me again. Not even as friends.”
You told me to remember your words.
I love you, P'Toh!
How could you do this, Teh?!
I'm sorry.
Jimmy hurt P'Toh so
many times, and you knew it.
Now, you're taking his
side, not your brother's?
It was my fault. He looked like a
kicked puppy. I just felt bad for him.
You want to see P'Toh heartbroken again?
That will never happen again.
Saensee is fine. Let's go.
What about Jimmy?
I came to visit Saensee, not its owner.
Get in the driver's seat.
Get in.
Saensee,
your Mama's so mean.
I tried my best.
He was so stubborn.
What the hell was that for?
Honestly, I wanted to kick you.
Consider the slap a courtesy.
I should've never helped you. Fah has been
chewing me out and won't even let me cuddle him.
I regret getting involved in your mess.
Come on, man.
It's just a little scolding
from your boyfriend.
Please?
For the sake of your
brother and your friend's love.
- Please?
- Let go.
Come on,
please keep helping me.
I'm almost there.
P'Toh is about to forgive me.
Please, please. Pretty please?
I said let go!
The only one who's moving on is my brother.
Listen.
That dentist customer
already asked P'Toh to be his boyfriend.
Damn!
And what did P'Toh say?
"Let me think about it."
See?
P'Toh still has feelings for me.
Your ego never drops, does it?
Listen to me carefully.
Dr. Freeze is polite,
mature, and has a stable life.
He's not a player, and
he's a total green flag.
To put it simply: you're no match for him.
It sounds like you're insulting me.
I'm not.
I'm telling you to prepare
for disappointment.
Think about it.
The "green flag" guy is
hitting on him every single day.
It's only a matter of time
before P'Toh says yes.
Wow.
Did you really knit this yourself?
I made this specially for you.
Is there anything you can't do?
I'm not your boyfriend yet.
You never miss an opening, do you?
I have to. I'm scared
someone might cut in line.
Has your heart softened even a little bit?
I'm not talking to you anymore.
I'd better get back to making coffee.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Should I keep going or stop?
A guy like me never begs.
This is ruining my reputation.
But I miss him.
What should I do?
Jim.
Yyou okay, man? You're so heartbroken
you've started talking to yourself?
I'm practicing for my presentation!
Cut the crap! Exams are
over! What presentation?!
Man,
this is the first time I've seen
"Jimmy the Player" lose his cool like this.
Just keep barking!
You think I'm the one who got dumped?
I'm always the one who
gets bored and ends things.
You saw me the other day,
I didn't go to beg him.
I went straight back to
drink with you guys, remember?
You're bluffing. I saw you
daydreaming about him.
Yep.
Just admit you got dumped.
We won't tease you. We're all grown-ups.
Wanna bet?
If you see me begging for him back,
you can take my money.
Because a guy like me...
never begs.
Deal.
You said it yourself.
Hello, what would you like to have?
Hot Americano, please.
P'Toh, can you draw
something on my cup too?
Here is your coffee, P'Freeze.
Thank you, Toh.
P'Freeze, let's go outside for a bit.
I just need some fresh air.
Saensee.
Saensee,
Mama won't even talk to me.
Saensee, where are you?
There you are.
Your scent is starting to fade, P'Toh.
Yes! I passed!
That happy? Did you get a perfect score?
Just barely made it.
If it was a full score, I'd
be setting off fireworks.
How about you?
Whoa!
Straight A's!
Even for the midterms!
Beautiful... and brilliant.
An honors degree is calling your name.
I like that. Lunch is on me.
I'm gonna drain your wallet dry.
You've got the nerve?
It wouldn't be me if...
Teh!
This is bad!
Jim is down!
He's totally out.
But we have a meeting with the professor.
Can you watch him?
Go ahead.
I've got him.
Thanks, man.
P'Toh...
P'Toh, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry. I messed up.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry!
You moron!
Teh?!
- It's you?!
- Yeah, who else?
Why are you wiping me down?
Because you're sick, you idiot.
I'll do it myself.
I want them to have a partner.
How's my cooking?
Instant porridge with hot water.
I'm so "indebted" to your kindness, friend.
Hey, be glad I even bothered.
Does P'Toh know I'm sick?
Yeah, I texted him.
He knows... but he's not coming.
P'Toh, I'm sorry.
I messed up.
Please forgive me.
Why are you showing me this?
One of you is my brother, the other
is my best friend. I love you both.
Look…
I've done my best as
a friend and a brother.
How you choose is entirely up to you.
Okay?
I'm sorry, P'Toh.
I won't do it again.
Please forgive me.
Please…
forgive me.
I messed up, P'Toh.
Teh, why are you here so late?
Is everything okay?
It's nothing.
I just missed you and need a hug.
Are you okay?
You're worried about P'Toh again?
Yeah.
I hate seeing him like this.
He acts so...
emotionless.
Listen,
P'Toh is a grown-up now.
He has the right to make his own choices.
Our job is just to stay by his side.
Comfort him when he's sad,
and be happy when he's happy.
Fah,
I love you.
I love you too.
Stop stressing out, okay?
Smile.
That was a quick change of mood.
I just couldn't help myself.
Well...
Fine.
Hey,
thanks for coming to check on me.
Oh, man.
In all the years I've known you,
you've never been sick.
We have to see how
you are with our own eyes.
Where's your boyfriend?
Isn't he here to nurse you?
They broke up. Why would
he come back for him?
Oh, I thought you went
to beg for his forgiveness.
He told us he ended it
because he was bored.
Oh, Mr. Bad Boy.
Oh,
Big Boss Jimmy says If he ever
goes back to beg for that guy,
he has to pay us big time.
He made a bet with us.
Hey, hey, hey.
A guy like me never begs. And I've
never fallen in love with anyone either.
Toh?
You asked me to come here urgently.
Is everything okay?
I have an answer for you.
Regarding what?
About you asking me to be your boyfriend.
Do you still want to be with me?
Of course I do.
What's your...
My answer is “yes.”
A guy like me never begs. And I've
never fallen in love with anyone either.
But with P'Toh, it's completely different.
I miss him so much.
I want to hold him...
smell his scent...
and hear his voice again.
You love him.
I do.
I love him so much.
Then why the hell are you telling us?
Go tell him.
What are you waiting for?
Go get him back!
And don't forget to pay us.
You said it yourself, remember?
(Next Episode) I truly love your brother.
But I don't want to cause any more trouble...
for anyone.
If you'd acted like this from the start,
you'd probably be happy with him by now.
I'm going to see P'Toh.
I'll ask for one last chance.
I got the scholarship to study in England.
Come with me, Toh.
England...?