(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
[electronic beeping]
[woman 1] They could've told me
to wear running shoes.
They knew I'd be walking a lot.
[breathless] Instead,
they said to dress up nicely.
What is this? Where am I?
Ow, my legs hurt.
[sighs] This is awful.
[woman 2] Ms. Cha Mu-hee,
we're turning the mic on now.
[sighs] About time. Jeez.
Please hold up the selfie-cam now.
[breathes deeply]
[sighs]
This looks good?
These damn heels are scuffed.
Hey, sorry. Is my manager around?
[man] What's up, Mu-hee? I'm here.
Were these shoes on loan,
or were they bought?
They are a loan.
Make sure to take care of them.
Oh, okay.
[uplifting pop music playing]
Wow!
[uplifting pop music continues]
[man] Follow Cha Mu-hee
just like that. Got it?
[uplifting pop music continues]
Drone one,
find a closer opening shot of Ms. Cha.
Producer Park,
the interpreter's connected?
It's all set and prepped. Mr. Joo.
- Welcome.
- [Mr. Joo] Hello. Thank you.
- Let's have the camera…
- [woman 1] It's ready.
[woman 2] Mr. Joo, are you ready to go?
Yes. I'm set in place.
[uplifting pop music continues]
[music stops]
[Mu-hee] Whoa,
this castle's really high up.
Once there was a king
who owned all this land
while he lived in this castle.
- [gasps]
- [distant bell ringing]
It must've been really nice to look down
and know all this belongs to you.
[sighs]
This property is huge.
Don't press your body on that railing.
Oh?
Mr. Joo, you're speaking to me
while we're shooting?
Are you worried
that I may be blown away, by any chance?
It's on the numerous signs right by you.
[speaking Italian]
[in English] "Do not lean
or climb on the railing."
I was only translating it.
[melodic Italian music playing]
What about those that don't know Italian?
- Should be in English too.
- [music stops]
It's written in English, below.
You just didn't see it.
I was looking at… the view
and other things.
That isn't English.
That's German.
The English is underneath.
[lively German music playing]
Oh. This place must attract tourists
from around the world.
The ones who know how to read
every sign are the oddballs.
- [music stops]
- Hmm.
I'm glad today's the last day of filming.
I practiced my speech in Japanese earlier.
I'll say it to Hiro,
so there's no need to translate.
No problem.
Let's follow the leading man now.
[soothing pop music playing]
[Hiro speaking Japanese]
[in English] "Such a gorgeous day."
"I'm glad the weather's working out
on our last day."
"I wanted us to shoot here."
[Hiro speaking Japanese]
[Mr. Joo in English] "The view
over there's even better. Let's go."
You've been here before?
[Mr. Joo translating in Japanese]
[Hiro speaking Japanese]
[Mr. Joo in English] "When I started out
as an actor, I was very green."
"I made a lot of mistakes."
"The lines from that… that movie
will stay with me forever."
"I didn't know what I was doing."
Oh, forever?
Was it awkward?
Is it on YouTube? I wanna see it!
[Hiro in Japanese]
Please don't look it up.
I really don't want to remember.
What was it again?
"Cringewar"?
"Cringeworth"?
[in English] Uh… uh, what?
Oh! Cringeworthy?
- [in Japanese] That's it! Cringeworthy.
- [in English] It's cringeworthy.
[laughter]
Wow, they've really hit it off
since we started filming.
I know, right?
Shooting's almost over,
and they're basically the best of buddies!
[laughter]
[music fades]
[sighs]
[speaking Japanese]
[Mr. Joo in English] "So beautiful.
It makes me wanna keep looking forever."
- [soothing music playing]
- Yeah, sure.
[sighs]
We've seen many magical
and special places.
It's so sad it's nearly over.
What a bummer.
[in Japanese] I agree.
I would like…
to keep seeing you.
[music fades]
I think the reason every moment
of our journey has been beautiful…
is that you
were a part of the scenery.
[romantic music playing]
[in English] I'm ready.
What did he say? Translate?
Is it time to say goodbye?
I've prepared a whole speech for Hiro.
[in Japanese] Mr. Joo,
if you were too shocked
to interpret what I just said,
can you just pass on
these words to her?
[romantic music continues]
[speaking Japanese]
[in English] Mr. Joo, please translate.
If you don't tell me what he said,
I can't say my prepared farewell speech.
A farewell might not be necessary.
I'll translate his speech.
He asked me to pass on this…
"I need
Cha Mu-hee to know that I adore her."
Have you heard me?
Have you received the message, Mu-hee?
[music fades]
[lively music playing]
CAN THIS LOVE BE TRANSLATED?
JAPAN
[woman on radio] It's Monday, April 8th,
and here is the weather forecast.
It'll be mostly sunny throughout
the majority of the country today.
In the morning, rain's expected
in the Southern Kanto region,
but the sky will clear up,
and it'll be sunny.
1 YEAR AGO, APRIL
[lively music continues]
[host speaking Japanese]
[in English] Let's listen to Mr. Kim,
who has an impressively large
fan base all over Japan.
Yes, I'm very excited to bring,
uh… this book, my novel,
to my Japanese readers and my great fans.
I'm truly hoping you enjoy reading it
and it resonates
with everyone who reads it.
Thank you very much.
[translating in Japanese]
[host speaking Japanese]
[in English] They'll open it for questions
from the foreign press.
Many of your fans showed up.
- [laughs] You saw that? I'm very popular.
- [music fades]
You're the only one
who sees my faults, so…
And I keep my mouth shut.
Thanks for coming with me
and interpreting for this old man
these past few days.
I had a great time with you.
Here.
The publisher gave it to me.
They're so great at giving gifts.
[laughs]
You're passing the gift they got for you?
In a month or so,
a man from a Japanese magazine
is coming to Seoul.
I'd like you to be my translator then.
I won't be in Seoul, so I can't.
I'm sorry. I'm all booked up.
Oh, because you're going
to be in Spain, right?
Yeah. I won't be back in Seoul
for a few months.
Oh no, that won't work.
You're the only one
who interprets my gibberish well,
no matter how much crap I spew.
Mm, so you must delay your trip for me.
Could you?
Hey, isn't it enough that you dragged
a busy person to Japan and put me to work?
That's too big of an ask, sir.
So, we'll go for sushi at the airport
and a drink.
Mr. Kim, listen.
You need to cut out your drinking.
You confused the protagonist's names
at the talkback.
The husband of the main character
is Nam Hyeon-su. It's not Park In-cheol.
Was Yeong-suk's first husband,
Nam Hyeon-su?
The one who wrote it doesn't know?
I was shocked,
but had to contain it while translating.
All right, I hear you. You roll with it.
I'll treat you, then. Let's go, okay?
The next time, buy me sushi.
I have things to do
while I'm still in town.
Really?
You're going somewhere nice alone?
Really? Meeting someone?
Going on a date?
Mr. Kim, I hope you have a safe trip back.
You're going on a date, aren't you?
[laughs] I was concerned
you had no luck in love whatsoever.
If you're going on a date,
share those cookies with her!
- They're sweet!
- [chuckles]
[soothing melodic music playing]
[lively jazz music playing]
[woman on PA] To transfer
from the JR Line to the Enoden Line,
put your ticket
into the turnstile and exit.
Then turn right,
and you'll see the central square.
Keep walking past the square.
When you reach the platform sign,
go through the left turnstile.
[lively jazz music playing]
- Oh, sorry, sorry. Sorry.
- Sorry.
[lively jazz music playing]
[knocking on door]
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
The leaflets in Korean
seem to have run out.
- Oh, sorry. I'll get them for you now.
- Thanks so much.
[lively jazz music playing]
[woman on PA] Thanks for waiting.
The train will be around shortly.
For your safety,
please stand behind the yellow line.
[train horn blows]
[music stops]
[indistinct chattering in Italian]
- [indistinct chattering in Italian]
- [both chuckle]
[chattering in Italian continues]
[soothing melodic music playing]
- [clatter]
- Oh.
[in Italian] Paolo,
stop messing around, please.
[in English] I'm sorry.
[in Italian] It's all right.
He didn't do it on purpose.
Wow! You speak Italian.
We've never met a Japanese person
who speaks Italian.
I'm not Japanese. I'm Korean.
- [man] Really?
- [woman] Oh, Korean?
- Have you ever been to Italy?
- [Mr. Joo] Yes, I have.
[in English] "Hashtag, Momo-chan Ramen."
"Hashtag, a new beginning."
"Hashtag, grateful to you."
"Hashtag, I promise to make you so happy."
[music fades]
[sighs]
[waitress in Japanese] Excuse me.
The food is hot. Here you go.
[customer 1] Thank you.
[waitress] Let me know
if you need anything.
[woman in Italian] Can kids eat this?
[Mr. Joo] Yes, but kids
might find it a bit spicy.
[waitress in Japanese] Welcome.
Please sit anywhere you'd like.
Ma'am?
- Please.
- [chair rattles]
Excuse me.
Here's our menu.
[in English] Are you Momo-chan,
the owner of Momo-chan Ramen?
[phone translation in Japanese]
[in Japanese] Yes.
One Momo-chan Ramen coming right up.
Excuse me.
[in Italian] I would recommend
that you order… this.
[woman] Okay, thank you. [chuckles]
[in English] She looks younger
in real life, huh?
[footsteps approaching]
[chair rattles]
I came to find a South Korean man
who wants a fresh start with you.
He wants to rebuild
his whole life with you.
[phone translation in Japanese]
[volume lowers]
[jaunty music playing]
[in English] No. The male voice sounds
like a news anchor.
There could be an option to maybe change
the tone, to make it a little tougher?
[Chinese music plays]
Mm, he's Chinese?
I thought he might be Korean.
[jaunty music resumes]
Let's see if I can make
your voice female, then.
It's very important you translate well.
Can this app curse?
Fuck.
Fuck bitch.
[phone alert in Korean]
Kakao Talk.
Could he be from…
[mysterious music playing]
Do you understand?
[music fades]
You do. You're Korean?
I didn't wanna eavesdrop--
It must have been fun
to pretend to be Chinese.
I never pretended that I was Chinese.
Yes, you did.
You're reading that pamphlet in Chinese.
I'm not pretending. I read them.
I collect language brochures.
English, French, Italian
to practice and keep updated.
Don't be ridiculous.
You're a Papago app on legs?
Look, I have…
[woman] Paolo!
[Paolo coughs]
Paolo!
[in Italian] Our son!
Please call an ambulance.
We don't speak Japanese.
What happened to him?
He has an allergy.
Something in his snack earlier
must have triggered a reaction.
[in Japanese] An ambulance.
Please tell them
a boy is having an allergic reaction.
Okay.
- [coughs]
- [in Italian] What snack did he eat?
Here.
[uneasy music playing]
This one.
You'd better take this with you
to the hospital.
Okay.
[in Japanese] I called an ambulance.
But the alleyway here is narrow.
It may be a while before they arrive.
[in Italian] She says
the alley's too narrow,
so the ambulance might take a while.
- I'll carry him to the main street.
- Okay, honey.
Uh, I'll carry him.
- Thank you.
- [man] Thank you.
[in Japanese] Tell the ambulance
to meet us at the main street entrance.
[Momo] Okay.
[in English] I'll look after
your belongings.
Thank you very much.
[uneasy music continues]
He must be Papago, for real.
[animated tense music playing]
[in Italian] Excuse me.
I let the paramedics know
what's going on with Paolo.
Give me a call if you need
additional interpretation at the hospital.
Thank you so much.
- [in Japanese] Take care of him.
- Got it.
[voice from ambulance]
Turning left soon. Please be careful.
[siren blares]
[in English] Thank you.
I'll take my things.
[Mu-hee] Uh…
Can you help me, please?
This is a big emergency.
The Papago app was my first choice,
but a human voice would be better
'cause AI… AI can't be heartfelt
in authentic ways.
A lover's quarrel isn't something
I wanna be a part of.
I knew it. You heard everything.
- Fuck bitch.
- F…
You heard me curse too, didn't you?
I didn't mean to.
Using a stupid AI to win the man I love
would be very wrong.
So please help me.
Getting dumped is bad enough.
But through Papago, it's even worse.
Okay, fine. I'll volunteer.
Just… no swear words. Not with me.
[speaking Japanese]
[in English] Mr. Yu-jin went to Tokyo,
so he's not here.
Went to Tokyo?
He knew I was coming and went into hiding?
I wonder if those two
might be lying to me.
- [whimsical music playing]
- Well, but you want me to say that?
Please, don't.
Could she tell us when he'll return?
[speaking Japanese]
[in English] She can ask his girlfriend
to come out and talk.
What?
[Momo in Japanese] Eiko,
can you come out here for a moment?
[in English] She's… she's not the one
he wants to pursue.
But… but it fits!
[jaunty music playing]
He uploaded a photo of her
with a hashtag "new start."
I mean, tell me that's not her?
You picked the wrong one.
Wait.
Oh no.
I thought he was with the younger one.
[music fades]
[Momo sighs]
Oh. Well, no.
Could you ask her, please,
how far along she is?
[speaking Japanese]
[in English] Seven months along.
He left me almost three months ago.
Seven?
[sighs] I'm so crazy. What a…
What a fucking bastard!
[door opens]
[in Japanese] Excuse me.
Is she Ms. Cha Mu-hee?
Uh, probably.
I have something I'd like to say to her.
Could you pass it on for me?
[sighs]
[Mr. Joo in English] Wait!
Excuse me!
[Mu-hee sighs]
I got something for you to translate.
At this restaurant,
the chef is a hashtag two-timing cheater,
man whore, and a pathetic jerk!
Cheaters must die.
You there. I curse you,
and I hope your business closes!
I won't translate profanity or curses
that might hurt others.
I don't wanna be involved further.
The woman back there
asked me to tell you this.
[intriguing music playing]
[in Japanese] The father of my child
is my ex-husband, not Yu-jin.
[chuckles] Even though
I knew it was selfish,
I wanted to rely on his kindness.
But if Ms. Cha Mu-hee
is able to change his mind,
I'd happily let him go.
[music fades]
[in English] She said I could have him?
Maybe you misunderstood?
I heard exactly what she said to me.
Why would she…
Maybe she's playing a trick on me
by saying that, and she's…
What does she actually want?
I repeated what she told me.
I mean, why would she say that to you?
It's just so weird.
Um, why would she be nice
when her life sucks?
I only pass on what people say.
I don't judge them
or think about their meaning.
Oh, fine. Then I'll go back for more info.
- Come, Papago.
- That's enough!
Cha Mu… Mu-hee?
It seems that man and you broke up,
so there was no… no infidelity.
The baby isn't even his.
The two of them must be--
In love?
That's what you're saying?
- I hate that.
- Exactly.
You make this anything more,
and you'll be the bad guy.
If I'm a crazy bitch,
that's none of your concern.
- I need you to interpret for me.
- I don't want to, Mu-hee.
If you wanna be crazy or bad,
that's on you.
I'm not gonna take part
in hurting someone.
You don't need an interpreter
to have your misguided anger
accurately conveyed.
Might as well use a language
that's universal.
Best of luck to you.
You've said you wouldn't judge me,
yet I'm somehow the villain?
[melancholy music playing]
Their love's good and pure,
so everybody else can go to hell, right?
He told me it was over for good.
Then he was gone.
He's done this before,
so I thought he'd return.
Then three months later, he shared a post
talking about a fresh start.
So I came here to find him.
You can judge it as crazy,
but this is love too.
I don't want to end it like this.
Just help me finish this
with a little dignity.
I ask you to translate for love.
Please help.
- [in Japanese] Hey, Yu-jin.
- [music fades]
Yes, everything is fine here.
You'll be back tonight?
[chuckles]
No, I wouldn't want you to hurry.
Come back tomorrow as scheduled.
Yes.
Okay, see you tomorrow.
[disconnect tone]
[knocking at door]
[sighs] Sorry, but we're closed…
[in English] I see
that you might have a kind heart.
But well, there's something
I need to ask you.
[translating in Japanese]
[in English] When your boyfriend
and I were together,
from time to time,
he would disappear on me and
leave me for weeks on end.
Was he spending time with you instead?
[Mr. Joo translating in Japanese]
[scoffs softly]
[in English] Wow! So, I'm right.
But, of course,
he betrayed me and cheated a lot.
[Eiko speaking Japanese]
[in English] He comforted her
and helped in her time of need.
Well, she can't say
the man's a saint for cheating.
He's helping because she's a charity case?
Maybe he held on
because he feels sorry for her.
[jaunty music playing]
I'm assuming you're saying things
out of anger,
and I won't translate them to her.
Please be kind and keep some dignity.
[Mu-hee clears throat]
Still, though,
he returned to me afterwards.
But now he'll feel stuck with the baby
and you both clinging to him.
And, no,
I wouldn't even bother taking him back.
Since you've refused to translate,
tell her, "Congratulations."
Your love's off to a bad start, but I, uh…
I wish you the best.
[music stops]
[speaking Japanese]
[in English] There's something
she wants to explain to you.
[in Japanese] Actually,
Yu-jin and I have been dating
since he was studying in Japan.
But his heart was stolen by another woman.
She was abandoned by her family
and had no one to turn to,
helpless in a miserable situation.
It was as if
she was the tragic heroine of a movie,
weighed down by a burden of misery.
Every time, I would try to make him stay,
but he still left,
saying he couldn't leave her alone.
[in English] Who
is she talking about?
[translating in Japanese]
That woman is you.
[in English] Tell me what she said.
Please tell me.
[Eiko in Japanese] The one
who used their misery to be loved
is you.
[melancholy music playing]
Even after realizing her man betrayed her,
she still came all this way. [laughs]
She must have been really lonely
to throw away her pride like this.
- [in English] Just, well--
- Don't translate, Papago.
I refuse
to understand this woman's words
and give her any satisfaction.
So what do you want?
[sighs]
I'm not sure.
Oh no, I think I'm about to cry.
If I cry in front of that woman,
I'll die of humiliation.
[music fades]
[inspirational music playing]
Just stay like this.
I'll work it out gracefully
as much as I can.
[in Japanese] There seems to be
a misunderstanding.
She and I are traveling together.
We just dropped by to say hello.
The two of you are traveling together?
We brought a gift from Tokyo.
She was just trying to be polite,
yet you have been incredibly rude.
What you just said will stay with me.
I won't pass along any words
that may hurt her.
[in English] Once you feel better,
let's get up.
[breathes deeply]
[chair rattles]
[jaunty music playing]
[music stops]
[jaunty music resumes]
[music fades]
Thank you.
You helped me a lot today.
Oh. Oh, I got foundation on you.
Uh, it's fine.
That gift must have been expensive.
I'll pay you. How much?
Don't worry. I got it as a gift too.
Are you sure?
I feel bad. Really.
Maybe we can have some food together?
My treat.
No, but what I meant was…
- Let's put it behind us.
- All right.
I wish you the best.
And also, I wanted to thank you
and say sorry for today.
Enjoy your stay!
[in Japanese] Thank you.
[Eiko] She still came all this way.
She must have been really lonely
to throw away her pride like this.
[melancholy music playing]
- [in Italian] Thanks.
- Thank you.
[melancholy music continues]
[Mr. Joo in English] Is she a woman
weighed down by her past?
Doesn't seem like she is.
[music fades]
[man in Japanese] Here you go.
Thanks.
[phone ringing]
[gasps]
[in English] You there!
Excuse me! Hey, Mr. Papago!
- Your phone. I have it and forgot to--
- What is it now?
- A call just came.
- Yes?
- From a foreigner.
- Oh.
Hello?
[in Italian] Yes, hello.
[woman] My son is fine,
thanks to your help.
Thank you so much.
I'm glad to hear that.
We'd like to give you a gift as thanks.
No, there's no need.
We had a dinner reservation,
but we won't be able to go
as we need to stay at the hospital.
The reservation is for two people.
If the person who answered
is a friend of yours,
you could go with her.
Right, friend.
The reservation was hard to get,
and it's already paid for.
We'd love for you to go.
Okay, then. I will.
Thank you very much.
Yes. Okay, thank you.
Goodbye.
[disconnect tone]
[in English] Were you speaking Italian?
Yes.
Was it about that kid at the restaurant?
He's okay?
Thankfully. He's feeling a lot better.
Good. I'm glad he's fine.
If I hadn't taken your phone by mistake,
you would have been in a pickle.
It's your lucky day today.
Cha Mu-hee.
Uh, do you have any plans
for this afternoon?
Well, I came and did what I had to do.
You were there. Why?
Perhaps you would like
to have dinner together?
[romantic pop music playing]
- I invited you, and you said no.
- I never said no.
I just… I didn't see the point
in being together.
Why do you want to now?
Those Italian tourists with the child
gifted me a dinner reservation
they made earlier for two.
- It would be a waste, otherwise.
- That would be unfortunate.
- Must be expensive?
- Probably.
♪ I heard it in the sky… ♪
I'll be doing you a favor
if I say yes and join you.
♪ I greet the breeze… ♪
I'm the one who helped you,
but you're making it sound like
you're helping me out instead, right?
Well, having yummy food
is not the same experience
when eating alone.
Okay? Let's share a taxi.
The reservation is at 7:00.
Oh.
[inhales]
Should we go and then meet
in front of the place at 7:00?
♪ One quiet voice
Answers them in gentle word… ♪
Let's spend time together.
Until dinner, if that's okay.
Sure. What do you wanna do?
♪ Round and round… ♪
Sightseeing. Take a look around.
Like good tourists.
[Mu-hee] Hey. I forgot to ask you earlier.
What's your name?
Joo Ho-jin.
[Mu-hee] Mr. Joo Ho-jin,
it's nice to meet you.
[train crossing sounding]
- I'm Cha Mu-hee.
- I remember.
- [laughs]
- It's nice to meet you, Ms. Cha Mu-hee.
♪ I feel the love in the morning sun ♪
♪ But why am I blue… ♪
We're heading to Enoshima next.
Let's go!
Okay! Let's go, everyone!
♪ My life just goes on ♪
♪ I greet the breeze ♪
♪ And nod to the trees ♪
♪ I hear the winds reply ♪
NA JIN-SUK
You're an actress?
Does that make you a celebrity?
No. Not all actors are celebrities.
Not even close.
A few, maybe.
Like, 5% in the industry.
Either way,
look me up on the Internet.
- Mm!
- What? Oh.
Wow, you've been in many things.
You've done a lot.
What? You had a role in the movie, Crooks?
Now you're wondering
what role I played, right?
I get it. It was a small part. Tiny.
I felt kind of embarrassed
to put it on my résumé.
The CEO of my agency asked
to put it online. Now you can find it.
It's a credit to be proud of.
Over ten million people watched it.
Well, nobody remembers me in it at all.
The film may have been a huge hit
with a festive firework celebration,
but only for the people in the limelight,
not for me.
That woman said I'm a person with no luck,
who's never had love or success.
Then that means
you'll be successful from now on.
If a guy with a history of being
with unlucky women, like he was,
decides to leave you,
then it makes sense to think
only happiness awaits you in the future.
[feel-good music playing]
You're able to see the silver lining.
And you're a great translator.
[feel-good music continues]
It got great reviews.
It's just a little further down there.
A NEW START. A FESTIVAL WITH FIREWORKS!
WITH #PAPAGO #GRATEFUL_FOR_YOU
[music fades]
Mr. Joo, you're not taking photos?
You don't have Instagram?
I have it. I don't post much.
I'm not that into it.
Right now, my followers are at 9,989.
Like, I'm so close!
What?
A few more, and I'll be at 10,000.
[sighs] But it's been like this
for a while.
So you're asking me to follow you?
It's not a hard thing to do.
With many, I don't follow back,
but we'll follow each other.
Oh, well, I'm not sure.
Following a famous actress
makes me nervous.
Why would you be nervous?
No one would call me famous.
Well, you might be.
You have mentioned earlier you might
blow up and become a huge star.
Then strangers would see my account. No.
[laughs]
You seem to say things,
well, in very flattering ways.
[laughing]
Let's head back down.
The observatory has a beautiful view.
However, if we go,
we'll be late for dinner.
This is your second time here?
Yeah.
And you're here again?
Alone?
This island's legendary.
[soothing music playing]
The dragon god of the sea
fell in love with a fairy from the heavens
and created this land
to give as a gift to her.
Oh! Hmm.
The dragon god was invested.
I came here with someone before
who wanted this place
as a present for her birthday.
Today's her birthday, so I'm here
to see how much I've missed her.
She wanted an island for a birthday gift?
So you came here wishing to be with her.
You're talking about love. Who is she?
[melodic ukulele music playing]
What's wrong?
You know everything about my love life.
It's fair to tell me yours.
I'm under no obligation to share
that with a stranger. Why would I?
Actually, because we're strangers,
you're free to speak
since you'll never see me again.
You know everything about me,
so don't get embarrassed.
I knew her a long time ago.
And even then,
I was fooling myself.
I misunderstood her like you did.
Oh no!
So, then, she confessed
in a roundabout way
and thought you were saying no.
You didn't offer for her to come this year
since it's her birthday today?
She has somebody in her life
that she celebrates with now.
[gasps]
So let's get going.
[Mu-hee] Uh…
Hey, wait up.
[music fades]
[jaunty music playing]
[Mu-hee breathing heavily]
I think we're almost there.
We could ask someone for directions.
Japanese is a language you know.
No way.
I know where we're going.
Just this way. Two more blocks there.
But…
We're going in circles.
[train crossing warning]
- My phone says it's this way.
- Stop. Stay there.
The restaurant isn't far.
It's down this way, not back there.
- It's this way. I'm correct.
- Let's bet for real?
I win the bet, you follow me.
Because reaching 10,000 followers
is that important?
Yes. To me, it is. You agree to the bet?
[chuckles]
Hey! Excuse me. Do you live here?
- Hi. I need to find this place.
- [phone ringing]
[Mu-hee] It's a restaurant.
- Hey, Jin-suk.
- [Mu-hee] Is it that way?
I'm traveling.
In Japan? I'm asking
because today is Ji-sun's birthday,
but we had a fight, and I can't find her.
She put up a photo on Instagram.
It might be in Japan.
Could you take a look and let me know
if you can maybe find her?
[wistful music playing]
- [in Japanese] It's that way.
- [in English] This way? [laughs]
Thanks for the directions.
[laughs]
Hey! You! The restaurant's this way.
So, I win. [laughs]
[music fades]
Something wrong?
The woman who wants the island…
I just heard she came here today.
[gasps]
Terrific!
Hurry up, then. Go be with her. I'm fine.
This opportunity's a gift.
Don't waste it on me,
or you'll end up alone again, Ho-jin.
This time,
don't act like you don't get her.
Then things can change.
[train horn blares]
[romantic pop music playing]
[romantic pop music continues]
He's gone.
Oh, well.
It's a shame.
I don't know how to reach him.
I hope he follows me.
[romantic pop music continues]
[woman on PA] This is an announcement
for all visitors to Enoshima Observatory.
The observatory is open
from 9:00 a.m. to 8:00 p.m.
We close at 8:00 p.m.
[romantic pop music continues]
Please note
that the last entry is at 7:30 p.m.
We kindly ask for your cooperation.
Thank you.
[breathing heavily]
[phone buzzing]
NA JIN-SUK
[sighs]
- [music fades]
- [phone continues buzzing]
[thud echoes]
[jaunty music playing]
[dark waltz music playing]
[intriguing music playing]
[chuckles]
[doorbell buzzes]
[man] Who is it?
[chuckles]
[music fades]
Your room service.
[indistinct chatter on TV]
[playful, sinister music playing]
[man 1 on TV] That's crazy.
You can't recreate a thing like that.
[man 2 on TV] The hall was 43 feet.
[Mu-hee] Have a pleasant evening.
- [thud]
- [ominous music playing]
[snarling]
- [snarling continues]
- [metallic clatter]
[whimsical thrumming]
[playful, sinister music playing]
[growling]
[man grunting, screaming]
[screaming continues]
[music fades]
Cut! That's a keeper!
We're moving on!
[laughs]
How was that? Okay?
Well, the movements are gorier.
Way more than they were going to be.
Oh.
Oh, but with the music, you know,
the bright fun of it
will bring a more joyful atmosphere
and less creepy goriness.
So much fun, right?
Uh, yeah.
[both laugh]
Uh…
Today's our last day of shooting.
This movie's going to be huge.
As our lead, Do Ra-mi,
you got this!
I've got this!
[both laugh]
The dress is cute.
[Mu-hee sighs]
Mu-hee.
It's almost over,
but I still don't understand
what the movie is about.
Is this a horror flick or a comedy?
The director is a genius.
No one would even dare judge his vision.
This is your first big role.
I'm honestly worried about your career.
Even the name of your character is weird.
Do Ra-mi.
"Do Re-mi," maybe.
If anyone thought this movie'd be a hit,
they wouldn't have cast me for the lead.
I have to give it 100%.
Today may not be the last day.
There was an issue,
and they might not be able to shoot.
Seems like the director
and the stunt guy clashed.
We still have to do the setup,
and it hasn't been rehearsed.
[man] They're fighting again.
- [woman] Calm down so we can--
- This isn't about calming down!
Doing it faster
isn't going to make it better.
I need more time to prepare.
I already told you,
it can't be done today!
[sighs]
[indistinct chattering]
[intriguing music playing]
[breathing nervously]
[groans]
Uh, thanks a lot
for doing the stunt yourself.
- This is a tough one.
- Oh.
I should do it
because it's a crucial scene.
And it's the last day today.
[director] We'll do this in one take,
exactly like we promised. It'll be great.
[breathes nervously]
- Mm.
- Please be careful.
You got this.
[woman] There's a fireworks festival
tonight at 9:00.
Let's hurry this up
so we can get it done before then.
[intriguing music continues]
Set.
And ready?
[radio beeps]
Action!
[tense music playing]
HOTEL DIAMORTE
HOTEL DI E
[music intensifies]
Cut! Okay!
[woman] We got it! That's good!
[director] That's a wrap!
Pull her back up!
- [crew 1] Good job!
- [crew 2] Great!
Okay! We're all done!
[cable tensioning]
- [cable snaps]
- [gasps]
- No!
[thud echoing]
[distant fireworks whistle, explode]
[melancholy music playing]
[moans]
[Mu-hee] As I closed my eyes
for what I thought would be the last time,
in another part of town,
a festival was taking place.
I realized then,
my life never had any fireworks in it,
and yet, I could hear them
exploding in a sky far away.
How beautiful.
This just sucks.
[melancholy music continues]
[music fades]
[man muffled] Ms. Cha Mu-hee?
[heart monitor beeping]
Ms. Cha Mu-hee?
[heart monitor continues beeping]
You've woken up, Ms. Cha Mu-hee.
[chuckles] This is wonderful!
- Go, go, go.
- Okay, let's go.
[door closes]
[doctor] Ms. Cha Mu-hee
has regained consciousness.
We've all been rooting for Do Ra-mi.
- Now, she's finally back.
- [upbeat music playing]
And despite our fears,
Ms. Cha Mu-hee is fully cognitive.
She knows the people around her
and has no problems with communicating.
[reporter] Exciting news today.
South Korean actress, Cha Mu-hee,
who plays Do Ra-mi,
has woken up from a coma
and is doing well.
Last July, while working on the hit film,
The Quiet Woman,
Cha Mu-hee had
a life-threatening accident…
…became a global phenomenon
with her role as Do Ra-mi.
[reporters continue in multiple languages]
[in French] The actress
suffered a serious accident
when she fell from a roof
while filming the movie The Quiet Woman.
- [in English] Global phenomenon.
- You blokes seeing this?
Next round's on the house!
[all cheering] Yeah!
[indistinct chattering]
[exclaiming]
[all exclaim excitedly]
[exclaiming excitedly]
[squealing]
[upbeat music continues]
[reporter in English] The actress,
Cha Mu-hee, who played Do Ra-mi
and sparked a worldwide frenzy,
has woken up from a coma.
[upbeat music continues]
[Mu-hee] I closed my eyes
for what felt like a second,
and when I opened them,
the world had become
a fan of my work and me.
For the first time in my life,
there was a festival of fireworks
being held for me.
The actress, Ms. Cha Mu-hee,
has miraculously regained consciousness
without any mental or physical issues.
Fans hope she'll soon return
to her acting career.
You've woken up, Ms. Cha Mu-hee.
[reporter] Around the world,
those who loved her in The Quiet Woman
are sending their best wishes…
[upbeat music continues]
CAN THIS LOVE BE TRANSLATED?
[music fades]