Mom
Even though your panic disorder
seems stable for now,
you still have to take your meds on time,
or if something unusual happens,
you could have a stress reaction.
Panic disorder?
Sheng Yuanzhou has been sick all along.
Mom!
What's wrong?
Why is the washer making so many suds?
Oh my God.
How much detergent did you put in?
I only put in one bag.
One bag?
Here, let me handle it.
Go start the rice in the kitchen.
Put it in the pot.
In the pot.
Go on.
Okay.
Look at you.
Are you crazy?
What are you doing? I'm cooking!
Cooking?
Looks like you're trying to burn it down.
Cooking? Watch closely.
This is how you use a rice cooker properly.
So it's that simple.
What a genius.
No idea how you survived all these years
living like this.
None of your business.
How did you get in?
You left the front door open.
How else do you think I got in?
Then what are you here for?
At Prosperity Group,
I got you a job.
I'm not going.
Why not?
I've decided
I'm not working anymore.
I've tried way too many jobs.
Catching chickens, hauling cargo,
even delivering takeout.
I'm really sick of it.
So I
decided to be a writer.
Write novels.
Come on, take a look.
Look.
Look at your family's situation.
Who can afford to support you writing?
My parents didn't object.
You're the one making a fuss.
Look at your dad.
He doesn't work,
and he's been a loser his whole life.
Sheng Yuanzhou.
Who are you to come here and boss us around?
And criticize my dad?
Life isn't just about making money, okay?
Being happy matters too.
So your happiness
is built on your mom's suffering, right?
You...
Why are you here again?
Honestly...
Sorry, Mom.
I messed it up again.
It's okay.
I already cleaned it up.
It's fine.
Don't come here and hurt my child.
Think it over carefully.
Even if I get a job, I don't need your help.
Leave. Now.
Go. Now.
Go, now! Go!
Go! Go!
I'll be back soon.
I'll come back with money.
Mortgage it?
Yeah.
I want to mortgage that land my mom left me.
Put it up as collateral.
Why not just sell it?
I heard the bonded zone's relocating.
Keeping that land will just lose you money.
And a few days ago I met this
newly rich coal miner from Xinjiang.
He's dumb and loaded.
I'll sweet-talk him a bit,
you sell him that land,
and I'll only take five percent.
How about it?
That's Sheng Yuanzhou's mom's gravesite.
Forget it.
I'll mortgage it instead.
Help me negotiate a better price.
When I make money trading stocks,
you'll still get your five percent.
That's nothing.
Just consider that I owe you a favor.
You owe me way too many favors already.
How are you gonna pay them back?
How do you want me to?
A favor for a favor...
Pay with your body.
With Sheng Yuanzhou's identity backing me,
even this body of mine looks tempting now.
Look.
Pretty handsome, right?
Then why do you eat boxed lunches here?
No money, obviously.
His family's really poor.
I heard he works in the cafeteria to get by.
Every day he secretly packs up leftovers.
Leftovers?
To feed the dog?
To feed a family of four.
No wonder.
I smelled something stinky.
That kind of guy won't do.
Exactly.
I'll leave the mortgage to you.
I've got something to do. I'm leaving.
He's decided to mortgage Bai Zimei's land.
As long as I've got this as seed money,
Before I turn back into Zhang Xiaobei,
I'll definitely save up enough money.
Then
Mom, Dad, and I
won't have to live a hard life anymore.
No one will look down on me, Zhang Xiaobei, again.
You?
I was about to ask you that.
What are you doing?
I was just heading home and you caught me.
Then don't act so sneaky.
It's because it reeks!
I covered up because I didn't want anyone to see.
Where have you been?
Why do you smell so stinky?
Did you fall into a cesspit?
It's all that crooked restaurant's fault.
What are you doing?
Boss, this tofu's gone bad.
I'll toss it out.
This is hairy tofu.
Hairy tofu is fine.
Boss, you can't just for a little profit
throw your conscience away.
Customers will get stomachaches from it.
Can't you understand plain language?
It's safe to eat.
Boss, selling expired food will get you arrested.
If you keep this up, I'll report you.
Are you out of your mind today?
Give it to me.
Give it to me!
Get out, now. Get out!
You're really something.
You threw away another perfectly good job.
That boss was really nice.
Whenever there were leftover ingredients,
he let me take them home.
How do you know?
I...
Why so many questions?
Let's go, it stinks.
I get caught by you every time.
The rainy-day video.
Is all this aimed at Sheng Yuanzhou,
or aimed at me?
If it's aimed at me,
then maybe besides me,
there are other people
who know the Key of Fate exists.
Sheng Yuanzhou showed up there...
Was it really just a coincidence?
Or was he behind all this...
Come in.
Young Master, your father wants you in the study.
Got it.
I heard you got a hotel room with Zhu Yutong.
Yes.
You never had a habit of playing women.
After Zhu Zipeng was arrested,
control of the Zhu family
fell into Zhu Yutong's hands.
She's good at socializing,
with a wide network.
I think getting closer to her
won't hurt.
And the Lin family's dignity?
You still need to consider it.
Lin Chengren has already come to me.
What do you think we should do?
How about we
call off the engagement.
A man
just fooling around with a woman,
and you let them make a fuss, then cancel it?
What about the Sheng family's reputation?
Go to the Lin family right now.
Settle this for me.
Actually,
I don't feel anything for Lin Siqi.
You think marriage runs on feelings?
I'm telling you,
whether you like Lin Siqi or not,
the matter between the Sheng and Lin families
is already decided.
Looks like calling it off won't be that easy.
With you showing up like this,
are you here to visit the sick?
You're joking.
About last time at the hotel,
sorry about that.
So I came to apologize to your dad.
It's fine.
Good for my dad to face the truth sooner.
Now we're even.
Fair enough.
If you can talk your dad into it,
that's best.
I'm confident I can.
Then these fruits...
take them in.
At least it shows I came.
Thanks.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
We found it.
Yes.
From our investigation, that motorcycle
had fake plates.
The rider was also wearing a helmet,
so we can't ID them yet.
But we found a strange lead.
That bike
once showed up at Jiang Lai's doorstep.
Jiang Lai?
Why'd you think to ask me to shop with you?
I just wanted to pick up a few clothes.
Aren't you doing that...
fashion blogger thing?
So I figured I'd ask a pro like you
for some advice.
Sure.
I can give advice,
but why'd you bring me to a mall?
Then... should we shop online?
You're really funny.
Except for this plaid one,
try on all the other clothes.
Okay, please wait a moment.
Where are you going?
Aren't you going to try them on?
You planning to try them yourself?
So many?
Won't you get tired?
No.
Can't you find a few more models?
So I can take my time looking.
How long is this going to take?
Understood, we'll be more careful next time.
But for fitting models,
they need to match the VIP's height and weight,
with the same leg and arm length.
They're really hard to find.
So this one you found matches, then?
I pay you to meet my needs,
not to listen to you waste my time here
making excuses.
Yes, yes, yes.
We'll switch someone out right away.
You're pretty good at making things hard for people.
Making things hard?
I'm giving them a chance to make money, okay?
Being able to enter this VIP room,
they must be thrilled.
As long as they get in,
all spending in this room today
they're entitled to a cut.
That outfit on the far left was pretty good.
It'll go great with the dress I
left here last time.
Bring the dress over.
I'll try it on myself.
Yes.
You go ahead; we'll wait outside.
Hurry up, go.
Wait for me!
Help me pull up the zipper.
What are you doing?
Do it.
The same thing we did before.
Did you forget?