Maybe it's not our time,
- Or maybe…
Can I join you?
Okay, this is happening,
I'm about to go
Wait, did you actually mean join me on…
- The world tour,
What? No, The world tour?
- I thought you were asking to come with,
- For the whole summer,
No, No, no, no, That would be crazy,
I mean, us? Imagine spending
- We would drive each other nuts,
Hi, Kitty,
Because tonight's kickoff party
- I've never been on a yacht before,
I could kill some time with you in Busan
Um, sure,
But you might wanna bring
because that outfit's not gonna cut it,
- What is wrong with my skort?
There's literally a dress code,
Yacht chic,
Okay, give me like five minutes to throw
What? Wait, no one told me
Okay, so maybe inviting myself
but definitely epic world tour with Min Ho
But I'm not giving up yet,
So, did you tell him how you feel?
I was going to, but then I chickened out,
Oh wow, A matchmaker
That's kind of tragic if you think…
So then I asked
- On the tour?
- For the summer?
I am so lost,
I am too, but I do know I have 14 hours
and see if he feels the same way,
Okay, so, do you…
No, I don't know, okay? He told me
What if you just ask him?
What if he doesn't feel the same way
- Oh wow, Okay,
Come to Busan,
- Please?
- It's my last night before training camp,
Is there any way you can come
to this super fun yacht party
On second thought, it does seem like
so I will be there as your wingman,
We, Jin and I,
Do you wanna help me,
Both, You know how I feel
- The tinier, the better,
- Settled, It'll be the four of us,
- Vibes ahoy, Smooth sailing,
Find your own way there
Remember, just the four of us,
Eunice just invited us
Oh! Oh! Can we borrow your dad's heli?
Oh, uh, actually, it's in the shop,
- I'll book us train tickets,
- Mm-hmm,
Oh my God, I look so cute in this,
Whatever, I'm gonna buy it anyway,
Actually, on second thought…
Let's go to Busan,
Yay!
Busan! Whoo-hoo!
Can you just act a little more excited?
I wanted to spend time together
Just the two of us?
And we will,
And then it'll be you, me,
and the beautiful view of a sunset
All right, Busan, here we come,
Can I come too?
You guys are going to Busan, right?
Um… That is right,
If this is about Eunice,
she's gonna be busy launching
Actually, it's about Yuri,
And she's coming too, apparently,
- Ah,
Yeah, Would you look at that?
Uh…
I can't believe the legendary Yisoo
- I'm so excited!
Eight times,
This is just the beginning, Eunice,
Get used to being the center of attention,
Did I just get demoted
I need a plan,
Uh, Min Ho, do you think we'll have time
Yeah, What… what
Mm, maybe Gwangalli Beach?
Apparently, they light up the bridge
Oh my God, That is so romantic!
If you want a great view,
we could probably
Oh…
- Yeah, I would love that,
I'm pretty sure my dad's gonna
so it'll probably just be me and Kitty,
- Who invited the girls?
And the boys?
That was kind of me,
Oh, Okay,
I guess a group thing will be fun,
Mm,
So much for romantic alone time,
Hi!
- Oh my gosh, This is so cool!
Yuri, I was hoping we could talk?
Uh, Mihee-ah,
Okay,
Kitty, I am so sorry,
Things just spiraled,
I'm going to help you, Wingman's honor,
Thank you, This crowdsourcing
Yeah, I get you, but we'll figure it out,
- I promise,
- Hey!
I just go get it
I get what I want, no sweating
On me, I'm betting
- I get what I want, go-getter
Go, go, I go and get it
- Go, go
Tell me, baby
Or should I keep it going?
I could talk forever
Something deep inside of me
- All you gotta do is just
I know what you're feeling
Don't be scared to lean in
Just follow my lead and let me in
I'm a go-getter
I just go get it
I get what I want, no sweating
On me, I'm betting
Anything I want, put in my bag
Everybody know that I do it like that
Like a boomerang, coming right back
Everybody know
- Go, go, go, go, go
Wow, this view is beautiful,
I agree,
I… I mean, Busan is beautiful
Wait, is Min Ho nervous?
There's only one way to find out,
- Min Ho, I--
You know how much
Our friendship?
Yeah, Yes, of course,
So if I were to tell you that…
Or if I told you that I…
What I'm trying to get at is--
Oh,
I should take this,
Hey, where the hell are you?
Hi, Dad, Wait, whoa, Are you in the bath?
Where else would I be
- How soon can you get to the hotel?
I've given it a lot of thought, And, uh…
What, really?
After everything that
you'd give me
You showed a lot of courage,
But I need to know
We need to make sure that Eunice
and seals a brand deal with Yisoo,
So, give Eunice whatever she needs,
and keep her out of trouble,
Yeah, got it, I'll head
- Thank you, I won't let you down,
I'm sorry, I have to go, Kitty,
And I can't screw this up,
You don't have to explain,
I'm happy for you,
I'm really lucky to have you,
- I'll see you tonight?
Okay, so my timing sucks,
but I still have eight hours
Joon Ho!
Joon, how you feeling?
- You made a great entrance,
This is glitzy as hell,
- Ooh, ooh, ooh! VIP gift bags,
Ooh, free gift bags,
SOS911! Can I get a quick picture?
Ahoy, mate,
I do not want to hear it,
I clearly had no idea
How'd things go with your dad?
Um, great, I'm supposed
I don't usually feel nervous
but for some reason, tonight I do,
Tell you what, if you're feeling jittery,
Act like you're just talking to me,
Yeah?
- Thanks, Covey,
Min Ho! Come here!
All right, I better go do my job,
- I'll look for you in the crowd,
Min Ho! Come here!
All right, All right,
SOS911, over here,
- You're the best, SOS911!
Kitty, gift bags!
Hi!
This is insane,
Wait, isn't that Tae-Oh
Where?
How can someone be
Maybe we can meet him,
Whoa,
Look, he's talking to Eunice,
Really? I don't see it,
Look this way!
Yuri, hey! Hi,
You look amazing,
Thank you, Uh…
- Madison invited us,
- Great,
Yeah, um, actually, so you know
And it is annoyingly chic,
- You know, relax, recharge,
Very White Lotus coded,
Yeah,
It was really nice talking to you,
- Whoa! Wait, That's actual champagne,
I know,
Thank you, bye,
You know who's looking real good? Min Ho,
Right? He is so fine,
Moon is making him go on tour this summer,
So, we'll all get to have a little taste,
Oh, uh, miss, could we get some
Uh…
Hi, Champagne? Yes?
- Yes,
- Coming right up,
You can kiss my bellinis, Ugh,
Hey, can I get another, please… Kitty?
Yes, no, that does seem to be
- Mm,
Impress Min Ho,
Yeah, I saw you two at the cable cars,
- So, how's that going?
A lot, And I have
three hours and 34 minutes
And I am very scared
We might not be on the same page at all,
I get it, But you're just gonna
I know, Does it even make sense, though?
Like, his world is so glamorous,
Yeah, that waitress look
But… I saw some Yisoo dresses backstage,
and there's one
- Okay,
- Oh, like, for me to… Oh,
Wow,
I've never worn anything
Or this heavy,
That's just the weight of being hot, babe,
All right,
Well…
What are you waiting for?
- Mm,
Bye,
Okay,
Yes, Yisoonim,
Tonight we have to be well-prepared,
Of course,
Eunice's dress is going to be iconic,
My custom dress! Where is it?
One moment,
Are you kidding me?!
Thanks, everyone! I will see you guys
So, this next performer…
will be, uh…
I mean, this next performer
Soon to be Korea's next breakout star,
Oh no, it's out,
What? Poor Yuri,
She's gotta be freaking out,
Focus!
Excuse me, Sorry,
Thank you so much, Sorry,
And as her manager and her dear friend,
I couldn't be more proud
So, without further ado, Eunice!
I think she's a little bit shy,
So, let's have
What's going on?
I can't find my dress anywhere!
What do you mean,
Start the music,
Ooh,
It lights up! It's really good,
That's probably Eunice's dress,
No, no, No, no, no, no, no,
Well, there goes Eunice's brand deal,
- I can't believe I did this,
Come on, let's light up like firework
Oh, Yuri,
Kitty? Is that you?
Hey, I just saw the news,
You okay?
Mm,
Not really,
I've had a lot of champagne,
- You good?
I'm so sorry I put you in a stolen dress,
I mean, I've been broke for,
And I'm already committing grand larceny,
You were just trying to help,
Why didn't you tell me what was going on?
Because it's humiliating,
I thought if I ignored it,
Have you talked to Dae about it?
- I can't deal with him right now,
Whatever Dae is gaining
I can guarantee
How about this?
You talk to Dae,
and I will stop being a coward
Deal,
Mm,
Well, if it isn't our main attraction,
Mr, Moon, I am so sorry about the dress,
I did not mean to ruin
And yet, you did,
but you're trying to fit
And right now, Min Ho needs
And not be distracted by you,
You don't want to be
Of course not,
Then you leave him alone,
Sitting here, trying to run it back
I can't seem to let it go
I'm waiting here in the aftermath…
Kitty, wait! Kitty!
That was such a disaster!
What am I going to do?
What am I going to do about the tour?
Everyone was too busy watching the stage,
They were only looking at you,
Thanks, Dae,
Have a great summer, and…
I'll really miss you,
Cold nights putting up a fight
Against the odds are always for me
A little red, no common sense…
Hey, Dae,
Hey,
Sorry I've been avoiding you,
Honestly, I know
But…
I just didn't think
I'm the only one of our friends
Uh…
Sorry,
I'm not saying I can help the situation,
Just talk to me,
Holding it back, yeah, holding it back
I can't shake this feeling
All I wanted
But his dad is right,
I can't get in the way
So I guess it's time to go home,
LJ? What's up?
Kitty!
- You left, What-
Especially after all the trouble I caused,
Enough… with the mixed signals,
I thought you wanted
But then you didn't,
I felt like you wanted
But then you invited all our friends,
And then you talk about
I do, though, and I'm scared to risk…
All I wanted all night was to get up
and see if you feel the same way,
The truth is,
I thought so,
- But then--
Well, it's not too late,
Come with me,
And you can tell me
Honestly, I want that more than anything,
Because I like you, Min Ho,
Like, I really, really like you,
And I really like you too, Covey,
So will you come with me?
I…
can't,
Lara Jean just called me,
She's going through
and she asked me to join her in New York,
- But--
My sister needs me,
Of course, I understand,
I mean, I'm… I'm sorry,
Family comes first, right?
Please stop talking,
Hold your head up high
This is our time
Together we will rise up
Step into the light
We were born to come alive
Hold your head up high
This is our time
Here,
- Thanks,
Min Ho!
We're doing body shots!
And we need your hot body!
Whoo!
Yes! Whoo!
- Let's go!
- Kitty and I were just about to--
Don't make me celebrate alone!
No worries, I will take good care of her,
Come on,
You go ahead, Stay with Eunice,
I have a flight to catch anyway,
I'll see you in three months,
Trust me, It'll fly by,
All right, girls, Move over,
Let's go!
Yes! Let's go!
Three months,
Then again,
Beat drop with a big flash
- Know I did that
Day one, know I been bad
- Can't touch that
I'm the highlight
Yeah, tonight, it's all 'bout me
You know it's my site
History
One look, give 'em whiplash
- Beat drop with a big flash
- Know I did that
Day one, know I been bad
- Can't touch that
Whip, whiplash, whip, whiplash
Whip, whiplash