(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
DECEMBER 2020
JINNAM BOXING
Oh, uh, sir.
You need to wear a mask on the bus, sir.
You can't ride the bus
without a mask. I'm sorry.
Let's go.
You'll be allowed on
when you return with a mask.
Who are you to tell me what to do?
- We get penalized--
- What? A mask?
- It's my choice!
- Please leave, sir.
You're a driver,
so drive the damn bus.
I'm telling you.
- Please put on a mask and come back, sir.
- You're just a driver. Come here!
- There are passengers on board.
- Please don't do this.
- What the hell is this? Whoa!
- Whoa!
- Sorry. Sorry.
- Get off of me.
What? Who the hell are you?
I'm sorry, I think
you'll have to walk home. Sorry.
I'm sorry.
You shi--
Sorry, sir.
I'm very sorry.
Whoa, I'm sorry.
I hope you're not hurt. Sorry, sir.
Goddamn you little--
I'm very sorry.
Bullshit.
- I'm really sorry.
- My ass.
Sorry about that. Thank you.
- Thank you, sir.
- No problem.
See,
the passengers are grateful too.
The guy in the mask kept saying…
I'm so sorry.
God, I had no idea it would go on
for this long.
I am so sorry that I have to ask you.
I'm sorry.
I'll try to put something together
next month. I promise.
So, do you think can you wait
just one more month?
I… I promise I'll pay you back.
Yes, yes. Next month. I'll try my best.
Yes, thank you.
BLOODHOUNDS
Amidst the ongoing recession
brought on by COVID-19…
CITIZENS TREMBLE WITH ANXIETY
ABOUT ABANDONED BUILDINGS IN THE CITY
…a suspended building construction project
is threatening the safety of the citizens.
NO TRESPASSING
Construction on the building
you see behind me had been suspended twice
due to on-site workers being diagnosed
with COVID-19.
When the company went bankrupt,
the building was abandoned
becoming an eyesore
in the middle of the city.
Seoul City must act quickly
to resolve this situation.
In the United States, over 3.5 million
hotel employees were laid off
in the third quarter alone.
I'm telling you
that for the next three to for years
there will be no foreign companies
interested in acquiring this hotel.
Domestic companies even less so.
You make these claims
as though they're facts.
I have a lot of friends
who are future leaders
of Korea's top fifty corporations.
I have thoroughly discussed it with them
and reached this conclusion,
so these claims are highly likely
to be factual.
Actually,
they are simply facts.
You'd be doing well to negotiate with me,
Mr. Vice President.
Mr. Hong.
As you know, our bank has already lent
400 billion won to this building.
Stating you will only be paying back
300 isn't a negotiation.
Shouldn't one be prepared to accept
some losses in the current situation?
How else can business be done?
I am not a businessman,
but I am the banker.
Uh, Mr. Director, Mr. Vice President,
the reason I brought the two of you
over here…
Yes.
…is to push for a speedy completion
of the construction work on the building
for the citizens' safety.
Talking to him
is like talking to a brick wall.
If you're suggesting
that I'm being unreasonable,
let me ask you this,
which part of what you said is reasonable?
I must apologize for my tardiness.
This is Mr. Kim Myeong-gil.
I mentioned him before our meal.
May I introduce you.
Assemblyman Seo Woo-hyeon,
a close acquaintance of the mayor,
introduced him to us.
Kim Myeong-gil.
KIM MYEONG-GIL
I'll contact you individually later today.
Okay.
Kim Myeong-gil.
Excuse me,
but what kind of work do you do?
Primarily I deal with investments.
When good people request my assistance,
I help them out
to the best of my abilities.
So are you a moneylender?
Hey, did you know
that this man's a loan shark?
Mr. Kim dabbles in various lines of work.
You really think this is the right place
to bring this predator?
And you must be the eldest son
of Chairman Hong Woo-geun.
When I was young, I worked for someone
named Chairman Bang in Myeong-dong.
You wouldn't remember
since you were a baby at that time,
but when the IMF crisis hit Korea,
Iil Group nearly went bankrupt
because they didn't have six billion
after fifty years in business.
Back then, Chairman Hong Woo-geun
went to my boss, Chairman Bang,
to ask for assistance.
He got down on his knees
saying he had to save the company
at whatever cost.
And with all his sincerity
and his passion,
he got to Chairman Bang.
So then,
I filled up a bag
with six billion in cash,
and I went over to your house.
I also remember your mother prepared
some refreshing Korean melon for me
to express her gratitude.
There is no dirty money
unless it's used for nefarious agendas,
but when used for good,
that makes it good money.
I came here
to extend what support I have to offer.
How are the negotiations?
There were differences
in the amount they had in mind.
- So we were just talking.
- Ah… How much of discrepancy?
A hundred billion.
Mr. Hong, do you plan on overseeing
hotel operations yourself?
I got my master's in hotel management
in Switzerland
and worked for four years in Hong Kong.
I see you are well-prepared.
With your permission,
I would like to make an investment.
What's your offer?
Well… you need 100 billion,
so I'll invest that much.
If need be, I will invest more.
What are the terms?
Right.
There are only three.
First off,
I would like to have a small casino
built on the highest floor
of the hotel's structure.
Just as you dream of managing a hotel,
Mr. Hong,
well, I dream of operating my own casino.
And secondly,
I ask that you help me set up a small bar
in the basement of the hotel.
The last thing is,
if something like COVID-19
were to spread again,
I would like our hotel
to be a quarantine space.
for those without money,
and it will be free of charge.
The harder the times get,
the more we all should be looking out
for one another.
Because… that's how we build
a better world.
The 100 billion won investment
can be available to you
as early as tomorrow.
It went well?
- Mm-hm.
- So they'll bite?
Mm.
Oh yay!
So I guess I need to start thinking
about how I want to decorate the bar!
Well, uh, people don't go to bars
to see how they're decorated.
They go to see the girls.
So you better get busy
hiring some pretty girls.
No, I think you should get busy,
you fucker.
You know, it would be better
if you could talk as nice as you look.
What would you know? You prick!
I need to wipe my face.
Oh.
Here you go.
Let's get going.
How's the Seongeun Building?
None of the tenants have any ties
to the police or prosecutor's office.
Did you also check in-laws?
Yes, of course. I told you
I only overlooked it that one time.
Someone could have a partner who's a cop.
Do your job well
so he doesn't have to worry.
Ah, why don't you worry about yourself?
Jang-do,
you should speak to my woman
with more respect.
Yes, you're right. I'm sorry, sir.
Hey, apologize to me, you asshole.
This asshole apologizes to you, ma'am.
Hurry up, please.
I could really use a drink.
Yes, sir.
This is the 2020 KBFC
Rookie of the Year Tournament.
The Rookie of the Year Tournament
is supposed to be held
amidst the loud shouting and cheering
of fans expressing their love and support,
but due to COVID-19,
there are no spectators today.
It feels rather gloomy in here,
don't you think?
That's right.
The Rookie of the Year tournament
is normally a rowdy affair
with lots of cheering for everyone.
As we speak, we begin
the third round of Hong Woo-jin's match.
Now we have a middleweight match here
with Hong Woo-jin in the red trunks,
going up against Jung Jae-hun
in the blue trunks.
Get in there.
Great combination of body shots.
Now we see Hong Woo-jin
leaning against the ropes.
He provokes his opponent
after landing body shots.
Would you look at that provocation.
I mean, I wouldn't go near.
Whoa, a body shot!
A clean hit to the body.
He landed a blow to the face.
He knocks his opponent down! Hong Woo-jin!
Whoa! A double right
followed by a one-two strike.
Look at that footwork.
He has great showmanship.
Whoa, it's a KO.
KIM RAE-HYEON
KIM GUN-WOO
We have Kim Gun-woo
going up against Kim Rae-hyeon.
Kim Gun-woo in blue, everybody,
the super rookie in blue trunks.
Kim Gun-woo is looking
for a chance with his guard up.
- A body blow!
- He goes to his knees!
That's right.
A precision blow to the solar plexus…
- That's the end of the match.
- Indeed.
Ending with just one blow.
Kim Gun-woo mows down his opponent
with a single blow again.
He's a matchless competitor.
A terrifying rookie has emerged.
Things are already getting heated.
He's getting cornered.
He grabs him and throws him over.
He threw his opponent down.
That was against the rules.
- He did it first.
- He's too agitated now.
- Box!
- Let's do this!
He parts his hair.
Hong's showmanship is unmatched.
That is Hong Woo-jin for you.
He provokes. He dodges.
Wow! Look at him dodge!
Here he goes again…
He connects! We have a knockdown!
It's Hong Woo-jin's specialty.
A double jab followed by a straight!
Hong Woo-jin, the marine.
Hong Woo-jin advances again.
HONG WOO-JIN
Go lower.
A match between
Kim Gun-woo and Lee Yong-gyu.
Kim Gun-woo in the red trunks
is built like a tank.
He dodges both blows.
Kim Gun-woo's strength lies in infighting.
He is leveraging his skills
in close-range hitting.
Another punch, and he dodges.
A body shot! He brings down his opponent
with one blow!
A left hook to the body.
I had that level of talent
when I was a contender.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah.
That's why you won a gold medal.
Now, Kim Gun-woo versus Hong Woo-jin.
- Yeah, let's see.
- Let's find out who takes home the trophy.
No big moves.
Short punches. Use your waist!
Watch out for his left hook.
His punches are no joke.
Bro, I'm a marine.
THE STRONGEST
Watch out for his left hook.
And I'm telling you,
I'm an invincible marine.
Okay, but don't cry
if you get the shit beat out of you.
All right?
- Let's go!
- You got this.
Keep your hands up.
Come forward to meet.
Now good luck to you both.
To your corners.
His fighting up until now
has truly been a marvel.
Kim Gun-woo, the super rookie,
has a very unique fighting style.
That's right.
Kim Gun-woo is an infighter
that's good against other infighters.
Right.
On the other hand,
Hong Woo-jin is an out-boxer
with a counter up his sleeve.
That's right.
Hong Woo-jin knows how to have fun
during his matches.
On the other hand,
we have his opponent
who stoically plays it by the book.
He's going in! He's going!
He's cornering him!
Can Hong Woo-jin get out?
Can he get out of this?
Wow! He got out of that really well.
Hong Woo-jin is just remarkably fast.
And since Kim Gun-woo
is also a middleweight…
Wow,
he goes for a wild swing!
Here we go. He guards the body shot.
Kim Gun-woo has a great defense.
- Doesn't he?
- He's like a rock.
And he keeps on guarding.
Uppercut!
He landed that one.
Indeed he did.
What a performance this is.
A right hook! Wow, what a dodge.
Hong Woo-jin is
constantly applying nonstop pressure.
- Another left.
- Can he recover?
And Hong Woo-jin-- He goes down.
- He's down!
- One… two…
- Three… four
- With stomach blows,
the shock does not come right away.
It takes around five seconds.
That is when it hits.
-
- Six, seven…
He gets up
after five seconds.
He recovered well from that one.
Yes, he did.
But that has definitely got to sting.
There's going to be an aftereffect.
I think so.
Come on.
Come on!
Hey… come get some.
Son of a bitch.
Come get me!
Will he take the bait?
- Kim Gun-woo has a lot to think about.
- Come on!
And there he goes! Will he connect?
Stop! One, two…
Three… four…
His tactics really backfired.
KO!
Kim Gun-woo went in for the kill
and ended the match
once again with the same body shot.
I'll tell you something.
That body shot is ruthless.
You all right?
I have tainted the honor
of my fellow marines.
A blow to the liver will do that.
Okay, I'm out of here.
What about dinner, huh?
There's the pandemic.
I mean,
your boy has just gone through a lot.
The least you can do is feed him.
Go home and order in.
Later.
Oh.
What? Huh? What?
Wanna grab a bite?
Why would I wanna grab food with you?
I was gonna get some pork belly.
Thought you might want some.
Are you pitying me?
No.
Go ask those other assholes you KO'd
to eat with you.
But they all went home.
- Wasn't the prize money ten million?
- Yeah.
Then why settle for pork belly?
Let's get rib eye.
- I'm only going to spend 50,000.
- Why?
I need to give the rest to my mom.
- Do you owe your mom money?
- No.
Then why?
I have to pay the rent for her store.
You're a good son.
Just spend an extra 10,000.
This barbecue buffet I know
charges 29,000 a person.
It's insane, and they serve Korean beef.
- You serious?
- Of course not, idiot.
How could they afford
to serve Korean beef that cheap?
Do you spend all your time working out?
Anyway, that buffet is all right.
Just spend a little more.
No.
Hey.
Let's go.
How is your left hook so strong?
Back when I worked part-time
at a junkyard,
I practiced my hooks on a tire.
Just your left?
Why would I only work on my left?
No, I'm asking
if you only worked on your left.
No, of course I hit with both hands.
Then why is your left so strong?
- Actually, my right is stronger.
- Then why use only your left?
Because I couldn't find a good time
to use my right.
What a show-off.
You think so?
You're saying you could take
everyone down with just your left.
At least today, yes.
Yeah, see? What a show-off.
Actually, I consider myself humble.
Flip the pork already.
Not yet. It needs 30 more seconds.
Well, I think it's ready now.
You're wrong.
I worked part-time at a barbecue place.
I know my meat.
Damn, bro,
you've worked a lot of part-time jobs.
- Are you poor?
- Mm-hm.
My family lost everything.
How?
My dad was a researcher
for a large corporation.
He sued them for wrongful termination
and ended up losing the suit.
Legal fees from back then all became debt.
You can't beat the big companies.
The rich always come out on top.
That's true.
- What were your other gigs?
- Well, I dabbled in this and that.
For the most part,
I made deliveries with my mom.
I guess you're a world-class part-timer.
Oh!
You are good at everything.
You've led a good life.
I see you grill with your right hand.
So when did you start boxing?
Uh, about three years ago.
- After school?
- After my military service.
Ah…
I first put on my gloves
for the first time in sixth grade.
My dad was on the national team.
Wow, that's so cool.
And so what's your father's name?
Hong Seong-geun.
Barcelona bronze medalist.
- Oh.
- Know him?
No.
Most boxers seem to know him.
Oh. Sorry.
I assume
your dad taught you how to box, right?
We aren't that close.
Why?
My dad is never satisfied
with anything that I do.
He won his bronze medal at my age,
so he judges me
based on his accomplishments.
Hm.
So you're basically saying
that your dad won a bronze medal
at the Olympics
when he was only twenty-five years old?
No, twenty-seven.
Oh, how old are you?
Twenty-seven.
Uh,
I'm sorry, man. I'm actually twenty-five.
I'm sorry. Please forgive my manners.
Ah, you ass!
Please forgive me.
- Hey.
- Yes?
Learn to respect your elders, got it?
- Yes.
- Understand?
Sure.
Flip it now.
Oh, not yet.
It still needs one more minute.
- I said to flip it.
- I can't do that.
Oh god, you are one stubborn punk, bro.
You've served in the army?
Yes, I told you earlier I started boxing
after I finished my military service.
Yeah, you did.
What I mean is,
where were you stationed, huh?
- Oh.
- You need to learn to keep up.
Um, yes, I was in the Marine Corps.
Hey! I'm a marine too!
Oh.
What class?
Uh, I was in the 1,207th class.
Sir! I was in the 1,216th class, sir!
What are you doing? Sit. Please sit.
I will sit when you return my salute, sir.
Oh, uh…
So you're Marine Kim Gun-woo.
- Mm.
- So which division did you serve?
The First Division.
Me too! Which battalion were you in, sir?
- Recon.
- Amazing.
I also wanted to get into reconnaissance,
but I didn't make the cut.
- Mm.
- The pride of the Marines, recon.
Recon!
Ah!
You can still call me "bro," okay?
Let's just speak casually.
I understand, sir.
Yeah, but let's be casual.
Casual it is, sir.
Bro.
Hm?
Here.
Yeah, I have a crazy amount of pride
as a marine.
Why?
I was kind of a thug back in Incheon,
but I joined the Marine Corps,
met some nice people,
and came to my senses.
I just loved it all.
Going through tough training together
and overcoming it all.
This looks delicious.
Waking up in the morning,
going on runs, sweating bullets,
then showering together,
washing each, all that, you know.
- You're one of those crazy marines?
- Of course not.
You have to try this.
How is it? How is it?
It's practically steak.
Really?
Let me show you something.
- Watch this.
- Wow, yes.
- Three pieces with ssamjang.
- Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Want some kimchi with that too?
Ah, ah.
- Marine Kim Gun-woo, sir.
- Yeah?
Mm. Mm.
- Amazing. Amazing, right?
- Uh-huh. Mm-hm
- Want to get some soju?
- No.
- Why? Because of your diet?
- Mm-hm.
You're such a perfectionist.
You're too much.
Excuse me!
A beer!
Please. Ah!
Bro, how much were your shoes?
- 1.2 mill.
- Seriously?
Why so expensive?
That's a month's rent for our store.
Damn, you are really gullible.
Obviously they're knockoffs.
Well, they look real.
Knockoffs have shiny toe caps, see?
And the real ones are suede.
The threads around the holes
are pretty shitty too.
Tell me if you wanna buy some.
I can get you better than the real thing.
- Really?
- Are you shitting me? No, bro.
There's nothing in the world
that tops the real deal, all right?
You should hang out with me more,
so we can work on your street smarts.
You spend too much time
on your part-time jobs.
Do you know about this?
I heard it's very common these days.
"COVID-19 special loans."
COVID-19 SUPPORT
SUPER LOW-INTEREST SPECIAL LOAN
Back in the day,
I was so strapped for cash,
that I worked in money lending.
Desperate people are easier to rip off.
The pandemic has made
many people desperate.
So I guess now
all the loan sharks have come out to play.
Really?
Since everyone is rushing
to cover their rent,
all the sharks need to do
is shake their hand and suck them dry.
My mom is also having a hard time
because of the rent payments for her café.
The business makes less than a fourth
of what we used to,
but the landlord still takes
the same amount of rent.
If we close down now,
it would cost us more to move out,
so we're just trying to stay afloat.
Apparently, you have to return the store
to its original state.
Damn.
Here.
I'll treat you
to something real fancy next time.
- Are we gonna have rib eye?
- Ah, just come with me.
I know a good barbecue place.
You aren't messing with me?
Hey, do you think I would tell
such a low-level lie to a senior marine?
- I think you would.
- So you don't believe me?
I just mean
because you've been lying to me all day.
Man, those were just jokes.
All right, I promise no more lies.
Deal.
I know.
I am so sorry.
I tried my best.
I just couldn't…
…get it together in time.
Yes, if I just get through this month,
I will come up with it somehow.
Again, I am sorry.
Oh, uh, sorry.
- Let me call you back in the morning.
- Mom!
My boy!
Oh my boy!
Look at you. You were incredible today.
- You watched it?
- Oh, of course I watched it.
The commentators kept talking about you
the whole time.
- Are you serious?
- Yes, they kept saying you're perfect.
So I guess I should watch it too then.
- Mom, hold on.
- Look at you.
I'm so proud of you.
Here.
What's that?
The prize, so we can pay the rent.
Oh.
Oh, no, no. I can't take this.
No, Mom, I won this to give it to you.
Let's pay… Uncle back first
for what we owe.
How… how do you know about your uncle?
He's also going through a lot, Mom.
Let's pay him back.
All right.
But listen, I will pay you back for this
with interest.
- Okay.
- Oh, thank you.
- Let's go, Mom.
- Ah, it's so cold. Let's go.
Did you eat?
Yeah, of course.
Oh, with who?
The guy I fought in the finals.
Oh, the boy with the curly hair?
Yeah, that one.
Mom, did you eat?
Oh, sure, sure. I ate.
Sir.
How are things?
Sir, as you predicted,
all tenants owed money to banks
or second-tier financial companies.
So my plan is to bring all of them to us
by next week.
Okay, can you make it happen by this week?
Assemblyman Seo keeps badgering me
to kick them out quickly.
I'll see what I can do, sir.
Yes, let's hurry things along.
The sales team's operations are key,
aren't they?
Yes, they are.
Beom, listen.
Let's get ready.
I am team manager Yoo In-yeong
from Smile Capital.
We are a financial company
that was recently government-certified
for excellence,
and I was wondering
if you had some time for a quick chat.
Okay.
Your business doesn't get many visitors
these days, huh?
No.
I believe you owe the bank 40 million won.
Is that accurate, sir?
Yeah.
Once you sign here,
we will pay off that debt today.
And we have an interest rate of 5%
which is way lower than the bank's 7%.
Doesn't that end up leaving you
without any actual profit?
That's true.
But, uh, the government has started
a special support project
to help the small business owners
who are struggling
because of the pandemic.
We won a support package,
which allows us to lower interest rates
even more than the other companies.
A 2% difference in interest
is not a small amount
In times like these,
just staying afloat is winning.
We know this pandemic will pass soon.
DEBT REPAYMENT
AND NEW CONTRACT AGREEMENT
But we want to extend
whatever help we can,
so that you can keep your business.
It's true this is good for us too.
but it's really good for you, sir,
- Yes, thank you.
- Thank you so much.
SMILE CAPITAL
SIGNEE YOON SO-YEON
Huh?
TEMPORARILY CLOSED
DUE TO A CONFIRMED COVID-19 PATIENT
We had dinner last night
with some of the other members at the gym.
Apparently, one of them tested positive.
Oh, do you think I should get tested too?
No, you're fine.
Anyway, your match was just yesterday.
Why did I hear
that you're back at the gym?
- To work out. Why else?
- Gun-woo.
Please take a week off and rest.
Rest doing what?
Nothing. If you're doing something,
you're not resting.
Just don't do anything and try to relax.
Okay.
GU-NOO
Uh, what are you up to?
Sleep.
- Huh?
- Sleeping.
- Uh, I can't hear you.
- Sleep, sleeping.
I am sleeping.
- Well, do you want to work out?
- No.
Ah, but I'm bored.
God, so clingy so early in the morning.
Let's hang out. Hm?
I'll send my address. Come.
Okay, sounds good.
Oh shit!
Fuck! Goddammit. Stop!
You son of a bitch!
Are you all right?
Uh, okay, wait here.
Who?
Huh?
Why'd you follow me?
Tell me who sent you.
To help.
What? Help who?
I thought that man was being chased,
and, uh, I didn't know what was going on.
- God fucking dammit.
- Huh?
That asshole is a fake.
- Just butt out of things you don't know.
Motherfucker.
Huh?
What brings you here?
Everything went well.
I mean with Mi-yeon's surgery yesterday.
Oh, really? And how is she doing now?
She's good, sir.
She's recovering very well.
It's all thanks to you.
If you hadn't helped us back then, sir,
my daughter might have died.
Here.
My husband had the good fortune
of moving over to a larger company,
so he just received his severance.
I came here
as soon as the money hit our accounts
because I wanted to pay you back
before I paid anyone else.
You can take your time to pay me back.
First, pay back your urgent debts.
Oh, no, sir.
Please. Please accept this.
I finally have some piece of mind.
Thank you so much, sir.
Thank you so much. Thank you so much.
Thank you.
MI-YEON'S MOTHER APRIL 14TH, 2018
20 MILLION WON
KOREAN ANTIQUE MALL
I found Yang Jae-myeong.
He tried telling me he had no money,
so I took this from him.
This watch goes for over 20 million won.
So what?
Yang Jae-myeong borrowed ten million won.
Yeah, plus interest.
Oh, did you get hurt?
I got in a scuffle
with Yang Jae-myeong.
By the way,
while we're already on the subject,
you and I need to talk.
Have some rice cakes first.
We need to talk.
Don't try to change the subject.
How long are you going to keep at it?
What?
Lending people money with no interest.
I mean, it's not profitable.
What do you mean by that?
I always pay you
your 30% in commission fees.
Not for me. For you, Grandpa.
You know Mi-yeon's mother?
Yeah, and?
She dropped by earlier
and paid back the entire sum in cash.
And that's the interest?
Hyeon-ju.
A sick child got a timely operation
that saved her.
Because I lent them money,
her parents didn't have to use their home
as collateral for a loan.
And now, when their child's better,
she has a home to go to.
You and I saved a family.
This is the most precious form of interest
in the world.
Well, anyway, I heard something
while digging around
for Yang Jae-myeong's whereabouts.
He and his crew are dressing up
as homeless people
and robbing the actual homeless
of their IDs
to take out loans in their names.
And who are these people?
They're not exactly the cream of the crop.
They met in prison.
You knew this,
and you went all by yourself?
Should I have you tag along next time?
Anyway, let me do some digging.
I think I will find something interesting.
As long as you're not in danger, okay?
Sure.
PRESIDENT MOON GWANG-MU
MARINE
IF IT DOESN'T WORK, MAKE IT WORK!
Hello?
Hi. Oh, is this a bad time?
No, sir. No, please go ahead.
Yes, I wanted to ask you a favor
to find someone.
One second, please.
All right, I'm listening.
"A good person."
"A skilled bodyguard
who is familiar with the loan business."
All right, sir.
I will find the best candidates.
I promise I will find the best.
I'll leave it in your hands.
Yes, sir. Anytime.
Mayweather is the top dog. No doubt.
But Mayweather feels
more like a businessman
than an actual boxer.
That's right.
My guy's in it for the money,
but he is ridiculously good at it.
Probably made a few hundred billion.
Does money matter to you?
What could matter more than money?
The heart of a boxer.
What?
- Dude.
- No, No. Sorry.
It's just you got so serious
all of a sudden.
You looked so serious
that it really caught me off guard.
Elaborate on this boxer's heart.
Hm.
I think Manny Pacquiao
is the best example because--
Pow! Pow, pow, Pacquiao! Pow, pow.
Come on, dude. Let me have my moment.
I never cut you off, man.
I'm sorry, marine.
I will never cut you off.
Well, I really admire Pacquiao's heart,
you know? He never gives up.
Okay, I can give him that,
but Mayweather made a lot more money.
But I bet a lot more kids started dreaming
of becoming a boxer because of Pacquiao.
That's true for me at least.
That's the kind of person I want to be.
A person who shows
that with strong will and undying passion,
anyone will be able to achieve
all of their dreams.
It's windy today.
That is a true boxer's heart
and the kind of hope we should inspire
in the people watching us.
- A boxer's heart--
- Hey, this is ready.
Let's eat.
Here.
- Is it good?
- So good.
Hey, what do you do for a living?
I used to teach gym classes
at a kindergarten my friend runs.
A gym teacher of sorts.
Ah, that doesn't suit you, right?
What do you mean?
Kids fucking love me.
Well, anyway,
I used to do that in the morning,
then worked out in the afternoons.
Since the kindergarten shut down,
I'm in a bind.
Hey, wanna go on deliveries with me?
You can make some serious money
on parcel runs.
- Is the pay good?
- Yeah.
If we put our minds to it,
we could probably make 200,000 each.
For real?
Yeah, delivery work is also good cardio.
And you get to work on
your non-boxing muscles,
so it's good for your balance too.
- Ah, killing two birds with one stone.
- Three birds.
Huh?
You make money, get your cardio in,
and work on your balance.
Yeah, cardio and balance are the same.
Uh, no, they're not.
Wait, but aren't you supposed to compete
in the Super Series
since you won
the Rookie of the Year tournament?
Mm-hm, but it's been postposed
due to COVID.
How much longer?
There's nothing I can do.
Except I'll make sure I'm ready to fight
whenever the time actually comes.
You know… you have a boxer's heart.
Hm?
- Come on, Pacquiao.
- Right now?
Whoa…
Man, how could you hit me for real?
Whoa, my bad. Sorry.
Hey, come here, come here. Come here.
Let go. Let go.
- Come here. Let go. Come here. Come here.
- Whoa! Whoa!
Come here. Hey, Kim Gun-woo!
Everyone, cheers!
Now for today's main event.
The greatest show on Earth!
Cracking a watermelon with In-beom!
Everyone, come on! Make your bets now!
A million that he fails!
Hey! Three million on his success.
And if I'm the winner of this pot,
everything is on me!
Beom,
I know you can crack it,
but I'm gonna bet four million
that you can't
- Kang In-beom!
- Let's go!
Kang In-beom!
He cracked it!
Tteokbokki for all! Yeah!
Let's have some tteokbokki!
Awesome job!
Woo!
I did well, didn't I?
DEAREST MAYOR
Shh. Quiet. Quiet!
Yes, Mr. Mayor.
Yes.
I understand, sir.
I will let him know.
Have a good evening, sir.
The mayor… has just decided that
he will back the casino bid.
- Yes.
- Yes!
I have prepared… a small gift for you,
Mr. Park, in honor of your birthday.
Open it.
Almost four kilos.
Mr. Park, these gold turtles are so clean
that no one will know if you have them.
I give you this with the hope
that our relationship will continue
for a long time.
So I would appreciate if you take them.
You don't want to be in City Hall forever.
I know you have big dreams, Mr. Park.
If you plan on going
to the National Assembly,
you will definitely need money.
Let us forge a lasting partnership.
I will support you every way I can.
My money never has known failure.
You can rest assured.
- Hey. Hey!
- Jeez.
Hey, where are we going?
Please get in carefully.
We'll take you home.
Let's go.
And Assemblyman Seo's building?
Just wait until Friday, sir.
All the stores will have
over 20 million in interest.
I think the small stores
need a little grilling.
People tend to give up faster
if they see their first-floor storefront
in complete shambles
every time they come into work, you know?
I'll do as you wish, sir.
Since Mr. Jung is not feeling well
and can't join you,
call them and tell them to send over
15 intimidating men.
Beom can wrap things up.
Should they be armed?
There's no need.
Tell them to suit up
and make sure that everyone is masked.
Sir, I think five men should be enough.
I'm sure that the boss has his reasons.
You're right.
I've made a huge mistake.
You shitheads, there you go again.
Come on. Focus.
Where should we begin?
Huh?
Oh, hello. Good evening.
Why didn't you keep your promise?
What?
You agreed to an extension fee
in exchange for a lowered interest rate.
Uh, what?
But you needed to pay that extension fee,
which is 10% of the principal,
within 24 hours of signing.
It says so on the contract.
But because you failed to do so,
your extension
has accrued 40 million in interest.
Not to mention
your credit score has dropped,
so your interest rate has gone up to 20%.
We really… started
with the purest of intentions.
You ruined everything, damn it!
What are you going to do now?
Do you have that kind of money?
I will call the police.
Police?
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Hey, Mom.
Hey, son, where are you?
- I'm almost there.
- Okay, I'm at the store.
And a bunch of strange people came over…
Strange people? Who?
They're still here.
Mom? What's going on?
Where the hell
do you think you're going?
Who the hell are you? Get lost!
Hey! I told you to scram, asshole!
This jackass! Hey, you!
- What's going on? Get him.
- You shithead!
Who the hell is this guy?
Fuck!
- Come here.
- Little shit!
- Mom, are you all right?
- Yes.
You aren't hurt, are you?
I'm okay. I'm okay.
Who are you?
Who are you to do this to our store?
I asked you, "Who are you?"
Calm down, kid.
Your mother has borrowed some money
from our company.
Mm-hm
So what do you want?
Pay us back.
Pay us for the damages first.
Go ahead.
Mom, it's okay.
Just go over there for a second.
Gun-woo!
That's enough.
Hey, I appreciate people with grit.
Because guys with grit…
They can get anything done.
Do you want to work for me?
I will make sure that…