Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.be or dramacool.club
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
♪That day♪
♪Nothing stays together forever♪
♪I've quit romance♪
♪Who hasn't failed again♪
♪Crying in death♪
♪And in life♪
♪Even now♪
♪We keep learning♪
♪It's no surprise♪
♪Being happy is so hard♪
♪Weirdly, I became a role model♪
♪On the day we met again, we said hi♪
♪It was a reminder,
a test, and a complaint♪
♪Who can do anything without regret♪
♪I am all right♪
♪May you live in peace♪
♪Let the world roar♪
♪Sounds like a carnival♪
♪Being alive is never dull♪
♪How wonderful to be free♪
♪I became even better without you♪
♪Nothing can be perfect♪
♪We bless each other in pain♪
♪We nod and smile♪
♪May we both be well♪
= Love's Ambition=
=Episode 14=
Welcome back.
The soup will be ready soon.
Fang Lei picked up Haochen
after school today.
She told me
that Shen Haochen is your son.
Is this true?
Yes.
He's my illegitimate son.
Why did you hide this from me?
Didn't I tell you
that do not say anything
affecting our relationship?
When do you want to tell me?
Never?
I always thought
you loved and understood me,
so you've silently supported me
in pursuing my career.
Only today did I realize
that you just wanted to use me
and my career
as your tools.
You just want to use
my profession to win over Jiang Yun
and every business partner
you needed for your career.
You're just trying to use me.
But I don't understand.
Why did you lie to me?
Speaking of it,
you're in no position
(Xu Yan's Profile)
to question me.
When I first met you,
you possess the charm I like.
You are interesting enough.
My mom is extremely particular,
and few women could win her favor,
but you could.
You get along with her.
I prefer smart women.
Second,
you have the qualities I admire
and the ability to endure.
If I find a woman
from a prestigious background,
they might not tolerate
the mistakes of my youth
or accept my son.
You look like a proper noble lady,
but without their arrogance
and unpleasant temper.
Third,
your ambition.
From the start,
you wanted to host a Family Feast,
and then you aimed
to be a news anchor.
It actually benefits my career.
Yes, I lied to you.
But didn't I generously provide
full support to you?
Lin Tao.
(I put pressure)
(on the bank where he was working.)
Zhou Zeyuan.
He blackmailed and threatened you.
When he was at his wit's end,
I gave him funding.
When a gambler is at his wit's end,
he won't turn back.
He would only take a big gamble.
Then, I put him to prison.
Zhou Zeyuan was arrested.
Because I lied to you,
I'm willing to spend money
to maintain your lies unrevealed.
All you need to do
is being a perfect wife
with a respectable job,
keeping my family pleased.
And me?
As your husband,
I'll fulfill my duty
to boost your career.
Stop looking at me so pitifully.
Didn't you approach me
with ulterior motives?
You tried every mean
to become my wife,
just wanting my wealth, my connections
and all my resources.
You used me to build your credibility,
winning the public trust.
Do you think this is absolutely safe?
They come back to me
once you turn around.
My generosity
made your sweet dreams come true.
Do you know that?
So everything you did to me
was all lies.
I just have one question.
Have you ever...
Have you ever truly loved me?
From the moment I knew you were a fraud,
I would never fall in love with you.
I lied to you too.
I didn't expect you
to genuinely love me.
Just take what we need.
I understand now.
I finally understand everything now.
So,
when I made your mom happy,
when I treated Haochen well,
when I pleased you,
I thought those watches,
cars, and jewelry you gave me
were out of love.
But to you,
they were just bonus to me, right?
It's kind of my recognition to you
for meeting my standards.
Xu Yan.
If you dwell on this,
it would make you look foolish.
♪When I melt into the crowd♪
(In this world,)
(there's no perfect choice.)
(You have to know)
(the choices you make)
(and the price should be paid.)
♪To the corner where I sheltered
from rain and tears♪
♪Only then did I realize
what I had was precious♪
♪Misplaced glory is just danger's omen♪
♪When city lights light,
but there's nowhere to turn to♪
♪How should I compromise?♪
♪When life resumes and settles the past♪
♪No need to hide this flustered state♪
♪Let my candor redeem my recklessness♪
♪Forgive myself♪
♪What kind of me♪
♪Is the best me?♪
♪Who defines it?♪
(I have something for you too.)
Your writing is full of emotion.
It deeply moved me.
I believe
you love osmanthus jam very much.
♪Is the best me?♪
After the nurse removed the needle,
I feared you'd keep bleeding,
so applied a band-aid.
♪Is the best me?♪
So what's this?
A reward for model behavior.
Yan.
Your kindness
makes me want to give you every single
good thing I see.
(Wangda Road)
(Looking at Shen Haoming now)
(makes me recall a saying.)
("Amidst the crowd.)
(in the dark dusk,)
(you are unrecognizable.)
(And we won't meet again.")
Have you decided?
If you want a divorce,
I'll agree.
The New District project just launched.
My career and family
can't tolerate any disruptions.
My upcoming schedule
requires your presence.
The New District project
launch ceremony is in two days.
As my wife, you must attend.
I don't want anyone
to notice any changes between us.
What if I say...
I can't do it?
You aren't officially part
of the News Department.
I assume you don't want
any mistakes in this process.
(Huanhuan's Call)
What's wrong?
Yan, the editing
for the last recording is all done.
When will you come?
Hello?
Yan, are you listening?
I am coming.
That's all the news for today.
Thank you for watching.
See you.
Great job. Wrap it up.
Thank you.
Xu Yan!
Elegant and composed.
Performed well.
I knew I was right about you.
In today's meeting,
the leaders publicly praised you.
They decided to have you host
the next Financial Forum.
As you know,
hosting the Financial Forum
is the ultimate recognition
from the leaders.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Get some rest.
You're the backbone now.
Your health comes first.
Poor rest affects your performance.
Alright, I'm leaving.
Goodbye, Ms. Xu.
See you, Ms. Xu.
(I can't refute)
(anything that Shen Haoming said.)
(I can't tell if my career's success)
(is due to the support)
(he provided to me.)
(If I quit being)
(as Mr. Shen's wife,)
(will all this enthusiasm)
(and smiles to me remain?)
(Fang Lei's Call)
You're back.
Wash up. Dinner is ready.
I made Western food for you.
Haven't cooked this in ages.
Wonder if I've gotten rusty.
Get to the point.
Haoming.
I've been thinking a lot.
You said I married you for wealth
and Shen family's
resources and connections.
As someone benefiting from all this,
I admit
everything I've achieved now
can't be separated from you
and the Shen family.
So I won't deny
I made the mistake first.
I sincerely apologize to you.
Support Admin Watch
on kissasia.be or
dramacool.club Translate
by =Qari= @Team Viki
Besides,
I'll genuinely accept Haochen
just as you wanted.
I'll properly take care of this family
and manage my career well.
I just want to tell you
my love for you have been genuine,
and I truly love you.
After everything we've been through,
how could all of it be fake?
I know I was wrong.
I truly understand now.
Can we please...
start over?
I love you.
I truly do.
Just go for the fame or wealth.
That way, I would think
you're being sincere.
Like you said,
we agreed
whether at work
or at home,
we stick to our roles
and maintain mutual benefit.
Isn't this perfect?
I recognize your value as a partner.
After you've become
an official news anchor,
I'll throw you a grand
celebration party.
Wish you have a success.
So you still don't believe
that I truly love you.
Right.
By the way,
there's no need for such efforts.
I admit your acting is superb,
but you can only
fool me once,
not again.
Delicious. Have a seat.
Let's eat.
(The current me,)
(like the boy
who cried "the wolf is coming",)
(told too many lies.)
(So when I tell the truth,)
(none will believe me.)
(The sandcastle)
(will eventually collapse.)
(I deserve everything)
(caused by my action.)
(Jinda Group Huanyu International Project
Groundbreaking Ceremony)
Ladies and gentlemen,
good day.
Welcome you
to Jinda Group New District
real estate project's
groundbreaking ceremony.
Jinda Group has long upheld
the concept of architecture in nature.
This project
must boost transformation
of the New District
and bring greater comfort and joy
to all our citizens.
Now, we'll proceed to
(Guest)
today's groundbreaking ceremony,
the most exciting moment.
All dignitaries and guests,
please come up here.
(Groundbreaking)
As hosts,
smile.
Take the golden shovels
and break ground together.
Let's count down together.
Five, four, three, two, one!
Congratulations to success
of Jinda Group New District
real estate project's
groundbreaking ceremony!
(Groundbreaking)
(We're reporters from Entertainment Frontline.)
Mr. Shen.
Regarding the New District project,
you've put your wife's creative
in the interior design concepts.
Is that true?
Right.
Her dedication
and professional competence
demonstrate remarkable wisdom.
I deeply respect her capabilities
and I'm always open to her insights.
What's the secret
to your strong bond?
Can you share some tips?
No secret at all.
Luck comes first.
Then,
mutual admiration
between spouses is crucial.
I admire her capabilities so much.
But what moves me most
is that she can choose an easy job,
even to be a housewife,
yet she chose
to pursue her childhood dreams
without pause,
striving tirelessly till today.
This deeply moves me.
So I want to cherish her more.
How would you describe your husband now?
What drew you to Mr. Shen?
Could you share with us?
My husband...
is exceptional in every way,
truly impeccable.
So I'm lucky to meet him.
But most importantly,
he respects me,
(Xu Yan's Profile)
trusts me,
and supports me.
They say
when choosing a husband,
we should choose someone
who truly cherishes us.
My husband not only does this,
but
exceeds my expectations.
I have to do better.
Thank you.
That's all for today's interview.
Please prepare for
the group photo later.
Thank you.
Have a big smile.
Here we go. Smile!
Perfect.
You performed terribly today.
Especially during the press conference.
You remained cold
and unsmiling
throughout.
Tomorrow is a charity gala.
I hope the same won't happen again.
As long as you perform well,
I guarantee you'll obtain the permanent
news anchor position.
Thank you, Mr. Shen.
(WeChat Message)
(Fang Lei: Can we meet?)
(Can we meet?)
(Han Weiping's Call)
What's wrong?
Fang Lei said
she'd kill herself if you don't show up.
Where is she?
At her home.
Got it.
If I'm to keep playing
the role of a good wife,
should I ask my husband
about things like this?
Unless I choose
to tell you myself,
don't ask any question.
- Mr. Shen.
- Where is she?
Living room.
You finally showed up?
You wanted to kill yourself?
Go ahead. I'm waiting.
Think I don't dare to?
Didn't answer my calls
or reply to my messages,
yet you showed up now?
So you do get scared.
You told Xu Yan about Haochen.
You deserve to die.
You still came here at this hour.
You were already in bed,
yet came to another woman.
This just proves
she only wants your wealth.
You're off the New District project.
What do you mean?
Used me and then kicked me out?
Never!
I'm not leaving!
Your bonus and compensation
will be paid in full.
Come to the office
and hand over your duties.
I won't let you off!
I'll kill myself!
I'll! Really!
Miss Fang, have a seat.
Why are you still here?
Get out now!
I suggest you stop escalating it.
I've accepted Mr. Shen's money,
and our cooperation will only end
until you stop making a mess.
It turns out all these dramas
get you nowhere.
Why keep going
and making me work overtime?
Well,
let me introduce you to some decent men.
They are my former clients.
Good guys, recently divorced.
Good for you to kill time.
Are you insane?
Why always keep an eye on me?
Studying homewreckers
like you
helps my work.
Get lost!
(Jingzhou Yuekang Hospital Outpatient)
Nurse Liu,
has Dr. Yu finished his surgery?
Just finished,
debriefing the family now.
Thank you.
Dr. Yu.
Before the operation, you told me that
the first operation
would take three to four hours.
But in reality,
six full hours!
My child is so young.
He suffered so much!
Please calm down.
We inform families
about estimated surgery duration.
But we also clarify
times vary between patients.
It's only an estimate.
Our priority is to ensure
patient safety
and prevent severe
lung damage during procedures.
It often takes three hours,
six at maximum.
This is normal.
I wonder if it's because
of your incompetence.
We're canceling the surgery.
Go now.
Get your supervisor now!
I want a satisfied explanation today!
Hello.
You might not know Dr. Yu well.
He's exceptionally skilled
and dedicated.
He sees 60 to 70 patients
daily in clinic.
After that, he has
to go perform surgery.
Standing over 10 hours.
He can't even get meals,
and sometimes can't even drink water.
You could ask around to verify.
Many of his patients
speak highly of him.
You brought me here
just to tell me
how hard-working Dr. Yu is?
What does this have to do
with my child?
Well, I'm sorry.
Not only that.
I just wonder
if you could show some understanding.
Of course, I understand
how you're feeling.
When a child gets sick,
no parent stays calm.
And the expenses are huge.
I just wonder
if I can help ease
your burden somehow
and give you proper assurance.
What?
Yes.
Here.
Please take this.
Who are you?
What's this with you?
I'm Dr. Yu's wife.
Absurd!
Bribing families to gain sympathy
for medical staff?
The complaint reached my office!
What?
Who bribed the families?
Your wife.
Yu Yiming.
When did you get married?
Why didn't I know it?
My wife?
I'm single.
Wait,
are you mistaken?
The girl who keeps visiting you.
I'm sorry.
So sorry
I caused you trouble.
I gave her money
just to help relieve
her financial pressure,
so you can do your surgery smoothly.
I didn't think that much.
I truly realize my mistake.
I'm sorry. So sorry.
I was so careless.
This is my fault.
I swear
it'll never happen again.
Did the hospital punish you?
I'll go explain it.
I'll apologize to the family personally,
and then clarify with hospital admin
that you had nothing to do with this.
It's all my fault.
I'll go do it.
Want to apologize?
Come with me.
Hold on.
Take them.
(I Miss You in China)
Is this enough?
You bought me ice cream.
I forgive you.
Not just that,
I should thank you.
After our communication
and explanations,
she understands
the surgery's complexity
and multiple procedures needed.
She's willing to cooperate with us
to continue the treatment.
Regarding your wife's actions,
she forgave her.
Yes! Fantastic!
I'm sorry.
What?
She kept asking me
about our relationship.
I didn't know how to answer
and said I'm your wife.
Sorry.
- Hello.
Hello.
Long time no see.
Today makes a difference.
See you.
Lei.
- You're here too.
- Yes.
Where are you sitting?
Over there.
So far away?
Can you even see the auction items?
Come here.
Sit here.
Have you been tired?
Not really.
Exhausted?
No.
Good then.
Working all day,
you must take care.
Lei.
I just noticed
your complexion looks dull.
Been staying up late?
No, my complexion has been great.
Good then.
I wanted to tell you
I've been really busy,
working overtime.
If you are available,
could you help
look after Haoming more?
I know you two
studied abroad together,
so you know him well.
Fang Lei.
The investors for Qingwan Project,
Mr. Qiu and his wife are at table six.
Go chat with them.
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.be or dramacool.club
Translate by =Qari= @Team Viki
Sure.
Don't tell her to do so.
She's seated here.
Just give her a break.
They can always chat another time.
Listen to me, stay here.
Look, it's starting.
Everyone,
welcome to
the 2024 Celebrity Entrepreneurs
Charity Gala.
Charity Spirit, Forever Love.
All proceeds from tonight's auction
will support Hope Primary Schools.
Let's give warm applause
to wish tonight's auction
a complete success.
Thank you.
Now I'll present
our first auction item.
(Angel's Tear Diamond Ring)
This ring features
a 7.09-carat royal blue
sapphire from Kashmir.
The color is fancy black blue.
Clarity is VS1.
It's like an angel's tear.
Not just jewelry,
but a spiritual symbol
and an emblem of love.
We'll start bidding
at 500,000 RMB.
Bidding begins now.
600,000.
600,000 from left.
650,000.
650,000 from right.
Any higher bids?
700,000.
700,000 from behind.
Current bid 700,000.
Any higher bids than 700,000?
Last call!
700,000.
One million.
Any higher bids?
Bid stands at one million.
One million.
Anyone else?
1.2 million.
1.2 million!
Any higher bids?
1.4 million!
Back row bids 1.4 million.
1.6 million.
Left side offers 1.6 million.
Any more bids?
1.6 million.
First call.
Second call.
Three million.
♪Like fireworks that loved♪
♪Rushing toward the stars♪
♪Undaunted by pain♪
♪Fearless of flames♪
♪Even if just a fleeting sparkle♪
♪We shed tears♪
♪Deep blue seas turn to foam♪
♪We regained freedom♪
♪If you remember me♪
♪Then I'm pleased♪
♪I just wanna take my time tonight♪
♪To do all the things I said I'd try♪
♪I go surfing, go diving, go driving,
and go flying to a different place♪
♪I go drink, go party, and go dance♪
♪Even if I'm lonely♪
♪Cause I just have been hurt
too many times♪
♪I'm giving it all to get nothing back♪
♪I was lost in the dark,
and it's too hurt to even see♪
♪See the world and how it flows.
We never let go♪
♪So I'll take my time♪
♪To reignite♪
♪The love I should deserve♪
♪When the time is right♪
♪You realize♪
♪It will all be alright♪
♪Cause I just have been hurt
too many times♪
♪I'm giving it all to get nothing back♪
♪I was lost in the dark,
and it's too hurt to even see♪
♪See the world and how it flows.
We never let go♪
♪So I'll take my time♪
♪To reignite♪
♪The love I should deserve♪
♪When the time is right♪
♪You realize♪
♪It will all be alright♪