Previously
on Captain Tsubasa...
Meiwa's team captain,
Kojiro Hyuga,
burst into Nankatsu's
training match
to challenge
star goalkeeper
Genzo Wakabayashi...
and to show off
his skills.
After his teammates
criticized him
for his aggressive
playing style...
Hyuga decided not to
play in the last game...
and told his teammates
to win without him.
In addition, Wakabayashi
suffered a leg injury...
and will not
be able to play
until he has
completely recovered.
Thanks to Tsubasa
and his teammate's efforts,
Nankatsu was
able to advance
without the help of
goalkeeper Wakabayashi.
What challenges await
this young team?
We are here
for today's elimination game
to see who will represent
Shizuoka Prefecture
in the National
Tournament.
Today's match features
team Nankatsu
versus team Shimada.
Good luck to both teams!
Nankatsu, Nankatsu,
we will win!
Shimada, Shimada,
we will triumph!
NANKATSU SC LOCKER ROOM
What? So Genzo's not going to play?
Why isn't he, coach?
I'm sorry, boys,
but unfortunately,
Genzo is still injured.
-What?
Hey, guys, don't you worry.
For now, I'll just rest,
but I will be ready to play
in the final match.
Shimada is not
a strong team.
I feel very good
about the match.
I'm sure we can win
without him.
Hey, relax, guys, I'll be
ready to play with you.
Yuzo...
I'm counting on you
to protect the goal.
I know you can do it!
I will!
I won't let you down!
Get better soon, yeah?
All right, get some rest.
You'll see that
we'll defeat Shimada.
You just relax!
Mhm.
SHIMADA ELEMENTARY SOCCER TEAM LOCKER ROOM
You have all done a great job so far, kids.
But our opponent today
is Nankatsu.
Don't take them
for granted, boys.
-Yes, Coach!
I don't want any of you
thinking that we can't win.
Remember,
the first thing to do
is study the opposing team
to find their weakness
and exploit it to beat them!
-Yes, Coach!
Don't worry, we'll give it
everything we've got!
[opening theme]
Episode 11: Surprisingly Difficult Match.
The second semifinal match
to represent Shizuoka Prefecture
is about to begin.
It's Nankatsu versus Shimada.
The Nankatsu boys
are the favorite
coming into today's match.
At the Center Forward
position
we have Tsubasa Ozora,
who led the league
in goals scored
with nine goals over
the course of the season.
Also, Goalkeeper
Genzo Wakabayashi
has kept his streak going
with zero goals in six games
and looks to keep going.
However,
due to an injury,
Genzo won't play
in today's match...
and player number 12,
Yuzo Morisaki,
will replace him
in the net today.
The Shimada squad
is known for
their incredible teamwork
and endurance.
Thanks to that,
they are here today.
In the first
semifinal match,
Shimizu advanced
to the final...
thanks to captain
Morimichi Kawakami...
the goalkeeper with
the same stature
as Genzo Wakabayashi.
The winner of this match
will move on
to face Shimizu.
Now,
may the best team win!
Wow! We're playing
against Nankatsu!
They look like they're
all great players!
-It's a pleasure to play
-against you Team Nankatsu!
Teppei, what's wrong
with them? I don't get it.
They're very friendly.
Go!
You won't get by me!
Looks like this is
gonna be pretty easy!
Mamoru, look.
But why aren't they moving?
Maybe they don't want
the ball or something.
Well, they don't seem
to care about it.
Hah! Well, that will
make it easier.
Take it, Tsubasa!
Mamoru Izawa
sends a long pass
-to Tsubasa Ozora!
-I got it!
The pass is
intercepted by team Shimada.
Now they have
the possession!
Excellent control, Koichi!
-What?!
-No way!
Where did he appear from?
Captain!
Koichi Fujisawa
-passes the ball to
-Where do you think
-captain Junichi Nagasaki,
-you're going?
who's streaking
down the field!
Junichi receives
the pass easily.
You'll see!
Now Shimada
is moving down the field.
They're approaching
Nankatsu's goal!
Why're you standing there,
Yuzo?
You have to go for the ball.
Get out of the crease!
Huh?
Yes!
All right!
Get ready for this!
What?!
Junichi Nagasaki
shoots a high lob shot.
The ball's headed
toward Yuzo Morisaki!
Oh, no,
goalkeeper Yuzo hesitated,
and ball is in the back
of the net!
Goal for Shimada!
All right!
I didn't think it'd go in!
-We did it! That's the way
-I can't believe that
-it's done, guys!
-we're beating Nankatsu!
What the heck, goalie?
Are you crazy?!
You couldn't stop
such a lousy shot?!
-That's embarrassing.
-Uhh...
-You should be punished!
-Sanae, calm down.
Shimada is now winning
1 to nothing...
with a lob shot
from inside the box.
Now Nankatsu will have
a tough battle
ahead of them.
We have a surprising
match on our hands!
I thought Nankatsu was
a strong team.
I'm really sorry.
Hmm, relax, don't beat
yourself up, Yuzo.
Remember,
we scored nine goals
in our previous matches.
Don't worry,
we'll get this one back.
Relax!
Thank you, guys.
We'll show them that
they can't beat us
so easily!
We'll tie the game
in an instant!
Today's
elimination match
between Shimada
and Nankatsu
has taken
an unexpected turn.
No one would've imagined
at this point...
that Shimada had scored
a goal against Nankatsu.
It looks like
it's going to rain.
SAITAMA TOURNAMENT SEMI-FINAL
Semi-finals match of the Saitama Prefecture.
NANBU FC MEIWA FC
The referee blows the whistle
for half time.
NANBU FC MEIWA FC
The Nanbu team has the lead,
three goals to nothing.
Good job!
What a nightmare.
Captain Hyuga said that
we could win the matches
on our own.
Hmm, you can't win
without me, huh?
Huh?
-Captain!
-Well, what's wrong, guys?
I thought you'd all win
with your lovely
playing style, huh?
Captain, don't say that!
You have to play for us!
We can't win without you!
Please, Captain.
-Please, Captain!
All right, I will...
but first,
you must promise me
you will play by my rules.
-What?! You want us to play
-following your style?
Exactly!
My style has never failed!
Only the strong
deserve to win!
And now,
the second half
is about to begin!
It looks like Meiwa
will make a substitution.
Substitution for Meiwa.
Nakamoto, number 13, out,
Hyuga, number 10, enters.
Seriously?!
Kojiro's going to play?!
He didn't play
in the first half,
but why's he playing now?
Substitution for Meiwa.
Koyama, number 14, out,
Sawada, number 15,
enters the match.
That's great! I'll finally
play alongside Kojiro!
But Captain, Takeshi
is only in fourth grade.
Are you sure?
Why did you put him
in to play with us?
In no time,
you'll understand why.
Takeshi is
a very important weapon.
Let's win this, all right?
Yeah!
The second half
of the elimination match
between Meiwa and Nanbu
to represent
the Saitama Prefecture
is about to begin!
NATIONAL JUVENILE SOCCER TOURNAMENT SHIZUOKA TOURNAMENT, SEMI-FINAL SECOND MATCH NANKATSU SC SHIMADA ELEMENTARY
Teppei Kisugi
takes a shot on goal!
Oh, what a shame!
It was a poor shot
from inside the box!
Nankatsu still
doesn't have a goal!
Son of a gun!
Teppei, why didn't you
pass the ball to Tsubasa?
He was in front of the net!
Because I wasn't marked,
so I took a shot!
Show off another day,
man. We're losing by a goal!
SHIZUOKA TOURNAMENT, SEMI-FINAL SECOND MATCH NANKATSU SC SHIMADA ELEMENTARY
Did you forget the score?
Focus!
Up to now, we've taken
more shots on goal,
and we've had more time
of possession.
Even so,
we still can't score!
I don't get what
they're doing!
It doesn't make sense.
The goalie for Shimada
makes a goal kick
to midfield.
Takeshi Kishida from Nankatsu
intercepts the pass.
Someone get him!
Here comes the tying goal!
Guys, go and mark him!
-Okay!
The Shimada club are
known for its defense,
as strong as a brick wall.
Three defenders are
now marking Mamoru Izawa!
Mamoru passes to
Teppei Kisugi!
Teppei gets close
and takes a shot!
Oh, but the goalie
is able to stop the ball!
Nankatsu aren't able
to apply pressure.
The Shimada defense
is too strong for them.
Why don't they pass
the ball to Tsubasa?!
And now,
we have finished
the first half
of the match.
The score is still
1 to nothing
in favor of Shimada.
This is something
we did not think
would be happening.
We are witnessing
a meltdown of Nankatsu,
who haven't been
able to score.
Care to tell me what
you are doing?
Your rhythm is horrible.
It looks like
you're all strangers!
Why don't you follow
Tsubasa's lead?
Well, we've been able
to make good passes
fairly easily.
After breaking
their defense,
I had a clear shot, Coach.
Hmm... I understand
why you feel that way,
but Tsubasa's
the only one who's
supposed to score the goals!
In the second half,
I want all of you to pass
the ball to Tsubasa!
-Understood?
-Yes, sir!
Please, Coach,
will you let me play
in the second half?
No, that won't be necessary.
I'm counting on you,
understood?
Understood!
-Huh?
It's starting to rain.
We've never seen anything
like this before!
Takeshi Sawada,
number 15,
weaves his way between
Nanbu defenders!
For a fourth grade boy,
he has a very impressive
football skill!
I didn't think Takeshi
could play like that!
Kojiro, it's yours!
Takeshi Sawada
crosses the ball to
Kojiro Hyuga,
who is in front
of the goal!
This is impressive!
Both players
have lifted their team
in the second half
to tie the game!
I want everyone
to mark Kojiro!
We won't let them score
any more goals!
-Get him!
Here's my shot!
The ref
blows the whistle
for full time!
The scoreboard
reads 4 to 3!
With their dramatic
comeback,
Meiwa will represent
Saitama
at the National
Tournament!
It's all thanks to
superstar captain,
Kojiro Hyuga.
He's definitely
someone to watch out for
in the upcoming
National Tournament!
We'll follow him closely!
Taro Misaki
intercepts the ball!
It seems that Nankatsu
refuse to give up.
Taro advances.
Taro, pass the ball!
Here!
Ah, oh, ugh!
Oh, what a shame!
Hajime Taki can't
control the ball
because of the rain!
It looks like luck
is on our side this time.
Hey!
What're you guys doing?!
The Shimada players
don't look tired.
They've played
several matches.
I don't get why they're
not tired right now.
-Listen, Coach...
-Huh?
Do you think I can see
the scouting report
for Shimada?
Well, yes, here.
No, that's not possible!
Nankatsu
has the ball again!
Izawa receives
the ball easily
-and sends a pass
-Tsubasa!
to Tsubasa!
-Okay! Ah!
-Oh, no!
The ball lands right
in a puddle of water!
According to the report,
Shimada don't attack
very often,
but they don't allow
many goals
scored against them.
Well, what does
all that mean?
In each game,
their opponents attack them
for the whole match.
But Shimada has
a solid defense
to recover the ball,
-and then they make
-Captain!
long passes
to attack the opposition...
to score a lucky goal.
Their strategy is
to counterattack!
So then, Shimada are a...
Yes! They specialize in
very strong defense!
Shimada sends
a long pass down field!
Hey, quick, everyone,
get back!
Junichi Nagasaki
takes a shot on goal!
Goal!
Shimada have now scored
their second goal!
Huh?!
We're two goals ahead,
Naoki.
I know, this is like a dream!
Very good!
Now the game is ours, boys.
We never had a player
good enough on the team
to be the goalscorer.
We could never score goals!
That's why we decided that
if we can't score,
we wouldn't allow
anyone to score
a single goal on us!
Our style of play
may be very passive,
but thanks to the hard work
and effort of the team...
the boys have shown
their true capabilities,
and I couldn't be
prouder of them!
The determination
of the Shimada boys
will always prevail!
All right!
This time, we will win!
This is
completely unexpected!
In the first ten minutes
of the second half,
Nankatsu are now losing
2 goals to nothing!
No!
We're not losing this match!
CAPTAIN TSUBASA
We'll be right back with Captain Tsubasa!
AFFILIATION: NANKATSU SC BIRTHDAY: MARCH 12 HEIGHT 158 CM WEIGHT: 45 KG BLOOD TYPE: A
NATIONAL JUVENILE SOCCER TOURNAMENT SHIZUOKA TOURNAMENT, SEMI-FINAL SECOND MATCH NANKATSU SC SHIMADA ELEMENTARY
And we're back!
With fifteen
minutes left in the match,
Nankatsu have
not been able
to break the defense
of Shimada.
Can Nankatsu
score the equalizer?
Listen, Coach!
Please put me in!
We have to counterattack
Shimada!
We have to force them
to break their defense
so they have to attack!
And then--
I won't let you play.
Listen, Genzo,
our objective is
to simply play at
the National Tournament.
Our objective is to win.
If we can't overcome
this obstacle...
there'll be no way
we can win the tournament,
so therefore,
the best thing...
is to lose
this game already
and avoid the humiliation!
But wait, Coach...
Shimada has returned
to their defensive
formation.
Can Nankatsu get close
to the goal to score?
Oh, Roberto!
Tsubasa won't lose, right?
I don't know.
It's difficult to know.
The whole team must
solve the problem.
What?
They're passing
the ball around
trying to break
Shimada's defense, but...
the rain is inhibiting them.
It's the first time
they've played in
these conditions.
Ughhh!
Overall,
Nankatsu has better
possession of the ball,
but due to the rain,
their speed, balance
and precision
has decreased significantly.
They're now playing
at the same level
as their opponents.
All of this gives Shimada
an advantage in the match,
-and it's a problem.
-Oh...
Worst part is they
stay marked on Tsubasa
so he can't go anywhere.
Although...
There goes Tsubasa!
He's looking for space!
He now has it and shoots!
But the ball goes directly
-into the goalie's hands!
-Ah!
But the ball slips
through the goalie's hands
and it looks like a goal
for Nankatsu!
But the defense miraculously
deflects the ball!
So Shimada
escapes a danger!
Nankatsu are
still scoreless!
-Good job, Naoki!
-Good deflection!
Not even Tsubasa can score.
What will we do?
They've lost.
This is Shimada's game.
Koichi
Fujisawa kicks the ball
and crosses it midfield.
The Nankatsu defenders
chase after it,
but the rain is
slowing them down.
I can't believe it.
-Tsubasa!
We're not going to lose!
Do you hear me?!
Look at
Tsubasa Ozora's tenacity!
It's motivating
his teammates
-as they go on the attack!
-Don't let them get close!
We have to stop them!
Let's focus, guys!
One-touch passes,
you hear me?!
Quickly, Taro!
Go!
Teppei!
Tsubasa!
All together now.
We have to support him!
Yeah!
Incredible!
Nankatsu is making
one-touch passes
and the ball is no longer
getting stuck in the mud!
Good job!
That's how it's done,
Tsubasa!
A football team
isn't just one player.
Control the pace
of the game...
and make them follow you!
Here!
Even without Genzo,
if they work as a team,
they can win the match!
Nankatsu
are now on the attack,
and they are near
Shimada's goal!
Tsubasa!
Tsubasa Ozora
jumps wonderfully
into the air for
a scissor kick
that's headed toward
the goal!
-Ah!
-Goal!
Thanks to Taro Misaki's
beautiful cross,
Tsubasa put
a powerful shot on goal!
Now they just need
one goal to tie!
-You did it, Tsubasa!
-Yes!
That's how it's done!
Perfect!
Now we need just one more!
That goal
breaks Shimada's record
for most shutouts.
Such a pity!
Relax, guys,
don't worry about it.
Will Nankatsu be able to
score the tying goal,
or will Shimada hold out
until the end?
There five minutes left
until the final whistle.
Take it, Tsubasa!
Here, Taro!
To you!
Taro Misaki makes
a beautiful cross
to the center!
The ball is mine!
The rain
can't stop them now!
Mamoru Izawa
heads the ball
between two
Shimada defenders
to Tsubasa...
And Tsubasa heads ball
past the goalkeeper!
Goal for Nankatsu!
Nankatsu tie the game
with just a few minutes
left to play!
You did it, Tsubasa!
Their team is really strong!
Yes.
It looks like they're
finally showing
their strength.
What should we do now?
Should we continue
to play on defense or what?
-What?
-Well, yeah,
we've always played
like that, Captain.
I think it's
the perfect time
for Nankatsu to see
our true strength.
How about this time we play
on the offense
instead of playing
defensively?
-Hm...
You have to get
out of your comfort zone!
-Huh?
Our work as a team
has always been admirable,
right?
We're nobody if we play
individually,
but together,
I know we can do it!
If we're going to win,
we have to do it properly,
by attacking!
That way, we will be
honoring our beloved coach!
Let's play football
the Shimada way!
-Yeah!
Incredible!
Shimada have broken
their line of defense,
and now, they're heading
toward Nankatsu's goal!
-What is this?!
Nankatsu
don't know what to do
about this!
Shimada now has complete
control of the ball
and the pitch!
What are you doing?!
Don't just stand there.
Mark them!
I got it!
All together!
Shimada is now advancing
toward the goal!
What a sight to see them
playing like this!
Right now, the match
could go either way!
We'll show them what
Shimada is made of!
-Yeah!
-They're a great team!
-Mhm!
I feel as though
they enjoy soccer!
So now, I won't
give up either!
Tsubasa tries to take
the ball with a slide tackle.
But Shimada maintains
possession and regroups!
No!
That's it!
That's the true
Shimada spirit!
Football is about
working as a team!
We all help each other
like brothers...
on the path to victory!
I can't believe it!
Junichi Nagasaki
-centers the ball
-Naoki!
to Naoki Uesugi,
who is all alone
and unmarked!
And
goalkeeper Yuzo Morisaki
makes a save!
What a nice attempt!
Good, Yuzo!
Yes, Genzo!
I can do it!
The goalkeeper
fires a long kick...
launching Nankatsu's
counterattack!
Everybody, get back,
quickly!
Number 10
has the ball for Nankatsu!
-He's going straight
-It's mine!
for the goal!
Shimada can't
catch up to him!
Now it's Tsubasa
against the goalie!
Goal!
And the referee blows
the final whistle!
Yeah!
Nankatsu is victorious!
They were able to
erase the deficit,
and now they have
advanced to final!
Nankatsu will now face
Shimizu in the final,
and the winner
will represent
the Shizuoka Prefecture.
With his last goal,
Tsubasa has now scored
hat tricks
in six consecutive
matches!
Good job!
Great job today, boys.
Hey, guys, don't be sad!
We gave it all we had
against Nankatsu.
We should be proud of that!
We were a worthy and
resilient opponent!
-Thanks for a great game!
It was really fun playing!
-Good luck in the final!
-Thank you!
-I hope we play again!
-Yeah, me too!
Well, we're counting
on you guys
to represent our city
with dignity, all right?!
We won't let you down!
Shimada today
gave us a lesson
to work as a team.
They made us see
what our team needs...
what we have to do.
Hey, Tsubasa, now we just
have to win the final!
Yeah.
Now...
together, we will win
the final!
-Yeah!
[ending theme]