Solar.
Are you going to take medicine to sleep?
Do we really need to rush
and push him out of our lives like this?
I can feel
that he's not okay with this at all.
I probably didn't wake up on our anniversary.
Is that a music CD?
Play it for me, please.
Hey, Sun!
Who knows?
Your song might just be the thing
that helps Sun turn into Solar faster.
Can I cuddle you all night?
Yes!
There! He's fallen asleep!
I'm not asleep yet!
What are you doing, uncles and auntie?
Why are you making me watch this guitar clip?
Just go.
Go. It's time for class.
But I want to know.
Here.
I'm giving you this, so tell me.
I'm giving you this
so I don't have to tell you.
Go!
Hurry up!
Looks like just playing any clip won't work.
How about you guys take the CD
to a repair shop?
At this point, I think it's ready.
- Ready to be fixed?
- Ready for a memorial service
for the CD that was once our hope,
now gone from us.
Why does this always happen to me?
Come on.
Don't lose hope just yet.
At least you still have me.
You still have Sodchuen.
We're always here to support you.
But for now, let's head to the meeting.
I have something urgent
to announce to all the teachers.
And finally... it's that time of year again.
The day teachers like us
wish would never come.
What day is she talking about, Jee?
How would I know?
That is...
Class Play Day from the English department!
I've called this meeting today
because I want to hear all of your opinions.
Since Teacher Solar isn't well,
how should we handle Grade 2 Class 1?
Can't we just cancel it?
No! I will never let a tragedy
like last year happen again!
A tragedy?
What tragedy?
That day should've been an ordinary day
for a little girl who had just become
the new principal.
Alas...
[Justice For Our Play!]
[The Play! The Play! The Play!]
She completely forgot
she had to organize the class play.
Give us back our play!
[Justice For Our Play!]
[No Play, No Us!]
Give us back our play!
[The Play! The Play! The Play!]
- Help!
- Give us back our play!
Help me!
So...
does anyone want to volunteer
to take care of that class
instead of Teacher Solar?
Well, can I take care of Solar's class?
Oh!
Teacher Pobmek!
You're being funny.
I'm not.
If it's for Teacher Solar, I'll do anything.
Teacher Pobmek, this is serious.
- Are you sure you're up for it?
- I am.
Let me be honest.
I don't believe you.
And I'm not comfortable with that.
So let's have Teacher Jee help you out.
Happy to help.
Everyone, please don't forget...
[Important: Record every kid's performance!]
Take videos and send to their parents.
[Parents' request!]
And please refer to this schedule
for more details.
Most importantly, first,
we'll have the kids choose a director.
Then we'll let
the little director take it from there.
Okay.
As long as the kids don't choose Sun
as the director,
it should be easy.
If anyone has any questions...
Won't Sun sulk?
- Feel free to ask them now.
- Please.
He won't.
We can just give him a lollipop
to keep him quiet.
Sun is so easy to trick.
So our director this year is Sun.
Yay!
Sun! What have you done?
Guys, pick me as your director.
I think we should do Avengers.
The fighting will be fun.
Ew, no.
Guys always go for fighting and violence.
I think Snow White is better.
It's a legendary classic.
Gosh, Elsa! What era are you from?
Snow White is ancient!
If it were really that old,
they wouldn't have made
a live-action version.
- No!
- Avengers is better!
Avengers is better!
Snow White!
I think
both Elsa's and King's ideas sound fun.
But to make it even more fun,
you should choose me as your director.
Huh?
Why?
Because I'm going
to do Snow White and the Seven Avengers!
Sun for director!
Trust me! Trust me!
Well... students, I think...
Sun might not be a good fit for director,
since he can only come to school
every other day.
The rehearsals aren't going to work, right?
Yeah.
It's okay, teachers.
We're professionals.
Besides, everyone's already voted for Sun.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
What are you going to do?
No! We can't let Sun be the director!
Will the kids be okay with that?
[Director = Sun]
[Justice for Sun]
Sun for director!
Here.
This is to keep you quiet, Uncle.
I'll do my best as the director.
Sun for director!
What do you want to play?
What is it again? Snow White?
You want to play her?
Hey.
How's it going?
Nothing much.
The kids are rehearsing the play.
I just got the brief for the set.
Maybe it's not as bad as we thought?
Hey, I'm usually optimistic,
but look at this.
[Snow White and the Seven Avengers]
This is the brief I got.
Do you think we can get it done
in this lifetime?
I'll handle it.
Hey, that's an invader!
Attack!
Hey!
What are you guys doing?
Teacher Pobmek?
Oh, I thought the class next door was coming
to copy our ideas.
Let's get back to the meeting. Come on!
Sorry.
I forgot to warn you about that.
The play is definitely going to be a mess.
"Which mannerly devotion shows in this;
For saints have hands
that pilgrims' hands do touch,
And palm to palm is holy Palmers' kiss."
"Have not saints lips..."
You look confused.
Do you want to start over?
Come on!
No! What are you even making me do?
What?
Hey! Help me.
Please.
You know my scene partner and I
haven't even rehearsed together,
and my exam is today.
Can't we do a simple scene?
Like sitting next to each other,
watching birds, trees, or fish. Anything!
But I have to do the scene
where they first meet.
- No.
- Pretty please.
Please.
Please, or you won't get any sleep.
I'll keep bothering you like this.
Please!
Fine!
Come on.
You're a sweet roommate.
Let's put our masks on slowly.
Both walk around,
taking in the atmosphere of the ball.
They're not paying attention
to anyone in particular,
until their eyes slowly meet.
Their gazes are drawn to each other,
looking at each other,
the way you look at someone you like.
We can just angle it.
No need to actually kiss.
What if I actually want to kiss you?
Do you dare?
Shit!
It's time for the exam!
I have to go!
You really helped me with the rehearsal!
Thank you!
Solar, did you forget something?
Oh, I don't need it anymore.
Oh? Why?
My rehearsal partner
forgot the exam was today,
and went to a camp out of town,
so I ended up without a partner.
Let me ask around if anyone else
is doing the same scene as you.
Hey...
Why don't you be my rehearsal partner?
Huh? Me?
What's with that frown
so early in the morning?
What's wrong?
Well, yesterday we started
rehearsing the class play.
Sun was chosen as the director.
Seriously?
Jee and I tried to stop him
from being the director,
but he somehow got hyped up
and just went for it.
Are we going to survive?
Do you remember this?
Then you know how much
both Sun and I are into acting.
Just let the kids work on it.
Your job is just to watch from afar.
Trust Little Sun.
I really want to know
how Director Sun's play will turn out.
[Play Rehearsal]
And action!
Who... Who are you?
I am Snow White.
Snap your fingers!
Squirm more!
Squirm harder!
Yes! Squirm more! Harder!
Go harder! Squirm more!
Whoa.
Is this for an elementary school play,
or Rachadalai Theatre?
I'm relieved to hear that.
I was so worried about how it'd turn out.
Please make it turn out well.
I'm tired of arguing with the parents
and explaining where the school budget went.
Principal, that's not the right way to paint.
Let me show you.
You should do it like this.
I was doing it just like you, wasn't I?
No.
You have to do it exactly like I do,
so the colors will be perfect.
I'm the principal!
Feel free to take a break, Principal.
The set needs to be done next week,
not next academic year.
Oh.
Tinker Bell, Four, is everything alright?
Teacher Pobmek, Sun and Elsa are fighting.
- What?
Sun, what have you done now?
You caused trouble again, didn't you?
Pobmek, calm down.
Let's listen to the kids first.
Kids, what's going on?
Elsa wants to play Snow White,
but Sun already picked Aurora for the role.
So Elsa said Aurora isn't pretty,
and doesn't deserve to play the lead.
Then Sun said Elsa isn't pretty either,
and Elsa cried.
You caused trouble again.
Elsa started it.
- Weren't you listening, Uncle?
- I was!
But you're the one who made things worse,
weren't you?
You're the director,
so you should talk to your friends nicely,
not scold her and make her cry.
What about you?
You don't even talk to me nicely.
Okay.
As the play supervisor,
I'm removing Sun as director.
You're mean, Uncle.
I hate you so much.
Pobmek, do you really want to do this?
How much longer are you going to sulk?
It's your own fault!
Open the door! I haven't showered yet!
Fine!
Sulk all you want!
You'll snap out of it eventually!
Do I really have to shower
with the water from the dish washing sink?
[Sukhum Udom Rak School]
Darn!
I can't take it anymore!
Come on.
Will there ever be a day
when you don't complain at all?
What did you do?
Why does your hair smell weird?
I used the dish washing liquid
to wash my hair.
Hey.
Pay attention to me!
Give me a second. Aurora's mom is calling.
Hello?
Hey, Jee!
What are you doing?
Look at this.
Ready?
What do you think?
- Isn't it cool?
- Gosh!
Can you just make a simple set
and help me look after the kids?
Sure.
But let me finish this first.
- Just give me four...
- Four hours?
Four days, man!
Hey.
Aurora's mom said Aurora is sick,
and needs to take the day off.
If she doesn't come to school tomorrow,
I'm going to visit her at her house.
Hold on.
Aren't you waking up as Sun tomorrow?
[Teacher Solar & Teacher Pobmek]
Solar.
Are you really not going to sleep?
Will you be okay?
Of course.
I'm worried about Aurora.
It's just one night. I'll be fine.
Okay.
Then I'm staying up with you tonight.
What are you doing?
Keeping you awake.
But you always fall asleep before me.
You're exaggerating.
We've stayed up till morning before.
That was when we were students.
We're still students.
What subject?
Love.
What an uncle joke.
Did you borrow that from your dad?
You're really going for it, huh?
But you have to promise
you won't fall asleep.
You're supposed to pinky promise.
Come on. I'm not falling asleep!
[Aurora's Mom]
Hello?
Got it, Ma'am.
I accidentally fell asleep.
How did you even stay up?
You're not sleepy?
Oh, by the way, Aurora's mom just called.
Aurora's taking another sick day.
I already called Sodchuen
and asked to be a bit late,
so we can go visit Aurora.
Aurora,
why have you been missing school
for the past two days?
Are you sick?
Yes, I'm sick.
Or are you skipping school
because you're fighting with Elsa?
No, Teacher!
Oh? Then why do you look fine?
Well, the other day,
I fell and sprained my leg,
but I don't want anyone to know I'm weak.
But your friends are waiting to see you.
I want to see them too, especially Elsa.
But why didn't you say anything back to her
the other day?
Well, Elsa was already sad enough
about not getting the lead role.
I didn't want to hurt her even more.
That's my lead girl!
- Huh?
You're Sun?
Teacher Pobmek...
About Elsa, Sun didn't do anything wrong.
He just wanted to protect me.
So, could you please let Sun
direct the play again?
Alright.
But you have to promise
you'll do your best.
Sure. I promise.
What should we do with the branch?
Like this.
Hey, don't tease her.
That's it!
Are you ready, kids?
Yes, we are!
Three... Two... One!
[Snow White and the Seven Avengers]
Finally!
The play is today!
I know.
What, Uncle?
Aren't you excited?
Forget excited. I'm not even awake yet!
Pobmek!
We're in trouble!
Huh?
What is this?
I'm sorry.
Sodchuen, what happened?
It's that guy.
He went up to fix the broken light,
but the scaffolding collapsed
and smashed the set.
It's completely ruined.
I get that it's an accident...
but we spent a whole week building it,
and it came crashing down in one day!
Teacher Pobmek, what should we do now?
Sun, how about we postpone the play?
Sun!
Sun, where are you going?
Sun, what are you doing?
Uncle, please take these to Teacher Jee.
Auntie, what are you daydreaming about?
Hey! I'm the principal!
Yes. Help me out, Principal. Please.
Let me grab some more, just in case.
What are we going to use these for?
Little Sun, what are you doing?
Painting, of course.
Does anyone have a handkerchief I can use?
Hey! Teacher Pobmek!
Teacher Jee, you'd do anything
to make it turn out perfect, right?
Of course! Why?
[Class 2/1]
Yes, sir.
I definitely won't forget
to take videos of your kid.
Okay, bye.
Snow White and the Seven Avengers.
And action!
Once upon a time in the forest,
there lived a kind and gentle girl
named Snow White!
Wow!
Snow White was about to meet
the Seven Avengers!
Whoa!
Sun, where did Elsa go?
Is she not playing the tree anymore?
She didn't go anywhere.
She just changed roles.
Aurora, I'm sorry
for saying you're not pretty.
And I'm sorry for getting the lead role
instead of you.
Actually,
we both should've been the female leads,
don't you think?
But there can only be one female lead
in the play, right?
One day, Snow White found some magic water.
When she drank it,
something amazing happened!
She found her other self.
Wow!
Suddenly, the magic water appears?
Are you sure that's a good idea?
It doesn't have to be good.
As long as the cast is having fun,
the audience will enjoy it too.
Here. This is your new mask.
I'm so nervous.
Am I really going to do well?
It'll be fine.
As long as the cast is having fun,
the audience will enjoy it too.
Come on.
Solar, who's your acting partner?
He doesn't look familiar.
Oh, he's a friend from another faculty.
You two are just friends?
We're really just friends.
Alright, if you say so.
Let's give the stage to the next pair.
Thank you.
We did it!
I'm so glad I asked you to act with me.
Is something wrong?
No, I'm fine.
What do you mean you're fine?
You clearly look like a sad puppy.
Well, you made it clear to the professor
that we're just friends.
Pobmek.
I trusted you today.
I trusted you to act in the scene with me
as a friend.
From now on,
will you trust me too?
Trust you with what?
Well...
Trust me to take care of you...
as your boyfriend.
Huh?
Boyfriend?
Hey.
I thought you said you're just friends.
We were just friends a moment ago.
But now we're boyfriends.
You did amazing today, little director.
Here.
A lollipop again.
What do you want then?
You can ask for anything.
Today's an exception.
Really? Anything at all?
Try asking.
[Drop off Your "My Dream" Assignment]
I want to go to the beach.
I've never been there before.
Can I go?
I've already signed it.
I'll take you there.
- Really?
- Yup.
- You're not lying, are you?
- No.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Yay!
Love you as big as the world, Teacher!
I'm glad you and Aurora made up.
It's all thanks to Sun.
Sun?
The friend who said you're not pretty?
Which one is that?
This one.
Wait.
Isn't this Teacher Solar?
No, it's Sun, not Teacher Solar.
Come on, Teacher Jee! Stop wiping it off.
Aren't you going to eat?
Honestly, I was worried
the play wouldn't turn out well,
since it's not how we expected it to be.
But seeing the kids happy
was a nice surprise.
That's because you care about the kids
more than the work.
That's it.
Wow.
My friend is in Mr. Moral Teacher mode.
What's wrong with you? Just eat!
Let's eat.
By the way,
when I was helping Sun carry the paint,
I found this.
Give me a second.
Here!
Here.
Why don't you practice with this,
so you can play it for Sun?
Maybe it can replace the CD you broke.
You were such a pro at playing the guitar.
Why did you quit?
I was hoping we could play as a duo.
Hey, you guys still haven't left?
Not yet.
Come on, Solar. The pot is still hot.
Thank you.
How was the play?
Did it go okay?
It went way better than okay.
Sun was really amazing, you know?
So... does that mean I'm getting a reward?
Hey.
No. Too many people.
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
Kiss! Kiss!
Aw!
What?
That's not enough to make a BL girl happy.
No! I'm shy!
Too many people!
- Just eat!
- Kiss again! Kiss again!
Kiss again!
Kiss again! Kiss again!
- Kiss again!
- No way!
Alright, enough.
Let's just eat. Just eat.
Don't let me find out
you two kiss behind our backs.
Who's going to eat that now?
This is Teacher Solar, isn't it?
Why?
I'd like to have a little chat with him.
Take Solar home! Now!
- Go!
- Solar!
Sun, let's go!
What?
I can't get up. Help me.
[Kiss Voucher - 1 kiss/hour]
Are you really going to use it here?