QUEEN OF TEARS
FOUR YEARS AGO
EPISODE 3
We own this entire orchard.
I see.
I thought my mom would be here.
Maybe she's at the store.
She runs a store as well.
I told you that our family
was influential in this town.
Right.
Mom!
Mom?
YONGDU-RI SUPERMARKET
Gosh.
She's not here either.
Pick whatever you want.
Have this.
It's a new flavor.
ICE POP
It's strawberry flavored.
All the kids buy one after school
since it's so popular.
It's good and refreshing.
It's my first time.
It's your first time having an ice pop?
Wait. Maybe not as an adult, but as a kid?
Did your mom never buy you one?
No, she didn't.
To be honest, I kind of knew.
Knew what?
You always wear t-shirts
with holes in them.
What?
That's vintage.
-I got them made in Europe--
-What you're wearing today looks like
something my grandma would wear.
No, hear me out first.
You'd be shocked to find out…
the price of this cardigan.
-You don't have to pretend with me.
-Trust me.
I'm not that poor.
Really.
You should trust me instead.
I give you my word.
From this moment on,
I'll let you enjoy
all the things you couldn't enjoy in life.
That won't be easy.
Didn't I tell you
that my apartment was leased?
You did.
But there's more.
To be honest…
I save two million every month.
Don't look at me
like you don't understand.
I'm not bragging.
I'm saying it's okay.
I don't care if your family has debt.
If we have debt?
Even if there's more than that,
I really don't care.
Because…
I'll be by your side.
You'll be by my side?
Yes.
I'll be there
for you.
Why did this memory pop up?
Would you be the last person on my mind
if I died right now?
Are you okay?
Hae-in.
Are you hurt?
Are you okay?
Can you wrap up here?
She looks startled.
She needs some rest.
Let's go.
Okay.
It felt surreal at the hospital,
but I really thought I'd die back there.
So I told myself again
that I would never die.
Because I felt
offended.
Are you okay?
I think you sprained it.
Am I being dramatic again?
Yes, if this was any other day.
But since I'm injured,
I think it's reasonable.
Right?
Isn't it easy to set wood on fire?
But this is oak.
-So is it impossible?
-No, it's not.
But campers like me
prefer plum tree to oak.
The burning smell of plum seeps
into the meat and makes it tasty.
Okay. Go on then.
Gosh, this makes me nostalgic.
I'm reminded of when I went to Africa.
My twenties were filled
with wildness and barbarism.
You mean how you stayed
in the hotel the whole week
due to the mosquitoes?
I had enough of the wilderness
just looking out the window.
What?
-There's only smoke.
-Right.
I think this wood is damp.
Even the most skilled campers
can't do anything about this.
Hyun-woo was never picky about wood.
He's from the countryside.
You can't compare me to him who probably
played soccer
on unpaved roads with pig bladder.
He has experience.
Jeez, you and your excuses.
Where is he, by the way?
You can stop. Just ask him to do it.
No, I can do it.
Soo-cheol, that's enough. You can stop.
Chamomile?
Yes.
Can you make two more
for the chairman and me?
Sure.
Why did Father return early
instead of hunting?
Well…
The great shaman contacted me.
About what?
The shaman suddenly asked
if the chairman had gone hunting.
-How did she know?
-No wonder she's great.
She said the chairman would be
in danger if he went hunting today.
Is that why he came back right away?
Yes, but at least
it's good news for Hae-in.
She got to take his course.
Mom!
Hae-in got injured.
What? How?
I heard she met a boar while hunting.
But her injuries
aren't that bad. They're not bad.
Goodness. Is she okay?
How did you know?
You truly are the best.
What did she say?
Anyway, thank you so much.
I'll visit you sometime soon.
What did she say?
Your ex-wife appeared in her dream.
She was holding a knife
at a hunting ground.
She wanted to take you with her.
You could've been in grave danger
had you hunted today.
See?
You were wise to listen to me and return.
Don't ignore superstitions.
Check in with the shaman
before making big decisions.
Okay.
Shouldn't we call Doctor Kim?
I'm okay. I just sprained it.
Hyun-woo saved your life.
I thought he couldn't even shoot a bird,
but a boar?
He was pretending all along.
He probably has experience.
Did you just compliment him?
You need a lot of experience to catch one.
Boars are thick-skinned,
so you need to hit the right spot.
If not, it could be even more dangerous.
Exactly. Thank God he was lucky.
What if he missed?
Think about it.
He shouldn't have been
so reckless as a rookie.
He was a marine in the Special Guard Team.
-He was known for his shooting.
-Really?
Yes, really.
Do you finally understand
how much of a fool you were
to offer to teach him how to shoot?
One thing is for certain.
I wouldn't be here right now
had he hesitated even a bit.
You lucky brat.
-What?
-I could tell by his muscular arms
that he didn't spend all his years
only studying.
How could you tell?
When I was in jail,
he handed me the agreement
with those muscular arms
and said, "Please sign this."
And my heart
fluttered.
-Aunt.
-Aunt, come on.
You amaze me at times, Hyun-woo.
How did you make that decision
in that brief moment?
I wasn't thinking.
It was instinctive.
Your instincts knew
that you shouldn't let her die.
You had to save her
so she'd revise her will. Right?
Hello?
Where's Hae-in?
She took some meds and went to bed.
She must've been so startled.
I can't believe this.
Actually, I scanned the course earlier.
I noticed that the fence was pried open.
I believe the injured boar
had entered through that hole.
That was supposed to be
Chairman Hong's course.
What are you getting at?
Are you saying someone purposely lured
the injured boar to harm him?
We wouldn't know
even if that was the case.
I'll check the nearby CCTV cameras
and dashcams.
I'll check them myself.
Would you like to do that?
Okay, I'll get them ready.
I'm sorry
this had to happen
during your visit, Mr. Yoon.
Don't worry about it, sir.
Mr. Yoon, try the soup.
I caught that pheasant.
Come on. Don't lie, Dad.
We bought them at a nearby farm.
All right. Let's eat.
Eat up.
Thank you.
Why did you season the bellflower roots?
Hyun-woo prefers them charbroiled.
No, I like this too.
Really?
Yes.
Eat up.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Yoon.
These are lacquer leaves.
They're pretty rare.
The mountain-bred ones
are very tasty and hard to find.
I had them when I was younger.
"Younger"?
Didn't you grow up in the US?
No, I went there when I was 13 years old.
I was in Korea up until then.
Did your family immigrate there
or were you studying abroad?
I was adopted overseas.
My adoptive parents passed away
right before I graduated university.
So I have no family now.
I lost my parents at 15.
And I came this far by myself.
I wasn't aware of your family history.
You're unlike today's young generation.
I agree.
I'm proud of you as if I'm your mother.
Feel free to consider us
your Korean family.
I appreciate that.
Eat up.
Come here. Yes, over here.
Thank you.
Is he a Pungsan dog?
Yes, sir.
He's a handsome one.
Not only is he handsome,
but he saved my son years back
when our house was on fire.
-Is that so?
-Yes, sir.
My son was home alone.
He would've lost his life
had our dog not woken him up
and dragged him outside.
He's intelligent and loyal.
Would you be willing to sell him?
Well…
I'm sorry, sir.
He's family.
-I'll give you 100 million.
-Sorry?
But he doesn't even have a pedigree.
That doesn't matter.
I'll offer less with time.
Ninety million.
-Eighty million.
-Wait.
Honey.
I'll sell him.
But…
could you give us 100 million?
Sure.
Honey.
There's only one thing I don't have.
It's prejudice, right?
But what about it?
It's about Mr. Yoon.
Doesn't he seem too laidback for someone
who has gone through so much in life?
He must've worked hard to make up for it.
Don't judge a book by its cover.
You can never know
what someone's thinking deep down.
Are you sure you're from the US?
You know our language and Korean proverbs
better than me.
I already told you.
My father made us only speak Korean
and read Korean books at home.
What a wise man.
Not everyone can become
an Ivy League professor.
Would you like some?
Right. Even beer is too bitter for you.
You know I feel terrible that
I can't be your drinking buddy, right?
What do you mean? Don't feel bad.
I need the toilet.
He's so chatty.
Your room is the very last one
on the second floor.
Yes, I know.
Have a lovely night.
You should go upstairs.
I will.
Good night then.
Right, Soo-cheol.
You asked me for advice last time
on how to get
on the KFTC members' good side
when they summoned you.
Right.
What do you say?
Do you want some detailed tips right now?
Right now?
Based on the legal expertise I obtained
during my law school days at SNU
and years of working at the Legal Team,
I could offer an extensive
yet simple explanation.
I'm free from now
until late into the night.
I'm not. My wife is waiting for me.
Really? What a shame.
I mean, it's a shame for you.
This is a great opportunity.
Are you afraid?
Of what?
Sleeping in the same room as Hae-in.
Soo-cheol.
That's absurd.
We're married.
Why would I be afraid
of sleeping next to my wife?
All right.
Where are you going?
Your room is up there.
I know.
Go straight.
I truly
pity him.
-Where's the alcohol?
-What do you mean?
You drank it all.
I did?
Are you drunk already?
How cute.
-Let's go to bed.
-Okay.
I drank it all.
What took you so long?
Were you not sleeping?
I woke up.
I asked you a question.
Right.
Soo-cheol asked me something,
so we were talking.
What?
That lunatic.
Was he pestering you at this hour?
Honey. Hae-in.
Please don't be so hot-tempered.
Should I go back out there
and give him a stern warning?
That's okay.
Right? That's what I thought.
-Help me take off my top.
-What?
I think I sprained my fingers.
It hurts to unbutton it.
Can you do it?
-Me?
-Yes.
-Unbutton you?
-Yes, back here.
Here.
That's enough.
I can do the rest.
Okay.
Right.
Why aren't you undressing?
Do I have to?
You're not showering?
Should I not go out?
What's wrong with you?
Don't glamorize him.
He wasn't that handsome.
Are you okay?
No. Stop it.
Don't replay it in slow motion.
Don't do it.
Don't.
I couldn't find
a bathrobe.
Right.
I see.
I'm so dumbfounded.
Does he think
he's sexy?
What in the world
happened to his body?
Seriously.
What? What do you want?
I…
There's a lot of water on the floor.
You don't like that,
so I was going to wipe it.
It's okay.
Just go dry your hair.
Don't tell me…
you didn't dry your hair
because you looked in the mirror
and thought you looked like
a drenched Timothée Chalamet
or a young Leonardo DiCaprio.
What do you mean?
If that's not why,
then go dry your hair.
Okay.
I will.
Unbelievable.
Was he trying to seduce me?
I'm too stimulated
for this hour.
Are you sleeping?
Not yet.
The bed is small.
Is this queen-sized?
It's king.
I see.
It feels too small
to be king-sized.
There was a time
when we slept together
on a single bed.
When?
Don't you remember?
My first visit to Yongdu-ri.
CERTIFICATE OF AWARD
DILIGENCE AWARD
Spend the night here.
It's too late.
It's 9:00 p.m.
That's pretty late.
-It's dangerous to drive at night.
-That's true.
Right.
Sleep here.
I'll be in that room.
I'll be there
if you need me.
Good night then.
The moon looked pretty.
Maybe we could look at it together.
Come in…
if you want.
-By the way…
-Yes?
How did we even sleep
on that bed?
We cuddled.
Right.
Did we cuddle?
Do you want to cuddle
if the bed is too small?
I'm okay.
It's not too small.
I have some room.
-Really?
-Yes.
Then…
do you want to cuddle
nonetheless?
I'm just kidding.
Don't be so scared.
What are you doing here?
Goodness.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't in my right mind yesterday.
I'd like to give this back.
Please help us.
We couldn't sleep last night.
I already gifted the dog to him,
so I can't do that.
I'm sorry.
He's family to us since he saved our son.
I must've been insane
to have sold him.
All right. I'll take this.
-Thank you.
Thank you so much, sir.
Goodness.
What are you doing?
You felt guilty for selling him.
So let's just kill him off.
Would that be better?
What are you doing?
Jeez, I almost shot you again.
I asked you a question.
I was just joking.
Was that a joke to you?
What do you think it was?
Did you return the money?
Did you get it?
I'm your witness.
The deal has ended.
You may go.
Thank you. Let's go.
-Hurry.
-By the way,
why can't I kill it?
You heard him.
He doted on the dog.
The dog is like family.
I see.
In that case, is it okay
to kill abandoned or stray dogs?
That's the entrance to the forest.
No one else entered except for our family.
Does that mean this was an inside job?
Hold on.
Stop there.
Who is that?
I can only see his back.
That's your brother.
That can't be.
Honey.
We don't know for sure.
Beom-seok wouldn't do that.
Find out if he's still in Korea.
Yes, sir.
Pack up.
-Already?
-The day is ruined.
Let's go home.
-Honey, do you remember that boy?
-What?
It happened over two decades ago.
That incident where
the German Shepherd of a brewery died,
and the killer
turned out to be a little boy.
Right, the one
from the Evergreen Hope Orphanage.
He received a scholarship
from Queens Group because he was so smart.
I fed him several times when he visited.
Yes, him.
Remember what he said to the police?
This is you, isn't it?
Why would you kill someone's precious dog?
I won't let this pass.
Do you know how much he cost?
I'm sorry.
Apologize to him this instant.
What makes a precious dog any different?
Then would it be okay to kill
a normal dog?
What's wrong with that kid?
Gosh, what is he saying?
Gosh, you're right.
He did ask that question.
It was creepy to hear a boy say that.
-Didn't he look like him?
-Who?
Hey, it's me. Did you get home safe?
I booked you a meeting with Mr. Hermann.
Are you serious?
Thanks.
Okay, see you then.
You won't be disappointed.
ALL MAIL
WE APOLOGIZE…
I'm going
to die?
When Hercyna is just around the corner?
When I'm this close
to the One Trillion Club?
Impossible.
I have so many limited editions
that I haven't worn yet.
I bought so many islands
but haven't visited them yet.
And yet, I'm going to die?
No, that'd be such a waste.
I bought all these from artists
in their nineties
because posthumous works skyrocket.
So how could I die before them?
That'd be such a waste.
You'd be the biggest waste.
Then let's wrap up this store's contract.
Good work, everyone.
-Secretary Na.
-Yes, ma'am?
Are there women whose hearts still race
when they see their husbands
despite being married
for over three years?
Why would their hearts race?
-Do they have arrhythmia?
-No, not that.
Maybe…
because…
they're handsome?
-Their husbands?
-Yes.
Maybe she's ill.
Do you know someone like that?
Yes, I do.
On some days,
she looks him in the eye
and wants to embrace him.
Why?
Because she pities him.
She feels bad
that such a soft soul
has to endure this harsh world.
-No way.
-On other days,
his shoulders look
so broad.
She wants him to hold her.
He looks like a walking, sexy dynamite.
She wonders
if she should let the homme fatal
roam freely in this world.
Please tell her
to see a doctor. She's ill.
-Do you think so?
-I'm telling you.
Make sure she gets a brain CT scan.
Something's seriously wrong up there.
Secretary Na.
You're pretty good.
-I've been very strange these days.
-How so?
I feel sympathy
for others.
-Is that strange?
-I was never like this.
I've always been cold-hearted.
So it's odd.
You're so noisy.
Stop crying
when I'm sacrificing my arm for you.
And I keep empathizing
with others.
What was that?
Solicitors aren't allowed here.
I'm sorry. He's my acquaintance's husband.
So you're doing him a favor?
Their baby is in an incubator.
I felt bad so…
He won't come back.
-I'm sorry.
-How long does the baby…
Sorry?
…have to be in there?
-About three-
-Forget it. One week? Two?
I'll only let him come by until then.
You'll let him do that?
I better not see him
once his baby is discharged.
No insurance will cover it.
I wanted to use
our security deposit for her surgery,
but my mom won't listen.
She says it's my wedding money.
Money is always the problem.
I'm sorry.
Unbelievable.
Her mom isn't the only one who's sick.
Her mom can get treated,
so why would she cry…
Why are there so many sick people?
How annoying.
I was never like this.
I never cared
about people's pain,
so why am I like this?
My husband makes my heart race.
I believe my brain
isn't functioning properly.
Are these symptoms of my illness?
Not really.
Many terminally ill patients
experience such changes of heart.
They realize things
that they wouldn't have realized
if they weren't dying.
"You're changing because of death."
"You're going to die soon."
I think that's what you're insinuating.
But you're wrong.
You see, I've been
on the brink of death many times.
And my miraculous luck
saved me every time.
If you're not skilled enough to save me,
then just watch.
Another miracle
will save me.
Hey, Hyun-woo.
Long time no see.
Yes, I went to the hunting ground!
So what?
Why did you?
To see Father.
He's there around this time of the year.
But you left without seeing him.
Are you
suspecting me?
The fence was pried open
and there was bait nearby.
Then the boar that had been shot
attacked Hae-in.
-Someone purposely--
-So?
My daughter almost died.
Tell me the truth.
This is your last warning.
You're upset because Hae-in was involved.
Why weren't you upset
when I was falsely accused and kicked out?
Fine, sit down.
I went there because I knew
it was the family's hunting day.
But when I went there,
the great Moh Seul-hee said
he was asleep and didn't let me see him.
I begged her but to no avail.
So I came back. That's all.
Fine.
Beom-jun.
Help me meet him just once.
That's all I need.
I want to reconcile before it's too late.
Sometimes,
it's better to let go.
Hyun-woo.
Isn't my family so odd?
Sorry? Not at all, sir.
We have seven lawsuits against each other.
You must've walked
on eggshells as you took care
of our trivial matters.
You've done so much.
Hello.
The chairman is already asleep.
Already?
Should I wake him up?
That's okay.
I just came by to greet him.
Goodbye then.
Ms. Moh.
Did Beom-seok come to our hunting ground
and ask to see Father?
No, he didn't.
Is that what he said?
Look.
I don't like saying this,
but be wary of him.
He's been holding a grudge for a while
after getting kicked out.
Those who have nothing to lose
are the most fearful.
What kind of person
is Mr. Yoon Eun-sung? Do you know?
Mr. Yoon?
I know his business side,
but not him as a person.
You know that people like us
shouldn't trust others easily.
If this deal
goes down the drain as well,
Father will abandon Soo-cheol.
Don't worry.
I'll look into him discreetly.
Looking for me?
Gosh, you startled me.
A background check?
She's quite cautious.
She's just afraid,
but it's only in the beginning.
People like her trust easily
once they let down their guard.
She did let down her guard somewhat.
By the way, do you see
any hope with Hae-in?
Money is important to me for sure,
but I'd also love to see
that couple break up.
Why?
It's safe to say that I pioneered
the matchmaking scene in this country.
Yet I failed
to properly marry off Queens' daughter.
How humiliating is that?
I will tear them apart at all costs
and retrieve my lost honor
and performance.
In that case,
don't repeat what you did.
-You'll get in the way.
-That was…
I was told to do that.
But Hyun-woo stepped in, killed the boar,
and saved Hae-in.
I never saw that coming.
Hyun-woo, you've leveled up.
From Mr. Cinderella
who married into a wealthy family
to a lifesaver
who saved their daughter's life!
They are treating me differently now.
It was my first time eating
a pheasant leg.
I was normally given
the neck or the lean cuts.
But my father-in-law gave me the leg.
It's too early to be complacent.
Keep up the good work.
How?
"I was only doing my job."
Don't ruin this opportunity
by saying such nonsense.
"Yes, I was scared too. I could've died,
but I did it for Hae-in."
You need to take credit.
-Do I have to?
-Yes, you do.
Taking credit
is like collecting coffee coupons.
You need to collect ten coupons
for them to realize
you're a regular and give you freebies.
I don't need
any freebies.
All I want is to be free and unscathed.
What an idiot.
Say goodbye if you're going
-to be fake.
-Goodbye to what?
"Goodbye, my Italian suits."
"Goodbye, my handmade designer shoes."
"Goodbye, my foreign car."
"Goodbye, the luxury watch on my wrist."
"Goodbye, Hae-in's fortune."
Mr. Cinderella will now return
to his orchard down south.
But the problem is, his family
won't welcome him with open arms.
I'm sorry, Coach.
My son isn't interested in boxing
and wants to do Taekwondo instead.
That's okay. Kids are like that.
Goodbye then.
Let's go.
By the way, Jae-hyeon,
why do you like Taekwondo?
They have belts.
Belts? For your waist?
Is that why?
That's why he wants to go.
Jae-hyeon, we have belts too.
Look at that.
It's the champion belt.
Coach, that's okay.
-Ta-da.
-Gosh.
Check this out.
What do you say?
Isn't it fancier than those belts?
They smash things too.
Smash?
We smash things too.
We just didn't have time.
Should I show you?
No, you don't need to show him.
Hold on.
Give me one second.
Where's the board?
There it is.
Okay. Look.
Check this out.
This is how you do it.
I'll smash it this time around.
Watch me.
Gosh!
See? I smashed it, right?
-Isn't boxing cool too?
-But…
What? What is it this time?
I want to do Taekwondo
because Ji-seong does it.
Ji-seong is his best friend.
I see.
Ma'am.
I'm only saying this
because I care a lot about Jae-hyeon.
Don't you think
he should have various friends?
Sorry?
-Do you know Baek Ho-yeol?
-I do.
He's my son, and he's just like you.
He loves games just like you.
How great would it be to come here to box
and play games with him after school?
Ho-yeol has the lowest grade.
Hey.
Coach.
You're bleeding.
Gosh.
Why am I…
Gosh, don't worry about me.
The wood must've scraped me.
Goodbye then.
Are you leaving?
-Let's go.
-Get home safe, ma'am.
Goodbye.
Okay.
Jae-hyeon, see you again!
Bye.
Goodbye, ma'am.
-Hey, you're bleeding.
-It's just a scrape.
The wood scraped me.
Why are you so irritated?
I haven't been getting much sleep lately,
so I closed down my salon today.
I should close down this gym soon
and consider working under someone
once Hyun-woo divorces.
Stop talking about his divorce.
I should accept reality
and prepare myself.
-Should we go to Seoul?
-And do what?
I called Hae-in, but she didn't pick up.
Let's meet her in person and dissuade her
from getting a divorce.
-Get ready.
-What?
Let's go.
You were so against this whole plan,
but I guess you eventually got into it.
Well…
I always do my best
when I set my mind to something.
You're right.
You always do things wholeheartedly.
But here's the problem.
Fool her halfheartedly,
and all will be fine.
But do an outstanding job,
and she'll be livid
if she finds out.
-Probably, right?
-Right.
So you should never get caught. Got that?
I won't get caught
as long as you and I
keep this a secret.
Right.
By the way, shouldn't we tell Hyun-woo
that we're going to see Hae-in?
You idiot.
Do you think he'll allow that?
We've got nothing to lose now.
We should try to stop them
at all costs, right?
Step on it.
ONGOING RECRUITMENT
What should we tell them?
We don't need to introduce ourselves.
Do you not watch dramas?
The secretary's office manages
the VIP families.
They'll be startled the moment
they see our faces and say,
"Ms. Hong, your sister-in-law is here."
Then they'll let us in right away.
You need to book an appointment.
You must be new here.
Look at this.
That's me.
This wavy-haired guy is him.
Okay? That's us. See?
Leave your name and number,
and I'll hand it to her.
Look.
We're her family.
We're part of the royal family.
Why must we book
an appointment to see our family?
Jeez.
Please book an appointment and come back--
Hae-in!
Long time no see.
I'm Hyeon-tae, Hyun-woo's brother.
I know.
I wondered if it was you, and I was right.
We need to talk. Even Hyun-woo
doesn't know that we're here.
Well…
Should we go upstairs?
All right.
-This way.
-Okay.
Are you surprised?
But you see, we won't punish you
for not recognizing us.
Don't worry.
We don't abuse our power in that manner.
You must be busy.
Sorry we came by unannounced.
I had actually called several times,
but I couldn't reach you.
I don't pick up unsaved numbers.
You must not have my number.
What brings you here?
You see…
Where should I begin?
It was our dad's 60th birthday recently.
You must be here because you were upset
that I didn't show up.
Gosh, not at all.
No?
Of course not,
because we weren't upset at all.
I don't know how you'll feel about this,
but Hyun-woo…
-Yes?
-He's difficult, isn't he?
-Sorry?
-Gosh, I understand.
Understand what?
The person who's the polar opposite of you
isn't on the other side of the globe.
It's the person you're married to,
the one you sleep and eat next to.
They fail to understand you the most.
Right.
My husband and I
argued all the time because of the AC.
He'd turn on the AC in the summer,
and I'd be freezing.
We even cursed each other out
because of it.
He used to be head over heels
for me when we got married,
yet he couldn't even
turn off the AC for me.
We don't argue over such things.
Is that so?
Then that's great.
You have a good relationship.
We sleep in separate rooms,
so we each have an AC.
That's understandable
if you have many spare rooms.
Anyway, this is what
I say to him all the time.
"Now that you're married,
you're no longer one of us.
Consider yourself a part of Queens
and stay there even after you die."
"Don't you dare come back
or set foot into our house."
So speaking of which…
Div--
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but you're going to be late
for your meeting with Mr. Hermann.
I'm sorry, but I need to go.
I have an important dinner today.
Okay, you should go.
I'll text you
the rest of the conversation,
so please save my number.
-I'll visit you sometime soon.
-Really? Would you do that?
I admit that we've been distant
after Hyun-woo got married.
After all, you got us a building.
A building?
Yes, the one in our town.
Did I purchase a building there?
Yes, you did. You told me
to get one when you got married.
I see.
Are you using that?
Yes.
But don't you worry.
I do the cleaning and repairing.
I do everything.
Don't you worry about the building
since I have it under control.
By the way, why did your in-laws visit?
I'm not sure.
She mentioned
how I didn't attend her father's 60th.
So she came to nitpick?
She said no.
Then?
She said marriage
was like turning the AC on in the summer.
What? What does that mean?
You never agree on the temperature.
I see.
That makes sense.
Hey.
-Where's Mr. Hermann?
-Right.
He went to see his baby daughter
because she flipped over.
He ditched this meeting
just because his baby flipped over?
He's a family guy.
That must be why he divorced four times
and had a baby at 60.
How irritating.
I even brought the floor plan
since he wanted to see it first.
This is actually better.
You see, he already has a picture in mind.
Knowing that beforehand
would give you an advantage.
What does he want?
What? You're back?
I thought you went home.
I have more documents to look over.
-You can go home first.
-Yes, sir.
By the way, Secretary Na told me earlier
that Ms. Hong had a dinner appointment.
I see.
She said Ms. Hong was meeting
with Mr. Yoon Eun-sung
and might come home late. So sir,
I think it's safe for you
to go home instead of staying here.
Who is she meeting again?
Hercyna wants two floors.
-Two floors?
-Yes.
You'll need a fancy staircase around here.
How can we do that?
This won't be a simple renovation.
I'll have to change
the structure and get it approved.
Exactly. He'll make that suggestion
and choose whomever gets it done first.
That's insane.
It's ridiculous…
but only I know this?
Correct.
Sir, did you hear about your siblings
visiting Ms. Hong earlier today?
-Who?
-Your sister and brother.
Secretary Na just told me about it.
Did you not know?
Eat first before they get soggy.
Hold on. "I know it's tough.
Dot, dot, dot."
"But you still can't get a divorce."
"Can you reconsider it for my sake?"
Why would she do that?
She barely knows you.
Just eat your udon.
Why did you mention
cleaning the building to her?
I was so shocked.
How did she not know
about her own building?
Is this similar to how I forgot
about the 10,000 won I left
in my winter coat?
Is that what owning
-a building is to them--
-Stop talking!
"Whatever the reason
for your divorce may be,
I believe Hyun-woo is to blame."
"So could you please
be understanding this once
and not get a divorce? Crying emote."
I'm sending it.
It's Hyun-woo!
BAEK HYUN-WOO
-What do I do?
-Pick it up.
What? Yes, I met her.
Why do you think I did?
To tell her not to divorce you.
But she was too busy,
so I texted her instead.
-What?
They're not separating.
-Did they reconcile?
-Did you reconcile?
No, she just doesn't know that he wants
-a divorce.
-What?
He never brought it up.
What do I do?
HONG HAE-IN
BAEK HYUN-WOO
POWER OFF
Are you okay?
Yes.
Let's go.
What kind of person
is your husband?
That was random.
You were always cold
and suspicious of others.
So I was curious about the person
you chose to marry.
Let me think.
It feels like
you're hoping I'd bad-mouth him.
But you're wrong. He's a good man.
You saw how he jumped in
to save me in that dangerous moment.
You're wrong.
I saw him hesitating.
He hesitated
to save you.
Hae-in.
HONG HAE-IN
The number you have dialed
is not available…
That's the difference between you two.
You were watching him at that moment,
but he was watching me.
You actually believe that he loves you.
Yes, I do.
I don't know what love means to you.
But to me, it's not about being happy
and whispering sweet nothings.
Love is when
you endure the pain together.
When you choose to stay
instead of running away.
Even if they have a debt
or something more than that,
you still stick together.
That's love.
And he's doing just that.
That was lengthy.
What?
People tend to ramble when they're unsure.
You don't look confident.
I didn't know you were here.
Where's Hae-in?
Well, you see…
What brings you here?
Hae-in had a lot to drink.
She drank?
Hae-in.
-Hae-in.
-Let her be. She's sleeping.
She sleeps when she's drunk.
Hong Hae-in.
She's been sleeping the whole time,
so give her ten more minutes.
Or I'll bring her in later,
so you can wait inside.
How much alcohol did you feed her?
Sorry?
Look.
She doesn't usually drink,
but she can hold her liquor.
So how much did you feed her for her to be
this drunk?
I mixed alcohol.
I can't sleep because you're too noisy.
Thanks. Go home safely.
Okay. Sleep well.
-See you tomorrow evening.
-Why would she--
I mean…
I heard you guys met
with Mr. Hermann today.
So what's tomorrow for?
Mr. Hermann didn't show up today.
It was just us two.
And we drank
by ourselves.
Right. Don't forget to drink
orange juice in the morning.
That's your hangover cure.
Whatever. Okay.
Okay.
-Bye.
-Goodbye then.
Please take good care of her.
-Mr. Oh.
-Yes, sir?
Please take him home safely.
He seems to be very drunk.
He seems very out of it,
so walk him to his door.
Yes, sir.
What are you doing? Get in.
Why did you suddenly drink so much?
Because it was unlike me.
I'm going to try new things from now on.
It's so unfair.
I lived differently from others
so I could live a long, healthy life.
But look at me now. It was all useless.
I'm going to speak my mind,
do everything I want,
and kill those who deserve it.
What's with the last one?
I'm going to kill
every single scumbag who betrays
and stabs me in the back.
Think about this.
Even if I do commit murder,
I'll just need to attend trial
a few times before I die
in three months.
Right. You could be my attorney.
Okay, give me that. Let's go inside.
You have a knack
for saying such terrifying things.
Don't be afraid.
I know you would never betray me.
Of course not.
I'm not afraid.
By the way,
your phone was turned off.
Where is it?
Is it not in there?
Right.
I must've left it in the car.
In the car?
Go in first. I'll get your phone.
Mr. Oh, have you left? Where are you?
What? Here it is.
It was in my pocket.
What? It's turned off.
Hae-in, wait.
-What are you doing?
-I'm not sure.
What…
am I
doing right now?
I'm glad
that you found
your phone.
It could've been
a hassle to get it.
Why wasn't I…
confident?
What?
What did you say?
Right.
I told you, right?
I'm going to try
new things from now on.
SANSSOUCI PALACE, POTSDAM, GERMANY
THREE YEARS AGO
Did you say this place had no worries?
"Sans souci" in French
means "carefree."
That's just ridiculous.
How could such a place exist?
Do you know The Happy Prince?
The prince who made
a swallow poke out his eyes?
Yes.
The prince used to live in this palace.
I only realized one thing
after reading that book
as a child.
"You'll always suffer away from home."
Even the prince probably missed his home.
He left home only to suffer.
He gave away his gems and eyes.
Hae-in.
That's why he's the "happy prince."
Please. He wasn't happy.
He just changed before his death.
We should stay true to ourselves
and not act out of character
just because we're dying.
I'd like to build something.
A cancer support center
that aids employees' families.
Sorry?
You want to offer financial help
to their families?
Why?
For efficiency, of course.
What do you mean?
Imagine if your family member has cancer.
Could you focus on work?
-Probably not.
-Right?
Then you wouldn't be able
to sell your products.
That would be my loss.
And you'd cry in the toilet
about how you're in need of money.
Your makeup would run,
your eyes would be swollen.
It would only bring down
our department store's reputation.
I see.
I'm not trying
to help others out of goodwill.
It's all about the efficiency
and the financial aspect.
QUEEN OF TEARS
-Are you going to bed?
-Let's do it.
It was because I was scared.
That's why my heart was racing so much.
Now that I've been cured,
you're going to betray me?
Watch out!
What kind of lunatic yells like that here?
You're not the Eun-sung I knew.
I've worked very hard
to hear this from you.
I don't even like Hae-in.
Why would I be jealous?
I have something to tell you.
Don't worry.
It's good news that you'll love.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim