[Episode 1: A Wish Born of Despair]
I did my best.
You did your best?
I did my best, too.
It was already too late when I took over.
It was already too late when you took over？
Can you just give me one more chance?
Then who's gonna give me a chance?
You are not suited for this industry.
He's so bad I don't even know what to say.
Why don't you consider a career change?
Haven't you considered
going to a cram school?
He is absent from every sketching class.
Honestly, it's better if he's not there.
I've cleaned up enough
of your mess already.
What are you trying to say?
Why can't we just work hard
and get better together?
I honestly think he's just...
1, 4 ,2, 8, 5, 7.
[Wishing Upon the Shooting Stars]
Come on, we have arrived at Xingpu Island.
Let's get our luggage up ahead.
What do we have
the most of here?
The sea turtles.
The ice shop on the hill is also delicious.
Besides
snorkeling and the ice shop,
what else do you want to do here?
Listen—
Besides the ocean,
there is very little light pollution
on the mountain at night.
You can ride a bike up the mountain.
Maybe you will see a shooting star
and can make a wish.
Hong.
I am telling you,
I'm really damn good at playing guitar—
[Stairway Corner Ice]
Today's fruit is really sweet.
-The seasons are important.
-You're all here.
Village Chief.
-Village Chief, you're here.
-The Village Chief is here.
Just in time, just in time.
Come.
Village Chief, have some fruit.
Okay, thank you.
I will get you a fork.
Don't be so polite.
I will get a fork for you.
Thank you.
It is super sweet.
Wanzhe.
You're up.
Li Wanzhe.
You're only coming down now?
You're hitting me first thing
in the morning?
What about your reputation?
Hama-chan.
Morning.
Won't your stomach hurt
eating shaved ice this early?
I like it.
Suit yourself.
Deliver 5 bowls of shaved ice later
to the pier.
Okay.
Then, when you go to the main island today,
help me stop by the fishing harbor
to buy some turtle-shaped cakes.
1, 2, 3, 4.
Alright, back to work!
Xiangyong!
Xiangyong, why are you back?
I missed you so much.
Dad.
Old man.
My idol is back.
Xiangyong.
Watermelon candy.
Your favorite.
Thank you, Hong.
I'm not into watermelon candy anymore.
Then...
what about sea turtles and drawing?
Do you still like them?
Xiangyong.
Oh, Xiangyong.
Mr. De.
It has been a long time.
Weren't you going abroad
for some exhibition?
-No.
-Xiangyong.
Come in and chat with me more.
Okay, I will talk to you next time.
Xiangyong is busy.
-Don't keep dragging him.
-I'm leaving. Thank you.
-Hey, this is my chance to pursue my dream.
-Are you really not eating?
Why did you interrupt me?
Hey, chase my ass.
-Xiangyong is Xiangyong. And you?
-You'll pay for my trip to the main island, right?
No way. Pay for what?
Get back to work.
The money for the boat ticket.
Village Chief, you are really great.
All 5 of us in our family
will vote for you.
You have to keep your word.
When I am Village Chief,
the streets are clean,
and the gutters are cleared.
-I will vote for you.
-Is that Xiangyong?
Xiangyong.
Xiangyong is back.
It is Xiangyong.
Xiangyong.
It was hard for him to make it back.
You are back!
Xiangyong, how do you have time to come back?
Come here, come here.
Xiangyong.
Have you published a book yet?
He was the one
who held an art exhibition last time.
Right, we even went there.
I didn't hold an art exhibition.
Yes, you did.
I always tell my younger brother
to be like you.
You are really amazing.
Let me take some photos.
He is the best at drawing
on Xingpu Island.
I've watched him grow up
since he was little.
-He Xiangyong.
-Be careful.
-Come here!
-Watch the car!
Thanks.
Come on.
We've known each other for so long—
We're totally in sync.
You know, those residents on our island
have nothing better to do
than gossip.
But there is no other way.
You are the pride of Xingpu Island.
I originally wanted to go find you
for a bowl of jelly ice.
It is fine.
I will pack a bowl for you later.
You came back so suddenly this time.
Why didn't you tell me in advance?
You said it was sudden.
How was I supposed to tell you in advance?
That is true.
I bet you missed me.
Listen,
while you were away,
my mom was so annoying.
She kept saying He Xiangyong is great,
going to the main island
to fulfill his dreams.
And then she said
I only stay in that tiny room
playing video games
and told me to look up to you.
I am almost sick of hearing it.
Village Chief Wang
is planning to build a resort
and set up solar power projects.
I strongly suspect
he wants to run for Township Mayor.
We're here.
Mr. He.
Dudu, have you seen Mr. He?
Where are the others?
Mr. He.
Your He Xiangyong is back.
I know. I know.
Your mom broadcast it
in the group chat long ago.
Mom.
I am back.
Are you hungry?
How about I make you some noodles?
Okay.
I'm not hungry.
This scrap wood wasn't here last time.
If you aren't going to use it,
why pick it up?
You don't even put away
the storage baskets and brooms.
What kind of guesthouse is this?
And you're drinking
so early in the morning.
Come on.
How many times do you even
come back in a year?
And you come back with that face?
If you don't want to come back,
don't force yourself.
No, Mr. He.
He is just too busy and tired from work.
The waves were big this morning,
and he got seasick.
He didn't mean it.
Poor thing, tired.
Aren't you tired from work?
Yes.
I am also very tired.
Dudu is also very tired.
Who isn't, huh?
Everyone is tired from work.
Today isn't even a day off.
He came back on a workday,
and you told me he's tired?
I'm telling you,
I am also a boss.
If I found an employee
as lazy and messy as him,
do you know how unlucky I would be?
-You have to...
-Yeah.
I am just lazy and messy.
If you don't want to look at me,
then don't look.
You can just pretend I didn't come back.
I didn't ask you to come back.
You're the one
who skipped work to come back
and then showed me a grumpy face.
If I don't come back, you'll scold me.
If I do come back, you will still scold me.
Didn't I get this face from you?
Look—
Every time I come back,
it's the same with you.
Okay.
Stop.
1m 10.09s.
Congrats, you just broke
your record again.
Congratulations.
Alright, don't be angry.
Hey.
Don't be angry.
Come on, cheers, Mr. He.
Cheers.
Drink my ass.
Got nothing better to do?
Shouldn't you be at the shop?
No.
My mom told me to tell you
that our Village Chief
is hosting a banquet today.
Xiangyong just happened to come back,
so she said you must come.
Mr. He.
I'll go back to work first.
Sorry.
The chair.
Thank you.
He Xiangyong.
You must come tonight.
Come on.
Drink, drink.
Thank you.
I have served you for all this time,
right?
You all know it,
You must vote for me.
Okay?
Is that a deal?
Vote for me, okay?
Please.
Enjoy your meal.
Take your time.
It is so delicious.
Eat well.
Enjoy it.
Let me see.
No, not this song.
I want...
24206.
-78257.
-Okay, I'll select them for you.
I'm not done yet.
27394.
Thank you!
Remember to vote for me.
Thank you.
Mr. He.
When is your son going to America
or Europe to hold an art exhibition?
Yeah right, try making it to Luzhou first.
Don't say that.
Come, drink, drink.
What kind of paintings does he even paint?
I am not too sure, either.
Eat more.
Come, Xiangyong.
You haven't eaten anything.
He.
The helper at your place didn't come today?
It's his day off.
He went off somewhere early this morning.
Since when did we have a helper?
Well,
he has been here for a while.
And he is really handsome.
He's a "young hunk,"
right?
He's not bad.
But,
he managed to last more
than 3 days at my house?
Watch your words.
He has a good personality
and is easy to get along with—
unlike you.
You're so hard to get along with.
What's with that face all day?
I'm not making a face.
You're literally doing it right now.
You are the easiest to get along with.
Come on, let's not argue while eating.
OK.
Right.
Come.
Come, come, come.
Listen to the doctor.
Those who don't know
how to talk shouldn't talk.
Let's drink.
Come, drink.
Village Chief Wang.
Let's sing together.
You sing.
This is a good song.
This is my signature song.
What's wrong? You're not eating?
It's too hot.
I don't have much of an appetite.
No appetite?
Don't think I can't tell.
It's obviously because of your dad.
If your mom spoke to you like that,
would you be able to smile?
I could.
I wouldn't care.
Wanzhe.
Long time no see.
Do you want to eat something here?
OK.
Help me clear the level when you get back.
Don't eat the stuff in my room.
I'll think about it.
Think about it?
Don't eat it!
Are you going to study in Japan?
No.
You're planning a trip to Japan?
I have no money.
Then why are you so close to Xiaohai?
He is so cold
and talks so little.
It is good that he talks little.
How peaceful it is for my ears.
Look, my mom—
One of her is enough for me.
I want to sing.
Sing!
What are you singing?
What are you singing? Come on.
An English song.
Tell me,
how long are you staying this time?
Probably
for quite a while.
What does that mean?
Did you use up all your annual leave?
I don't have annual leave anymore.
You don't have annual leave?
Are you using special leave?
No.
Then what?
I don't have a job anymore.
I can't hear you.
I was fired!
A song—
I think I'll sing a Taiwanese song instead.
A Taiwanese one is good.
I also think I should sing
a Taiwanese song.
Chen Lei's.
Sing Chen Lei's.
I'll select it.
Okay?
Everyone sing together.
Eat up.
-Hurry up and sing.
-Drink.
Hurry up and sing.
I'll sing Chen Lei's
"Happiness Is All That Matters."
He Xiangyong.
Drink.
Come on.
Come.
It's okay.
Where is the instructor?
Happy birthday to you.
Good thing I am smart enough
to know you were here.
Look.
There are so many shooting stars today.
I really miss this.
Do you remember?
We used to come here often
to make wishes when we were little.
Every time you said
you wanted to be a great painter.
Actually, I really admire you.
What do you admire about me?
I am not a painter now.
I don't even have the right to hold a pen.
Everyone kept talking about
Europe and France.
It's hilarious.
I even got fired
from being a simple editor.
And I still owe...
Anyway, you don't need to envy
this kind of pathetic life.
I'm so done with this.
I wish I didn't have to be
He Xiangyong anymore.
Hey, you've been speaking very quietly.
Can you speak louder?
I said,
I wish I didn't have
to be He Xiangyong anymore!
That's easy.
Just jump into the sea.
Good idea.
It is.
Let's go.
Together.
Right here.
No, no, no, I'm kidding.
I'm not kidding.
Let's go. We'll jump together.
No, I'm really kidding.
I'm sorry. I didn't...
I'll just jump.
Then He Xiangyong can start over!
Really...
If I hadn't known you
for over 20 years,
I would push you down right now.
Let me help you.
Uncle Hua?
You're back.
You haven't gone back yet?
Goodnight.
Xiangyong.
I cooked this for you.
Your dad was worried
you didn't eat enough tonight.
He was drunk
but insisted on cooking
garlic shrimp vermicelli for you.
I was worried he would blow up
the whole kitchen.
I told him to go to sleep
and that I would handle it.
So eat some in a bit.
Thank you, Uncle Hua.
Wait a second.
Vermicelli.
This brat.
Don't come back.
I can't guarantee the taste.
What's wrong?
Is there not enough garlic?
I'll go get more...
No, Uncle Hua.
It's delicious.
I thought you were eating so gloomily.
What is it?
Are you in a bad mood?
I just remembered
when I was little,
it was only when there was
something worth celebrating at home
that my dad would cook
garlic shrimp vermicelli for me.
But today...
Uncle Hua,
did I disappoint my dad?
Xiangyong.
When young people enter society,
it's natural to have ups and downs.
It's impossible for everything
to go smoothly forever.
Back when I was in the big hospital,
it was the same.
Only through setbacks
can one grow in life.
I just...
Anyway, I feel like
my current self
is useless.
You have to see
what it is you are pursuing.
Is it being useful?
Or being liked?
Or perhaps,
it's enough that you like yourself?
You should know that parents
are easily satisfied.
As long as their child is doing well,
they ask for nothing else.
So,
don't take your father's harsh words
to heart.
He is actually very happy you are back.
Is he?
Is he happy?
Don't just look with your eyes,
feel with your heart instead.
Listen.
Find some time
to have a good talk with him.
Sometimes,
the one who gives in
isn't the one who loses.
But you know,
when the two of us talk,
it's hard to last more than 3 sentences.
Then don't rush.
Take your time.
Sometimes when things happen,
they aren't necessarily bad things.
Let's look at it from another angle.
Maybe,
maybe it's a chance from God
to make some changes.
It just depends on
whether you seize it or not.
Alright, eat up,
or the vermicelli will get cold.
No matter what,
I will support you.
Thank you, Uncle Hua.
Well...
Do you want more garlic?
No, thanks.
Are you sure?
How about
I add some chili?
Okay.
Why isn't he back yet?
It's already late at night.
[Beautify the Home Painting Competition]
[Xingpu Island Junior Ironman Competition]
Who said growing up is great?
That's bullshit.
Growing up isn't good at all.
It sucks so bad.
Who is it?
You should know that parents
are easily satisfied.
As long as their child is doing well,
they ask for nothing else.
Good heavens.
How did it get so heavy?
It's too heavy.
Hurry and help me.
Chen Haowei!
Coming.
Hello, I am Chen Haowei, from Class 2.
From that day on,
He Xiangyong!
I decided
that this name
-has nothing to do with me anymore.
-Chen Haowei.
Don't come looking for me ever again.
I never thought I'd bring it up…
until...
we met again.
[Epilogue]
Hey.
The instructor is here.
You're not leaving?
The instructor is here, up there.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
What on earth are you doing?
Where is the instructor?
Still running?
Let's go. He's right behind us.
Where is the instructor?
Behind us.
Wait, stop for a second.
Just run.
Stop right there!
Chen Haowei.
[Next Episode]
So, he's the helper you hired?
I can't even say my own name.
Why?
You don't know him?
Who?
You don't know him, either?
No.
It's the shooting star.
Didn't you make a wish yesterday?
Then why are you fine?
Wishes don't affect me at all.
Li Wanzhe.
I like you!
Have we met somewhere before?