♪Shrugging off past burdens♪
♪Beneath the mask, who am I?♪
♪Release and find wider shores♪
♪Love's a riddle, and rain pours heavy♪
♪Crossed paths, now downward fall♪
♪From dust arises starlight's spark♪
♪Tearing through
the night's dense blockade♪
♪Heart's flame illuminates all solitude♪
♪Let time's sails drift endlessly♪
♪Through wandering exile♪
♪Breaking free from the cocoon,
I start anew♪
♪Moon as song, life as flame♪
♪Nameless heart clings fiercely♪
♪Let me♪
♪Charge toward the next raging river♪
♪Moon darts, snow falls♪
♪We tread rugged paths to reunite♪
♪Hands held tight♪
♪We forever live for love's sake♪
♪Shadow's spear burns fiercely♪
=Legend of The Female General=
They're crossing the line,
putting loaches in my shoes.
I'm sorry.
It was an accident.
These candies got dirty.
Put them back.
Don't eat those.
Should I buy you new ones?
No need. Go to class.
=Episode 5=
You dug so much
into his past, but to no avail?
That's right.
Everything matches his military records.
Maybe He Yan really has nothing to do
with He Rufei and Xu Jingfu.
This only proves
those covering for him
are remarkably capable.
Covering for him?
Commander, have you
discovered something?
An unexpected lead.
Have people keep looking.
Yes.
And what's going on
with the delay in provisions?
Yezhou Magistrate Sun Xiangfu
claims the harvest is poor,
the farmers are owed payments,
and the grain reserves
are critically low.
So he can't spare us any grain.
Absolute nonsense.
It's not like there were
any natural disasters.
There were none.
But man-made troubles exist.
I bet Xu Jingfu told him to oppose you.
Xu Jingfu got me transferred to Yezhou,
away from the capital,
without any chance to turn the tide.
He never imagined
that you had already chosen
to bide your time here.
But now that
you've trained these misfits
into capable soldiers,
he's rushing
to tamper with our provisions.
That's right.
The new recruits lack cohesion.
If provisions run short
in times of good harvests
and rumors of embezzlement surface,
the new recruits will
lose their trust in me.
What should we do?
The remaining provisions
can last a bit longer.
After the contest of capturing flags,
I'll visit Sun Xiangfu in person
and find out
what kind of pawn
Xu Jingfu had planted in Yezhou.
(He Yan,)
(those closest to you)
(despised you,)
(abandoned you,)
(and killed you.)
(Since you've come back
with a new identity,)
(from now on,)
(your life)
(will be solely in your hands.)
Mr. He.
Your lanterns are hideous.
What matters is the sincerity.
Mr. Cheng.
Isn't your lantern
way too huge?
This lantern
is not just for my ancestors.
It's also for Huaijin.
So I made it bigger than usual.
With both families together,
it's livelier
and less lonely.
My grand-aunt
feared loneliness most.
Madam Xiao
also passed away?
Yeah.
She and my great-uncle
were a loving couple.
After my great-uncle died,
my great-aunt was devastated.
After Huaijin
escorted my great-uncle's coffin home,
she took her own life.
Huaijin is also quite lonely.
My family,
including my mother,
and friends acquainted
with the Xiao family
don't really like him.
They prefer my eldest uncle,
Huaijin's older brother,
Xiao Jing.
Why?
Aren't they both members
of The Xiao family?
The Xiao family comes from
a long military lineage.
One child must join the army.
Xiao Jing is more of a scholar
than a military man.
So Huaijin joined the army
for his elder brother
and the entire family.
He left at an early age
and rarely visited home.
So, he's become quite aloof.
He's distant even with his own family,
let alone relatives like us.
Even his mother
doesn't feel bonded with him.
Makes sense.
They're like strangers
after years apart.
It leads to prejudice.
Mr. He, it's late.
I should head back.
Rest early.
In times of hardship,
take a piece of candy.
Let its sweetness
comfort you.
Such little sweetness
can attenuate the bitterness of life.
Premium Osmanthus wine.
I hear noblewomen
in the capital adore this.
May the deceased
witness my devotion
in folding these lanterns
and bless my wishes.
Disturbing the deceased
doesn't make you ashamed at all.
Leave mortal affairs
to be handled by the living.
How do you know
I'm not speaking
the wishes of the deceased?
The regrets of the dead
must be redeemed by the living.
This is my promise to them.
Want to fold some?
I'll share some with you
to repay you for saving me back then.
No need.
This one
carries blessings
to those heroes who died
defending our land and people,
and their loved ones.
Though I don't know your names,
these blessings
come from my heart.
Not bad.
Hideous.
This is called free-form one.
Perhaps
the heroes prefer it this way.
You mock my lanterns,
but you won't make one.
All talk, no action.
So picky.
What's the fuss?
I touched your hand, so what?
(This woman has no sense of propriety.)
♪Constant yearning♪
♪Still vivid as our first meeting♪
♪Endless gazing♪
♪Step by step, falling deeper♪
♪How to untangle this love♪
♪Buried deep within dreams♪
♪My heart, unyielding as stone,
remains true♪
♪Awaiting the crescent moon's
reflection in your heart♪
♪Splendor fades from your eyes♪
♪Crimson threads entwine like rings,
binding our first vow♪
♪Time lingers as you and I share
overlapping palm lines♪
♪Zither and harp
accompany our dancing dreams♪
♪The brocade moon writes our vow,
keeping this promise♪
Done.
It's ready.
♪In the vast world♪
♪I searched for years♪
♪Shadows hustle♪
♪Scenes reappear♪
Hurry up.
♪What is there to fear♪
♪We'll weather storms together♪
♪Through endless dawns and dusks,
to eternity♪
♪Awaiting the crescent moon's
reflection in your heart♪
♪Splendor fades from your eyes♪
♪Crimson threads entwine like rings,
binding our first vow♪
♪Time lingers as you and I share
overlapping palm lines♪
♪Zither and harp
accompany our dancing dreams♪
♪The brocade moon writes our vow,
keeping this promise♪
Done.
♪Awaiting the crescent moon's
reflection in your heart♪
♪Splendor fades from your eyes♪
♪Crimson threads entwine like rings,
binding our first vow♪
♪Time lingers as you and I share
overlapping palm lines♪
♪Zither and harp
accompany our dancing dreams♪
♪The brocade moon writes our vow,
keeping this promise♪
Under the bright moon,
I long for my kin.
I wonder if the deceased
shares this moonlight
with us, the living?
Yes, they do.
New recruits, listen up!
Red flags are placed
throughout Mount Baiyue.
There are 15 in total.
This competition
lasts until sunset.
The team returning
with the most red flags
shall be the winner.
Remember. Don't cross the mountains.
Don't take lives.
Violators will face
military discipline.
- Yes.
After the competition,
the most outstanding recruit
will join the Nine Banners Battalion.
- Really?
Soldiers!
Set out.
- Yes.
This is the map of Mount Baiyue?
Where did you get it?
I memorized the paths while patrolling
and drew this map after I came back.
You memorized the paths
while being chased by wolves?
I checked the routes
while fleeing,
and then reviewed them later.
So I know this place well.
Trust your leader.
Those flags
are usually placed in visible areas
near foothills and water sources.
So the nearest flag
should be
on this open mountainside.
Come on, let's go for it.
No.
We're not going there.
Those flags in the open
are easy targets.
Many teams will notice them.
If we go there,
we'll be caught in chaos.
So,
we'll head
here.
It's among dense woods,
behind a cliff.
It will be a challenge.
Classic carrot-and-stick tactic.
They lure us with rewards
and then slap us down.
Of course, it's challenging.
Or they can just hold
a martial arts contest.
Let's go.
Cliffs on Mount Baiyue are dangerous.
I doubt anyone
can take this flag.
New recruits can't.
But veterans might
have realized the purpose of the patrol
and completed a thorough mapping.
Do we have
such a talent here?
Yeah.
He Yan.
It's in such a precarious position.
Only you could get that flag, He.
Piece of cake.
He, you're amazing.
With only one patrol,
He Yan
has learned Mount Baiyue by heart.
Impressive new talent.
But I bet on Lei Hou's team.
Everyone
in that team is a top martial artist.
It takes teamwork to capture flags,
not individual heroism.
Therefore, deployment matters
more than muscle.
So I still bet on
He Yan.
H-Hand over your flags.
(The members of He Yan's team are)
(of mixed quality,)
(but each has talents.)
(If he can harness their talents)
(through deployment,)
(they should)
(make quite a team.)
Take action.
Do you surrender?
Y-Yeah.
W-Where are your flags?
Commander.
He Yan's team
set up ambushes and snatched
many flags from the other teams.
"Hold the ground,"
"stay fresh, and strike"
"when the enemy is weak."
Those new recruits
are being thoroughly outplayed.
What a surprise.
You also captured seven flags.
That's impressive.
You flatter me.
Now we each hold seven flags.
Whoever claims
the last one in the valley
becomes the winner.
That terrain is treacherous.
Why don't you retreat
with your team to secure second place?
That may be good,
but I crave first place.
Very well. We'll meet in the valley.
Mr. Lei, this isn't much fun.
Why don't we spice things up?
I'm listening.
What do you want?
A duel.
The loser
surrenders all his flags.
Those guys? Are they up to it?
No way, He.
We worked so hard for these.
It's okay, don't worry.
If we come to duels,
I won't hold back.
You may lose even second place.
I don't like fighting.
But no one can take what I desire
from me.
Therefore,
I'll have to beat you.
He Yan trusts us with his back.
Naturally, we'll eliminate all threats.
You agreed to duel.
But you resorted to tricks?
E-Even bandits...
Bandits keep their word better.
(Odd moves.)
- Nice!
- Well done!
Remarkable, Mr. He.
I concede.
You honor me.
Commander.
He Yan has claimed all 15 flags.
His team has returned.
You've lost.
Commander,
you're a great chess player
and talent scout.
I humbly
admit defeat.
(If she were truly a planted spy here,)
(she wouldn't eagerly draw my attention)
(by flaunting this conquest.)
(But she is no ordinary recruit.)
(He Yan, what's your intention?)
Commander.
The contest concludes.
Shall we proceed with rewards?
No rush.
The Mid-Autumn Festival is
in five days. Wait until then.
Have you decided the one to be
enrolled in the Nine Banners Battalion?
We took first place.
But there's no celebration?
This is lame.
There will be a feast.
It's just postponed.
Rest assured.
You'll get your banquet.
Don't mock me.
Aren't you craving meat?
- Of course, we are.
He,
after you join
the Nine Banners Battalion,
don't forget us.
Never would I.
(Let me ask Xiao Jue about this.)
Morning, Master.
Master.
I lived up to your expectations
and won first place in the competition.
Thanks to your guidance,
I can join the Nine Banners Battalion.
(Great Master and Talented Disciple)
This is a flower basket I made.
These 15 flags
represent my newly earned honors.
Please accept it
as a token of gratitude.
"Talented disciple"?
You really know
how to toot your own horn.
How am I tooting my own horn?
Look, it says "Great Master" right here.
With our bond,
once I join the battalion,
I'll surely
stand by you
through thick and thin
forever.
So eloquent.
It's a pity you're not teaching literacy
to the troops.
Master,
how can you value my silver tongue
over my true capabilities?
With abilities like mine,
I'll become your right-hand man
once I join the Nine Banners Battalion.
Are you really
so eager to join the battalion?
Of course.
I'm a real talent.
It would be your loss if I didn't join
the Nine Banners Battalion.
I won't let you
suffer such a great loss
in your life, Commander.
Commander.
All instructors are waiting for you
at the main tent.
Military affairs take priority.
Go ahead.
We can talk anytime.
Wait.
Take the pastries from the table.
Thank you, Commander.
(General Feihong's Mansion)
General.
There is
no conflict of interest
between us.
Wouldn't it be nice if we both
served the Master?
He wasn't
avoiding you that day.
He's just been burdened with worries
and has become short-tempered.
I wonder what troubles
the Chancellor.
It's Xiao Jue.
He's causing trouble even in Yezhou.
He is drawing attention
with the training
and making outrageous demands
to Yezhou Magistrate Sun Xiangfu
for provisions and funds.
Sun Xiangfu is running short on those,
but Xiao Jue refuses to back down.
They're at an impasse.
As the Chancellor's disciple,
I'm obligated to go to Yezhou Garrison
for mediation.
It's just that
I've never been there.
Besides, I'm merely a scholar.
Unlike you,
who commands numerous talents,
I only have one maid working for me.
My guard here knows some martial arts.
Once you arrive in Yezhou,
you can ask him to run your errands
if you need anything.
That would be most helpful.
But
I can't travel fast.
Perhaps, I'll meet
your guard in Yezhou
so as not to make Magistrate Sun wait.
Alright.
Then I'll take my leave.
Once you reach Yezhou,
go straight to Sun Xiangfu
for cooperation.
General,
won't you
be implicated?
What's the problem?
Yezhou is Sun Xiangfu's territory.
Even if things go south,
Sun Xiangfu is to blame
for his incompetence.
What does it have to do with me?
Chu Zhao wants
to claim credit from Chancellor.
We can't let him steal the spotlight.
So, Ding Yi,
make sure you succeed.
No mistakes are allowed.
Yes.
(Chu Mansion)
(Late Mother, Chu Mingfang)
Mother,
I'm going to Yezhou.
I won't be able to speak
with you for a while.
Young Master.
He Rufei envies
that you're valued by Mr. Xu
and is eager to impress Mr. Xu.
If his men reach Yezhou,
they might ruin everything.
You're mistaken.
They'll help us.
He Rufei's guard is
as skilled as you
in martial arts.
It'll save me much effort
if he takes on Xiao Jue first.
Besides, once he steps in,
whatever happens
won't trace back to Master.
And I can stay in the shadows,
watch them stir things up in Yezhou,
and find a chance
to obtain what Sun Xiangfu holds.
Alright. Thanks.
Try it.
Another veggie dish?
The meat dishes will come.
Here we go.
Let's all eat and drink heartily today.
Happy Mid-Autumn!
- Happy Mid-Autumn!
Come on, try this.
He Yan.
Why are you zoning out?
What's out there?
Isn't it the Mid-Autumn banquet?
Where is the Commander?
Huaijin won't come.
Why not?
Since when do you care
so much about him?
Wasn't he supposed to
announce the enrollment
into the Nine Banners Battalion?
If he came,
would you dare
to eat and drink so casually?
That's what I mean.
You're awkward around him.
He's uneasy in such lively places, too.
Why make everyone
uncomfortable?
Come on.
Top performer.
You go first.
Pass them around, guys.
Alright.
(What's mine is mine.)
(I can wait a bit longer.)
(Joining the battalion)
(brings me one step closer
to reclaiming my position.)
Mr. Shen.
Go on.
Dig in.
Don't hold back.
- Sit down.
- Yes.
Come on, dig in.
This is
a Mid-Autumn feast
as well as your celebration banquet.
We're usually not allowed to drink,
but you won first place.
So I
brought this reward for you.
Easy.
Don't be late
for the morning training.
Or you'll face military discipline.
- Yes.
Yes.
Get bowls.
Get bowls. Hurry.
Come on.
Look at you.
Mr. Shen.
Need something?
Are you here to announce the enrollment?
Mr. Shen,
do you have good news
for us?
Yeah, Mr. Shen.
Stop keeping us in suspense.
Yeah.
After I'm done here,
I'll offer Lei Hou
my congratulations.
Lei Hou?
Not He Yan?
Wait, Mr. Shen.
But He took first place...
So what?
Get back to it.
Don't make a scene.
Listen up.
Commander selected soldiers
based on a comprehensive evaluation.
The contest was just one aspect.
He Yan.
Stay sharp.
You've got real potential.
You'll have many more chances.
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪I've seen the mountains♪
♪And trodden through ice♪
♪Day after day, I venture alone♪
♪Destiny is my creed♪
♪Ideals surge beneath the surface♪
♪Igniting the flame against the winds♪
♪A restless yearning in my soul♪
♪Gazing through the mire♪
♪Who cares about this boundless void♪
♪Charge ahead with blazing fervor♪
♪Stubbornly fighting with my life♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪