(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
because we are investigating
the Valtrovi’s.
What do you mean you don’t know them?
Mom and Dad don’t easily trust people.
But for some reason,
you gained their trust right away.
What are you doing here?
Help us to build a case
against the Moraviano’s.
Angelito D. Pinagpala!
-What’s this?
-That’s not mine, sir!
I don’t want to be part of your schemes.
This is also about your brother, Angelito.
Get in.
CZECH CABLE COMPANY
Welcome to our humble abode!
Our surveillance van is nice, right?
It's high-tech!
I personally designed that,
just like Tony Stark.
It was Sianong’s idea to show this to you.
So you can see how serious we are
about our mission.
I already told you
that I don’t want
to get involved in your mission.
This is a raid! This is a raid!
We received information
that your brother was arrested
in a drug den during a buy-bust operation.
And he was caught
with a significant amount of drugs.
Enough for him to be considered
a pusher by the police.
That’s not true.
-Explain that at the police station!
-He could be imprisoned for life.
Especially if it’s proven
that he was involved in the selling
and distribution of illegal drugs.
I said that’s not true!
-Hey!
-Mikoy, wait!
-Mikoy!
-Wait!
Can we talk?
I was showing you that
because I want to help.
I have no idea what really happened.
Just unlucky that he
got caught in the raid.
As if nothing happened.
And he can still continue
the dream you have for him.
Don’t mess with me!
Because I know what you’re doing!
You’re behind everything
that’s happening to Angelito.
You’re setting him up,
so I’ll agree to what you want!
Do you really think I’m stupid?
Huh!
Just because I didn’t finish school
means I’m dumb?
Huh?
You have the nerve
to drag my brother into this.
Mr. Pinagpala.
We’re only saying this because
maybe you don’t actually know
your brother that well.
Oh really!
-Come on!
-What do you mean no!
Come on! That's enough!
You’re right!
We set Angelito up.
Were we right to do that?
But if we don't do anything,
more innocent people
will get caught up in the crimes
being committed by
the Moraviano Syndicate and Viktor.
Chiara’s family!
So you left me with no choice.
Will you help us?
Or will your brother
spend the rest of his life in prison?
This is what I’ll do.
I’ll tell Chiara the truth.
And I’ll tell her mom and dad
about the bullshit you’re doing!
And if it’s true that
they’re syndicate members
and completely ruthless,
I’m sure they won’t be happy about this.
Bok.
Bok, this is not good.
Alex, this is not good!
Why did you still have
to tell him about our mission?
Huh?
Are you listening to me, Bok?
This is not good!
If Viktor finds out
that we’re investigating him,
we’re both dead!
Then he’ll start targeting you, me,
and our entire agency.
Bok, right?
Huh?
Why did you even have to say that?
That hasn’t even been approved
by our higher-ups yet!
If we can’t use Mikoy anyway,
might as well just silence him.
Bok!
Have some restraint!
You’re going to kill a fellow Filipino?
May I remind you, Mikoy is innocent.
So, he has nothing to do with the things
the Moraviano has been doing.
He became part of the syndicate the moment
he chose to protect Chiara!
That’s why we have higher-ups.
We cannot make that call, Alex.
So what?
So we’ll just let him
ruin our investigation?
What’s the problem?
Chiara.
There’s something you need to know.
What do I need to know?
Shit!
What’s the problem?
Chiara.
Sorry, but…
I won’t be able to continue
with our plans tonight.
There’s…
There’s just a problem
at home all of a sudden.
Oh.
Well,
it’s okay if you don’t come with us
tonight, Mikoy.
But I’m already part of your life now.
Maybe I can help.
Or at least
I can be someone
you can talk to about your problems.
My brother was arrested.
In a… In an anti-drug operation.
He was caught with drugs?
I still don’t know the full details, but…
Maybe it’s my fault.
I’m the reason why
he ended up in that situation.
Chiara, it’s too complicated.
What I need right now
is to find a way to help him.
Please don’t blame yourself.
Maybe.
Maybe he can help.
My mom and dad have friends
in the Philippines
who hold high positions in the government.
Maybe they can find a way.
Friends in the Philippines?
My mom and dad are active
in the Philippines
because of their business.
And through the years,
they’ve also developed relationships
with powerful and influential people.
So I am sure
they can do something
to help your brother.
Don’t.
No.
This is my family’s problem.
So, let us handle it first.
Mikoy, are you sure?
Just remember, if you need anything…
Thank you, Chiara.
Thank you.
Pair of Jacks.
-Beat that!
-Wow!
Fold.
Child, it’s your turn.
Are you getting bored
with me and your father?
Or is something bothering you?
But yes, something is bothering me.
Care to share what it is
that’s "battering" you?
Bothering you.
-Ah, okay.
-Bothering you.
-Close enough.
-Oh, okay.
Mikoy?
-No.
-No, Papa. No.
It’s about his family.
His family in the Philippines.
Are they having financial problems?
Mama,
you know very well
how proud Filipinos can be.
If it were about money,
Mikoy would find another way first
before coming to me.
But…
But what?
It’s about his younger brother.
He got arrested.
As far as I know, they found drugs on him.
Oh, I feel so bad for Mikoy.
MOM
Hello, Ma?
Son?
We weren’t supposed to call you anymore,
but your father insisted.
He said you need to know everything
that’s happening to your brother.
Why, what’s the problem?
We went to Manila, son.
We’re here at the police station.
Your brother Angelito
was caught during a raid at a bar.
Oh my God, and then
they said he had drugs on him!
Wasn’t the reason he went abroad
to send his sibling to college?
Is that him?
And what’s even more frustrating
is he is blaming himself for that.
Angelito, Mom.
How is he?
Son, we already spoke with a lawyer
who is studying what remedy
can be given to your brother.
He’s okay.
He’s comfortable here at the station.
And the police are treating him well.
Oh my!
He couldn’t have done
the things they are accusing him of.
You know your brother, right?
He wouldn’t even hurt a fly.
Drugs, of all things!
Mikoy, we’re okay here, all right?
I’ll handle it.
But son!
He wouldn’t ruin his life for that.
No!
He wouldn’t throw away everything
you all have done
for drugs.
All right, Mikoy.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
It’s just me!
Why? Why did you send these things to me?
We need to leave as soon as possible.
Huh?
Our local operator
is waiting for us there,
and he is arranging
us a flight back to Manila.
Why didn’t you go through with it?
Especially since we’re not in Manila.
So what you mean is
maybe Mikoy already reported us
to Chiara and her father?
We need to leave.
But do you understand what’s happening?
So now Viktor will know that he is
being investigated by our agency,
so he will become even more careful.
And his surroundings
will be even more protected.
And wait, one more thing.
It will be very hard.
It will be virtually impossible
to infiltrate his syndicate.
He might even use his influence
to undermine our agency.
We still shouldn’t stop
fighting his syndicate.
We need to fight back
or more people will become their victims.
If we can’t use Mikoy,
then we’ll just find another way.
-Let’s go.
-Okay.
That’s not my phone.
This is Mikoy’s number.
Why is he calling you now?
I want to meet now.
I want to talk again.
Where are you?
Bok, are you okay? Bok!
What if this is just a trap by Mikoy?
What if Viktor is only setting us up?
Then the two of us are doomed.
You know, you’re so overdramatic
and way too negative.
What negative? Okay.
The Moravianos
have homecourt advantage here.
Like in basketball, here in Prague,
Viktor Valtrovi
has the homecourt advantage. Okay?
We don’t stand a chance here.
So, if I’m overreacting,
then I’m overreacting.
But we’re at a disadvantage
here in Prague!
But what if Mikoy has another reason
for wanting to talk to us?
Maybe that’s what Judas said
before he betrayed Jesus.
That he has a reason to be able
to have dinner face-to-face with him.
Look, if you don't want to come,
that's okay.
I'll be the one to face him first.
You can go back
to the surveillance van first.
And if you don't hear
from me within an hour,
leave Prague immediately.
Do you think
I would let you face this alone?
We're already here anyway.
Do you think I would abandon you here?
Do you think I would leave you hanging?
We're together until the end.
Bok, someone's here!
Abort, abort!
-Civilian.
-All right, all right.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Wait! What's that!
Did I do something wrong?
Are you alone?
Yes.
I'm alone.
How can we be sure that you
didn't tip Viktor off about us?
I don't have anyone with me.
I'm really alone.
He's telling the truth. He's alone.
I hope you understand that
we have to take precautions.
Especially the last time we talked,
I know you were determined
to report us to Viktor.
So our assumption is,
Viktor will make a move against us.
But you still met with me?
Just like I said,
I am desperate.
We have already tried everything
we could do
to infiltrate the Moraviano.
But it is really impossible.
So when you called us,
we had to take the risk.
Maybe you changed your mind.
Do I even have a choice?
If I don't cooperate with you,
you will ruin my brother's life!
Like I said,
I am desperate, Mr. Pinagpala.
As time goes on,
the operations of the Moraviano
in the Philippines
are expanding and getting stronger.
I am afraid that I have no more time left.
I did that so that you would agree.
So if I agree,
my brother will be released?
His record will be erased and cleared?
As if nothing happened
regarding his arrest.
Can I trust you?
I will not risk coming here
if I were just fooling you, Mikoy.
Tell me now,
how did you find out
that Chiara's parents are connected
to this syndicate?
We don't have evidence
linking him directly,
but we caught a low-level operative
who we forced to talk.
Investigate this.
That is an import-export company
used by the Moraviano
for all of their operations.
How?
On the surface, this import-export company
looks legitimate.
Unfortunately,
no one can easily get inside this company.
And the last informant we placed inside
was killed.
Wait.
So if I become your informant,
that means
my days are numbered too?
What do you mean it won't happen?
It already happened to someone!
Huh?
How am I different?
Their only daughter loves you.
Chiara loves you.
And if you really love Chiara,
you will do this for her.
Because sooner or later,
if you do nothing,
she will get dragged into the mess
her family is making.
This life is really so difficult!
What do you need me to do?
You go in tomorrow, as if we never met.
Mikoy!
Mikoy, my child,
I have good news for you.
What is happening?
Mikoy, your brother has been released.
And the police said
they will not file charges.
Isn't that wonderful news, my child?
Thank God!
And my child, thanks also to Sir Kian.
Sir Kian?
Kian is the police officer
handling your brother's case.
And he was the one who talked to them
not to pursue the case.
Angelito is also a victim.
May I speak with Mikoy?
Ah…
Hello. Um…
Mikoy, wait, someone
wants to speak with you.
Yes of course, sir!
You can also explain it to him.
Hello, Mikoy?
This is your Sir Kian.
I feel like I already know you
from all the stories I’ve heard about you.
But anyway, don’t worry anymore.
Your brother has been cleared.
Just remind him to stay away from trouble.
Because next time,
he might end up in jail.
Good thing he has a family who loves him.
And a very supportive brother.
Thank you, Sir Kian.
You're welcome.
He is the one making sure
that Angelito will be released.
And that they will not
file any case against him.
So now, Mikoy,
you help me.
Have you read everything?
I am voluntarily coordinating
with your agency.
You need to find a way
to put this in Donabel and Viktor’s room.
Anyone in my place
would definitely be afraid, right?
I don’t know about you,
but I don’t want to die too soon.
MkvDrama.net