What?
What is this?
Ma'am, what are they saying?
They are saying that
our shop violates the rules.
Drivers are finding it
difficult to pass by our shop.
They are saying many such things.
Just like we feared,
we've lost our shop, Vetri.
Ma'am, sorry.
Leave it, Vetri.
You don't say anything.
We can keep blaming each other.
But, what is the use?
It had to happen
and it has happened.
I should've just
stayed back that day.
But, I went shopping
instead of sending Pandi.
That's why..
Hey, he is coming..
What? How was my magic?
What did we do, sir?
You started the problem, right?
Hey, if you had spoken
like this yesterday,
you wouldn't have lost your shop.
How did you talk to me last night?
You thought I'd forget
just because I was drunk.
You even tried to hit me.
Did you think I would just
leave after getting hit?
I will make you beg
on the streets for three months.
Just keep in mind. Yuu shouldn't
have caused trouble with me.
Go and find a way to survive.
Go.
- Sir..
Hey, what do we do now?
House rent, groceries,
my daughter's college fees..
Oh, my God! Just the thought
of it makes my head spin.
Hey, say something.
Don't stand like a statue.
Hey, Vetri, are you
still thinking about that?
If one door closes,
another door will open.
No, ma'am,
I don't mind if I had lost my job.
You lost the business, ma'am.
Hey, what are you saying?
Only after you came
did my business start going well.
Did you forget that?
Every good day is followed
by a bad day. Leave it.
We'll deal with it.
Butcher, I need
200 grams of chicken.
Here is the garnish.
Hey, just keep it and leave.
Looks like you're going to
be here all day, just watching.
Sir, this is not an order list.
This is a cooking guide.
Oh, a cooking guide?
- Yes.
Are you irritating me?
Sir, it wasn't me.
It is from Mr. Ragupathi.
If you try to weasel your way in
by using Mr. Ragupathi's name,
you'll be in big trouble.
Sir, I'm not lying, I swear.
If you don't believe me,
you can call him and ask.
Tell me, Nedumaran.
- Sir.
Sir, they have given me a list
of things like 'karpooravalli',
'adhimadhuram', 'sukku', 'thippili'..
You've given a list of ingredients.
I just wanted to know..
I had sent it.
- Oh.
I just wanted to
cross-check it, sir. That's all.
If I'd known what the issue was,
I'd have made you a herbal drink.
No, nothing serious.
I saw it on the internet and liked
it. That's why I sent you the list.
Okay, sir, definitely.
I will probably try to add some
more wonderful ingredients.
I will send you
a good herbal drink, sir.
Okay, good.
- Take care, sir.
John.
Something is fishy.
Something is wrong.
I don't know what it is.
Anyway, let's see.
Chef, shall we start
the prep for this?
Check the ingredients properly
and start the preparation.
Okay, Chef.
Shiva.
- Yes, Chef.
Chef.
Light the burner
and put it on low flame.
Then place a pan and pour
some water. - Okay, Chef.
Yeah.
Chef.
- Yes, get some turmeric powder.
Correct..
Ask another room service
guy to come. I will give it to him.
Why?
Go, why are you standing here?
Stop glaring and leave.
I'll pluck your eyeballs out
and put them in a soup. Get lost.
Actually, it's a perfect mix, sir.
Measurements and ingredients
are on the correct scale.
You can't find it anywhere on
social media or the internet, sir.
That's Nedumaran's brilliance.
- Thank you, sir.
Ask Vetri to come.
- Okay, sir.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir.
Vetri.
- Tell me, sir.
Check if the ingredients are
correct in this herbal drink.
I'm telling you, just check it.
- Okay, sir.
Sir, he has added
everything correctly.
He has added some extra things.
It will help your cold, sir.
Nedumaran.
- Sir.
Everything you said is correct.
- Okay, sir.
You can't find it on the internet.
Because all the ingredients
in this were listed by Vetri.
If Vetri had asked you,
you wouldn't
have done it in the kitchen.
That's why I asked you to do it.
But, I never thought you would
make it yourself and give it to me.
Sir, the guests are waiting.
I'll take my leave.
Thank you, sir.
Nedumaran.
- Sir. - Are you okay?
Yeah, I am fine, sir.
Not bad at all, Maran.
This herbal drink is very
soothing for the throat.
That's Nedumaran's touch.
Sir, I am getting late
for my dinner prep, yeah.
Shit..
Chef, you asked me to come.
Anything important? - Damn you..
Did you see Mr. Ragupathi?
What did he say?
Did he taste the dish?
I tasted the dish.
It was fantastic, Chef.
S-Sorry, Chef. Any problem?
He is testing my patience.
Who, Chef?
- The room service boy.
You mean Vetri?
Who else is disturbing me other
than him in the room service team?
W-What happened, Chef?
- First, he stole my dish.
After that, he entered my
kitchen without my knowledge.
Now, he has made me cook his dish.
- Wow.
So, the one who made us do
the fantastic dish is our Vetri?
John, will you please
shut your mouth?
Just shut up!
Sorry, Chef.
He is screwing up my peaceful
and happy mind from day one, yes.
Chef, you could have fired
him from day one, right?
It is a stupid decision, John.
Nedumaran will not do it.
I hope you know about it, John.
Yes, Chef.
What shall we do
about him now, Chef?
I will catch him one day
in the kitchen.
I will say that he is nothing
and throw him out, right?
Like that, I will make him
feel that he is fit for nothing.
And he is just shit.
Correct, Chef.
- I will do everything for it.
Okay. Chef.
Relax, Chef.
Chef, there is no need
to do all this.
He will do something
and get caught of his own accord.
Sorry, Chef, I-I will go.
Give it to me.
- Yeah.
Everything was good.
Shruthi.
- Yes, Mom.
Give me two minutes.
I will talk to Joji and come.
Why, Mom? You stay here.
Don't do unnecessary things.
After your dad passed away,
I have lived my life only for you.
I am not asking you.
I am telling you.
Mom..
Sorry, Joji.
We had a fight
in the room last night.
I am the one who usually
starts the fight.
But yesterday, I was getting
scolded by them for a change.
Sorry.
I put you in an uncomfortable
situation yesterday, right?
Nothing like that, dear.
- No.
I know.
You would have felt bad, right?
- Leave it, Padma.
I too want to apologise to you.
It is because of me that there is
so much problem in your family.
That is not a problem.
I'll deal with it.
I also want to stay
for a few more days.
But, I can't.
But, the days I was with you..
Like the way
you remembered my dress code..
I want you to always
be in my memories.
Before you came,
I had no motive in my life.
But, after this, I will
think that you are with me.
With that, I can spend
the rest of my life.
Will anyone get a chance
to relive their past life?
I don't know. But, I got it.
I am very happy.
- Okay, Joji.
If you feel like it, call me.
- Sure.
If that is all,
we will come together again.
We will definitely meet.
- Sure.
Mom.
It's okay, dear.
They are waiting for you.
You leave.
- Okay, Joji.
We will meet again. Bye.
Bye.
What are you saying?
How can I find someone
at the last minute?
I've given it to that room.
In this room..
I found one.
Hang up the phone.
Hey, do you know
how to play the guitar?
Guitar?
I want to play it.
But, I don't know how to play it.
Is that it?
Okay, come with me.
I will give you a guitar.
Just act as if you are playing it.
What if someone finds out?
I will take care of it. You come.
You will take care of it. You know
how to sing and you'll rock it.
But, when I don't know how
to play it, I'll be ashamed, right?
I will take care of all that.
There will be music
in the background.
Just play it.
If the music stops, then
I will play it like a mad man.
Will you give me a signal
before the music stops?
Oh, are you okay with it then?
I'm okay, why?
Why did you say okay so quickly?
Hey, do I have to come or not?
I was just kidding.
But, you won't make
a fool out of me, right?
Hey, Kumudha,
why are you laughing?
I am coming because I trust you.
No old traps, right?
You come, let's see.
Is there any payment?
- Yes. A lot.
If you'd told me sooner, I wouldn't
have asked so many questions.
It was good.
- Is it?
I have been playing
guitar for a year.
You did very well.
It was very professional. - Thanks.
Was it professional?
Oh, wow..
Whenever I play, I play
as if it's my first time.
Who are you talking to?
- Aishu, she is a fan of mine.
Sister.
How come you're here?
Even I know where I'll be.
How did you come here?
- I am following you closely.
I have seen you at an event before,
without your knowledge.
You could have come
and talked to me.
I came to talk to you.
But, you were in a hurry.
So, I didn't want to stop you.
How are you?
Is everything fine?
I am fine.
How are you?
How is Dad?
Is he still angry with me?
Then?
How could he not be angry?
He carries a lot of anger.
Even though I am angry
with him, I want to see him.
He will be home.
Will you come?
Oh, no.
If I think of coming
to our house in this situation,
I feel like I am entering
a haunted house. I'm so scared.
It's okay, come and eat.
I am a ghost who cooks well.
Hey.
She is my sister.
- Sister?
Mr. Nedumaran has two daughters?
Stop staring
and take a photo of us.
Here.
Smile, you two look alike.
Take a nice photo, not like
your fake guitar pose from before.
Okay?
- What are you saying?
Was it acting?
- Yes..
He was acting.
- Sorry..
Oh, no.
How long will you take?
- He keeps calling.
Oh, no, I attended the call.
'Hey..'
'What the hell?'
- Sir.
'Aishu..'
Hi, sir.
'What the hell are you doing there?'
- What happened? - What happened?
Hey, hello..
What is it?
- Nothing..
Shall we take a selfie?
- Yes, let's take one.