YUMI'S CELLS 3
EPISODE 22
THE STICKLER
He's not here.
Did he go out for lunch?
Ms. Kim.
Oh, Ms. Kim. You're here.
- Hello.
- Gosh.
You're early.
Isn't the meeting at one?
There was no traffic.
Am I too early?
Oh, not at all.
The details aren't decided yet
so feel free to tell us what you want.
We'll incorporate everything you tell me.
What do I know?
You know best, Chief Editor Ahn.
Ms. Kim.
You need to review
these things carefully now.
You're not the rookie writer
Kim Yu-mi anymore.
I'm the same Kim Yu-mi as before.
My, that's not true.
Your aura is already different.
LITERATURE RADIO
By the way...
But you're especially glowing today.
Did something good happen?
Sorry?
Well, nothing that special happened...
That's right, Ms. Kim.
Is Soon-rok...
Soon-rok...
Yes?
Is he doing well?
Is he not causing any trouble?
Oh, not at all.
He's doing well.
Well, that's a relief.
If there's even a tiny thing
you don't like about him
tell me right away.
I've been keeping
a close eye on himlately.
Why?
I don't like his actions lately.
He wasn't like this before,
but I guess he's gotten a big head.
Well, he's doing well on our team
so don't worry.
I tolerate him because he's a junior
I know and care for.
But lately...
Well, well. Look at that.
Speak of the devil.
It's Soon-rok!
Soon-rok, did you have lunch?
Ms. Kim came a while ago.
Where have you been?
Hello, Ms. Kim.
Hello, Shin PD.
JULLY LITERATURE RADIO
Ms. Kim, would you like more coffee?
No, I'm fine.
The production team has arrived.
They'll be up soon.
Okay.
By the way, Ms. Kim.
Yes?
You look pretty today.
I always
look this good.
You have princess syndrome, don't you?
But, Soon-rok.
Don't you think
we should tell the Chief Editor?
That we're dating?
Yeah.
If he finds out later
I think he'll feel really betrayed.
I'll tell Ida,
so you tell the Chief Editor.
Absolutely not.
If he finds out
he might kick me out
of the Editorial Department.
No way.
I'm serious.
It's because of something I said before.
You know
producers who can't keep
work and life separate
and date their writers?
I think they're pathetic.
How can they be objective about work?
So?
What did you say?
They lack
the basic sense of a producer.
You think so too?
People like that
should be kicked out
of the Editorial Department.
And last time in Busan...
And?
Toying with a writer's feelings
for personal reasons is wrong.
How is that toying with them?
He was expressing his interest.
I was rooting for him too.
Was I toying with them too?
Things like that can happen on a trip.
I don't think that should happen.
It's a workshop, after all.
You should separate
your public and private life.
For goodness' sake.
What a stick-in-the-mud.
You're so high and mighty, huh?
Acting like you've never had
an office romance in your life.
I've never done that.
Yeah, right. Not even a fling?
I don't do that at work.
Why not?
- Sorry?
- Well, why not?
It's not against rules.
It's my principle.
Principle, my foot.
You just wait.
If I ever catch you
having a fling, I'll just...
That will never happen.
Wait, you really said that?
That's why we can't.
Why did you say something
you couldn't keep?
I was...
- trying to.
- So...
is that why you drew a line with me, too?
But...
you couldn't help it because of my charm.
And you had no choice
but to break your principle.
Because of a woman like me.
That's what it was?
You have a serious princess complex.
You can't deny it, can you?
Yu-mi.
You said you wanted to go to Kyoto, right?
Yeah, why?
Want to go for two days
on Friday and Saturday?
Because Saturday...
is your birthday.
Really?
I'd love to...
Then I'll book the tickets.
But I thought
you had a trip to China today
and were coming back on Friday?
And you have another trip next week.
I can just transfer flights
at the airport.
That sounds like you're overdoing it.
I'm fine.
- We can go later.
- No.
Going after your birthday
doesn't count as a birthday present.
Why?
Because it goes against
one of Soon-rok's principles?
I love it!
If that's your principle, I love it.
Let's go.
You're here?
- Come in.
- Hello.
Hello.
Indeed.
If there's a castle for Writer Cell
in Yu-mi Village...
there's an equally impressive tower
in Soon-rok Village.
Its name?
The Tower of Principles.
It's the very symbol of Soon-rok Village.
This tower is built on the principles
Soon-rok established over 29 years.
And on each block, big and small
important or trivial principles
are engraved.
NO SINGLE USE PLASTIC FOR DELIVERIES
ONLY STRAWBERRY CUSTARD BUNGEOPPANG
LAUNDRY ON WEDNESDAYS
PEACHES MUST BE FIRM
Recently
this tower has faced a crisis.
Laundry on Wednesdays.
What?
Ms. Kim.
Do you want to...
watch the movie together?
Never see a movie alone with someone
you have no romantic feelings for.
A broken principle must be discarded.
You're cool.
Never make comments about a writer
other than about their writing.
Do not share an umbrella
with a female colleague.
Wait.
Wait, hold on!
You can't just pull them out like that.
What if the tower shakes?
NO MATTER HOW CUTE,
DON'T CARELESSLY PET ANOTHER'S DOG
See? It's shaking.
I know.
But a broken principle...
must be discarded as that's the principle.
Hold on, this is a crisis.
Soon-rok's principles
should never be broken.
How many is that already?
All because of Writer Kim Yu-mi?
This is why you need to draw the line.
The crisis didn't end there.
Don't cancel plans at the last minute.
Hey, let go.
Do not argue during work.
I think I...
I think
I like you, Writer.
Don't confess romantic feelings to a woman
you have professional ties with.
- He's crazy.
- He's gone nuts.
He actually confessed to a writer.
What do we do?
- It'll collapse if he pulls that out.
- Is it gonna collapse?
Be careful!
This is too dangerous.
If even one more comes out,
it could collapse at any moment.
Do something about Writer Yu-mi.
I drew the line.
I even put up an absolute defense.
What more can I do?
Rational!
Look at Soon-rok.
No matter how much I think about it, I...
I like you, Writer.
It's pathetic
I've only just realized, but...
Perhaps from the very beginning...
I think I've liked you.
THE TOWER OF PRINCIPLES
Don't make a move on a woman
who has rejected you.
He went to see Writer Yu-mi again.
DON'T MAKE A MOVE ON A WOMAN
WHO HAS REJECTED YOU
- It's collapsing! It's collapsing!
- Oh, no.
DON'T MAKE A MOVE ON A WOMAN
WHO HAS REJECTED YOU
LAUNDRY ON WEDNESDAYS
Oh, no!
Just look at that disgraceful sight!
This is the first time it's happened
in Soon-rok's 29 years of life.
To think the tower
is in danger of collapsing.
I'm sorry.
I tried drawing lines
and going on dates to keep my distance...
but Writer Yu-mi's influence
is too strong...
What's so special about Kim Yu-mi?
Is Kim Yu-mi the priority?
Or are the principles the priority?
Soon-rok's principles
are his identity.
He's painstakingly built them up
for 29 years.
If they collapse...
then Soon-rok is no longer Soon-rok.
That's right.
FRIDAY
I wonder if he's arrived.
I guess he's not here yet.
Yu-mi.
Soon-rok.
Have you arrived?
I just landed.
I just arrived at the airport too.
It'll be crowded,
so let's meet inside after security.
I'll get my bags and head right over.
Okay.
I can't wait to see you.
- See you soon.
- Okay.
Bye.
Gosh, how many days has it been?
It's almost been a whole week.
Hurry up.
Let's go see Soon-rok.
I'm going.
- This way.
- Thank
you. Where are you?
I've boarded.
I'm at the gate.
I'll head in soon.
It's really been a while
since I've played golf.
I know, right? It's been so long.
By the way, will you go to duty-free?
Which gate is ours?
Are you going to duty-free?
Did you see
who just walked by?
No, I didn't see.
Why? Did a celebrity walk by?
Who?
Emergency, emergency!
Soon-rok.
What do we do?
Hey.
Soon-rok.
Hey, what are you doing here?
Hello.
Hold on. Ju-ho!
Ju-ho!
What's this?
- Whoa, whoa.
- Hello.
Wait, wait. What are you doing here?
Where are you going now?
Didn't you just tell me
you got back from Shanghai?
Yes... yes, I did.
So where are you off to again?
- Well, it's just...
- Yeah?
Well...
I already had a trip scheduled.
So you're going on another trip
without even stopping by home?
I booked it a long time ago.
What?
Do you get it? Because I don't.
He's young, so I guess it's possible.
Where are you two headed?
- Our golf club's regular tour.
- I see.
Sir, I'll check your seat for you.
- Oh, yes.
- Yes.
- Anyway, see you later.
- Okay.
- It's a window seat.
- Yes.
Hey, it's fine. Just come on, get in.
Is he traveling alone?
You think he's alone?
He is.
That empty seat is taken.
- Who?
- Who do you think?
Who else would be this passionate
even after a business trip?
Is that it?
So he has a girlfriend?
Since when?
He travels with his woman
but won't let others have a fling?
Selfish jerk.
Soon-rok, Kim Ju-ho, and Chief Editor Ahn
are on our plane.
What do we do?
THE TOWER OF PRINCIPLES
BARLEY TEA OVER BOTTLED WATER
Don't date coworkers,
and don't get caught.
This is Soon-rok's Grand Principle
of Grand Principles.
If this one gets broken...
It's all over.
The tower collapses.
Hello?
Yu-mi, why aren't you getting on?
Those two got on, right?
They did.
Of all the flights,
how could we be on the same one?
- I shouldn't get on.
- What?
What am I supposed to do
with Ju-ho there too?
I think you'll get in trouble.
- I won't get on.
- What will you do if you don't?
I'll just take the next flight.
There are plenty of flights to Osaka.
No, no. Yu-mi, wait.
Then I'll get off right now.
Soon-rok. Meet me at the airport.
I'll be right behind you.
Hello? Yu-mi.
Arah Air Flight 701 to Osaka.
- We'll be closing the cabin doors.
- Sir, please be seated.
- I'm sorry but...
- Ju-ho! Look at him.
What's with him?
We will close the door shortly.
I guess he's really going alone.
You really think that?
- He is.
- No, his girlfriend's waiting in Osaka.
Oh, is that it?
Ladies and gentlemen
our plane will now be taking off.
Please check that
your seatbelts are fastened.
Yu-mi prevented Soon-rok's
principle from collapsing.
However...
Dear passengers, welcome to Osaka
a city for all seasons.
The current local time is...
Yu-mi, where are you?
I just arrived.
WRITER KIM YU-MI
- Yu-mi.
- Soon-rok.
- I can't make it.
- What?
There are no tickets.
I mean, there are so many flights
but not a single ticket is available.
They're all sold out
until tomorrow morning.
So...
I'm on my way home now.
Well, it's the weekend.
That's why you should've taken the flight.
For a two-day trip
there's no point
in flying tomorrow afternoon, right?
What should I do?
You're there, so just have fun.
- Okay?
- No, that's...
Shin PD.
Don't tell me you got stood up.
Right?
Your girlfriend is waiting for you
at the airport, isn't she?
You didn't really come on this trip
alone, did you?
Hey, I said that's not it.
Shin PD is different from us.
Jeez.
Take care.
- Call me.
- Let's go.
Gosh, I'm so stiff.
My body isn't what it used to be.
When using the hot spring
we recommend that you stay hydrated.
To all our passengers,
thank you for flying with us.
Our plane has arrived at its destination.
Please remain seated until the plane
comes to a complete stop
and the seatbelt sign has been turned off.
Soon-rok, call me when you arrive.
I'm here to pick you up.
Soon-rok!
I could've just taken the bus.
I still came because I wanted to see you.
I'll drive.
Will you?
A present.
What's this? Oh, snacks.
Let's have them with some beer.
How could they have been
on that specific flight out of so many?
We're so unlucky, really.
I wanted to visit Kyoto.
What did you do there?
I took a bath, ate, and slept.
Then I woke up, ate
took a bath, and came back.
You got some good rest.
Yes, I did.
Are you mad?
- No.
- Why do you seem mad?
It's not something
I should be mad at you for.
I was so upset too.
Can you imagine how I felt?
I had to turn back right at the gate.
But I did it because I was worried
you'd be in a difficult position.
You insisted on separating work
and private life so many times.
If we couldn't get caught like that
you have your image to keep, too.
That stupid principle.
Where are you going?
Who are you calling?
SHIN SOON-ROK PD
- Hello?
Dae-yong, it's Soon-rok.
I have something to tell you.
Sure, what is it?
I'm...
dating Writer Kim Yu-mi.
Wait, what?
I'm dating Writer Kim Yu-mi.
It's been a while.
What... what did you just say?
So just know that.
I'll tell you the details later.
Have a nice trip!
Hello... hello?
GRAND PRINCIPLE
DON'T DATE COWORKERS AND DON'T GET CAUGHT
TOWER OF PRINCIPLES
Yu-mi.
We can go on trips whenever we want now.
Hey, what are you doing? Your principle...
I'm throwing away that stupid
principle and everything.
What's the point of having principles?
They're going to be broken anyway.
Because of me?
Are all of your principles being broken
because of me?
Because you like me that much?
Can you stop being so full of yourself?
What are you going to do?
All your precious principles
are broken because of me...
I didn't mean for that to happen.
I wanted to protect
your precious principles...
But, Soon-rok
I feel really great right now.
Better than a birthday gift
or a trip to Kyoto
I feel amazing right now.
I feel great too.
And so, the Tower of Principles
in Soon-rok Village collapsed.
Conquered by Yu-mi
now only its ruins remain.
on her birthday.
EPISODE 23
A ONE-WAY LIFE
Hello.
Shin PD, you're here.
Yes.
The Chief Editor has been looking for you.
He told me to let him know
the moment you got in.
Just a moment. I need to send an email.
Shin Soon-rok, you're being summoned.
Did you do something wrong?
I'm not sure.
Did you have a good golf trip?
Whether I had a good trip or not
is none of your business.
Hey, you punk.
PDs who can't separate work and life
PDs who date their writers...
Didn't you say they should all be fired?
That they have no basic principles?
Didn't you say that?
Huh? I remember all of it.
You said you wouldn't have a fling.
That that was your principle, right?
- I did.
- And?
Well...
A person's principles
can change, can't they?
What? What did you say?
People's minds change.
How can this punk be so shameless?
We're human because we change.
Otherwise, we'd be robots.
Hey, look at this punk.
Are you laughing?
What's so funny?
Sorry, but I have an urgent email.
Can we talk after I send it?
- Are you trying to get away?
- I need to reschedule
tomorrow's meeting from Shanghai.
Shanghai? Right, you take care of that.
All right. Then let's talk over lunch.
I can't have lunch with you.
Why not?
Who do you think you are,
turning down lunch?
-I have something to take care of.
-Why?
Are you going on a date?
Not exactly.
I haven't gotten her
a birthday present yet.
If I go on my business trip today
I won't see her for another week.
Wow, just... So openly like this?
You weren't this kind of guy before.
I've always been this kind of guy.
It's just that
my direction has changed.
The Tower of Principles
the symbol of Soon-rok Village.
This tower was guarded by a warrior
named the One-Way General.
Watch out!
When the Tower of Principles,
which he had long guarded, collapsed
the One-Way General, now purposeless
was flustered.
What should I...
protect now?
If he wasn't protecting
something worth devoting his life to
he was a cell with no reason to exist.
He finally made a decision.
The conqueror of love
who destroyed the tower.
He vows to protect Yu-mi.
Welcome.
Can I help you find something?
I'm looking for women's earrings.
Sure, this way.
Do you have a particular style in mind?
Well...
It's a birthday present.
For your girlfriend?
- Yes.
- What's your girlfriend's taste?
I'm not sure about her taste
but I'm sure she won't like anything big.
So she doesn't like big pieces.
Because her face is tiny.
So big ones wouldn't suit her.
Oh, I see.
So she has a small face.
It's as small as a fist.
And she has fair skin.
Right.
Her face is very small and fair.
Oh, right.
Do you need more information?
Oh, yes.
Then it's easier for me
to make a recommendation.
She's the intellectual type.
And elegant...
Also...
she's pretty when she smiles.
She's slim.
No, more like slender.
The kind that makes you
want to protect her.
I see.
Do you have any earrings
that would suit that style?
These designs are very popular these days.
Since she's intellectual, elegant,
and has a small face
I think a simple design is better
- than something too flashy.
- Yes.
One-Way General!
Come back!
- The One-Way General Cell
- That's not the way!
- started walking down a new path.
One-Way General!
I'm not going back.
I've already
chosen this path.
Would you like to see something else?
Can you
show me this one?
Yu-mi.
You should've waited inside. It's hot.
The weather was so nice
I waited outside on purpose.
But why were you coming from over there?
I was just looking at something.
The Chief Editor is at work, right?
Was everything okay?
I was questioned for over an hour.
A whole hour?
What kind of interrogation
takes a whole hour?
Let's talk on the way.
I have to be at the airport by 9 o'clock.
Then we don't have much time.
We should eat first. Let's hurry.
There are many good places here.
Wait, not here.
Let's go to a famous spot nearby.
- A famous spot?
- It's close to here. Let's go.
But there are other places here.
That place is good too.
It's a must-visit spot
whenever I'm in this neighborhood.
You'll like it too.
What kind of place is it?
It's a bunsik restaurant.
It's 30 years old
and the tteokbokki is amazing.
I love tteokbokki.
Wait a minute.
Something feels...
That's right.
It's definitely
this alley.
What's the name of that place?
The name?
It's...
I can't remember it all of a sudden.
It was an English name.
An English name?
Hold on.
We aren't going there, right?
It's this way.
We're here.
I knew it!
Oh, right.
Yes, it's Ba-bi's Snack Bar.
It's my regular spot.
Why couldn't I remember it?
This is your regular spot?
Yes.
You'll be so surprised when you try it.
Let's go.
- Let's go somewhere else.
- Why?
But you said you love tteokbokki.
I do.
But...
I'm full.
Or do you want to go eat by yourself?
I'll wait for you at that coffee shop.
What are you talking about?
You have to try this
even if you're full.
- Come on, let's go.
- No, wait. I really...
Wait a second.
BA-BI'S SNACK BAR
CLOSED FOR VACATION FOR A WEEK
07/24 - 07/31
They're on vacation.
Let's go somewhere else.
I know another good tteokbokki place.
Thank goodness it's closed.
It would've been so awkward
if I ran into Ba-bi's dad.
Hunger Cell. Isn't this your appetite?
I was so surprised earlier
that I dropped it.
Then what's that on your head now?
My appetite grows back once I calm down.
CELL SNACK
- This place is delicious too.
- Right?
This place is pretty famous too.
I should get some to go on my way out.
But they don't do takeout here.
Ba-bi's Snack Bar does takeout.
This place is good
but it can't beat Ba-bi's Snack Bar.
The combination of green onions
and broth there
is amazing.
I didn't know
you were so serious about tteokbokki.
By the way...
why were you acting like that earlier?
Why were you so against
going into Ba-bi's Snack Bar?
It's...
complicated.
What is it?
What should I do?
Soon-rok noticed.
Tell him.
Soon-rok is Yu-mi's boyfriend now.
There should be no lies between them.
The truth is...
That place...
It's run by my ex-boyfriend's father.
I've been there before.
So it's a bit awkward
for me to go there.
Wait a minute.
Then your ex-boyfriend...
His name is Ba-bi?
Is that right?
Yeah, it is.
That's right. So it is.
The owner said
he named the shop after his son.
Oh, I see. I guessed Ba-bi right.
I see.
But...
I know his son.
- You know him?
- Yes.
I saw him at the counter a few times.
But...
that guy...
He was really handsome.
- No, he wasn't.
- No.
He was very handsome.
That's why I remember him.
What's going on?
Soon-rok looks upset.
He seems to care too much.
He was just...
average.
Just a very average...
You really...
do care about looks.
Yeah, that's right.
I do care about looks.
Soon-rok, thanks for your looks.
It's all thanks to my parents.
I'm glad my Soon-rok
is so understanding about it.
I can't tell if he's being
innocent or cool, though.
What a relief. My appetite is back.
One-Way General.
Don't just keep going forward.
It's about her ex-boyfriend.
Could it be that guy we heard about?
The one who fell for a young intern
so they broke up.
What does it matter?
I've already chosen this path.
But still...
aren't you curious?
Out of my way.
Only the one-way life.
What was that?
The One-Way General kept to his path
and finally reached his destination.
Who is that?
Is it one of Soon-rok's cells?
It's not the Love Cell.
- Who are you?
- What?
- What? I asked who you are.
A fist-sized face!
Skin as fair as snow!
What was that?
A fist-sized face
with snow-white skin.
Born with intelligence and grace.
The one with a million-dollar smile
and so delicate that she makes you
want to protect her!
The conqueror
Kim Yu-mi!
What's going on?
I am One-Way General
guardian of Soon-rok Village.
Please open these castle
gates wide and clear a path
so that I may walk a one-way road
for you my entire life
and protect you.
One-Way General Cell?
That cell isn't in our village.
It must be a cell that only exists
in Soon-rok's village.
He says he'll protect her.
What does he plan to do?
It's good, right?
It's delicious.
You have to eat the tteokbokki first.
Then their Einspänner completes it.
I discovered this place last year
and it wasn't famous back then.
But just six months later
it got super famous.
What's this?
Your birthday present.
You already gave me a birthday present.
You paid for the whole trip.
That was for my solo trip,
so it doesn't count as a gift.
Oh, I'm fine, Soon-rok.
Open it.
You surprised me.
I really wasn't expecting this.
But what is it?
This is an expensive brand.
Is it earrings?
It's a ring.
Yes.
A ring?
A ring for a birthday present?
Gosh, it's beautiful.
But this is only
- crystal, right?
-It's real.
- It's real?
- Of course, it's real.
This is a real diamond ring?
You're giving me a diamond ring
for my birthday?
- Try it on to check the size.
- Hold on.
How much is this?
I can tell just by looking at it.
Who gives this as a birthday gift?
It's too much.
Why not? It's possible.
It's pretty.
What, you buy everything that's pretty?
Is your family rich or something?
You're not.
I'm so flustered right now.
Does buying something like this
mean nothing to you?
I thought it would look good on you.
So you'd just buy anything
if they look good on me?
It's not that I just bought it.
It's a birthday gift and...
I was thinking of it
as an engagement ring.
A proposal?
I'm so shocked I lost my appetite again.
- Did I mishear?
- Hurry!
Open the castle gates
and welcome me!
I will walk this one-way path for you
for the rest of my life.
Yu-mi?
What if...
we got married?
I think it would be great.
What do you think about it?
EPISODE 24
THE THIRD PROPOSAL
What do you...
think about it?
Soon-rok proposed.
A proposal?
While drinking an Einspänner.
Hey, let's go, let's go!
Let's hurry.
Rational, where are you going?
I heard Yu-mi got a proposal.
There's something I need to check.
Follow me!
The sudden proposal
made her reflect
for the first time in a while.
- A proposal... A proposal...
- Here it is.
THE DAY YU-MI PROPOSED TO GU UNG
There have been two proposals
in Yu-mi's life.
The first proposal...
Ung.
Should we...
get married?
Yu-mi proposed first...
but she never got an answer.
I get it.
I haven't said anything yet.
I was just curious
what you thought.
You don't have to think about it so hard.
The second proposal...
Yu-mi...
let's get...
married.
I'm sorry.
I think I know what you mean.
It ended with Yu-mi returning the ring.
When was that?
She proposed to Ung
after nine months of dating.
She got a proposal from Ba-bi
after one year and four months.
But what about Soon-rok now?
After one month.
It's way too rushed.
This isn't right.
Hunger. Give me a boost.
Okay.
What took you so long? I was waiting.
Let's just say yes already.
No.
Huh? Why?
Even when she thought she knew them
it ended badly.
But after only one month?
It's too reckless.
We have to turn him down.
Hey, what if we miss our chance?
What if he walks away?
What if Soon-rok can't work up
the courage to propose again?
But we can't give him
an answer this hastily.
Yu-mi isn't young anymore.
Hey, that's enough!
I'm stronger than you now!
Let's answer quickly.
The Einspänner is getting watery.
What do you...
think about it?
Guys, stop!
Emotional Cell is right.
Love is all about timing.
If Yu-mi loves Soon-rok
there's no reason to hesitate.
But...
I'll decide.
I, Love Cell!
In the name of the Prime Cell,
I accept the proposal...
Love!
Love.
Hey! Who said you could?
I'm the Prime Cell!
I'm the Prime Cell too.
I, Writer Cell,
in the name of the Prime Cell
object to this!
Are you crazy?
Do you know how far behind
the manuscript is due to her dating?
Why is she thinking about marriage
during serialization!
Tell him to come back after it's all over.
If Soon-rok gets his feelings hurt
will you take responsibility?
If he gets upset over a manuscript
Soon-rok isn't fit to be an producer.
Everyone.
But I think we need to answer quickly.
Too much time is passing.
Yu-mi?
Don't you want to
marry me?
You're getting a call.
Is it from work? You should get it.
Yes, hello?
Have you left?
Yes, I'm about to leave now too.
I'm taking the airport bus.
Let's meet at the counter.
Okay.
They all left?
We have to get up.
No, I'm not late.
What if you miss the bus?
- Let's hurry.
- Wait...
Isn't that it?
You can't get on if it's full.
Let's hurry.
Soon-rok, hurry up.
You won't be late, right?
Call me when you get there.
Oh, okay.
- But...
- Safe trip.
Go on.
Let's talk later.
Let go.
But...
we didn't get Yu-mi's answer.
I think Soon-rok is upset right now.
Do you think Soon-rok's feelings are hurt?
I think so.
Yu-mi's feelings were hurt too.
When?
When Ung didn't give an answer...
I think I know now
why Ung couldn't answer.
It wasn't that he didn't love Yu-mi
but he had too much to think about.
I was so upset back then
but now I understand.
But he lost Yu-mi
because he thought too much.
There's such a thing
as timing in love.
If you miss it, it's hard to get back.
That's true too.
But...
if you rashly put it on
and you change your mind...
Putting it on and giving it back
would really hurt the other person.
That's worse than
never putting it on at all.
Are you going to inflict that pain again?
Then what should we do?
The more Soon-rok is like this
the more careful we need to be.
Yu-mi is the older one.
Let's not make the same mistake again.
This is the third proposal.
It's raining.
SHIN SOON-ROK PD
Hey, Soon-rok.
Yu-mi.
Did you get there okay?
Are you on the plane?
No.
Then?
I'm...
outside your place right now.
My flight
was canceled due to an engine malfunction.
My new flight is tomorrow, so I came back.
How could something like that happen?
Yu-mi.
Can I stop by for a bit?
Yes, come on in.
Okay, I'm coming up.
Thank you.
He's throwing all the proposals
in at once!
What do I do?
I was just glad I had time to think.
What should we say?
Yu-mi hasn't decided on an answer yet.
Yu-mi.
Did you get caught in the rain?
I should've come out with an umbrella.
- Hang on. I'll get you a towel.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- All that traveling must be tiring.
I am tired.
Aren't you hungry?
Do you have anything cold to drink?
- Should I make you an ade?
- That sounds good.
What time are you leaving tomorrow?
It's a morning flight.
I have to leave at six.
You're leaving at dawn.
I'll give you a ride tomorrow.
Yu-mi.
Yes?
Should I...
return this?
- What?
- If you feel burdened by it
I can...
return it.
Why...
I got carried away and bought it
but you seem to feel burdened by it.
If you say you're not ready...
I...
can wait.
I just...
I was so sure
that we would end up getting married
that I bought it
without thinking too much.
That...
How can you be so sure?
We've only known
each other a month, Soon-rok.
We don't even know each other that well.
How can you be so sure about that?
If I wasn't sure...
I wouldn't have run to you
in the first place.
If I wasn't sure back then...
Shin PD?
I wouldn't have gone to see you again.
Since then
you've been sure?
- Yes.
- That certainty...
where does it come from?
Because I can just tell.
How do you know?
How do I know?
Yes.
In my entire life...
it's the first time
I've ever felt this way.
That's how I know.
The reason love is always surprising
is because no two loves are ever the same.
So...
Soon-rok is a different person.
For a man whose values on love
are completely different
what's the point of applying
my own past experiences?
That was the thought that crossed my mind.
Then, Soon-rok.
Let's do as you say.
What?
Let's return...
the ring.
I...
like you so much right now.
But I think I still need some time.
I feel like I need to.
-Yu-mi, you don't have to feel...
-So...
when that time comes...
I'll tell you too.
Okay.
But the ring...
I think it's best we return it.
I already bought it,
so you can just accept it.
- It's a birthday present.
- It's too much for a birthday gift.
If I accept this
I'll feel uncomfortable every day.
You're leaving early tomorrow
so give me the receipt.
I'll return it.
- No...
- Instead
let's...
go on a trip.
Don't you think that would be better?
Are you upset?
No.
You seem upset.
I'm not upset, it's just...
Just?
It's just...
I have no energy.
Thank you so much.
The fact you even thought of spending
so much money on me is touching.
But it's such a waste.
I'm sorry if I hurt your feelings.ß
I'm telling you, I was really touched.
I mean it.
One more time.
You still don't have any energy?
Well, I'm starting to feel it.
Then what should I do?
- Is it not enough?
- Of course.
But...
how much more time do you need?
Well, maybe...
a year?
A year?
One year is too long.
How about six months?
Isn't that enough?
I'm someone who thinks a lot.
Then nine months?
Are you haggling with me?
How about we pick a holiday?
- Like Christmas Eve.
- Christmas Eve is only months away.
Or Valentine's Day?
Or my birthday?
No, that's too far away.
Or the day we first met, on that day...
Who is that?
I don't know.
Yu-mi.
Mom.
- Is she not home?
- Huh?
The light was on.
Right?
Yu-mi!
Hey, open the door.
- Dad. You're here too?
- Yeah.
- Open the door.
- Just a second.
Hide.
- Hide?
- If they see at this hour
it'll ruin your first impression.
Wait, Yu-mi.
- But Yu-mi, still...
- Your image hasn't recovered yet!
No...
Come on, Yu-mi!
- Mom! Dad!
- Yu-mi.
Why did you take so long to open the door?
I was in the bathroom.
Why did you come without calling?
We came from your aunt's
and Dad insisted we stop by.
I told you she doesn't like it
when you show up unannounced.
Why? I wanted to see my daughter.
Can't I see my daughter when I want?
Of course. Anything for Dad.
- Of course, of course.
- Definitely.
- Of course.
- What is all this?
Things our Yu-mi likes.
Look, it got rained on. Look at it.
This is expensive leather,
and it's all wet.
What do I do?
Oh my.
- What's this?
- Ta-da.
What is?
Oh my, what kind of ring is this?
This looks like a diamond.
This... Isn't this a wedding ring?
What is this?
Yu-mi!
Isn't this a wedding ring?
You received this?
- From who?
- Oh, Mom.
- Hey.
- Mom.
- It's not!
- What, a wedding ring?
Who did you get this from?
You have a boyfriend?
No!
This thing...
Hey, this is a real diamond!
It's a wedding ring.
No, it's not.
It's cubic zirconia, Mom.
Hold still. Let me see.
This is a diamond. Yes, it is.
It's a diamond.
So, what kind of guy is he?
What does this guy do?
How old is he? Huh?
Here, look.
It's cubic zirconia, not diamond.
This is getting out of hand.
Now that Mom and Dad have seen it,
it's a done deal.
It's a done deal.
I bet they'll be married within a year.
My gosh!
Who... who are you?
Hello. It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Yu-mi's boyfriend
Shin Soon-rok.
Ta-da! Surprise!
Surprised?
Say hi, Mom, Dad.
This is my boyfriend, Shin Soon-rok.
Hello, ma'am.
Sir.
Yes...
It's nice to meet you.
- I'm Yu-mi's mom.
- It's a pleasure to meet you.
He came from work...
It looks like Mom
already likes him, right?
Yu-mi's Mom is a sucker for a pretty face.
Don't you think it'll be
sooner than a year?
Wanna bet it won't even take six months?
I bet it happens before Christmas Eve.
- No, silk would be prettier, right?
- Nice to meet you.
I'm Yu-mi's dad.
Yes. Nice to meet you, sir.
Gosh, Mom.
Why are you being like this?
Sir.
He had that exact expression.
I'm Kim Yu-mi.
Oh, I see.
I think I like you.
He's a very calm and rational person.
You can do it!
Hit a satisfying one for us
Ms. Kim!
I want to date you.
- A dried-fish woman.
- A handsome PD
has arrived.
Okay. One butler secured.
Instructor, wait a minute!
Seriously.
Smile.
Yu-mi, smile.
Everyone, it's time.
Gather around, everyone!
Yu-mi is so pretty!
- Hehe. Soon-rok, don't be nervous.
- You look great.
Smile.
Love.
Hey, Love...
Okay, shorter people,
please move to the front.
It would be better if you moved
a little to the left.
Don't block my face.
Let's take it quick and go eat.
- Okay, I'm taking the picture.
- How nice.
One, two...
- Yu-mi.
I'm so fucking happy.
This is fucking great.
Don't let it get away!
- Forever.
- I'm anxious.
Let's go to sleep.
Bring back a big catch!
I'm so frustrated!
I'm Ung's Love Cell.
I'm new.
What are you going to do being so frugal?
- Fashion Cell is guilty!
- It's the effortless style.
It's Hysterius.
We are cool.
Oh, that's a good story.
I got it. I'm sensing it.
This world has rules and manners.
My skin condition is the best too.
I should go rest.
You have a separate stomach for dessert
so don't worry, man.
You can push yourself a little here too.
I wrote a scenario
for the first time in a while.
You say it's nothing?
The X-ray of love!
I have arrived.
Yu-mi, you look pretty today.
There's only one main character here.
- Bye.
YUMI'S CELLS 3