QUEEN OF TEARS
Du-gwan!
Look!
Oh, dear!
FORMER CEO HONG HAE-IN TERMINALLY ILL
-Gosh!
-Gosh, Du-gwan!
Du-gwan!
Don't forget your shoes!
Mi-seon!
Because I was told
that I have little time left…
to live.
When were you diagnosed?
Is Chairman Yoon aware of this too?
Hae-in.
I can't die yet.
I haven't
told you yet.
Moving through!
That it's okay.
That I never resented you.
What's the use of it?
It only gets on my nerves.
Let's part ways. I want a divorce.
I haven't thanked you
for being by my side all these years…
despite all the harsh words
I didn't mean.
I love her.
I love you, Hae-in.
I love you.
You were the reason
I wanted to live even more.
You can't come in.
You're not allowed to come inside.
I thought I had more time.
We're looking for Hong Hae-in.
Ma'am, where's Hong Hae-in?
I haven't apologized to everyone yet.
INTENSIVE CARE UNIT
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for everything.
EPISODE 11
I thought you hadn't found him.
-You see--
-Get out.
What gives you the right?
This isn't your hospital.
You're going to see the chairman.
Get out since I won't let you.
Your son betrayed you and moved him here.
So do you still think
that you're his legal guardian?
Do you think I'd let that slide?
I'll get out myself.
Damn it.
Hey! Damn it!
Hey!
EMERGENCY STAIRCASE
-Open the door.
-I'm sorry, but I can't do that.
I wasn't talking to you. Open it.
Me too!
Let me in too!
Look. I'm begging you.
Please. I'm sorry for being
so rude to you all this time.
Please forgive me.
Please let me see my father
just this once.
Please.
Should I kneel?
Should I?
Fine.
Fine? Really?
Do you mean that?
But I want you to leave right afterward.
If not, you'll be dragged out.
Thank you.
Father?
Father!
You woke up!
I'm so proud of you!
You did well!
Come on, now.
Don't you know who I am?
Jeez.
Father!
What? Did he pass away?
You bitch.
You're done for.
So he made you his legal guardian?
He's awake now.
So you've lost the power
of attorney now. Am I right?
Yes, that's true.
-Wait. Let's call his doctor--
-Shut up!
Call the police.
Father.
It was her, wasn't it?
That bitch harmed you, didn't she?
Who are you?
Father…
Damn it!
Why are you kicking me out too?
Damn it.
INTENSIVE CARE UNIT
What's… wrong with her?
Mother…
What's her problem?
The CT scan shows acute brain swelling.
The brain tumor cells pressured
the surrounding tissues
and temporarily increased
her intracranial pressure.
We should lower it first--
Brain tumor?
What do you mean?
Were you aware of everything
Hae-in announced? Is that so?
-Honey.
-Then why didn't you tell us? Why?
What have you been doing?
You should've told us that she was sick.
Why didn't you?
-Stop.
-He deceived us again!
He kept it a secret from us.
He deceived us
when Hae-in was this severely ill.
-What are you scheming this time?
-I told you to stop.
We have no right to get upset.
I'm sorry.
We had no idea
despite being her parents.
Please explain.
Please elaborate
on her current condition.
Ms. Hong is suffering from Cloud Cytoma.
It's a type of malignant brain tumor.
Unlike your typical tumor,
where the tumor is
a big lump,
these tumor cells have spread
throughout her cranial nerves like clouds.
Her case is a very rare one worldwide,
so it's been difficult to treat her.
I'm sorry, Mother.
I'm truly sorry
that I didn't tell you sooner.
She probably told you not to.
It must've been a great burden.
Hae-in didn't want her parents
to be heartbroken.
So she wanted to tell you
once things were looking up.
I hope you don't get the wrong idea.
Dad.
By the vast and endless ocean
Stood a single humble cottage
Dwelt a fisherman father
And his young daughter
Oh my love, oh my love
Oh my love, Clementine
Why have you abandoned me forever
Leaving your old father behind
Judging by the MRI results,
I believe he has vascular dementia
due to a head injury and brain hemorrhage.
The significant damage
to his frontal and temporal lobes
is making it difficult for him
to think rationally or remember things.
For now, we have no choice
but to wait until his brain recovers.
Let's give him two weeks.
Does that mean he could recover?
It varies per case,
so I can't guarantee anything.
Seon-hwa.
You must be stunned.
I just heard and--
You knew she was sick.
That's why you told me
not to do things I'd regret.
I'm sorry.
Everyone knew.
Everyone knew but me.
But, Mom,
I just told you
that I had a serious matter too.
Aren't you curious?
You always know what to do
whether it's big or small.
Right.
I'll take care
of my business.
Jeez, don't be so dramatic.
I'm anemic too.
I'm also dizzy
since I couldn't sleep much either.
It's not like Soo-cheol
is doing fine either.
We're all suffering here.
-What?
-What is this about Hae-in?
Is it true? Is she sick?
I doubt her family knew.
Not even Soo-cheol.
He must be shocked.
That's why you called?
It's a small favor.
He has anxiety disorder.
It happens when he's stressed.
It's serious. He needs medication.
I don't think he took any with him.
We have some at home.
Can you tell someone to get it?
-It's--
-Hey.
-Cheon Da-hye.
-He might faint and die!
-Then let him die.
-Hey, how could you…
What do you want me to do?
Should I kill him?
Don't ever call me again
over something like this!
Or I'll kill him myself.
Hyun-woo.
I think this was why.
What do you mean?
What is that?
I was told to carry this around…
so it'd subdue her energy.
I didn't believe it.
I just wanted
to be better than her for once.
But…
what if this damn talisman
is the reason why she's sick?
It's all my fault.
I shouldn't have carried
this stupid talisman.
Hae-in.
Hae-in!
What about a talisman? You lunatic.
Did you see that?
This talisman must be powerful.
She woke up once I ripped it up.
Soo-cheol.
I'm sorry…
for everything.
Hyun-woo, I don't think
she's in her right mind.
Go get the doctor and the family.
Our family…
-Are you okay?
-I love you.
I've loved you
from the moment we met
until now.
I'm sorry that I didn't treat you better.
I'm also sorry that I left you all alone
with my family.
I think a part of me already knew
that you wanted a divorce.
You put up with us for so long.
So…
it's okay. Don't feel bad.
What are you doing?
If I don't say these things before I die,
you'll never know how I really feel.
I'm telling you this now
since I don't know when I'll die.
Last night,
I prayed
more than I had done in my entire life.
I said I'd do nothing,
but cry every day,
drink a ton of alcohol,
sleep on the street,
and live recklessly
if you died.
That's a threat, not a prayer.
I don't care.
If you die,
I'll give up on myself.
You just watch.
How can I watch when I'm dead?
So cut the nonsense.
I'm opening my heart to you.
I was even scared
in my sleep in case I wouldn't be able
to tell you.
Don't be scared.
You're not going to die.
You won't die.
I won't let you.
ENDOSCOPY
Mom!
Hae-in woke up! Hurry up!
Where did she go?
Why didn't you tell us about this?
But it's okay. I know about it now.
Don't worry. Many of my close friends
are renown doctors.
They're all around the world.
Is that so? I should've told you sooner.
I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry?
You're the one who's sick.
You should've told me sooner.
It must've been so painful
to keep it a secret.
You're okay now.
Everything will be fine. Okay?
Okay.
Where's Mom?
Mother.
Let me be alone.
I'm truly sorry that I didn't tell you
sooner.
Forget it.
What kind of mother
doesn't know that her child is dying?
I know nothing about my own daughter.
How pathetic.
I can't believe I took my pain out
on my own daughter.
Whenever that young child
reached out to me…
I didn't hold her
even once.
Even I can't live with myself.
I'd hate to have a mom like me.
Hyun-woo.
It's all my fault.
I caused my daughter
pain and stress.
That's why she's sick.
Are you a doctor?
How could you know things
that a doctor doesn't even know?
They don't know the cause
or how to prevent my illness.
It's not caused by stress either.
How are you…
so naive?
You're so annoying.
And…
I would've struggled
to have a daughter like me too.
So it's not all your fault.
Hae-in.
Did it hurt
a lot?
Well…
There were times when it hurt
and times when it didn't.
I had no idea you were sick.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
I was wrong.
I told you.
This has nothing to do
with how you treated me.
I didn't want to tell you because I knew
you wouldn't understand.
I'm sorry.
I'm…
I'm really sorry.
I can't live
without you.
No.
Don't die.
Please don't die, Hae-in. I'm sorry…
My dear Hae-in…
I'm sorry…
Lady Luck is only on her side
since that evil bitch is so hardworking.
She sure is something.
Chairman Hong.
Do you recognize where we are?
Come on, don't be scared. We're home.
Let's go inside.
Ma'am, there are many
nice electric wheelchairs these days.
The chairman may be out of it,
but he refuses to be fed
by anyone but me.
So I can't leave his side.
That's why I asked you to come here.
We understand. It's only thanks to you
that he woke up.
Enough with the flattery.
Explain yourselves.
How could he hold
such a press conference right now?
We had no idea either.
Chairman Yoon suddenly--
You should've known better.
You're only getting paid so much
so you'd prevent
such disasters from occurring.
Goodness, should I not have said that?
"You have no right
to say such things to us."
"What do you know when you only cook
and nurse the chairman?"
-Is that it?
-Of course not, ma'am.
In that case, submit all the drafts to me
before you give them
to Chairman Yoon and tell the PR Team
to come by tomorrow morning.
What for?
Do you not read the news?
The public is enraged.
They're sympathizing with
the former management and criticizing us.
Am I the only one who's worried
about the falling stock prices?
The anchor LPs are furious.
They're worried that
the exit point will be delayed
due to the plummeting stocks.
Rumor has it they want
to set up a co-GP investor.
We must find the secret fund
if we want them to shut up.
Did you dig into it?
Yes, it was confirmed that Jamal Ibrahim,
the bank president of LCC Investment Bank
in Labuan, Malaysia,
managed the account.
I think he withdrew the money
and wired it.
-How much?
-Almost 900 billion won.
Send someone to Labuan right now.
Find out the next route.
This restaurant is known
for their kal-guksu.
-Try to eat.
-I'm sorry.
I don't think I can.
You need to eat well at times like this.
Your family relies on you.
You need to stay strong
if you want your kids to do the same.
They don't look up to me for strength.
I'm not the pillar of our family.
In fact, it was my father all along.
That hurt me at times,
but I was honestly relieved too.
Pathetic, right?
I was relieved
that my kids didn't rely on me.
My daughter is dying,
and I told her to trust me.
But I doubt that meant anything to her.
You're wrong.
Our kids don't look at us that way.
My father passed away before his time.
But even to this day,
I think of him
when I need to make a tough decision.
"What would he have done?"
You are
a lighthouse to your kids
no matter who you are.
So eat well, stay strong,
hold your head up, and shine your light.
Here.
Let's eat.
Even the tastiest kal-guksu is bad
if it gets soggy.
"What did I just watch? Is this a drama?"
"She's still foolishly in love
with her ex-husband."
"I've never seen someone terminally ill
-so in love."
-Enough.
You've become the talk of the town
while you've been asleep.
Don't be silly. It's mortifying.
What do you mean?
You're going through dramatic changes.
You were ambitious
about joining the One Trillion Club.
Then your family went broke
and fled in a single day.
And now, you're Juliet.
Simply put,
people think I'm hopelessly in love
with my ex-husband and that I revealed
my illness just to save him.
-That's true.
-That's why I'm mortified.
There are other things to worry about.
Such as?
What's this?
I bought a formal dress.
I bought it at full price
at a department store.
-What does this signify?
-You tell me.
That I'm very excited
about your return.
But I should get a refund.
Don't bother.
They'll assign you to someone else.
You can wear it then.
-No thanks.
-Why not?
You know I'm shy around strangers.
Given my occupation,
I won't have many opportunities.
So come back. I'll be waiting.
I can't guarantee that.
But I'll do my best.
I thought that didn't matter.
You always said to just make it work.
So I'll say the same.
Come back before I pay
all the installments.
And when is that?
In six months.
-That's a bit--
-Just come back.
Fine, I will.
Why are you mad?
I'll…
give you a hug today
because you finally woke up.
Look at this.
I became a divorcée who's still in love
with her ex in a single day.
Is this funny to you?
Why would you let that bother you?
Look behind you.
They were pitying me, weren't they?
No one has ever looked at me
that way before.
It's a first.
This won't do.
Dote on me in front of them.
"In front of them"?
-How?
-First…
-Gaze at me lovingly.
-"Lovingly"?
Like this?
Well…
Not bad.
How long will you keep looking?
What?
What's your left arm doing?
Right.
Like this?
SUNGMIN UNIVERSITY MEDICAL CENTER
I was surprised you called.
I had something to say.
How are you feeling?
I'm doing better.
I'm leaving tomorrow.
Why so soon?
-There's not much they can do for me.
-Then come back home.
It'd be more convenient.
I didn't call to discuss that.
-I'm listening.
-I know you're in a pickle.
You're struggling to deal with the media.
The anchor LPs must be burdening you.
You wouldn't have
enough stocks to stop them
even if they wanted a new GP.
So you know.
It's all thanks to you.
So…
are you worried about me?
No. I don't feel bad about your situation.
Provoke me again,
and you'll lose something even bigger.
That's all.
Fine.
That may be why you called.
But my heart skipped a beat
when I got your call
even though I knew why you called.
You don't know
how long I've had these feelings
or when they first developed.
No, I don't.
And I don't need to.
Do you remember why
I cut ties with you in university?
I was grateful for your help
when I was struggling.
But you were the reason
why I was struggling
in the first place.
Maybe you should've liked me back
before I did those things.
I only did such things
because I couldn't get close to you
no matter how hard I tried.
That's how you treat others.
Look at you even now.
You pushed me into a ditch
so you could get me out of it.
So who could possibly like you?
Then what about Hyun-woo?
Does he deserve your love?
He was going to leave you.
Did your tumor mess with your memory?
Did you forget?
He's with me now.
He's with me
right now.
Must I explain more?
-Are you done talking?
-Mr. Baek.
Why are you still by her side?
Why must I tell you?
Did you develop feelings
after finding out she was dying?
Or are you hoping
she'll leave you something?
Just come to me.
I'll give you anything you want
if you leave her side.
You're really testing my patience,
so just go.
Hey.
I didn't want to tell you something
I haven't even told her yet.
But try all you want.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm going to stay by her side forever.
I'll be with her.
So don't hold your breath
and just get lost.
You're home.
The chairman is here.
Did you hear?
You look happy.
Of course not.
How can I when
the love of your life broke your heart?
What happened to your face?
-Are you hurt?
-It's none…
of your business.
I've always lived a hopeless life.
No pain is greater than another,
and I don't care if I get hurt.
So quit trying to act
like a typical mom.
You have a guest.
Why haven't you been picking up?
Do you feel no guilt
about what happened to me?
I told you not to call me,
so why are you here?
I dodged getting arrested,
but they haven't let me off the hook.
-Baek Hyun-woo won't sit still!
-So?
Will I be the only one going down
if the world finds out
about the double contract
and the land investment fraud?
Do you think you'll keep your position,
Chairman Yoon?
This is the amount of stocks
Eun-sung's LPs have.
I sounded him out today.
"Aren't your LPs furious?"
"Don't they want a new GP?"
And he agreed.
That means--
He still hasn't located
Chairman Hong's secret fund.
Were you aware
of the secret fund in Switzerland?
Three corporations
are founded in the Virgin Islands,
Moldova, and Singapore.
The secret fund in Switzerland
is moved to Singapore.
Then the Virgin Islands
make it look like
they lent money to Moldova,
and Singapore underwrites Moldova's debt.
Then Moldova announces
that they can't pay it back?
Correct.
Then the Virgin Islands
files a default suit,
and the court demands Singapore
to pay it back.
The court makes it possible
to move the secret fund legally.
Once everything is done,
these three corporations
shut down
and make it difficult to track the fund.
They continue to launder this way.
And finally, they send the money
to a bank in Labuan, Malaysia.
Incredible.
Does that mean the secret fund
is in Malaysia right now?
I don't think so because Eun-sung
sent someone to Labuan today.
So he doesn't know
the final destination either.
By the way,
how did you know this?
Many people are unhappy
about the current situation
but they can't express it.
Some of them have been working
for Queens for over 30 years.
Secretary Jang had been
Chairman Hong's secretary for years.
But he turned down a hefty salary
and resigned.
Secretary Jang.
How have you been?
They told you these things for us?
No, for the company they dedicated
their entire lives to.
They don't want to see
the company crumble anymore.
What about you?
Why are you doing this? For the company?
Yes, it's for the company.
Because I know how much you love
your company.
We have taken into consideration
each of our members' opinions.
You have violated
your duty of confidentiality
and leaked information--
-Who are you?
-Right.
We're here to defend our client,
Mr. Baek Hyun-woo.
Look. You have no right
to interfere in this internal audit.
According to Article 12, Paragraph 1,
Item 3 and Article 11, Paragraph 4
of the Administrative Procedure Act,
our client has the right to hire
an attorney to represent him.
Let's continue.
Due to these reasons,
we've decided to fire you--
Your reason for firing him
is that you received a tip-off
from a rival company's executive
who claimed that Mr. Baek leaked
VIP information to them.
And you confirmed that he got his hands
on it by using his company ID.
-Yes, and?
-When did you receive that tip-off?
On August 6th.
When did Mr. Baek extract the VIP list?
August 1st and 2nd.
-Two different occasions.
-How odd.
His intranet ID was deleted on July 28th.
Correct.
I returned my ID card,
company card, laptop,
and everything else that day.
Maybe it wasn't your ID.
You could've used someone else's.
Like whose?
Maybe one of his team members'.
That means a regular employee has access
to Queens Department Store's VIP list.
-Isn't that a problem?
-Correct.
There needs to be proof that
the certain information was restricted
for it to be considered classified.
If anyone could gain access
and download the material,
that just shows that the store
didn't keep the VIP list a secret.
The real problem is the embezzlement,
and he signed all the related documents.
We requested an authentication
to a document examiner who used to be
the former Chief of Document at the NFS
regarding those 27 signatures.
The sizes and the details
of the signatures
were proven to be exactly the same.
This is only possible
if his signature was duplicated.
We can't trust this result
since you requested it.
Then let's ask the prosecution
to appraise it.
For your information,
there's no fine for document forgery.
Only imprisonment
for a maximum of three years.
We hope
you'll make
a wise decision.
-It's me.
-Hello, sir.
Get rid
of Baek Hyun-woo.
He's a nuisance to both of us.
Boracay, was it?
I'll send you there
and pay you handsomely.
Chairman Yoon.
There was a hiccup last time
because I was a bit careless.
I'll take care of it properly this time.
The more attorneys, the better.
It's great that you have us.
Despite having different specialties,
we got together to help a friend.
We're like the Avengers.
I'm sorry, but I'm also here
because people kept asking
if you were
getting back together with your ex.
Are you?
That's none of your business.
You majored in commercial law.
He's right. You excelled at
the Bills of Exchange Act and Check Act.
That's the past.
I take all sorts of cases now.
Take a look at this
and track the money.
WSB SWITZERLAND BANK
Where did you get these?
Hello.
Take this.
-I'll throw this away on my way out.
-Thank you.
-Second basement level?
-Yes.
Secretary Na, hello.
Hello.
Have one.
Thank you.
Eun-sung is looking
for the chairman's secret fund
so he can buy more stocks.
A secret fund? How much?
Nine hundred billion.
I'm going
to find it first.
Ma'am, be careful of the UV rays.
Why do you keep coming?
Didn't you side with Beom-ja?
Sorry?
Gosh, you got the wrong idea.
That time,
I felt terrible because she begged me
to help her see her father just once.
I'm unusually soft at times.
Fine. Side with whomever you pity.
Gosh, Ms. Moh!
You know me.
I only side with money and power.
After all, you're the queen right now.
I don't need to be the CEO
or anything like that.
I'm just going to stick with you
like your maid.
Maid, my foot.
Let's see then.
Sure thing.
I, the amazing Grace,
will serve you amazingly.
Sir, do you remember this room?
They said being in a familiar environment
would help you recover,
so I brought you here.
It's not easy to be a caregiver.
Let me give you a massage later.
How about some frankincense oil?
Sure.
Thank you.
You can go and let him rest.
So?
Does that bring back memories?
Tell me. Where's my money?
Where's the secret fund that
you stashed away under my name?
Keep watching her no matter what.
Who knows what else she'll do to him?
I'm hanging up.
Goodness.
Gosh, he's showing so much skin
in broad daylight.
What is it?
"Check me out."
"I'm good-looking."
"I have a great body too."
Is that it?
Goodness.
What are you doing?
I…
Well…
I believe you were peeping.
No, I wasn't. I was just passing by
when I saw you there.
Do you want some?
-What is that?
-Mulberries.
As in…
-berries?
-Yes, you're right.
They're good for women.
-How much?
-They're not for sale.
They're free.
Why would you…
How original. I'll give you that.
What?
You're the first guy
to make a move using mulberries.
But let me be clear.
Accepting these
doesn't mean I'm accepting your love.
-What's your MBTI?
-What?
I think you're an ISTJ.
-I… What?
-You don't express emotions well.
You're a perfectionist with a good memory.
You look cold, but you're actually soft.
Both Robert De Niro
and Natalie Portman are this type.
What is he saying?
But why are you home?
Shouldn't you be working like the others?
I don't work
that much.
Why not?
Because life is too short.
I just work enough to be self-sufficient.
So what? He's a self-sufficient farmer?
Did he save these for me?
Jeez.
Natalie Portman?
Goodness!
That's a lot!
They're from Yeong-song.
He picked some mulberries.
He says he has more.
He picked way too many,
so he's been sharing them.
He's ridiculous.
He could just sell the extra.
He always puts aside
just enough for his family
and gives away the rest.
What'll we do with all this?
Someone once told me that
the wise eat meat when times are rough.
Yes, you're right.
Determination alone
can't strengthen your willpower.
Your health matters too.
-Wipe your hands.
-Okay.
Also, think about what you ate
on all your special occasions.
It was meat.
Right? Birthdays, graduations,
the day you got a new job…
And look.
We're celebrating her discharge
over some meat too.
We always had Chinese food on my birthday.
What's sweet and sour pork?
What about chili chicken?
-Let me grill it.
-You?
You only eat meat
that's served on your plate.
I'll be grilling
my family's meat from now on.
Put down your tongs.
-Let me.
-Yes, sir.
Hae-in, I remember
the doctor saying
that your WBC mattered the most.
He said you needed to reach
a certain level
to receive treatment in Germany.
That's correct.
My WBC needs to be
between 4,000
and 10,000 cells per microliter.
How high was it in Germany?
It was 1,500 cells/µL.
That's so low.
But it went up a lot recently.
It's about 3,000 now.
That's double the amount.
I'm proud of you.
Well… It's not that big of a deal.
-I still have over 1,000 to go.
-You're almost there.
Try harder.
Hey, this isn't like studying.
I can't just "try harder."
In that case,
what should you do? Get injections and?
I looked into it.
It's all about her stamina and immunity.
She needs to eat well
and take a lot of vitamins and proteins.
She needs good rest too.
Then she needs to eat a lot of meat
and beans.
I'm going to plan her diet.
-Beom-jun.
-Yes?
Flip them over.
Right.
No.
They're burned. What should I do?
We can just cut them off.
-Can you give me the scissors?
-No.
I'll do it.
So she needs meat and beans.
What else?
Bananas and nuts…
-This is good.
-Gosh.
This is tasty.
It's really good.
-Look.
-He's excited.
Goodness.
You need to flip this.
Look at this.
She needs a lot of protein.
She does.
Eat while you do it.
Wipe it off for her.
Come in.
This isn't working again.
Is it not?
You just need to press this part.
I'm not as good as you.
Should I buy a new one?
Why?
Because you struggle to use it.
Then you can do it for me.
Look how good you are.
I think
I'm getting better…
the more I dry your hair.
You're right.
You did a good job on the curls.
Now that you're better,
keep drying my hair for me.
Sure. That's not a problem.
What else?
Tell me what else
you want me to do, and I'll do it.
I'm happy
as long as you dry my hair
with the broken hair dryer.
So just this?
It's a big favor.
You'd have to be by my side every day.
I don't think
I should be greedy for now.
No, be greedy.
You can.
Don't try too hard to treat me well.
I didn't confess my love to you
so that you'd treat me better.
I was simply
expressing my feelings.
Same goes for me.
My heart wants it.
I want to do better
if I can.
That's how I feel.
Yesterday…
I couldn't recognize Soo-cheol's face
for a few seconds.
I couldn't remember
my doctor's name either.
I also lost my way to my hospital room
for a minute and just stood still.
When my doctor
first told me about my illness,
he mentioned memory loss,
sensory loss, and speech impediment.
But I didn't believe him.
I thought that only happened to others.
I thought I was different.
But it's happening in that exact order.
I can expect the next symptom,
and it's terrifying.
I don't want you
to be next to me when it happens.
What are you saying?
Let's be happy with where we are now.
And when my illness worsens,
I want you
to leave me.
That's my wish.
What? When did he leave the game?
Did something happen?
DEACTIVATED MEMBER
Damn it.
Room service.
Drink up.
Is it that bitter?
-Not as much as my life.
-Dear.
Master, please talk casually to me.
"Master"?
Please teach me how to box.
I couldn't land a single punch
on Eun-sung last time
and fell down humiliatingly.
I understand.
But if you suddenly start working out
out of rage,
-you'll injure your joints--
-Joints?
That's fine by me!
I'm going to go insane at this rate!
What if I need to protect
my family in the future, but I can't?
I'm dreading it.
Oh, dear.
Fine.
I'll teach you.
Thank you.
Sit down.
But since we're doing this in a haste,
I can only teach you one thing.
And what's that?
Landing a single punch
on someone powerful.
There are two core skills.
Soo-cheol.
Hit me.
Are you serious?
Am I that strong?
No, this is the first skill.
Exaggerate.
So that they'll feel arrogant and think,
"He's no match for me."
"I pretty much won."
"I'm surprisingly strong."
-I see.
-Okay, bring it on.
-Well done.
-That really hurt!
-I'm sorry.
-My nose!
Why must I learn this?
So they'll let down their guard.
You must wait
until they let down their guard
then land your critical punch.
But get beaten up until then?
That's the second skill.
Endurance.
You need stamina to take blows well.
Do you think I can do that?
Muhammad Ali, my mentor, said this.
"Impossible
is not a fact, it's an opinion."
I see.
You can do it, Soo-cheol.
Take some blows for now
and become a champion in life.
Did your mentor say that too?
No, this is me talking.
All right.
Let's give it a try.
Okay.
Goodness.
I didn't know you were relaxing
in such a beautiful
and clean environment.
Relaxing, my foot.
How dare you come here?
Mother, I invited her.
Really? Why?
There's something I haven't told you.
It's about Grandfather's secret fund.
Nine hundred billion?
And that money is in Malaysia?
No, I think it's here.
-In Korea?
-Yes, sir.
It was laundered in Hong Kong
before coming here.
That paper company
lent the money
to five investment companies in Korea
before shutting down.
That means the five companies
don't need to pay it back.
Does Father own those companies?
The ownership was transferred
before he collapsed
to Ms. Moh.
What did you say?
Are you saying that bitch took it all?
I don't think so.
She's still looking for it.
Tell me.
Where's my money?
Where's the secret fund that
you stashed away under my name?
Are you sure Grace is allowed
-to hear this?
-You can trust me.
I've defected.
Remember Lee Woong-pyung?
I've also flown my jet
to this land of freedom.
We'll see about that.
Let's take a look at your jet.
Tell us.
Someone I know in the real estate business
said something strange.
That Director Jin of Queens Gallery rented
a 5,000-pyeong warehouse
on the outskirts of Gyeonggi Province.
It's not like they're building a film set,
so why do they need such a huge one?
So you think the money is there.
You told me to bring you
all the mails sent
to the former chairman.
Good.
I could've come by myself.
You didn't have to swarm over here.
We can't trust you. It's like leaving
a kid to her own devices.
You were all exposed on the media.
-What if they recognize you?
-We disguised ourselves.
We'll take over from here, so you may go.
You're hurting my feelings.
This is an undercover mission.
Have you ever faked anything before? No.
My entire life has been fake,
so how could you leave me out of this?
Okay. Attention, please.
I'm a real estate agent,
and you're wholesale dealers
who need a huge warehouse.
I'll do the talking,
so don't say anything.
Let's go.
There's no place to stash all that money.
By the way,
what will they store?
-Golf clubs--
-Clothes--
He imports
golf equipment,
and she sells clothes in Dongdaemun.
He's from China.
He understands Korean
but can't speak it.
Sir. No coriander.
I don't speak Chinese.
Is the temperature and humidity in here
being regulated?
You noticed.
Our former customers
used to import artwork.
I know a bit about art.
Which artists?
They weren't famous.
They were rookies.
But they're very famous now.
Their works have jumped
20 to 30 times in price.
This place brings good energy.
-No cilantro in my dish, please.
-Yes.
He'd like to see the artwork.
Sure thing.
Your Majesty, what has become of my child?
The main door is open.
We're headed inside, so check the office.
Okay. I'll do that.
This is considered a business trip.
I'll pay you extra.
They really shouldn't catch me
doing this here.
This is the wrong way to store artwork.
Did you say these pieces
of artwork jumped in price?
Yes, that's what I heard.
I have a good eye for art,
but they don't look that great to me.
I think the money is in the artwork.
This is where he laundered it.
So he purchased the rookie artists' work
at a high price with the money?
Yes, by ten to twentyfold.
After wiring the money,
I think 90% or more of it
was given back to him via cash.
That's a substantial amount.
I wonder where all that money is.
DECRYPTING…
We need to leave.
We have no time.
Darn it.
There's too much data.
I'll ask my clients
and give you a call right away.
Goodbye.
OFFICE
PLEASE KNOCK
Is it broken?
You shouldn't get wet.
Wait here while I bring the car over.
Hae-in.
Hyun-woo, that was quick.
Why are you out here?
Get up.
I was a bit dizzy.
I'm hungry too.
Let's have something tasty
before we go home.
Sure.
Was I out for long?
No, not that long.
Hae-in.
Hang tight.
Why?
Are we being tailed again?
Don't worry. I can lose him.
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
Should we call the police?
-Wait.
-We should.
You were attacked
by three men last time too.
Hae-in!
Jeez.
Look at these comments.
This is because Eun-sung
spread false rumors about
how you were being investigated
for embezzling money prior to the divorce.
It's okay. Ignore them.
How can I possibly do that?
"Hong Hae-in's ex
must've married her for money."
"He's a scammer."
"This is why you should be wary
of handsome men."
How dare they curse at you?
Let's sue them all.
Forget it. Let's go.
Wait. Someone bad-mouthed Hae-in too.
"She already got a rebound
after the divorce. She must be easy."
They know nothing about her.
"Maybe she lied about dying."
This one crossed the line--
What's the ID?
Screenshot this.
Make a PDF file and sue them.
I won't settle or negotiate.
What's with your eyes? You're scaring me.
They will all pay for this.
QUEEN OF TEARS
I'm close to locating the secret fund.
That's it!
Snap out of it.
We have our own movie-like story.
How lovey-dovey.
Where is the statue?
Da-hye!
Scumbags!
I'd have to check.
I can't be sure of anything anymore.
It was me
who developed feelings for you first.
So he knows where the money is?
Is this real? Am I not dreaming?
Subtitle translation by Soo-ji Kim