Long live our emperor
Zhuge Yue
You call me dead
imprison me here
No worries about food and clothing, treat me like a distinguished guest
So much trouble
What exactly do you want?
The person who ordered you to be killed is Zhao Che
Aoyamain is just following orders
Zhao Che has coveted military power in the southwest for a long time
only you die
Only then can the Southwest Army be completely owned by him
General Meng
His Royal Highness was not like this back then.
Things are impermanent
Zhao Che today
He is no longer the Zhao Che he used to be
Today he
Only authority in eyes
He is aggressive
Determined to annex the Western Alliance
Zhuge Yue
what do you want
I hope General Meng
stand on my side
Zhuge Yue
My family has been loyal for generations
I will never conspire with you
General Meng
I never thought of rebellion
I just want to change this rotten world
The four gate valves have a solid foundation
Could it be that you killed one or two family heads?
can be shaken
This matter is very difficult and dangerous
Lord Zhuge
can i trust you
General Meng
if what you said
Loyal to Dayong
Is loyal to the Zhao family and the imperial power
Then I can't be trusted
But if you are loyal to the people of Dayong
Then I'll be with the general
They are in the same boat
what do you want to do
I want you to help me stop Zhao Che together
Completely change Dayong's world
General Chu
Our troops are already here
We are divided into four groups
Wait for Zhao Che's honor guard to arrive at the Faceless Temple
Let's start from southwest to northwest
Folk alleys in the four directions of southeast, northeast and
Go through the city
Surround the temple
Set off
In our Zhenhuang City, a new emperor has ascended the throne.
But outside Zhenhuang City, it is surrounded by enemies from all sides.
Lost the battle with Ximeng
Bian Tang's army also came
We are about to reach Baiquan Pass.
you do not know
I heard that after the new emperor worshiped the Faceless God today,
They will mobilize all the Rong troops to reinforce the army.
Quanrong
Didn't Dayong always regard Quanrong as his enemy?
How could it be
Zhuge Yue
His Majesty
Now let me answer your question that day
I'm not your person
I don’t want to be the loyal dog of Aoyamain either.
I turned against you and returned to Aoyama-in
All for the purpose of uprooting you for Dayong
A serious illness like your father's
Someone coming
Take down Zhuge Yue
Now the guard outside
They're all Aoyamain's spies.
From the day they entered Aoyama-in
risk one's life
It's just a dog in your eyes
do you think
They are at this time
Will you still be willing to take action for you?
Prince Jing will come to escort you soon
Southwest Army and the Forbidden Army of Zhenhuang City
They are all his men
Do you think Aoyamain’s spies can survive?
Prince Jing will not come
Because General Meng
Not dead
General Meng
Aren't you dead?
Disappointed the prince
General Ben
still alive
Everyone listens
Capture the rebels and rebels
promise
Zhuge Yue
You actually betrayed me
Zhao Che
It was you who betrayed yourself first
Zhuge Yue
We have surrounded this place
The coalition forces of Yanbei and Ximeng
The Dayong Defense Line has also been breached
Zhao Che
Defeat is decided
today
I'll just take a look inside this Faceless Temple
who is the winner
Zhuge Yue
Why
Xinger
I'm bleeding from the snow
and Huiyuan Dan
Already broken heart
You have the dream of freeing the slaves and ending the war
I want to spend my last life
Help you realize your wishes
Zhao Che is in the temple
People from Aoyamain
I've arranged for them to evacuate
a while
General Meng will come to help you
Just kill me, the sinner
Homecoming from all over the world
Peaceful times
will come
Xinger
don't be sad
Back then in Ximeng
I knew it
you won't follow me
because
You are Chu Qiao
you are destined
Not an ordinary woman
You will go one way
a more difficult road
And I
I can only send you here
If I don't die
Aoyama-in cannot be completely abolished
cannot be completely disintegrated
Zhuge
Disintegrate the four gate valves
Xinger
don't feel sorry for me
don't stop for me
keep moving forward
Miss Chu
Tell me before you leave
Dayong is already seriously ill
If the gate valve cannot be uprooted
establish new deal
No matter who is the emperor
This world will not be good
so
He pretended to be with Zhao Che
I just want to take the opportunity to remove the four gate valves
Drawing firepower from under the cauldron again
Eliminate Zhao Che's gang members
including today
He has already arranged everything
The young master has been ordering people from Qingshanyuan
Searching for you and King Yan
He also wanted to
Hurry up and save you before Zhao Che takes action.
Young Master said
Wait until everything is done
The whole Dayong will change the world
By then
No more brothers from Aoyamain are needed
Go work for your life
There will be no more common people
And slave life is like a piece of grass
This is him and you
common wish
He wants to take over this world with his own hands
Bring it to the girl
I don't believe it
He must be lying to us
Even espionage has a way to fake death
What's more, he
He must want everyone to think
The Zhuge clan has really fallen
The four gate valves are really gone
Yes or no
girl
The last thing I want to leave you is the Young Master.
Let the girl not blame him
I made such a decision without permission
As long as the girl believes that he hasn't left
He will be like before
Always stay behind the girl
Zhuge Yue
General Chu
General Xing
what happened
General Chu
Urgent news came from the border
Quarong people took advantage of the opportunity of marriage
Entered the gate of the northwest defense
One hundred thousand troops and horses originally lent to Zhao Che
Massacres are being carried out in Dayong territory
Once Quanrong entered Dayong,
Not only Dayong
Both Yanbei and Biantang will be in danger
Now we have nothing but to challenge
no other way
Chun'er
Li Yan
you are the world
The only person who treats me well
Thank you
Zhao Che
Are you here to laugh at me?
I am today
I came here to say goodbye to my old friend.
deceased
Chu Qiao
What old friend did you say in front of me?
Zhao Chuner opened the border
Attracted the entire army to enter the country
I have decided
Go out to fight
Chun'er
Zhao Che
i was born a slave
grew up in Dayong
these years
people i know
Zhao Song
Chun'er
Li Ce
Even Zhuge Yue
They have all left me one after another
And you
I met him in the past years in Dayong
the only one still alive
Initially
I became Dayong's imperial army instructor
under your command
I knew Zhao Che at that time
He is an upright and decisive person
A good general who loves his people like his own son
Dayong's soldiers are not cold-resistant
You will personally supervise the making of winter clothes
personally
Sent to border soldiers
I still remember
You want to reduce taxes for the people
Strive to argue with the powerful officials in the DPRK
I almost lost my military power
I remember
You are in a winter blizzard
Pick up the wounded personally
Even if my feet are sore from the cold, I don’t care at all
Zhao Che at that time
it's all of us
A general who everyone is willing to follow
I know
You don't want to be like this
If I hadn't forced you into a desperate situation
you will be a good person
Very good general
enough
Why do you have to say these heartbreaking words to me?
I have no other purpose
I just want to say goodbye to you at the end
Zhao Che
I'm going
Life or death is unknown
You are me except Yan Xun and He Xiao
The only person I contacted again
I just want to talk to you
Chu Qiao
give me a chance
what chance
Please let me go with you
I am willing to be the most ordinary soldier
I will rush to the front
Fighting swords, mountains and seas of fire without hesitation
I know I'm guilty
can never be repaid
But I just want to keep this land
for those who have been
Everyone I've ever let down
atonement
Chu Qiao
I, Zhao Che, am a general
Even if you die
He should die on the battlefield too
Zhuge Yue
Today the whole Ximeng Dayong
Both Yanbei and Biantang were dispatched
This fight is not about past grudges.
But to protect the common homeland
Fight against the Quanrong
behind me
You He Xiao
There is Zhao Che
There are thousands of soldiers
Go on an expedition
What to say
The foreign troops took advantage of the situation and entered
Send troops to China
I won’t play with you anymore
General Chu took the lead
United Western Alliance Yanbei
Bian Tang and Dayong soldiers and horses from all directions
Finally defeated the entire army
Zhuge Yue