Previously on Seducing Drake Palma
What did you say?
Make Drake Palma
your boyfriend!
So how exactly are
you planning to pull off
your- Mission Impossible:
Seducing Drake Palma?
Hi, Drake!
Psst! Psst!
What?
I’m just tying my shoelace.
Hi, Drake!
I like you, Drake.
Can you be my boyfriend?
Okay.
What the…
Seriously?!
That’s it?!
We’re done.
For all the girls who were hurt by Drake!
Drake Palma!
You’re my boyfriend now!
Three…
Two…
One…
We’re done!
Bye!
Me?
Drake, who is she?
Hey!
Why are you so happy today?
Nothing.
Why? Is it wrong
to be happy now?
Ooh, I smell juicy gossip.
So, what is it, bestie?
Spill it.
What is it?
Promise, it stays between us.
Promise.
Come on, tell me.
You’re being selfish now?
Caught you!
You’re annoying.
Liar. You’re still trying to fake it.
It’s not effective, girl!
It’s not working.
Try harder to convince me!
If you won’t tell me,
I’m going to hit you in the face with this.
Wait, okay.
Calm down, girl.
This is what happened.
I’m his girlfriend!
Girlfriend?
Oh, why does she
look so shocked?
Actually—
Yes! I’m really his girlfriend.
As in girlfriend!
As in one word, girlfriend.
We’re really a couple!
Right? Right, Drakey baby?
Oh no, what if he lets go of my hand
and pushes me away?
That can’t happen!
Wait, he didn’t push me?
He’s improving!
Really? What’s your name, dear?
Oh, I’m Alys.
Alys Zyril Perez,
soon to be Palma!
Nice to meet you!
This girl is so amusing.
Right, Katrina?
Wow, she’s really pretty!
Why don’t we all go inside?
Let’s have some snacks.
No, I really just came here to
tell you that I’m Drake’s girlfriend.
How long have you been together?
Five minutes?
But I promise, Drake’s
dad, we’re going to last.
Right, Drakey baby?
Really, Alys?
But don’t call me “Drake‘s Dad”.
It’s too long.
Then what should I call you?
Just call me “Uncle Steve.”
And she’s your Aunt Katrina, my fiancée.
Hello, Uncle Steve, Aunt Katrina.
Nice meeting you!
I’m heading out now!
Bye! Bye, Drakey baby!
That was nerve-wracking!
Drakey baby?
You’re gross!
Why do you care?
It rhymes!
- It’s cute!
- Whatever.
So, why are you so happy?
Why?
You’re so slow!
Because Drake is
my boyfriend now!
Wow, delusional!
True! So ambitious, huh?
As if Drake would go
for someone like her!
Whatever with
these bitter girls!
But for me, he’s
my boyfriend now.
He really is!
Keep dreaming!
He’s going to break up with you!
No way!
We’re legal.
Uncle Steve will get
mad if he dumps me!
Bestie...
You’re insanely shameless - it’s epic!
Whatever! What matters
is I finished my mission.
Keep dreaming.
He’s going to dump you later!
What if he doesn’t?
Then I’ll teach you
how to read time.
- Deal?
- Sure!
- You’re buying me lunch, too.
- Deal.
Bestie...
Bestie, there he is.
Oh no, please don’t
break up with me!
Not now.
I don’t have money to treat Aya.
Does he even sleep at home?
He just got here and already
has his face buried in the desk.
But the teacher doesn’t reprimand him.
So unfair!
But what’s even more unfair is
if you don’t teach me how
to read time and buy me lunch.
Because he didn’t
break up with me!
I love you, Drake Palma!
Thanks for the treat, bestie!
But take it easy with your sugar.
It’s low sugar, okay.
Hurry up and eat. I still need
to teach you how to read time.
Chill. We’ve got plenty of time.
It’s all your Drakey baby’s fault.
He’s so unpredictable.
I thought he never keeps a
girlfriend for long.
Why didn’t he break up
with you right away?
I lost my bet!
It’s frustrating.
Alys, look.
- Yuck, Aya!
- Shut up!
Look, Kei is following Drake!
Oh my gosh!
Kei’s really following Drake!
Why, though?
Come on, let’s follow them.
What if this is the time she’ll push
with her dark plan to be with Drake?
Oh no, that can’t happen!
I can’t watch Sheen cry again.
Come on, Aya!
Let’s go after them!
Let’s go.
Hey, Alys!
Wait up! Hey!
You’re so fast!
Drake, I think we’re
a perfect match.
Bestie, can you lip-read
what Kei’s saying?
I can’t understand.
No one deserves you
in this campus...
but me.
Wait, it’s hard to read.
I think she said,
“Come on, Drake! I like you!”
“Let’s be together!”
Oh no, Aya! We
have to do something!
You’re so overacting, bestie!
You're overacting
too—with the slap!
We’re not even sure
that’s what Kei said.
What do you think? We
look good together, right?
I can’t really read
Kei’s lips that well.
She speaks so dramatically!
You know what, I’ve got it.
Come on, let’s go over there.
- Ugh! What the heck!
- Oh no!
Sheen my…
What are you and Aya doing here?
- We were just checking something.
- Yeah, just checking.
Right?
Sheen, come on.
Let’s go to the classroom.
Gosh, why are his
tears welling up again?
So much for a man, Sheen.
You cry too much!
Here, a hanky.
Alys, it’s okay now.
Sorry, Aya, okay?
I just love Kei so much.
Sheen’s tears are
affecting me too much.
Let’s go, Sheen!
You stay here, Aya, okay?
- Hey, where are you going?
- Let’s go, Sheen!
I’m coming too!
Wait for me.
Hold on. Sheen, I got you!
What now, Sheen?
Are you my stalker now?
Excuse me, Kei.
Sheen’s here because I’m
introducing her to my boyfriend.
Drakey baby, this is
Sheen—my best friend!
Sorry?
You?
Drake’s girlfriend?
Keep dreaming.
Hey! I’m your girlfriend, right?
Ah...
You heard that?
He just said, “Ah…”
“Ah” means “yes!”
So, goodbye and good riddance!
Oh Sheen, you were
about to leave right?
Go ahead, tag along, Kei.
Maybe you’re still
bitter about Drakey baby!
Sheen’s right there too,
she’s bitter about you!
Whatever!
What are you looking at?
I’m yelling at
him, but honestly,
I’m scared!
His stare is intense, promise!
Tss.
Hey, Drake.
You’re only my boyfriend
in front of Sheen and Kei!
Just in front of them!
You think I like you?
Dream on!
Oh no!
What to do?
He looks mad about what I said.
Keep dreaming. You’re ugly.
Ugh, you’re so full of yourself!
Keep dreaming.
You’re ugly.
Daddy…
Mommy…
Someone hurt your princess.
He said I’m ugly.
Which part? I’m gorgeous!
I’m a Perez!
There’s no ugly Perez.
That Drake is so weird!
Hey, ugly!
You too!
Hey...sorry.
You’re not ugly.
What happened earlier? Tell me.
What happened?
I should be the one asking that.
You’re the one who disappeared!
Nature called, so I had to leave.
And you and Sheen
were talking so long.
I wonder what happened
with Sheen and Kei?
Did they get back together?
Oh no!
I’m jealous!
Ugh, I don’t want
to think about it!
So dramatic!
Bestie, come on, just tell me.
Promise I won’t tell anyone.
I won’t tell.
She’ll just laugh at me.
Promise, I won’t tell.
Never mind.
I’m too lazy to tell you.
Alys, come on!
We are not done yet,
Alys Zyril Perez!
When a household,
or any business,
have surplus cash,
or extra income,
it falls down into what we were
discussing and
studying last module two.
Do you guys remember that?
Oh my.
I can’t even read the
numbers on the clock properly.
I’m struggling!
These are the entities
that help move
that excess money!
It’s very important
for you to understand,
because this movement
gets the money where?
To where it’s needed,
and where is that?
Mr. Palma, why are you late?
Good thing he woke up.
You know what, just sit down.
What the heck?
When Drake doesn’t answer the teacher,
it’s totally fine?
Is it because he’s a transferee?
What if I transfer to a
different school, too?
Am I allowed to sleep and be late, as well?
Someday, I swear, I’m
reporting this to the principal.
Where’s the equality?
As I was saying,
we will be putting
your learnings to a test.
You know what the red box means?
Quiz day! Twenty items!
Good.
Okay.
Alright class, begin.
Oh my God! This is so hard!
I need to finish early
so I can go home!
Why do we even need to study
Business Finance?
I don’t need this!
All I need is basic arithmetic!
Well, he works fast!
It’s been less than ten minutes
since the test papers were handed.
Class...
If you’re like Mr. Palma,
we’d all be a lot happier.
You can be late.
You can sleep.
Just make sure your
exams are perfect.
You may leave.
He’s lucky.
Ugh, annoying!
Show off.
Fine, you're the genius!
Huh?
You may go.
You cheated, didn’t you?
- Let me just get my bag.
- You cheated.
I’ll wait for you outside, okay?
Annoying.
Miss Perez...
finished or not finished,
please pass your paper!
Whew, finally!
You’re probably the
last one to finish, Alys.
You’re really a record holder.
Well, sorry!
Who told you to wait for me?
Because I wanted to
ask what happened.
Look at you!
You’re the one who
didn’t want to spill the tea!
What happened after I left?
Alys!
Well, it’s better than
seeing him always crying.
Oh, my poor love life.
Stop going after Sheen!
He’s totally into Kei,
he won’t even notice you.
And he doesn’t
like losers like you!
What? I’m just
telling the truth!
That’s what real friends do.
They roast each other.
So what now? Come on, spill it.
Come on, do I really need to beg?
So, this is what happened.
Earlier in front of Kei,
I introduced Sheen
and Drake to each other.
I told them that Drake
is my boyfriend.
Kei didn’t even believe it at first.
But when Drake and I were left alone,
I told him clearly that
we’re only pretending to be a
couple in front of Sheen and Kei.
Then I told him I’m
not even into him.
- You know what he said to me?
- What?
He said I was
delusional and ugly!
Drake actually said that?
Wow! Drake has guts!
What’s so funny about that?!
He insulted your best friend!
The nerve to call me ugly?
Me? A Perez?
There’s no ugly in our family!
That Drake is so infuriating!
Sorry.
It’s just that Drake barely talks and
that’s what he chooses to say.
It’s kind of epic!
Exactly!
If that’s the only thing he’s gonna
say, he should’ve kept quiet.
- So annoying!
- Oh, calm down, bestie.
It’s just really epic.
Stop it, seriously, stop!
You’re ugly and delusional!
Alys!
Uncle Steve!
- Hi!
- What are you doing here?
I was just about to
have dinner with the family.
And I saw you.
So, I parked to say hi.
- Oh.
Drake’s in the car.
He doesn’t want to get out.
You know how that kid is.
I wonder what he and the beautiful
Aunt Katrina are talking about.
Oh, is that so, Uncle?
That’s okay, Drake’s
always been like that.
You should’ve
introduced me, bestie.
Oh, Uncle, by the way
this is Aya, my best friend.
Hello, nice to
meet you, Uncle Steve!
- Hi, Aya!
- Hello.
You’re more handsome
than Drake. Legit.
Thanks!
Want to join us for dinner?
Come with us.
- Oh, yes!
- Oh no, it’s okay!
Seriously, Aya!
You just heard
“food” and jumped in!
Yes! Let’s go, Uncle Steve!
We’ll go ahead. Come
on let’s go, quick!
That’s food!
Hop in. I’ll take you
home at eight, don’t worry.
- Okay, Uncle. No problem.
- Okay, Uncle.
You go first, bestie!
Quick, quick!
Go on!
Fine, I’m going! Wait!
- Hurry, scoot over!
- Wait!
There!
Why did I even come along?
Are we broke now that I have
to crash someone else’s dinner?
This is all Aya’s fault!
Look at Drake and Aunt Katrina
staring at each other. Hmmm.
Fishy?
Oh no, they’re both staring at each other.
Wow!
Honey, let’s eat!
Everything looks so good!
I’m eating some of
these for the first time!
Aya, what are you doing?
This is your first and last,
bestie, okay?
Look, you almost
finished everything!
You’re exaggerating,
I’ve barely eaten.
Good thing Uncle Steve is nice!
It’s okay. If it’s not
enough, we’ll order more.
- Oh—
- Really?
Uncle, it’s okay.
This is more than enough, thank you.
- Come on, Alys.
- Right, Aya? Right?
Botejyu is so good.
You really like food, huh?
We own several restaurant
franchises abroad.
- Wow!
- Wow! Really?
Maybe we can get a free
meal sometime, Uncle Steve?
Oh my god, Aya!
What? It’s free food!
By the way, I’m curious.
What happened to Drake’s mom?
Bestie!
Why are you asking
so many questions?
It’s embarrassing.
Why not? I’m just curious.
If you don’t mind.
It’s okay, no problem.
Drake’s okay with it,
so it’s fine by me.
Drake was around twelve or
thirteen when his mom died.
Then I met Katrina.
Now she’s about to
become part of our family.
Oh.
- Bestie.
- Oops, I dropped it, sorry.
Ouch!
Is there a problem?
No...nothing.
Everything’s delicious!
We’re really enjoying
the food. It’s super good.
Alys!
- Mom!
- Come here!
Hi, mom.
Where have you been?
Aya and I
just finished a project.
We needed to get it done.
Oh please! Maybe you
just have a new boyfriend?
Dad!
You just don’t want
to bring him here.
I don’t like him--
I mean, I’m not ready to
have a boyfriend right now.
You know, it would be a
distraction from my studies.
Alys, it’s okay to
have a boyfriend.
Think of it as an inspiration.
Don’t take it too
seriously, okay?
That’s right. Just have fun.
But don’t forget
your studies, alright?
Just chill.
Yes, mom. Just chill.
Oh, by the way, your brother
called earlier from the US.
He said he couldn’t reach you.
Seems like he’s
having fun over there.
I really miss that crazy guy.
That’s probably
why he’s been tex—
What?!
What is it, Alys?
Is something wrong?
Nothing.
I’m chill.
I’m just chill. Okay, bye!
What happened to your face?
Why are you even asking?
You were sending
random texts last night.
Because I saw it myself!
Oops.
- Bestie...
- It fell, sorry.
Ouch.
I’m really sleepy.
Sorry.
It was a juicy gossip.
You needed to know because
we’re partners in crime, right?
So, what now?
Come on, bestie!
Ouch, what’s your problem?
Aren’t you curious
why they were holding hands?
If I know, Aunt Katrina
is a cradle snatcher.
Gross.
I won’t call her Aunt Katrina.
Just Katrina because
she doesn’t deserve my respect.
So what if there’s something
between her and Drake?
Duh?
Wow, Alys, I didn’t
know you were like this.
After everything Uncle Steve
has shown you kindness,
you’ll let him be fooled,
even though you know
you can do something?
You’re making me
feel guilty, bestie.
Do you want me to be a spy?
Exactly, bestie! You got it!
Are you serious?
I’m just kidding.
You always want me to do
the weirdest things.
Bestie, do it for Uncle Steve.
Whatever!
All I want to do now is sleep.
So let me sleep!
I’m already stressing
about Sheen my loves,
now you want me to deal with
this Drake–Katrina thing, too?
But…
What if it’s true?
Poor Uncle Steve.
This is Aya’s fault.
Now my conscience
is eating away at me!
This weirdo here
can sleep like a log.
I wish I could sleep too—
if only I wasn’t
thinking about that weird
and shady something
with Aunt Katrina!
Seek the truth. Tell the truth.
Live the truth.
Aya!
For today, class,
you’ll work in pairs.
It’s up to you, class, what
you want to make.
As long as the ingredients are
available in the Home Eco room.
Alright?
- Yes, ma’am!
There!
Good thing we have an activity today!
This will keep me awake.
I really love this subject.
Avery Clyde Balasbas.
Danielle D. Marchan
with Xander King.
Mohaira Sanama
with Arvic Roy Manalo.
Aliyah Cassandra Dedel.
Herbert Harold Lacsi.
Duna Duncan, Gabriel Lago
and Gabriella Pineda
with Albert De Joya.
Lord, please.
Not in my favorite subject.
Perez, Alys Zyril...
Palma, Drake Sebastian.
What?!
Baking is my stress reliever.
I forgot all my problems—
my love for Sheen,
and the fishy relationship
between Drake and Aunt Katrina.
For now, I’ll bake first.
Let’s go, Alys Zyril Perez.
You can do it, aja!
Class, just to reiterate...
You’ll stay in pairs and
make identical products
using the ingredients available.
Consistency in appearance
and quality is very important.
I’ll be in the faculty room
if you need me, okay?
- Yes, ma’am!
- Move! Move! Move!
Yes, ma’am.
So...
Should I go up to him?
Of all people, why did I have
to be partnered with him?
If I approach him, I’d be tempted
to ask him about Aunt Katrina.
I was born a gossip!
No, forget it.
If he doesn’t want to help,
I’ll just report him to Ma’am.
- Alys!
- Yeah?
You’re taking forever.
I’ll go ahead, okay?
- Go ahead, bestie!
- Love you!
Bye! Take care!
- Aja!
Oh my God.
Tada!
This turned out so pretty.
A total masterpiece.
I’m bringing this home.
I’m so proud of myself.
Where’s that weirdo?
He’s probably asleep again.
Oh well, I don’t care.
What time is it?
I can’t read this!
I don’t know with myself.
It’s only four-thirty.
I can still shower.
Hi, mom!
I’ll bring you cake.
How are you?
Really?
Sure, that sounds good.
Take care, dear!
Oh.
I need to get this checked by
Ma’am first, then I can go home.
Who’s that?
No way.
Drake? Baking a cake?
What’s your problem?
Well, you’re doing the wrong thing.
Whatever.
Hey, why are you taking my cake?!
- Give it to me.
- Are you serious?!
This is mine!
I’m bringing it home!
This is mine.
Just make another one!
No way, this is mine!
- It’s mine now!
- No, it’s mine!
My cake!
Why did you leave me?!
Mmm. Mmm.
What am I supposed
to do with that?!
Stare at it!
Tss.
Hey, Drake Palma!
Don’t turn your back
on me while I’m talking!
You ruined my cake,
so help me replace it!
Tss.
Annoying.
Annoying your face!
You ruined my cake, so you’re
helping me make a new one!
Whether you like it
or you like it!
I already told mom
I was bringing her cake!
There. You're smart, right?
Mmm, you got this!
Fine, whatever!
Just copy what I’m doing.
Not like that—like this.
There you go.
What now?
You’ve got flour on your face.
So grumpy.
Oh my gosh...
Is there anyone
colder than this guy?
- Ouch!
- What now?
Oh, sorry.
I didn’t mean to.
Hey, Drake. Are you done?
Let me see!
So grumpy.
Help me clean up,
before we get this
checked by Ma’am.
We’ll lose points if
we don’t clean up.
I can’t believe he left me
to clean up.
You’re so annoying.
Seriously, so annoying!
So annoying!
Good thing you guys caught up!
Why did it take you so
long to bake your cake?!
This is your fault!
Why do your
cakes look different?
We didn’t do it in pairs.
Hey!
Drake Palma!
Good thing you’re still here!
You’re really something, aren’t you?
You’re the one who didn’t help,
you’re the one who ruined my cake,
you’re the one I taught how to bake,
you’re the one who didn't help
in cleaning up the kitchen,
Yet you're the one
who got a higher grade than me.
Because you told Ma’am
that we didn’t work in pairs?!
Where’s the justice in that?!
Are you done?
What are you smiling about?
Bye.
Who was he texting?
Oh gosh...
Being a gossip is hard work—
I’m becoming like Aya.
No.
This is not gossiping.
This is truth-finding.
Data gathering mode.
You know what Drake,
you’d be lucky if I
became your girlfriend.
There’s only one of me.
We’re the same in every way—
rich, smart, good-looking.
I’m not available.
Huh? I thought—
I like someone else.
On the next episode of
Seducing Drake Palma.
You’re burning up.
Drake.
You have a fever.
You’re not a pervert.
You’re just a concerned citizen.
Oh, pervert!
Bestie, let’s go home
Look at that.
Your tutor is Drake.
Unbelievable.
You’re destined to be together.
What do you want?
We have to go
somewhere, hurry!
I told Uncle Steve that
we’ll go to their house.
Huh?
By the way,
don’t you ever dare
seduce Drake during your tutorials,
okay?
Excuse me.
Why would I have
to seduce Drake Palma?
He’s already my boyfriend.
Boyfriend?
Do you think I’ll believe that?