Subtitle Provide by Kisskh.Asia Translator [ Admin Qari ]
Make them fall in love with us.
That’s when we kill them.
Cheers!
Bison!
We still have to see the northern lights together.
I quit.
If you don’t want to get in trouble,
go home and be with your little brother.
Untie me and I’ll help you look for your brother.
I know you work for the police.
Jump!
Once I find my brother,
I’m going to kill you and your friend.
Pull over here.
Why are we at a motel?
Did you get turned on while we were on the way or what?
Stop talking and hop off.
What?
I’m just curious so I know what to expect.
It’s not like I can just turn the switch on, you know?
I’m not sleeping with you.
This is where I told Bison to go.
Now get off.
I’ll wait here.
No.
You come with me.
Walk ahead of me, actually.
Get off.
He used to come here,
but I haven’t seen him in a while.
Oh, you were always here with him.
You were, last time, too.
I want to know if he was here recently.
No.
I don’t think so.
Did something happen?
Did he run away from home?
Yes, actually.
He’s my boyfriend’s brother.
He’s a troubled kid so he ran away.
Ran off with a dude.
We’re worried about him so we’re looking for him.
I see.
He didn’t come this way.
And don’t waste your time looking for him.
You ought to let these kids have fun all they want.
They’ll come back when they’re sick of each other.
We parents can only do so much to take care of them,
but their hearts are out of our control.
Well, what about you two?
Need a room?
Yes.
No.
Hey.
Come on.
I’ve been driving all this way.
Can’t we just take a rest for a night?
It’s not like we’ll find your brother soon.
Isn’t it better to just get our sleep and think?
We can’t waste time.
We need to go.
We need to go?
My arms are sore from driving.
I can’t possibly drive like this.
Come on.
Just stay for the night.
Don’t you feel sorry for your boyfriend?
He’s literally begging.
He’s not my boyfriend.
He’s not?
It’s alright.
Let me put you up in the suite.
I’ll even give you free condoms and lube.
The narc habits are hard to kick, huh?
Your house?
Yeah.
Got a problem with that?
No.
You’re one hell of a wimp for a snitch.
Were you actually weak or faking it?
I wasn’t faking.
I just really don’t like the ocean.
I need a better excuse than that.
People have their fears, you know?
You didn’t seem to fear anything when you decided to fool me.
Think I’m easy, huh?
You don’t know me, Kant.
Give me a chance to explain.
I have my reason.
What the hell is that?
The only reason is that you’re an asshole.
I’ll tell you everything.
But please give me a chance.
Your chance has run out.
The rest of your life
is to spend making up to me
for the way you made me feel.
And what did I make you feel?
Say it.
Say what you feel for me.
Give me a chance to explain myself.
And after that,
you can do whatever you want to me.
You’re in no position to negotiate.
The rest of your life belongs to me.
You’re going to die here.
Your wound still hurts?
Be careful.
Stay out of my business.
So we got out of one car to sleep in another?
Don’t you have any other room?
No, I don’t.
The place is fully booked.
I don’t know what’s in the air today,
but it seems everyone just wants to get laid tonight.
It’s alright.
I love the theme.
Fast.
Hard.
Furious.
Well, get comfy, then.
Here’s the complimentary gifts.
I’ll put them here.
Damn.
I’ve never been to a motel like this,
and I’ve never had sex in a car as well.
Kinda like a fantasy, don’t you think?
Doing it in a car
with a mechanic.
You like that?
What the hell?
I ain’t running away, you know?
I don’t trust you.
And if I need to take a piss?
Tell me and I’ll uncuff you.
What about these complimentary gifts?
Not gonna use them?
How about… chains and whips?
I’m all in.
Didn’t you say you’re tired?
I bet it’s because you run your mouth too much.
Shut up and go to sleep.
Before you kill me,
can you do me a favor?
Tell my dad I love him.
Tell him to take care of himself.
If the garage becomes too taxing on him,
tell him to quit it.
Tell him to spend his savings on traveling and fishing trips.
When I die,
I’ll probably see my mother.
She died when I was a kid.
And just tell Dad…
I’ll take care of her up there.
Are you crying?
Duh.
I know I talk all big,
but even I am afraid of death.
Stop being dramatic and just go to sleep.
I don’t want to hear your sob story.
What is this?
Don’t you know what a fishing net is?
Of course I do.
I’m asking what you want me to do with it.
I’m hardly asking you to tailor a suit out of it, am I?
Oh, come on.
It’s not unheard of.
I’ve seen it done before.
Don’t mess with me.
Catch some fish.
Hey.
I’m no fisherman.
And you know…
I can’t get in the water.
Then you’re going to starve to death.
I’m not here to feed you.
Okay.
I’ll try.
But can you at least let me call my brother?
I don’t want him to worry about me.
You ain’t in no place to make requests.
Know how generous I am to spare your brother.
Hey.
Don’t hurt him.
This is entirely on me.
My brother and my friend have nothing to do with this.
If you’re going to blame someone,
blame it on me.
Cool as hell.
Too late, though.
If you really loved your brother,
you shouldn’t have said yes to this job.
That’s exactly why I took it.
If I didn’t,
Captain was going to reopen my cases.
And if I went to jail,
Babe wouldn’t be able to live.
I’m all he has.
You don’t have to feel sorry for me.
But please think about Babe.
I don’t freaking care.
It’s a poor excuse.
You’re going to die here.
Don’t think you’ll ever see Babe again.
Maybe I’ll be generous, after all.
I might burn you to the ground and send the ashes to your brother.
Pick it up and catch some fish.
Do it!
Get in the water.
You’ll never catch anything in shallow water.
Can’t we just eat something else?
I really can’t do this.
Sure.
What would you like?
Kurobuta pork?
Wagyu beef?
Salmon?
Really?
I love salmon.
Sure.
I’ll send it as an offering.
You’ll be fed when you’re in hell.
How about that?
Keep going.
Hey.
There ain’t no fish around here.
Only trash and plastic bottles.
How irresponsible to throw these bottles into the ocean.
What if it killed Nemo?
This is no time to be environmentally conscious.
Catch some fish!
And pick up the trash.
Yeah, as if I’d catch anything.
What did you say?
This won’t be enough to feed anyone.
Of course it will.
It’s just the two of us.
Unless you expected me to catch a shark for a whole village?
Now light a fire.
Thought you had a stovetop?
No cooking gas.
You’re welcome to swim to the mainland to buy some.
Here.
They’re wet.
How should I even light a fire with this?
Do it.
If a caveman did it once, you can do it, too.
If Tom Hanks can make it out alive in that movie,
so can I.
Wilson.
The hell are you saying?
That’s your name.
In that Tom Hanks movie,
he’s got a volleyball for a friend called Wilson.
Your face is as round as a ball.
Never watched it.
It’s okay.
Wilson isn’t supposed to answer anyway.
He only listens.
Wilson.
You hungry?
I don’t know if we’ll get to eat today.
But don’t worry.
I’ll do my best.
It’s all my fault.
I’m sorry.
I’ll light a fire for us.
Root for me.
Smile.
Don’t get hangry now.
What, are you hurt?
Why didn’t you just give me this in the first place?
I just wanted to see you fooled for once.
You’re so mean, Wilson.
I forgot to tell you.
We don’t have rice.
And?
You want me to grow some?
Don’t get funny with me.
I’ll fetch some rice.
You cook it.
Okay.
For that cut on your hand.
It’s unhygienic when you cook.
I don’t want to taste your stupid blood.
Just admit you’re worried about me.
No need to hide it behind hygiene and stuff.
Does your wound still hurt?
You should take a rest.
Don’t worry about me.
Just focus on your task.
Did you change the bandage?
Do you need my help?
No.
Just do what you’re here to do.
I can take care of myself.
Hello, sir.
Is the young master home?
Young master?
Young master who?
Mr. Bison, of course.
I took you both here on a boat.
Oh.
He’s inside.
Can I leave this with you to pass to him?
I believe it should be enough for two people.
Oh, sure enough.
You save us.
Thank you.
Sir.
Can I ask you something?
Of course.
Have you been working here long?
Yes,
ever since his parents were still alive.
I used to work at the hotel they owned.
When they were murdered,
I had nowhere to go.
I remembered they had a house here,
so I asked him to take me in.
Luckily no one claimed this place.
Did you say the young master—
I mean, Bison’s parents—were murdered?
It was all over the news.
All because they refused to sell their lands.
Even now, they still haven’t caught the people who did it.
The young master always looks so sad
when he comes to visit.
And he only rarely visits.
I’m happy he’s here with a friend this time.
Maybe he won’t be so lonely.
I have to go.
Call me if you need anything.
I live in a cottage just over that hill.
Of course.
Thank you.
What the hell are you playing at?
I’m not doing anything.
Something’s wrong with your car.
Crap.
Oh, no.
I don’t think it can keep going.
The radiator’s broken.
Can’t you fix it?
What kind of a mechanic are you?
Give me some tools and I’ll do it.
I can’t otherwise.
It ain’t no magic fixing cars, you know?
I’m no Harry Potter.
No service.
And I don’t think there’s a garage around here.
I told you to use the main road.
You insisted we took a shortcut.
Because you could tip the police off if we ran into them.
What are you worrying about?
I told you I wouldn’t run.
What do I have to do for you to trust me?
I can no longer trust a single word that comes out of your mouth.
What do you want to do?
Wait until some car passes by?
Or what?
You push it.
What?
Are you insane?
Push it where?
Just push it until we find a house or something.
No way.
I can’t do it alone in this heat.
We haven’t had anything to eat.
What if I passed out?
I’ve never felt so weak before in my life.
It’s so hot today.
I’m so hungry.
I’m literally dying.
No way, not doing it.
Stop whining.
I can’t help you.
I’ve only got this one hand right now, haven’t I?
Fine.
Okay.
I’ll just die of exhaustion before I ever meet your bullet.
Shut up and push it.
Yeah.
It’s hot as hell.
Push harder.
I’m pushing.
We’ll never find a house at this rate.
We’ll never find a house in the first place, dude.
Go!
I can’t do it anymore.
I’m gonna take a rest.
Take it.
Thought you’d let me die of thirst.
Either a hitman like you still have his humanity,
or you’re in love with me.
You’re well prepared, huh?
To think you packed snacks and drinks.
I am always well prepared.
I have plans for everything.
If it wasn’t for you and your friend,
my brother and I
would have had our long-awaited break already.
Hey, what happened happened.
Let it go.
Shouldn’t you be looking forward to the future?
Focus on the future.
Let go of your grudge.
What good would a grudge do—
Eat.
That will shut you up.
Couldn’t you have been more gentle?
I’m getting paranoid, though.
We broke down in the middle of the woods.
This is just like the beginning of a horror film.
A murderer is gonna come after us in a minute.
The first to get murdered would be a yapper like you.
I honestly can’t keep pushing the car.
No.
You have to.
I can’t leave the car here.
Just lock it and leave it here.
Who’d steal it?
Not even a dog passes through this part.
We can come back for it later.
If my car was stolen,
not only would I kill you,
I’d take a car from your garage.
Take it.
Take them all.
You own my life.
Take my cars,
my body,
my heart.
Take everything.
You have your food,
but still made me find fish and make fire.
Now you have me tied up and starving, too?
I’m hungry.
Won’t you let me join you?
Hey.
I can’t eat when my hands are tied.
Well?
You wanna help me with that?
Pork, too, please.
You’ll have to wait until I’m done eating.
For my leftovers.
He made enough for me, too, you know?
Hey.
Please, untie me.
I’m dying over here.
I’m starving.
I’m thirsty.
You might as well just shoot me.
Let’s waste nobody’s time.
Thirsty, you said?
What do I have to do
for you to believe me I was forced into it by that captain?
I didn’t have a choice.
Everyone has a choice.
You chose to betray me.
What did he order you to do?
He wanted to know who’s behind your operation.
Did you tell him?
No.
I never found out.
I thought I was going to see the mission through
and wipe my criminal record for good.
But who’d have thought
that I’d fall for you?
I really do love you, Bison.
Everything that happened between us
was real.
I just never found the right moment to confess.
If you really did love me,
you wouldn’t have let me find out like this.
I’m sorry.
I really am ashamed.
You never trusted anyone.
I let you down.
Shut up.
You remember the trip we planned together?
I still want it to happen.
Shut up!
Let’s go to Iceland together.
I said shut up!
Penguin.
Hey.
There's a house.
The plot thickens.
Car breaks down.
Finds a random house.
Bet there’s a family of cannibals inside.
Good.
I’ll ask them to cook you.
I’m getting hungry.
Don’t say that.
It’s scary.
Should we get back on the road?
Stop being ridiculous.
There’s no murderer.
I’ll shoot them in the face if there’s one.
Hello.
Is anyone home?
Hey, it’s not too late to turn back.
Hello.
Excuse me.
We need help.
This is getting scary.
What are you doing?
Hey.
You’re trespassing.
I don’t care.
Hello.
Hey, is anybody home?
Excuse me.
Baby, no!
Jimmy.
Stop running!
What do you want?
Should we just call it quit?
Baby, calm down.
I didn’t mean to lie to you, Popcorn.
“Didn’t mean to”?
What did you mean to do then?
You made me a fool.
Die, you jerk.
Hold it. Calm down!
Let’s just talk it out, alright, sir?
Who are you?
How did you get into my house?
I…
Are you his other side bits?
- No!
- Of course not!
Die, you jerk!
Oh, a gun…
Baby. He has a gun.
Let go.
Baby!
Leave me!
Baby, I love you.
- Stop pulling!
- I love you!
- Let me go.
- We’re in love, baby!
Stop it.
If you’re done, go look for what you need.
Hurry up.
Sir, please, don’t hurt me.
(Watch on www.kisskh.la or www.kisskh.co to support Admin)
I don’t have anything valuable here.
The only thing I have that’s worth anything is my heart.
And even that is shattered into little pieces by this jerk!
Hey.
Pull yourself together.
Don’t provoke them.
Hey, we’re no thieves.
It was you who threatened to hurt us.
We just…
needed help.
Don’t you dare lie!
I know you’re his lovers!
Delivery guys and postmen and whatnot.
Don’t think I don’t know he’s into all that.
Jimmy, for real.
Is your brain between your crotch or something?
Hey.
They all meant nothing to me.
You and I are getting married.
Can you please just let this go?
You’re the only one I’m serious with.
“Serious with,” my bum.
You were never serious with me!
You made me fall for you and then betrayed me.
You lying bastard, you jerk.
Popcorn.
Give me another chance.
The likes of you don’t deserve second chances.
The likes of you who lead people on
deserve nothing but death!
You want him dead?
I’ll kill him.
Fadel!
Calm down.
Don’t kill them.
I was just being dramatic…
Of course I don’t really want him to die.
But he lied to you.
Well, we bicker all the time.
But I never want him to die.
Do it.
Kill me.
Just please let Popcorn go.
I know I’m a jerk.
Blame it all on me.
He has nothing to do with it.
I love him.
If you love him, why did you fool him?
I’m sorry.
I’ve been lying to you, yes.
But you’re the only one I truly love.
How could I believe you?
If you don’t believe me,
just let this gentleman shoot me dead.
No, no.
- I’ll die here in our house.
- Don’t say that.
- I’ll be with you forever, baby.
- No. No.
I know I ruined our wedding.
Before you kill me,
I’ll be glad to know we have each other.
Shoot me.
No, don’t.
I know I nitpick
and that I talk too much.
But I do it all because I love you.
I left everything behind to be with you,
which I’m not even sure if it will work out, by the way.
But…
Let’s try it.
Love is a risk, isn’t it?
Popcorn.
I know I’m a loser.
But I will try to be a better man,
not for me.
For you.
I know the future is scary,
but we will brave it together.
Do you take Popcorn as your husband,
to be true to him and only him?
Yes.
Of course, I do.
And I will do my best to be true to him.
Do you take—
I do.
And if he ain’t true for a moment,
will you do me the honor of shooting him?
Baby!
You may kiss the groom.
Slow down, you guys.
The client who ordered a hit on Ruerat
is currently very unhappy with our failed operation.
They said if they don’t get a refund,
they’ll take us down, too.
One miss, and they dare threaten us?
We can’t give them a refund.
The only solution is to take Ruerat out.
Have Fadel and Bison made any contact yet?
Not at all.
And we can’t reach them, either.
They’ve disappeared.
Where could they have gone?
It’s strange that they don’t contact us at all.
Maybe they’ve run away.
Maybe they’ve decided to wash their hands clean of this job.
They have been asking you to make this their last mission.
But since their operation fell through,
they could have just made a run for it.
Oh…
I heard they have boyfriends.
They do?
Both of them?
Yes.
I saw them.
I guess they really wanted to quit.
But they could have just told me.
There was no need to take off like that.
I’m quite sad that they chose to do this.
They abandoned their Mother, after all.
They’ve become negligent and self-centered.
I guess this was why they failed their last mission.
I think it could be.
Keen.
I might have to do something I don’t want to.
But those two must come back to take responsibility for their actions.
They’ll ruin us otherwise.
I can’t let everything I’ve built crumble to the ground.
If we just let them go,
they could come back and hurt us, dear.
Will you let me handle this, Mother?
Okay.
I give you my permission.
Whether you do it yourself,
or hire someone to do it,
the decision is yours.
Yes, Mother.
You’re my only hope now, Keen.
Bison.
Won’t you please untie me?
Just do it.
Just knock me out and leave.
I can’t do that.
Stupid.
But I don’t want to go.
If I wanted to,
I wouldn’t have let myself get to this point.
Can we talk?
Please?
What lies are you going to feed me now?
Think I can’t kill you, don’t you?
If you want to kill me,
just do it.
I deserve it.
It was my job to fool you.
But…
In the end, I only fooled myself.
I was really happy
to have spent time with you,
to have hanged out with you,
to have made plans together.
But that happiness was…
ridden with guilt.
I wasn’t fully myself
when I really wanted to be.
I wanted you to see the real me.
When you got stabbed,
just thinking you could die,
did you know…
the thought nearly killed me?
If I were to lose you
without letting you know my feelings,
it would have been the worst thing ever.
I love you, Bison.
I love you.
With all my being.
You’re not fooling me again…
You’re not fooling me again, are you?
No, I’m not.
Do you believe me now that I’m not lying?
Eat your fill, you guys.
We prepared the food for the guests at our wedding,
but someone had to go and ruin it.
Baby.
Thank you for being here.
Help us finish all this.
Popcorn made all this, you know?
I guarantee he’s an amazing cook.
He is?
My boyfriend is also good in the kitchen.
His burgers are to die for.
Here.
Eat something.
Say “ah…”
Good boy.
Excuse me, but…
Why did you guys live so far out of town?
Did you know you’re the only house around here?
Don’t be nosy.
I’m just curious.
It’s alright. We don’t mind.
We used to live in the city, like typical salarymen.
But I happened to fall in love.
We moved here because Jimmy loves nature.
So ’m no longer an uptown girl.
Now I’m just a regular farm girl.
There it is.
It took us a long time,
but we made it work.
Very romantic.
You left everything behind for him.
He did all that for you
and you still cheated on him?
It’s a human thing to be lost,
but at the end of the day, I’ve come home.
Only because you take him for granted.
Well…
No need to be mad on my behalf…
I forgave him.
Where are you guys heading to, anyway?
We’re heading south.
Kinda hoped it was going to be a romantic road trip date.
That’s cute.
You two look really good together.
How did you meet?
I was kinda dared into taking him out,
but then I actually fell for him.
Oh, you did, huh?
Such is love, isn’t it?
It can start from deceit,
but it zigzags its way
into something beautiful at the end.
It’s only normal, right?
You bicker,
you fight,
then you bone.
It’s all part of the process for any couple.
Since we already bickered today,
and we already fought…
I guess the only thing left to do is to bone.
Oh, baby.
This is our song, do you remember?
It was playing when we met at the company party.
Of course, I do.
We sang it on stage together and then we…
♪ It’s always been you and me ♪
♪ We love and live in harmony ♪
♪ People wonder if we’re always happy ♪
♪ Of course, that just can’t be ♪
♪ We do argue and disagree ♪
Cute couple, aren’t they?
Just like us.
♪ Just overlook what is trivial ♪
We’re not a couple.
Didn’t you hear the chorus?
“Just overlook what is trivial.”
No?
You think what you did to me was “trivial”?
Come.
Dance with us.
Do our wedding the honor.
Let’s dance.
Let’s go.
Get up.
No.
Hurry up.
It’s their wedding.
Don’t let them down.
Get up.
Come on.
♪ Just overlook what is trivial ♪
♪ Don’t let it sting ♪
♪ Just forgive what is trivial ♪
♪ Don’t let it cling ♪
♪ This is just how we love, you and me ♪
Congratulations.
I wish you both happiness.
♪ We’re understanding and sincere ♪
♪ With you and me ♪
♪ No matter how hard, we will persevere ♪
I know what I did wasn’t “trivial.”
But I’m ready to do anything
to make you forgive me.
♪ Just overlook what is trivial ♪
♪ Don’t let it sting ♪
♪ Just forgive what is trivial ♪
♪ Don’t let it cling ♪
Fadel!
They may not be serial killers,
but they nearly killed us.
You trust people too easily.
Got swayed by their love story.
I’m a hopeless romantic.
Can’t help it that love stories touch me.
What are you doing?
Doesn’t your arm hurt?
It’s annoying.
It’s in the way.
Let me help.
How did it get to this?
I was going to kill you here.
Now look at us.
I never thought
that someone like you could kill anyone.
Grudges…
will make you do something you never expect you could.
After I kill someone,
I have to go out there and do something to forget it.
Do something fun.
Play bowling.
As for Fadel,
cooking is his therapy.
Do you plan to live two lives like this forever?
It’s exhausting, you know?
I know because I’ve done it before.
What’d you say that for?
You can quit
and start over.
I don’t care what kind of past you’ve been through,
since mine is not much better.
But if I got a second chance in life,
then, you deserve it, too.
How could I quit?
If I did, I’d have to keep moving.
You okay with that?
You don’t plan to stay with Fadel at the restaurant?
I don’t know if he’d keep the joint.
If he does keep it,
I guess this is goodbye between us.
Hitmen like us,
we can’t have a home,
family,
or a lover.
You have me.
If I were to quit,
I have to move somewhere where no one knows me,
like here.
Kant.
Hmm?
If I quit one day,
will you move here with me?
Well…
Let me think.
Of course.
I’ll go anywhere as long as I’m with you.
What about Babe?
Once he graduates, he’s on his own.
I’ve lived my life for him long enough.
It’s time for a new goal.
I want to live for you now.
Move.
Let me get in, too.
Leave me alone.
Won’t you let me relax a little bit?
I’m sick of arguing with you.
I’m glad you didn’t kill them.
I told you.
I only kill bad people.
I don’t like the fact that he cheated,
but it was none of my business.
You’re pretty decent at your core, you know?
How come you’re a hitman?
Someone hires me.
That’s it.
No way.
I don’t think you’re the type to do it for the money.
Why not?
You don’t know anything about me.
I might not know who you were in the past,
but I know who you are now.
You said you only kill bad people.
How can you tell who is and who isn’t?
Experiences.
It’s not your job to judge that kind of thing, you know?
Why don’t you just quit?
If you keep going,
it will never be over.
I don’t need a lecture.
I’m not lecturing you.
I just think there’s no one out there
who wants the best for you more than I do.
I just need to stretch my legs.
You’re messing with me.
Just because I let you do this
doesn’t mean I won’t kill you, you know?
Go ahead.
Blow my head off whenever you want.
I’m a bad person
for making you fall for me,
head over heels,
and then betraying you.
I deserve to die.
Don’t be so full of yourself.
I never fell for you.
You might be good at cooking
and shooting,
but you’re not very good at lying at all.
Does your arm hurt?
Let me see.
What are you doing?
As long as I’m alive,
I’ll make you kiss me again.
How about my parents’ place on that island?
We can lay low there.
I think I know now
where Bison is.
Why don’t you let that grudge go?
It will only make this worse.
But he destroyed my family.
You sure those two are there?
Style, get down!
That’s Style.
Fadel!
Style!
What the hell?
You started all this!
If you really like Fadel,
you need to prove it to him.