Gai.
I-I've parked the car at the company.
Don't worry.
Be careful with it!
Gai, it was nothing.
J-Just a sound-activated light.
Okay.
Gai.
Alright, alright.
Call me if you need anything.
Alright, Gai.
Alright.
You must get it fixed
before tonight.
Bro.
Your bumper's completely broken.
I'll have to replace it with a new one.
Replace it then!
Anyway, before tonight,
you have to get it fixed.
Alright?
I'll go get the money for you right away.
Daddy.
[Born with Luck]
[Episode 17]
What are you doing!
Trying to hit me, huh?
What are you thinking?
Trying to escape?
My people are all over this place.
Don't even think about escaping!
Chao.
This God of Wealth statue
looks like ours.
You know what, it really does.
Where did
you two pop out from?
Shut up.
We're robbers.
Robbers?
The two of you?
You don't even know who I am, do you?
Shut up.
Now, can the two of us
rob you or not?
Can we or not?
Sorry.
I was just kidding.
Someone!
Is that Rong's voice?
Yeah. That's pretty loud.
There's no one else here.
Didn't we see all his men leave
when we came in?
Wait. You want money, right?
I've got money here.
This—
all yours.
Take it all.
Don't move.
Just this little?
I-I don't keep
cash at home.
Don't you usually brag
that your house is loaded with money?
Wh...
When did I ever say that?
You're asking me when?
Can I transfer it to you?
Do you think we're so stupid
as to take a bank transfer?
Then that's all the cash I have.
I hate people
who are full of hot air the most.
We only got this little bit in the end?
Don't!
There's money in that suitcase.
You can take all the money
in that suitcase.
Let me keep my phone, will you?
There are...
There are photos of
a deceased relative of mine on it.
Is it him?
Is this the money you talked about?
One million.
US dollars.
Let me keep some memories, okay?
You can take all the money.
But please,
let me keep my phone.
♪ Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny,
bunny, bunny ♪
You're a sentimental guy.
♪ Love you, love you, love you ♪
It's just a shabby phone anyway.
Here you are.
♪ Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny,
bunny, bunny ♪
Thank you.
♪ Love you ♪
That's not right.
You are lying to us.
No.
It's just a shabby phone.
Password.
Let me see the other photos.
I have no idea.
You don't know the password
to your own phone?
How can you not know?
Chao.
He saw my face.
I didn't.
This is not over.
Spare him. He's still useful.
Useful.
Do you have a business card?
[Zhou Rong, Chairman]
Mr. Zhou, if you call the police
after you wake up,
then this phone will...
I absolutely won't.
Never come back.
I won't.
Our main job today
is robbery.
As for business matters,
we can discuss them later.
We'll contact you when you wake up.
What do you mean "wake up"?
What do you want to do?
It hurts.
Chief Zhang, what should we do?
You go in with me.
The rest of you, wait here.
Yes.
W-Who are you looking for?
I'm the Deputy Chief
of Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau,
Zhang Yi'ang.
I want to see Zhou Rong.
Please wait here for a moment.
Stop there.
Stop right there!
I need to see Mr. Zhou about something.
She's a police officer.
Go check on Rong.
Put it down!
Police.
Officers,
she's a thief!
-I was trying to catch a thief.
-Enough.
She's also a police officer.
What were you trying to do
in broad daylight?
Does being police mean you can just
trespass into a private residence?
I should ask you what you want to do
in broad daylight instead, okay?
Chief.
Zhou Rong was robbed
by two masked men.
In the study.
Did you hear that?
He was rob...
There was a robbery.
This is a crime scene.
We're going to
conduct an investigation now.
No, no need to investigate.
No need to investigate.
Chief Zhang.
I was just having a drink
with 2 friends over there.
So,
there was no robbery.
Did you hear that?
There was no robbery.
Since there was no robbery,
then you're trespassing.
I'm acting in self-defense now!
Didn't you just say
I was a thief?
If the police are catching a thief,
how is that trespassing?
Chief, hurry to the study.
N-No need.
You're...
You're also
a guest I invited, right?
Chief Zhang.
Everyone here today
was invited by me.
Everything in my house is peaceful
and perfectly fine today.
Really.
Put the sticks down.
He really was robbed.
A whole suitcase of money.
Mr. Zhou,
tell us if you lost anything.
We will help you get it back.
I didn't.
You see, Chief Zhang,
with you in charge of Sanjiangkou,
who would dare to commit a robbery?
Who would dare to rob
a suitcase of money from someone's study
in broad daylight, right?
Besides,
how could there be
a suitcase of money in a study, right?
Also, look around—
it's like a fortress here.
So, no losses?
Really none?
Did you lose anything?
Did you or not?
No, no. I didn't.
Did you lose anything?
No.
How did they get in?
Mr. Zhou.
The police entering
doesn't count as trespassing.
They wanted to see you.
I called you but you didn't answer,
so I brought them in.
Rong...
Shut up!
I was in there yelling for someone
for ages!
How come nobody came?
Is my house somewhere
anyone can just walk into?
Is this how you guard the house?
Aren't you dizzy?
Yes.
I am.
Then fall down already!
Aren't you dizzy? Aren't you?
Aren't you?
Chief,
I really didn't go undercover on my own
without permission.
No one's blaming you.
Tell us what happened.
Mr. Zhou.
Please.
I tried to escape,
but there were people outside.
I heard Zhu Yifei
and Zhou Rong trading the bianzhong.
Keep your eyes on the road.
Trading the bianzhong?
And then?
Then I sneaked out, trying to escape,
but bumped into Zhou Rong
as soon as I got out.
So I had to follow him to the study.
Then two armed men in maid outfits
with their faces covered showed up.
In women's clothes?
-Female...
-Male...
-Male.
They knocked me out,
took Zhou Rong's 1 million US dollars,
as well as a phone that was
very important to him.
The wallpaper
was a photo of Lang Bowen.
Then they ran away.
Then I woke up.
And then, you arrived.
You already saw it,
so how could you let them
take the phone away?
I was a bit dizzy then.
B-Being dizzy is no excuse.
That phone is definitely
a very important clue.
Look at you. You...
They were
2 armed fugitives.
You can't expect her to confront them
empty-handed and risk her life, right?
It's important to protect yourself.
You didn't do anything wrong.
R-Rong.
Why are you back so late?
I took our men
and chased them all the way,
almost out of the city,
but we didn't see Zhu Yifei
and the others.
Then halfway through,
I got a call saying
something had happened at home,
so I rushed back immediately.
Where's my medicine?
Give me my medicine first.
Rong, you can't keep taking this medicine.
It's not good for your health.
I'm already not doing well!
Rong, it's okay.
I'm back.
It's okay.
Sit!
Jianren.
My head's already
a mess right now.
Help me figure this out.
Today, Zhu Yifei
was supposed to come for a deal.
Halfway through the transaction,
he took a phone call and left.
He didn't even take the money.
He left me a phone
that belonged to Lang Bowen.
Then out of nowhere,
a policewoman
showed up.
After that
came 2 perverts
dressed as women.
The moment they walked in, they started
grabbing the phone and beating me up.
In my own house, for god's sake,
they kicked me in the ass
and gave me 3 judo chops.
And in the end,
Zhang Yi'ang showed up too.
Tell me—
who's actually trying to
screw me over here?
Zhu Yifei,
those two perverts,
or Zhang Yi'ang?
Maybe...
Speak Chinese!
They're all possible!
Call Lang Bowen.
Why call him at a time like this?
He caused the trouble,
so have him clean up his own mess.
Okay.
Rong,
you must be joking.
Do I sound like
I'm joking?
So it really happened, Rong?
How could it be?
What do you want me to do then?
Figure it out yourself.
Rong?
[Fang Yong]
Sorry,
the user you dialed is busy.
Please try again later.
Sorry,
the user you dialed is busy.
Please try again later.
What's going on?
You guys...
Gathering together, huh?
Letting Liu Bei ran away just like that!
With so many of you there!
Trying to hide, huh?
You didn't even notice a thing.
You didn't even notice a thing!
There are 9 bianzhong in total,
and we already have 8.
We're only missing a small one, right?
So I think the loss
is still under control!
"The loss is under control."
The loss is under control?
Those 9 are a set.
You lost one,
so it's no longer a set.
Who do you expect me to sell it to?
A pair of shoes is worth 10,000 yuan,
and you lost one of them.
Who do you expect me to sell
the other one to?
Alright, I heard everything.
Why do this?
They are all honest kids.
We're a family.
We're a team,
not a gang!
Who did you hit?
For talking back.
Get up.
Go take a rest.
G-Get lost!
Uncle.
[Pinghe] [Liu Bei's location]
Do you think Liu Bei
will ask for an exorbitant price?
Liu Bei broke the rules of our trade.
He must be taken care of.
Zheng, oh Zheng.
They all say
the underworld is dangerous,
but it's also addictive
because it's so charming.
Let me tell you—
every suitcase
has a hidden compartment.
I put a small tracker
in every hidden compartment,
just in case.
When I checked the phone,
the tracker was moving.
What does that tell us?
Liu Bei can't get away.
Where are you going?
Trying to kill him in broad daylight?
Wait,
are we not killing him?
Of course we'll kill him,
and it will be bloody.
Let's chop him into pieces.
You bring him here,
and I'll do the chopping.
Okey-dokey.
[Police]
What are you doing?
My neck hurts.
Go to the hospital if it hurts.
Go do your work.
[Baoku Fresh Produce Delivery Center]
Come on, let's have a meeting.
Guys,
let's have a quick meeting.
First, let's talk about Li Qian.
Chief Qi,
I really wasn't going undercover.
Did anyone ask you?
We just checked
the surveillance footage
outside the bun shop on Qingchun Street.
It proves that Ms. Li Qian
was indeed forced into the car.
This is already very clear.
But Chief Qi,
this doesn't prove
that she didn't act on her own.
From the time you got into his car
to the time you entered Zhou Rong's house,
so much time passed.
Why didn't you contact the bureau?
I wanted to,
but my phone got smashed the moment
I got in the car.
Captain Wang, you forgot.
I tried to call her,
but you didn't let me.
Song Xing!
You see,
I just called Li Qian,
but she suddenly hung up on me.
I wanted to ask what was going on,
but now I can't get through to her.
Is this really the time to be doing that?
Let's put this matter aside for now.
Let it slide, alright?
Let's talk about the case instead.
According to the report
from our colleagues
staking out Zhou Rong's villa,
after we left,
the security team from Zhou Rong's company
and Hu Jianren rushed over.
This shows that the intelligence
provided by Li Qian
was correct,
that Zhou Rong had indeed been robbed.
Li Qian, tell everyone
the basic characteristics of
those 2 robbers.
Both robbers were
about 1.8 meters tall.
One was more heavily built,
the other thinner.
They were both wearing maid outfits
and had their faces covered.
They actually dared to break into
Zhou Rong's house and rob him.
I'm afraid they're no ordinary people.
Chief Zhang.
Could they be those 2 people
who killed Lin Kai?
[September 3, 2012]
Judging from their builds
and gaits,
they did look like them.
Captain Wang, what are your thoughts?
Tell us what you think.
If we try to cover everything at once,
we definitely won't have enough manpower.
We need to keep monitoring Zhou Rong
and keep searching for
Liu Bei and Zhu Yifei.
But I think the main focus
should be on those 2 robbers.
Because the phone is in their hands,
after all.
That phone is definitely
the key to cracking this case.
I disagree.
I think the key should be Liu Bei.
Li Qian.
Regarding the matter
of you going undercover,
I...
It was my mistake.
I... I apologize to you.
But don't bring your emotions
into work,
alright?
I didn't, Captain Wang.
I really think
the focus should be Liu Bei.
Then why is it not Lang Bowen?
Keep quiet.
But
why
can't it be Lang Bowen?
It should be Liu Bei.
The robbers.
Question:
suppose a student
transfers from Class A
to Class B.
Is it possible
that because of his transfer,
the average IQ of
both classes
increases?
For Class A,
it's possible.
If that student's IQ
is lower than Class A's average
but higher than Class B's average,
then after he transfers,
the average IQ of both classes
will increase.
Correct.
So the key is
the one with the highest IQ?
Wrong.
It's the one who poses the greatest threat
to society among those people.
Wrong.
Wait, what does this have
to do with the case?
Nothing at all.
I just said that
to break
the tension just now
and let everyone relax a bit.
Because arguing won't
lead to any results.
But we really should
investigate Lang Bowen.
Why?
The phone is in the robbers' hands now.
Why not follow
Captain Wang's idea to find the robbers?
Because those two
had their faces covered.
And ever since Lin Kai's incident,
we've been looking for them,
but we haven't found them so far.
Without new clues,
how do we find them?
Good question.
Captain Wang,
have you considered this question?
What's the point of
investigating Lang Bowen?
Right now, we only know
the wallpaper on that phone
was Lang Bowen,
so we're assuming the phone is his.
If you go to him,
will he just tell you everything
and confess?
See,
that's your loophole.
Why look for Liu Bei?
Zhou Rong and Zhu Yifei
didn't complete the deal.
I presume it was because of Liu Bei.
Could it be
that Liu Bei took the bianzhong away?
If that was really the case,
then neither Zhou Rong nor Zhu Yifei
would let him off.
His life might be in danger.
We have to find him as soon as possible.
Also, we've obtained Liu Bei's
physical description,
so it should be relatively easy
to find him.
Chief Qi.
That's also what I'm thinking.
Water.
Uncle,
when does it get dark?
What's the rush?
Same time as yesterday.
You really are to blame for this.
I told you back then that...
Well,
I also made a huge mistake.
Zheng,
I know you're a good kid.
You're just a bit careless
when you handle things.
You need to pay attention to details.
Don't worry. I
will definitely get the bianzhong
back for you.
I promise I won't let you down this time.
Also,
when you handle things,
don't rush them.
Make sure you're doing it right first,
then worry about speed.
Right, one more thing.
Every time you come back
from killing someone,
you're covered in blood.
It looks terrible.
Clothes don't come for free.
Even if you're rich,
you shouldn't waste it like this.
Understood, Uncle.
Details.
Alright.
Go check if the meat is perfectly stewed.
Get ready to eat.
[Fenglinwan]
You're here.
Mine?
All yours, bro.
Yeah, yours.
Go on and drink it.
Cheers.
Yibo,
you should go in and talk to him.
He'll drink himself to death
if he goes on like this.
Why bother?
Bowen is rarely this happy.
Let him drink as much as he wants.
We've got plenty.
♪ Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny,
bunny, bunny ♪
♪ Love you, love you, love you ♪
♪ Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny,
bunny, bunny ♪
♪ Love you, love you, love you ♪
♪ Oh Gimme ♪
♪ Dance me in the richness ♪
♪ Raining make it rain ♪
♪ Oh cash is my revolution ♪
♪ Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny,
bunny, bunny ♪
♪ Love you, love you, love you ♪
♪ Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny,
bunny, bunny ♪
[No SIM card] [No service]
Every time I look at this bastard,
I get furious.
What's the rush?
A real man should stay calm
even when Mount Tai collapses before him,
and remain unshaken even when
a fierce tiger is behind him.
Let's give him a chance to try.
[No SIM card] [No service]
[You've entered the password incorrectly
5 times.]
[Please try again in 30 seconds.]
Stop trying.
So it locks for 10 minutes
if I get it wrong, what's the big deal?
But I heard
if you enter the wrong password
10 times in a row,
all the data inside will be wiped.
[No SIM card] [No service]
If this bastard isn't dead,
I'll definitely kill him.
Chao,
what should we do next?
Tomorrow morning,
we'll leave Sanjiangkou.
I'll take you somewhere else
to enjoy life.
Wait,
so we're giving up on this deal?
A man who's never content is like
a snake trying to swallow an elephant—
that's exactly you.
Sanjiangkou is Zhou Rong's territory.
He's rich and powerful here.
Even if he's willing to pay a ransom,
would we really dare to take it?
Let's leave Sanjiangkou first.
We can deal with the phone later.
Money can never be earned out completely.
Life is more important—
a lot more.
Makes sense.
Then if we leave tomorrow,
what are we doing today?
Tonight, I'll take you out
to enjoy ourselves.
Chao,
this place must be expensive, right?
Can't we afford it?
Besides,
don't we have this?
[Spa Card]
[Fenglinwan VIP Exclusive]
We've been like frogs at the bottom
of a well for so many days.
Tonight, I'll take you to enjoy
something luxurious.
Chao, is there something wrong
with this guy?
This way, please.
Am I right?
Right.
Then let's play dice.
Bro, come on.
Come on.
I've called 15.
-15.
-20.
15!
-10.
-15.
-10. 15.
-Come on.
-15. 10.
-5.
Drink.
You gotta drink this.
-Come on, drink it.
-Drink it for me.
Let me say something!
Stop drinking, you brats.
Go home and find your own mothers.
Who the hell are you?
I'm your daddy,
number one of Sanjiangkou.
Bro. Bro.
This is just a misunderstanding.
L-Let me grandly
introduce him to you all.
This is Mr. Lang,
Mr. Zhou's friend, one of our own.
He drank too much.
Here, I'll drink this on his behalf.
Mr. Zhou's friend?
Pardon my disrespect.
Mr. Lang, why not
sit down and have a drink with us?
Why should I?
Call me daddy!
Daddy.
You're my daddy, alright?
You guys keep drinking.
Let's go home, alright?
Stop drinking, you brats!
Alright, alright. Enough.
Stop drinking!
Go home to your mom!
Right, right.
Easy, please.
Drink less.
Yes, sir.
This is our VIP card.
Can I get a discount with this card?
How much of a discount?
With this card, everything's on the house,
sir.
So everything's free?
Yes, sir.
No matter how much I spend?
Then I won't hold back.
Bring me 2 dozen bottles of Snow Beer!
Chao.
There are photos of
a deceased relative of mine on it.
Chao.
You wanna die?
No,
this person isn't dead. He's still alive.
Zhou Rong's deceased relative.
This phone is yours?
What's the password?
One five?
Two fives?
Three fives?
Pat me.
Give me a pat.
Thanks, brat.
Chao,
should we beat him up?
Don't cause trouble.
Just get the phone password.
What's the password to your phone?
Call me daddy,
and I'll tell you.
Daddy, what's the password to your phone?
Beat him up.
♪ He ♪
♪ A rusted flower etched
across his chest ♪
♪ Oh, he ♪
♪ Says your worldview's still too small ♪
♪ A rat that steals rice—
humans call it cunning ♪
♪ A human who steals honey—
calls the bees hardworking ♪
Lang Bowen was beaten up?
Lu Yibo said they hit pretty hard.
Who did it?
Did anyone see their faces clearly?
Two experts.
Very professional.
Could it have been Zhu Yifei who did it?
Besides Huo Zheng,
does he have any other experts under him?
Hard to say.
Could it have been
the 2 guys who robbed you?
Zhu Yifei
sneaked in driving a truck.
It wouldn't be impossible for him
to have brought two people in with him.
Go to the company
and get the gun back.
What about Lang Bowen?
Just have Lu Yibo handle it.
Delete the surveillance footage.
If the police ask,
just say he got drunk
and caused trouble himself.
Okay, I'll go teach him.
Hurry up.
Don't rush me, bro.
I'm almost done.
Okay, done, bro.
How is it, bro?
I did a pretty good job, didn't I?
You really did.
Great job.
Bro, where are you going
in such a hurry?
I must drive the car
back today.
But...
I just
called you daddy, didn't I?
Blood is thicker than water, isn't it?
It is.
Can a son possibly owe his dad money?
Of course not.
There you go.
I'll pay you in a few days!
[Rongcheng]
Hello?
Liu.
I think I forgot to turn off
the space heater in my room.
Can you go check for me?
So it doesn't catch fire.
Look at the weather.
[Gatehouse]
Why are you still using a space heater?
I was drying my insoles this afternoon.
[Gatehouse]
Alright then.
[Rongcheng]
Where's the guard on duty at the gate?
No idea.
You stay here and keep watch.
43 million
divided by 9.
Ones, tens, hundreds,
thousands, 10 thousands,
hundred thousands, millions, 10 millions.
47 million.
Rongcheng Group.
Group.
Rongcheng World.
[Contact Information]
Hello.
I want to talk to Zhou Rong.
I sounded too kind.
Have Zhou Rong answer the phone!
R...
Rong.
I've got the stuff.
352866.