How did you get so badly hurt?
On a night like this
why would your family
send a young lady like you
out here all alone?
My mother is ill.
My father
is tied up at the yamen.
He can't get away.
Leaving the search to the servants—
for one thing
I worry they might not
recognize Rong.
And also I'm worried
that if anything changes
I can make a decision right away.
Your wound has been cleaned.
Now
I'll apply the medicine.
Alright.
Rong, are you alright?
Thank goodness you're back!
You're safe now.
Miss Gu was worried sick.
We were all so worried.
We were frantic.
That was so dangerous, don't you think?
How is he?
You're fine? No one's hurt, right?
How is everything?
You've been through a lot.
I'm fine.
Rong.
Jinzhao.
Keep sending people to search.
Jinzhao
I...
How did you end up like this?
What are you doing here?
Lord Chen's guards
found me.
He sent them out
last night.
And they actually tracked Rong down
in a village miles away.
Lord Chen's men are truly capable.
We searched for ages
and got nowhere.
What matters is you're back.
I've troubled you again.
No need for such formalities with me.
If you ever find yourself in trouble again
you can always come to me.
Lord.
My Lord.
Wake up, Ye Xian.
Ye Xian.
Move away.
Lord, please wake up.
Where am I?
You drank too much last night
and slept here at the tavern again.
Lord, you must get up.
We need to head back to the Marquis's at once.
I'm not going back.
My Lord,
I understand
you're like this because of Miss Gu.
How many times have I told you
don't mention her to me.
This is the last time, I swear.
Mrs. Gu is gravely ill.
They even posted notices yesterday
seeking renowned physicians.
Why are you telling me this?
It's not like I have a renowned physician.
Unless my master were here.
But he's far away in the southwest.
That's exactly what I was about to say.
Mr. Xiao has returned.
What?
When did he get back?
Just last night.
Lord.
Master.
Greetings, Young Lord.
Thank you, Young Lord
for being willing to lend a hand.
I am beyond grateful.
Of course—
My Grace always repays malice with kindness.
This is
the Divine Healer Xiao I told you about.
He's also my master.
It's an honor to meet you, Healer Xiao.
Miss Gu.
Right this way, please.
This is the prescription
from the previous physician.
This prescription is fine.
How long has she been taking it?
About a month or so.
By all accounts
there should have been some improvement.
Why hasn't she shown any sign of recovery?
May I see the medicinal herbs?
Of course.
Nanny Zhao.
That explains it.
Master.
This is...
Rhubarb.
This prescription
doesn't call for rhubarb.
Here lies the source of the ailment.
Rhubarb is cold in nature.
It's used to purge fire and cool the blood
expel toxins and clear stasis.
However, rhubarb is fiercely potent.
Mrs. Gu is already frail
with a weak and cold spleen and stomach.
The medicine she needs
works in the opposite direction of rhubarb.
If taken over a long period
I fear it could be fatal.
If the prescription is sound,
the herbs must have been tampered with.
It seems
someone has been adding rhubarb
to the prescription.
Mrs. Gu's medicine—
who usually picks it up?
Miss Gu,
we always send someone from the General Services
to take the prescription to the pharmacy.
When it comes back, they hand it to me
or Molan.
As for brewing it
Molan and I
take turns watching over it.
About this matter—
not a single word is to leave this room.
Yes,  Miss Gu.
If Lord Gu
or Rong should ask
just say we consulted a new physician
and he found nothing unusual either.
Understood?
Understood.
Divine Healer Xiao.
Given how things stand
please speak plainly with me.
My mother—
can she still be cured?
Recovery is not difficult.
But the root lies in excessive worry and rumination
which have turned into an ailment.
If she cannot open up her heart
even a temporary recovery
would be like water without a source
a tree without roots.
Gu Jinzhao.
What's on your mind?
Will you investigate?
Of course I will.
And I'll get to the bottom of it.
I knew you'd say that.
So—
do you have the people for it?
If not
I can lend you Li Xianhuai.
Not just yet.
This time I definitely won't do anything rash.
So don't overthink it.
I have to find the culprit first
and then I'll trouble you for help.
You've got it all figured out.
Fine then.
I'm off.
Ye Xian.
Thank you.
Miss Gu, honestly—
Since you've run into him anyway
why are you hiding over here?
Even just greeting Young Lord
would have been the proper thing to do.
What's there to see?
Young Lord has eyes only for Jinzhao.
He doesn't even notice anyone else.
I've no desire to make a fool of myself again.
Luo Liu, go.
Quickly, take this prescription
and get the herbs.
Yes.
Hurry, hurry up.
Sir, your medicine is ready.
Take care now.
What took you so long?
Are you trying to get yourself killed?
Where is it?
Look.
Just as I thought—rhubarb in every packet.
That concubine Song
truly has a vicious heart.
You saw it all clearly?
Crystal clear.
It was from Concubine Song's quarters—
Liuxiang and Luo Liu.
Ah, this wine...
This girl's quite something.
Thank you for your help, Guard Li.
Please, on behalf of my lady
convey a message to Young Lord.
Just frighten them a bit
no need for actual punishment.
I understand, sir.
Before the midday meal
Mrs. Mu paid a sudden visit.
She came about her eldest son's marriage.
Mu Zhidi.
Yes.
That tall, dull-witted one.
Xuanqing's classmate.
This rose dew is so fresh and sweet.
Have a taste.
Alright.
So this Mu Zhidi and the marriage proposal—
what did she say to you?
Could it be
she's taken a liking to our Yanying?
Not Yanying.
It's Miss Gu.
It was last year, during the chrysanthemum viewing.
He seemed perfectly quiet at the time
but apparently he'd already fallen for her.
They say from that very day
he couldn't get her out of his mind.
Then a few days ago
when the family brought up arranging his marriage
he could no longer hold it in and confessed.
When the Mus heard she's a daughter of a concubine
they said absolutely not.
What do you mean?
A concubine's daughter?
The second daughter of the Gu family.
The one they call Lan.
Born of a concubine, indeed.
But that Mu Zhidi, of all people
is a stubborn romantic.
He actually put on
a "I'll marry no one but the Lan" act.
Mrs. Mu was at her wits' end
so she came around asking questions
wanting to find out
what sort of person
this Lan really is.
Honestly, that Mrs. Mu
has no sense of direction at all.
She went on and on about the Lan
then suddenly started asking about Jinzhao as well.
Go on, eat.
I've had enough.
Why is she asking around about Jinzhao?
She says
she's heard Jinzhao is a great beauty
with a generous dowry
and the firstborn of the lawful wife.
A perfect match for their Mu Zhidi.
And since
I have a connection with Old Mrs. Ji
she wanted to ask me to play matchmaker.
Tell me—
is this match suitable or not?
It's not.
The Mu Zhidi clearly has his eye on
the Lan.
But Mrs. Mu is trying to twist it
into the eldest Miss Gu.
What status does she think her family holds?
And what does she take the Gu family for?
It's utterly absurd.
This matter—
you needn't
bring it up with Mrs. Ji.
It would only
upset people for no good reason.
I'm consulting you first, aren't I?
And I wasn't really going to do it.
That's fine then.
I have other matters to attend to.
I'll take my leave now.
Please enjoy your meal, Mother.
What's gotten into him?
From what I can tell
He seems angered.
That much I've noticed myself.
But what is he angry about?
Lord.
Go and discreetly find out
what's really going on with the Mu family
proposing to the Gu household.
Yes.
Help!
Speak.
How did you slip the drug
to poison your mistress?
Confess truthfully.
I did no such thing!
Still trying to deny it?
Luo Liu has already confessed everything.
He said you told him to add rhubarb to the medicine.
I didn't!
Then who?
It was Nanny Zhou.
Nanny Zhou told me
to give the herbs to Luo Liu.
Lord.
They confessed.
Both of them confessed fully.
We didn't even have time to frighten them.
They just spilled everything.
Let's go.
To find Gu Jinzhao.
Yes.
The Marquis arrives!
Greetings, Your Lordship.
I heard you've seized two people
and set up your own private court here.
Helping a friend
interrogate a couple of household servants, that's all.
No torture was used.
What utter nonsense.
Which one of your lowlife friends is it this time?
Even if I told you, you wouldn't know them.
And if I pointed them out
your arm wouldn't reach that far.
Insolence!
Just looking at this confession
it's clearly one of those degenerate households
with corrupt morals and low breeding.
You spend your days carousing with them
stirring up trouble.
Do you not care about your future at all?
You make it sound as if I'd have a future
if I stopped carousing
and stirring up trouble.
Lord.
My Lord.
Sir, please calm yourself down.
Young master spoke in a moment of anger.
He doesn't need you to plead his case.
I know exactly what he is
better than anyone.
Guards.
Keep an eye on this brat.
Without my express order
he is not to take a single step beyond the Marquis's gates.
As you command.
Master Xiao.
Come with me.
I have something to ask you.
Yes.
What you said just now is true?
I practiced medicine in the southwest for many years.
I saved the lives of several bandits.
They would not keep the truth from me.
Their leader told me himself
that their entire families
are held hostage by Prince Glorian.
He forced them to assassinate the Crown Prince.
Without Prince Glorian working from the inside
those bandits could never
have concealed themselves in the capital for so long—
let alone learn the Crown Prince's movements.
Years ago,
I believed that eliminating Prince Chengqing
would mean Prince Glorian—
his brother from the same mother—
would surely not remain either.
But His Majesty, in his mercy, spared him.
From this day forward
set aside all other tasks.
Focus solely on surveilling Prince Glorian's residence in secret.
At the first sign of trouble
report it to me immediately.
What is it that worries You?
His Majesty is gravely ill.
I fear that rogue
will try something.
Xiaoyou understands.
You've worked hard.
Lan, you too.
I didn't do much, Mother.
Jinzhao did all the real work.
The Divine Healer Xiao this time—
she's the one who brought him here.
Those days you were unconscious
Jinzhao watched over you day and night.
She's only just gone to rest a little.
You are both good children.
All of this for me.
I am fine now.
Go and get some rest yourselves.
Off you go now.
What's written here—
is it all true?
Signed, sealed, everything in order.
If you don't believe it,
the culprits are tied up right here.
You can question them again yourself.
Guards.
Bring Concubine Song
and Nanny Zhou here.
Yes.
This here—
your favorite pigeon soup.
I simmered it a full four hours.
Have at least a little.
Here.
My Lady.
Concubine Song.
Nanny Zhou was taken to the front courtyard
by the Master's men.
Why would the Master take Nanny Zhou?
I don't know.
I only saw a few old serving women
dragging Nanny Zhou away
fierce as demons.
It didn't look good at all.
What has Nanny Zhou done this time?
Mother.
You know something, don't you?
No, I don't.
Is Concubine Song here?
Lan.
Ziling, go and stop them.
Don't let them in.
Yes, My Lady.
What's really going on?
Say something.
Lan, I...
Move aside.
You can read.
Luo Liu and Liuxiang have both confessed.
They say you put them up to it.
Do you admit it or not?
I admit it.
Everything
was all done at my bidding.
How utterly vicious.
What did the Mistress ever do to you
that you could commit
such a heinous, unhinged act?
Lord Gu,
Nanny Zhou
is nothing but a lowly servant.
What grudge could she possibly hold against the Mistress?
She had to be acting on someone's orders.
Ms. Jinzhao, don't make reckless accusations.
No one put me up to it.
It was all
my decision alone.
Lord Gu.
Concubine Song is just outside.
Bring her in.
Qingpu.
Gag her.
Yes.
Lord Gu.
What is all this?
Such a grand commotion.
You know perfectly well what this is about, don't you?
I—
I don't understand.
Then let me ask you.
Nanny Zhou instructed Liuxiang
to pass the rhubarb to Luo Liu
to mix into the Madam's medicine.
Were you the one behind it?
Listen to me.
From beginning to end—
you knew nothing about this.
What medicine?
What… what Luo Liu?
It was all Nanny Zhou
and the people she hired.
No matter where you are—
even if you end up before the Shuntian Prefecture—
you must say, that from start to finish
you knew absolutely nothing.
Lan, but I—
No "buts."
We are at a critical juncture now.
Do you want to die?
Think of me!
If you die, what will become of me?
Mother.
Think of me—please, think of me.
I wasn't the one behind it, Lord Gu.
I know nothing about it.
Is that so?
But Nanny Zhou just confessed.
She said it was you who gave the order.
She's lying!
Lying?
Why would she lie?
She plotted against the Madam
and it was all because of you, wasn't it?
Liuxiang—
Nanny Zhou—
both of them are from your own quarters.
And you dare claim you knew nothing
about any of this?
Ms. Jinzhao.
I truly knew nothing.
Still clinging to your story?
Then we'll have to take this to the Shuntian Prefecture.
Nanny Zhou was your wet nurse.
Liuxiang was your personal maid.
They committed such
utterly villainous acts
and yet you claim to know nothing?
How utterly foolish can you be?
From now on, you are not to leave your quarters.
Confine yourself and reflect upon your misdeeds.
Lord Gu
As for the rest of you—
Liuxiang.
Luo Liu.
Forty strokes each.
When that's done
throw them onto the estate for hard labor.
Nanny Zhou.
Sixty strokes.
Make every stroke count.
Lord Gu.
Send her to the estate as well when it's over.
A moment, Lord Gu.
She nearly drove the Madam to her death.
And her punishment is merely confinement?
Did Nanny Zhou not just say
that she alone was behind it all?
Concubine Song knew nothing of it.
Those words you just spoke—
do you even believe them yourself?
Nanny Zhou
slipped rhubarb into the Madam's medicine
all because of Concubine Song, did she not?
Liuxiang already confessed
that since the tenth month of last year
they have been tampering with the Madam's medicine.
All this time
Concubine Song—
how could she possibly know nothing?
And what of it?
In judgment and in household governance
one cannot rely on mere supposition.
You go on about the Shuntian Prefecture—
but in Liuxiang's deposition
there is no mention of Concubine Song.
Nanny Zhou, too, says
Concubine Song knew nothing.
Since there is no proof
even the Shuntian Prefecture
could only rule the same way.
Since you say there is no proof
then I will go now
and search Concubine Song's quarters.
I refuse to believe I won't find something.
Qingpu—and Nanny Zhou—
we're leaving.
Yes, My Lady.
You—
What are you standing there for?
Drag them away, quickly.
Lord Gu, Lord Gu.
Lord Gu, you mustn't!
Sixty strokes
will be the death of Nanny Zhou!
Lord Gu
I beg you, Lord Gu!
Can't bear to part with Nanny Zhou?
Perhaps you'd like to join her?
Think of your daughter Lan.
For goodness' sake.
Take them away now.
What are we going to do?
Concubine Song's quarters—
there's probably nothing there.
Should we still go, then?
You go ahead.
I'll make one more attempt to probe Concubine Song.
What do you want now?
Nanny Zhou
slipped rhubarb into the Madam's medicine.
You knew all along—
you were the one who ordered it.
Weren't you?
No.
I don't know anything.
Nanny Zhou
has been sentenced to sixty strokes.
On the estate, there is little medicine and no proper care—
it is very likely
she may never come back from this.
If you are willing to tell the truth
I can guarantee she will survive.
You and Nanny Zhou are as close as mother and daughter.
Everything she did
was for your sake.
Can you truly bear
to watch her go to her death?
Gu Jinzhao.
Lan.
My mother knows nothing.
She did nothing.
Nothing at all.
Then why so defensive?
I am not defensive.
It's you who won't stop hounding us.
You know full well
that Nanny Zhou will never
come back in this lifetime.
Why are you still not satisfied?
What exactly do you want?
My mother is Father's concubine.
How she is to be dealt with
is for Father alone to decide.
There's no need for you to usurp that authority.
Lan.
Ms. Jinzhao.
I truly know nothing.
You are overthinking this.
Mother.
No need to explain to her.
This household—
she is not yet the one in charge.
Ms. Jinzhao
We found nothing at all.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
I was just thinking
about what Gu Lan said.
She was right.
This household
Is indeed not mine to rule.
But so what?
Regardless of who holds sway over this house
the truth between right and wrong can never be overturned.
Lord Gu is inside.
Nanny Zhou received sixty strokes
and has been banished to the estate.
She likely won't last much longer.
That counts as
avenging you, in a way.
And what of Song Miaohua?
Concubine Song genuinely knew nothing.
It was all at Nanny Zhou's instigation.
I'd like to ask you for a favor.
Concubine Song is, after all
Lan's mother.
Even setting her aside
we must at least
consider Lan's standing, mustn't we?
In the end, Lord Gu still cannot bear to part with her.
It's no wonder Song Miaohua
gave up even her own parents back then
just to be with His Lordship.
Oh, you.
I'm speaking with you calmly, aren't I?
It's getting late.
You should rest now.
Madam.
I owe you everything this time.
They told me what happened.
If not for you
I might have truly
this time
been killed by Song Miaohua.
Don't dwell on any of that.
Put those matters aside.
What matters most right now
is that you focus on recovering in peace.
I'll take care of everything else.
You may all leave us.
I have something to say to Nanny Zhou.
Lan.
Nanny Zhou.
My mother has been confined.
She can't come out.
I came on her behalf to see you.
It's better this way.
That you've come to send me off—
it makes me glad, too.
But now that I'm leaving
you must take good care of your mother.
I truly fear she'll suffer without me.
I'll take good care of her.
Don't worry.
Little Blackbird.
Quick, say something nice.
Good fortune and blessings.
Madam.
Have you ever considered
parting ways with the Lord Gu?
What?
This whole business—
I've thought it through carefully.
On the surface
it looks like Concubine Song and Nanny Zhou
out of jealousy and spite
slipped rhubarb into your medicine.
But the reason they dared do such a thing
is because they could clearly see
that between you and the Lord Gu
there is a rift.
The Lord Gu knew full well
that Concubine Song must have known
what Nanny Zhou was doing.
Yet she received no punishment whatsoever—
merely a cursory brush-off.
It only goes to show
how he feels about you.
What I believe is this—
rather than waste away here in the Gu household
you'd be better off leaving the Master
and returning to Tongzhou.
We can build a good life on our own.
You wouldn't have to keep using your dowry
to support him.
Let them fend for themselves.
Are you suggesting
that I should divorce your father?
No, no, no.
Let me explain.
Say no more.
this is utterly impossible.
Why?
What are you afraid of?
Your grandmother is old.
She couldn't bear something like this.
Grandmother wouldn't mind.
All her life
what she's cared about most
is that you live well.
And what of you and Jinrong?
The two of you—
one unwed, one unbetrothed.
If I
were truly to divorce your father
what would become of the two of you?
Who would be willing to marry
a girl whose mother left her husband?
Take such a girl as a daughter-in-law?
And who would be willing
to marry their fine, respectable daughter
into a household broken by divorce?
No.
It must never happen.
But in this household
you are not happy.
Rong and I see it with our own eyes—
could we possibly
with clear consciences
go off and marry while you suffer?
What sort of people would that make us?
And Grandmother—
that dear old lady—
what worries her most is you.
She gets up in the night, sighing and sighing
unable to rest.
If you agree to a divorce
no one would be happier than she.
To be honest
all I hope
is that you will truly think this over.
Before you were with the Master
what kind of life did you live?
What were those days like?
And now—
what kind of life do you live now?
Not another word.
I will not—
divorce your father.
And besides, your father would never agree to it.
Do not bring this up again.
Molan.
Yes, Madam.
Help me to my bed.
I'm weary.
Yes, Madam.
Is Mrs. Gu  gravely ill?
Yes.
While I was looking into the Mu family's proposal
the Gu household servants told me
that a concubine has been causing trouble—
slipping poison
into Madam Gu's regular medicine.
The household is in complete chaos.
I imagine Miss Gu right now
must be at her wits' end.
This Gu Dezhao
lacking in morals, leaving his house in turmoil—
is hardly fit to hold office at all.
Have the culprits been caught?
They have.
Once the matter came to light
Miss Gu seized them herself.
She had people to call upon, then.
Ye Xian helped her.
He had the culprits taken to the Marquis's residence for interrogation.
Ye Xian.
She turned to Ye Xian for help.
How—
that I do not know, sir.
As for Madam Gu's grave illness—
has a renowned physician been called in to treat her?
Yes.
Ye Xian assisted there as well—
he brought in a divine healer.
Can't handle the brush or the sword
but ever so diligent in matters like these.
Well.
Go
to the residence of Vice Minister Wu of the Ministry of Revenue.
Tell him
I will visit him tomorrow.
Yes.
Wait.
That won't do.
Vice Minister Wu has only recently taken up his post.
Gu Dezhao
is a mere storehouse director—
he likely doesn't even know
what the man looks like.
Better to have the censors impeach him—
cite his corrupt household morals
favoring the concubine over the wife.
That won't do either.
Not that either.
It would harm Jinzhao's reputation.
And if word got out and made a stir
it might also be bad
for Mrs. Gu's condition.
I recall—
Assistant Censor-in-chief Gu Deyuan
is Gu Dezhao's elder brother.
Yes.
No—that won't work either.
It's not right. Not right at all.
Here's what we'll do.
Come with me to the Gu Manor.
What is it?
Nothing.
Then let's go.
It really is Mr. Chen.
It is.
Chen Yi climbed over the wall to find me.
He said to keep it quiet and not disturb the household.
Miss Gu.
Mr. Chen is waiting for you over there.
Come with me.
Greetings, Mr. Chen.
Rise.
Between us
here's no need for such formalities.
What's happened in your household—
I've heard something of it.
Take this.
What is it?
Among those who serve under me
there are many
who have been at my side for years.
Most of them are quite skilled.
If you ever find yourself in danger again
just blow on this whistle.
The day after tomorrow
at the Dragon Boat Festival
I will be at Baoxiang Temple.
[He treats me so kindly—]
[what does it truly mean?]