[theme music playing]
LOVE NEXT DOOR
[amusing music playing]
Just wait, my baby.
I'll make it look nice for you.
[young Seung-hyo crying]
What am I going to do now?
[continues crying]
Don't worry. It'll be all gone
when you wake up tomorrow.
What if it's not gone?
Then…
I'll take responsibility.
I, Bae Seok-ryu, will take responsibility
for you, Choi Seung-hyo.
I promise.
Seal it.
Good. Great job.
PUPPY LOVE
Okay. Let's eat this.
[amusing music continues playing]
I said I didn't need the banana milk.
Why did you buy it?
That was that, and this is this.
What?
What is "that"?
What do you mean by "that was that"?
What do you think? It's "that."
In English, it's called "that."
It's a demonstrative pronoun.
Yeah, I know. That's what that is.
But what I meant… was that…
Jeez.
This word's losing all meaning.
Hey.
What?
What are we now?
I don't know.
Whatever a relationship after a kiss is?
Hey!
That kiss…
Can you not say that word
so suddenly like that?
I don't kiss my friends.
I said stop doing that!
We're not kissing now. We did before.
No, what I meant was…
Stop saying that word itself.
-The word? Kiss?
-Stop!
[chuckles softly]
Also, I don't do that
with my friends either.
Then, it's settled.
We're not friends anymore.
[scoffs]
How can 30 years of friendship
end just like that?
It was the hardest thing
I've done in my life.
Winning an Olympic medal
would've been easier.
[Myeong-u] Seung-hyo! Seok-ryu!
-Mr. Yoon.
-What? You two already met up?
You were looking frantically for him.
I thought he owed you
money or something.
-Really?
-[Myeong-u] Yeah.
Goodness, Mr. Yoon!
When did I ever act like that?
-You did…
-[Seok-ryu] Jeez.
[Na-yun] Then, why did you come here?
I mean, why would you come
all the way from Seoul to see him?
-Well, actually--
-Hey!
-Hold on! [chuckles]
-You scared me.
Do you really think
I came here to see him?
I just came and was in the area,
so I thought I'd call him.
[Myeong-u chuckles] Right.
Yeah, so why did you come?
I just came here!
I just came here, so I called him.
[Myeong-u laughs] Okay, great.
But it's still a pretty far drive.
So what brings you here?
No, I'm telling you it's personal!
It's personal, so why do they keep asking?
-I didn't take him for the type.
-[Myeong-u] Wait, are you crying?
Did I do something wrong?
-I feel like I was scolded.
-[Na-yun] Is she mad?
This is what I believe.
If you're someone who cooks,
you have to try food
from Gangwon Province,
which subtly enhances
the original taste of the ingredients.
[inhales deeply, exhales]
So you came all the way here to eat?
See? I knew you wouldn't believe me,
so I wasn't going to tell you.
[inhales, exhales]
It's true.
This gajami sikhae
is especially good. Seriously.
Gajami sikhae? What?
They made sikhye with fish? No way.
It's red too. I can't eat spicy food.
-It's not what you think.
-What?
It sounds like sikhye,
but it's not the drink.
-It's spelled differently.
-Is it?
-It's flounder.
-Okay.
They add rice and salt to it
and ferment it.
-That's how the dish is made.
-[Myeong-u] Fermented?
He's messing with you.
He loves fermented fish dishes.
[Seok-ryu] What?
You're a total food connoisseur!
Well, I wouldn't say "connoisseur."
[laughs]
He's marked
over 100 restaurants on the Greip map.
No, it was 328 as of yesterday.
[Seok-ryu gasps]
Can you share those with me?
No way!
I'm going to hand them down
to my twins. [laughs]
-Please!
-Still…
You've helped us out a lot.
So I'll give them all to you.
[gasps] Thank you!
This meal is on me then.
Thank you! Let's eat!
I bet you're hungry. Eat this.
[amusing music playing]
Me.
You like marinated raw crabs, right?
-Eat this.
-[Myeong-u] I do?
No? What about Na-yun?
What did you like?
You. I like you.
Okay, you can eat whatever you like.
I want to eat that. It looks so good.
[Seok-ryu] Eat up.
[Na-yun] Okay.
Mmm.
The gajami sikhae has great texture.
I could absolutely destroy it.
-Eat up.
-[Myeong-u] Okay.
[knock on door]
-Yes?
-[Seung-hyo] Can I come in?
-Sure.
-[door opens]
[Seok-ryu] Hey,
is it really okay to stay here?
Seriously, I can find another place.
There are plenty of empty rooms.
Also, here.
I thought you'd need more clothes.
Right, thanks.
Gosh, I've been borrowing
clothes a lot lately.
[chuckles softly]
The bathroom's at the end
of the hall, so you can wash up.
Okay, I got it. [clears throat]
[amusing music playing]
Were there any bugs?
-[Seok-ryu] No.
-Okay.
-[Seok-ryu] You're not leaving?
-What?
Aren't you going to go?
-Just for a moment--
-[Na-yun] Seung-hyo!
Seung-hyo, where are you?
Go on. She's looking for you.
Are you sure you want me to go?
What?
Back then and now.
Why do you keep giving me dirty looks?
What are you talking about?
My gaze is so gentle right now.
You should look in the mirror
when you say that.
Wait a second.
Are you jealous?
Don't be ridiculous. Hurry and get out.
Stop laughing. Go.
Fine, I'm leaving. Why are you pushing?
Just go.
[door closes]
Seung-hyo.
What?
My wife's not here, so I can't sleep.
[snoring]
[exclaims softly]
[Myeong-u continues snoring]
[amusing music playing]
-[Seung-hyo] Are you asleep?
-[Seok-ryu] No.
-[Seung-hyo] Want to come out?
-[Seok-ryu] Yard in 10 minutes.
[exclaims]
-[snoring stops]
-[thuds]
[snoring]
[dog barks distantly]
It's late. Why weren't you asleep?
What about you?
I was reading.
Mokminsimseo?
The book Jeong Yak-yong wrote?
Yeah.
Who reads those kinds of books these days?
I do.
It's been a classic since long ago
that transcends time.
It teaches integrity, responsibility,
and how to lead by example.
It tells you how to live.
This book provides
enlightenment about life.
Okay, don't get worked up.
Did I get worked up? [clears throat]
Well, it just seemed like
you didn't know the value of this book.
By the way, it's really nice here.
It's too bad I'm only staying for a day.
You can come again next time.
I'll go back with you tomorrow.
What about your work?
I finished earlier than expected.
I was going to leave the day
after tomorrow, but I can go a day early.
Let's go together.
How? You drove here.
I need to drive Mo-eum's car back.
For my car…
-I'll call a designated driver.
-Are you insane?
Do you know how expensive that would be?
Yeah, that does sound crazy to me, too.
But when I thought about it,
I realized spending time with you
was worth more.
Please. You've got to be kidding me.
You like me that much?
-Yeah.
-I see.
[pleasant music playing]
Well, how much do you like me?
[inhales]
Even after 30 years together,
I'm still not sick of you.
Wow, that's a bit of an exaggeration.
[chuckles softly]
Have some shame
and take out the times we were apart.
But there weren't any.
I've always been with you.
Here.
When we were eight,
you splashed paint all over me.
When we were seven,
you put sticker tattoos
on my face while I was asleep.
When we were six,
you gave me magic candy
that turned my lips purple
so you could tease me.
[pleasant music continues playing]
[chuckles softly]
And when we were five,
I spat bubble gum on your hair.
Jeez. [chuckles]
[Seok-ryu chuckles]
Wow, how could you still like me
after enduring all that suffering?
See?
I told you I was a femme fatale.
-Get off me.
-No.
You said we've always
been together like this.
[sighs] I'm a bit sleepy now though.
You are?
Yeah.
Maybe it's because of that long drive.
We can't have someone
come out and see us though.
[pleasant music continues playing]
[chuckles softly]
[music ends]
[exclaims softly]
[upbeat music playing]
[door opens, closes]
Ms. Jung Mo-eum?
Yes.
INTERVIEW ROOM
INTERVIEW FOR SOUTH POLE
RESEARCH STATION PARAMEDIC POSITION
[interviewer] Ms. Jung Mo-eum.
You have a high TOEIC score
and a recreational watercraft license.
You're also a certified Level 1 paramedic.
You're well-prepared.
Yes, sir. Not only did I do my best
to excel in fire safety management
but I also worked hard
to perform my duties in the field.
Why do you want to go to Antarctica?
To be honest, my dream
was to become Superman when I was a kid.
[chuckles softly]
Then, I wanted to be Spider-Man.
I realized I couldn't be either,
so I joined the Korea Fire Service.
And I've been very satisfied with my job.
Because I'm still able to help people.
[chuckling]
Yes, I guess you're right.
I'd like to go to Antarctica
to experience an unknown world
and to help preserve world peace.
MINISTRY OF FOREIGN AFFAIRS
[serious music playing]
Thank you for telling me
about Hye-suk last time.
I'm glad she's safe.
But…
this is as far as my gratitude
for Hye-suk will go.
-Excuse me?
-Seo Hye-suk is my wife.
She's my woman.
I know that.
Then, that's more reason
to not behave like this.
Don't try to sway her anymore.
I think there's a misunderstanding.
I heard your nickname is Alain Delon.
Why suddenly bring that up?
-Yes, you're handsome.
-Excuse me, Dr. Choi.
However, my feelings for her won't change.
-The reason for that is…
-[door opens]
…I love Hye-suk!
Darling.
What's going on?
What are you doing here? Well?
Well…
Hye-suk and I are just friends.
She just called you "Darling"!
What kind of friends call each other that?
-We do, because we're close.
-We're really just friends.
I've never once harbored
feelings for her.
That's why it's so ridiculous!
She's such a beautiful
and intelligent woman.
How could you not fall for her?
Are you a robot?
[amusing music playing]
I'm gay.
-Gosh.
-Excuse me?
I like men.
[music ends]
You're such a beautiful
and intelligent woman.
-[chuckles]
-[Hye-suk] Stop it. Jeez.
I'm sorry. I'm so embarrassed.
Don't be sorry.
It was actually nice.
He can declare his love for you
with such confidence.
Gosh, he's such a fool.
Seeing that made me envious.
-What's there to be envious about?
-[laughing]
I'm pretty old now too.
Maybe I should be braver as well.
Whatever you choose to do,
I'll support you.
You know that, right?
I know. Always and forever.
[Se-hwan chuckles]
[pleasant music playing]
[groans softly]
[scoffs]
[sighs softly]
I'm so embarrassed by you right now.
-Stay two steps behind me.
-Okay.
[scoffs]
I mean, how could you…
-How could you doubt me?
-I didn't doubt you. That bastard…
I mean, I was afraid
he might've had bad intentions.
Regardless of the reason, I'm sorry.
Unbelievable.
Gosh.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
I wouldn't have misunderstood if you did.
My friend trusted me with that secret.
How could I tell you?
He must've been so uneasy living
in this conservative and rigid society.
That's so cool. You're so cool.
Jeez.
-What are you doing? Let's go.
-Coming.
[Hye-suk groans softly]
Gosh, I'm so embarrassed.
That was so embarrassing.
Goodness. What do you think you're doing?
SEND YOUR NAME,
ADDRESS, PHONE NUMBER
ORDERS WILL BE PROCESSED UPON PAYMENT
-Yeah! I did it!
-[door opens, closes]
You scared me. What are you yelling for?
Mom, are you ready?
Yeah, the food's ready. Help yourself.
No, not food.
Are you ready for the good life?
-You know the money you lent me?
-Yeah?
I'll multiply it by a hundred. A thousand!
Are you an influenza now?
No, not influenza. An influencer.
Right, influencer.
No, wait. Like a virus,
I'm going to be deadly.
And I'll become more infectious.
Just try to break even.
Mom, trust your son!
It's for real this time.
Also, don't carry around
things like this anymore.
-Let's throw it out.
-Hey!
Why would I toss out a perfectly fine bag?
[sighs]
Mom, this won't do.
Have a bag picked out.
I'll buy it for you soon.
Even if I had a bag like that,
I have nowhere to bring it to.
All I want is for you to be a success.
That's all.
Bye.
-Mom, go to the mall. Okay?
-[door opens]
-[door closes]
-Pick one out!
-[Jae-suk] Eat this first.
-[In-suk] Okay.
[playful music playing]
-Hey.
-[In-suk] What?
How much does
a designer bag cost these days?
-Prices vary greatly.
-[Jae-suk] Right.
But they're at least
two to three million won.
Goodness, that's insane.
With that kind of money,
you could buy 30 kg of Hanwoo!
Gosh, that's expensive.
-But why do you suddenly ask?
-[exclaims]
Is Geun-sik buying you one?
It'd be faster to be reborn than
to expect something like that from him.
[all laughing]
No, Dong-jin…
Never mind. Later.
-What? [laughs]
-No, it's nothing.
It's just…
-Hey, Mi-suk.
-Yeah?
I don't know
if it's right to ask you this or not,
but it's about Seok-ryu.
Would she be interested in a blind date?
A blind date?
[dog barking]
Why is the dog barking so much?
Don't you think you were a bit harsh?
About what?
How could you drive all the way back
without stopping at a rest area?
Did you want to go to the bathroom?
It's not that.
It was supposed to be a date.
I should've just driven my car.
I need to give Mo-eum her car back.
I told you
we should drive back separately.
-But…
-[Mi-suk] Seok-ryu!
-Hey, Seung-hyo.
-Mom.
-Aunt Mi-suk.
-Why are you…
Mom, the reason why we're together is--
No, I was just about to call you.
Do you want to go on a blind date?
A blind date?
Goodness! Why are you the one surprised?
Jeez, Mom. Don't be ridiculous.
Your Aunt Jae-suk wants to
set you up with someone.
I'm not forcing you either,
but he seems decent.
No, she can't.
[clears throat] She's in
no position to do that.
-Mom! Let's talk at home.
-[Mi-suk] No, not later. Now!
I have to tell her quick.
Jae-suk wants to introduce him to Mo-eum,
but she won't listen.
[Mo-eum] Me?
There's that disobedient girl.
[amusing music playing]
[Mo-eum] Give me an answer now.
What?
Wow.
I was busy eating that night
I didn't look around properly.
Goodness. Company benefits are good here.
There's a massage chair too.
Yeah, we're trying our best.
Right. [grunts]
Even the massage chair
is different at an architecture firm.
It's so pretty.
[Mo-eum exclaiming]
All right, then.
How about we hear the report now?
-What report?
-Come on.
My car came back today,
which means Seok-ryu spent the night out.
Are you two…
dating now?
I did spend the night out,
but it's definitely not
what you're thinking.
[Seung-hyo] Yeah, we were at our lodgings.
We slept separately in separate rooms.
Yeah, sure. Let's say that happened.
But why won't you answer my question?
What?
Are you two dating?
[amusing music continues playing]
Yeah, we are.
[exclaiming]
[claps hands]
Finally! At long last!
I feel so refreshed.
Seriously, you two!
[sighs]
This feels like my body
and soul's been massaged!
Gosh, this feels good!
[chuckles]
Why are you so happy about us dating?
Because I almost died of frustration.
I bet everyone who's watched you two
feels the same way.
However, I knew you two
would end up together.
Hey, how would you know
something even we didn't know?
There's power in words.
[amusing music playing]
[kids chattering]
[kids] ♪ Seung-hyo and Seok-ryu
Sitting in a tree ♪
♪ K-I-S-S-I-N-G ♪
♪ First comes love ♪
You're all dead!
[kids] ♪ Then comes marriage ♪
[young Seung-hyo crying]
[kids] ♪ Then comes baby
In a baby carriage ♪
♪ Seung-hyo and Seok-ryu ♪
[young Seok-ryu] Get back here!
[kids] ♪ Sitting in a tree ♪
[amusing music continues playing]
[kid 1] Hey, why do you two
always go home together?
We live next door.
[kid 2] Still, boys and girls
shouldn't hang out with each other.
♪ Seung-hyo and Seok-ryu
Sitting in a tree ♪
[kids] ♪ K-I-S-S-I-N-G ♪
That's not true! He's just my sidekick!
[kids] ♪ First comes love ♪
♪ Then comes marriage ♪
♪ Then comes baby in a baby carriage ♪
♪ Seung-hyo and Seok-ryu ♪
Hey, Choisseung.
Give me your history textbook.
What am I, the library?
[boys taunting]
Hey, what's with you two?
-Are you two dating?
-Nope.
Seeing him naked wouldn't faze me at all.
Just think of her as a guy.
Hey, you two.
You heard the same thing
over and over again,
so whether you liked each other or not,
it was subconsciously ingrained in you.
Hmm.
So I was a victim of gaslighting?
Do paramedics carry air rifles?
-I want to shoot him.
-What?
Maybe I should've become a cop.
No, you're fine as is.
Hey, but the thing is
all three of us hung out together,
so why did people put us two together?
That's because I'm way out of his league.
[chuckles softly]
Yeah, it's okay.
Her sights have always been
out of this world.
Her standards of beauty
are different from ours.
That is true.
By the way, you look cool today.
Why are you in uniform?
-Good question.
-Well…
I had an interview today.
The South Pole position?
Your application passed?
Of course!
[Seung-hyo] Wait a second.
Are you really going to go
if you pass this too?
[Seok-ryu] Wow!
Then, does that mean
you'll get to see penguins in person?
Penguins right before your eyes?
That's right.
-Take a lot of pictures--
-No.
In Antarctica, the penguins are in danger
due to the climate crisis.
Polar bears are in danger too.
-[door opens]
-[Mo-eum] I'm home.
-Hi.
-[Yeon-du] Mo-eum!
Yeon-du!
[Watch on www.kisskh.la or www.kisskh.co to support Admin work]
-What were you up to?
-[Yeon-du exclaims]
-[Mo-eum] What were you doing, Yeon-du?
-[Yeon-du giggles]
[Mo-eum] What have you been doing all day?
We read books together.
-Okay. [gasps]
-And we removed the guts from anchovies.
You did?
Mom, did you make Yeon-du
remove the guts from anchovies?
Are you Cinderella's stepmother?
Seriously?
No. It looked fun,
so I said wanted to help.
Really?
Jeez. Did you think your own mother
would abuse a child?
No. I just wanted to make sure.
Yeon-du.
I'll take the anchovies
we prepared together,
and I'll stir-fry them nice and well!
Okay, thank you!
That sounds so good.
It sounds so good! [chuckles]
Hey, if you're not going to get married,
go somewhere and bring back
a daughter like Yeon-du.
What?
That's how badly I want
a grandchild of my own. Okay?
Go and stir-fry the anchovies.
I swear…
Yeon-du, aren't you bored
from just reading books all day?
Mmm.
I don't know.
Is there anything else you want to do
besides reading books?
Want to go ride bikes?
I don't know how to.
Really?
Then…
-How about scooters?
-I can't ride those either.
You don't like to play outside?
It's not that, but my dad says
it's too dangerous outside.
I see.
[quirky music playing]
[Mo-eum laughing] It's you!
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
[both] Minus one!
Ribbit, ribbit!
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
Minus one!
-Yeon-du.
-Ribbit!
Dad!
[both exclaiming]
Yeon-du, I missed you so much today.
Did you miss me too?
[Yeon-du] Well…
Yeah, I'd say so.
[chuckles]
[exclaims]
Thank you. I owe you a lot.
No, it's fine. Do you have work tomorrow?
-Yes.
-[Mo-eum] I see.
-Take a day off.
-Sorry?
Let's meet here at 10:00 a.m. tomorrow.
But…
-No refusals.
-Wait.
No questions.
But…
And no mudflat shirt.
-Yeon-du, see you tomorrow.
-See you tomorrow!
-[Mo-eum] Ribbit!
-Ribbit!
[chuckles]
[Yeon-du] Dad, let's go.
[Seok-ryu] Hey, isn't this
the tree I gave to you?
Did you kill it and buy a new one?
That's right.
How did you know?
That's the secret of its origin.
[scoffs]
Wow.
It's grown so much. This is so neat.
How did it grow so much?
-Seok-ryu.
-[Seok-ryu] Yeah?
[clears throat]
Are you going to go on that blind date?
Are you crazy?
I'll make something up and turn her down.
This won't do.
Let's just tell her we're dating.
What?
Who knows? This might happen again.
Let's also tell your dad.
We'll tell my parents too.
Let's officially get their approval.
We should tell the entire neighborhood.
We can't.
[amusing music playing]
-Why not?
-I mean…
We've just started to date.
Telling everyone seems a bit too much.
It's pretty obvious that it'll be chaos.
It's a little bit of an issue.
Our moms are friends.
And we're all so close.
And to be honest, you don't know
what could happen to us.
Let's keep it a secret for now.
All right. If that's what you want…
Let's keep our relationship a secret.
Top secret.
We have to be diligent. No one can know.
No one will know.
[music ends]
[birds chirping]
[groans]
Is he up?
Choisseung.
[playful music playing]
Bonjour, Seok-ryu!
-Aunt Hye-suk!
-[Hye-suk] Hi.
Seung-hyo went to work early today.
Is it urgent?
No, it's nothing.
Hey, I didn't know your windows
were this close.
You could trip and kiss each other.
[chuckles nervously]
I bet you two hardly ever spent
any time apart.
That's right. [chuckles]
That's why I'm so sick of it!
I bet Choisseung feels the same.
But still, don't fight
and try to get along, okay?
Okay.
-I have something on the stove.
-Go ahead!
Sorry. I'll see you next time. Bye!
Gosh, that scared me.
[line ringing]
[phone vibrating]
BAE SEOK-RYU
[phone continues vibrating]
-[Seung-hyo] Na-yun.
-Yes?
What did you just do?
Oh…
Well…
[Seung-hyo sighs]
You know what you did
was excessive, right?
Yes.
I've allowed your actions to slide
because I thought of you
as just a cute former classmate.
But I can't anymore.
I'm sorry for what I just did.
But Seung-hyo,
you know that I like you.
I thought it was half crush, half joking.
No, it's not. I'm serious.
Then, I think I need to
be perfectly clear.
There's someone else I like.
Is it someone I know?
She's someone I found
after a long and difficult journey.
I don't want to do anything
that would make her feel uncomfortable.
[sniffles]
[phone vibrating]
[Seung-hyo] I'm sorry I didn't pick up.
Want to see a movie later?
What is this? Is he officially
asking me out on a date?
Sounds good.
I have to wash my hair.
-Mo-eum!
-[Mo-eum] Yeon-du!
-My sweet Yeon-du!
-[Yeon-du screaming]
[Mo-eum exclaims]
Did you sleep well?
Any dreams about being
an alien's friend?
No, I dreamt of something else.
[Mo-eum] What was it?
It's a secret. I'll tell you later.
Okay.
Wow.
You're very punctual.
It's the basics of being a reporter.
I came because you asked me to, but…
I don't need to say
where we're going, right?
[both exclaiming]
Let's go!
Dad, bring that stuff and follow us!
-[Mo-eum] What?
-What?
-We're not going to help?
-[Yeon-du] Let's go.
Ms. Jung?
[pop song playing]
[Mo-eum exclaims]
[exclaims]
I'll just do it.
No, it's fine.
-I'll do it.
-[Yeon-du] Dad.
-Dad?
-[Dan-ho] Yeah?
[pop song continues playing]
[exclaims]
[exhales]
[chuckles softly]
[inaudible]
Careful, it's hot.
Try some.
-I'll eat it on my own.
-Okay.
Mmm.
-Is it good?
-You're pretty good at grilling!
What are we doing next, Mo-eum?
What we're going to do next is…
-Wow!
-Wow! [laughs]
[both exclaiming]
Don't shoot Yeon-du!
[Yeon-du laughing]
[Dan-ho exclaims]
[Yeon-du laughs]
[Dan-ho] I give up!
[Yeon-du laughing]
[Mo-eum] You're drenched.
I was able to borrow this.
Oh.
But we don't have any electricity.
How can we use that?
Just a second.
[pop song continues playing]
[hair dryer blows]
Wow!
[Mo-eum] Wow!
I'll dry your hair, Yeon-du.
Let's dry your hair.
[Yeon-du] What was the most fun for you?
I liked playing
with the water guns the most.
Me too. [giggles]
[chuckles softly]
-All done.
-[hair dryer stops]
[Mo-eum] Wow, Yeon-du!
I'll tie your hair nice and pretty later.
-Okay.
-Your hair's wet too.
I'll dry it myself.
What?
I see! Right!
[hair dryer blows]
[pleasant music playing]
[Dan-ho] I thought you might be cold.
Yeon-du, how about we go over there?
All right.
[pleasant music continues playing]
[pop song playing in the background]
Hey, Choisseung.
Hey.
I'm here and you won't even look at me?
I did look.
[amusing music playing]
What are you so busy with?
I was tasked with remodeling
a movie theater.
I thought of something when I got here,
so I wanted to draw it before I forgot.
Will it take long?
No, I'll be done
before the movie starts.
So this is what a blueprint looks like.
Yeah.
Do you want popcorn? I'll buy some.
No, I'm fine.
Really? Then, I'll just buy a drink.
Okay.
[amusing music continues playing]
[sighs wearily]
[lady in movie] You want more?
Oh.
Sorry.
[lady in movie] They said they'd analyze
the photos and bring them here.
[exclaims]
The sun is already setting.
Should we go before it gets too late?
No.
Yeon-du just fell asleep.
Let's stay for 30 more minutes.
-Okay.
-[Mo-eum faintly chuckles]
She must be heavy. Give her to me.
Oh.
Yeon-du, let's sleep on the bed.
It was fine though.
[both exclaim]
[Mo-eum] So how was camping?
Not bad, right?
Yeah.
I've never thought about it,
but Yeon-du really liked it.
Yeon-du said she couldn't ride a bike.
She can't ride scooters
or rollerblades either.
It's because of the accident, right?
It wasn't on purpose.
I just keep getting so worried.
I understand how you feel.
I know I have no authority
to tell you what to do either.
But…
if you keep a miracle
hidden away like that,
it'll never really be a miracle.
I want Yeon-du to feel the wind
and stomp her feet.
And sometimes, she'll fall down.
That's how I'd want her to grow.
I want her to see and hear
all the good things in this world.
I hope she can take it all in
like a sponge and grow healthy.
[mellow music playing]
Wouldn't that be a real miracle?
I'm so sorry to Yeon-du.
It would've been nice
if I was as brave as you.
Sometimes, I think it would be nice
if I was Yeon-du's mom.
[chuckles nervously]
Come on. Still, that's a bit much.
I can't?
I know I'm moving really fast right now.
It's like I've just traveled to Andromeda
over 2.5 million light-years away.
But…
that's how I feel right now.
Ms. Jung…
My heart races whenever I see you.
It beats rapidly like a drum every time.
I even see you in my dreams too.
So I was wondering.
About our kiss…
Can't we cancel our agreement?
I don't think it was a mistake.
[music fades]
No, we can't. Never.
Yeon-du can't become your daughter.
And what happened that day was a mistake.
It has to be.
Why?
Because it can't happen.
[slow music playing]
From now on,
I won't leave Yeon-du at your house.
And I'd appreciate it
if you didn't hang out with her anymore.
-Dan-ho…
-We should go.
Yeon-du.
-Wake up. We have to go home.
-[Yeon-du groans softly]
[Dan-ho] Let's sleep in the car, okay?
[amusing music playing]
Go on in first.
What? Why?
What if we run into
your mom again like last time?
Come on. We've hung around
with each other for years.
-She won't be suspicious of this.
-But still…
To keep this secret, we need to be careful
around the neighborhood.
I'll take a lap around the block.
Go on in first.
Okay, then.
Since when did he start
listening to me so well?
Ridiculous.
[inhales]
[exclaims softly]
Alzheimer's…
-It's not that.
-Really?
-[doctor] Yes.
Take a look for yourself
if you don't believe me.
Hey, you're going to break it!
There's nothing wrong with her brain.
Of course,
we'll have to see if your symptoms
reoccur in the future.
Then, why did I keep forgetting things?
You could say
it's a type of short-term memory loss.
I see.
Have you experienced any shock
or a significant amount of stress lately?
[pleasant music playing]
Yes.
Then, it could be from that stress.
It could be due to heightened anxiety.
If you rest and take care of yourself,
you'll be fine.
Thank you.
[sighs in relief]
I'm so relieved.
No, "relieved" isn't enough
to describe how I feel.
I've been in an emotional hell
for the past two weeks.
You said it would be okay,
but I thought of the worst-case scenarios.
Are you listening to me?
-[groans softly]
-[Hye-suk] Honey!
Honey, what's wrong?
[crying]
[Hye-suk] Honey, what's the matter?
What is it?
What? Honey, don't cry. What's wrong?
[voice shaking] I thought something bad
was going to happen to you.
I just learned the truth not too long ago,
and I was finally able to express
my true feelings.
But I was afraid I was too late.
I was afraid you'd forget me. [crying]
[Hye-suk exclaims]
I was scared I'd lose you. [crying]
Honey.
I can't live without you, Hye-suk!
-[exclaims]
-[crying]
-For goodness' sake.
-[Gyeong-jong sniffles]
[exclaims]
I swear.
You've been embarrassing me
a lot these days, you know.
But this isn't so bad either.
-[sniffles] Honey.
-[crying]
[crying] He said
I didn't have Alzheimer's!
Stop crying, Gyeong-jong!
Why didn't you say
anything like this before?
You big dummy! [crying]
[upbeat music playing]
[sizzling]
[music fades]
See you next class!
[both] Bye!
[line ringing]
-Hello?
-[Seok-ryu] Hey, Choisseung.
So I made neobiani in class today.
It's so good. Want me to bring you some?
I had work to do outside,
so I'm not at the office.
Do you want to come by later at night?
-At night?
-[Seung-hyo] Yeah.
[Tae-hui] Seung-hyo!
I have to go. I'll see you later.
[line disconnects]
At night?
If it's at night…
Then, it'll be dark
and no one will be around.
[amusing music playing]
ORDER DETAILS
What? I made the post days ago,
but why are there only ten orders?
Damn it.
Were my abs not defined enough?
[exclaims] I should've
worked out a bit more.
[phone vibrating]
JAE-YEONG
Hey, Jae-yeong.
What? Haeundae Beach?
I'm in no position to go now…
Really? I don't have to pay?
You're paying?
[Seok-ryu] Choisseung!
I made a lot of good food…
for us.
[playful music playing]
You're all here.
It's been a while, Seok-ryu.
Hi.
[gasps]
My goodness! This was made with such care!
Why did you bring so much food?
Oh.
You must've come
to congratulate Seung-hyo.
Congratulate him?
Yes. To celebrate the launch
of the collaboration with Fresco,
they interviewed him.
Hey, that article should be out now.
-Show it to her.
-Right.
I've been looking at it for a while.
The picture came out well too. [chuckles]
[Tae-hui] I was going
to leave right after,
but Myeong-u told me to stay.
[Myeong-u] Aren't you glad I did?
You can have all this good food.
[Tae-hui] Whatever.
I've finished my coffee, so I'll go.
What? You're leaving and not eating?
I'm busy.
-You're going to go?
-[Tae-hui] Yes.
I did want to congratulate you,
so I'm glad I can.
Congratulations
on your official start to cooking.
[chuckles softly]
It was thanks to your advice. Thank you.
It was thanks to your delicious kalguksu.
[playful music continues playing]
Great job today. I'm off.
All right, get home safe.
-Thanks.
-[Jeong-min] Good night.
Bye. Thanks. Great job.
Get home safe.
It would've been nice if she stayed.
I texted you and said I'd call you later
since tonight wasn't a good night.
I saw it just now.
Why didn't you tell me
you had an interview with Fresco?
Was it because of Tae-hui?
They said it wouldn't take long,
so I was going to tell you after.
-But it ended up like this.
-What?
You thought I wouldn't understand?
No, it's not that.
I'm sorry. I have no excuse.
It was nice seeing her
after all this time.
She's still pretty.
Tae-hui didn't come
because she wanted to either.
Myeong-u kept insisting.
Did you tell her we're dating?
No.
You told me not to tell anyone.
But an ex-girlfriend
is different…
[sighs softly]
Okay.
Also, we didn't have time
to talk about anything personal.
It was an official event.
Now that I think about it,
you two are like Hollywood actors.
I could never work with my ex-boyfriend.
I mean, think about it.
Even if you try,
feelings don't just disappear.
And things were once good.
It's all in the past.
I want to stop talking about this.
What's wrong? I know everything anyway.
[sighs]
Hey, when you told
Tae-hui earlier to get home safe,
your voice was no joke.
-It was so deep.
-I never did that.
You did. You were so worried about her.
I mean, why didn't you just take her home?
Seok-ryu.
How were you around her
when I wasn't here?
Were you mature
and understanding around her?
[sighs softly]
I don't want to answer that.
I'm not obligated
to tell you things like that.
[amusing music playing]
[sighs wearily]
[sighs deeply]
What's wrong with me?
[sighs]
You have some nerve, Choi Seung-hyo.
[sighs deeply]
Are you heading out now?
Yes. Where are you going?
I'm going to Seoraksan Mountain.
Your father and I are taking
an overnight trip with Seok-ryu's parents.
[gasps] I forgot to tell you.
You're staying one night.
Why did you pack so much?
No. The thing is, your dad…
What is all this?
Compression bandages and heat packs.
Your ankle hasn't fully healed yet,
so it's just in case.
I have acupressure patches
if your feet hurt from walking a lot.
Why not bring crutches
and a wheelchair too?
You think I should?
I'll call the hospital.
[scoffs] No, honey. It's fine.
Come here! We're late. Let's go. Jeez!
[playful music playing]
So that's what Dad's really like.
[Mi-suk] I said hurry up!
[Geun-sik] Hey, you washed my pants wrong.
They shrank!
-You should've washed them right.
-Honey, they're mine.
[laughing]
-They're not mine?
-Seriously?
I see. It has a lace trim.
-I told you to pack earlier!
-[Geun-sik] I don't have any tank tops!
Is there a black hole in the drawer?
I can't find anything in this house.
Seok-ryu, your dad
would be a perfect slug.
-A slug!
-[Geun-sik] Is that how you talk of me?
You turn me into a slug?
When are you leaving?
-It's been 30 minutes!
-[Mi-suk] Why look for that now?
We'll probably go tomorrow
thanks to your dad!
My tank top. My sunglasses are gone!
-Find my sunglasses.
-Dad, they're on your head!
[laughing] There they are!
Jeez! And where are you going?
What? I'm going to Busan with my friends.
-Wow, you're all going without me?
-Here it is. Here!
Jeez, it was right there!
How could you not find it?
-I caught it.
-Good grief.
-Let's take these!
-Where's Dong-jin going?
-Busan with his friends.
-[Mi-suk] All of a sudden?
Dad, could you not wear those?
-No, I need these.
-Goodness.
-Don't wear those at Seoraksan.
-That's a fashion crime.
Sorry! He kept on dawdling.
It's okay. We didn't wait much.
[Geun-sik] You took forever
in front of the mirror picking scarves!
-"This or that?"
-Let's go!
[both] Okay!
-Get in.
-[Gyeong-jong] Here.
[Hye-suk] Thanks, honey.
-Here.
-Honey, get in.
Honey?
The car looks so sleek and shiny.
I've always wanted to go for a ride in it.
-Wow!
-[Hye-suk] Your first time in our car?
-[Geun-sik] Yes.
-[Hye-suk] I see.
GANGNEUNG DAEGWALLYEONG SERVICE AREA
Are we almost there?
-Yeah.
-Honey!
-[Hye-suk] The water's so cold.
-Here. Dry your hands.
[Hye-suk] Thanks. The water was so cold.
-Really? No hot water?
-No.
That's terrible.
Honey! Man, these have
entire walnuts in them!
My hands feel frozen.
-That's cold. Hey!
-[Gyeong-jong] Hey!
-You're so rude.
-Come on.
-I think it got on my face. Look.
-[scoffs]
-Geun-sik!
-Goodness.
-Just lightly pat it.
-Do you have a handkerchief?
A handkerchief?
Yeah. But I used this
to blow my nose. Is that okay?
You're so rude.
-What's wrong?
-I want those walnut pastries.
Do you want some of these?
Wow! Let's take a picture here!
Mi-suk, let's take
our individual pictures first.
-[Mi-suk] Individual ones?
-Yeah.
Take a picture of me.
-Just a second.
-Okay.
Honey, take a picture of me with this.
-Just take it yourself.
-No, with the bear!
For goodness' sake.
-With the bear?
-[Mi-suk] Yeah.
-Okay.
-[camera shutter clicking]
That's how you get the bear in it.
No, take some more.
-Jeez.
-[Geun-sik] Weather is amazing.
It's unbelievable.
[dramatic music playing]
[Hye-suk] Should I stand here?
[Gyeong-jong] That's good, honey.
Who carries around something like that?
-[Mi-suk] It is heavy.
-Goodness. What is he doing?
Now, that's funny.
Goodness.
He's going crazy now.
You two have both gone crazy.
-Is that okay?
-Let's see that jawline!
[Geun-sik] I feel embarrassed.
[Mi-suk] What's with you?
[Gyeong-jong] Good!
-Great!
-Let me see.
-I'm next!
-No, let's look.
-[Hye-suk] Honey.
-[Gyeong-jong panting]
Since when did you take
such great pictures?
I went online and studied how to take
good pictures of your girlfriend.
-Do you like it?
-[camera shutter clicking]
[Hye-suk] I love it.
You did great. It's amazing.
You idiot. You made me look like a dwarf.
It looks just like you.
Hey, Gyeong-jong.
Can you take a picture
of me with that too?
-Yeah, okay!
-Make my legs look long.
Take your own.
-Mo-eum.
-[Mo-eum] Yeah?
Can you call my phone?
[Mo-eum] Okay.
-[line ringing]
-[phone vibrating]
It works.
-[line disconnects]
-It works very well.
It was so quiet I thought it was broken.
[amusing music playing]
SEOK-RYU
[knock on door]
Come in.
-Dan-ho.
-Mr. Choi.
-I mean, Mr. Kang.
-Seung-hyo.
Didn't we go back to being formal?
Right, we did.
Take a seat.
-Thank you.
-Of course.
[sighs softly]
-You can sit anywhere.
-Right.
[Dan-ho sighs]
I'm sorry for interrupting if you're busy.
Mr. Yoon said you were in your office
and it was okay to go in.
No, it's okay. I'm glad you came.
But what brings you here?
I have a favor to ask of you.
I've been writing articles
about my experiences lately.
For my next feature, I want to highlight
the lives of construction workers.
I was wondering if you could
introduce me to a construction site.
Oh.
Of course, I can.
We have a few sites under construction.
I'll call them and let you know.
Thank you.
I owe you a lot.
Gosh, there's no need to say that.
You've helped me out a lot.
You helped me catch those scammers too.
-And you provided advice last time.
-I see.
About your friend…
May I ask how things turned out
with your friend's friend?
They just recently started dating.
Congratulations.
[amusing music playing]
I mean, congratulate your friend for me.
Congratulate. Right.
What's wrong?
Is something not working out?
No, it's just…
He says dating is hard.
Love is quite hard.
[chuckles softly]
[clears throat]
How could he take
Tae-hui's side in front of me?
I don't think he took her side.
Whose side are you on?
Seung-hyo, that bastard!
Also, I asked him how he was
when he dated her,
and he didn't want to answer.
He said he wasn't obligated to tell me.
Then, what answer did you want to hear?
-What do you mean?
-Think about it.
You'd be upset if he said
things were great with her.
If he said things were awful…
Would you want him to be a scumbag
who bad-mouths his ex-girlfriends?
No.
Right? So why would you
ask about his past?
That's self-harm.
[sighs] You're right.
-I know that too.
-You know but what?
But it makes me jealous!
[mellow music playing]
Hey, from now on,
I'm going to be Seung-hyo's friend.
Seok-ryu, you brat!
He was kind enough to let you say goodbye
to Hyeon-jun, so you can't do this to him.
I know. I know that too.
But I can't control how I feel,
so what can I do?
[sighs audibly]
[clicks tongue]
She's right. You can't control feelings.
Hello.
Uh…
[exclaims softly]
There was only one left.
Take this.
No, it's fine. You can have it.
Really, it's okay. You take it.
No, I want you to have it.
It's my feelings for you.
-What?
-[Mo-eum exclaims]
The fire in my heart
won't be extinguished
until it's completely burned out.
So, enjoy.
[sighs softly]
[scanner beeping]
[slow music playing]
I think I have to stop drinking this.
But I don't know if I can.
[sighs]
[Hye-suk] Stop laughing.
-Do you enjoy teasing me?
-[Mi-suk] Hey.
If those were signs of dementia,
we'd all be in a nursing home right now.
It was really serious. I mean it.
I told you. I couldn't remember anything.
Hye-suk, I forgot what we had for lunch.
What did we eat?
Sweet and spicy chicken.
We had chicken, remember?
-Sweet and spicy chicken.
-Right!
-Chicken!
-Get a grip, Mi-suk.
It was so crunchy and delicious!
-[Hye-suk laughing]
-Hey, this is how we are now.
Anyway, I'm so relieved that you're okay.
Yeah. I learned so much
after going through this incident.
Family, friends.
Knowing I have people
I can lean on in my life
was so reassuring.
I thought that too
after learning
about what happened to Seok-ryu.
I wanted her to meet someone who's willing
to embrace all of her pain.
Someone reassuring and generous.
I want to find
a nice partner for Seung-hyo too.
He was lonely
for a long time because of me.
Hey, let's introduce them
to good people if we find any.
Let's do that.
[both] For real!
-For real, okay?
-Yeah, for real!
-Find good ones at the foreign ministry!
-For real.
Okay.
Hey, they left to buy alcohol,
but why aren't they back?
Good question.
Are they brewing it themselves?
-Did they go to karaoke?
-Those lunatics.
They must be crazy.
Geun-sik mentioned his favorite song.
He was talking about it earlier.
-[Hye-suk] Where is it?
-[Mi-suk] That fool.
-The basement!
-[Hye-suk] Really?
Let's hurry!
What's that?
Tae-hui kept her word.
[giggles] Time for the unboxing!
Right. You sold me for a bowl.
[exclaims softly]
Seung-hyo, I might be a traitor to you,
but this was worth it. Look.
Ta-da! [gasps]
-Wow, it's beautiful.
-[chuckles softly]
-Benedict Yoon?
-Yes?
-You like it that much?
-Yes, of course.
I'm going to hand this down
as a family heirloom.
My future descendant will be
on Authentic Masterpieces with this,
and it'll be valued
at 100 billion won! [gasps]
I should take a picture and show my wife.
[chuckles softly]
Take this too.
That's yours.
Gosh. Mine's bigger.
[chuckles softly]
[Tae-hui] In a traditional
wedding ceremony,
the bride and groom use
a hollowed gourd split in two
to share ceremonial wine.
[pleasant music playing]
They say it symbolizes how one
is the perfect match for the other.
It's my gift to you and Seok-ryu.
I wish you both happiness.
[pop song playing]
PRINCESS
[sighs] Boring.
[groans softly]
[breeze blowing]
Hey.
What are you doing?
What do you think?
Were you always this kind?
[pop song continues playing]
Did you think
your boyfriend was cold-hearted?
Boyfriend, my foot. Are you crazy?
Wait.
If I'm not your boyfriend, then what am I?
I mean, you are. But…
I don't know.
[exclaims softly]
It's just awkward to say that word.
Did you make that house too?
Yeah.
[Seok-ryu] No, stay away.
He's hurt, so he's still sensitive.
I think you're the one who's sensitive.
[sneezes]
[coughs]
Why did you bring in a cat
if you're allergic to them?
It was hurt. I couldn't just abandon it.
You said you were
out of money for the snack bar.
Was it for the medical expenses?
[muffled] Yeah, my hands are shaking
from chocolate withdrawal.
But what do I do?
It has nowhere to go after it heals.
The weather's getting hot. Don't touch.
[cat meowing]
[Seok-ryu] I'm so worried.
[pop song continues playing]
Hey, you sure you're doing it right?
The roof has to be sturdy
to keep the rain and snow out.
Do you want to make it?
[Seok-ryu] Hey,
the walls have to be sturdy too.
Winter will come right after summer.
You'll get diabetes that way.
I'll worry about myself.
Wow!
-Great job!
-Hey!
-Hey! Why you…
-[exclaiming]
Come on!
[Seok-ryu] I'm sorry! Sorry!
MADE BY
CHOI SEUNG-HYO
I'm continuing to reconstruct it.
I think the cats that use this
are descendants of the one we knew.
-They have the same coat pattern.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-I want to see.
-Forget it, okay?
-[sniffles]
Your allergies are about to flare up.
Isn't it a tragedy?
I love cats, but I can't touch them.
The cat house I made back then
was the first house I ever made.
I built it so poorly.
But I was proud of it.
I created a home
for a living thing with my own hands.
I think…
that's when I wanted
to become an architect.
[Seok-ryu gasps]
That means that cat was your first client.
No.
It was you.
I made it for you.
You were worried about the cat.
[pleasant music playing]
I wanted you to be happy.
[stomach growling]
[Seung-hyo coughs]
-[stomach growling]
-[coughs]
[chuckles] Let's go eat.
Let's go.
[Seung-hyo] I'm starving.
[Seok-ryu] Why haven't you eaten
anything so late?
[Seung-hyo] Where should we go?
[Seok-ryu] My home.
Your mom made a whole pot of soup
before going on the trip.
It's either this or curry. Eat up.
[slurps]
-I'm sorry about before.
-[Seung-hyo clears throat]
What are you talking about?
I'm the one who caused the problem.
I'm sorry.
No, I was too harsh.
Seeing you two together turned me
into someone petty and cheap.
I'm the one who's done
more unpleasant things though.
[chuckles softly]
It's not great sharing
our past relationships with each other.
Not knowing is one thing,
but knowing makes it hard.
No wonder it's an unwritten rule.
From now on,
I won't hide anything from you.
I won't get involved with her
like that again.
No, I won't leave any room for it.
But…
I was honestly happy to see you jealous.
-What?
-Not a lot.
Just a little bit.
-[Seok-ryu clears throat]
-Still, let's not fight.
It felt awful to fight with you.
I couldn't focus at work,
and I was frustrated.
This was a first for me.
It was?
Yeah.
I didn't want to be someone
who was consumed by a relationship.
It felt so unfamiliar.
I didn't feel like myself.
Hey, that's normal.
How long have you been pretending
to be cool?
I don't know.
I'm sure of one thing.
You make me feel warm on the inside.
[harp music playing]
Hey, I borrowed a lot of comic books.
They're in my room.
Let's eat this quickly and read them.
Yeah, sure.
[amusing music playing]
[Seung-hyo clears throat]
[Seok-ryu] What are you doing?
Why are you looking around
like it's your first time in here?
No, it's just…
[clears throat]
Ta-da! I borrowed a whole series for you.
What is this?
What do you think?
It's Princess. It's your favorite.
Well… Here it is. This is what I wanted.
The book you wanted…
was Princess?
Oh, that.
I just made that up.
What?
To be honest,
I went to the comic book room to see you.
What?
Well, after being like that back then,
why do you treat me this way now?
[music fades]
What did I do?
You don't seem that interested in me.
Me?
You can't look me in the eyes,
and you act indifferent.
You treat me worse than how you did
before we started dating.
Well… I mean, that's because…
Well… [clears throat]
I was just really nervous.
It was because I was nervous.
[mellow music playing]
[pop song playing]
How can you sleep
in this kind of situation?
Why am I so nervous? This is so strange.
[Seok-ryu] So this is what
a blueprint looks like.
Yeah.
[heart thumping]
Really? Then I'll just buy a drink.
Okay.
[pop song continues playing]
I'd waited for so long.
But when you're actually next to me…
[exhales]
My mind goes blank,
and I don't know what to do.
I thought…
you were being…
so calm.
Now that we're dating,
maybe you didn't see me as attractive.
That's what I thought.
I got anxious and worked up by myself.
That's not it at all.
It's the opposite.
I like you so much.
I don't know how to treat you.
[song ends]
Let's take these downstairs.
You don't want to read them here?
I don't think we should stay here.
Why not?
I'm having bad thoughts.
What bad thoughts?
Thoughts I shouldn't be thinking.
Cheap and crude thoughts.
Unhealthy thoughts.
I used to like unhealthy junk food.
Powdered candy, taffy, and dalgona.
-Crunch balls, corn nuts, and slushies.
-[Seok-ryu] Yeah.
So go ahead.
Think bad thoughts.
What about bad deeds?
You can do those too.
[pleasant music playing]
[pleasant music continues playing]
[pushes switch]
PUPPY LOVE
REAL LOVE
[upbeat music playing]
[pop song playing]
Subtitle translation by: Sue Mounce