CHAPTER 4:
STARS ARE BORN OUT OF CHAOS
-Jeon Ji-min.
-Here!
-Oh Ji-ho.
-Kim Ga-yeong.
-Here!
He's taking attendance
before introducing himself?
Who does he think he is?
Kim Dan-ji.
Here!
-Kim Yeong-jae.
-Here!
-Eun Ha-su.
-Here.
I hear you won gold at the KMO?
Yes.
KMO?
What's that?
No idea.
How was it?
Not that difficult.
Why is he talking to her
and only calling others' names?
Are they best friends or something?
-Oh A-rin.
-Here.
-Choi Yu-mi.
-Yeo Eui-ju.
-Here.
-Yeo Eui-ju?
-Yeo Eui-ju!
-Here!
-Choi Go-ya.
-Here.
Choi Ji-a.
Choi Ji-a?
Here.
I am Mr. Ga, your new homeroom teacher.
-So handsome!
Math is a discipline
that knows no falsehood.
Euclid's Elements begins like this.
"A point is that which has no part."
Isn't that beautiful?
Points connect to form lines.
Lines move to create planes.
Planes form boundaries that make solids.
And solids
exist within time and space.
In other words,
math is the language that explains
how the universe exists.
That's why to understand mathematics
is to understand the universe
you were born into.
I think of you as stars in that universe.
Each of you shining,
each with your own world.
When a star is born,
countless clouds of dust
surround it so densely
you can't even see an inch ahead.
That's why people say
stars are born out of chaos.
You're probably the same.
-Oh, that's so deep.
-How cool is that?
In the midst of that chaos,
some of you may have figured out
what you like, what you don't,
what you're good at
and what you want to do.
But for those that haven't,
I hope the rest of this semester
will be the time you find it.
If you're having difficulty,
I'll help you.
But it must be you yourself
that takes that final step.
What the heck?
All that guff about stars
and the universe to say that?
His pride in math is unbelievable.
What a nerdy math geek.
Yeo Eui-ju.
Yes, sir.
What score did you get in math
in the last mock exam?
Why is he asking that out of the blue?
It was…
I can't hear you.
Four…
Forty…
Four points, sir.
Four points?
If that's all you got…
you ought to go back to grade school.
Come with me to the teachers' office.
Class dismissed.
Why me?
EPISODE 2
Sir.
I really didn't film you.
PHOTO GALLERY
See for yourself.
This is my video folder.
And this is my recently deleted folder.
See, it's empty.
See?
Is that not why I'm here?
Is it because
I came into the homeroom after you?
Then…
His pride in math is unbelievable.
What a nerdy math geek.
If you perhaps heard what I said earlier
I was just upset about my phone, and…
I'm sorry, sir.
I must have been out of my mind.
-How could I have done that?
-Enough.
How could you only get four points?
I don't even want to open my math book.
It's difficult and no fun.
I don't even get the point of studying it.
I just hate it.
Difficult?
No fun?
You just hate it?
Yes.
What is math?
Math is
math.
How can you be so sure you hate math
when you don't even know what it is?
Math is where philosophy has blossomed.
And what is philosophy?
It's thinking precisely.
Thinking!
Why do mathematicians prove things
through logic?
Why are numbers the root of everything?
Have you considered such things?
-No.
-Exactly. So how can you say you hate it?
So, to reflect on your ignorance of math
and reconsider its origins,
I want you to write a letter to Euclid.
Twenty pages. By the final bell tomorrow.
Twenty pages?
Go. And send Choi Ji-a in.
But, sir!
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
What's your next class?
-Hello.
-Good morning.
I'm sorry about Mr. Ga
having a go at you earlier.
He can be a bit prickly at times.
Sometimes he can be childish and immature,
but he's not a bad guy at heart.
I see.
Sir, that's not the issue here.
You're being gaslit right now.
There's no need to defend him like that.
This is me.
It was nice to meet you.
He's such an angel.
Why does an angel like that
hang out with a demon like him?
Ji-a.
Choi Ji-a!
Hey, wake up.
I said wake up.
Mr. Ga wants to see you.
What did he say?
He wants me to write an essay.
Twenty pages at that.
Because you mocked him?
No.
Because I got four points in math.
Why were you late?
Even if you overslept or didn't want
to come, there must be a reason.
Coming to school on time
is also a kind of promise.
Be on time from now on.
And if you can't, please explain why.
-Yes, sir.
-Off you go.
Oh, you've been lumbered with her, I see.
With kids from the shelter, just be
grateful if they don't cause any trouble.
Don't wear yourself out
trying to establish your authority.
Just get through the year
without incident.
That's your best bet.
CHAPTER 5:
YOU'RE SOFT AND SQUISHY
"Our hall, is a hall of love,
touched by old customs."
"Sun, lower your crystal eyes,
which are like those of a gentle doe."
"And I will smooth my hair,
which is tangled like a lion's mane."
From now on, when I'm with Dong-ju,
the girl we loved back in the day
will be me.
"…before the bright flame…"
Get your hands down sooner, okay?
Eui-ju!
You got this!
Sorry.
Give her a hand!
"Pleased to meet you."
-All right.
-Mr. Noh!
You look like Luciel of Else.
-Right!
-No way!
I was actually scouted
on the street back in college.
-Really?
-Tell us more!
Didn't I tell you this?
-Please tell us!
So what happened was…
It comes out like this.
As I said, x minus y isn't zero.
And y minus z isn't zero either.
Try and solve it.
What a jerk!
…the greatest value of x…
Great work today, guys.
-Thank you, sir.
Where's Choi Ji-a?
She skips homeroom
and leaves straight after class.
Yeo Eui-ju and the next two will clean up.
Why?
-The rotation should start from one.
-Dismissed.
-Thank you, Mr. Ga.
I should've just kept my mouth shut.
That hurts. Can you be more gentle?
How nervous were you to get this stiff?
Hey!
It was so hard writing on the board.
I suddenly stiffened up.
Oh, boy.
How's your tummy?
Okay.
How was your class?
Don't ask. I just want to go home.
That feels great.
That arm is fine.
I'm just touching you.
You're soft and squishy.
"You're soft and squishy"?
Don't you think the female students
are braver than the boys?
Tell me about it.
They were staring so blatantly
I didn't know where to look
and ended up losing my train of thought.
It was so embarrassing.
The mighty Yoon Dong-ju
trembling in front of his students.
-Dude, they'd faint if they found out.
-Let go of me.
Amazing!
Why can't I come up
with dialogue like that?
"You're soft and squishy."
Mind your own business.
Why do I feel like such a pervert?
-Hello.
-Hey, you're here.
Are you doing okay?
Sorry for asking to switch
with no warning.
Don't sweat it.
Take this medicine.
My mom gave it to me and it's great.
Thanks so much.
I'll do your shift on Thursday.
It's fine. I can do it then too.
I have something to do.
Okay.
Then I'm off.
PAZER WEB NOVEL PORTAL
BEST WEB NOVEL RANKINGS
I'm so envious.
When am I going to see my name here?
I WAKE UP AND FIND MYSELF HIS SECRETARY
"When I opened my eyes,
I had become that guy's secretary."
"Reincarnated as a slave
to an evil family"?
Are regression stories all the rage?
No, I tried something similar
and it was a flop.
Shall I go full on for tears?
Obsession and terminal illness?
College senior and junior?
CEO and secretary?
I've done it all before.
Or…
You're soft and squishy.
Friends?
Childhood friends?
I'm bored.
I'm bored, bored, bored.
Jerk.
Stop it.
The pen's a jerk too.
No, no.
Stop fantasizing about your teachers!
Don't do it.
It's wrong.
I'd like to check this out.
Hold on.
CHAPTER 6:
MY FIRST SNOW… IS A BLIZZARD
Hey, turn that off!
That darn alarm.
Someone wake him up.
Okay.
Hey, Da-ju!
-Noh Da-ju!
-Yes?
Wake up.
Eat your toast while it's still hot.
Is it crispy?
Hurry up!
Is that an alarm or a siren?
Turn it down a bit.
You ignore it every morning.
It's not crispy.
You should have toasted it more. Crispier!
Then don't eat it.
What's with the racket every morning?
What's the key to living together?
Don't disturb your roommates.
It's common sense.
I can't even have an alarm
in my own house?
Can I have your attention, please?
You're my tenants.
This kind of attitude is problematic.
You should be more considerate of me.
You've got the biggest room.
Whenever something happens,
it's "tenant this, tenant that."
Isn't that a crappy thing to do?
-I'm off.
-Crappy?
Did you just call me crappy?
Finish your breakfast!
You carpool with me every morning.
Pay for it.
What the heck? Your car's a junk.
-We're leaving in ten so hurry up and eat.
-Pay me 50 million won.
MURIM GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
The crags and oceans in this poem,
what do you think they mean?
Literally, they just mean
mountain and sea.
But here…
CHARACTERS
KOREAN LITERATURE
Right.
SONG OF THE GREEN MOUNTAIN
Also, the word night in verse four,
and stone in verse five.
DEPENDENT
Has a dependent personality.
Bit of a pushover. Doe-eyed.
KOREAN LITERATURE
DEPENDENT, PUSHOVER, DOE-EYED
We use these words all the time.
But in this poem,
they all have separate other meanings.
Let's leave it here for today. Well done.
-Thank you.
Watch and learn.
Mr. Yoon!
Yes?
I got you a chalk holder.
Since we still use blackboards, I thought
you might get chalk on your hands.
Thank you.
Go-ya?
Yes?
Thanks for this.
Hey.
Why? What's wrong?
I think
I'm up against a formidable opponent.
My first snow…
is a blizzard.
Loyal, dependable type.
Beefcake with a bulldozer personality.
Reticent but sweet to his man.
An obsessive top.
-Good morning.
Good morning.
Today, you'll be doing a long-distance run
for the basic fitness test.
Five laps.
-No way!
-Mr. Jung!
The quicker you run,
the more you can rest.
Line up in rows of twelve.
-No way.
-Sir!
Ready!
CRUSH THE CSAT
I'm just touching you.
You're soft and squishy.
What are you doing?
Put some effort in! You got this!
Faster! Move!
Run! You got this!
Faster!
Come on! Faster!
Harder!
Faster!
Stop it, Eui-ju!
No!
Stop it!
That's it!
Whoever wins, I don't care!
Are you okay?
I asked if you're okay.
Yes, I'm fine.
Are you a runner?
No.
Want to join after-school sports?
Give it a shot. Wednesdays at five.
We'll focus on the practical exam.
Drop by my office later
for an application form.
You have real talent.
Sir, I'm going to go wash my face.
You're crazy.
Why is my heart beating so fast?
No way.
You have real talent.
No.
It can't be!
It's beating like that thinking of him
as a character in a novel.
That's all.
CHAPTER 7:
WE WERE FRIENDS
CHARACTERS
KOREAN LITERATURE: DEPENDENT PERSONALITY
PE: LOYAL AND DEPENDABLE TYPE
But there's no obstacle
standing in their way.
Do I need a third guy?
PE, KANG TAE-HA
KOREAN LITERATURE, CHOI YOON
Han Jae-min, who studied abroad,
as the third wheel?
No.
He's too lightweight.
He can be a bit prickly at times.
Sometimes he can be childish and immature,
but he's not a bad guy at heart.
If any footage of this turns up online,
I'll make you regret it.
A regretful top?
The kind that acts like an asshole
and later regrets it?
That's him to a tee.
The asshole of a math genius
turned down offers of professorship
from every Ivy League school.
Why would he do that?
To go to college with his buddy
who majored in Korean literature?
He treated him badly
but secretly liked him?
So, is this how it goes?
The Korean teacher had a crush on the math
teacher ever since they were little.
Attracted by his bad boy charm.
Seeing that,
the PE teacher had his heart broken.
Math, never realizing how much he cared
for Korean, treated him terribly,
and didn't realize his true feelings
until it was too late.
Not wanting to admit it,
he deliberately avoids Korean…
But then PE comes back
as an obsessive top.
Regretful Math clings to Korean,
trying to win him back! Cue tears!
Amazing!
This dynamic is amazing.
This ship…
will sail.
WE WERE FRIENDS
EPISODE 1
IMUK
AS DAWN BEGAN TO BREAK…
AS USUAL, CHOI YOON WAS THE FIRST TO WAKE
SEEING YOON SOBBING,
TAE-HA CAN'T HOLD BACK
Are you dumb?
Huh?
What's so great about that asshole
who always treats you badly?
He can be a bit prickly at times.
Sometimes he can be childish and immature,
but he's not a bad guy at heart.
He's not doing it deliberately,
so don't get the wrong idea.
HE'S JUST USING YOU
He's just using you.
He knows you're kind,
so he just does whatever he wants.
I don't care.
Still, you're the only one
who worries about me.
You're a great friend, Tae-ha.
Friend?
Yeah, my best friend.
YOON'S EYES CRINKLE AS HE SMILES
That made me mad.
Like you were telling me
to keep my distance.
TAE-HA PUSHES YOON AWAY
What about Ju Si-on?
What is he to you?
TAE-HA'S VOICE TREMBLED
WITH JEALOUSY AND FEAR
Si-on…
CHOI YOON HESITATED
What the heck?
Why is this going so well?
I shouldn't be doing this.
They're my teachers.
No.
No!
It's a novel. Besides, I changed all
their names so maybe no one will realize?
I've never written so seamlessly.
The characters, the dialogue…
Still, this is wrong.
What if someone finds out?
SUBMIT A NEW PROJECT
But my writing is so good.
WE WERE FRIENDS, EPISODE 1
SAVE DRAFT
Hey, Yoon!
What are you doing here?
I thought you wanted
to take Discrete Math together.
Yeah, let's go.
Stay away!
BEYOND EUI-JU'S IMAGINATION
TAE-HA, YOON AND THEN…
Okay, let's go!
What's going on?
AND HAN JAE-MIN
Subtitle: Paul Carver