=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 3=
(He must've killed many,)
(even more than these warriors.)
Since when did the General
become so formidable?
These moves are so unfamiliar.
I've never seen him use them.
How Strange.
This is absolutely bizarre.
Xiaoxiao,
the General wouldn't
have noticed us, right?
He wouldn't.
What is going on?
Commandant Wu,
you think the nobles from Nandu
are just idling their days away.
(The gap between those two)
(is too wide.)
Judging from his experience...
But I'm not one of them.
He could never have such skills.
I know you've never respected me.
Back on the battlefield,
you never made things hard for me.
Where did he learn that?
But now, we face a formidable foe.
You understand the stakes here.
You were displeased
with my strict discipline
because you care for your men
and thought I was being too harsh.
But Commandant Wu,
you know the gap
between the foe and us.
Without strict discipline,
they'll only die faster.
A win is a win.
Cut the nonsense.
I am outmatched.
I accept my defeat.
You can promote
whoever you want.
Commandant Xia,
thank Commandant Wu
and Captain Han for their blessing.
Thank you, Commandant Wu,
Captain Han.
Alright.
If there's nothing else,
I'll take my leave.
Please wait.
(Strict Enforcement)
We are all here today.
Gentlemen,
will you share this drink with me,
so we may retake Yuzhou one day?
Yuzhou?
60 years ago,
North Chong invaded the north.
Heaven is ruthless;
the Guanhe River is frozen.
The North Chong Army marches south,
burning and pillaging,
taking both Yuzhou and Liangzhou.
Though we've retaken Liangzhou,
the people of Yuzhou and the north
still suffer under their cruel rule,
struggling to survive.
Commandant Wu,
will you join me
to save the people from this misery?
Is this the real reason
you called me here?
If I hadn't spread the rumor
about the promotion,
would you fight by my side
with your high standards?
Alright.
Then let's prove it
on the battlefield.
Xiaoxiao,
why am I getting so excited?
Then I should send you
to become a general.
Really?
Never mind.
Why?
Because I want
to always stay with you.
Xu,
your martial arts...
Just a past encounter.
(Grace Upon the Masses)
Strange.
Seed shells are falling from the sky?
(Liangzhou Government Office)
(Liang)
Captain Meng.
What is it?
I didn't know the General
would promote me beforehand.
I thought he valued you more.
Is a Great Liang Commandant
so weak?
You see?
This is the real Xia Qingsheng.
And the true Commandant Xia.
But you were hurt saving me before.
That was a personal matter.
I can't beat you in battle.
That's official business.
Personal and official must not mix.
But you'd better be careful.
I'll catch up to you soon.
After all, you're the only one
I don't dislike other than Xu.
(7th day of the 11th month)
(Liang)
A true man bears his blade
to defend this land until he dies!
The General is truly bold
to send 70% of the troops
to attack Yuzhou.
(Guanhe River)
By now,
they should've crossed the river.
Once they cross
the Guanhe River,
does it mean we have won?
Who told you crossing the river
means victory?
One day,
I want to be
just like the General,
so I can fight on the battlefield,
protect our country,
and avenge my father.
Do you want to follow Duan Xu?
I've looked around the city.
Everyone is struggling.
There aren't any families
worth entrusting you to.
Duan Xu isn't a bad choice.
I helped him read the wind.
I can ask him to take you in.
His family is prominent.
If you follow him,
you'll never go hungry.
You might even earn an official title.
Xiaoxiao,
are you abandoning me?
I just want to stay with you.
I can eat less.
I don't need any fruits
or snacks.
That won't do.
As I told you from the start,
I'll only take care of you for a while.
(We walk different paths.)
(You can't follow a spirit forever.)
Besides,
do you think
you can just follow Duan Xu?
He might just die in Shuozhou
and never come back.
Xiaoxiao,
the General is a good man.
Please don't let him die.
You just reminded me.
(This time,)
(Duan Xu will surely die.)
(Then I can get the Deliverance.)
(I have always been fair.)
(So, I won't take it for nothing.)
Xiaoxiao,
you're so powerful
and can do magic tricks.
Please save the General!
Please?
Save him?
Alright.
I'll use the highest standard
in my hometown to save him.
When we spoke with the neighbors,
they said
the only musician here had passed away.
His widow
is named...
What was her name again?
Ms. Song.
Yes, invite her over for melon seeds
and ask her
to bring their Ruan.
Go then.
Enemies!
Light the signal fire!
(Spirit Aura, ascend.)
(Go.)
Foxy,
since you're the rare
Deliverance master in 300 years,
I'll grant you a tune.
Fengyi,
what is it?
Surely, I'll report
the situation to you.
Duan Xu deserves
to be the Deliverance master.
He's been renowned for his talent.
He has an eidetic memory.
At the age of 12,
he was sent to serve his grandmother.
During that time,
his essays often circulated
(Scholars must focus)
and were famous in Daizhou.
But compared to that,
I found something unusual.
When he was 19,
on his way back to Nandu from Daizhou,
he encountered bandits.
His attendants and servants
were all killed.
He alone survived
and trekked all the way to Nandu.
Since then,
he's settled down in Nandu.
Coincidentally,
shortly after he returned to Nandu,
his grandmother passed away.
So, all the people he knew
over the seven years in Daizhou
are all gone?
Yes, interesting, isn't it?
For a 19-year-old scholar
like him,
how could he single-handedly
fight off a gang of bandits?
Perhaps
the real Duan Xu
died alongside his servants
at the age of 19.
(From 12 to 19)
(is when a mortal child
changes the most.)
(During this time,)
(even if he was replaced
by someone else,)
(no one would necessarily notice.)
(I found you,)
(Duan Xu.)
You are a spent force.
Just a dying struggle.
I don't even need to strike you myself.
Let me play a dirge for you.
A cornered beast still fights.
Interesting.
Let me see how long you can hold out.
General!
Xu!
You asked me to read the wind.
Aren't you crossing the river
to attack Shuozhou?
Must you go?
Only by seeking peace
through battle
can Great Liang
and North Chong lay down their arms
and embrace peace.
This is my deepest wish.
If possible,
please help me achieve it.
In four days,
on the 8th of the 11th month,
east wind at You hour.
(Liang)
Red birds are to burn all living beings.
Attack!
Fire arrows!
Reinforcements are here!
Our reinforcements are here!
Attack!
Attack! Attack!
Red birds are to burn
all living beings.
Authentic Chong language.
Red birds are to burn
all living beings.
He's surely not the old Duan Xu.
(Born into a family of civil officials,)
(you possess superb martial arts;)
(aiming to be a Chief Councillor,)
(you speak fluent Chong language.)
(You claim to be Duan Xu,)
(but those
who could prove your identity)
(are long dead.)
(How many secrets are you hiding?)
The battle is won.
It seems
I'll have to wait
to play the dirge for Foxy.
Red birds are to burn all living beings.
Red birds are to burn
all living beings.
Red birds are to burn...
Things are getting interesting.
Perhaps letting you live in this world
would be more entertaining.
Great victory in Shuozhou!
The Tabai Army crosses the Guanhe River
for the first time in 30 years!
Great victory in Shuozhou!
The Tabai Army crosses the Guanhe River
for the first time in 30 years!
We crossed the Guanhe River!
The Great Liang Army won!
We won! We won!
(Honor the Worthy)
Xiaoxiao!
The General won!
We've taken Shuozhou City!
Xiaoxiao!
The General won!
We've taken Shuozhou City!
- Xiaoxiao!
- Alright, I get it.
Also, Xiaoxiao,
the General sent someone to pick us up!
Let's go now.
Captain Han Lingqiu of the Tabai Army
requests to see Miss He.
(Liangzhou Government Office)
Miss He,
the General has a message for you.
Shuozhou has fallen.
Your insight from the wind
contributed greatly.
Thus,
he humbly asks you
to keep reading the wind for us
and head to Shuozhou.
The General knows you are delicate
and averse to bloodshed
and worldly affairs.
He promises
to spare you from hardship
and ensure your safety.
He won't force you.
What do you think?
Foxy,
you're quite clever
to know my likes and dislikes.
Since the General invited me,
I'd be honored to accept.
I'll go pack our bags.
Since you want to play,
I'm happy to oblige.
(Shuozhou City)
- Be quick.
- Yes, General.
The supplies the enemy left
have all been confiscated.
Inventory and add them to the armory.
And set aside a portion
for the citizens.
The captive citizens of Great Liang
must be registered
and properly settled.
Yes.
Slow down.
Xu,
by now,
Captain Han
should've reached Liangzhou
and picked up Miss He.
They should've met by now.
Captain Han is acting suspiciously.
If he really is a spy,
wouldn't Miss He be in danger?
Xiaoxiao,
it seems we've reached
North Chong's occupied territory.
Xiaoxiao,
what is that pattern?
Flame pattern.
The symbol of North Chong.
What's wrong?
Feeling unwell?
Xiaoxiao,
my grandfather said
our ancestral home was in Shuozhou.
When he was still alive,
North Chong attacked us.
He took our whole family
and fled south to Liangzhou.
At that time, we had
no home or food.
My grandfather said
that in his lifetime,
and even in mine,
we might never return to Shuozhou.
But today, I've returned.
I want to travel even further.
(How pitiful of mortals.)
(The journey of their entire lifetime)
(is but a mere few steps.)
Mr. Lin,
thanks for letting me stay here
these past few days.
No need to be so polite.
We, the people of Shuozhou,
have longed for Great Liang's army
for 30 years.
(Lin Jun, Shuozhou merchant)
We hope
to be Great Liang citizens again.
- General Duan.
These two gentlemen
are members of the Shuozhou guild.
They came today
to represent the guild
and the people of the city
to ask you a question.
Please speak freely.
Then,
I'll be completely frank.
You took over Shuozhou this time
through a surprise attack.
Now, you're surrounded by enemies.
If the citizens welcome you now
and become slaves to North Chong again,
they'll surely be slaughtered
out of anger.
Liangzhou's tragedy will repeat itself.
So, I want to ask you:
How long do you plan
to stay this time?
How long will you protect its people?
Rest assured, everyone.
For 30 years,
Great Liang never forgot
Shuozhou's people.
The Tabai Army has crossed the river,
and we won't take a single step back.
We'll live and die
with Shuozhou's people.
We know defending the city is hard.
Since you've decided
to protect the people of this city,
we will certainly do our utmost
without any hesitation.
We too will do our utmost
It has been 30 years.
We finally crossed the river again.
North Chong held Shuozhou
for 30 years.
We took it suddenly,
so they won't just let it go.
Their Fenglai Force is watching
from Yuzhou in the south.
Awo'erqi is leading
200,000 soldiers
right toward us.
Our troops are now exhausted;
we are short on rations.
The city's people refuse to cooperate.
Can we still hold the city?
We must.
For 30 years,
the people of Great Liang
were enslaved and slaughtered
by North Chong.
It's not that they reject our rescue.
They are just terrified.
They fear this slim hope
is just fleeting.
So, we must protect
this hope for them.
Ambush! Ambush!
On guard!
Hold them off!
Xiaoxiao!
Are we there yet?
An ambush by North Chong.
They have at least 200 men.
We only have a few dozen.
We're doomed this time.
Will the General come save us?
We're still far from Shuozhou.
He's too far to help.
If we're caught,
I'll just read the wind for them.
I'm reading it anyway,
no matter who it's for.
Right?
You'll help them?
They drove my grandfather
from Shuozhou to Liangzhou
and killed my father in Liangzhou.
Why is it always them
bullying us?
And you'll help them?
I'd rather die than help them!
A remote path like this
shouldn't have so many ambushers.
Foxy,
I knew getting on your carriage
would mean trouble.
Miss He!
It's dangerous! Please go inside!
On guard!
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪