(Previously) And the director
of this year's stage play is…
Jack!
I'm making Romeo &amp; Romeo.
I will retell the story.
As for the lead actors…
we're holding auditions.
Oh, hey, are you interested
in joining our faculty play?
Me?
You'll get paid too.
I will?
Shit!
Shit! I'm sorry.
How should I make it up to you?
Don't worry.
You will surely get the chance to.
There's no point in holding auditions.
The Romeo role is mine. No question.
Your method won't work.
We won't know…
unless we try. Right?
Hey.
We barely get any time together,
yet you keep staring at
that book instead of my face.
Hey.
Dean!
I was just about to get an idea.
What kind of idea?
No matter how many times you read it,
the ending never changes.
Romeo and Juliet still die.
No.
If you were Juliet, what would you do?
If I were Juliet?
If anyone tried to stand
between us, I'd fight.
Until my last breath.
What about you?
Would you fight for me?
I guess so.
And if I couldn't win,
I'd just take you and run.
Sounds good?
Fine. No problem with that.
Hey.
I want to reinterpret Romeo and Juliet.
Make it about two men
from families divided by their beliefs.
But this time, they have a happy ending,
where they get to stay together.
What do you think?
You're right.
Why can't people in love be together?
A project this good,
you have to let me play.
Mm.
I'll direct. You'll act.
You're both my boyfriend
and my favorite actor.
Hm?
Here.
What's this?
Your anniversary gift.
And you're just handing it to me like this?
Yes. Just like this.
Happy first anniversary.
Let me put it on you.
Thanks a lot.
Hey, Dean.
What are you doing?
People can see.
Are you scared they will?
What are you doing now?
Hey, stop it.
Dean, I said stop.
That's enough.
Oh, come on.
"Only Friends: Dream On"
(Episode 2)
Can't we cuddle a little longer?
No.
I have a casting to
get to. I need to hurry.
Why do you still need to cast?
You already had your Romeo.
Many times.
I mean the other one.
For the Romeo you're aiming for,
I haven't decided yet.
I gave you my body.
Am I really getting nothing in return?
We're just exes hooking up.
No feelings involved.
How cruel.
Hey.
What are you doing?
You can't post that, Dean.
It was just for me.
Why?
Why don't you unblock me?
Then you'll know whether I post it or not.
I'm not posting it.
I was just messing with him.
Why do you care what other people think?
Isn't what we feel for each other enough?
Or are you not feeling it?
Cut.
Ah… Arnold.
Have you ever hit on someone before?
Hit on someone?
I have, kind of.
But most of the time, people approach me.
Ah, I see.
How about you forget the script this time
and improvise for me?
Timmy, help him.
Are you crazy?
I can't act.
I'll make a fool of myself. No way.
Tua, don't laugh.
Go help Arnold with the improvisation.
What?
Go on.
- Me?
- Yes.
Give me the script.
- Hey.
- Just go.
- For real?
- Yes.
You've got this, buddy.
Okay.
This time.
You can touch his arms, hold his hands.
Do anything to make him melt.
Are you serious?
Yes, I am.
Whenever you're ready, Arnold.
Tua.
How long have we known each other?
Three years.
We're going into our fourth this year.
Mm.
Have you ever counted how many times
you've sat behind me on my bike?
Who would even count that?
42 times.
Huh?
You counted?
From a guy who forgets his own birthday?
Because it's you. That's why I remember.
And if you look closely, you'll see
I've never let anyone else ride with me.
Only you.
At first, I hesitated about telling you.
But we're graduating soon.
I don't want to miss this chance.
I like you, Tua.
What about you?
How do you feel about me?
Uh…
I…
Cut!
Was that okay?
I don't think Jack knows.
Maybe it's just a coincidence.
I hope I didn't blush so
much that people noticed.
I wasn't blushing.
I just felt ticklish, having
to confess to my friend.
Tua should understand.
Honestly, I'm more nervous
about the audition results.
I've got my two Romeos.
All right, everyone. Listen up.
This is the moment
we've all been waiting for.
The audition results for our faculty play.
The first Romeo goes to…
Arnold!
Hey!
You did it.
Thank you so much, Tua.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
And the other Romeo is…
Dean!
Raffy.
It's okay.
I can give you a friend role instead.
I'm sorry, Jack.
I think you should find
someone else for the part.
I'll help out behind the scenes instead.
Gosh.
The play hasn't even started,
and someone's already quitting.
Which god do I need to
pray to for this play to survive?
Dang it.
If you're here to get under
my skin, I'm not in the mood.
You're this worked up
over not getting the role?
Isn't being part of the play good enough?
You don't have to quit.
I want the lead, not some supporting role.
Or you're really this furious
because you won't get to be near Jack.
I'm furious right now because I'm near you.
Ooh.
Actually, I came because
we need to go buy a new DJ controller.
You spilled a drink all over mine.
Why do I have to go?
Just tell me the price. I'll
transfer the money right now.
You wasted my time that day.
Today's your turn to waste yours.
Or did you not mean what you said?
You don't actually want
to take responsibility.
What do you want, then?
How about a swim race?
First to finish three laps wins.
And if I win, you come with me.
And if I win?
Not happening.
Movie ticket, please.
How many?
Two, please.
Two for 600 baht. Please scan here.
Sure.
All done.
Did you follow me?
I did not.
I wanted to watch La La Land, too.
Besides,
this is our favorite movie, right?
Thank you for choosing me.
I chose you because of your talent.
It had nothing to do with
the sex the other day.
Okay, Jack.
I'll try to believe you.
If I chose based on sex,
I wouldn't have just two Romeos.
Hey, Jack.
Are you here to see...
I came alone
and ran into a friend.
Are you here alone, Ice?
Mm.
Should we… watch it together?
And tonight…
let's catch up.
Who's that?
Another one of my Romeos.
I'll see you inside.
One cup of cocoa, please.
Ice, right?
Yes.
I'm Dean. A friend of Jack's.
Do you come here often?
Not really.
I just love this movie,
so I'm here for a rewatch.
I love this movie too.
But I like to watch it here.
It gives better vibes
than watching at home.
Here's your cocoa.
Thank you.
I'll see you inside then.
Okay.
Shit!
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to.
I'm sorry.
That's enough!
Damn it.
If I don't get what I want,
nobody does.
Hey.
This seat is taken.
No, it isn't.
I don't see anyone sitting here.
He's coming.
He's not.
I saw him leave.
I guess he had an emergency.
You don't have to look.
Just watch the movie.
A favorite movie should
be seen with a favorite ex.
Movie time.
What's that face?
Nothing. I'm just a little on edge.
I don't know if I'll fit in
with everyone in the play.
Don't worry. They're super chill.
Just be ready to answer one question.
I'm sure they'll ask where
your name comes from.
“My dad loves The Terminator.”
“He's a huge fan of Arnold Schwarzenegger.”
“That's how I got this name.”
Tua, stop it.
“Talk to the hand.”
Quit that.
“I'll be back.”
I'm poking your eyes out.
I'm just teasing.
But there's one person. Jack.
He's a bit strict.
Just be patient and follow his lead.
Mm.
Jack also told me…
there are scenes where I
have to hug and kiss Dean.
Why?
Are you worried about kissing a guy?
No. I have no problem kissing a guy.
But I've never kissed
someone I'm not close to.
Come on.
You'll get closer after the workshops.
Speaking of kissing,
it reminds me of my first kiss.
Mine was back in junior high.
It was with a girl from a lower grade.
But it didn't turn into anything.
What about you?
Hm?
When was your first kiss? Hm?
Mine was…
a little late.
It's just last year.
Huh?
Last year?
Hey, wait!
Where have I been? How did I not know this?
Tell me. Who was it?
Just some asshole.
That's why I don't want to remember.
Shit.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have asked, right?
Forget it. It was a long time ago.
I'm okay now.
Hey, Dean.
Sorry.
I thought no one was home.
Am I invading?
I can leave.
Hey, it's fine.
This is Tua's place, after all.
I'm just his housemate.
If he's okay with it, I am too.
Have a seat. Eat with us.
So you two can get to know each other.
Wow, this looks amazing.
You made so much.
Arnold's worried about the love scenes
you two have together.
Tua!
Talk to him.
No worries.
We'll get used to each
other after the workshops.
Wow, this is a lot.
Are you Ranchalee's son?
Right?
I'm Raffy.
Okay, Little Raffy.
Can I take photos with you?
I'm your mom's biggest fan.
I've loved her since Love
Beneath the Sea of Stars.
Let's take photos.
One more, please.
I have a name.
But people keep calling me Ranchalee's son
or Little Raf.
Thank you.
Just pick whatever you like.
I'll give you a special discount.
Take your time.
How cool.
Just make it quick so we can leave.
Help me choose.
What? No.
It's your gear. You choose.
Oh, come on. Just pick one.
Which one would you
choose between these two?
Go with the one that catches your eye.
You're such a pain.
Here.
Let's go with this one.
This one?
Mm.
Whoa.
Nice taste.
Can I try this one?
Of course.
All you do is act cool.
Who knew you were actually good?
GOT TIME? COME SEE ME AT THE UNI.
LET'S TALK. JUST THE TWO OF US.
Hey, you want this controller, right?
Excuse me. I'll pay by card.
Hey, I'm not even sure yet.
Here.
Just a moment, please.
I gotta run.
What's the rush?
None of your business.
I'm buying this for you. We're even now.
Get my card for me.
What?
Bye.
Hey!
Say what you want.
Are you going to yell at me for quitting?
Why would I yell at you?
I just want you to
reconsider the supporting role.
That friend role you want me to play
could be played by anyone.
Hey. Not just anyone.
No character in my play is unimportant.
Didn't you say you wanted to
act in something I direct?
This might be the last chance
we get to work together.
Please,
Raffy.
Well…
If you want me to do it that bad,
I'll do it.
Holy shit.
Thank you, Raffy.
I actually prepared to
pester you some more.
I thought I'd have to beg.
Well…
You're the one who asked.
Here.
The new script I edited just for you.
Take a look.
This is the first act.
Jack was clearly pleading.
With that kind of effort,
of course I went back.
Jack.
Why did you include Raffy in this project?
Was there really no one else?
Dean, be professional.
I think Raffy suits that role.
Suits?
You never change.
You're always casting the people you like.
Why?
Are you jealous?
Dean, learn to separate things.
Work is work. Personal
matters are personal..
Hey, sorry.
Am I interrupting, Jack?
No.
What is it?
I need to tell you something.
Go on.
I'm dropping out to focus on my band.
We've been getting busier,
and I need to give it my full attention.
But Billy, this is your final year.
It was a hard decision.
But the opportunity is
here. I have to seize it.
Come on now.
I'll come watch the play, alright.
See you then.
See you, Dean.
See you.
Why are you so tense?
Of course I am.
I picked the best people for this project.
What else can you do?
Billy wants to chase his dreams.
You'll find someone else.
Your little brother Rome.
He's good. And he has good taste.
He's not my little brother.
Besides, I don't want to work with him.
I don't want any trouble.
Okay.
But you just told me to
separate work from personal matters.
If you don't pick Rome just because
he's your mom's new boyfriend's son,
then you're not separating
work from personal matters either.
Hello.
Hey, you came home today.
Did you forget something?
Where's that jerk Rome?
Call your brother properly.
How many times do I have to tell you?
We're family now.
Where is Rome, Mom?
If he's not out,
he's always in his room, DJing.
My oh my.
You still remember the way home, huh?
I thought you were too busy with your play.
I came because of the play.
I need your help.
Is my capable big bro
really asking me for help?
So you're not helping?
Fine. I'll leave.
Wait, wait.
Tell me what it is.
Maybe I can.
Can you…
do sound for my play?
Have you even seen
my work before asking for my help?
Dean recommended you.
So I checked out your channel a bit.
Your style can fit the play.
You're back with Dean?
Stay out of it.
Are you helping or not?
Fine. I'll do it.
But let me make one thing clear.
Even if you're the director,
don't boss me around.
You get it, right?
Artists need freedom to work.
Mm.
No problem.
Now people will finally see
how talented I am.
I just didn't have a choice.
I never knew there was
a pre-production party for stage plays.
It's just our excuse to drink.
What about the others?
Are they coming?
Jack and Dean are out to buy wine.
Timmy is always late.
The rest are on their way.
Here. The vegetables are washed.
Just tell me what else to do.
Can you help me slice the meat?
Of course.
Let me.
Hey.
It's your phone grip.
When people ask about your name,
just point to it.
You won't have to explain anymore.
No freaking way, Tua.
It's cute.
The Terminator?
Where did you get it?
Thank you.
Looks like you, huh?
Stick it on my phone?
Mhm.
“I'm the Terminator.”
“I… will be back.”
Nice impression.
My whole body is made of steel.
Now you're teasing yourself?
What's up, big actress's son?
You again?
Did you follow me here?
I took you to buy that new controller.
What else do you want?
Don't flatter yourself.
I'm here for the party too.
What?
Why?
I'm part of the production now.
Jack asked me to run the sound.
From now on,
we'll be seeing each other a lot.
♪ When we get too close, too real ♪
♪ Tell me if you dare ♪
♪ If you want to be just friends ♪
♪ Stay in that lane ♪
Gosh, Timmy.
Do you have to turn into
a singer every time you're drunk?
What?
Are you saying I'm not good?
Cheers. Come on.
Of course.
Wow!
Here they come.
Took you guys long enough.
I thought you murdered each other.
Who told you that? We're on good terms.
The director and his
favorite actor are back.
Wow!
What are you all looking at?
Stop teasing.
Dean and I are just coworkers,
like the rest of you.
Sure.
Okay?
Since everyone's here,
why don't you say something, Jack?
Let's give it up for our director!
Say something about the project.
Okay.
Thanks so much, everyone.
We'll be working together
for the next few months.
It's going to be exhausting,
but I'm sure it'll turn out great.
And thank you, Arnold, for being my Romeo.
It took me forever to find the right one.
Thank you for having me, guys.
Clap!
And…
Thank you, Raffy,
for taking on that role for me.
I should be the one thanking you
for asking me to come back.
Come to think of it,
I might learn a lot from this project.
Let the others learn. Let us drink.
Hope it's a success!
Cheers!
We should play a game.
Name a province
I want in.
Come on.
Name a province that ends with “buri.”
That's easy.
You go first.
Hey.
If you're too drunk to ride home,
you can crash here.
I'm not drunk yet.
You've been drinking a lot.
It's not safe to ride your bike.
Tua, don't worry.
I never ride when I'm drunk.
If I go over my limit, I'll book a ride.
Okay?
I'm going to the bathroom.
Mm.
Asking him to stay over, huh?
Don't tease me.
Nice move.
Sneaking your crush into the project.
Dean.
Keep your voice down. People can hear.
If you like him that much,
why don't you just tell him?
What are you afraid of?
If it were that simple,
I would've done it a long time ago.
But if you don't do anything,
how is this going to move forward?
Tell you what,
it's not that hard to create sparks.
You should try kissing him.
Huh? Kiss him?
Yeah, kiss him. Trust me.
No.
I'm not that bold.
I'm not you.
If he kisses you back,
it means he likes you too.
Build it up.
Your courage.
This is the best way.
So Tua can finally get a boyfriend.
Can I light my cigarette from yours?
Sure.
Hey.
Have you read the script?
Yeah, I have.
But honestly, I'm not
sure I can pull it off.
Oh, please. You need
to believe in yourself.
I believe in you.
Mm.
I'll do my best.
To thank you for
rewriting the script for me.
What's the deal between you and Raffy?
The way you look at him,
it feels like more than just friends.
You into him?
Why do you care?
Just answer me.
He's kind of cute.
Teasable.
Even though he likes Jack?
Screw that.
Why?
Why does everyone like Jack?
What's so great about him?
Do you really want me to say it?
You two are back together?
Not yet.
But…
I don't want anyone else to have him.
Wow.
You're evil.
How about this, Rome?
Let me serve him up for you.
Whether you take him
or not, that's your call.
I really like the new script you wrote.
How did you even come up with that?
You made the character so well-rounded.
I'm glad you like it.
Jack.
Oh, hey.
That Past Lives poster you said you liked,
I finally got it for you.
Want to come and get it?
You can go get it and show me.
What's wrong?
Are you afraid you won't be able to control
yourself like that night in your room?
Sorry.
It's an inside joke.
It's fine.
I don't mind.
What the fuck is wrong with Dean?
Acting all territorial over his ex.
Did you see his face?
What are you doing?
Why would you say that in front of Raffy?
I don't like seeing him with you.
Keep this in mind.
You and I are never getting back together.
I didn't even do anything.
I don't mind if you
move on with someone else.
Just not Raffy.
Why?
Scared of losing?
I never lose.
But someone like me…
could make you lose.
But no one knows you better than I do.
Ouch!
I told you.
Someone like me can make you lose.
As for the poster, I'll
transfer you the money.
Oh, wow.
Look at you.
Already drunk?
That was fast.
Just a little tipsy.
Looks like everyone likes you.
Guess you can relax now.
It's all thanks to you, Tua.
I don't usually have
friends outside my major.
You're the only one.
So, thank you.
Let me get another drink.
I have to keep up with you.
Look.
About that kiss.
Do you want to try?
Huh?
Why don't you try that kiss with me?
If you're curious what
it's like to kiss a guy.
So?
Feel anything?
I'm not sure yet.
Maybe it's because I'm drunk.
I guess I'll know when I'm sober.
Running off after you lost?
It's normal for people with history
to end up in bed again, right?
None of your damn business.
They say constant dripping
wears away a stone.
Too bad the stone you want won't budge.
And it's already claimed by someone else.
Hold on.
I think…
I'm top-tier myself.
Whenever you want it…
I'm always ready.
If we do it one more
time, will you tell Jack?
Nope.
Why would I?
Something this delicious…
I'd rather keep to myself.
Cheers.
Hey.
Who's here at this hour?
I'll get it.
Hey!
You're here, American boy?
Am I too late?
No.
Guys, this is my friend Boston.
He's shooting our poster photos.
Mind if I join your friend group?
(Next Episode)
What's up with you and Boston?
Still mad about before?
Why would I be?
So you're not mad,
but it's still on your mind, right?
If you see him again, give me a signal.
I can be your human shield.
Can I tag along?
There are lots of secrets at this party.
Whatever you see, don't tell anyone.
Poor thing.
All you'll ever be is a supporting role.
Don't fall.
Or I'll step on you.
You didn't spread this around
because you were mad, right?
You have no right to question me
or be mad at me!
Jack, you bastard!
Hey!
What?