( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
Why is that girl here?
President Ace.
Fritzy is still the SSG Secretary.
Get out of my sight,
Ms. Fritzy Saldivar.
Bitch.
From now on.
Ms. Zein Shion is
the new secretary of HU.
Follow me.
The Dark Hell Jail
is waiting for you.
If I were you, Zein.
I'd step aside from your position.
You won't like it when
he shows his true colors.
Where are your music sheets?
It's okay ma'am. We can share.
Thanks.
You've been saving my
ass since earlier.
I didn't catch your name.
My name is Nazzer Lumia.
You're the leader of
the Black Blood Gang?
When the gangs have made you their target
you will never know peace.
Raven Robles,
Paulo Roxas,
Jules Santos.
It seems that the people here
have been disrespecting
the authority of the
student council.
Am I right?
Be better at doing your jobs.
The council cannot afford
to lose its power.
Do you understand?
Am I clear?
I'm sorry.
Ms. Shion.
Do you want us
to move this meeting
so you can get some snacks?
Supremo
with all due respect
stop overreacting.
You're not the only one
keen on stopping the killings.
Don't be dramatic.
I know she's hot-headed
- but this disrespect is on another level.
- Ms. Shion.
Let's just see what happens.
Maybe you'll get
your position back.
Can you repeat
what you just said?
You heard me loud and clear.
You still lack disclipine.
Onel.
Supremo.
Get the files
Madam Violet asked for.
Copy that, Supremo.
And now
as your punishment
when Onel gets back
photocopy all of it.
Bring it here
then bring it to
the admin office.
Copy that, Supremo.
At least I'll be away
from all of you
even for a moment.
Supremo.
Isn't Zein's
punishment too light
for the insults she said to you?
Are you questioning my methods?
Fritzy
besides
you don't have the right to
voice your opinion anymore
since you're no longer
a part of the SSG.
My apologies, Supremo.
We need all the help
we can get from our members
even if it's from that
disrespectful brat.
Now
what's the next agenda?
You're lucky that this is
your punishment, Ms. Shion.
Thought for sure he was going to
drag you to the Dark Hell Jail.
Disappointed, Onel?
I'm hurt you would
think that, Ms. Shion.
But no, not disappointed
surprised
it seems like Supremo has
a soft spot for you.
I don't need that or want his help.
Maybe you’re right
it pays to be cautious.
It's dangerous to
get close with Supremo
we don't know
what he's capable of.
It’s like befriending a wild animal.
You mean a snake.
You're joking now, Ms. Shion
if you thought that
the Dark Hell Jail
was the worst punishment
Supremo can give
you thought wrong.
I'm ready whatever it is.
Are you sure?
Whatever nightmare you're
losing sleep over every night...
like a predator
playing with its prey...
Are you done now?
Can't you just do
as you're told?
I have work to do.
I hope you finish your punishment
as soon as possible, Ms. Shion.
Soft spot?
From a person who
locks people up in the Dark Hell Jail?
From a person who punished me
just because I was
drinking water during a meeting?
Is Vice Onel joking?
Whatever.
But this is for the best
at least I'm away from them
especially from Supremo.
Whoever she is
she's too audacious.
Oh my gosh.
She thinks she's all that.
Oh, Zein is here.
Well, well, well
so the rumors are right.
You're the new secretary of the
Supreme Student Government.
Well, you must be quite proud.
But don't be too proud
because you're still
their errand girl.
Not like a queen
but more like a slave.
Low class.
Move aside.
I said move.
Oh my god
can you still stand?
How adorable.
You're still unaware of your
place in this school?
If I spit right now
people here would see that my
saliva has more value than you.
That's how far we are
from each other.
So if I were you
stop with that attitude.
Because you
will never be better than me.
You never will be.
You're like dirt on my shoes.
I don't care about the
opinion of a girl
who monitors her rank
and is too conscious
of her image.
You're just showing everyone
your real face.
An insecure little bitch.
I'd laugh if it weren't so pathetic.
H-how dare you!
Do you know who I am?
Your slap hurts.
Fifty degrees if I'd rate it
I'll show you how this game
should be done.
Taste this one hundred-
eighty degree slap.
What did you do to me?
Oh my god!
I heard you're a queen here?
Funny cause I can
only hear a whimpering dog.
A pathetic bitch.
You're going to regret this.
Raze will know about this.
Wow, go ahead.
That's what you're good at.
Coward.
You'll regret this you
fucking bitch!
I'll fucking kill you!
Enter.
Madam Violet.
Supremo asked me to
give this to you.
The council activities are
done for the day as well.
Did something catch
your attention, Ms. Shion?
It's nothing.
You know curiousity
is an important trait
that students should have.
Did this pique your interest?
I wasn't so ambitious before.
I was content with teaching.
But I see it clearly now.
The systems people grow accustomed
to are not easily undone.
So you build a new one.
I attempted to climb the ranks
to attain a position where I can
dictate what I want
to happen to this school.
I did okay. Didn't I, Ms. Shion?
What do you think?
Of course you do.
I believe that I've
reminisced enough.
You should go before
the Bloody Night starts.
It's going to be such a shame
if something happens...
if the new SSG
Secretary disappears.
So...
I'm going to have someone else
send these copies to the
SSG office tomorrow morning.
You remind me of someone.
Madam?
You may go now, Ms. Shion.
Come here.
Vanessa, what's wrong?
Is it true?
You started a fight with Roxane?
This place is a gossip
mill, isn't it?
She had it coming, trust me.
She was such a bitch, Van.
If you only heard-
That's not the point, Zein.
Of course, it is.
When did we ever let these
bullies and bitches
get the better of us?
That's when we were still outside,
not here inside Hell U.
You know how different it is here.
Aren't you scared?
You’re putting
yourself in danger.
What do you want me to do?
Let her push me around?
Yes!
Because you're not the only
one who'll be in danger.
Didn't that cross that
head of yours?
Instead of starting fights
you should have focused on
climbing up the ranks.
That should be our top priority!
You only think about
yourself, don't you?
Stop being selfish.
Think of the rest of us for once.
Hey!
Are you done with our assignment?
It's hard, isn't it?
I can't find the answer
to question number three.
Me too.
I haven't answered everything yet.
How about you guys?
I'm not done yet.
Let me copy your answers, Matt.
Come on!
Isn't our plan to study hard
so we can join Hell U's top ten?
How is that going to happen
if you keep copying my work?
Come on. Let me copy it!
So we can finish it together.
Please.
Try to study.
Are you sure that's the correct answer?
You're complaining? Are you serious?
Zein...
your best friend is here.
Why is she here?
Supremo is asking for you.
What does he want?
I don't know!
I'm just a messenger.
All I know is he's waiting for you
at the SSG Office.
Maybe this time you can do your job right.
You keep hanging out with your friends.
I'm sorry, guys.
Supremo asked for me.
Go ahead. It’s your responsibility.
Don’t worry, we understand.
Zein might get in trouble again.
Zein is so stubborn.
Hey!
Oh shit...
Stop that.
Are you okay, Zein?
Yes, better now.
Are you and Van okay?
Did something happen?
We had a fight.
I need to apologize to her.
Zein, I can see that you have
a lot of love for your friends.
Of course, I do.
But...
I've noticed that your love has shifted.
That Supremo
you two are getting too close.
Am I getting replaced?
You know...
we just seem close
because we're always working together.
What are you talking about, Matt?
He doesn't even greet me good morning
or ask about how my day was.
For whatever reason
he's isolated.
Why do you seem disappointed?
I'm joking.
I'm assured that I'm the one in your heart.
You're so lame.
Lame?
That's not lame, Zein.
I'm just telling the truth.
I know I'm your crush.
You know...
that Supremo
he's overworking you.
I don't understand why
he keeps calling you.
I just miss you.
I miss having quality
time with my best friend.
You know...
I have to go in.
Thank you for coming with me
best friend.
I'll head in.
Okay.
Wait, Zein.
I have to ask you something.
What is it?
Who's more handsome
me or that Supremo?
Of course, you!
You're late.
Get inside.
Bye.
I have kept my side of the bargain
haven't I?
Ms. Shion?
You have time for your friend
but when I call upon you
it's not right to keep me waiting.
Am I right?
You already know.
Don’t be late again.
But that's not your only fault
you've been busy...
reckless
a liability.
The fight you started
what did you gain?
I slapped her 180 degrees
it made me feel a whole lot better.
Roxane is the queen of HU for fuck's sake.
You're not allowed to touch her.
What was your intention?
You're nothing but a powerless secretary.
Hell yes
and I don't fucking care.
If I get mistreated or hurt
I'll fight back
even if it's a queen or a supremo.
Okay
clearly my words aren't being
absorbed by that brain of yours.
I'll level with you
I'll speak in a language
you would understand
clean the whole cafeteria.
Excuse me?
The whole cafeteria.
Clean it for a week.
Make it spotless
shiny.
Do you understand?
For a week?
For real?
You can start today.
Okay, fine.
If that's all, goodbye...
Supremo.
Now, can anyone tell me
why hope is a core human value?
It's different compared to
what we previously discussed.
Come on, class.
This is important.
Anyone?
Hope
is not a wish or a dream
it’s faith.
Faith that what we wish for will come true.
Like our faith
that we will enter heaven
when we pass on.
At least
that’s what i think.
Very good, Lyka.
Hope is the sister of faith.
And together
they allow us to believe
in a better future.
Is Lyka Ms. Aya's favorite student?
They seem to glow when they're talking.
Is she her mentor?
Ahh... they look like family.
Whatever their relationship is.
It's nice to see moments
like this in Hell U
laughter
protecting each other
like me and my friends.
They are the reason I survive in this hell.
I really need to apologize to Van.
Celine.
Are you okay?
You look...
They're coming
be careful, Zein.
This isn't a joke, Zein.
You're in danger.
All of us.
There's a traitor among your friends
they're about to know
what's missing in the formula.
If I were you
I'll strike first.
Thanks a lot, Supremo.
You asshole.
Way important things are happening
and I'm wasting my time
cleaning this shithole.
He's already heartless,
how can be still be so oblivious
to other people's struggles?
No, oblivious isn't the right word for him.
It's too generous.
He decided this punishment
knowing the circumstances.
He's just being a dick.
You missed a spot.
Don't forget to sweep the crevices.
Yes, boss.
Do you have a family?
Ms. Shion?
Huh?
Family.
Why are you suddenly
engaging in small talk?
Are you bored?
You never know
maybe if we talk a bit you'll clean faster.
So we can leave the cafeteria.
(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
So
Indulge me.
I'm going to ask again.
How's your family, Ms. Shion?
I guess.
We're a normal family.
My mom
is hardworking
affectionate
and is addicted to watching shows.
My older sister Allison.
Textbook eldest daughter
she's good at everything, she's beautiful
and brave.
My mom's stressed all the time because
her two daughters are fighters.
There was one time
when we ate at an
unlimited samgyupsal place.
Someone flirted with Allison
and...
Again, we're a normal family.
I miss them.
I see.
How about your friends?
How are they?
You already know them, don't you?
Yeah, but
by name only.
My duties don't really get
me to meet the students.
Only if they crossed the line.
My friends.
We're like family too.
Mia is the heart of the group
she's like sushine.
Dave and Jerome
they're trouble in the best way.
If you need to laugh
they're the best ones to go to.
Vanessa...
matter of fact, Van is braver than me.
If she thinks something will hurt us
she'll call it out without
hurting us even if she's mad.
Matt...
he's my constant.
How about you, Supremo?
I shouldn't be the only one sharing things.
What's your family like?
Friends?
Chaotic.
It's a long story, Ms. Shion.
I'll tell you next time.
- Don't forget to sweep the.
- Crevices.
I know.
I'm done.
Can I go?
A bit slower than I thought.
But
you're good to go.
I'll go ahead, Supremo.
Okay.
Go faster!
Stay quiet!
No one has ever
attempted to hurt the queen.
I'm actually impressed.
What do you think the boss will do to her?
Death. I'm sure he'll kill her.
This one's a fighter.
Let her be.
Let's just see where
her bravery will get her
once the boss arrives.
Is that her?
Yes, boss.
Leave us.
An eye for an eye for Roxane.
Nice to meet you, Zein.
I am Raze Silvenia.
You sure are brave
like what they said.
But how about your friends?
Are they as brave as you?
Maybe I'll punish them instead?
I can start with Mia.
I bet she shrieks when she gets hurt.
My patience is running thin.
I carry death with me.
And believe me
he'll come for you, Zein Shion.
Raze Silvenia?
Maybe you'd like to release me
before I reveal your secret to everyone.
I don't know any secrets of mine
that you can use against me.
You can't faze me, Zein Shion.
Is that so?
You’re sure that you don’t have a secret
that can kill you
when it’s revealed?
What secret of mine do you know?
Just because you wear his mask
doesn't mean you can fool everyone.
You're not Raze Silvenia.
See?
One mention of his name
you're already fazed.
No one can compare to how terrifying he is.
It doesn't matter how many masks you wear
you can't fool me when it comes to Raze.
I've already met the real Raze.
Even if it's just one time.
I can see the differences.
You can't compare to Raze.
You?
You're lucky
if I can remember you tomorrow.
Shut your mouth!
Boss?
What happened?
We heard a scream.
I'm okay.
Get out!
If I'm being honest.
I can kill you now.
But they won't allow it.
I'm impressed.
I underestimated you, Zein.
I fooled everyone!
I even fooled Roxane.
This complicates things.
Maybe we can help each other?
Oh?
Now you have authority?
Enough to make you an offer.
6:53 pm.
I'll set you free
but you can't betray me.
Wow, the sudden kindness irks me.
The clock's ticking.
Do you want to leave
and keep this secret between us.
What's your answer, Zein?
Deal.
Your secret is my secret.
Zein
stop finding him.
Let go of me!
Come here!
You can't escape from me.
Let go of me!
You thought you could escape?
I said let go!
Where do you think you're going?
Get away!
I said get away from me!
Ms. Shion.
But I don't have any idea
where the hidden laboratory is.
Just do your job as a secretary
and monitor all their movements.
What if they find out I'm the mole?
I'm not ready to die yet, Sir Alvarez.
I still need to escape
with my friends.
Please help us!
We thought you're the next
Samantha but you're both useless!
I thought
you're like Samantha
but I was wrong.
I'm just a secretary.
Stay away from Alvarez.
Why do you care?
Good morning, our dear students.
We are gathered here today
to honor our late headmaster
Dominic Valdez.
You killed the late headmaster!
You both should be punished!
Get rid of her.
Stop!
Let go of me!
Don't cross the admin.
Or me.
Hey...
what's bothering you?
Let me help you.