-Yu Ji-hyuk! -Yu Ji-hyuk!
-Congrats! -Congrats!
-On your 100-day -On your 100-day...
vacation!
Did you sign up for manual labor instead of the military?
What's with your face?
I thought you renounced the world.
Haven't you heard of sunscreen?
Of course, it was around before you joined too.
What shall we eat now?
We spent a lot of money.
Let's buy soju and go back to school.
It's a good night!
Thank you.
What's that?
Go.
She shouldn't have drank so much. That scared me.
Sorry about that!
I'm sorry.
Is she alone? Shall we take her?
She's begging for it.
Ignoring her wouldn't be polite.
Absolutely. That wouldn't be chivalrous.
Attack!
-Who's that? -Who's that?
Are you okay?
A pole...
Sorry.
Are you okay?
Are you alone? Are you with anyone?
I'm alone.
I'm completely alone. Seriously alone.
My dad passed away on March 2nd.
So,
I'm alone.
Also, my boyfriend and I broke up.
So I'm seriously alone.
What about a friend?
I'm sure you have a friend.
A friend...
People don't like me, so I have no friends.
I smell alcohol.
What's wrong?
It smells good.
Excuse me?
EPISODE 5
What do you want to know?
I want to know if this is beer or soju.
I have terrible vision.
You can tell this is beer with your eyes shut!
If you can't tell that,
then you probably shouldn't drink any more.
But I bought this beer.
Goodness.
Thank you.
Doesn't your forehead hurt?
It doesn't hurt.
But I really am allowed to drink tonight.
Then drink at your place.
You want me to drink alone? I'm always alone.
My dad passed away three months ago.
March 2nd.
I know, and you broke up with your boyfriend too.
Do you have other family? Where's your mom? Do you have siblings?
I don't have siblings.
My mom left home 3,193 days ago.
I was in middle school.
Also, friends--
No one likes you, so you have no friends.
How did you know?
Are you a fortune teller?
Here's your beer.
Thank you.
Beer's the best!
Actually, I do have one friend.
But I can't reach her
when I need her and am having a really hard time.
Maybe she's busy.
I know. We have such bad timing.
I'm sure she wants to be with me too.
I'm sure she's sad.
But...
I think if I was with Su-min
on a day like this,
I'd feel like a loser.
My boyfriend
suddenly started being busy,
and he said he was always tired.
When my dad passed,
he didn't even come.
That's when it hit me.
Still, I pretended not to know.
For three months at that!
Because...
being alone
would only be sadder.
So my boyfriend...
I noticed that he's been smiling at Su-min a lot.
But that's natural.
Su-min's nice, pretty, and cute.
Also, she's my only friend.
Do you know that feeling?
I'm sure Su-min's nice,
pretty, and cute.
But when I stand beside her,
I feel so shabby.
Like a big fat loser.
If that's how she makes you feel, don't be her friend.
Who cares if she's good or bad? You're uncomfortable.
Isn't she bad for you?
Do you know what it means to not have a family?
Have you been on a boat?
After my dad died,
it feels like I'm on a boat every day.
My feet are firmly planted, but the boat keeps rocking.
I feel anxious.
I want stability.
I want to step on solid land.
Su-min's the only one who will be my land.
I only have her.
But this is because I'm a loser. The end.
I guess that makes me a loser too.
My mom passed away 15 years ago.
Exactly 5,328 days ago.
After some time, I got a stepmother and a younger sibling.
They're good people, but I feel strange.
I hate it.
Wow, you really are a loser.
I should get a grip.
The real loser was right here.
I mean, what happened to your mom is sad,
but the fact that your dad could start over is a good thing, right?
My dad should've done that.
If he had...
he wouldn't have died.
My dad was able to start over, but he died too.
Don't think that way.
Cheers.
You're so warm.
Let's just say we're both not losers.
Still, you're right about one thing. My dad was happy before he died.
Your dad left you with a new family.
Congratulations!
Congrats on having a solid friend.
No.
You're able to have a good and solid friend.
Congratulations.
STIR-FRIED ATHLETES SPORTS CLUB
Yu Ji-hyuk wins!
Ji-hyuk.
Jo Dong-suk, a reserve for the national team,
has been beaten by an ordinary economics student.
Why?
Why are you going this far?
You're a civilian!
You're not a pro athlete!
You're a soldier. Let's take ten.
What?
You want to go again?
I think he does.
Why did he go into economics then?
I woke up,
and I was snoring beside an unpleasant-looking old man!
I was so surprised.
I hope he doesn't go to our school.
That would be so embarrassing.
I hate that.
But he was strange too.
Why do that with a drunk girl?
-I mean... -True.
I need to get a grip.
I'm already 23.
When will I grow up?
She was an upperclassman?
Since we're at it, can you beat Sin-u too? For real!
-I quit judo. -Please, I'm begging you.
Well?
Why?
Is something wrong?
I was snoring beside an unpleasant-looking old man!
Hey.
Am I an unpleasant-looking old man?
Which part do you mean?
The unpleasant-looking or old man part?
Do you want me to recommend a sunscreen?
What about now?
-That's good. -Good.
Really nice.
-You're so pretty. -Yeah.
Yeah.
Hey, wait! Stop!
Hey.
You're eating well.
Here's four.
I'll give you nine. Eat it all.
Eat it slowly.
Drink some water.
You'll get fat if you eat like that.
CAT SNACKS
Ji-hyuk. Why are you always here during your break?
-What is it? -What is he doing?
-Did his senior ask him to make something? -His service must be tough.
Thinking back, I had a few chances.
I didn't seize it because I didn't know.
Or I couldn't seize it.
2011 U&amp;K FOOD THE MOST INFLUENTIAL FOOD BRAND
I would like to introduce our team.
Yes...
-And if that wasn't it... -She's a Hankuk University alum.
Her name's Kang Ji-won.
Say hello.
As of today, Mr. Yu Ji-hyuk will be our general manager.
Ji-won graduated from Hankuk University,
but she slacks in her work. Yeah.
I have to pay a lot of attention to her.
-What happened to the proposal plan? -You said it was due tomorrow...
See? What did I tell you?
Let's keep moving.
Yeah, well...
It was a chance I shouldn't seize.
But it's different this time.
APRIL 19, 2013
I do feel better.
What was that?
What?
What's with that smile?
Follow me.
Didn't I tell you? He's interested in you.
What are you saying? He has a girlfriend.
Is that what he said? Did he say that himself?
You're acting so naive.
What does that matter?
Let me tell you about men.
All men cheat.
So he has a girlfriend?
He could have a wife and still like someone else! That's men!
Do you know what a guy's ideal type is?
An unfamiliar woman.
That's men! Okay?
Are all men like you?
Don't be foolish.
That's why you're the problem.
Guys are playing tricks because you look easy.
You wouldn't do
something like that, would you?
What?
Never mind.
I must've thought all men were like you.
Yeah.
They're all like that except for me.
That's why I know.
I'm telling you to be careful.
-You don't even know. -Okay.
Ms. Kang?
-Bye. -Yeah, okay.
I mean...
She's acting strange.
Strangely good.
She's prettier too.
This is revolutionary.
We didn't have this before!
This is what you call perks!
Did you see those broad shoulders!
His shoulders?
I was looking at his waist and back.
I couldn't see his shoulders!
It'll take two days to look at him closely.
Did you see how tall he is? He has everything!
-He's insanely hot! -He's insanely hot!
Yes, hello.
Mr. Yu.
The finance team has raised your stock transaction details.
I called to check.
Does it include personal accounts?
The amount was significant, and you don't normally buy other stocks.
If you want, shall I advise against reporting it?
Please, thank you.
Don't you usually avoid unfamiliar fields?
That's right.
GENERAL MANAGER YU JI-HYUK
That means he knows something.
Did you say it was Roijental?
Are you sure there's nothing special?
Yes, there was a sharp rise,
but it's still uncertain from our data.
It's not a company Ji-hyuk is affiliated with.
But he still hasn't sold it?
Let's keep an eye on it.
And see if he has a borrowed-name account.
Make sure he doesn't know.
Yes, I understand.
When something's changed,
what wasn't a problem in the past could become one.
He was so sexy!
-I mean it, that bottom... -He looked so tall!
Are we the only ones who don't care about Mr. Yu's transformation?
Everyone's surprised by it.
That's not my type.
People realize their partners aren't their type once they start dating.
I'm married. Getting excited is illegal.
Anyway, let's talk about the meal kit.
Green bell peppers are good nutritionally, but there aren't many farms that sell it.
So...
About that, green bell peppers aren't different bell peppers.
They're harvested before fully ripening.
-They'll supply with a purchase guarantee. -What?
That's right. I just found out too.
I bet all you did was study in school!
I grew up on a farm.
Which means I played barefoot in the dirt when I was a kid.
Really?
We played in the dirt a lot too!
Wait, was it sand?
We played on the beach a lot.
This brings back memories.
Do you remember the lady that sold jjokja? We ate so much!
Jjokja?
Dalgona.
Eating that at the beach is so good.
You always broke yours, so I did it for you.
Please take after Ji-won for me.
You have no idea how high-maintenance she is.
I was upset when she went to college in Seoul,
but she couldn't make any friends and spent her time in the library.
I kept going back and forth from Busan.
So did you come to Seoul to see Ms. Kang while you went to school in Busan?
Yeah, every week.
It was so difficult for me!
I had classes four days a week.
I was in Seoul for three days once.
Is that why she couldn't make friends?
That's too far even for a weekly visit to see a guy.
That's how close we were.
She's your other half. Friends like that are hard to come by.
"Friends like that" shouldn't exist.
Why did you go to school in Seoul, Ms. Kang?
To go to Hankuk University.
You have to give it to her, it's Hankuk University.
Are you here to have fun?
You should be working, but you're all here chatting away.
Hey, Hankuk University. Go move my car.
The parking spots all sucked.
I parked on the fourth basement floor. The plate's 75NA 1109.
Why? Is it out of your league?
Do you want to keep chatting here?
Women are all the same.
Hey, get back to work.
Get up right now!
I should blow up the breakroom.
There you are.
It's not your fault you have a crappy owner.
If my guess is right,
you'll be waiting for me.
Because you have to comfort me.
To teach me that you're the only one who's on my side.
I was worried, so I waited.
Did you move the car well?
Yeah.
If you can't give me your proposal, at least let me join.
I'll go to the farm and factory. I'll work really hard.
I have to become a full-time employee.
Please? Let me join.
I'll think about it.
You're not still mad at me, are you?
I'm not just saying this.
Let's talk it out if you're mad. You're going to hurt my feelings.
We're meant to be together forever! It's our fate.
If I become a full-timer with this, let's work here until we die!
Okay?
Hey, Ji-won! Get over here if you're done.
When will I get the revised proposal? You didn't report the team to me either!
I'm sorry. It's not done yet.
I'm sure. Yeah.
That's how far your skills go.
You can't do it alone,
I'll talk to Yang Ju-ran for you. I already told Su-min.
Ms. Yang is already helping me.
-Hui-yeon is helping too. -Is she useful at all?
What did she say? Forget it.
You already submitted your proposal,
I didn't say anything but it overlaps with mine.
Can I take you out of it?
Once my name is on it,
it becomes a whole new level.
But I'm willing to add you.
So stop arguing.
Get out.
Is this how it plays out?
Since I don't give Su-min my proposal,
Kim Gyeong-uk will steal it.
Then he'll add Su-min's name to it.
Ms. Kang?
Hello, sir.
Are you free tonight?
Do you need something?
No, it's not that.
I want to buy you dinner. Let's try to pick a time.
I have personal plans tonight.
If it's work-related...
tell me the TPO and I'll schedule a time and place to eat.
No, you don't need to do all that.
Okay.
Personal plans?
Eun-ho, I think you have a guest.
A guest?
Ji-won!
I thought this was just a restaurant. Do you know this place?
Yeah, our restaurant makes deals with this wine shop.
I wanted to show you a taste that's out of this world.
Doesn't it smell good? It's a Château Olrang 1999.
It was produced the year we first met in high school.
It has notes of cedar and cassis.
Also, it's not easy to get rich blackberry notes.
I can really smell it!
I can smell grapes and trees.
-It's nice. -Is it?
Wait a second.
The wholesale price
for all the wines here are over a million won.
Let's try all of it.
Eun-ho.
To be honest, I came out to buy you dinner.
Have you eaten?
Me?
I tend to eat dinner a little early.
I didn't think that far ahead.
No, that's okay. Come and sit.
It's been so long. Let's talk.
Okay.
What is she doing right now?
I wanted to take care of her tonight.
She's got terrible luck.
Wait a minute.
Hey, Min-hwan.
Hi, Su-min.
Are you with Ji-won by any chance?
I can't reach her.
Ji-won left earlier.
She looked pretty. She kept looking in the mirror.
I figured she was going on a date with you. Was I wrong?
What?
She looked pretty and left?
Min-hwan, you should control Ji-won better.
Control? Come on.
She wouldn't run off or anything.
Why not? She suddenly changed her style too.
You never know with women.
Her mom found her soulmate after she had Ji-won.
Still, as a woman, I think that's really cool.
But it's a shame for Ji-won though.
No, wait...
Ji-won's mom...
had an affair?
What?
Did you not know?
What do I do?
Did I make a mistake?
Never mind!
It wasn't Ji-won. It was another friend...
I mean...
I just figured that you already knew.
Yeah, well...
I know her mom left her
when she was just a kid. I knew that already.
But the affair hit later...
I mean...
But you didn't know that she left because she found true love, right?
What do I do?
This is driving me crazy.
Min-hwan?
Just pretend like you didn't hear that.
I made a mistake.
Having an affair isn't genetics. It's not a big problem.
Of course. Yeah.
It's not a problem.
I knew it. You're a great guy, Min-hwan.
In return, I'll find out what Ji-won did tonight and let you know.
I'm sure she's just working though.
Yeah, I'm sure. Yeah.
Okay, well. Call me.
Okay.
So you told me to never speak to you again because you thought I turned you down?
I never want to speak to you again.
No, no, no, no.
Don't bring that up.
You didn't just turn me down--
What did I say?
By any chance, do you have the letter I wrote you?
Yeah, I do. You told me to bring it, so I did.
Let's see.
DO YOU THINK EVERYONE LIKES YOU BECAUSE YOU'RE POPULAR?
YOU MAKE ME VOMIT. DON'T SPEAK TO ME!
KANG JI-WON
Isn't that your handwriting?
Yeah, it is.
But I really didn't write this.
That means Su-min is able to copy my handwriting.
I can't believe it.
Are you cold?
Wait a second.
No.
I think the air conditioning is strong here.
Shall we go?
Sure.
Let's do that.
Go ahead...
Eun-ho.
I can see through Eun-ho at 31.
However...
I have a boyfriend.
Really?
By any chance, is he tall and wears horn-rimmed glasses?
Horn-rimmed glasses?
Yeah.
He wore a three button suit.
He wasn't fashionable...
I mean, he looked classic, and he had an expensive watch.
Was it Mr. Yu?
How do you know him?
He's the one that told me about the reunion.
How does he know you?
Come to think of it, you're right.
I thought he was your boyfriend.
He was really worried about you.
You drank six bottles?
So six million won?
Then she turned you down?
-She didn't turn me down. -Yeah, she did.
If she hadn't, you wouldn't be sitting here sulking like this.
Before I give up on her,
she didn't turn me down.
Even if she has a boyfriend.
Even if...
another man has feelings for her.
Did you even take her home?
-What? -She turned you down.
Just give up.
Darn it...
Goodness.
ASSISTANT MANAGER KANG JI-WON
CALLING ASSISTANT MANAGER KANG JI-WON
PARK MIN-HWAN
PARK MIN-HWAN MISSED CALL
It's just stomach cramps.
It's not good to drink wine on an empty stomach.
Okay.
Once the pain subsides, take the medicine with warm soups.
Okay, here you go.
Wine isn't good on an empty stomach.
You scared me!
Are you crazy? Why are you overreacting?
Was it you?
Why?
Were you hoping it was another man?
No...
Why would you follow me like that? You could've just called out.
Why should I make you comfortable? You don't even pick up my calls!
What?
Be real.
You're being overly self-conscious.
Men aren't interested in you! Got it?
Still, seeing you scared
made it more fun.
Is this fun for you?
Yeah, it's fun.
By the way...
Where were you?
Did you reapply lipstick after work?
What are you saying?
See!
Why are your lips so red?
Who were you hitting on now? What's on your face?
Is that blush?
Your face is rosy.
The apple doesn't fall far from the tree.
What did you just say?
What?
What did you just say, Min-hwan?
I didn't say anything.
I'm only being like this because you're being shady!
It was Su-min.
She told him about my mom.
What?
You are acting strange lately.
You don't normally buy clothes!
What's this?
Is that perfume?
What perfume? It's soap!
Where'd you go after work?
Tell me the truth.
Let go of me!
That hurts.
This little...
I'll see what time you clocked out.
So tell me the truth.
What did you do?
What the hell?
Is that you, Mr. Yu?
Sir?
What's your deal? So what if you're the general manager?
What's going on between you?
Are you crazy--
Wait...
She was going to die anyway, right?
Mr. Yu!
You can't do this!
Let go of me!
Damn it...
Damn it.
Wait. Why did I run away?
Yu Ji-hyuk, that bastard. I could've taken him any other day...
It's Yu Ji-hyuk. He has no reason to follow me.
What?
But why didn't Ji-won follow me?
Is she out of her mind?
What?
Together?
Crap!
Leaving a woman behind in a situation like this
was my husband.
How's your wrist?
But what are you doing here?
I had business in the area.
What business?
Well, the thing is...
you wouldn't answer your phone.
I figured nothing happened, but just to be sure.
Why are you worried about me?
It's after work hours.
Even if something were to happen to me,
-it has nothing to do with you. -Yes, it does.
I'm worried
Mr. Park might hurt you.
Why would you think that way?
People don't change.
They repeat their actions.
He does have violent tendencies, did he catch on to that?
I didn't know before I got married.
-Min-hwan has never touched me like-- -I just saw him.
This isn't that bad.
No, don't say it like that.
No one is allowed to touch you like that.
It's no big deal?
I should've broken all of his fingers.
I could tell he is insightful because of NurTV.
The problem is...
No.
It was fun seeing Min-hwan so scared.
So that's not the problem.
What's going on?
I came to see her fight with Min-hwan.
PARK MIN-HWAN
SLIDE TO ANSWER
Hello?
Yes, Min-hwan?
The way you're acting is uncomfortable.
I'm just worried...
I don't want you to worry.
Your feelings make me uncomfortable.
Do you know how I feel?
I don't like cheating for personal reasons.
I don't think a person should betray anyone.
I've taken care of that.
You what?
Is your girlfriend a task to be taken care of?
-No, that's not-- -Wow, I didn't take you for that type.
You're worse than I thought.
Hui-yeon is a very precious person to me.
Hui-yeon is so nice and pretty.
She's very lovable...
Forget it. I'm going to talk to her myself.
No, wait, Ji-won. Just a second.
Calm down first.
Will you hear me out?
You think I'm dating Yu Hui-yeon
and I'm trying to cheat on her?
Because I have feelings for you.
Are you not?
You're right.
Just the part about me liking you.
Now...
MOST BEAUTIFUL
Why are you calling so late at night? It's scary.
-Hui-yeon. -This phone will self-destruct
in five seconds if you don't get to the point.
-Five, four-- -I love you.
Does she sound like my girlfriend?
MOST BEAUTIFUL
Just so you know, Hui-yeon saved it like this.
I shouldn't see you for a month after that!
But I'll have to see you at work tomorrow.
Are you terminally ill or something? Are you leaving the family register now?
END CALL
I...
Wait...
So, she's your sister!
Yu Hui-yeon.
Yu Ji-hyuk.
What do I do? I'm so sorry!
Please forget everything I said today.
I have made a huge misunderstanding.
You didn't misunderstand all of it.
I...
like you a lot.
Thanks for bringing me home.
Mr. Yu...
Mr. Yu.
Mr. Yu!
What do I do?
Mr. Yu?
Mr. Yu!
So for Ji-won's sake,
you should break up.
Don't you think you're out of line?
The first step to win is to get on the mat and face your opponent.
I have to stop letting shameless people take things from me.
He's the most decent man Ji-won has ever met.
You're out.
It'd be good to use Director Wang's name to promote it.
You're capable of fighting well.
First, get on the mat and face my opponent.
The problem is, how do I flip it?
Translated by Suyun Mounce