[Fated Hearts – An Elopement Easily Stopped]
[On-set of "Fated Hearts"]
All right, up.
[Lifted high on wires]
[Lands safely]
Your Highness.
[Tense standoff at the foot of the mountain]
Don't hurt my brother!
[Arrows released simultaneously]
One, two—release!
[Successfully dodges]
Brother!
You're my only family.
Please let us go.
Everyone—
retreat!
[They choose to withdraw]
[Radiating authority]
Stop right there!
[Completely frozen]
Go on, keep moving!
Cut!
[All stunned by Suige's aura]
[Can't resist mimicking]
Stop right there!
They're still—
It's raining.
[Casting a spell]
Freeze.
[The rain grows heavier]
It's raining harder now.
[Draws the sword with effortless grace]
Once he comes down,
you can say that line—
"Don't hurt my  brother."
You dare come again?
Brother—
you're my only family.
[Voice filled with emotion]
Don't push me any further.
Don't hurt my royal brother!
[Xiyang's impression show]
Don't hurt the Prince!