(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
(Yoo Yeon Seok)
(Esom)
(Kim Kyung Nam)
(Kim Mi Kyung, Jeon Seok
Ho, Son Yeo Eun, Lee Ah Rin)
(Choi Kwang Il, Jung
Seung Gil, Yeon Je Hyeong)
(Phantom Lawyer)
(Supported by Ministry of
Culture, Sports and KOCCA)
(All people, places, and events
in this drama are fictional.)
(Child actors filmed
safely with guardians.)
(All scenes involving
animals were staged...)
(and filmed safely by welfare standards.)
(Episode 12)
Doggy, come here!
He crossed over peacefully.
Are you okay?
You must have grown pretty fond of him.
You know, he really loved his wife so much.
But his wife...
She went her whole
life without ever knowing.
That's what's so heartbreaking.
See? I told you.
Words like "Thank you,"
"I'm sorry," and "I love you..."
You'll end up regretting it if
you don't say them in time.
So if you don't want any
regrets later, Yi Rang,
you need to be open about how you feel.
What is it?
I won't have any regrets.
I know. You're not like that.
Because I'm going to say it right now.
What?
Right now.
I'm going to tell you.
How I feel.
Doggy!
Doggy?
Don't tell me...
Play with me.
What's your name?
Hey, you were supposed to
finish what you were saying.
Leaving me hanging like that.
Go.
(Phantom Lawyer)
Lightning Man Power!
Hey, seriously, just knock it off.
Hey, come on. Sit down and
talk with me for a second, okay?
Hey, you, get over here.
Lightning Man, help!
Please, I'm begging you!
What's wrong, mister?
I'm dying of curiosity.
What are they? Tell Lightning
Man, and he'll help you.
You know, back at Sky Park...
Sky Park?
You know, where we first met.
When you chased after that doggy.
- The doggy.
- Yes, the doggy.
Do you remember being me back then?
You were running all over the place
on my legs and talking with my mouth.
- Yes! It was super fun.
- It was, right?
But the thing is, I don't
remember any of it.
So I was hoping you could
tell me what happened.
What did you say to that lady back then?
- The lady?
- Yes. The one who was with me.
The lady...
Doggy!
Gosh, you're so cute.
Mister, what do you think you're
doing, just touching him like that?
Can't you see you're scaring my baby?
Did that scare you?
That lady.
She was really scary.
She got mad and glared at me.
What? She got mad and glared at you?
I blew it.
I totally blew it.
- I'm done for.
- Want some more?
Eat up now. Okay?
- You're up?
- Good morning.
- I'm heading out.
- What about breakfast?
I'm not hungry.
Yi Rang. Here, at least have
some of this before you go.
No, really. I'm fine.
Then just take it with you for later, okay?
Okay.
I'm off.
Is something wrong with Yi Rang?
Apparently, a little boy
came to him this time.
A boy? Who?
What?
He's the son of a friend of mine.
It's nothing you need to worry about.
Who said I cared? I only
care about Woo Jin anyway.
And who's Woo Jin?
He's someone. And you don't need to know.
- What? Mother, you know him?
- Of course I do.
Sure. He's a handsome
kid, cute as a button.
Wait, what? You know him too?
Of course. He's very
well-mannered and so adorable.
- Am I the only one who doesn't know?
- This is yummy.
Goodness! Fine then!
What's wrong?
I won't have any regrets.
I know. You're not like that.
Because I'm going to say it right now.
What?
Right now.
I'm going to tell you.
How I feel.
No way. It can't be, can it?
Gosh, this is going to
be so awkward if he does.
- I'm going to go check on Yi Rang.
- Wait, Mom. Take this too.
- Okay.
- That looks heavy. Let me take it.
- I'll go with her.
- Okay.
Grandma, me too! Me too!
Me too. I want to go too.
- Isn't that heavy?
- No! I want to go too! Me too!
Don't you ever wonder
about your mom and dad?
I'm not really sure.
I can't remember them.
I see.
By the way, what's that in your pocket?
What? What's this?
A golf ball?
Can I see that for a second?
Here?
Hey... Where did he go?
I see.
I guess this was the last thing you held.
Can I get a closer look at that ball?
GSG?
Uncle!
- Da Bong Bong!
- Ta-da! We're here!
Gosh, she's so cute.
Uncle, what's wrong?
Do you like Hachuping?
You already know I do. Why ask?
I'll give you my love! Hachu, Hachu, ch
- I'll give you lots and lots.
Hachu, hachu chuchu - Hachu, hachu chuchu.
- It's Hachuping Time, full of love.
- Hachuchu, hachu, Hachuping!
- Chuchu, hachu, Hachuping!
- Hachuping Power!
- Snap out of it.
- No, wait.
- We have to feed the kids.
- Chuchu, hachu, Hachuping...
All right, you two.
- Let's eat first, then we can play again!
- Yes!
- Gosh, this looks so good!
- It looks so good!
- This is great.
- Dig in, everyone.
I'll have this.
It's so yummy.
This is good.
Good morning.
I know a really fun playground.
What's with you, Yi Rang?
You're kind of creeping me out.
Am I scawy?
She says I'm scary.
- Na-na na-na boo-boo.
- The grown-up's a big scaredy-cat!
- Lightning Man, let's go!
- Let's go!
Da Bong! Wait! Oh, hi.
If that's an act, he deserves an Oscar.
Looks like we've got a handful this time.
I'll be on my way then. Wait
up, let's go together, okay? Gosh.
I know.
I know, but I just can't
seem to get used to him.
- Let's go!
- Gosh.
- Be careful! Gosh, this is fun.
- Mom!
- Lightning Power!
- Come on.
Auntie, you know what?
My uncle is the sweetest
person in the whole world.
Sweet?
Do you even know what that word means?
It means understanding how someone feels.
When I'm upset, my uncle cries with me,
and when I'm happy,
he gets all excited too.
And that's not an easy
thing to do, you know.
That's why my uncle's my favorite person.
By the way, why do you
look at my uncle that way?
Me? How was I looking at him?
It's the way my mom looks at my dad.
With kind eyes.
With loving eyes.
No, I wasn't.
Slow down.
- Lightning Power!
- You're in our territory!
You're not allowed in here.
- You okay, Yi Rang?
- Uncle!
- What?
- Yi Rang, are you all right?
Why am I... What am I doing here?
Come on out. Careful. Be careful.
Na Hyun.
Are you just going to play around all day?
I mean...
Aren't you going to work?
You have a job to do.
You okay, man?
- Uncle.
- Da Bong. Why is she so angry?
She was fine when she was with me.
Maybe it's because you
were teasing her earlier?
What? You think I was teasing Lawyer Han?
You don't remember? You were
going, "Na-na na-na boo-boo."
You were wiggling your butt.
- What?
- "Na-na na-na boo-boo," like this.
I really did that?
Okay, that's enough. But
you also did this too. Like this.
What did she mean about
the way I looked at Yi Rang?
I'm here.
That was fast.
Yes.
By any chance...
- Are you mad at me?
- Why would I be mad?
Earlier I
- was messing with you.
- I know you were possessed. Why be mad?
But is it okay for you to
get possessed so often?
What?
In movies, when people see spirits,
it takes a toll on their bodies.
Well, it's nothing like that.
The ghosts I meet
aren't that different from regular people.
Did you learn anything about the kid?
He had a golf ball.
A golf ball?
Yes, the initials GSG were on the ball,
but I'm not sure what it means.
Golf clubs put their initials on
golf balls so they don't lose them.
Maybe it's something like that?
That makes sense.
If the kid found the golf
ball right before he died,
it could be a huge clue
as to where he died.
(Seoul, GSG, Seocho-dong,
Golf Driving Range)
(Attorney Shin Yi Rang)
Were there always this many
driving ranges in the heart of Seoul?
This isn't going to work.
Do you have any other ideas?
No.
Do you have something to say to me?
No, I don't.
You look like you have
something on your mind.
What were you going to say
yesterday at the Sky Park?
What?
That lady. She was really scary.
She got mad and glared at me.
That...
It's nothing.
Really.
It's absolutely nothing.
Don't worry about it.
Where did I put that golf ball?
Here... No, it's not here.
Here? Where's the ball?
What was that about?
So it really was nothing.
(Shin Yi Rang and Han Na Hyun Law Office)
(Dance Studio)
(Seoul Manpower)
- Dad?
- Na Hyun. Are you off work?
No, not yet. What's up?
The thing is...
You know the CEO of Taebaek?
Yang Do Kyung?
Yes. He called me a little while ago.
Hello, sir. This is Yang Do
Kyung, the CEO of Taebaek.
We met once before in
front of Lawyer Han's office...
Yes. Hello, sir.
Please, sir. No need to be so formal.
I'm a close friend of your daughter's.
Please, just call me Do Kyung.
Goodness. I couldn't possibly do that.
The reason I'm calling
I was just calling to check on you,
and see how you're
feeling since the accident.
I'm perfectly fine. Nothing's wrong at all.
That's a relief.
But the thing about car accidents is...
You might feel fine now, but later
on, you can start aching all over.
It can easily lead to chronic pain.
No, really, I'm perfectly fine.
No, I'm not okay with it, sir.
You're Lawyer Han's father. We've
been through thick and thin for years.
I can't just leave this in the
hands of the insurance company.
As it happens, there's a great
acupuncture clinic near my company.
So, what does your schedule
look like tomorrow, sir?
So, before I knew it,
I ended up making an
appointment for three tomorrow.
Why does Mr. Yang
keep doing things like that?
Na Hyun.
Is there something going on
between you and Mr. Yang?
What do you mean, "something"?
There's nothing. Absolutely nothing.
Then I guess he's just a really nice guy?
Dad, call Mr. Yang right now and
tell him you're not going. Got it?
Okay, fine. I will. All right. Take care.
(Available)
- Yes, sir?
- I don't think I should go after all.
You're not coming?
- Why the sudden change of heart?
- It's just.
I'm not really hurting
anywhere. And I'm a bit busy too.
- And also...
- There isn't some other reason, is there?
It's Na Hyun.
Lawyer Han?
My daughter isn't happy about it.
I'm sorry, Mr. Yang. I just
got a fare, so I have to go.
- I'm sorry.
- Sir, wait, that's not...
Hello?
Sir?
Goodness.
(Pit-a-Pat Butcher Restaurant)
- Chief Prosecutor.
- Oh, hi.
What brings you here?
I came hoping to get a bite to eat,
but are you already closed for the day?
I'm so sorry. Today's our regular day off.
That can't be helped. I'll
come back another time.
Wait.
Actually, I've been wanting
to treat you to a meal.
Why don't you come to my home?
No, I couldn't. I wouldn't
want to impose so suddenly.
No, not at all. Honestly,
I'd feel better if you did.
Let's go.
If you insist. Thank you.
Please, take your time and eat up.
I'm just going to go finish
cleaning up at the restaurant.
- Of course, take your time.
- Okay.
Excuse me... Are you looking for something?
No. I just finished eating,
and I couldn't find you.
I'm sorry. I brought you
here and just left you.
Not at all. It's my fault for
dropping by unannounced.
Thanks to you, I had a wonderful meal.
- I'm so glad.
- I'll come by again sometime.
Of course, please do.
(Pit-a-Pat Butcher Restaurant)
Darn.
Excuse me...
Are you looking for something?
No. I just finished eating,
and I couldn't find you.
Wait, why was he in the master bedroom?
By any chance...
Are there any files that Ki
Jung might have left behind?
- Files?
- Case files, like Ki Jung's notebook...
The key evidence related to the
case was nowhere to be found.
(Attorney Shin Yi Rang)
Good Shot Golf?
(Good Shot Golf Driving Range)
- I found it.
- Really?
Does that mean you can
find my mom and dad now?
It's too late tonight, so let's go
home and get some sleep first.
We'll meet with Na Hyun
tomorrow and talk it over.
But can I stay with Grandma?
Why with her?
Because I like being with Grandma.
Okay. Let's do that.
Oh, yes!
Just a little longer.
I promise,
find your mom for you soon.
Darn it!
The more I think about it,
the more pissed off I get.
She's not here yet.
"Not a big deal?" Is he kidding me?
(Attorney Shin Yi Rang)
The person you've called is
not available. After the tone...
It's not like Na Hyun to be late.
Who's Na Hyun?
The woman from Sky Park and the playground?
The one you said got really mad at me.
No. The one who got mad
was the doggy's owner.
She was yelling about
how you scared her dog.
What? So it wasn't Na Hyun who got mad?
Actually, she was looking at you
like she was expecting something.
Like a kid about to open
a Christmas present.
Na Hyun
was expecting something?
What? I was worried for nothing.
(Attorney Han Na Hyun)
Is she running late because it's awkward?
(Shin Yi Rang and Han Na Hyun Law Office)
I'm here.
Yes?
How can I help you?
Ma'am, please, how can I help you?
My child... My child is missing!
Please find my child!
- Please, you have to find him.
- Please calm down, ma'am. Okay?
Please find my child. Please.
You're looking for a child?
I think he's in 1st or 2nd grade,
and had an accident at
Good Shot Golf Range.
One moment.
Stay still...
But the Good Shot Golf Driving
Range has been closed since 2020.
And there are no accident reports on file.
Then what about any records
of a child in yellow rain boots?
I was hoping you'd focus
on that fatal accident.
(Case search: No matching data found)
There's nothing on that either.
So, why are you asking about this?
Is this related to a crime or something?
I'm not sure about that myself.
Okay, I understand. Thank you.
Lightning Man! Let's go.
Is that guy a little off?
When do we get to see Da Bong?
Later this evening.
But I want to play with her now.
(Good Shot Golf Driving Range)
(This location is permanently
closed or has no information)
Guess I'll just have to go myself.
Should we get something tasty to eat?
- What do you like? Burgers? Pizza?
- Pizza!
Pizza? I love pizza too.
Well, you're the first ghost I've
met who has the same taste as me.
Lightning Man, listen to me carefully.
Later, when you smell the pizza,
just like at the playground,
you're going to become me.
Then you can eat all the
delicious pizza you want. Got it?
Okay.
What kind should we get?
- Sweet potato?
- Sweet potato!
- Bulgogi?
- Bulgogi.
Let's go!
I want to divorce
my wife.
May I ask the reason
you're seeking a divorce?
When my wife is with me,
she suffers.
To protect my wife...
This is the only way.
Hey, thanks for the food.
Lightning Man, after you finish the pizza,
just splash a little water
on your face. Got it?
Gosh, he actually ate the whole thing.
It was so, so good.
Good. I'm just glad you're happy.
I'm just going to wash my
hands. Wait right here, okay?
Hello there.
Detective.
You're a little early. It'll
be about five more minutes.
That's fine. I don't mind waiting.
Okay. You know, seeing
as you buy one every day,
your son must really love pizza.
Yes. He especially loves your pizza.
That's great to hear.
You should bring him by sometime.
I'll throw in something on the house.
I'd love to, but he's really
shy around strangers.
At that age, they're all...
- Can I pay?
- Yes, that'll be 42 dollars.
That was delicious. Thank you.
Counselor?
Sorry?
You don't remember me?
I'm Detective Jo Chi Yeong
from the Seocho Police Station.
Shin Yi Rang, your
lawyer is here to see you.
Hey, you have a cop friend?
- So cool!
- When you were in for juvenile assault,
we met back then.
Hey, who did you hit?
Detective, about that... They
were the aggressors, remember?
That's right. My apologies.
It was a slip of the tongue.
No, don't worry about it.
Since you're in the Detective
Division, you might know something.
I'm looking for a boy
who had an accident
at the Good Shot Golf Driving Range,
do you happen to know anything about it?
- At the Good Shot Golf Driving Range?
- Yes, he's about
a 1st or 2nd grader. He was
wearing yellow rain boots.
Let me see. I don't recall a case like that.
Why? What's this about?
I know the kid, but he
can't remember the accident.
So I was just wondering
if you knew anything.
- It's okay if you don't.
- All right, you're all set.
Okay. I'll be going then.
- Take care, Counselor.
- You too.
Hey, Senior Officer Lee, did any
missing person reports come in?
Oh? Yes, I was just about to tell you, sir.
A report for a missing elementary
student came in a little while ago.
- An elementary schooler?
- Yes, an 8-year-old 1st grader.
- Description?
- White sweatshirt and yellow rain boots.
A boy, maybe 1st or 2nd grade,
and he was wearing yellow rain boots.
Text me all the details.
- Yes, sir.
- Okay.
(Pit-a-Pat Butcher Restaurant,
Shin Yi Rang Law Office)
My son overslept that day.
He normally wakes up with no problem,
but for some reason, he
just couldn't get up that day.
I felt his forehead, and
he had a slight fever.
- Go on, get your shoes.
- All right, I'm heading out. Okay.
- My wife leaves for work earlier than me.
- Si Ho.
So I was the one who got
our son ready for school.
But I couldn't suddenly take
the day off because he was sick.
Si Ho, Daddy's got an
idea. Hold on a second.
So to cheer him up,
I got out his yellow rain boots.
It just so happened to be raining that day,
Ta-da! He loved wearing his rain boots.
Open the door, then the
umbrella 1st. Umbrella 1st.
Have a good day at school,
Si Ho. Okay, close the door.
Hurry on, go meet your friend.
Go on.
I never would've imagined
that it would be the
last time I saw my son.
The last time?
Like most couples who both work,
my wife and I took
turns picking up our son.
That day, it was my wife's turn.
But then...
(Yongjin Express, Fast
Delivery, Same-Day Delivery)
Can you pick up our son today? Sorry.
(School Bus Stop. Child Safety Zone)
(Yongjin Express)
By the time I saw her text and rushed over,
My son was already gone.
Si Ho!
Excuse me! Sir, have you
seen a boy about this tall?
He was wearing a blue backpack,
He's in the first grade, and
he wore yellow rain boots.
He was wearing his yellow rain boots.
Have you seen him?
- Sorry, I haven't.
- Si Ho!
Yoon Si Ho!
Si Ho!
Where on earth are you?
And so, after our son disappeared,
My wife and I
were plunged into a living hell.
(Pit-a-Pat Butcher Restaurant,
Shin Yi Rang Law Office)
Detective?
I checked, and an elementary
student was in fact reported missing.
So I wanted to talk to you
about it more, Counselor.
Perfect.
In that case, would you
like to look around with me?
I figured searching together would
be faster than for me to explain.
So you think the kid is in here, Counselor?
Yes. I can't get into the specifics,
but I have a strong feeling that he is.
Will you come with me?
If a child is in danger,
it's our duty to save him.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
Could you wait here for just a moment?
Sure.
While I go with the police officer,
I need you to wait right here, okay?
Can't I go with you?
You know how some things
on TV are for grown-ups only?
This is one of those times.
It might be dangerous in there for a kid.
But I want to stay with you.
I'll be right back, okay?
I'm scared of being alone.
Here, the Lightning Man.
- Here, why not watch this for a bit?
- Okay.
- Shall we go?
You're even getting your gun ready?
You can never be too careful.
I feel much safer with you here, Detective.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
(Good Shot Golf Range, GSG)
(CCTV recording in progress)
By the way, how did you
find out about this place?
You can't tell me that either?
I'm sorry. You wouldn't
believe me even if I told you.
Hey, where are Officer
Park and Sergeant Kim?
They just went out on
a public intoxication call.
Then get ready, Officer Kim. A
missing person report just came in.
- A missing person?
- Yes, it's under an embargo for now,
and there's no evidence of
kidnapping or contact from the culprit.
Start canvassing the
neighborhood for now. Got it?
I emailed you the flyer, so
take a look and print it out. Okay?
(Seocho Police Station: Request
to Circulate Missing Child Flyer)
(Details: Kwon Ye Jun, Male, Age 8)
(Wearing: White sweatshirt,
blue jeans, and yellow rain boots)
Then what about the record for
the child in the yellow rain boots?
You should focus on
that fatal accident case.
Did you hear that?
There's a construction site nearby.
It sounds like it's coming from there.
Is that it?
No, that's not it.
It sounded much closer.
That missing child from earlier,
when was the report filed?
- This morning.
- This morning?
That doesn't make sense.
There's another one.
- What do you mean?
- There's another missing child.
Counselor.
By any chance...
Have you ever been here before,
back when it was a shaman's house?
How did you know that?
The child's ghost.
I'm sorry to ask,
but could you please tell me
your son's name and birthday?
Why do you ask?
Power!
I figured out who the child is.
Born April 16, 2017.
(Yoon Si Ho. Born: April 16, 2017)
Yoon Si Ho.
(Yoon Si Ho)
Butterfly - Butterfly.
Look at him smile.
Goodness.
(Police)
I'm sure I heard it from over here.
Who on earth are you, jerk?
Hey there, kiddo.
What are you doing here?
Shouldn't you be home?
Mister, that cop is dangerous.
- Lieutenant.
- How did you know about this place?
How can you possibly know about
something that happened a year ago!
Help me!
See? Now you've scared the kid.
It was you.
You were the culprit all along.
- Help me!
- My goodness.
Darn it!
Just die.
Hands up!
- I'm Jo Chi Yeong, Seocho Police.
- Show me your ID.
I'm here looking for the missing child.
- Yes, sir.
- Right.
- What about him?
- Him? He's the suspect.
I have to take him in,
so lend me your cuffs.
Yes, sir.
Mister! Snap out of it!
I'll help you.
We have to defeat the bad cop!
Lightning Man, let's go!
No, don't.
You could get hurt again.
Don't.
No, don't.
Excuse me, sir. Is that white
SUV parked outside yours?
Yes. Why?
Never mind, sir.
Lightning Man, change of plans.
Hide.
Darn it.
Where's the other one hiding?
You're not listening to Daddy, are you?
I guess my boy needs a lesson.
What did Daddy tell you?
I told you, good little boys
are supposed to be quiet.
Please, spare me.
I told you, if you just
bear with it a little longer,
you can live with me.
How many times do I have to tell you?
How many more people have
to die before you'll listen to me?
That does it. Come here.
Freeze!
- Power up!
- Lightning! Lightning Power!
Justice is served.
Time to change back into a regular guy!
Hey, kiddo. Are you okay?
Mister!
- The hospital. We have to get there now.
- Right.
(Pit-a-Pat Butcher Restaurant)
Don't worry.
It's all over now.
Okay.
The phone is turned off. Please
leave a message after the tone...
Why is it off?
I hope nothing's happened to him.
(Seoin Hospital)
(Emergency Medical Center)
Emergency patient! We need help out here.
- Sir! Are you okay?
- Sir, sir! Stay with me!
Emergency! Clear a path!
Sir! Can you hear me?
Try to open your eyes. Sir!
- Coming through!
- Sir, try to stay with us!
What do we have?
Penetrating wound to the right flank.
- Vitals unstable from massive blood loss.
- Where's his family?
We're trying to contact them now.
Hello?
I'm calling from Seoin Hospital.
Do you know Mr. Shin Yi Rang?
Yes, I do.
Mr. Shin Yi Rang was brought
in, and he's in critical condition.
We found this number on his necklace and...
Hello? Hello?
I'm on my way.
I'll be right there.
(Okcheon Building)
Hey, Han.
Listen, there's something
I need to tell you.
What's wrong?
What's wrong? What happened? Tell me.
Yi Rang is...
What about Shin Yi Rang?
He's at the hospital.
I have to go.
You're going to drive like this?
I'm telling you, I have to get to Yi Rang.
- I'm going to wipe this clean. Okay.
- Wipe right here, please.
- Bong Soo.
- Yes?
- Call Yi Rang and ask when he's home.
- Sure. Right away.
(Emergency Medical Center)
- Excuse me, where is Shin Yi Rang?
- Are you his next of kin?
I'm so sorry, but he was already
unconscious when he was brought in...
No.
I should have been there.
I should have been there with him.
What's this?
Don't tell me... Am I dead?
I...
Am I really dead?
(Phantom Lawyer)
- Yi Rang. Honey, Mom's here!
- Doctor!
I'm begging you, please.
We've already attempted
CPR several times, but...
- Mister, please don't go.
- Who are you?
- No.
- Who am I?
Our Si Ho will be fine.
They say Jo Chi Yeong is
pleading the fifth about Si Ho.
- I don't know who Si Ho is.
- Then he must be completely insane.
- Because there isn't enough evidence yet.
- What do you know?
You promised you'd find my mom.