(Watch on www.kisskh.li Support Admin)
"Contrast"
(Episode 4: Just Pretend to Be Asleep)
What was he trying to do just now?
Akira...
A kiss?
No, I...
But...
That's not the point...
Oh, Akira, did you finish the assignment?
Yeah, I'm done.
That was fast.
You're not finished yet?
There's no way I could
finish it that quickly.
Whoa, that was close...
You okay?
Watch where you're going.
Yeah.
I've been craving this so much.
And they were out of my usual
bacon bread today.
What kind of bread is that even?
Come on, I got curry bread too.
- Curry bread again? With apple juice?
- I have curry bread every day.
I'm seriously sick of it.
What's up?
Hmm?
It's nothing.
You're just hoping some cute girl
will come confess to you, right?
- Right?
- Hey, where? Where is she?
That's not it.
Makki, let's go.
See ya, Kanata.
- You're addicted to that curry bread.
- Hey, wait up!
Hey, by the way...
Back then, weren't
our faces... really close?
No, wait...
A kiss.
Were you trying to kiss me?
Huh?
I knew it.
You were pretending to be asleep.
What are you talking about?
Never mind then.
Anyway...
You're not really the type
to make jokes like that, Akira.
Like what?
How do I put it...
You don't seem like the
type to talk about dirty stuff.
Not really.
I talk about it.
With who?
You're asking me with who...
(Kanda Yoichi: Usual time?)
Who's Kanda?
A friend of my brother's.
You have a brother?
How old is he?
Around 23, I think.
Wait, don't tell me...
You talk about dirty stuff with adults?
I guess so.
Wait, Akira, are you...?
Oh... never mind.
No comment.
Ah, don't say anything.
You don't have to say it.
I didn't even give you an answer.
Oh, right...
I guess so...
Yeah.
I feel like...
there's still so much I
don't know about you.
Yeah.
Makeup classes are exhausting.
Good work.
Want to walk home together?
Sure.
He's really working hard.
Yeah.
That competitive streak
of his hasn't changed.
Mm-hmm.
But I feel like...
he's a bit different now.
Oh?
It's just...
How do I say it? He's
started to smile for real.
Yeah.
Oh, the day after tomorrow...
I'm going to a late-night
movie with Kanata.
Mizuki, do you want to come?
Oh, I'd love to.
OK, I'll book the seats then.
Thanks.
By the way...
How's Hikaru doing lately?
Oh...
My brother?
He seemed fine when we
talked on the phone recently.
I see.
You guys don't keep in touch?
Not as much as we used to.
Oh, it's not like we're on bad terms.
It's just that I'm working...
and he's still in grad school.
We just naturally talk less.
Right.
Hard to believe how close we used to be.
I'm back.
Excuse me.
This guy is your tutor.
Tutor?
Yeah, a friend from high school.
He's been to our house plenty of times.
I thought you said you'd stop
cram school before summer...
Yoichi was looking for a part-time
job, so I thought it'd be perfect.
Entrance exams are important, after all.
If you're okay with it, Akira.
I...
I'd appreciate it.
Good.
Looking forward to working with you.
Do you like music too, Akira?
I... don't really know much about it.
I see.
My brother's the one into it.
He listens to really trendy stuff.
If you were to listen...
is there a specific kind of music you like?
Hmm...
Maybe something loud.
Loud?
Like...
something that feels cathartic.
Something where...
you don't have to think
about anything while listening.
In that case, I have a few recommendations.
They're foreign bands.
I have the CDs. I'll bring them next time.
Thanks.
Hikaru didn't seem to like this style much.
When the band came to Japan...
I ended up going by myself.
Oh, but we did go to a
music festival together.
You guys are really close.
Ever since my brother came back...
he's always been with you.
He's in Kansai now, so
it's hard to see each other.
We weren't in the same
class in high school...
but I remember wondering
who was getting better grades than me.
Turns out it was him.
You're both pretty amazing.
But your grades are good too, right, Akira?
They're okay.
But I've never been top of the class.
Hey, that's still impressive.
Well... I guess.
Compared to my brother...
I really can't beat him at anything.
Do you feel inferior?
If there's ever a day you don't need to
maintain that balance, make sure to tell me.
Okay...
Come on, just tell me.
You actually have a girlfriend, don't you?
What school does she go to?
I'm not sure if I'd call
it "liking" someone...
but there's someone
who kind of feels that way?
Senkawa-kun.
Thanks for the other day.
About Kanata.
Oh... I didn't really do much.
I think Kanata has changed
since he met you.
Huh?
It's like he's back to how he was
when he took soccer seriously.
I'm really happy about it.
I see.
So...
thank you, really.
Sure.
If you don't mind...
want to walk to the station together?
Oh, okay.
Senkawa-kun.
Do you study more after cram school?
Huh?
That person we ran into...
didn't you say he was your tutor?
Oh...
He's my tutor, but...
he's actually a friend of my brother's.
I see. So you have a brother.
Yeah.
He's at university in Kyoto right now.
Oh, Kyoto.
That's nice. I've never been there.
Um...
Yeah?
There's something I wanted to ask.
What is it?
Kanata...
Hmm?
Sorry.
Never mind.
Yo.
Good work today.
Ah...
My muscles are killing me.
How's the club?
How's it going?
It's alright.
Are you having fun?
Yeah.
I mean, I am...
but it's complicated.
We didn't even make it past the
prelims for the next tournament.
But I'm just a rookie...
so I don't really have a right to complain.
I see.
Oh, but there are some
surprisingly good guys.
Next year should be more interesting.
I guess that sounds a bit cocky.
I'm just glad you're getting to play.
Yeah.
Getting sleepy?
Think of it as a reward for working hard.
What's that supposed to mean?
Hey.
Hmm?
Akira...
Have you ever kissed anyone?
What about you, Kanata?
Ah.
That's not fair.
I asked first.
I have.
You?
Me too.
Someone you were dating?
No.
Someone you liked?
Who knows...
What? That's so vague.
What about you?
Me...
Like I said before...
I didn't really care about anything.
As long as I had something
to do besides soccer.
So... I was just messing around.
Just to distract myself.
Do you look down on me?
No.
I see.
I thought you'd be more
serious about that stuff.
But I'm different now.
Oh.
But...
You knew I was pretending to be asleep...
and you still did that to me.
Huh?
At the festival.
You got really close to my face.
Oh...
Sorry.
Stop messing with me.
I wasn't messing with you.
It's just...
I was a little jealous of you.
What do you mean?
I thought if I got closer to you...
maybe I could become more like you.
You want to be like me?
Better not. Your grades will tank.
Though you'd get better at soccer.
True.
But the grades part is a bit...
We're different, and
that's a good thing, right?
Besides, even if we got that close...
it wouldn't make you be like me.
You're right.
You're changing the subject, aren't you?
Is that not allowed?
No.
This time... you should
pretend to be asleep too.
Crap, I gotta go.
Hey, we're all going to a movie today.
You want to come, Akira?
Sorry.
- I'm seeing my brother today...
- Oh, I see.
See you next time, then.
What's wrong?
Huh?
Your face is bright red.
I'm almost late.
That's why I was running.
Okay.
Now then.
This poem describes the joy of
seeing a loved one in a dream...
and the sadness of waking up.
Wanting to see the person
you love, even in a dream...
To care for someone that much...
is actually a beautiful thing.
Sorry I'm late.
No worries.
I was just killing time
around here anyway.
By the way, where's Jun?
Oh, he messaged saying he'll be a bit late.
And he's the one who insisted we go today.
Oh.
Should we see if Senkawa-kun wants to join?
If he just finished cram school...
he should still be around here.
No need.
He has plans today.
Something with his brother.
Huh?
I heard Akira has a brother.
Yeah, I know.
We talked about it on the
way back from cram school.
Oh, really?
But...
I heard his brother is
at university in Kyoto.
Wait, what?
I mean, maybe he's back for a visit.
I guess.
How do I put this...
Akira...?
(Next Episode)
Let's have a training camp.
Are you even trying to study?
Wow, amazing.
Wait, only mine has brakes!
Kanata.
Why did you kiss me?