[A Splendid Match]
[Episode 27]
When a nation is about to fall,
traitors like you always appear.
I'm willing to risk my life
to purge you rom our land.
Marquis Changxing's spirit
is truly formidable.
But don't forget
that your son is still in my hands.
If you're not afraid
of leaving your line without an heir,
then go ahead and take my head.
You!
Do it.
My Lord.
Ye Xian suddenly fell ill.
It doesn't look good.
What have you done to him?
Go check on him now.
[Marquis of Changxing's Signed Confession]
This...
He's still breathing.
Fetch a physician immediately.
My Lord.
Ye Xian is still Marquis Changxing's heir.
If anything happens to him,
I'm afraid His Majesty
will hold us accountable.
The Penal Court can't shoulder this blame.
Well, then report it to the court.
Yes!
Take the pill.
I'll make sure Ye Xian
takes the poison.
It'll force his blood
to circulate violently
and trigger a heart attack.
When it happens,
you go in under the excuse
of checking on him,
and give him the antidote.
As long as he receives it in time,
it won't do much harm to his body.
My Lady.
Qingpu, how is it?
Young Lord Ye...
and the Marquis have both been released,
and returned to the Marquis's Mansion.
Thank goodness.
Wait.
If they're already back home,
then I don't need to visit him myself.
I'll ask Fifth Aunt
to pass it along for me.
Let's go.
Ye,
if you walk out of this Gu Mansion today,
don't think about coming back!
So be it.
I don't care about this place anyway.
Dismissed.
Whether you like it or not,
you're not leaving.
Today, within this mansion,
not a single person,
high or low,
no one can leave the mansion
without my permission.
You...
Grandmother.
You're trying this hard to stop her—
does that mean you're certain
that the Senior Grand Secretary
would bring down Marquis Changxing,
and the Gu family'd be implicated as well?
Exactly.
That is a matter
of life and death,
so we can't afford to be careless.
But have you considered what happens
if the Senior Grand Secretary fails?
How many military generals in Great Yan
once served under the Marquis?
Now that the Marquis is in trouble,
we, as their relatives by marriage,
are actively stopping Fifth Aunt
from returning home to support her family.
Forget how disgraceful it would look
if word gets out.
If the Marquis family
ever recovers its footing
and decides to settle scores—
do you really think our family's status
is enough to withstand the revenge
of the entire military nobility?
What do you mean?
Did Lord Chen
tell you the Marquis family
would come through this unharmed?
He would never tell me such things.
But if you've been reading
the imperial bulletin lately, you'd know
the court's peace talks
with the Nothern Barbarians
have been dragging on without result.
If the talks fail,
there will be war.
And once war breaks out...
If I were you,
I would simply turn a blind eye
and let Fifth Aunt
come and go as she pleases.
No matter what happens
to the Marquis family,
if anyone questions us later,
we can stand firm and say,
"We're family by marriage.
Who wouldn't help
their own kin?"
Old Madam,
Marquis Changxing's Mansion men are here,
saying Young Lord Ye
suffered a sudden heart attack in prison,
and the Marquis collapsed on the spot.
They've been brought back
to the mansion for treatment.
Fifth Madam is requested
to go back and look after him.
I'll go back right now.
I'll go back right away.
Fifth Aunt,
you may take my carriage.
I'll see you off.
Let's go.
Fifth Aunt.
there's something I need to tell you.
But you must promise me
not to breathe a word of it to anyone,
including the Marquis
and his wife.
Otherwise,
the whole Marquis family
will be in danger.
If it concerns the safety
of the Marquis family,
I won't say a word.
Actually,
Ye Xian's heart attack wasn't a relapse,
but was induced with medicine,
intentionally.
Because it was the only way
to get the Marquis released.
His Majesty wants
to save Marquis Changxing,
but doesn't dare openly defy the mentor.
And with the Marquis Changxing's temper,
even under torture,
he'd never yield and beg for mercy.
He might even
say something treacherous
that would only worsen his situation.
So,
the only option was to rely on Ye Xian—
to have him enter prison with his father.
That way,
Marquis Changxing would think of his son
and wouldn't be so stubborn.
Once Ye Xian collapsed,
Marquis Changxing
would have no choice but to yield,
which would give His Majesty an excuse
to plead on his behalf.
It seems
the pill prepared
by the Marquis's Mansion worked.
His pulse is stable now.
It's just that His Lordship's
long illness,
combined with his time in prison,
has taken a severe toll on his body.
He needs proper care.
I will write a prescription.
Have him take it for half a month
and see how it goes.
Thank you for your trouble.
This way.
Thanks for your trouble.
My Lady,
Fifth Madam has arrived.
Fifth Aunt.
How is he?
He's taken the medicine.
The imperial physician said
his pulse is stable now.
That's good to hear.
Xian is blessed by heaven—
he made it through,
and brought Father home with him.
Right.
Thank heavens and the bodhisattvas.
Has Miss Gu left yet?
She wouldn't come inside,
and I didn't dare invite her in.
If Xian sees her,
it'll only cause another scene.
Gu Jinzhao.
Gu Jin...
-Xian.
-Xian!
Xian.
Is Gu Jinzhao here?
Where is she?
You can't get out of bed yet.
Let her in.
-I have something to ask her.
-Don't do this, Xian!
Xian!
Mother, don't stop him.
Let him go.
Zhao is waiting outside the door.
If you don't care
about this family anymore
and want to piss your parents to death,
then go find her!
But even if you go out there—
what then?
Zhao would rather wait at the door
than step inside.
Don't you understand what that means?
Even if you won't think of us,
at least think of her.
Xian,
I'm begging you.
For the sake of our old and frail parents,
and me, a married daughter
who's utterly powerless—
please stop chasing after Zhao.
Stop making a scene,
will you?
Xian,
I'm begging you.
Just listen to your sister.
Our family
cannot take any more of this.
Xian.
I know.
I won't go to her.
You may leave now.
Leave!
As soon as I heard that Ye Xian's
heart condition had relapsed
and Marquis Changxing had
coughed up blood on the spot,
I was so anxious
that I had them both sent back
to the mansion for treatment.
Looking back now,
it was rather hasty.
I hope you can forgive me, Mr. Fu.
Your Majesty overstates the matter.
[Honor and Illumination]
Your Majesty is kind and generous.
It's truly a blessing for Great Yan.
It's just that Marquis Changxing
has always been arrogant
and obstinate.
Your Majesty
alawys treats him with kindness,
but he
fails to appreciate it.
Your Majesty,
Lord Chen Yanyun
is already waiting outside.
Let him in.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
You may rise, Chen Yanyun.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Grand Secretary.
Chen Yanyun,
I heard that
while interrogating Marquis Changxing,
you were nearly killed by him.
Thank you for your concern, Your Majesty,
but I didn't suffer any losses.
Ye Xian spoke insolently
and openly resisted arrest.
And I
nearly strangled him to death.
Ye Xian has always been impulsive.
I've warned him so many times,
yet he never listens.
Both you and Ye Xian
are my most trusted ministers.
Why let a moment of anger
escalate things this far?
Your Majesty.
There is a limit to what a man can endure.
Ye Xian ruined the reputation
of my fiancée
and tried to assassinate me in the street.
I cannot
simply let that pass.
I ask for Your Majesty's understanding.
Has Marquis Changxing
confessed yet?
Marquis Changxing
had stubbornly refused to confess.
But when he heard that Ye Xian
had suffered a sudden heart attack,
he coughed up blood on the spot.
After receiving Your Majesty's pardon,
he returned
to Marquis Changxing's Mansion to recover.
From his sickbed,
he wrote a memorial
and asked me
to present it to Your Majesty.
[Ashamed to face my old friends, I beg
Your Majesty to strip me of my post]
[For the sake of my humble service,
please allow my bones to return home]
Marquis Changxing's requesting retirement.
It seems seeing Ye Xian so gravely ill
has truly broken his spirit.
Your Majesty,
although Marquis Changxing
has requested retirement,
he hasn't formally confess to the charges.
Since you and Ye Xian are at odds,
then for this case,
you should have recused yourself from it.
Your Majesty.
But...
Yes.
Mr. Fu,
Marquis Changxing
has outstanding military achievements.
When Prince Ruichang rebelled,
he risked his life to defend the throne.
He has made great contributions
to Great Yan.
Perhaps, we can spare him this time?
Since Your Majesty pleads
on Marquis Changxing's behalf,
I shall obey the decree.
However, the laws of the nation is clear.
We cannot
treat them too lightly.
Lord Chen,
when the imperial physician returned
from the mansion, what did he say?
Grand Secretary,
during the previous palace coup,
Marquis Changxing
suffered severe injuries
and never fully recovered.
Now, after with
Young Lord Ye's sudden heart attack,
he coughed blood on the spot.
His condition has worsened even more.
The physician's assessment
was that the damage is irreversible.
Irreversible?
In that case,
we shall spare Marquis Changxing.
Mr. Fu, you're truly magnanimous!
Issue the decree.
Considering Marquis Changxing's
past campaigns for the nation,
and his role in suppressing
the northern barbarians,
his contribution to the nation shall
offset his offense against the throne.
I hope that the father and son
will live up to my expectations
and make no more mistakes.
I hear and obey.
If Your Majesty wants
to save Marquis Changxing's life
and his reputation,
then forgive me, I cannot do that.
But...
if Your Majesty merely wants
to save Marquis Changxing's reputation,
then there may still be a way.
It may be
worth trying.
What is it?
Make Marquis Changxing
understand the stakes.
Make him bow his head first,
and
it must be genuine.
Bow his head?
Let alone Marquis Changxing,
even I, the Emperor,
must sometimes do the same.
[Ji family's Silk Store]
His Majesty
has pardoned Marquis Changxing's Mansion.
So the Marquis Changxing
and his family are safe now?
Yes.
That's great.
What a relief.
I want to thank you on Ye Xian's behalf.
There's no need to thank me.
Marquis Changxing
dedicated his life to military service
and made contributions to the country.
Even if His Majesty had said nothing,
I would have found a way to save him.
Right now,
the peace talks
with the Northern barbarians
are still unresolved.
If the northern side were to learn
that Marquis Changxing
had been imprisoned and gravely ill—
they might start the war again.
My mentor considered this as well.
He was afraid that Marquis Changxing
would suddenly pass away
before the peace talks concluded,
so he decided to let him off this time.
Then how serious
is Marquis Changxing's condition?
He doesn't have much time left.
I've managed to protect his reputation,
but Marquis Changxing family's prestige,
built over decades,
is difficult to sustain.
That year,
when I had become my mentor's disciple,
the Yellow River flooded,
and my mentor didn't sleep
for three days and nights.
His mouth
was full of blisters.
I was by his side,
attending to his writing needs.
I told him
he was pushing himself too hard,
and he said,
"Our suffering
will eventually end,
but the suffering of the common people
never does."
But what about now?
From the palace coup,
to replacing disaster relief grain
with bran,
to what happened
with Marquis Changxing's family—
I'm afraid my mentor
has already lost his original intention.
I remember
when I was seven,
after the great victory at Hulan Pass,
Marquis Changxing
watered his horse by the Wuliang River
and composed a poem
that became widely known:
"Becoming a lord is not my desire,
I only wish for everlasting peace."
Becoming a lord is not my desire,
You are right.
Why aren't you eating?
Even if you have no appetite,
at least drink some soup.
I can't.
You can't keep
ruining your health like this.
If you collapse,
what am I supposed to do?
What are your parents supposed to do?
Your Lordship,
Miss Xue sent someone over with gifts.
Miss Xue?
Who?
Xue Qinglan?
Exactly.
Throw them out.
Your Lordship,
there's ten-year-old ginseng
and the finest borneol among them.
Throw them out!
Understood.
[House of Virtue and Brilliance]
108 bolts of Yunjin brocade;
18 pairs of layered filigree
gold ruyi hairpins;
[66,600 taels of fine silver]
and the wedding money...
Why are there so many betrothal gifts?
Third Brother adores his future wife.
I showed him the draft
[Orchid Chamber Fragrance]
of the betrothal gift list,
and he added more items himself—
all from his own savings,
not the common fund.
So I couldn't say much about it.
He's practically giving away
his entire fortune.
The wedding is set on the 16th
of the second lunar month.
The Gu family sent word earlier
that they will formally
add to the dowry the day after tomorrow.
I didn't dare neglect the matter,
so I picked a pair
of filigree gold hairpins
and a pair of jade bracelets.
I'll have Sixth Sister deliver them.
Mother,
will you
also...
Adding to the dowry
is the bride's family's business.
Zhao
is my sister's
most beloved child.
The Ji family will certainly be generous
with the dowry additions.
There is no need for me to join the crowd.
Yes.
Never mind.
I do have a white jade ruyi here.
Take it with you,
and have Ying deliver it
along with the rest.
Sure thing,
my dear mother,
I knew you were the most generous of all.
By the way.
Second Master sent a letter yesterday,
saying he will come
for Third Brother's wedding banquet.
He should be leaving soon.
I've also sent a letter to Xuanqing,
asking him to return as soon as possible.
What's wrong, Mother?
She’s about to marry into the family,
and you still haven't
gotten over it?
You saw right through me.
To be honest,
I'm truly unhappy about it.
Mother,
Third Brother has risen rapidly
these past few years,
holding high positions and great power.
At court,
he's used to having the final say.
[Orchid Chamber Fragrance]
So when he returns home,
he naturally isn't accustomed
to being told what to do.
Besides,
Old Madam Ji
also just found out about it, didn't she?
But to put it bluntly,
there's indeed some suspicion
that he and Miss Gu
were privately involved
before the engagement.
You call that merely a suspicion?
[Thrice Reflections Against Greed;
Ninefold Virtues in the Sound of the Qin]
Send this over for her dowry ceremony
the day after tomorrow.
I was taking a nap,
and you called me over so urgently
just to deliver something?
Besides,
Jinzhao is already so wealthy.
Does she really need you
to add to her dowry?
Whether she's rich or not is her business.
Adding to her dowry is simply my gesture.
Hurry and deliver it for me.
Don't worry.
Look.
This one is for you.
Do you like it?
Alright.
I'll deliver it for you.
Your ink bamboo painting
is getting better and better.
At first glance,
I thought it was painted by Third Master.
Third Uncle's ink bamboo has
such elegance and depth.
How could I possibly compare to him?
You're far too modest.
Third Master is indeed exceptional,
but you also passed the exam as a Tanhua.
You aren't
far behind him.
Go away.
All you know is how to flatter me.
My Lord, there's a letter for you.
It's from my youngest aunt.
She probably wants to know
when you'll arrive in the capital.
[Gu Mansion]
[Gu]
These are all for Miss Gu's dowry.
Not just the Ji family...
Welcome, Madam Liu.
and the Chen family too.
They said after Old Madam
saw
the Chen family's list of betrothal gifts,
she immediately had an empty storeroom
cleared out to place the gifts.
Welcome, Madam Wang.
[Gu]
Zhao.
Lian caught a cold last night.
Early this morning,
a physician wrote a prescription for her,
so I told her not to come,
in case she passed it on to you.
This
is her gift for your dowry.
And these
are from me.
I only wish that, in the future,
everything will go exactly as you wish.
Thank you, Second Aunt.
My Lady, Mrs. Mu is here.
I see.
Which Mrs. Mu?
The wife of Lord Mu Shi'an.
The newly appointed
Vice Minister of Personnel?
Your Second Uncle didn't get the post,
and neither did Yao Ping,
yet he ended up benefiting instead.
I'll go with you to take a look.
After you.
Greetings, Mrs. Mu.
My Master
has been friends with Lord Chen for years.
This time,
when we heard about this splendid match,
we were both truly delighted for him.
Look at this beautiful face.
[Mrs. Mu, Mu Shian's wife]
You and Lord Chen
are truly a match made in heaven.
You're being so kind, Mrs. Mu.
Lan, you're here.
Mrs. Mu,
this is my third sister, Lan.
This is Mrs. Mu.
Greetings, Second Aunt and Zhao.
Greetings, Mrs. Mu.
So you are Lan.
Yes.
Zhao,
I didn't have
anything worthy of giving,
so I sewed a wedding quilt
for you.
Something made with your own hands
is worth more than gold or silver.
The embroidery
is really something!
Did you embroider this yourself?
Yes.
What a wonderful needlework!
I'll pack the wedding quilt
into the chest.
Okay.
Miss Gu,
the Sixth Miss of the Chen family is here.
Someone from the Chen family came as well?
I'll go welcome her.
Yanying,
I thought
you weren't coming today.
I didn't want to come.
But someone was worried
you'd feel slighted,
so he insisted I come over
to deliver gifts for your dowry day.
My dear sister, it's my fault.
I shouldn't have kept it from you.
Since you know you were wrong,
let me ask you something.
At your coming-of-age ceremony,
Yanyun was there too.
Was that when the two of you
start seeing each other?
Of course not.
What about the Mid-Autumn Festival
when we admired the chrysanthemums?
I don't think so.
Then when was it?
It couldn't possibly be
during the Spring Outing, right?
Wait, I know!
Was it in Tongzhou?
I remember two years ago,
Yanyun was in Tongzhou for a long time.
Were you in Tongzhou too?
Come with me.
I'm not done asking questions yet.
Don't think you can bribe me.
These were carved
by the best craftsman in Jiangnan.
There are 12 in total.
Each one has a different shape.
What are you doing?
As long as you promise me
not to ask any more questions,
and I'll give you
all of these.
How could you do this?
There's also a set of eight
jade puppies.
I came here to deliver gifts
for your dowry.
Why are you giving me
gifts instead?
And there are also four little jade boys.
If you wind up the mechanism,
they can even do flips.
Greetings, Third Sister-in-law!
I suddenly don't want to ask anything.
As long as you and Yanyun are happy.
Miss Yu is here.
[Generations of Excellence]
Wanxue.
What took you so long?
The banquet is about to start.
I had no choice.
I was going to leave early,
but my stepmother suddenly said
she had a headache.
I almost couldn't leave.
Luckily, Father came and helped me out.
I don't have anything especially fine
to give you, Zhao.
This box contains
the latest eyebrow powder.
And this
is the scented powder I made myself—
it's better than what you can buy outside.
And here is a box of silver ingots
for you to reward the servants with.
They're all great and very useful.
I like them all.
Hold on.
You're engaged to Xuanqing now.
You shouldn't call her Zhao anymore,
instead you should call her Aunt,
And you shouldn't call her Wanxue either—
you should call her Niece-in-law.
I thought about it all night yesterday,
whether I should call you Zhao
or Aunt.
But in the end,
I still called you Zhao.
I really couldn't call you Aunt.
Just call me Zhao.
Don't worry about the seniority.
You two might be willing
to keep it that way,
but I'm certainly not.
Come here, my dear niece-in-law.
Give your Aunt a shoulder rub.
Give you an inch and you take a mile!
I'm not talking to you.
I'm going to put these away.
She's shy.
Look at you.
I'm not talking to you either.
I'll go prepare the banquet.
Are you coming with me?
[Generations of Excellence]
Let's go.
Just place it behind that box.
My Lady.
Since Miss Ying is also here today,
why don't you ask her
about your marriage to Young Master Chen
and what exactly
the Chen family is planning?
How could I possibly
be the one to ask?
But, My Lady,
the Chen family scheduled the wedding
for the end of last year.
Then, out of nowhere, Young Master Chen
suddenly went to Shanxi for peace talks
with the northern barbarians.
Forgive me for speaking bluntly,
since he already
had a marriage arrangement,
why would he accept such an assignment?
If it were anyone else,
naturally they couldn't refuse
an order from the Imperial Court.
But Young Master Chen
is Lord Chen's own nephew—
going or staying
was entirely up to one word
-from Lord Chen.
-Enough.
I've clearly spoiled you too much.
You're speaking completely out of line.
[Chen Mansion]
[Orchid Chamber Fragrance]
Mother.
Xuanqing
has truly grown into a fine,
accomplished man.
Honestly,
the mansion feels so empty without you
around to liven things up.
Xuanqing.
Xuanqing?
Second Aunt.
I was distracted just now.
What were you saying?
[Orchid Chamber Fragrance]
Oh, nothing much.
I was just saying
you've truly become an accomplished man.
When I walked in just now
and saw you sitting there,
for a moment
I thought
I was looking at your Third Uncle.
It's a long and exhausting journey
back from Shanxi.
You must be very tired.
Hurry back and get some rest.
Thank you, Grandmother.
I have something to discuss with you.
I've been in Shanxi for half a year,
and there is still much unfinished work.
I was thinking
of moving into the Hanlin Academy
quarters tomorrow,
and returning after the offices close.
How busy can the Hanlin Academy be?
Don't carry
the weight of the world on your shoulders.
Rest for a few days
before taking on your next assignment.
Besides,
in a few days,
your Third Uncle is getting married.
You can return to work
after attending the wedding banquet.
[Orchid Chamber Fragrance]
Right,
don't forget about the Yu family.
Now that you're back,
remember to
visit your future in-laws early,
so they won't find fault with you.
Yes, Grandmother.
♪ Once I wrote of spring and fall ♪
♪ Yet fell through time's abyss ♪
♪ Every shade turned bitter ♪
♪ Every longing became sorrow ♪
♪ I've seen through right and wrong ♪
[Shunning the World, Returning to Nature]
♪ Old vows washed away like ash ♪
♪ True devotion is knowing
the freedom within your heart♪
♪ Word by word, hand in hand ♪
♪ My heart grows cold like rust ♪
♪ The stars send you far away ♪
♪ Yet one thought still remains ♪
Now you know
the so-called truth.
Whether to get married to the Yu family
♪ You share bright days with another ♪
and try to keep this secret
as tightly as possible,
♪ I walk with my lonely shadow ♪
or to give up the marriage
♪ Filling every broken fold
with memories of us ♪
and prepare to face everything
after you pass the examination—
the choice is yours.
♪ We once drank to talk of love and hate ♪
♪ But we fell into
the deep ditch of rumors ♪
♪ Meeting and parting were like
moves on a chessboard ♪
♪ Every heartfelt word ended as a fault ♪
♪ Seen the sun rise and the moon set ♪
♪ Only sigh that we are no longer
on the same path ♪
♪ One wrong choice drove
my old friend away like a drifting bird ♪
♪ With every step, I look back ♪
♪ My heart grows cold like rust ♪
♪ The stars send you far away ♪
♪ Yet one thought still remains ♪
♪ You share bright days with another ♪
Yunting.
♪ I walk with my lonely shadow ♪
♪ Filling every broken fold
with memories of us ♪
Deliver this letter
to Miss Gu for me.
This is inappropriate!
I just want to see her.
What's inappropriate about that?
I just want to ask her
why she agreed to this marriage.
Does she have some hidden troubles?
Young Master, it's really inappropriate!
What if Third Master finds out?
♪ With every step, I look back ♪
If you are afraid,
I will deliver it myself.
No, no!
♪ My heart grows cold like rust ♪
Please don't.
Fine.
♪ The stars send you far away ♪
I'll go deliver it now.
♪ Yet one thought still remains ♪
Go now.
♪ You share bright days with another ♪
♪ I walk with my lonely shadow ♪
♪ Filling every broken fold
with memories of us ♪
My Lady.
This is the dowry gift
from Madam.
Madam said
she has been staying at the mansion
taking care of the Marquis these days.
She can't get the medicine smell off her,
so she won't come personally
to congratulate you.
Please give Fifth Aunt my thanks,
and send my regards to the Marquis.
Thank you, My Lady.
My Lady.
This...
Whose letter is it?
It's from Young Master Chen's servant,
[Respectfully Presented to Jinzhao]
Yunting.
He also said
that Young Master Chen,
has lost his appetite for days,
because you are getting married.
[Respectfully Presented to Jinzhao]
My Lady, aren't you going to read
what's written inside?
No need.
Even if I read it,
there's nothing I can do for him.
It would only upset me.
Indeed.
[Respectfully Presented to Jinzhao]
It was clearly Young Master Chen
who broke his promise first,
yet now he acts
as if he's the heartbroken one.
By the way,
if Yunting hasn't gone far yet,
catch up to him
and pass on a message for me.
Tell him to inform his master
to eat well and take care of himself.
I moved on a long time ago,
and he should do the same.
[Respectfully Presented to Jinzhao]
[A Splendid Match]