♪Just To Meet You, you fell for me♪
♪Just to meet me, into my trap you fell♪
♪Wanna try a breathless love?♪
♪Every move hits the heart, close and sure♪
♪Just To Meet You, you love my playful charm♪
♪Just to meet me,
my romantic little schemes for you♪
♪Wanna play another brand-new game?♪
♪Layer by layer, we close the gap♪
=Just To Meet You=
=Episode 14=
=Ye Lang Pleads for Love=
Mom.
My wish finally came true.
I'm taking Xiaodi
back to your hometown.
This will be the last time
I come to see you.
Sis.
Look!
It's snowing even in summer.
It's really snowing.
He didn't lie.
Niannian.
(One day earlier)
Here, Xiaodi.
Careful, it's hot.
We're leaving Manlong
and going to our mom's hometown.
Over there,
they've got better medical facilities.
It's a better place to live.
It's safer too.
From now on,
we won't have to live in fear anymore
and you won't get lost again.
Sis,
actually, these past few days,
Brother Ye's taken good care of me.
He's only doing it for his own reasons.
Sis.
Not like that.
I can feel it.
He's not bad.
- Xiaodi.
- Who are you?
Don't touch me!
My name is Ye Lang.
I'm your sister's...
friend.
My sister's friend?
Why have I never heard of you?
What did you do to her?
Xiaodi.
This hospital
is the best in all of Manlong.
Once you're better,
I'll take you to see her, okay?
Why should I believe you?
I want to see my sister now!
She asked me to give you this.
You really know my sister?
Mm.
Curry's autograph.
Once you're better,
I'll take you to play basketball
and take you both to an NBA game, okay?
From now on,
if you feel unwell,
go see Dr. Zheng.
He'll contact me.
You mean my sister took 200,000
and sold you to a rich woman?
Mm.
Absolutely true.
When I tried to leave,
that woman came
with eight bodyguards.
She said,
"Hey, handsome,
stay with me, and you'll live well."
That does sound like her.
She never trusted men,
only herself and money.
Back then, she...
Anyway,
my sister once said
if a man would protect her
and make money for her,
then love may happen.
I can protect her,
and I'm rich.
(Brother Ye Lang)
Xiaodi.
I'm going to propose to your sister.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Just have your surgery tomorrow.
When you two get married,
I'll bring the rings up myself.
Okay.
I'll walk your sister up there,
and place her hand in mine.
When the wedding comes,
I'll buy you the sharpest suit.
You'll be my best man.
Okay?
Xiaodi.
Promise me
you'll make it out of the Operating Room.
The three of us
still have a long future ahead.
Mm.
Don't worry.
I wanna be an uncle someday.
Okay.
Even if he did all that,
it's still true that he lied to me.
I just
don't want you to miss
someone good for both of us.
Sis,
can't you give him one more chance?
(When I checked his phone that day,)
(the message that led me here)
(didn't seem to be from him.)
(Could someone be stirring this up?)
(Jiang Niannian.)
(You're in trouble.)
(You're still making excuses for him.)
Forget it.
Get some rest.
We're leaving the day after tomorrow.
Mm.
How are you feeling?
My dear little heart.
You and Jiang Niannian
really are a perfect match.
I honestly thought this time
you'd end up on my autopsy table.
What do you mean?
The injury Jiang Niannian caused
didn't hit anything vital.
It was sharp enough
to avoid extra tissue damage.
Your real issue
was excessive blood loss.
The blood bank reserves
were used up during Xiaodi's surgery.
That's why you stayed unconscious.
In the previous life,
she clearly could have...
She clearly...
No.
Jiang Niannian didn't intend to hurt me.
Just like previous life,
it was a misunderstanding.
It wasn't her.
I was such an idiot.
She loved me so much.
How could she really do that?
It was me.
My own selfish desire.
I thought I could control it all.
What do I do?
I feel Jiang Niannian's leaving me.
Bro,
I have no interest in dissecting you now.
Just focus on recovering.
(At this point,)
(why am I still thinking of him?)
♪When I come back once again♪
♪I'd still walk toward you♪
♪Letting go of all calculations♪
♪Just to melt your frozen heart♪
♪When I let go of everything♪
I'm sorry.
Forget me.
♪Even if the seasons go astray♪
♪Cannot forget you
even if the world ends♪
♪I'll take you to see more views♪
♪And leave the mark of my love♪
♪The only answer♪
♪Is your name♪
♪Don't let me go♪
♪Let me believe it again♪
♪Shape unknown roads into your journey♪
Love-brain.
Your precious Jiang Niannian
ran away
with her brother.
Careful.
He didn't lie to me.
It's really snowing.
Niannian.
Snow can really happen in June.
Can our love
be reborn?
Sis.
Are you really leaving?
Mm.
Actually, that day I...
What is it?
You always said
I was your pride,
but I've always felt
I was your burden.
When Mom was leaving,
I promised her
I'd protect you.
But then I got sick.
You had to earn money
to treat me,
and that's why
Dad and that woman
kept using you.
That day,
I hid some sleeping pills.
I wanted to end all of this.
That way,
you wouldn't have to suffer more.
What did you say?
How could you think like that?
Brother Ye found it.
He saw I'd hidden sleeping pills,
but he didn't ask a thing.
He only said
that the one you loved most
was me.
That without me,
you wouldn't be able to go on.
He also said
he would
take my place
to protect you.
He promised
he'd save you
from those two awful people,
and free you from your past.
- (I promise I'd give her a freer future.)
- He promised he'd give you a freer future.
♪Stitched-up lips
tear open a blood-red dusk♪
♪You return reborn,
seeing through all my cracks♪
♪This tenderness, a trap or a gift?♪
♪Still, I'd wager my next life on it♪
♪Just for a moment to recognize you again♪
♪You are the blazing light in my despair♪
♪Lighting the edges of my frozen wings♪
♪I burn myself,
leaping into an illusion of fire♪
♪Breaking free
from dead vines in the ashes♪
♪You are the brightest star in the night♪
♪Awakening my dormant fate♪
♪Freeing me from this half-life prison♪
♪As the bells shatter the past♪
♪Life finds its way again♪