(Yoo Yeon Seok)
(Esom)
(Kim Kyung Nam)
(Kim Mi Kyung, Jeon Seok Ho, Son Yeo Eun, Lee A Rin)
(Choi Kwang Il, Jung Seung Gil, Yeon Je Hyung)
(Phantom Lawyer)
(Supported by Ministry of Culture, Sports and KOCCA)
(All people, places, and events in this drama are fictional.)
(Child actors filmed safely with guardians.)
(All scenes involving animals were staged...)
(and filmed safely by welfare standards.)
Darn it!
Lee Tae Geon! Stop right there!
Lee Tae Geon!
Where's Lee Tae Geon?
He got away.
I'll call the police first.
- I'll go look for the recorder then. - Okay.
(Okcheon Building)
What should we do about Han Na Hyun?
Do Kyung.
Forget about her. Just secure the recorder.
Come out.
They came to take something. And there were...
- Hello? - This is Lee Tae Geon.
I've secured the recorder.
(Episode 16)
The voice recorder...
He took it.
The Saryonghoe.
I put them behind bars, so I know them all too well.
When I wanted to know more about you, Dad,
someone told me...
that if I went to Chinatown,
I could learn more about you.
But there, I heard you were covering for Saryonghoe...
and taking bribes.
They said you were even more vicious...
to the merchants than the gangsters were.
I'll leave now.
The one who sent me there...
was Yang Byung Il.
Okay, first...
Let's start by finding Lee Tae Geon.
Then I'll have to go to Chinatown and meet with President Honggwan.
The fact that he lied about you, Dad...
It means he must be connected to them.
We barely got our hands on the recorder.
And now it's gone again.
Still, we're better off than when we hadn't even seen it.
You've grown into a fine man.
I learned from my father.
He's a truly great man.
(Taebaek)
The voice recorder?
Yes. I ordered Lee Tae Geon to take it.
Why are you only telling me this now?
- Where is the voice recorder? - Lee Tae Geon has it,
but he must be on the run. I can't reach him right now.
I told you to tell me first as soon as you found it!
Why are you so upset?
It's not like you killed someone, Father.
Do Kyung, look...
I'm glad you're looking for the recorder, but...
It's not just about the results. It's about how you get them.
You can't just stir up all this trouble.
Now go and clean this mess up quietly.
Understood.
I'll tell him to bring me the recorder as soon as I reach him.
But Dad...
Is there anything you still haven't told me?
- What are you talking about? - Anything at all.
If there is, please tell me now.
I said there's nothing!
How many times do I have to tell you? Now get out!
Goodness.
Chairman Yang, it's been a while.
Chief Justice.
We need to find Yoon Dae Myeong's recorder.
Who has it now?
Lee Tae Geon.
I'll send a police officer I can trust.
Darn, I keep putting too much power into it.
Maybe I should skip a meal.
I thought you worked best on a full stomach.
Or maybe I should just snap my wrist.
You're that desperate to win? Why are you so obsessed with winning?
Because I like winning.
In the end, the winner is the one who survives.
You know the saying, "It's the journey, not the destination?
That's just a load of nonsense meant to sound nice.
Still, I actually kind of like that "nonsense."
The results are temporary, but the process sticks with you.
The tough journeys are where you learn,
have realisations, and grow as a person.
You think so?
This...
is why I like you, Gi Jung. You see?
You have a purity that's so rare these days.
All right.
You're the one who survived,
and yet you still seem so anxious.
(Honggwan)
Mr. Park.
You made sure it wasn't too salty, right?
Of course. It's not salty at all.
Yes?
I see. Okay.
Well then, please enjoy your meal.
Hello, sir.
I'm Attorney Shin Yi Rang. We met about Prosecutor Shin Gi Jung.
Right.
Let's talk upstairs.
Follow me.
Last time, you said that Prosecutor Shin Gi Jung...
was the one who harassed the merchants...
with the Saryonghoe gangsters, right?
That was a lie, wasn't it?
Someone threatened you, so you lied to us, right?
No, that's not true.
Threatened? I wasn't.
Who would've threatened me?
I asked the long-time business owners around here,
and they said Prosecutor Shin Gi Jung...
rounded up all the Saryonghoe thugs...
and made sure they did some serious time.
Sir.
Please...
Hold on...
- Why are you trembling so much, sir? - Anyway, I don't know anything.
- Please, just leave for now. - Sir.
Please trust us and tell us the truth.
Did someone put you up to this?
Was it Lee Tae Geon? That psycho?
Hey.
What?
Seeing how pissed off you all are...
- You must be the Saryonghoe guys. - Yi Rang.
They're armed.
Yes, I know.
Yi Rang!
Score. A rare item.
- Yi Rang! We have to leave that! - Sorry.
Learning Lee Tae Geon is fleeing tonight is a huge break.
The problem is, we don't know which port.
He's trying to flee the country.
It was a long time ago,
but Saryonghoe had two main sources of income.
(Chinatown, Cash Stash)
The money they extorted from the merchants...
here in Chinatown as "protection fees,"
and their profits as smuggling brokers at the Port of Incheon.
Knowing Lee Tae Geon...
(Incheon Port)
He'd take the safe route.
Wouldn't he have gone to the Port of Incheon?
Then let's go.
Let's go get Lee Tae Geon.
Five minutes after we depart, knock on the door three times,
and the captain will open the door for you.
Got it. You can go.
There are this many?
How are we supposed to find him in all this?
And all the doors are locked.
That's what I'm here for.
So cool.
- Why? - My dad just went into this one.
I'll check this way.
Na Hyun.
- Call me if you see anything suspicious. - Will do.
Be careful.
What was that?
Hey, hurry up.
I'm about to piss my pants.
Hey, Captain, where are we?
Where do you think? The road to the fiery pit, sir.
What?
You're going to use that thing?
Let's go.
Hey, what is this?
You son of a gun. What do you think you are doing?
What are you...
What are you doing, you jerk?
Who do you think you are? My goodness.
Darn it.
Me?
I'm Prosecutor Shin Gi Jung.
Lee Tae Geon.
Did you think you could get away with trashing my son's office?
No way... Shin Gi Jung?
No.
But Shin Gi Jung is dead.
I couldn't rest because of you jerks, so I came back.
The voice recorder.
Where is it?
I don't care if you're a ghost or not.
Why on earth should I tell you that?
If you don't talk,
you'll be joining me.
Do you want to come along?
What?
Then again, dragging someone down with me doesn't sound too bad.
Are you serious...
What are you doing? What do you think you're doing?
- Should I drop him in? - What?
He doesn't seem like he's going to talk. Why waste time?
- It's getting cold. - Darn it. Goodness.
You think that's going to scare me?
Should I care?
What?
No! No!
I gave it to Yang Do Kyung! Right after I left the office that day,
I gave it to Yang Do Kyung!
Don't kill me.
He's telling the truth.
Dead men tell no tales.
If it's in Yang Do Kyung's hands...
That means it's all over, right?
No.
Yang Do Kyung didn't give the recorder to his father.
He says he didn't give the recorder to Yang Byung Il.
But Dad, how did you know that?
After Lee Tae Geon ran away,
I secretly went to Taebaek.
Lee Tae Geon has it, but he's on the run, so I can't reach him right now.
I didn't realise it at the time,
but putting the pieces together, I realised Yang Do Kyung...
had already gotten his hands on the recorder by then.
He pretended that he didn't have the recorder.
Why would he do that?
Because what was on the recorder...
was completely different from what Yang Byung Il had said.
For a long time, Chairman Yang hasn't trusted his son.
So Yang Do Kyung would do anything to know his father's true thoughts.
Whether it was tailing him or wiretapping his calls.
So he just confirmed once again...
that his own father doesn't trust him.
I'll go see Yang Do Kyung.
I'll ask him in person what he knows about his father.
All right.
Have you found Lee Tae Geon?
I'm afraid he's been captured by Shin Yi Rang.
What do we do now?
We have to arrest Shin Yi Rang. By any means necessary.
(Chairman Yang Byung Il)
The truth?
- What truth? - About Yoon Dae Myeong and Shin Gi Jung.
The truth about their murders.
You've really lost your edge since you left Taebaek.
Yoon Dae Myeong's death was a suicide.
Shin Gi Jung's death was a car accident.
It's all in the case files.
- So why are you asking me? - Because you know.
The real truth.
That my father is completely innocent.
That's the truth.
- What are you getting at? - What if you had someone who...
accepted and believed in you no matter what?
Things would have been so different.
What are you trying to say?
I'm saying that you need to be the one to stop this.
If you can't atone for the Chairman's past,
(Taebaek)
your version of Taebaek...
will crumble before it even has a chance to start.
You wouldn't want that, would you?
(Shin Yi Rang Law Office)
Yang Do Kyung had no intention of telling the truth.
By now, Yang Byung Il...
must know that we've captured Lee Tae Geon.
In that case,
Yang Byung Il will assume that we have the recorder.
What would Yang Byung Il do then?
I'll just have to ask him.
Do you have a moment?
There's something urgent I need to discuss with you.
Perfect timing. I was just about to call you.
I have something to say to you as well.
Then I'll come to your office.
Don't go. It's too dangerous.
She's right, Yi Rang. He thinks you have the recorder.
There's no telling what he might do.
I know you're both...
worried about me.
But this is our only chance...
to catch the tiger.
I'll go and get the answers...
we've been looking for.
(Taebaek)
- I'm Attorney Shin Yi Rang. - Please, go in.
Don't be afraid, Yi Rang.
So, you had something you wanted to tell me?
Before that,
I'd like to hear what you have to say first.
Shall we?
There was...
a reason I didn't tell you about Gi Jung's corruption.
I was worried that learning about your father's past mistakes...
would make you go down the wrong path.
Thinking about what happened to Gi Jung,
I couldn't just stand by and watch his only son get ruined too.
Or was it that you were afraid the truth would get out?
Fine. Blame me all you want.
But...
I hope you don't misjudge my intentions.
I wanted to protect you. But...
I see now I made the wrong call.
Mr. Shin Yi Rang.
This is a warrant for your arrest.
Lee Tae Geon and others are pressing assault charges...
against you.
What?
I asked to speak with you before they made the arrest.
I wanted to at least hear your side of the story.
But...
It seems that was all for nothing.
Where did you put it?
What?
The recorder?
That recorder...
- Yang Do Kyung has it. - Stop with these petty tricks.
You'd know right away if you just asked your son.
Why would I lie?
You were worried I would go down the wrong path?
I don't think you're in a position to worry about someone else's son.
You have your own fires to put out right now.
Let's see you run your mouth like that in a holding cell.
Take him away.
(One hour earlier)
Yes?
So this is your office.
What are you doing here?
My apologies. I thought this was the Chairman's office.
This place is huge.
Just as I would expect from Taebaek.
Who do you think you are, looking for the Chairman's office?
I'm here to see the Chairman.
- Why my father? - He said it was something important.
What about?
How would I know?
Well, I'll be going. Don't let me keep you.
By the way.
That voice recorder... You're the one who has it, right?
- What? - It seemed to be...
very important to the Chairman.
You're keeping it safe, aren't you?
You never know. It might have vanished without a trace.
Like a ghost.
Just gone.
What's wrong with that jerk?
(Yang Do Kyung)
What? A power outage?
Yes, I'm here now.
Inside the Taebaek building model. Passcode is 0525.
(Brother-in-law)
(Inside the Taebaek building model. Passcode is 0525.)
- I'm Attorney Shin Yi Rang. - Right this way.
Don't be scared, Yi Rang.
So, I hear you wanted to tell me something?
- This can't be good. - Goodness.
I came because of the blackout. It won't take long.
Okay.
(Inside the Taebaek building model. Passcode is 0525.)
Jackpot.
You'd know right away if you just asked your son.
Why would I lie?
- Where is it? Where's the recorder? - It was right here, but it's gone.
Move.
Where is it? The recorder!
Shin Yi Rang...
- Call security! Don't let anyone leave. - Yes, sir.
We have a huge problem. You should get down to the lobby.
I am here today to expose a very serious crime.
Just a moment, please.
I'm Prosecutor Kim Hyun Woo of the Seoul Central Prosecutors' Office.
What's going on here?
Well, it's...
You can't just drag someone away like this without following procedure.
Let me see the warrant.
Perfect timing.
Here's Chairman Yang Byung Il and CEO Yang Do Kyung.
Mr. Chairman!
What do you think you're doing? Are you out of your mind right now?
Of course not.
Do you really think this is going to change anything?
Everything is going to change.
Thank you for your patience.
I will now reveal the truth about Chairman Yang Byung Il.
But first, please welcome Attorney Shin Yi Rang.
- Shin Yi Rang? - She's calling Shin Yi Rang?
I...
am the son...
of a corrupt prosecutor.
A man some called a corrupt prosecutor,
and others remember him as a man of integrity.
Prosecutor Shin Gi Jung.
That man...
is my father.
- Shin Gi Jung? - What?
- What's going on? - Shin Gi Jung?
Twenty years ago, my father...
was framed for targeting Yoon Dae Myeong in an investigation...
and driving him to his death.
At the time of his death, a mixture of cannabis and hallucinogens...
was found in his system.
And his office was flooded with evidence of his corruption.
But all of it was a lie.
And the one who orchestrated this entire frame-up...
is none other than Taebaek's own...
Chairman Yang Byung Il.
- That crazy son of a gun. - Father, there are too many reporters.
I will now play...
a voice recording that reveals the truth from 20 years ago.
One voice belongs to Yang Byung Il.
The other belongs to the Chief Justice of the Supreme Court,
Choi Chang Soo.
Yes. First, we'll lure Yoon Dae Myeong out to Incheon.
A vice principal who committed suicide, unable to handle the pressure.
That's how we'll frame it.
Excellent.
But what are you going to do about that by-the-book junior prosecutor?
He's the type who will never let this go if you let him be.
Prosecutor Shin Gi Jung will be in a car accident,
and we'll frame him as a corrupt, drug-addicted prosecutor.
So Shin Gi Jung...
will quietly disappear, branded a corrupt prosecutor.
Exactly. Dead men tell no tales.
This recording...
was obtained by Yoon Dae Myeong before his death.
I'm aware this evidence...
is not admissible in court.
But I believe...
that no matter how long it takes,
the truth...
will be revealed.
This case is now...
out of my hands.
I'm counting on you to investigate this properly.
Understood.
Take him away.
Chairman Yang, a comment on the recording we just heard!
Did you, in fact, order the murders of Yoon Dae Myeong and Shin Gi Jung?
Please give us a clear statement on what happened.
Is it true you've been covering this up for over 20 years?
- Please, give a statement on this. - Is it true?
It really took a long time.
Attorney Shin Yi Rang.
Thank you.
The reporters are all gone.
You're going to be swamped with interviews...
and written questions starting tomorrow.
It's thanks to you...
that I made it this far.
You've faced so much, Yi Rang.
Thank you.
Come on, let's go. Let's get some much-needed rest today.
They just won't let me rest, will they?
Tell me about it. They really don't give you a break.
For a little pick-me-up, want some of this?
Sure.
That's refreshing.
It's really waking me up.
Ready to go wrap this up?
And now for our next story.
Chairman Yang Byung Il of Taebaek Law Firm...
has been implicated as the mastermind...
behind the deaths of Shin Gi Jung and Yoon Dae Myeong in 2003.
Prosecutors charged him with soliciting murder and destroying evidence.
We have more on this story.
This morning, Chairman Yang Byung Il was moved...
to the Nambu Detention Center.
Prosecutors are focusing on questioning Chairman Yang...
about his role in soliciting murder...
and ordering the destruction of evidence.
Meanwhile, they've also stated that Chief Justice Choi Chang Soo...
will soon be summoned on charges of soliciting defamation.
(Yongjin Delivery)
(Chairman Yang, Chief Justice Choi to Face Prosecutors Tomorrow Morning)
Father.
(Late Prosecutor Shin Gi Jung's Family)
(The Full Truth Must Be Revealed.)
What are you doing here? Yi Rang, I have nothing to say to you.
I...
have something I need to say,
Byung Il.
Gi Jung...
I've been waiting. I knew you'd show up.
Why did you do that to me?
Why have you changed...
so much?
- I was always this way. You didn't know. - No. No, that's not true.
The man I looked up to wasn't like this.
That's not who you are.
When I...
was practising kendo, there was one thing...
I realised.
To beat a faster, stronger opponent, you have to break the rules.
Play by the rules, and you'll always be one step behind.
Just like you, Gi Jung.
So...
when you broke the rules and trampled over others to get ahead,
- were you satisfied? - Your naivety is what got you killed.
It's not too late, even now.
Sir, admit to all your crimes,
to me, my family,
and to the family of Yoon Dae Myeong...
Apologise.
Apologise?
If I were going to apologise, I wouldn't have done it to begin with.
You...
You're incapable of remorse or regret,
aren't you?
I only have one regret.
The fact that I failed.
To think a ghost is what did me in.
How pathetic.
Still haunting me even after you're dead.
We won't be seeing each other again.
Because...
where we are headed to...
are different.
- Da Bong, you got this? - Yes.
(Premium Korean Beef and Pork)
Dad, are you ready?
- You think this is a good idea? - It's our family. It'll be fine.
All right.
I'm ready.
(Premium Korean Beef and Pork)
It's fine. I'll just open it for a second.
Gosh, Yi Rang said he'd be here by now. What's taking him so long?
There you are. Go wash your hands and come join us.
Da Bong, go say hi to your uncle.
Hi, Uncle.
I guess Mom's really missing Dad.
Go comfort her a little and bring her out, will you?
Okay, I got it.
What? "Okay, I got it?"
Is it you?
You'd still be the same.
I've gotten so old, haven't I?
In my eyes, you'll never change, Kyung Hwa.
For staying alive all this time...
For still being here in this world...
I can't tell you how grateful I am.
Thank you.
It tastes especially good today. Man, the kimchi is delicious too.
Just as I thought...
No one's cooking can touch Mom's.
How does it taste exactly the same?
Shin Sa Rang.
You need to eat your vegetables with your meal.
But I hate bell peppers.
Goodness.
And stop poking your food with one chopstick.
But the sausage is too slippery. I can't grab it.
Try it slowly.
Look, you corner the sausage so it can't get away...
and then you grab it.
Sa Rang.
Go on, use both.
It's easy for you. You're a lefty.
Actually...
Dad's ambidextrous. Now, eat your veggies.
- Yi Rang. - This is delicious.
My Sa Rang. Here, eat up.
A little of everything...
Dad?
Dad.
It really is you, Dad.
I've missed you...
I missed you so much, Dad.
Me too.
I missed you so much.
My little girl.
Honey, Sa Rang had something spicy. Look at her, teary-eyed and sniffly.
- My dad used to say... - Have some of this pancake, all right?
That some truths are harder to believe than any lie.
You have to eat it all.
I'll enjoy it.
But a truth that you earn through hardship...
is stronger than anything else.
You know, in this world,
if you have just one person who believes in you,
they say you can get through anything.
Even if the whole world is against you, that one person...
is all you need to find your courage.
And for you, Yi Rang, I'm that person.
The one person who'll believe in you no matter what.
Dad, let me make a formal introduction.
Yoon Bong Soo.
Your son-in-law.
Yes. We've met before, but...
this is our first formal introduction.
As Sa Rang's husband and your son-in-law,
my name is Yoon Bong Soo.
Yes, Father. To mark the occasion, should I pour you a drink?
- I'd like that. - Yes.
My son-in-law...
Please take good care of our Sa Rang.
I will.
- How about a toast, everyone? - Yes.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
It went beyond longing, beyond just a precious memory.
There was a deep, unspoken understanding between us,
and soon, our whole family shared the same heart.
You got this!
(Chairman Yang Byung Il)
Dad is here.
Father, please don't worry.
I'll take good care of our family.
I'm grateful I could at least see you and say goodbye like this.
Take good care of our Sa Rang and stay healthy.
He says to cut back on the drinking and to treat my sister well.
Yes. I will.
Dad.
Dad, can't you just stay here with us?
There are still so, so many things I want to do with you.
I know. I'm sorry I couldn't do more for you.
My dear Sa Rang...
Thank you for being my daughter.
Dad...
Dad, we can see each other again, can't we?
We will, won't we?
Of course. A long, long time from now,
let's meet again with smiles on our faces. Okay?
Okay, Dad.
Dad.
Being able to enjoy your cooking to my heart's content...
made me so happy.
Thank you for coming to see me.
Farewell.
Yi Rang. For your mom...
and for Sa Rang's family, be a rock and take care of them well.
My family...
I love you all...
so, so much.
I will.
I'll protect them from now on.
Don't you worry.
Dad says...
he loves all of us very, very much.
Dad!
Dad...
You have no idea how proud I am to call you my father.
Rest easy now.
(2026, Present day)
(Na Hyun and Yi Rang Law Office)
(Shin Yi Rang Law Office: Farewell with the clients)
Hello.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
You can see me?
Yes.
I can help you find out who you are and the story of how you got here.
I'm Attorney Shin Yi Rang, and I'll work with you to resolve it.
First, you'll need to sign a contract, but...
I have a really, really important appointment today.
Can we meet here again tomorrow?
- Oh, sure. - Okay.
Have you been waiting long?
No. I just got here myself.
It's taken us a really long time...
to get to this point.
I understand.
What can you do when ghosts show up at all hours?
Don't worry.
Actually, a new ghost just showed up a moment ago,
but I told them that today was out of the question.
That's a relief.
Na Hyun.
There's something I've always wanted to tell you.
All this time.
Oh no.
Yi Rang?
Na Hyun, you trust me, right?
- Yes. - Then run!
That looks great on you.
I've been wanting to say it for a while.
That you look beautiful.
Thank you.
You believed without seeing,
and even when you couldn't understand,
you stayed by my side.
You were the one who showed me when it was time to be brave.
That was you, Na Hyun.
I'm the one who should be thanking you.
I was just charging full steam ahead.
You stopped me in my tracks.
After meeting you, Yi Rang, my once-cold world...
You have no idea how much warmer it has become.
Oh, no.
Not now.
What?
Merry Christmas.
(Special thanks to guest stars, Choi Won Young and Jeong Jae Seong)
Hey there, who are you?
Gosh, you're so cute.
What? How did you get in here?
Good dog.
- It's okay. Come here. - Uncle.
Oh, Da Bong!
There you go.
Wait, were you by yourself?
- Seemed like you were talking to someone. - Oh, that?
- A lost puppy wandered in. - Where's the puppy?
What? He's right over there.
- Yi Rang. - Yes?
No way.
Uncle...
(Phantom Lawyer)