(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
(All characters, places,
and organizations are fictional.)
(Children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
(Episode 6)
What a pair...
What's this for?
Are you making flower pancakes?
Did Director Shin ask for them?
Or are you just making them?
Are you all ignoring me?
Is Director Shin your only deity now?
You too? Hey, Lee Shim!
Park Soo!
I can fire you both.
I'll be the one making
Director Shin's birthday dinner this time.
Don't you two work well together...
Why not just get married?
Who's the senior here?
Lee Shim.
How old are you?
It's impossible to tell her age.
You all have no manners.
I looked into it,
and on that day, two babies...
Yes...
But...
I don't think it's you.
I just have a feeling.
You don't resemble my family at all.
Family members don't always
have to look alike.
What about the other child
left at the church that day?
- Yes.
- Can you get in touch with her?
Yes.
Could you explain the situation
and arrange for me to meet them?
Yes, but shouldn't we get a test done?
I'll meet her first.
If I feel she isn't the one either...
What's her name?
Kim Jin Ju.
We even have the same last name.
I'd like to call her now.
I'll try calling her.
(Kim Jin Ju)
The phone is turned off.
Please leave a message after the tone.
She must be working.
Her phone's off.
- What does she do?
- Jin Ju?
- Yes.
- She's a stylist.
- Like celebrity outfits?
- Yes.
And where did she go to school?
You can ask her that in person.
You seem to have a job too.
Yes.
- Where do you work?
- The culture desk at Sungwoo Daily.
You're a reporter?
Yes. And you?
I was away...
this year for a while.
When Kim Jin Ju gets in touch,
could you give her my number?
Okay. But...
you really don't think it's me?
Do you want me to be your dad?
I need to meet everyone to know for sure.
They're treating him
like he's absolute royalty.
I don't eat carbs.
Did you say you wanted to eat these?
It's because I remember how my mom
used to make them for me...
around this time of year.
So your comfort food is azalea pancakes?
For me,
it's chive and pumpkin pancakes.
I hate the word "bindaetteok."
It just sounds so destitute and poor.
I'll make your birthday dinner this time.
Something really special and grand.
We'll invite your friends.
I'm busy.
And it's too much trouble.
Still, you should have
at least one proper meal.
Shouldn't you be resting in bed?
I'm much better now.
I've pulled a muscle before.
Right.
It wasn't this body.
What dishes do you miss the most
made by your mother?
Meat and rice.
Meat and rice? How do you make it?
Even when Nurse Park uses prime beef,
it just doesn't taste the same.
Although it might look the same.
When will you stop being so formal?
It's going to become a habit.
What if someone hears you?
I'll get there.
I know men can't keep secrets.
Are you telling Ha Yong Joong everything?
It's always the ones closest to you
who betray you.
Hey.
You called? I'm out working.
This time,
you might actually get to meet
your biological dad.
Is someone looking for me again?
The Self-Reliance Center director
contacted me.
So, I met a man named Kim Gwang Cheol.
Kim Jin Ju!
You're not done yet?
I have two scenes left.
I'm the last one off,
so I don't think I'll be done
until after 1 a.m.
The news stories drop at dawn,
so I need to get to sleep now.
- Tomorrow, then?
- Okay.
James!
Hey, you're here.
What is all this?
A monk I know...
What about a monk?
Did he give this to you?
- Yes.
- Why?
Are you hungry?
Let's have breakfast. It's been a while.
It'll just take 30 minutes.
Why did he tell you to do this?
I told him I had insomnia.
Does it work? Are you sleeping?
Yes.
So is this the logic?
When you get sleep paralysis,
the spirits see this and can't get you?
Want rice or toast?
So you gave the painting
to Ba Ra after all.
No.
"Do you want to take it back
and continue our relationship?"
"Or should I take the artwork,
and we go our separate ways?"
When she puts it like that, what can I do?
I had to take it back.
She even rejects you in a lovely way,
making you feel good about it.
Don't take it too far.
Even if I don't,
you know what they say,
"You can't hide love, poverty,
or a cough."
Hide it.
If you cause trouble by being selfish,
I'll be really disappointed in you.
I'm saying this because it's us.
I don't think of Professor Lee
or Professor Shin as someone I'd marry.
It's just for a bit of fun,
a passing interest.
Reporter Geum may be smart
and have the looks and pedigree,
but would just any family accept her
as a daughter-in-law?
The age gap aside, she's perfect for me.
We're kindred spirits.
Age doesn't matter these days,
as long as you don't look old.
You think you can control that?
We have the world's best cosmetic tech.
It's too late for you.
They'll say you're going senile.
Don't you know what people look for
in a marriage prospect?
I don't. All I know is love.
So you think it's best just to rip
the band-aid off?
Then go on and confess everything to her.
You'll probably never see her again.
Want to bet?
He said he doesn't think it's me.
I don't look alike at all.
What does he look like?
His clothes and everything.
- He's just average.
- You mean shabby?
No.
But we were the only two babies left...
at that church on December 21, 1999.
You have the same last name as him,
so it has to be you.
I'm so nervous.
I'll text you his number.
Kim Jin Ju?
Yes.
An iced Americano, please.
- Same for me.
- Okay.
We don't even need a DNA test.
You're the spitting image of the mother
you've never even met.
Really?
Do you have a picture?
You don't?
I don't have one.
We weren't married.
What was your relationship, exactly?
So you just dated and then broke up?
Or were you already married
when you met her,
- and I was the result of an affair?
- No.
We dated for about a year.
When we drifted apart,
I didn't even know she was pregnant.
How...
I didn't know...
Her name was Hwang Mi Sook.
- My birth mother?
- Yes.
She left you with my mother
and then disappeared.
- So...
- Then who threw me away...
in the box at Minjin Church?
- I wouldn't say threw away...
- But that's what it was.
I only found out later.
Then my grandmother did it?
Let's not speak ill of the dead.
Her own flesh-and-blood granddaughter?
Given her circumstances,
how could an old woman raise you all
on her own?
Then what were you doing?
Do people only raise kids and grandkids
when things are easy?
That was a long time ago.
- Does the past really matter?
- "The past doesn't matter?"
I grew up in an orphanage
without any parents.
I'm so ashamed.
You must resent me so much.
I would too, in your shoes.
Look, it's a long story.
I heard you studied fashion design.
At Seshin Community College.
I'm so proud. You've turned out so well.
Are you really sure about this?
Of course. I recognized you right away.
You're the spitting image of your mom
in her twenties.
You look a bit like your grandmother, too.
I have a picture of her.
I don't want to see it.
From your grandmother's point of view,
she'd only heard one side of the story,
and she doubted if you were really
her son's flesh and blood.
Plus, she had a bad leg. So...
If she cared so much,
did she at least write my name on a note?
No.
Anyway, she told me the exact date
and everything.
She made me promise to find you
and make sure.
And you're just now getting to it?
Here are your coffees.
Did something happen
that you can't talk about?
No, there's nothing I can't talk about.
Let's get something to eat first.
People get cranky when they're hungry.
- Didn't you have breakfast?
- Isn't it lunchtime?
Do you often skip meals?
Don't do that. It's bad for your health.
I saw a restaurant in the lobby
on my way in.
They might not have a table.
If they don't,
we can just eat somewhere else.
Hello.
Thank you.
Where do you live?
In a studio.
No, I mean, which neighborhood?
Hyeonmi-dong.
And you work around here?
In Gangnam.
Do you have a reservation?
- No.
- A table for two?
- Yes.
- Let me check for a table.
Do you have a business card?
(Kim Jin Ju, Staff, Lim Company)
Where do you live?
What?
I need to find a place now.
Did you live abroad?
Right this way.
Okay.
I'm afraid all the private rooms
are taken.
Hello? Oh, hello, sir.
Tomorrow? Alright. Thank you.
(Kim Jin Ju, December 3, 1999)
Look at CEO Ju, schmoozing.
(Art Folder...)
(Culture Desk 3)
Do you have plans tonight?
- No.
- That's good.
I'm meeting CEO Ju Yeong Ae. Join me.
Is it okay if I come?
You covered her last exhibition,
didn't you?
- But you were the one who...
- French food at the Sun Hotel.
Order whatever you want.
- You have the lunch special, right?
- Yes.
- We'll have that.
- The lunch special for two?
Yes.
Isn't a studio apartment
a little dangerous...
for a woman on her own?
It's fine.
What about a boyfriend?
I don't have one.
I'm a man myself,
but there's really no need
to get married these days.
If you do, do it later in life,
after you've done everything you want.
I've learned that life doesn't
always go as planned.
I don't know what you'll think of me
for saying this,
but as time went on, I missed you
more and more, and I wondered...
if you'd be tall or short,
or if you took after me at all.
You never left my mind or my heart.
Hwang Mi Sook wouldn't lie
about our child,
and she has no reason to.
For 27 years,
I failed to be a father to you,
so I'll do my best to make up for it
and then some from now on.
Are you managing to save
any of the money you earn?
Let's eat before it gets cold.
This is delicious.
She kept appearing in my dreams
for a while,
and now it's like she's been
reincarnated or something.
Have you ever told her you love her?
To Oiji?
Did I?
Of course I loved her.
You know, Ba Ra likes puppies too.
I wonder if she'd accept
a puppy as a gift.
Ms. Noh Hye Yeong said she was
running 30 minutes late.
That woman has no sense of time.
Is Jin Ju out on set?
It's her day off today.
It's uncanny.
It's like I'm sitting here
with Hwang Mi Sook.
What did she do for a living?
A nurse.
At what hospital?
I found out she got married and emigrated.
If you're anything like me,
you're probably a very honest person.
I don't hide things or deceive people.
You'll find out eventually anyway.
I was away at "school" all this time.
You know what I mean by "school," right?
Prison.
That's why I couldn't look for you,
even though I desperately wanted to.
I got tangled up in some things,
and parts of it were unfair,
but I just see it all as fate.
For that long?
I got out on parole eight years ago.
But you went back in?
From now on, I'm going to live for you,
and only for you.
That's why I came looking for you
with so much confidence.
Are you disappointed?
Were you hoping for some big-shot parents?
The past is in the past.
You have to live for the future.
There's no moving forward
if you're stuck in the past.
You're not alone in the world anymore.
You have a dad you can count on,
so hold your head high.
If you have even the slightest doubt,
we can get a test tomorrow to be sure.
No.
There were only two babies left there
on December 21, 1999.
Geum Ba Ra doesn't look anything like me.
You just know
when it's your own flesh and blood.
Is there anything you're curious about,
or anything you wish for?
I'll have to think about it.
Why aren't you eating?
- I'm full.
- Are you on a diet?
I just don't have much of an appetite.
So, family shouldn't live apart, right?
We need to save money on rent.
I don't have much stuff anyway.
I could move in tomorrow.
- To my place?
- Yes.
- Why?
- What do you mean, "why?"
Aren't we family?
It's a studio apartment. Just one room.
I know it's a studio.
It has a living room and kitchen area,
doesn't it?
I can just sleep in a corner.
I just need a sleeping bag.
- Hello.
What about Kim Jeong Ah?
She had to kill a story
at the last minute.
I see.
A journalist I’m close with once said,
"Being a reporter would be a great job
if you didn't have to write stories."
That's what she said.
Right.
Hello.
A pleasure to meet you.
Our reporter, Kim Jeong Ah,
had to kill a story at the last minute.
- So I'm here instead.
- Well, not "instead."
Your exhibition article was so great,
I've been meaning to set something up.
There was so much great work
to write about.
How long did it take to prepare?
Almost a year.
Ma'am, the hospital just called.
She's suddenly taken a turn for the worse.
My mother-in-law is in the ICU.
- You should go right away.
- I'm so sorry about this.
Which hospital?
- Korea Sam Hospital.
- But traffic is terrible right now.
- I'll take care of the bill later...
- No, please don't worry about it.
- Go on.
- No, really.
Well, I'll make it up to you next time.
Please, don't get up.
You too.
Oh, Father
Our prayers
Please, answer them
Answer them?
(Answer them?)
My foot.
(My foot.)
I've never met an artist based in Germany.
How did you end up there?
This isn't an interview, by the way.
My closest friend
from my high school class...
went to study abroad in Germany.
So you followed your friend to Germany?
You could say that.
When you live there a long time,
do you start to become like the locals?
Do I seem a bit stiff?
I get that sometimes.
You definitely have a different vibe
from most Korean men your age.
I'm a Korean man too.
I just had to change my citizenship,
that's all.
You're not much of a talker, are you?
This is our second time meeting,
and that's the sense I'm getting.
I'll make an exception today.
How do you feel about
the positive reaction...
your work has been getting in Korea?
Sorry. That came out sounding
like an interview question.
When my hard work is seen and appreciated,
it feels good, of course.
I think people are drawn to the affection
in my work.
Is that the main theme?
Isn't it?
How many years were you in Germany?
It seems like it's been over 20.
Yes, a full 26 years.
But your Korean is perfect.
- Is your best friend still there...
- No.
I never even got to meet him there.
I was in an accident
the day after I arrived.
My gosh, what kind of accident?
A car accident.
I had a pretty bad head injury,
so I was unconscious for a while.
And even after I woke up,
I was in and out of it for a few years.
- Oh, dear.
- So I never had the chance to find him.
I actually met up with him
when I came back to Korea this time.
Turns out he's a managing director
at Jeil Auto.
You must have been so happy to see him.
Yes.
After almost three decades,
Korea's changed a lot, hasn't it?
- Yes.
- How many times did you return?
Just once, 11 years ago...
It was when my mother passed away.
I couldn't be there when my father passed.
You must have gone through a lot
in Germany.
But it turned out to be
a lucky break, in a way.
The person who caused my accident
passed away last year.
He was my adoptive father.
- Oh my.
- He must have felt so guilty about it,
though he always said it was
because he recognized my talent.
He adopted me as his son.
Thanks to him,
my language skills improved quickly,
and he was a famous painter and professor,
Ilias Becker.
You can look him up.
He truly saved my life.
So that's how you got your citizenship.
I just assumed
you had married a German woman.
A blessing in disguise, isn't it?
To think that an unfortunate accident
led to...
Yes. You win some, and you lose some.
And misfortune can turn into good luck.
You must believe that
someone up there was looking out for you.
I believe that the skies help
those who help themselves.
As my father's assistant and secretary,
studying and working on my art,
I don't think
I had a single second to spare.
That's incredible.
Are you okay now, health-wise?
Are there any lingering effects?
I recovered fully.
I even slept less
to make time to exercise.
Listening to you makes me realize
how much further I have to go.
You made it as a reporter
for Sungwoo Daily by giving it your all.
They don't just hand you that job,
do they?
- Mr. Kim. I mean, sir.
- Call me what you're comfortable with.
Thinking about Korea now
versus when you left,
is there anything that's changed
in a way you don't like?
When do you feel out of place?
I'm asking a lot of questions, aren't I?
There's just so much I'm curious about.
No, this is what
we're supposed to talk about.
Otherwise,
we'd just be staring at each other.
One thing that throws me off sometimes...
Maybe it's because I'm used to
the German way of thinking,
but it's when people just hit you
with personal questions out of nowhere.
Like, "Why aren't you married?"
or "Have you ever dated a German woman?"
Or, "Let me set you up with someone."
Yes.
That's just our way of showing we care.
But we should focus that energy
on ourselves.
Excuse me.
Of all the photos taken of me in Korea,
this is my favorite.
(Yong Joong)
It's been a while.
Do I always have to call first?
I could tell you were busy.
Did you bug my place?
You've never even been to my house.
I just close my eyes,
and I can see everything.
Seeing whoever I thought about
would be a great power.
Momo?
No, you.
You're home, right?
Yes.
Come to think of it,
you've never invited me over.
That's why I'm calling.
I want to invite you over today.
- How long will that take?
- You're here?
- Yes.
- Oh my gosh.
Don't worry about dressing up.
Just come as you are.
One minute.
When did you get so pretty?
I've always been pretty.
- Are we really going to your place?
- Yes.
Then I should get you something.
It's my first visit.
- Did you have lunch?
- Of course.
- You haven't yet?
- It's not that I didn't eat, I couldn't.
I was swamped.
You're always busy.
It's already 4 p.m.
Have you fallen out of love with me?
I won't expect a phone call.
But you could send a text at least.
You're the one who acts busy.
Don't you dare turn this around on me.
- You don't eat street food, do you?
- Why wouldn't I?
It's too early for dinner,
so how about some tteokbokki? Okay?
Okay.
Here you are. Enjoy.
- Thank you.
Tteokbokki was the very first thing I made
the day I moved out on my own.
I'll never forget that day.
What was the best part
of being on your own?
Having my very own space
for the first time in my life.
A real home, not an institution.
It was so quiet at night,
with no one snoring,
that I couldn't sleep
because I was so happy.
Girls snore?
When they're tired,
it's so loud it shakes walls.
You probably snore too, right?
I don't think so.
No one's ever told me I do.
My brother says
I'm a pretty quiet sleeper for a guy.
Have you seen my brother recently?
No.
Listen, just in case...
What?
Now that my brother is getting older,
he can sometimes go overboard.
If he does, try to be understanding.
He's my brother, after all.
Go overboard how?
He's just different from me in some ways.
Sir. I just got a call
that Lee Eun Hye came to the office today.
A man claiming to be
Kim Jin Ju's father came...
and is demanding her address.
He says he hasn't been able to reach her
for ten days.
What are you talking about? What father?
That's what I mean.
Tell him she quit.
We did, but he still demands her address.
He says he knows she's in Hyeonmi-dong.
What should I do?
He's not leaving until we give it to him.
Tell Eun Hye to call me.
Hello.
I'm Kim Gwang Cheol, Jin Ju's father.
I see.
Are you the CEO?
I am. What is this about?
On the 14th, I met my daughter, Jin Ju,
at the Joongang Hotel.
Did you hear about that?
No.
We even ate at the hotel's Japanese spot
before parting ways.
But four days later, I couldn't reach her.
Her phone's been off ever since.
She quit almost a week ago.
Did she say she found another job?
I asked, but she said
she just wanted to take a break.
If she'd gotten another job,
I would've heard about it right away.
I have to go find her.
If you don't trust me, send someone along.
I only know that she lives
in Hyeonmi-dong.
Please give me her address.
You never know,
something could've happened to her.
She might have gone on a trip...
Will you take responsibility
if something happened?
Let me speak to my employee.
Hello?
- Yes?
- Are any of the men working today?
Hwang Jae Young.
You didn't eat on purpose, did you?
Not at all. I really enjoyed it.
I've been craving
the tteokbokki from here.
(CEO James Ha)
- It's Mr. Ha.
- I'll get it.
What's up? I'm here with Ba Ra.
Good. Put her on.
- Why?
- I need to ask her something.
A man came by
claiming to be Kim Jin Ju's birth father.
Did Kim Jin Ju meet her birth father?
- Hello?
- It's James.
- Hello, sir.
- Please, drop the "sir."
Did you happen to hear that
Kim Jin Ju met her birth father?
- Yes.
- And you haven't spoken to her recently?
No, it's been a while.
What about quitting her job with us?
She quit?
The phone is turned off.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Charges will apply...
What was the man
who claimed to be her father like?
He was pretty well-dressed.
What does he do for a living?
I didn't get into that.
He said right away that I wasn't her.
At least she met her biological father,
right?
We're making one stop first.
Where?
Can't you tell me? I'm curious.
A pet shop.
- I can't get a pet.
- Yes, you can.
I can't just leave it at home alone.
I've already thought about all that.
Then, instead of buying one,
let's go to an animal shelter.
If I were in a position to have one,
I was thinking of adopting a rescue.
Okay?
Think it through so you have no regrets.
I won't. I've even volunteered there.
Yong Joong.
The address.
I don't know who'll be the first
to read this,
but by that time, I'll probably be...
with the grandmother I never got to meet.
I'm so exhausted,
and my last glimmer of hope is gone.
I wonder what my real parents are like.
I would dream and imagine,
and that's what gave me hope.
That's how I kept going.
But that hope was shattered.
Mr. James,
I'm sorry, and thank you for everything
you've done for me.
Momo, while we worked together,
I had so much fun
and really developed an eye for things.
Thank you.
We have to report this to the police,
right?
Oh my gosh!
What is going on now? Seriously.
I like big dogs,
but in an apartment...
Don't worry about it.
Choose from one of these.
(James)
Is Reporter Geum with you?
No, it was loud,
so I stepped out to take the call.
Kim Jin Ju, Ba Ra's orphanage friend,
disappeared, possibly to take her life.
Are you serious?
Yes.
- Why?
- I don't know the details,
but Reporter Geum
is going to be devastated. This is awful.
What do we do?
I heard they grew up like sisters.
Are you sure about this?
Her father and a staff member of mine
went to her home,
and they found a letter she'd left behind.
Just when I finally met her.
After everything I went through
to find her.
Ba Ra.
Even if I didn't always show it,
and if there were ever times I hurt you,
because we were like sisters,
please just remember the good times.
Having you with me
really made it less lonely.
You were such a big support for me.
When I think about it,
I must have been happiest in the womb.
They say even fetuses can feel things,
you know.
You know I've always loved water, right?
I'm going to find my peace in the water.
I thought we would be
like a family forever.
A wave of sadness is washing over me.
Jin Ju, eat up.
- I heard your grades went up.
- Yes, they did.
Eat up.
Hey, did you get a banana?
Yes.
If you get adopted,
that lady won't volunteer anymore, right?
She said she'd keep coming.
She finds it rewarding.
Will you come back and visit?
- I'm going to miss you.
- Me too.
I can't come weekly because of school,
but I'll visit as often as I can.
Everything should be finalized
by next week.
Thank you.
You've worked so hard for us.
To be honest, our foundation's chairman...
really doted on Ba Ra
and thinks the world of her.
It's not that he was against it,
but he wasn't exactly thrilled about it.
He kept asking why it had to be her,
saying she's the face of the orphanage.
It's impossible not to love Ba Ra.
She's so kind and hardworking.
Excuse me.
What?
Did you lose something?
- My wallet...
- Your wallet is missing?
Hello? Hi, honey.
I'll call you right back.
Everyone, down to the auditorium.
Deok Young, go and get
Mi Su and Seon Uk. Quickly.
Okay.
Don't just glance around.
Search everywhere!
We have to find it.
(Kim Jin Ju)
Is this...
Thank you.
Is anything missing?
There was 500 dollars in cash.
I'm positive I put exactly 500 dollars
in here.
All in new bills...
I was going to give it to the kids
for their allowance.
(Geum Ba Ra)
Why would I do that?
I have no reason to.
Go to your room.
Didn't you hear me?
(Unpo Police Station)
Her phone's last signal was
at Yeongdeung Port.
And we've seen no signs of activity since.
Considering she left a note,
it's pretty clear.
But you can't be sure.
She might've faked it
to escape her father.
Then she would've at least taken money
or her credit cards.
Her bank accounts and debit card
are untouched.
I'm telling you,
there's no sign of activity.
- We have Kim Jin Ju on CCTV.
- Where?
A convenience store at Yeongdeung Port.
Does this make any sense to you, Ba Ra?
I can't believe it either.
Is she that fragile?
- She must be somewhere...
- This might be out of line,
but have you considered that...
she might not be your biological daughter,
although the facts might line up?
I already had it checked, just in case.
I got a hold of her toothbrush
and some hair.
(DNA analysis report)
(Test result details)
(Genetic match test results:
99.99 percent paternity match verified)
(Paternity between Kim Gwang Cheol
and Kim Jin Ju is confirmed)
I didn't even know she existed,
and this is how she twists the knife?
I need Momo's number.
Someone like Momo
could easily be hiding her.
Momo just had a death in her family, too.
She has neither the time
nor the reason to do that.
What are you, her spokesperson?
Whatever.
- I only have her agency's number.
- And you're a reporter?
You have no idea how strict
celebrity agencies are in Korea.
Especially with reporters.
No matter what her biological father
was like,
how could she just throw her life away?
That has to be the only reason.
She must have been
incredibly disappointed.
Especially since she saw
the ankle bracelet.
I'd be horrified too, if I were her.
Especially with some man
who's claiming to be your father.
- Manager Yoon.
- Yes?
Let's live a long, full life.
No matter what hardships we face.
Right.
You don't think...
Do you think she might have
gone to Momo's?
- No way.
- But Jin Ju was so good to Momo.
Even though Jin Ju's the older one,
she catered to her every whim.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
You haven't heard from her, have you?
I haven't spoken to her in ages.
Okay, got it.
Are you going to stay there?
I hurt my back a little.
It's a long story.
Besides, she probably just
went off the grid for a bit.
It's absurd to think she'd kill herself
over something like that.
- That's a relief.
- On the 23rd, it's Director Shin's...
It's his birthday. Come with CEO Ha.
Why would I go? He can go by himself.
You two came here together late.
Only because he asked me to come.
I'm getting a call.
Yes.
If she dies, it's her own loss.
Anything's better than being dead.
(Surgery time, Current time,
Anesthesia time)
Ever tried Baijiu? It's a Chinese liquor.
No, I haven't.
Don't bother sipping it.
Just throw it back in one go.
It might seem strong,
but you won't have a hangover tomorrow.
Okay.
Are you happy with your life?
I'm just trying to do my best.
I'm asking if you're happy.
You want me to be honest?
You should be,
especially with a good drink like this.
I'm struggling.
Kim Jin Ju.
Yes?
Ever think about getting on
an operating table?
If you do, I can change your life.
Director Shin, you do plastic surgery too?
A surgery to reshape your life.
It's possible.
Don't you want to live like Momo?
As Momo.
I'm not kidding.
I'm going to be honest with you tonight.
So you have to keep this a secret.
Take it to your grave.
Yes.
The Momo you see now is
only Momo on the outside.
After the accident, she was a complete...
a complete wreck.
How could her mother bear to see...
her own daughter in such a state?
And this is the world-famous Momo
we're talking about.
So I...
Momo's mother was the one
who suggested it,
but regardless, I did the surgery.
It was a success.
But...
people can have a change of heart.
The plan was for me to break up with her
naturally after the brain swap,
but now she has other ideas.
No matter how much she looks
like Momo on the outside,
on the inside,
it's my future mother-in-law.
How could that possibly work...
from my perspective?
I can't even imagine.
Jin Ju.
I'm not forcing you.
But I want it to be you.
Is that really possible?
If you don't believe me,
go meet Momo and ask her some questions.
Ask her about her old job.
Or you could just casually part her hair
and check for the surgery scar.
What do you think of me?
Not as the Chairman of the orphanage
or the hospital director,
but just as Shin Ju Shin, the man.
Aren't you interested in finding out?
I couldn't possibly...
Strip away the titles,
and we're all just people.
Just a man and a woman.
For a while now,
I feel like you've been slowly
finding a place in my heart.
We're similar in a way.
You're an orphan too.
Now that all my family is gone...
And with what's happened to Momo...
I'm lonely.
But what if it fails?
What would happen to me then?
I'm fine out here.
I'm starving. You got anything to eat?
Even just some ramyeon?
We can't afford any mistakes.
You'll become Momo, have and enjoy
everything you've ever wanted,
including all of her wealth,
automatically.
So then, CEO Hyun Ran Hee
would take my body?
If CEO Hyun's brain
were to go into your body,
do you think she'd just accept that
and live quietly?
Actually...
Go on.
A man claiming to be
my biological father showed up.
Really?
That smug Geum Ba Ra...
Just you watch
what this Kim Jin Ju becomes.
I...
I, Kim Jin Ju...
will become Momo.
(Kim Gwang Cheol)
- Hello?
- It's me.
- Yes.
- Are you done with work?
I'm at a work dinner.
Then why's it so quiet?
I'm in the bathroom.
Okay.
I'd like to buy you an outfit tomorrow.
Are you free?
I feel bad that I haven't done
anything for you.
I have a shoot that runs late.
What about Sunday, then?
I'll give you a call.
We're not strangers anymore.
You can stop being so formal.
Okay.
All right.
Kim Jin Ju.
You've lived such a sad life.
(Power off)
Jin Ju, have a seat.
- Does Reporter Geum like dogs?
- I think so.
She always stops to look at dogs
when we pass them.
What kind does she like? Small breeds?
Or a bigger dog, like a poodle?
Should I ask her?
No. She even returned the painting,
so I thought she might accept
a living gift.
Sir.
I'd like to take some time off.
For how long?
About a year.
And that was it.
And she got her severance pay?
Of course.
Did she mention meeting me?
Not a single word.
When she was working as Momo's stylist,
how did the two of them get along?
They were very close.
Hey, Yong Joong.
You have something tonight, don't you?
What's with your voice? Are you sick?
A little.
What's wrong? Did you take anything?
I don't really take medicine.
Why don't you come make me some porridge?
Is the housekeeper not there?
She's a terrible cook
when it comes to porridge.
The passcode is the last four digits
of my phone number.
Hey...
Here.
He's the one, right?
Are you feeling better already?
Give him a name.
You scared me.
I already gave him a bath,
and he's had all his shots.
I didn't know you could pull off
a surprise like this.
It's a birthday present
to make up for all the ones I missed.
But I'm the only one getting gifts.
That's what older brothers are for.
Drop by to see him anytime.
Better yet, just move in.
It's sweet of you to say that. Thank you.
I mean it.
I want to do something for you too.
There is one thing.
Put my mind at ease.
I haven't done anything to worry you.
I'll never cause you any trouble.
Because I don't want anything from you.
What's that supposed to mean?
Exactly what it sounds like.
Go on, ask for things. I can afford it.
Just...
having you is enough for me.
It's incredible that I get to see you.
It's been almost 20 years.
When I was in elementary school,
the one thing I begged my mom for...
was a little sister.
But she'd just give me a vague smile
and brush me off.
Looking back on it now,
my mom was over 40.
I guess she didn't think she could do it.
If she'd explained it better,
I would've gotten it.
She underestimated her son's maturity.
So how could I not be completely smitten
with my little one?
At first sight?
I'm about to turn 30.
Don't I age too?
To me,
you'll always be that little kid
from the corner store.
In a past life, we must've been
brother and sister,
or maybe a father and daughter?
You believe in past lives?
Logically, it makes sense that they do.
I guess I must've committed a lot of sins
in my past life.
People would swear at you for saying that.
They'd ask if you've looked in a mirror.
Focus on what you have.
You've got me.
You're my everything.
But don't feel pressured.
Pressured? We confessed
our feelings to each other.
The housekeeper left a whole feast for us.
It's not your birthday, though.
It's your belated birthday dinner.
You've already had plenty to eat.
All you can do is watch.
I told her to make it
a kid's birthday meal.
You're not wired like other guys.
Is that a compliment?
Are you saying I'm androgynous?
It means you were raised right.
You're considerate and thoughtful.
I was raised right,
but I went through a serious angsty phase
as a freshman.
Do you look just like your dad?
Not at all.
I'll show you a photo after we eat.
- I should heat up the soup.
- It's okay. I don't like it too hot.
Seaweed soup is fine
when it's not super hot.
Hey...
I don't want to lose you
to some other woman.
You're too good for them.
Then just keep me by your side forever.
I'm serious.
Even if I get married,
how I feel about my kiddo
will never change.
Does he not see me as a woman at all?
Your housekeeper is an amazing cook.
I specifically asked for marinated beef
instead of the braised ribs.
Because when I was a kid,
I thought marinated beef was tastier.
And now you prefer the ribs?
Steak.
Royal court rice cakes.
- Are these rice or wheat cakes?
- Rice cakes.
I like the rice cakes, too.
Ever since I met you again,
I've been so happy.
I'm the one who should be saying that.
What are you going to name him?
Pickles.
Have you heard from Director Shin?
About a birthday invite.
No.
Momo said she was going to invite you.
Ju Shin hates that stuff.
He hasn't celebrated his birthday
since his mother passed away.
Before his mother passed away,
what was Director Shin like?
Do people ever really change?
Even back then, was he blunt?
If that's a nice way of putting it.
What would be a bad way of putting it?
There's nothing bad, really.
He may not be warm,
but he's not one to look down on people.
(Doctor Shin)
You're with some other guy right now.
You must be here to run
an errand for my guy.
Here to pick something up?
Don't you ever think
Geum Ba Ra is a little too smart?
What's wrong with being smart?
I see Ba Ra as a sister, not a woman.
Do you think she feels the same way?
- Can you video call?
- Yes.
Look at me and go potty.
My love has begun...
with Director Shin Ju Shin.
Do you think I could get an MRI?
Are you feeling unwell?
Email me Geum Ba Ra's files.
- All of them.
- Understood.
What are your thoughts on a brain swap?
Have you ever thought about it?
You mean how they say AI can replace
an entire human brain?
The face would stay the same.
If we could swap only the brain...
You mean you, Director?
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)