(Episode 3)
Let's listen to "Love in The Air"
How was everyone's morning?
Today's topic is
"It's too late to regret"
Everyone must have something they
regret but didn't realize it
in time, right?
Watch me,
I'm going to make you fall for me.
For example, "I should have said it."
Dammit.
The future of love...
Why did I say that?
Finally...
Go back to the beginning.
What will you do next?
Here, change your clothes.
Before we say goodbye this morning,
I wish everyone...
- to be cheerful.
- Should fit.
Then let's listen to this song.
I'm sure.
"Rainstorm"
(Boxer shorts, size S)
Are you kidding me?
I'm not that small!
How's the size?
Awesome.
Presentation materials for a project.
Could I ever create something like this?
Sure,
if you're willing to work for it.
What are you doing?
What do you think?
Oww!
Thought I was going to kiss you?
No.
With how you're going,
it'll take you decades to ‘win' me.”
It won't take that long!
You think so?
Once you hit your second year,
assignments double.
What does that mean?
Meaning, if you want to ‘win' me,
better aim for your first year
while you still have free time.
No.
Still, you have to use your time wisely.
Even then, it'll be tough for Rei.
Don't look down on me.
A month.
Huh?
I'll make you fall for me in a month,
guaranteed!
"Love in The Air -Premonition of Love-"
This deadline here.
(Special class, submit the assignment)
After that...
(Final exam)
There is a final exam next...
Then...
(Additional commentary)
Not enough time.
I'll never make it!
Kai.
Don't ignore my calls. I'm worried.
Oh, sorry.
A lot of things happened.
Ans you? Did you get home okay
after everything?
Yeah, somehow.
Oh, that's a relief.
About all the things you mentioned,
What is this?
A lot of things...
A lot of things!
Hello, Fuma Delivery.
I won't ask anything.
Huh? Why? No problem at all.
C'mon, ask me!
‘Why do you look so happy today?'
Hey.
You know, as your best friend,
I have to say you should take more
interest in other people.
Right back at you.
Well, well,
if it isn't the top racer
and his genius mechanic, right?
I've already lined up
your next challenger.
It shouldn't be difficult, right?
Let's teach that brat a lesson
to be humble.
"Brat?"
Yes.
That brat...
The one whose body only grows.
Mhm.
Mhmmm!
The racer with the ‘special invite'?
I'm the type of person who
can't refuse if someone asks me.
So kind.
That's great.
Only hot guys can get in there, right?
That's me.
How many times do I have to tell you?
- Oh, wait, that's cheating. Me too.
- Who are you calling? This kid...
Hey.
Baba!
Hmm?
Hmm, what will Eri-chan teach?
Huh, what should we do?
It's impossible to win over the
legendary Arashi-senpai in a month.
Yeah.
Impossible, right?
By the way, you've changed from
Rinka to Arashi-senpai?
Not at all.
I don't like Arashi-senpai at all.
Just want revenge.
Hmm?
Thanks.
In your heart,
who's really in here?
Huh?
Good morning!
Ow!
Don't joke around.
Help me think this through.
Go see Arashi-senpai every day.
Huh, that's all?
Did you know?
Fortune favors the bold.
Alright.
"Fortune..."
"favors the bold?"
That's right.
People who take action will have
a better chance of success than
those who do nothing.
Alright!
That's so simple!
So innocent.
(Day 1)
Arashi-senpai!
What is it?
Is Arashi-senpai here?
He's out at the design office today.
No clue when he'll be back.
Is that so?
(Day 2)
Excuse me. Where's Arashi-senpai?
Too bad. He just left in the car.
(Day 3...)
Arashi-senpai!
Hello.
You're here every day.
That guy's been busy lately.
I'll come again.
So how's that plan going?
I haven't seen him at all.
If you can't solve the first problem,
you can't go to the next one.
Another thing...
There's the work, too.
If you don't hurry up, you won't be
able to submit it in time.
Yes.
What you said is right.
Arashi-senpai!
Umm...
Raita-san said I could sit here.
See? I'm not in the way.
Sorry.
I'll leave no.
You eaten?
What do you want, Senpai?
Trying to learn about me?
No! I'm just asking for the order.
And what do you like, Rei?
Hamburg and...
Fried rice and...
Uhm, stir-fried vegetables.
Mami-san, I'll have these.
Okay.
Huh?
I didn't ask you to order what I like.
Too late, idiot.
You're trying to trick me
into answering,
it's still 10 years too early.
Calling me stupid again.
So,
what's your big plan to ‘win' me?
Can't see it at all.
Keep your voice down!
The people around will hear everything.
Huh?
Embarrassed of the people around?
You could always back out.
Don't talk like I don't dare.
I'm trying to woo this guy.
Support me, please.
Good luck!
- Oh!
Dammit.
Good luck, idiot.
Don't be mad, I said I'm sorry.
You tricked me, made me angry,
and then I yelled in the store.
And you laughed because
you think it was funny.
I won't forgive you.
I laughed because I thought it was cute.
It's different from mocking.
What?
Wait up.
Let's talk properly.
Talking about what?
Next time, if you want to come,
contact me.
Don't waste your time waiting for me.
I told you to use your time wisely.
If I'm at the garage, I'll contact you.
That means...
- You're starting to like me?
- No.
Just having fun around you.
You're teasing me again.
So today, let's reward
the kid who tried hard.
Try using the word "cute"
instead of "stupid".
Too late.
Cute kid.
Good luck.
Hey.
If you're not going to follow me,
I'll leave you here.
Arashi-senpai is cheating.
This makes the current rules obsolete.
On the other hand, doing so
can have negative effects.
For example, with today's new look,
there may be more strict regulations
than we can handle.
Also, when it comes to architecture,
there are other methods
(Arashi: I'll go to the garage early today)
that are added for the same purpose.
Success!
Then next week,
we'll continue on page 23.
Please prepare yourself.
Then I'll go back first.
Oh, wait, is the work done?
Uh, I have to go outside.
You know, we have to submit the work
by 8:30 tomorrow morning.
Let's not go see Arashi-senpai today.
Don't worry, I told you it's okay.
Easy, easy.
Rei, give me a moment.
Yes?
I have something to talk about.
Do you have time tomorrow?
Mhm, sure.
Mhm.
Maybe spring has arrived for Rei.
Huh?
That's good.
Yeah, well...
What kind of reaction is that?
Have you forgotten who you like?
It's not like that.
That's already sure.
"Sure?"
I'm off. See you tomorrow.
You're good.
Right?
I'm confident about this.
When's the deadline?
Why?
I just thought I'd treat you to a meal
for an idiot.
"Idiot"
means "cute."
It's okay if you don't want it.
Wait a minute.
I'll go.
I'll wait at the motorbike.
Hurry up and follow me.
I'm done.
Mhm...
Haa...
Let's sleep a bit.
If you want to seduce me,
make it more natural.
Yes?
Huh?
What time is it?
Oh no!
I'm sorry!
I can't accept this work.
But I finished it on time.
You and the other students
have the same amount of time.
And everyone else besides you
has already submitted it.
I'm really sorry.
I know I was wrong.
But can you give me another chance?
What do you think it would be like
if you did this after you graduated
and got a job?
Apologizing doesn't mean
you'll always get another chance.
(Lecture room)
Rei.
How is it?
Rei, are you alright?
No problem, I'm alright.
If you're worried, tell me.
I'm always ready to give advice.
It's really okay.
Mhm...
I haven't slept all night,
so I'm sleepy.
Sorry, Rinka.
Can we talk about what you said you'd
talk about yesterday tomorrow?
Mhm.
See ya.
Why did I come here?
Rei!
What happened?
I...
messed up completely.
You look like a drenched puppy.
Tell me everything.
Senpai...
I'm no good.
I couldn't meet the deadline.
I...
Yesterday's assignment?
Mhm.
Then I'm not going to comfort you.
I don't need you to comfort me.
I know it's my mistake.
Then all you can do is accept it.
Rei.
You shouldn't come here anymore.
Huh?
“Not Just the Rain, but the Storm Approaches”
"Love in The Air -Premonition of Love-"
Leaving your lips unguarded…
So careless.
I'll wait until you're ready.