You are already starting to love your car too much.
Everyone has things they love, right?
Isn't it enough to love only me?
It's different.
How is it different?
This car is something I love,
but you are the one I love.
Seriously,
why do you enjoy driving racing cars?
Actually...
I don't like racing with anyone.
I like driving alone.
It helps me focus more.
Most importantly,
it's another way for me to let out my anger.
To the extent that you own a racetrack,
your anger level must be really high.
Of course.
If it's me
who wants to vent my anger,
I'll shout it out.
For instance...
Go to hell!
- Dumbass! - Hey! Hey, calm down.
You're going to startle everyone around here! Why did you do that?
Just showing you an example.
That was a pretty harsh example. Did someone just make you angry?
I rarely see you driving racing cars these days,
which means you're in a good mood, aren't you?
Mm. I don't have much to be angry about.
Since we've been together,
I smile and laugh more than I get angry.
Wanna try driving?
Me? Driving?
But you're not dressed for it.
- Hey, you. - Hmm?
Next week,
my mother will organize a charity event to help eliminate violence against women.
Umm...
That sounds interesting.
Are you going?
Of course I am.
Then... do I have to go?
Yes, you do.
Sometimes,
that might be the right time for us to make our relationship public.
If I go there,
won't I steal the spotlight from your mother?
I don't care.
I care more about having our relationship recognized by the public.
Can I get a hug?
That's a pretty good idea.
I think your mother would probably like a big, dramatic moment.
Yes, Kee.
What I asked you to look into,
how's it going?
I have already looked into it.
It might not be true.
As far as I know, Ms. Ruwajee doesn't like Ms. Weiling at all
and doesn't want her to marry her brother.
This might be a made-up story
to bring about the inheritance lawsuit.
I shouldn't have believed a drunk person.
If we can't use their infidelity,
then we focus on their confidants,
those they trust the most.
They just made a token protest.
They probably want land values ​​to rise.
Get out! [Don't cheat us!]
[All our land was taken from us] [You cheating fat cat! We won't move!]
- Get out! - Go away! We will not leave!
Can you hear me?! Get out!
You! Greedy capitalists!
We won't go away!! [Don't cheat us! Our land! Our villages!]
We'll stay here!
Get lost, you pigs! Get out! [Greedy investors]
Do what we usually do.
But don't go over budget.
They'll get used to asking for more and more.
Or you can talk to their leaders.
He may help persuade the others.
Yes, ma'am. I'll take care of it.
What about the other things I asked you to look into?
You mean...
Everything.
About your friend,
I haven't found anything yet.
But if it's about Arisa,
I've found something that can be used against her.
What is it?
Well...
Mom, can I talk to you?
Yes?
I just want to talk about the upcoming charity event.
Why?
Well,
I want to use this chance to introduce Arisa
as my lover.
Did she ask for this?
No, she didn't.
It's what I want.
I want to make it public that I'm in a relationship.
Haven't you ever wanted
to hold someone's hand
and tell everyone they're your loved one?
Lalin,
I don't want you to be too sure.
If you two ever break up,
we'll become a laughingstock.
Why do you keep thinking we're going to break up?
What's behind that?
I just want you to give Arisa a chance.
How much does she have to prove herself to you?
Even giving us money to pay off the debt still doesn't satisfy you, huh?
No one
gives anything without expecting something in return.
We just don't know what that expectation is yet.
Lalin,
it's up to you.
Sometimes, I also think
I can't always protect you.
You'll have to learn on your own.
And one day, you'll understand
why I did
what I did.
I've already looked into Wit.
His family
has worked for Weiling since his father's time.
After his parents died,
he took over
and has sincerely worked for Weiling
for many years.
What's he like?
In terms of work,
he's like Weiling's personal assistant.
But in terms of his personal life,
he's been living with his girlfriend for many years.
So, is there any weakness we can use against him?
That would be his girlfriend.
From what I've found out about him,
their relationship
doesn't seem like a normal one.
Leave it to me.
Hello.
I'm a freelance artist
looking for a gallery space.
Are you available?
Ah...
Yeah, but...
our gallery has capacity limits
since I'm the only one responsible for it.
If there are too many people, I can't handle them all.
If you can't accept this condition, I can recommend some other galleries.
That's fine.
Just a small number.
Only one person.
I didn't know there was such a beautiful gallery around here.
And there's still plenty of availability.
We don't really host events very often.
I used to take on big projects, but I couldn't handle them.
So I only take on small projects.
My husband kept complaining to me about it.
Doing it alone and still handling everything this well
is already great.
Are you alright?
I'm kind of clumsy.
I often bump into things,
so I sometimes get hurt.
Excuse me, let me have a look.
This kind of bruise is from...
fingerprints.
This is my personal matter.
Once you've had a look around,
let me know if you're interested.
I have something to take care of. Thank you for coming.
Your husband did that, didn't he?
You've been through all this, and you still haven't broken up with him?
You hope he'll change, right?
I'm sorry for meddling in your personal matters,
but my father taught me that
a man who hurts a woman
or hits his wife
is not a good man.
You don't need to keep him in your life.
You... You're not with him, are you?
No, I'm not.
I'm not with him.
It's okay, I won't hurt you.
Hey...
I'm strong enough to protect you.
You just have to tell me.
Who did this to you?
And what has happened to you?
Tell me everything.
Wit is a devilish person.
He hits me every day.
Especially when he's stressed from work,
he hits me even more.
He always checks my phone,
including my call history.
I don't have any money.
I tried to leave,
but I didn't know where to go.
I have no relatives.
He is the only family I have.
Have you ever tried to file a complaint?
Yes, I have.
But it didn't help.
The police said it was a domestic matter
and just tried to mediate.
After that day,
I've been beaten even more severely,
so I think I'd better just keep enduring it.
Don't worry.
I'll help you.
But you need to listen to me.
Go home and wait for him like usual.
Don't be afraid.
I understand you.
But now we need damning evidence against him.
Stay strong.
Be patient.
I promise you,
he'll never lay a hand on you again.
Can you really help me get out of this?
Hey...
What do you think of this dress?
Why aren't you saying anything?
You're stressing me out.
Beautiful. It suits you.
You said that about the last one, too.
Well, you look good
in anything you wear.
Since it's our first event together as a couple,
I think this dress is perfect.
Okay.
I'll go with this one, then.
We'll go with this one.
Please send it to us.
Noted. Thank you so much.
So beautiful.
Do you like it?
Yeah, I like this one.
Hey, could you please zip it up for me?
Hey!
Hmm?
Are you teasing me?
I almost let my intrusive thoughts win,
but I didn't.
You're such a tease.
Better watch it.
If it's my turn, you'll fall into a trap.
Here,
let me zip it up for you.
No more.
Hey!
So refreshing.
Is there anywhere you want to go today?
I don't have any plans yet,
but the only plan I have right now
is to stick with you.
And you? Is there anywhere you wanna go?
Yes.
There is a place I want you to visit.
In a few more days, it'll be 20 years since I last saw you both.
Hello, Mother and Father.
I'm Lalin,
Arisa's girlfriend.
In the near future, Lalin will become part of our family.
If you were here,
things would be easier.
Unfortunately, I never got the chance to meet your parents.
But I know they must have done a wonderful job raising you.
Greedy investors, get out!
Get out!
Get out! [Greedy investors!]
Get out! Get out!! [Stop exploiting people!]
- Get out! - Get out!
Get out!! Get out!
If you won't get out, then come out and talk to us!
Get out!
Let's calm down first, everyone.
- Please calm down. - You! Greedy capitalists!
Why on earth are you opening so many malls? Huh?!
What the f*ck do you need so much space for?
We've been living here since our great-grandparents' time!
Where the hell are we supposed to go if we can't live here?!
Everyone, calm down. Please, calm down.
We don't have any bad intentions.
We just want to develop this land
and improve your quality of life.
Improve our quality of life?
You want to improve yours! What about us?
You build shopping malls! You build sidewalks!
You install air conditioners for your own comfort! But what about us?!
- Exactly! - We've got nothing at all!
You must get out!
I understand you. I understand that everyone here is deeply connected to this land.
But I just want to say that
"home"
means the people who live there.
What the f*ck are you saying?
Home is home.
You're demolishing our homes!
We have nowhere to live!
Where on earth can we live?!
Right! That's right!
Get the hell out of here!
I just want to let you know
that everyone has the right to start a family anywhere.
Our company
would like to offer
compensation to everyone.
One million baht for each family.
Everyone!
If you want the million baht, go ahead and take it.
But I'm not taking it!
Me, too!
The money isn't enough!
It's just hush money to keep us quiet!
- Yes! - Right!
We're not gonna move!!
- We don't want it! - We're not gonna move!
- Calm down, please. - Please, calm down.
Please, calm down first.
Calm down. Calm down.
Calm down. Take it easy.
- Go! - Get out!
Calm down. Everyone, please calm down.
Hey, what's up?
I'm in the alley now.
Yeah.
I already bought it.
Mhm.
Is the A/C broken?
Yes, it is.
Why didn't you call the technician this afternoon?
Doing repairs this late at night
means I can't get any rest.
It just broke,
so I called the technician.
It's done.
Thank you so much.
What were you thinking,
calling the technician this late?
You really want to be alone with another man that much?
Are you crazy? You're overthinking it.
How can I not?
Look at what you've done.
I work so hard for you,
and this is what I get?
I don't want to talk to you anymore.
- Talk to me first. - Let go! Let go of me!
Shut the hell up!
Pin...
I'm sorry.
Hello, Ms. Weiling.
Where are you guys going?
Honestly, you should teach Lalin how to work.
Now that my daughter has a partner,
I just hope you'll have a good future together.
You make it sound like Lalin is still a kid.
She knows what she's doing.
Anyway,
I heard you want to come to the charity event
and go public with your relationship.
Do you have any surprises for me?
No.
I just do what Lalin wants.
Whether we go public or not
doesn't matter to me.
Being together matters more.
How romantic...
No wonder Lalin's so obsessed with you.
It's not an obsession,
it's love.
It's the kind of love where we take care of each other.
What about you, Ms. Weiling?
Have you ever had someone you love and want to take care of?
All done! Here I am!
What were you guys talking about?
Arisa told me she also wants to go to the charity event.
She said she'll donate ten million baht.
Whoa!
That's a lot!
Awesome!
If it makes you
and your mother happy,
I'll do anything for it.
Come on, let's go.
Goodbye, Mom.
Goodbye.
All you do are things a rich girl would do,
like playing the piano or riding horses.
Of course.
It's called "pretty girl activities."
If you expect me to do something tough, I'm not doing it.
Back in the day,
my father brought me here every week for horse riding lessons,
while my mom often complained that it wasn't useful for business purposes.
I do agree with your father,
since these skills
can be useful someday.
My father was pretty cool, right?
I'll bring you to meet him next time.
Why not?
Did you have fun?
Of course, I did.
Hey! Kee?!
Hey, Kee!
How have you been? Long time no see.
How are you?
I'm good.
And what about you?
Pretty good.
But look at you...
You look better.
Leave your old self behind!
Oh,
this is Lalin.
Hello.
Alright, see you later. I work here.
We should grab a bite sometime. Let me know if you're coming.
Who was that? You seem close to her.
An old friend of mine.
Did she just call you "Kee"?
That's my old name,
but I go by "Arisa" now.
Let's go.
Let's.
How do you know that woman?
Tell me about it.
I'll pay you for that.
Closer, please. Yes, so beautiful.
Is this your official debut
as a real estate couple?
Not really,
and I don't want it to be a big deal.
We just want to let everyone know.
How lovely!
I also want to show respect to Lalin.
So, would Ms. Weiling,
Lalin's mother, be okay with her daughter dating her business rival, Ms. Arisa?
She fully supports our relationship
and never sees Arisa as a rival.
Business can't compete with love.
Aww... so sweet.
Could I take some pictures, please?
-This way. - This way, please.
The information about Arisa's past,
are you sure about it?
Yes, I am.
It's reliable.
Good.
So Lalin will learn
what Arisa is hiding.
Lalin chose her girlfriend well.
I like this one.
I'm also curious
how she managed to get close to you so quickly
that you ended up liking her so fast.
It's fine either way,
but I know Arisa is the one who makes my niece happy.
So, I'll help them get what they want.
I'm not a heartless mother.
If she loves a good person, I'll support her without hesitation.
If not,
I'll get rid of her without hesitation.
Hello.
First of all, I would like to thank all of our honored guests
for joining the charity event I organized
to fight violence against women.
I used to know someone
who went through a painful experience in love.
A broken,
divided
family.
That's where my idea came from.
To organize a fundraising event
to help victims of violence
who feel trapped.
I want to give them the courage to leave those situations.
I want them to know that from now on,
they don't have to fight alone anymore.
Speaking of violence,
one of tonight's donors
might know it best,
Ms. Arisa Kulnavee.
She was once sent to a Juvenile Observation and Protection Center
under supervision
due to a violent offense.
So today,
I want to invite Arisa to share her experience
with everyone here.
First of all,
I would like to thank Ms. Weiling
for attempting to bring up my past,
even though I've already moved on from it.
My past
is the biggest lesson of my life,
as it taught me to be strong
and showed me that
everyone can always start a new life.
All we need is someone who gives us a chance.
Everyone wants a chance, right?
I'm lucky
because I've already found that person.
She is Lalin.
Lalin is the only one who wants me to have a better life
and never cares about my past,
no matter how it is brought up.
I'm happy to be able to spend my life with you.
I used to say that to your mother once.
But today...
I'll say it in front of everyone here.
Lalin,
will you marry me?
Yes, I will.
No matter what you've been through,
I'll marry you.
How do you know that woman?
Tell me about it.
I'll pay you for that.
This man
is the one who will pay me
to get your past from me.
Did you tell him anything?
No, I didn't.
You and I have been through so much together.
I'll never betray you.
Why do you want to know about my past?
What about you?
You also looked into Ms. Weiling's past.
So why can't we look into your past?
Ms. Weiling will never show you her weakness for you to use against her.
Ms. Weiling may not have a weakness,
but you do.
What do you mean?
Pin...
I'm sorry.
Thank you so much.
What have you done with Pin?!
She is in a safe place.
A place where she is safe from you.
Don't worry about her.
The only woman you should worry about
is Ms. Weiling.
From now on,
you must work for me.
Otherwise,
you'll never see your beloved wife again.
Oh,
and as for my past you want to know about,
I'll tell you.
But you must remember every single word.
Don't you dare twist any words.
Please take care of Lalin for me.
What big news.
How did you explain yourself?
Why did I have to do that?
The truth remains.
Besides, I haven't done anything wrong.
I've already told the officers everything.
But it already happened.
Being involved with someone who has done an illegal business
is not a minor issue.
Not only you will be affected,
but also the companies you hold shares in
will be investigated, too.
More importantly,
what about Lalin?
Her reputation might also be ruined by this.
Don't worry too much about that,
I won't let this damage her reputation.
I hope that's true.
Soon,
Lalin will finally see
who the real
Arisa is.
It's true, though.
When it comes to a scammer thing,
people are ready to judge you.
It takes ages for the result to come,
and by that time, the news will have spread widely.
The truth comes too late, no one waits to hear it.
I see.
We tend to believe what we want to believe.
You're right.
But at least, you still got Lalin by your side.
When life's ruined,
having someone by your side is so important.
Lalin is just as great as her dad, Thana.
When I was a teenager,
I went to study in the States.
And I fell in love with a foreign guy.
My family really looked down on him.
Eventually, we couldn't make it.
I was told to fly back to Thailand.
My parents did everything so that I couldn't communicate with him.
But there was only Thana,
who said goodbye on my behalf.
He consoled me and everything.
I felt so lucky to have him as a young brother.
But on the day he passed away for good,
I learned that...
life isn't always that kind to us.
From that day onwards,
I had no one else on my side,
no family or friends,
only me.
Have you talked to Weiling?
She's still your sister-in-law, isn't she?
You still can't tell I hate that bitch?
The whole time she was dating my brother,
I knew she was secretly dating someone else.
Acting like a perfect queen.
Scolding me, saying I was a compulsive gambler.
She was no better than me.
Did Mr. Thana know about this?
Just like you said,
we all wanted to believe in what we felt like.
Don't tell Lalin about this.
Let this die with someone old like me.
OK.
Hey...
Is the shop closed?
No, you can come!
♫Happy birthday to you♫
♫Happy birthday to you!♫
♫Happy birthday, happy birthday♫
♫Happy birthday to you♫
Make a wish.
What did you wish?
I wished...
us...
Better not say it.
I'm afraid it won't come true.
I don't think I need to guess
how you found out when my birthday was.
Only Aiy knew about this.
Don't blame her,
I just wanted to surprise you.
I told you,
I'm not into birthdays.
And I don't like surprises either.
I don't know what you've been through in the past.
But it's time...
to recreate good memories.
I hope you can leave bad things behind.
If you can't leave some,
share them with me.
I want to laugh and cry with you.
But the surprise isn't just that.
You got more?
Umm! Follow me.
Can I be your new memory?
A memory that will make you smile forever.
Thanks.
Next week, my mom is holding a violence-against-women charity.
Sometimes,
it's the time we have to open our relationship to public.
For Arisa,
I already got something to attack her.
What is it?
Hey, Kee!
Who is that, dear?
Why do you seem close to her?
An old friend of mine.
How did you know that woman?
Tell me about it.
I'll pay you for that.
So Lalin will know what Arisa hides from her.
No matter how severe your past is,
I want you to know you will always have me by your side.