( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(Previously)
Do you like Jimmy?
No way!
It's fine if you don't
want to tell me the truth.
My friends went out last night.
They know Jimmy's been hitting on me.
My exams are coming up soon.
I'm thinking of turning off my phone.
If he doesn't listen, we have to let
him get hurt until he's had enough.
Are you here to spy on me?!
Did you think I'd sneak out somewhere?
Don't call me. And don't come
here again for a while.
Still clinging to my brother?
You should go ask your brother that.
The day my brother finally has enough,
you'll end up looking
worse than a stray dog.
And I'll be right here,
enjoying every second of it.
What are you space cadet for?
If I were a thief, you'd be dead by now.
I was thinking about P'Toh…
and got carried away.
What happened this time?
Yesterday,
I think he went to see Jimmy.
I don't know what happened,
but he looked completely drained.
That bad?
I feel so sorry for him.
I hate seeing him like this.
Thinking about it makes me so mad.
I should beat Jimmy up.
Violence won't solve anything. The
problem is our person refuses to let go.
You're right…
That's why I said P'Toh
needs to hit rock bottom
and to realize it on his own.
It's the only way.
Cold-blooded.
I didn't know my baby
could be this ruthless.
Wanna break up with me then?
You're scary, but I still love you.
We're at uni.
People are watching.
Promise me…
you'll never do that again.
I can't stand it.
You should head back now.
I can't concentrate with you around.
I need to study.
Hello, Jim!
"Love Alert" (Episode 6)
I just finished my exams,
so I wanted to treat you to lunch.
I can pay if you want.
Just you asking me out makes me happy.
No way. This one is on me.
You can… treat me when my grades are…
good enough.
Deal.
Hey, Jim.
You said you were busy today.
I am busy.
Oh,
This is Title, my friend from uni.
This is P'Toh... he's my brother's friend.
Man, I thought he was your boyfriend.
Just go away already. Shoo.
Just order anything you want.
I'll go to the toilet for a bit.
He asked you out. It's good enough.
Don't be petty and make him angry.
Understand?
P'Toh!
What happened? Your hair is all wet.
Oh.
Something got in my eye,
so I had to wash it out.
You should've told me. I have eye drops.
Using tap water…
will make it red.
P'Toh, I'm starving. Let's order.
Title knows Teh, and I
didn't want any drama.
That's why I introduced you like that.
You're not mad, right?
No, I'm not.
I promised you I wouldn't be petty.
You're the cutest!
Let's order.
Answer it.
Hello, Run?
Are you okay?!
Okay, I'm coming right now.
What's wrong?
My friend... is in trouble.
I'll treat you next time, okay?
A friend?
Right…
Just a friend.
Easy…
Rest here for a bit.
I'll go…
get you something to eat.
Okay?
Wait, Jim…
Thank you…
for letting me stay here,
even though we're over.
Don't mention it.
It's safest for you here.
You don't have to face that
model guy and get hurt again.
Give me a sec.
Run…
I need… to take this.
I'll be back.
Hello.
Jim, are you home?
Yeah. What is it, P'Toh?
I just wanted to make sure.
And what happened?
Why did you leave so suddenly?
Oh,
my friend… had…
a small issue. It's all sorted now.
Everything's cleared up.
Which friend was it? Do I know them?
What happened?
Why are you asking?
You're acting suspicious of me.
No, Jim. I'm not suspicious.
I'm just concerned.
I thought I could help.
If I wanted your help,
I would've asked for it already.
It's like you're not trusting me.
I freaking hate things like this.
Goodbye.
Was that... your new boyfriend?
I guess.
He's the only one for now.
He seems... pretty jealous.
He's like that because…
he probably loves me too much.
Can he…
really put up with you?
When we were together, when I was just a
little jealous and you'd snap at me.
Was it jealousy or throwing a fit?
For someone like me,
if you snap at me, I snap right back.
Stay if you can take it.
I should have been more patient.
At least...
you never laid a hand on me.
Go get some rest, Run.
I'll… handle things from here.
Finish eating?
Are you looking for Jimmy?
Yes.
Pour me a glass of water too.
What are you doing here?
Like I told you,
I wouldn't have let him stay
here if he wasn't in trouble.
I understand.
Sorry for coming unannounced.
I was worried about you.
It's fine.
And... I'm sorry too, for…
snapping at you yesterday.
Actually, Jim, I...
Jim, are you hungry?
I can whip up that shredded chicken noodle
you love. I saw the ingredients in the fridge.
Oh, I'd love that!
I've actually been craving your cooking.
P'Toh?
What's wrong?
Well…
I didn't realize you liked
shredded chicken noodles
made by this friend of yours.
P'Toh, we just cleared the air.
I told you Run is just a friend.
Why are you being so sarcastic?
Stop being so petty!
Just as good as I remember.
It's a thank you.
Tell me whenever you want some.
I can make it for you anytime.
What about your boyfriend?
Aren't you going to apologize?
He seemed really upset.
He just walked out like that.
I never crawl back to anyone first.
He's being that irrational.
Definitely not.
P'Toh,
if I hadn't come home,
I wouldn't have known
you were in this state.
Don't you love yourself at all?
Why are you doing this?
I'm sorry, Teh, for dating Jimmy in secret.
I already knew about that.
I didn't say anything
because I wanted you to see.
To see it with your own eyes and to realize
that Jimmy isn't good enough for you.
He's right.
There are plenty of fish in the sea.
Just dump him.
That's a bit harsh.
But go on.
Keep telling him.
Maybe my brother
will finally snap out of it.
Give your love to someone who deserves it.
Don't waste it on a man like Jimmy.
He treats you like a sure thing.
Calls you when he's hungry.
He disappears when he's satisfied.
It's like he keeps you
as a trophy to show off.
I know you understand what's going on.
You're just struggling to let go.
Jimmy, I'm so sorry.
(Toh: Jimmy, I'm so sorry.)
Need something?
I want an extra pillow.
The sofa was too stiff last night.
I need something to prop up my legs.
Oh.
You should've told me.
I would've slept on the sofa myself.
Just sleep here.
Do you think that we can…
get back together?
(Toh: Jimmy, I'm so sorry. (Read))
Did you think I was gonna kiss you?
It's time for you to leave.
You seem to be better now.
(Jimmy: If you want me
to forgive you, come over.)
(I want to hug and kiss you right now.)
(Wait for me. I'm on my way.)
So nice.
Huh? What's nice?
It's nice that you love…
and always spoil me.
Will you… love me like this forever?
As long as you aren't mean to me,
I'll love and take care of you forever.
Deal?
Deal.
I feel like such a joke.
I comfort him, and he
just runs back to that guy.
That's irritating enough to make me cough.
Who are you talking to?
You're acting weird.
P'Toh, what's so great about Jimmy?
Why are you so head over heels for him?
I'm going to finish this cake
and go celebrate Jim's birthday.
Look after the house for me.
Yes,
I'll look after the house for you.
Hey!
Teh!
To learn from pain is human
but to endure it...
that's my brother.
It's so frustrating.
He just has to suffer until
he hits his breaking point.
I hate seeing him hurt.
As for Jimmy...
I don't know when he'll
stop being such a jerk.
I know he loves my brother.
He just doesn't realize it yet.
What makes you so sure he loves him?
If he didn't, he would've
ended things a long time ago.
And if one day...
P'Toh finally decides to walk away,
what will you do?
I'll be there to comfort him.
Then…
I'll kick Jimmy while he's down.
Eat it.
See you guys there.
I'll catch up with you later.
Hey, P'Toh.
Finished with your exams?
Yeah, just stepped out of the exam room.
I see. Are you going out
to celebrate with your friends?
No,
I'm just gonna go home and sleep.
Exams have been so exhausting.
Is something wrong?
Nothing. I just wanted to ask.
Miss you, Jim.
Okay.
Wow, I want a bite.
Should we sabotage
P'Toh's surprise for Jimmy?
I think he'd kill us both.
I'd disown you, that's for sure.
That's a bit harsh.
We share the same blood. We're siblings.
Mess with my cake then.
You'll find out.
Want to surprise him?
You'll get a surprise yourself.
What?
Oh, nothing.
You should get going.
I'm leaving now.
Take care of the house, Teh!
Will do.
Why did you stop me? He's
going to find out anyway.
He has to see it for himself, not from us.
Hungry?
Where's your daddy?
Hey! Nobody's going
home until we're wasted!
Bottoms up.
Teh,
do you know where Jimmy is?
It's my birthday. Drink up, guys.
Let's get wasted. Cheers!
Cheers!
What?
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday. Happy birthday.
Happy Birthday, Jim.
Make a wish.
What did you wish for?
Wishing for another round with
the guy who brought you the cake?
Hey, it's a secret.
If I tell you, it won't come true.
So you are wishing for another round.
But what about the one you're dating now?
He's not serious about that guy.
Jimmy would've introduced him to us by now.
You've got a point.
Shut up, you guys. I'm hungry.
My blood sugar is dropping.
Make up, make up.
Hey, you.
Come on.
I'm a mess now.
Make up, make up.
It's getting everywhere.
P'Toh, wait! P'Toh!
P'Toh!
P'Toh, stop!
P'Toh.
P'Toh, wait.
Did Teh tell you I was here?
Yes.
But he didn't tell me on his own.
I called him
after I didn't see you at your house.
I get it. I'm sorry.
It was my fault for lying.
I'm sorry.
No.
You don't understand a thing.
Let me ask you.
What exactly am I to you?
Do we have to talk about this now?
What the hell am I to you?!
Why are you shouting at me?
Can't we just talk normally?
Whatever I do,
whatever I say,
it's always wrong to you.
Am I your partner…
or just someone you keep around for sex?
I think you're too emotional right now.
Oh...
really?
Try being in my shoes, Jim.
Just try being me for once.
Then what do you want?
Making a scene,
picking a fight, being rude,
what exactly is your goal?
I freaking hate it…
when you act like this.
You want me to leave?
Do you think I love you that much?
Isn't it you who's been chasing me?
Aren't you who's the one in love?
Let's break up.
Let's see who's going to die first.
You talk like you never loved me at all.
Yeah.
We're through.
Fine.
Once we're done,
never show your face to me again.
Not even as friends.
Remember what you just said!
Make sure you can actually do it.
It's okay, Toh.
It's just a breakup.
You'll be fine, Toh. You'll be fine.
Slow down, Jim! You're gonna pass out!
I want to be wasted on this crappy day.
- Take it easy.
- What's wrong with you?
Hey! Another round!
Easy there.
Hey, Jim?
You're coming back to me, right?
Of course, you will.
I'll be waiting for you.
I'm sorry, P'Toh.
(Next Episode)
P'Toh,
why are you burning up?
What did you do to my brother?!
He's not your toy!
You left him to suffer with a high fever!
Fine.
If you're gonna ghost me, let's see
who going to end up hurting more.
Congratulations on the cafe, P'Toh.
I hope it's a huge success!