In the previous episode,
the first match of
the national tournament
between Nankatsu
and Meiwa started.
Tsubasa fooled Kojiro
with a spectacular lob
and scored the first goal of
the match with ease.
Later, Kojiro kicked
a powerful shot
towards Yuzo,
hitting him with the ball
into the goal.
The second goal
to tie the match.
Unfortunately,
Kojiro's last shot
struck fear into
Yuzo's spirits,
making him unable
to guard his goal.
-Yuzo, do something!
-Stop the ball!
That was
a great play, Tsubasa!
You see, Yuzo?
The ball is our friend,
so don't fear it!
What?
You think
the ball's your friend, huh?
Well, if that's the case...
Here it is!
Kiss it!
Be careful, Tsubasa!
Be careful!
The ball hits
Tsubasa in the face!
What?
No! Tsubasa!
See? There's no need
to fear it!
Thank you, Tsubasa.
I will defend the goal!
-Now, I won't be afraid!
-That's it.
This time
you won't save it!
-Good job, Yuzo, you did it!
Yes!
The ball is my best friend!
I won't ever let it go!
That twerp did it again!
He got his goalie
to regain his confidence!
Here you are, Tsubasa!
Take good care of
our friend!
Yes! Now it's our turn
to attack!
[opening theme]
Episode 15:
I Can't Lose Because It's My Dream!
Here we are live at
the national tournament.
The first half of the match
is almost done
and the scoreboard's
at 1-2 in favor of Meiwa.
Nankatsu is pressured into
having to tie the match.
Tsubasa has the ball
and initiates the attack.
I'm counting on you,
Taro!
You got it!
This time around,
we're gonna show them
that we're friends
with the ball
and we're not afraid.
Don't get
too friendly, punk.
I don't want them
getting through you.
Stop them right now!
-Yes!
I won't let you score!
It's all yours, Taro!
Tsubasa!
Here it comes.
Nankatsu's famous
golden duo's combination,
Tsubasa Ozora
and Taro Misaki,
pass the ball to each other
in perfect synchronization,
getting closer
to Meiwa's goal.
Huh? No!
Come and try to get
the ball if you can.
Yeah!
No, I won't let you shoot.
Kojiro Hyuga
gets closer to Tsubasa
and tries to intercept
the ball from Taro Misaki.
You're mine.
What?
Simply incredible!
Taro Misaki fools Hyuga,
who doesn't make it
to the ball
and it goes directly
to Tsubasa.
It doesn't matter
who kicks it,
I'll stop anyone!
Let's score on them
with our friend, Taro!
And now,
Tsubasa returns the favor
to Taro with
a crossover pass.
No, this can't be.
And here comes Misaki
with a volley and...
Goal!
Team Nankatsu ties
the match with two-all
just before the end
of the first half.
Great teamwork, Taro!
-Thank you, it was
-What a shot!
-a great pass, Tsubasa!
Good job, Taro!
That's how it's done!
And with that whistle,
the first half ends with
a two-all draw
on the scoreboard.
-You're the best! Yeah!
Tsubasa, Taro!
Yeah! We tied.
-You guys did it!
-That was great, man!
-You two are a great duo!
-That was incredible!
Very interesting.
I have no idea
who's going to win.
NANKATSU SC
Team, you were incredible.
Great work, Tsubasa.
That means a lot, Ryo.
Thank you.
Great work out there,
everyone.
Huh?
You were able to
tie the match.
-Thank you!
Hey, Yuzo, think you can
handle the cage?
Of course, Coach.
Don't you worry about that.
I'll protect it for us.
I'll protect it for my life.
-That's right!
That's exactly it!
If we want to win this,
we'll have to attack.
I want you to
score more goals.
You got that?
-Yeah!
Damn it all!
Listen up! I want you
to pass me the ball.
Huh?
We have to score on them.
I'll do it
any way I have to.
I'm going to take care of
those two pesky twerps.
I'll show them
that my skill is superior.
-Yeah!
That young kid,
Tsubasa Ozora...
He's helped light the fire
in Kojiro's heart.
Hey, listen to me,
Kojiro.
Listen up.
Offense is the best defense.
You need to release
all of your strength.
-You hear me?
-All right, Coach!
I didn't come all
the way here just to lose.
Especially not...
to those two.
Everyone is
giving it their all
to make up for
your absence on the pitch,
-don't you think?
-Yes!
That's right, everyone.
You can handle
the second half.
Win this.
I know that you can do it.
Genzo...
I know you wish
to be out there,
but you must
be patient.
You can't help
in your condition.
The players are now
returning to the pitch.
And the second half
is about to start.
For sure in
the second half...
...we'll find out
who the best team is
between them.
You can do it.
Tsubasa versus Kojiro...
Don't get discouraged.
You got this, Taro.
Which of the two will
come out on top?
Will it be Tsubasa Ozora?
Or Kojiro Hyuga?
From now on,
I'll show you
my real style of play,
Tsubasa.
So you'd better
be ready.
And the second half starts.
Team Meiwa
initiates the attack,
but the pass is intercepted
by Taro Misaki
from Team Nankatsu.
Taro Misaki runs
with Mamoru Izawa
and Teppei Kisugi
towards the danger zone.
These three players
are running a fast break.
Nankatsu is switching
to offense.
Get the ball back!
-Yeah!
Two players from
Meiwa slide tackle,
but Taro Misaki manages to
keep control of the ball.
This is as far as you go!
Kojiro Hyuga
gets the ball back,
knocking down Misaki.
It looked a bit harsh,
but it's not against
the rules.
My style is better
than yours.
So you two should
watch and learn.
Huh?
I'm warning you...
You'll wish you had lost
since the very beginning.
You won't get past me.
Nankatsu attempts
to recover the ball...
but receives a direct
hit from Kojiro Hyuga.
Mamoru, no!
Takeshi!
Hyuga passes
to Takeshi Sawada
and runs towards
the opponent's goal.
Captain!
Takeshi Sawada sends
a crossover pass.
I will stop it.
I'm not afraid of you,
Kojiro.
Say your prayers!
Kojiro Hyuga kicks and...
What a goal from Meiwa!
This time, instead of aiming
towards the goalkeeper,
Kojiro Hyuga shot
a powerful kick
towards the other end
of the goal.
Meiwa is up 3-2.
Are you okay?
Are you okay, Mamoru?
Are you hurt?
I'm okay.
Did you see that,
Nankatsu?
-Huh?
You just witnessed
my real style of play.
Don't mind it.
It's just one goal.
You can tie the match.
Nankatsu goes
on the offense.
We won't lose to you.
Teppei!
Hajime!
I have it!
Nankatsu is far
from done.
They're looking for
a goal to tie.
Listen, everyone, I want you
covering Tsubasa.
It's all yours, Taro.
The ball is now
in possession of
the genius Taro Misaki.
But Tsubasa is
totally covered
and that's why he can't
seem to pass the ball.
-Huh?
Tsubasa manages
to outdo the defense
with two of
Meiwa's players.
There's no way.
Score again!
And he scores with
a beautiful header.
Team Nankatsu ties
the score once again.
No...
That little twerp!
This is a nail-biting match.
Both teams have
their minds set on
giving their all
for victory.
Everyone is passing
the ball to their captains
to look for
an opportunity to score.
The battle between
Tsubasa Ozora and
-Kojiro Hyuga is intense.
-I won't let you win!
-The scoreboard is
-Me neither!
updating constantly.
We don't know what team
will take home the win.
And Nankatsu ties
the match once again.
The scoreboard is
a five-all draw.
Neither Tsubasa Ozora
nor Kojiro Hyuga
have given up despite
the terrible heat
that surrounds the pitch.
There are five minutes
on the clock
for this fascinating battle
to come to an end.
I'll never let them win.
Looks like they're equal
in skill, my lady.
Well, actually,
under this boiling heat,
the main factor
for the match
becomes their endurance.
I wonder...
which of the two
will overcome
the major setbacks
of this match?
We'll soon find out.
I can't lose to him!
Which team will score
with such little time left?
Sawada manages
to outplay Urabe
and he moves forward
showing great ball-handling.
Over here, Takeshi!
All yours, Kojiro.
Sawada sends
a crossover pass
to Hyuga.
The ball is in the air.
I can't afford to
lose this match
under any circumstance!
I won't let
my family down!
It's an airborne battle.
Goal!
Oh!
15 minutes into
the second half,
Meiwa scores
a great header.
Kojiro's raw strength
won the duel.
Did you see that?
Soccer is a sport
for men only.
It's not a game
for little twerps.
It's not just a game for me.
What did you just say?
That soccer...
That soccer is my dream!
We'll be back
with Captain Tsubasa!
AFFILIATION: MEIWA FC BIRTHDAY: JANUARY 2 HEIGHT: 136 CM WEIGHT: 39 KG BLOOD TYPE: A
There are four minutes
left in the second half,
and everyone is
asking themselves
if Nankatsu
will manage to tie.
Everybody, let's tie
the match first
and then win.
We'll defend our goal,
no matter what happens.
So...soccer is
your dream, Tsubasa?
You're underestimating
the game.
I'll have to teach
you the hard way.
And the match starts again.
Their defense starts
running down the pitch.
All of Nankatsu is
on the offensive.
I know you guys can do it!
Come on! You guys have to
tie the match.
You can do it!
You can do it, Tsubasa.
I trust you.
Nankatsu is determined
to score again.
Urabe dribbles the ball
and looks for
an opportunity to pass.
Tsubasa Ozora,
the team's #10,
waits in
the opponent's goal,
but Kojiro Hyuga
has him well covered.
Tsubasa...
It doesn't matter how
many passes they make.
I'll stop them all.
Kojiro isn't letting him go.
Be careful, Hanji!
Huh?
And Nankatsu
loses the ball.
Listen up, everyone.
I want all of you
to go on the offense.
-Yeah!
-Yes, Captain!
Instead of
playing defense,
Team Meiwa decides to
counterattack
with all they've got
to secure victory.
Yep, that's it.
You have to
keep attacking
and looking to score.
You guys are
the stronger players.
Get back, guys!
If they score another goal,
it'll be too hard come back.
Sawada sends
a crossover pass.
I got it!
You won't be able
to stop me.
I'm gonna score!
And the ball lands
in the hands of the goalie!
What a great defense!
How did he--?
Great job.
Well done, Yuzo.
That was a great tackle!
No way Team Nankatsu
will ever lose to you!
The goalkeeper shoots
the ball and it lands
-at the feet of Misaki.
-I got him.
Misaki passes it
over to Tsubasa,
but Hyuga plans
to intercept the ball.
Kojiro!
I'm counting on you,
Tsubasa.
I'm gonna score that goal.
I won't let you, twerp.
This is
the decisive moment.
It's a mid-air duel.
It looks like
they're evenly matched.
Both captains go
straight to the floor.
Careful, Tsubasa!
But Tsubasa
quickly recovers!
You can do it, Tsubasa!
Score that goal!
And now,
he has the ball.
He's heading straight
towards Meiwa's goalkeeper
with great speed.
Oh, no, you won't!
Hyuga gets up and
desperately
tries to catch up.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is
a fast-paced battle.
In order to keep the promise
I made to Genzo,
I have to tie this.
You say that
soccer is your dream?
In soccer,
you can only play to win.
You can't lose.
Not only that...
Tsubasa Ozora...
Prepare yourself because
I'll be the one to win!
Tsubasa
manages to evade
Hyuga's sliding tackle.
This can't be!
The ball is
in the air...
Tsubasa shoots and...
Goal!
And Nankatsu
ties the match
right at the last
second on the clock.
But how?
How did he evade
my sliding tackle?
That's impossible.
I can't...
I can't lose like this.
I can't let
my family down.
That soccer
is my dream.
-Wow, Tsubasa, great job!
-You really did it.
You tied the match, Tsubasa!
Congrats!
Yeah!
After losing to Kojiro,
you learned from
your mistakes.
In the end, you improved
your soccer style.
That's one of
your strengths.
There's still a minute left.
If we attack them,
I'm sure that we can
come out on top.
Let's keep at it.
-Yeah!
I'm sorry, Captain.
-Takeshi...
-Huh?
When the whistle blows,
I want you to pass me
the ball immediately.
What?
Uh...
Tsubasa...
I admit it. I underestimated
you in the beginning.
I got cocky trying
to go head-to-head.
I never imagined that
there'd be someone
in this tournament
who could stop me.
But I'm far from done.
This time around...
you won't get
to stop me.
-Huh?
-He's going to shoot.
I'll show you
the real power
of Kojiro Hyuga!
No!
Hyuga shoots an amazingly
powerful shot
from midfield.
Tsubasa Ozora attempts
to get to the ball.
But he misses!
And the ball makes
direct impact
with the goalpost!
Nakayama receives it
and passes the ball,
but just like that,
Hyuga intercepts it and
he's determined to score.
The captain from
Meiwa wants the victory.
Kojiro,
you're incredible.
Your determination
and strength are endless.
You're just like Genzo.
Hyuga runs with
determination
towards the goal.
Meanwhile, the ref is
looking at his watch.
Impressive!
Tsubasa's in front of
the goal to defend it.
He doesn't plan to
leave it to luck this time.
Hyuga tries to fool him,
but it's futile.
Tsubasa doesn't fall for any
of his opponent's feints.
I won't lose to you.
I won't let you score,
Kojiro.
I will come out on top,
Tsubasa!
Don't give up, Tsubasa!
Do it, Kojiro.
Do it, Tsubasa.
The stadium's roars
are literally deafening.
From the start,
it's been a duel
between Tsubasa
and Kojiro.
Both of them
have shown to be
extraordinary players.
But in this last minute,
the winner of this duel
will be decided.
Don't get distracted,
Tsubasa.
Come on, Kojiro.
You have to
take advantage of
any opportunity
to shoot.
No! It looks like
Tsubasa Ozora
took a wrong step.
And now,
he's losing his balance.
This is my opportunity.
Hyuga sees
Tsubasa Ozora's blunder
and winds up for the winning
shot of the match.
Now!
Hyuga can't shoot.
Tsubasa kicks
the ball away with
-a miraculous
-No, you won't.
-sliding tackle.
-Damn you, twerp!
You fell down
on purpose.
That's it, Tsubasa!
The ball is now
under the possession
of Shingo Takasugi.
The referee is about
to blow the whistle and...!
Huh?
-Huh?
Goal!
And it's over!
Team Meiwa scored
at the last second.
Team Nankatsu lost!
Oh...
-Oh...
Oh, what a great match,
ladies and gentlemen!
Both teams played
splendidly well.
The captains faced off
in a six-goal duel,
but thanks to
Takeshi Sawada,
Meiwa defeated Nankatsu
by a one goal
making the score 6 to 7.
It's incredible.
The first match of
the national tournament
turned out to be
truly spectacular.
Even if Meiwa
won the match,
to me, the duel between
Kojiro and Tsubasa
is a draw.
Tsubasa...
Huh?
Oh!
No...
Is he...
crying?
Tsubasa...
Let's get going.
Meiwa, Nankatsu,
you both played well!
What a great match, kids!
The crowd cheers
and applauds
for both teams.
They played like
professionals!
It was a great match,
a real battle of titans.
NANKATSU SC
Why the long face,
everybody?
Don't sweat it.
It doesn't matter
if we lost.
You played your best.
Not everything's lost.
Relax, guys.
This match
doesn't determine
if we're out of
the national tournament.
Oh!
Yeah, that's true.
Because in the
elimination phase,
two teams from each group
can make it out.
If we win the next
four matches that follow,
we will still be in
the national tournament.
Yeah, you're right.
We can still do this.
Tsubasa...
You're the captain.
You can't put all
the blame on yourself.
Leave this defeat
in the past.
What's important now is to
win all the next matches.
If we win our matches,
we can go head-to-head
with Meiwa again later on.
Mhm.
That's it, Captain.
We can still win.
Don't get discouraged.
You got that?
Tadashi speaking.
Hey, Yuzo,
this is for you.
Huh?
Yeah, buddy, we lost.
But it was
an incredible match.
You really outdid
yourself, Yuzo.
I'm proud of you.
Thank you so much
for that, Genzo.
-Huh?
I'm asking you...
Take care of our goal
until I can come back.
Yeah!
Don't you worry about it.
It's a deal then.
Can you put
Tsubasa on, please?
Uh... Yeah, I'll put him on.
Just wait.
Hello?
Do you hear me?
Yeah...
Yeah.
Of course.
Leave it all to me.
All we have to do is
win the next four matches,
and we can qualify
for the finals
of the tournament.
Don't you worry.
We'll take care of it, Genzo.
No sweat.
Exactly, we're going to win.
Isn't that right, everyone?
-Yeah!
I'm counting on
all of you guys.
I'll try to recover
as fast as possible
so I can play
with you all.
We'll win the national
tournament together.
In the first round
of the tournament,
Team Furano got
a win over Team Nagano
in their first encounter,
2 to 1.
Nagano couldn't
keep up with
the teamwork of Furano.
And on the other side,
in the fourth group,
Team Musashi goes up
against Team Jonan.
And here is
Prince Jun Misugi
intercepting the ball.
Oh, I'm so jealous!
All the ladies love him.
Huh?
What an elegant feint.
And a beautiful jump.
Jun Misugi plays as if
he were painting a canvas
and all of the crowd
watches the maestro.
Tsubasa, I'm really
looking forward
to get on the pitch
to face you.
Jun Misugi.
Goal!
Team Musashi has
an overwhelming lead
in the beginning
of the match.
That's how
it's done, Captain!
First, it was Kojiro,
and now it's Jun.
I'm sure he'll be
an amazing opponent.
Jun Misugi.
If we want to win
the national tournament,
we'll have to
defeat him first.
I thought I had
everything under control.
My shot was
unstoppable.
Someway, somehow,
he managed to divert it.
He prevented the ball
from going into the goal.
The worst part is that...
I lost the last battle
against him.
Are you Kojiro Hyuga?
Huh?
We've taken an interest
in you, young man.
Are you guys,
player scouts?
Yes.
We represent...
the Toho Academy.
[ending theme]