( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
STILL SHINING
ACCESS
The changing room
is down the hall on the right.
You can put on a uniform in your size.
Did you bring a pair of black flats?
Yes.
You may go in.
CHANGING ROOM
Work starts at 2:00 p.m.
So we'll move at 1:55 p.m.
-Yes, ma'am.
Could you try these on?
Okay.
STILL SHINING
When are the guests leaving?
In 30 or 40 minutes.
How was the work?
It was hard,
but it was fun.
Geez, I'm tired.
So this is what it looks like from here.
I can see the mountains.
And the sunset too.
I'll work part-time on weekends for now.
Then, I'll decide to take time off or not.
You should once you're an intern.
Apply for the summer internship.
When you become an intern,
you can move into the residence hall.
What's that?
The dorms.
The dorms?
You can dorm once you become an intern.
How long is the internship?
It depends.
It can be for summer vacation,
for half a year, or for even a year.
If they're providing housing in dorms,
the internship must be long and tough.
I might take a break from school.
Have you selected a department yet?
Not yet.
Should I take
the first position that opens?
If possible,
I hope you get the position you want.
The position I want?
I'll ask what departments they have.
I'm happy just thinking about it.
You're good at English,
you like people,
and you draw vegetables well.
I told you there was a job for you.
Geez. I can't believe you remember that.
Vegetable drawings
are probably going to be useless.
I hope it's somewhere I can speak English.
I'm good at casual small talk.
Before So-hyeon was around,
I used to talk with guests
when there weren't too many of them.
I can speak English with confidence.
Impressive, right?
You're all excited.
I am.
My dream of becoming independent
felt uncertain,
but it's feeling more concrete now.
I guess this is what opportunity is.
I only work on weekends for now,
but I'll gradually start working weekdays.
I'm free only on the weekends though.
-Matching our schedules might be…
-How about Friday nights?
-Let's work it out.
-Yeah.
When it's destiny, it's not vague.
It's clear. You don't hesitate about it.
I guess that's how people find
direction in life and move forward.
I'm curious. In what way is it clear?
You can feel it.
Because of you,
I know what destiny feels like.
Why don't I know it then?
As soon as you see something, bam, boom!
It feels strong and clear.
Try to think back.
Bam? Boom?
I've felt that so many times.
When did you feel it?
What? When was it?
When you stumbled
as if you were about to faint
while walking across the schoolyard.
Me? Come on. I've never stumbled.
Sorry. Was that too strong?
Hey!
I guess you're okay with me
going home alone now?
Does it upset you?
A little.
Nice job adapting.
I'll come down Saturday night.
If I leave right after tutoring,
it'll be around 11:00 p.m. And…
I've never felt comfortable
seeing you leave alone.
Okay?
"I hope you enjoy your time here."
Your time here?
"Your time here."
We'll head out onto the floor.
-Yes, ma'am.
The guests are still here.
Okay. Have a good one.
SAINT OCEAN HOTEL
SUMMER INTERNSHIP PROGRAM
INTERNSHIP BENEFITS
FREE DORMITORY ACCOMMODATION
I'm so exhausted.
But it's so much fun.
Tae-seo.
How's the food?
-It's so well-arranged and delicious.
-Thank you.
Is there anything you need?
Gosh, there's so much food.
-We'll let you know.
-Thanks for the food.
Let's try them in order.
I'm coming in.
I think Eun-a's exhausted.
The work must be hard.
I don't know.
Ask her yourself.
She won't tell me.
This was cooked really nicely.
Could you take some to her
before it's gone?
Wait. Will she hate it
because it's fattening?
They're asking for me.
You should take it to her yourself.
She won't eat it if I do.
Don't be intimidated by her.
Check in on her and ask her everything.
Hold still.
-What?
-Is that it?
Eun-a.
Eun-a!
Why were you hiding your relationship?
We started seeing each other
during senior year,
so we didn't want our families to worry.
There's no need to hide it anymore,
but I guess we got used to it.
We won't do that anymore.
We're fine on our own.
Can you just come down and talk to us?
I understand.
It's a small town,
so they'd just gossip about it.
That's right.
Okay, let's keep it a secret.
I'll stay quiet too.
You're using contraception, right?
We haven't done…
Well, be careful in the future.
Don't try to act like my mom, So-hyeon.
Did I say something wrong?
You're 20 years old now.
You're not young anymore.
You should be careful about these things.
So damn embarrassing.
You're something else.
You don't even pry or tell me what to do.
How can I tell you what to do?
All I can do is wait
until you feel better.
She's going to marry my dad.
I like that my dad's getting married.
But I don't know
what kind of person she is.
She says she was born in Hawaii,
but she speaks fluent Korean.
Sometimes, I think she's a scammer.
But she goes harvesting
vegetables with Dad
and gladly does all the hard work.
One moment, I feel like it's good
that Dad has someone like her.
Then the next moment, I don't.
Anyway,
I feel uneasy at home.
I should hurry and move out.
Does that answer all the questions
in your head?
It's just…
I only want to tell you
about nice and happy things.
I try not to talk about my problems.
Do I seem like
I'm still having a hard time?
No.
But I don't know.
I end up telling you everything anyway.
Eun-a,
I'm all right.
You can tell me right away
when things are tough.
Tell me when you feel lost, not after.
Tell me even if I might not have
the right answer.
I'll do that.
Look at me, Eun-a.
You said you felt at ease
when you looked at me.
Look.
JUNE
I started writing my paper,
but it's still a draft.
Since it's about AI controllers,
it's interesting.
Which AI learning method are you using?
The reinforcement learning method.
I'm reading a paper about that.
Want me to look it up?
That'd be great.
Want to come to our lab during vacation?
It's fun studying there during vacation.
You might be able to become
a lab member too.
You'll go to grad school anyway.
-I haven't thought about it.
-Really?
You're an academic type.
People like you end up in labs.
What kind of person am I?
You?
You understand equations
in a physical sense.
Those who try to grasp meanings
fixate on the nature of things.
You should do what you like.
Can liking something
be the basis for everything one does?
Of course. What else would it be?
One's condition, situation,
or responsibilities?
That's refreshing to hear.
No one decides their future
on those these days.
They only focus on themselves.
Anyway, come join us this summer.
Hey, we don't let
just anyone join our lab.
I know.
Can I keep reading it?
Of course. You're our ace.
-I'm going to go see the professor.
-Okay. Thank you.
Sure.
What are you up to? Are you in class?
I have a free period, so I'm in the lab.
When should we meet?
Let's match our schedules.
When's good for you?
How about Wednesday evening?
I have tutoring that I can't reschedule.
Exams are coming soon.
I get off work at 7:00 p.m. on Friday.
I'm working Saturday afternoon.
What about Saturday morning?
SATURDAY
PREPARE FOR FINALS
It works. I'll come to you.
SEONG-CHAN
Yes?
Are you still at the hotel?
The GRO team is looking for an intern.
What's GRO?
It's basically working the VIP lounge.
You might have the upper hand.
The guests here often go to your place.
This department might fit you well.
It's perfect.
I'm pretty familiar with my guests.
That's why I'm recommending it.
Go to the second floor.
Introduce yourself
to the team leader, Yun Da-jeong.
She'll know your place well.
And tell her you're here
as a part-time worker.
-Ms. Yun.
-Yes?
-Guests are waiting downstairs.
-Okay. Thanks.
Hello, ma'am. I'm Mo Eun-a.
Right.
Seong-chan told me about you.
I'm working part-time at the banquet hall.
I'll get going then.
All right.
Right. Are you free this Saturday morning?
My team needs a part-timer.
Yes, I'm free.
See you then.
Right, Tae-seo.
Hello.
Please come this way.
Last time, we learned
-about Fleming's Left-Hand Rule, right?
-Yes.
This question's about that.
The direction of rotation is plus…
-Mr. Yeon.
-Yes?
Just a second.
Yes?
Should I book you for Saturday morning?
Well…
I'm going home on Saturday.
Mr. Yeon, their finals are almost here,
so weekends are a must for extra lessons.
This is why we need real teachers.
College students have no responsibility.
What about Sunday?
I can do it.
What time should I put you down for?
Around 1:00 p.m. or 2:00 p.m.
I'll schedule you at 2:00 p.m. then.
ROLLING STOCK DRIVER'S LICENSE
What's that?
Someone left it
and hasn't come to get it for months.
When I cover cup noodles with this,
it provides the perfect pressure.
Eat dinner at my place
before you go tutoring. It's nearby.
My mom makes chicken soup every day.
I'm sick of it. You eat it for me.
I already ate. I need more sleep.
Geez, this chair…
Excuse me.
Someone's sitting in Seat One.
Please tell them to switch seats.
-He's sitting there because he booked it.
-It's my seat.
Your one-month reservation
ended yesterday.
But I've always sat there.
You can't do this.
He's retaking the CSAT.
He came this morning
and booked Seat One for a month.
Of all the seats,
why did he have to take mine?
The one who studied there last year
got into Hanguk National University.
So, that seat is popular
among my classmates.
It's near the entrance,
so it's not that good. Try another seat.
Go look around.
It was 8:12 p.m.
That was when I paid with my card.
So?
That's when it would mark one month.
It hasn't passed yet.
You count the bookings by days,
but today's technically not over.
So it means that seat…
is still mine.
Since he's older and retaking the CSAT,
he can have the seat for just today.
I'll allow him that.
Excuse me?
Okay.
I'll talk to him.
Thank you.
I'll book Seat One for a month
starting tomorrow.
-My name is--
-I know.
Im A-sol, the high school senior.
Geez.
Number three is correct. Good job.
For this question, let's look here.
Here.
-This is for you.
-Thank you.
Can you give an extra lesson
this Saturday?
It's finals week. He's free all afternoon.
I can do it in the evening.
He goes to cram school in the evening.
Should I tutor him after that?
That might be too late.
Are you okay with that?
When do I sleep then?
-I'll get going.
-Thanks. Bye.
Tae-seo, how's 2:30 p.m. on Saturday?
Does that work?
Not really.
I may have to work on Saturday morning.
I'm really sorry.
I really need to take this job.
Yes?
I think I can do
an extra lesson on Saturday…
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
HUI-SEO
It was nothing. I can do it.
Thank you so much.
All right, then.
-Okay, good night.
-Good night.
Hey, Hui-seo. I was tutoring.
Tae-seo, you better do well
on your finals.
When you got a B on your midterms,
I was so worried
you'd lose your scholarship.
Okay.
I wasn't going to tell you this,
but Grandma's knees aren't looking good.
They said surgery would fix them,
but she just won't do it.
She has the money for it,
but she won't use it.
She said it's for your tuition
if you lose your scholarship.
So you better ace those exams.
Hey, Grandma is here. I'll call you back.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'll call you after finals are over.
Tae-seo.
Yes?
This question…
It's asking for the equation of a line
with a minimum slope.
You need to find the derivative of F
like I mentioned before.
Is there a place to see flowers near here?
My daughter loves flowers.
When you walk for five minutes
along the path near the beach,
there's a flowerbed.
-Really?
-Thank you.
-Do you like flowers?
-Yeah.
Here. It's for you.
-It's this way.
-Thank you.
It's a gift for you.
Thank you.
Tae-seo. See you at the lab
during vacation.
I'm done with finals. I'm leaving now.
Let's meet up. I'll come to your hotel.
I can see you for only a moment though.
I can't meet outsiders in my uniform.
At 2:30 p.m., I have 30 minutes,
so I'll get changed quickly.
I'm on my way.
There's something on my mind.
The answer is there,
but I have some doubt.
When I see you,
I'm sure it'll become clear.
Eun-a?
You should try this too.
They're making welcome cards
for the suites.
We're trying to come up
with new greetings.
Are drawings okay too?
What kind of drawings?
Something like this.
Give it a try.
If it gets selected, it'll be served
with the welcome food for a month.
Can I come back in 30 minutes?
Do you want me to wait for 30 minutes?
You drew that in a minute.
Why don't you do it now?
I need to be somewhere for a moment.
It's been a while.
It feels like it's been years.
I couldn't get changed. Sorry.
I'll be home during the break,
so let's see each other more often.
Ms. Mo Eun-a.
Excuse me. Where was the exit?
You can go around this way to exit.
Thank you.
Was he the guy?
Ms. Mo Eun-a, you can't go out in uniform…
Tae-seo!
I'm sorry!
You always have the right answer
because you don't jump to conclusions.
You don't do anything
just for the sake of it.
You came back exactly in 30 minutes.
Here. I liked your corn drawing.
I'll draw it now.
Your resume said you majored
in early childhood education.
I guess that's why
the way you treat people is different.
How should I say it?
You're filled with affection.
I am?
Thank you.
Sir.
I'm getting off.
Sir!
Aren't you getting off?
No, it's fine.
Get a job after graduating?
Honestly, studying for four years
has already been a luxury for me.
I see.
You want what you have to do,
not what you like to do.
That's strong. It resonates with me.
You sure you won't regret it?
I'm already sad.
I'm not the type to look back.
Can I wrap things up
and close the lab today?
JULY
Interns can move into the residence hall.
Why wait? I'm going to move in right away.
So you're going to live there then?
If you have a big bag like a suitcase,
could you lend it to me?
I've never traveled before.
I need to pack.
-You can use mine.
-Would that be okay?
So what will it be, Eun-a?
Want to borrow my suitcase?
Tell me
since you're the one who'll use it.
Could I borrow it?
Silver, black, white, or yellow?
Which one?
The biggest one.
The biggest one. Okay.
I would've prepared a better breakfast
if you had told me earlier.
I actually wanted pine nut porridge.
-What about your wedding?
-What wedding?
What? You made a big fuss about it.
We'll live together first.
She might run away.
If she does,
I should make it easy for her.
I don't understand grown-ups.
What? You don't like that I'm leaving?
When did you grow up so fast?
I've done nothing for you.
You gave me a lot of love.
Yes, I did that more than anyone.
You regained your health,
so I decided to go to college
in the summer of my senior year.
When college wasn't my thing,
I found another path.
It's all thanks to you.
I'll…
I'll be all right,
so go enjoy your life.
Live as if you're on a journey.
Just do all the things you want.
I'll do that.
You know I'll never waste
the time you've given me.
-Does it taste good?
-Dad, you're the best.
YEONWOO HIGH SCHOOL
YEON TAE-SEO
I didn't tell your dad about that boy.
You can tell him. He knows we're close.
Seong-chan told me
you're good at your work.
Don't ever leave Dad by himself.
Even if he's healthy now,
don't ever do it.
I'll stick close to him.
ROOM 407
JEONG JAE-WON
MO EUN-A
YEONWOO HIGH SCHOOL
YEON TAE-SEO
It's a job posting
for an overseas internship next year.
You'll have a good shot at it
once you build your career here.
Just study English in your spare time.
I hope this will help you
stand on your own.
CAFETERIA HOURS DURING SUMMER VACATION
I'll get home at 2:00 p.m.
When do you want to meet?
Grandpa, the light will work fine now.
Okay.
Grandma should see a doctor.
She won't.
There's no point in telling her.
I'll make an appointment.
You should take her.
Geez. I worry the roof will collapse
during the monsoon.
All the firewood will get wet.
I get paid monthly
for renting out the storage.
It's only a few tens of thousands of won,
but I have to make sure
this gets passed on to Hui-seo later.
I'll take that to mean
she'll go to the hospital.
YEONWOO WOODWORKING STUDIO
-Hello.
-Hey.
What brings you here, Tae-seo?
I'm on break, so I'm visiting.
Grandpa's worried
the wood will get wet during the monsoon.
He wants something to cover it.
That roof looks like it would leak,
but it never does.
But I'll get you something tomorrow
that will cover the whole thing.
Thank you.
I don't think it'll leak either.
But I guess he's so worried
he can't even sleep.
That's not it.
Anyway, you should hurry
and get your military service done.
That's all he talks about when he's drunk.
If something happens to them
when you're in the military,
he's so worried Hui-seo will be all alone.
You can enlist early these days.
Hurry and get it over with.
I'LL GET HOME AT 2:00 P.M.
WHEN DO YOU WANT TO MEET?
It's so hot.
Staying at the hotel would be better.
The schedule changes all the time.
We're always on standby.
Can you believe the AC's broken?
Aren't you hot, Eun-a?
Should I make the fan turn?
No, they'll fly away.
You're still working on the welcome cards?
I'm making them
with the writing and drawing this time.
The writing is the hard part.
I wasn't selected
when I only did the drawings.
I'll get it this time.
WELCOME TO OUR HOTEL
WHERE YOU CAN SEE THE OCEAN
ENJOY THE LAID-BACK VIBE
OF GANGWON AT OUR HOTEL
"Welcome…"
I'LL GET HOME AT 2:00 P.M.
WHEN DO YOU WANT TO MEET?
I'm home. When do you get off work?
I'm in the dorms.
I see.
You moved in.
I was going to tell you,
but I moved in
as soon as I became an intern,
so it was hectic.
Right.
Do you have time? I'll come over.
It's a quick bus ride.
If now isn't a good time,
I can see you in the evening.
Today, I…
Don't come, Tae-seo.
I mean today. Don't come today.
-I'll be there tomorrow.
-No, not tomorrow either.
When are you coming home?
I can't. Like I said, I live here now.
Tae-seo, the thing is…
I'm going back to Seoul
the day after tomorrow to tutor.
Let's try to work out our schedules again.
Don't.
Let's stop forcing our schedules to match.
This time is so precious to lose for me.
I want to make use of it all.
I've found something I want to do,
and it matters a lot to me.
I just need to do it.
I really want to excel at it.
You should stop wasting time
going back and forth.
Spend the time on yourself.
Let's not waste
a single moment of our time.
Well…
I mean…
I don't know what you're saying…
But why can I understand it?
Why do I get it all?
Okay.
Let's do that.
That's what we'll do.
This vegetable drawing is so cute.
Yes. The corn is so adorable.
Did you draw this, Eun-a?
Yes.
I think the writing fits
our hotel's image better too.
You like people, you're good at English,
and you draw vegetables well.
I know there's a job out there
you can give your all to.
It'll work out
in ways we never imagined.
We'll know for sure what that is
once we become adults.
You were right.
In ways we never imagined,
we…
DECEMBER
Goodness.
Is it because the weather's cold?
No one's picking up
because it's too early in the day.
What do we do?
We need help.
-It's okay. I can ride the bus.
-Aren't you going to be late?
And you need to shave your head
before going to boot camp.
-I'll make it if I go now.
-What?
-I'll get going. Don't come.
-Gosh. Oh, no.
Goodness.
-I'll go.
-You can't go like this.
Hey.
-Goodness, are you all right?
-Gosh.
-Gosh, dear!
-Tae-seo. What about him?
Go back. It's slippery.
Just go then.
Don't get hurt.
Don't you dare get hurt.
I'll get going.
I used to hate
thinking about the next step.
But I started to think about the future
because of what you would always say.
Where we'll be, what we'll do,
and with who…
It made me curious about my future.
About myself.
About what I wanted and what I could do.
The countless worries about the future
began with you.
And they ended
with the expressions on your face,
your responses, and your answers.
I realize that now.
Without you, I lose interest in myself.
I have no curiosity about myself.
That makes me scared and sad.
Where we'll be, what we'll do…
and with who…
SEPTEMBER, 10 YEARS LATER
The train will depart now.
The doors are closing.
Doors closed. Screen doors closed.
Train departing.
STILL SHINING
Subtitle translation by: Hye Won Yoon