( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
Exes hooking up is nothing new, right?
You wanna know?
Fine. I'll spell it out.
♪ What exactly is my status right now? ♪
♪ Am I still important to you somehow? ♪
♪ When people ask, it doesn't seem so ♪
♪ You just say, I'm just like your bro ♪
♪ The one who makes you smile ♪
♪ The one who makes your day worthwhile ♪
♪ The one who you're deeply attached ♪
♪ The one who always
Leaves you feeling matched ♪
♪ The one who makes your heart soar ♪
♪ The one who never
Refuses to take you everywhere ♪
♪ I want to give you
Another chance to answer ♪
♪ Just like brothers? Are we, dear? ♪
♪ Your answer is not what I want to hear ♪
♪ Brothers don't treat
each other this way ♪
♪ Brothers don't treat each other this way ♪
Jack
Let's go cheer for Dean up front.
Come on.
No.
I bet he loves it.
What?!
Being the center of attention.
Why are you so moody?
It's our seniors' farewell party.
Exactly. Keep the drama
off the menu tonight.
I plan on getting drunk.
Let's go now.
Come on, Jack.
Come!
No.
♪ Just like brothers? Are we, dear? ♪
♪ Your answer is not what I want to hear ♪
♪ Brothers don't treat
each other this way ♪
♪ Here's what I want to clearly say ♪
♪ What kind of brothers are we, anyway? ♪
Whiskey and soda.
Coming right up.
Whiskey and soda, please.
Hi, Jack.
Drunk already?
No. What about you?
No.
Just drinking for the vibes.
Just for the vibes?
Your face is already red.
Is it that obvious?
Mm.
You're right. It's hot too.
Feel it.
Yeah, it is hot.
Here you go, Jack.
Thank you.
I'll see you around.
Hey, Jack.
You've got my vote for
director of the faculty play.
You're competent.
It's a done deal for you.
Thanks a lot.
Bye now.
Here's your drink.
Thanks, bro, for inviting me to sing.
Well, you're the prince of Fine Arts.
Of course, you deserve the spotlight.
Prince? I've got no title.
Titles or not, the whole uni knows
Dean from Fine Arts is an icon.
Wanna grab a drink after?
Sand.
You done here?
Ready to leave?
I am.
Hey, Dean.
This is Ray, my boyfriend.
I watched you sing.
Nice voice, but…
your voices didn't really match.
Thank you.
Hope you still enjoyed it.
See you, Sand.
See you, Dean.
You didn't have to get jealous.
You were acting all flirty.
Don't overthink it.
He's just a friend.
Let's go.
I saw that.
Lucky you didn't get punched.
Singing and flirting with
someone else's man.
I wasn't flirting. Just teasing.
And if he actually went for it?
I wouldn't mind.
Evil!
So, how was my singing, Jack?
I didn't pay attention.
How could you not?
I saw you watching me.
I was enjoying the vibes.
Not enjoying you.
Something smells off here.
I think I'll take refuge.
I'm leaving too.
Hey.
You're leaving with me.
And wait until
you're done greeting everyone?
See you at home.
See you, Jack.
See you.
What?
Whoa, why so strong?
That's how I like it.
If you want something that matches your
taste,
go get your own.
Ever since we broke up,
nothing I do seems to please you.
Glad you know that.
FINE ARTS SENIORS' FAREWELL PARTY
Hey, Tua.
Arnold.
Leaving?
Mm. Just booked my ride.
I didn't want to wait for them.
Once they start
drinking, it goes till dawn.
That's true.
I'm leaving too.
If I stay, they'll keep
handing me drinks all night.
You're so drunk. Let me give you a ride.
Your house and my place
are in the same direction.
It's alright. I already booked my ride.
I don't want to trouble you.
Tua, don't say that.
We're friends.
You say that like I've never
given you a ride home.
Come on.
But… I already booked it.
Come on. Give it to me.
You can just cancel it.
Here. Catch.
If you feel bad, you can pay me the fare.
Let's go.
Ready?
Hello.
Are you home?
Can I come over?
(Are you drunk?)
Mm. A little.
I also miss you.
Let me come over.
(I can't tonight.)
(I'll hang up now.)
What the heck?
No one to unwind with?
What?
I heard you on the phone.
And how the hell is that your business?
You've finished already.
Is everyone from
the Acting major this feisty?
Got a problem?
If you're that horny, I can help.
You're fine with men too?
As long as they're cute.
You still got energy left?
Don't tell anyone about this.
I'm not the type…
to talk about my hookups.
You're my hookup. Not the other way around.
"Only Friends : Dream On"
(Episode 1: Game on)
Listen up, guys!
It's that time of year again.
Time to choose the director
for our faculty stage play.
If everyone's ready, let's vote.
Come on.
Help me pass them out. Hurry.
Jack.
Ninew.
RESULTS FOR
FACULTY STAGE PLAY DIRECTOR
JACK 36: NINEW 14
And the director of
this year's faculty stage play is…
Jack!
I'm making Romeo &amp; Romeo.
I will retell the conflict
between two feuding families,
with their children caught in the middle.
As for the ending…
They'll live happily together.
Great!
If they're in love, why
do they have to die?
Right? Right?
Exactly. Being torn
apart by death is so out.
Yep.
All right then.
I'll take the producer role.
I'll handle costumes.
I'll do sound.
Very nice.
If you want to take charge of anything,
contact Timmy.
As for the lead actors...
It has to be Dean, right?
Dean's the lead every single year.
No need to audition. Just come
here and play already. I'll watch.
I'm tired of seeing his face.
Everyone knows he's Jack's go-to actor.
That's true.
We're holding auditions.
There's more than
one good actor in this faculty.
Everyone has a chance to play Romeo.
That's fair, guys.
Only the capable deserve the role.
But don't forget, Jack.
I've played every show you directed.
One look into your eyes,
and I already know what you want.
He can't expect to get the role every year.
There are actors better than him.
There's no need for auditions.
Jack's Romeo belongs to me, no doubt.
Hey.
Tua!
When did you get here?
Just now. I didn't want to interrupt.
What brought you
all the way here to see me?
I came to pay the fare from last night.
Oh please, Tua.
How many times have I told you?
You don't have to.
Just don't forget to
return my helmet next time.
You don't even remember?
Do you realize what you did last night?
I didn't say anything weird, did I?
You did.
“Gosh, that asshole Dean
is unbearable when he's drunk.”
“I let him live at my place rent-free.”
“The only thing he has to
pay is utilities, but he never does.”
“He's lucky he's cute
and fun to be around.”
Enough. Stop performing.
Okay. I was wasted.
I didn't know you were such a nagger.
It's fine, though. It's cute.
Let me transfer the money. PromptPay?
Tua, don't do it.
I told you, it's fine.
No. I'm transferring it.
Don't!
It's done.
Hey, Tua!
That's too much.
It's back pay for the rides before.
I'm off.
Hey.
Tua's really sweet like this.
That's why he's the one
I'm closest to in the faculty.
Good thing I didn't let
anything slip about him.
I'm always like that when I'm drunk.
Did you review our last lesson, students?
All right. Let's move on to the next topic.
You enrolled in the same section as me.
Was I really that impressive?
Last night was amazing, wasn't it?
Will you stop talking? People can hear.
Sorry.
But last night was incredible.
I was drunk.
If I'd been sober,
I wouldn't have hooked up with you.
You two right there,
what are you talking about?
Uh… the seniors' farewell party
last night, ma'am.
Is that so?
Was the faculty event that fun?
Oh, it was totally fun.
It's unforgettable.
It was so-so.
Nothing special.
Oh, yeah?
You looked pretty into it.
It really wasn't that great.
It was a blast, Professor.
All right, all right.
We get it. It was fun.
But let's stop there.
Back to our lesson.
The next topic is…
I emailed you the casting script.
(I saw it.)
I'll leave it with you, Timmy.
Bye now.
This way, please, Mr. Golf.
Hello. Are you here for speed dating?
Yes.
Please write your name on this sticker tag.
Okay.
Each round lasts five minutes.
You'll hear a bell when time's up.
Sure.
All right, Mr. Jack. Please step inside.
Thank you.
Of course.
Hi.
You are…?
Jack.
I'm Ton.
What's your MBTI?
INFJ.
I'm ESTP.
We're complete opposites.
You're very good-looking.
You look like my next boyfriend.
Can I have your chat ID?
Sorry, my friend list is full.
Hello.
Hello, Jack.
I'm Dean.
I just broke up with my boyfriend.
So now I'm single.
Well?
Already looking for a new boyfriend?
My ex was a piece of shit.
I'm looking for an upgrade.
Is that so?
But I don't think you like anyone here yet.
Just admit it, Jack.
I'm the most compatible with you.
There's no point in holding auditions.
The Romeo role is mine. No question.
How would you know…
when I'm the one choosing?
And now I'm choosing
new things for my life.
Why?
Because you were jealous
of Sand and me at the party?
You want my full attention all to yourself?
You just…
think too highly of yourself, as always.
If that's what you think, fine.
I hope you find someone better than me.
As your boyfriend…
and as your actor.
Maybe your era is over, Dean.
Well…
We'll see about that, Jack.
It's our faculty stage play.
Are you interested?
Come to the casting.
It's the play audition. Are you in?
Are you auditioning?
Mm. I think I'll give it a try.
What about you?
I'll stay an accountant. Like always.
What role are you auditioning for?
A supporting role?
I'm going for the lead.
Romeo.
Whoa! Raffy!
What's the point?
Jack will always choose Dean.
Maybe not this time.
They broke up. That means I have a shot.
My moment's here. How could I not take it?
I love you, Romeo.
And I will not let you go.
Even if our families are at war,
it doesn't mean we can't love each other.
Hatred can't defy our love, Romeo.
Thank you. Thank you.
Please wait for the results.
Please.
Jack, that's ten people already.
No one's caught your heart?
We've been at this all day.
Right.
They're just not right yet.
Not right?
Then stop being stubborn.
Choose Dean and get it over with.
Exactly.
Or if you don't want to sign him up,
Timmy can do it for you.
Hey.
I'm auditioning for Romeo.
Hi, I'm Dean Dechakorn Prempreeda.
Height: 176 centimeters. Weight: 67 kilos.
I'm auditioning for the role of Romeo.
Should I begin?
Or would you like to
know my background first?
Though I doubt that's necessary.
The director knows me down to every pore.
Hey.
Can I join the audition
too? Am I still in time?
Sorry, I took a while to prepare.
What role are you auditioning for, Raffy?
Romeo.
If loving you means
I have to sacrifice and walk away
to make someone else happy,
then that isn't true love.
Because true love…
means burning together.
If you already know how it ends,
why choose the same path again?
You can choose something new.
And you won't regret it.
We built everything together.
Our lives. Our memories.
You can't turn back
and walk away from me, Romeo.
You can live without the others,
but not without me.
I'm not asking you to choose right now.
I just want you to know
I'm ready to stand by your side.
- Just choose me, Romeo.
So what's up, Jack?
You look stressed.
Can't decide between Dean and Raffy?
I'd be stressed too.
Jack, if you can't
choose, let them both play.
You need two Romeos anyway.
I can't.
Dean and Raffy have the same character.
Between the two, I can choose only one.
What about the other Romeo?
Didn't anyone from casting click for you?
Not yet.
Gosh.
Can you at least make our jobs easier?
Hey, boys.
This one's on the house.
I'm giving you the whole bottle
since you look so grumpy.
Didn't your boyfriend come too?
Who's my boyfriend?
Dean—duh!
Come on, Pink.
Dean's his ex.
They broke up, sis.
Seriously? I didn't know.
I didn't get the update.
I still see you hanging out together.
How nice.
Breaking up but staying
in the same friend group.
I really can't keep up
with Gen Z relationships.
Bye now.
That's because you're old, sis.
Damn you!
If you want people to stop talking
about Dean, you've got two options.
One, stop being friends with him.
Two, get a new boyfriend.
You're exactly right.
But if we're still sitting here,
no one's going to hit on you.
Let's go, Tua.
Give Jack some space.
Come.
Do I have to?
Come with me.
You don't want to be the third wheel.
Hi, Jack.
Why are you sitting all alone?
I don't know where Timmy and Tua went.
What about you? Did you come alone?
I'm meeting Pete, but he's not here yet.
Mind if I sit with you for now?
Sure.
And don't ask about the casting.
I haven't decided yet.
How was it, though? Was I okay?
I'm not very confident.
Hey, your acting has improved a lot.
I liked it.
Can you say that again? Let me record it.
It's not every day
I get a compliment from you.
You're exaggerating.
Hey.
I wasn't sure if you liked it.
I really want to work
with someone as capable as you.
I want to be your muse.
Don't you have friends?
Is that why you're here?
I was waiting for my friend.
Jack was alone too.
Hey, we never got to act together.
I want to play with you, but it's a shame
we auditioned for the same role.
Maybe we will.
I'll be the main character,
and you'll be ensemble, like always.
Dean!
That's fine.
You're actually my idol.
I want to be like you.
Whatever you had before, I want that too.
I think I should go.
I'll see you later, Jack.
I admire his effort.
He's been after you since freshman year.
You rejected him and chose me instead.
And he's still chasing
you in our fourth year.
Mm. But maybe it's not too late.
Are you giving him the lead role?
Maybe.
The audience might
want to see something new.
The old thing is predictable.
Boring.
Hey, we meet again.
Did you follow me?
Seriously, are you hitting on me?
If you are, don't.
It's a waste of time.
Cocky much? I'm a DJ here.
Then don't say hi next time.
I don't make friends with one-night stands.
Was I that bad
you don't want anyone to know?
I think I did pretty well.
How did you sound that night again?
Don't try.
I have high standards.
You don't meet them.
Are you sure they are high?
We talked for less than
five minutes and you already gave in.
You know what,
you don't have to play hard to get.
It doesn't make you more valuable.
Don't flatter yourself.
You were just in the right place
at the right time…
and right for my mood.
Whoo!
Tua, what's the casting result?
Did Jack choose me?
You don't have it easy this time.
We have to admit Raffy's improved a lot.
Raffy? Please.
I can control my tears.
Want them from the left eye or the right?
Inner corner or outer
corner? I can do it all.
I know.
No one's questioning your talent, Dean.
But Jack might be worried you'll
mess up his play again like last year.
You overslept and didn't make it on time.
Fine.
And another concern right now
is the other Romeo.
No one seems to be
catching Jack's attention.
Hey.
Arnold works here too?
Yeah. Pink just recruited him.
Whoever ends up as
his partner is going to be lucky.
He's hot and hardworking.
He's versatile.
Don't you think?
I don't know.
Come on, Tua. If you like him, go for it.
Can't you see how many people
are making eyes at him?
Someone else might grab him first.
Oh, hey, Tua.
You're here too?
I came with Dean and Jack.
Are you drunk?
Drunk? Come on.
Good then.
Don't get drunk too fast.
I can't give you a ride home.
Still on the clock.
Oh, hey, are you interested in
joining our faculty play?
Me?
Come on, I can't act.
Dancing, that I can work with.
I actually think you'd be perfect.
You've got the right look, Arnold.
You look like someone Jack would want.
Um… I don't think so.
If I spend time rehearsing,
I'll lose out on work and money.
I think it doesn't hurt to try.
If you get the role, you'll get paid too.
I will?
It's around 20,000.
Hmm. Let me sleep on it.
Thanks for asking anyway.
Here, a freebie for you.
Don't tell Pink.
And don't get drunk too fast.
Yeah.
Thank you, man.
I came prepared.
I mean… financially.
Whoo!
Cheers!
I'm stepping out for a cigarette.
Hey, your glass is still full.
Where are you going?
Watch the booth for me.
Hey, Jack.
Are you drunk yet?
Not yet.
So...
You hardly ever come home.
I've been busy.
Working on the play.
Mom keeps asking about you.
Is this your new boyfriend?
What a hotshot you are.
Boyfriend, my ass.
He's my friend.
Hey! Just a friend?
I thought you were
already seeing someone new.
What the hell are you talking about?
Are they siblings?
No one in the faculty knows.
Most people don't know we're related.
It's not like I'm eager
to call him my big bro.
Excuse me. Can I borrow your lighter?
I didn't bring one.
Are those glasses for poor eyesight?
How short-sighted are you?
Three hundred.
Can you see clearly without them?
I mean, how close would I have to be
for you to see me clearly?
Whoo!
Why didn't you tell me
you're Jack's brother?
What?
I asked why you didn't tell me
you're Jack's brother.
The exact reason you're thinking.
Why?
Do you like him?
Oh.
Are you scared that if Jack
finds out we hooked up, he won't want you?
Do not tell him.
Who knows?
I might let it slip when I'm drunk.
Asshole. I said don't tell him.
What do I get in return?
Are you blackmailing me?
Shit! Shit! I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Just leave.
What's going on here?
You're killing the vibe for my customers.
Fix it now.
I'll handle the problem.
Then handle it.
Give us a second, guys.
Boo!
Hang tight. The music's coming back.
It's done, sis.
Okay, let's get back to the fun.
How should I make it up?
Don't worry.
You will surely get your chance.
Keep walking.
Hey, Timmy, don't puke.
Of course I won't. Don't you worry.
Hey, where are Jack and Dean?
Worry about yourself, Timmy.
Jack bailed and went home.
Dean left with someone.
Hey, hey.
Hey, Tua.
Timmy, wow.
You're done?
Here, let me help.
Gosh. He's out of it.
How are you two getting home?
I'll book a ride and send him home first.
You're such a good friend, Tua.
Here, I'll give you a hand.
Timmy.
When did you get taller?
Tua, about the play you mentioned earlier…
I'm in.
I don't know if I'll get the part, though.
You will.
I believe you will.
I'll try.
Come on. Let's get Timmy home.
Thanks a lot.
It's my job to take care of customers.
Hey, I'm fine.
How did you get in?
You're still using
my birthday as your passcode.
Sorry for cockblocking.
But for my replacement,
this is the best you could find?
Are you drunk?
If you are, go home.
Why are you even here?
Why can't I?
I used to live here.
This bed…
we used to have sex all the time.
Well?
Did you miss me so much
you had to find my replacement?
I don't know what your deal is,
but I'm stepping out of this.
What do you want?
Say it and leave.
Why are you so mean to me?
It's two in the morning.
Can't I crash here?
No.
Why don't you sleep with
the guy you were flirting with at the bar?
I was flirting just for fun.
But tonight… I'd rather be with you.
Do you want the role so bad
you're willing to trade your body?
Huh?
Mm.
I want the role.
And I want you too.
You know I deserve that role
without even auditioning.
Your method won't work.
We won't know
unless we try. Right?
Can I audition again?
I'll prove to you
who's the most suitable for the role.
Just exes hooking up.
Whatever floats your boat.
(Next Episode)
And the roles of Romeo go to…
Nice work.
Sneaking your crush into the project.
If you like him that much, try kissing him.
Why don't you try that kiss with me?
I don't mind if you move
on with someone else…
as long as it's not Raffy.
Scared of losing?
How about this, Rome?
I'll serve him up for you.
Whether you take him or not is your call.