(Lee Je Hoon)
(Jang Hyuk Jin, Bae Yoo Ram, Kim Eui Sung, Pyo Ye Jin)
(Taxi Driver 3)
(This drama is a work of fiction)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(Children and animals were filmed under guidelines.)
(Episode 13)
What's wrong? Did you forget something?
I was sure I packed my tools,
but I can't find where I put them.
- This? - Here it is.
Wook.
If you're nervous, you can still head back.
Sorry?
It's okay if you do.
No one's going to give you a hard time.
It's okay.
Just take the boat back when it leaves.
I'll call you when I'm done with the story.
The reporting will be over in a flash.
I'm coming with you!
Sir.
200-ri northwest of Paju City. Samheung Island, with seed money.
(Motel, Gukbap Restaurant)
(Samheung Gukbap)
Here to eat?
You haven't even eaten,
and you're trying to pay first?
General Manager Lee Gi Hyeon sent me, ma'am.
I was told that with the seed money, you'd take care of everything.
I'm just trying to make something...
of my life.
To finally make one big score.
This is a gukbap restaurant.
No, it's not.
- Kim Woo Jong. - Sergeant Kim Woo Jong.
Just got discharged, didn't you?
I need to start my own business.
I spent my military savings on it. I even gave up the PX food.
Real impressive, kid.
A kid like you should be trying to earn money the hard way.
What was that? "One big score?"
Try that, and you'll get knocked out in one shot, you little jerk.
You want me to bust you up?
This punk.
200-ri northwest of Paju City. Samheung Island, with seed money.
But I know I'm in the right place.
This is weird.
You really don't know General Manager Lee Gi Hyeon?
How would I know a Lee Gi Hyeon, punk?
- Why'd you hit me? - Because you know him, I have to?
No, I mean...
Can a cop do that?
General Manager Lee Gi Hyeon.
We set him up on a Cambodian farm three and a half years ago.
He ran a database phishing scam, but got busted the year before last.
He's currently doing time in a prison in Korea.
Kim Woo Jong?
Yes, that kid worked for me for about a year and a half.
He actually came for a visit last week.
He said he wants to get into this line of work for real...
and asked for an introduction.
An introduction?
You guys always said you welcome referrals.
Hello?
Counselor. It came in very handy.
I'll give Officer Kim a heads-up.
(Samheung Gukbap)
It's a big world, and there's plenty of work to do.
And a young punk like you...
should be trying to get a proper job.
The little brat.
Have you eaten?
I'm asking if you've had a meal.
- Are you addressing me, sir? - Yes, you, punk.
He's offering to buy you food. Go get a free meal, punk.
Why don't you come get a bite to eat with me,
Kim Woo Jong?
Is there anything you don't eat?
No, sir.
You did great.
Let's go say hello together.
Okay.
Gosh, I am so sorry about this.
We should have just played along and let you fool us,
but I guess we figured it out.
I heard you're all investigative journalists.
So, since you're reporters, I'm curious about something.
You answer too, Kim Woo Jong.
Do you think...
the truth...
is worth dying for?
No.
That's what I thought.
Right.
(Police Station)
Gukbap.
Do you like it?
Yes, I do!
Let's go, then.
Understood.
(Taxi Driver 3)
The fish truck and the photographer are heading for the mainland.
Go Eun.
Got it. We'll tail them once they get to the mainland.
What? A police car too.
That means the temple will be empty.
Do Gi, shouldn't you go now to check...
for that ledger you mentioned?
I guess that means you'll have to go fishing by yourself, Mr. Jang.
All right, everyone, let's get moving.
- Yes! - Yes!
Of all the items going abroad, the top seven,
ship them out by the end of today. They said it's urgent.
Yes, understood.
Writer Go.
Did you take a lot of photos?
So, was your business trip successful?
Of course. It was a brilliant script.
By the way, what brings you to the mainland?
- To work on the "Ping" script. - I'm excited for this one too.
(Ping: Smishing, Voice Phishing)
By the way, I heard you had a visitor at the temple.
Did you happen to meet them, Writer Go?
He said he came to fish...
in a taxi.
You should meet him too, Monk.
I think I will.
Are you out of talismans?
When you're finished, come on up. I'll write you some more.
Yes, Monk.
Here, these are kimchi dumplings.
Officer Kim.
- Yes. - Go help him with the fishing.
Fishing?
Coming all this way in a taxi to fish.
What a life.
What was that?
Did it just take the bait and run off again?
I don't see your friend.
You still haven't caught a single fish today, I see.
Want me to show you a good spot?
I think I'll just try my luck here a bit longer.
You won't catch anything here, you know?
Get in. If the fish aren't biting here,
what's the point of waiting around all day?
Hop in. I'll take you to a spot where you'll catch a ton.
I'm okay, really.
Sir,
I thought you came here to fish.
You're right, I am here to fish.
Just give me a second. I'll pack up and come with you.
We just have to go a little further, and the fish are biting like crazy.
(Deluxe Taxi)
This is delicious. It's great for a quick bite.
Gyeong Gu, he's coming.
I'll tail the fish truck.
- Let's get going. - Yes.
I'll tail him.
Okay.
(Alcohol Addiction Rehabilitation Center)
Thank you for having the courage to share.
Okay, now who would like to share something with us?
- Have a seat. You're not late. - Okay.
Please make yourself comfortable.
All right. Who would like to be brave and share next?
Please go ahead.
Yesterday,
I got a final notice in the mail for a DUI fine.
My wife saw it and broke down, asking if I had been drinking again.
And I kept insisting that I hadn't.
- We cleared up the confusion, - Alcohol Addiction...
- I renewed my vow. - Rehabilitation Center?
- To quit for good. - Wonderful. Let's all applaud.
Okay. So, after that wonderful share...
How about the gentleman who came in earlier?
Sir? Would you like to share?
(Group Counseling for Alcohol Addiction Recovery)
The thing is, I'm working on a script for a show.
But...
I have the idea, but I wasn't sure how to write it in a compelling way.
I just couldn't get a feel for it at all.
But after hearing your real-life stories,
I feel like, "This is how to write. This is how to make it compelling."
It's like my writer's block has been completely cleared.
So you're a writer!
I'm sure you'll hear a lot of useful stories today.
- Yes, thank you. - What is he talking about?
Let's give our writer a round of applause.
(West Sea Breeze Live Fish Center)
(Honest Sales Guaranteed)
(Employee Manual)
You.
(Halibut: 25 dollars)
(Sea Bream: 30 dollars)
(Employee Manual)
This box came by courier. I think it's yours.
So they make it on the island and ship it all from here.
You.
You, and you.
These are your plane tickets.
The seven of you, head to the airport immediately.
(Kim Woo Jong, Kang Dong Su)
(Ping: Smishing, Voice Phishing)
(Site: Illegal Gambling Sites)
So this is their accounting information.
(Inmates Nearing Release, Former Inmates)
A day when the wind is still, yet the leaves tremble.
So, the taxi is here.
(Alumni Association of Auditors, Judicial Research and Training Inst)
(No parking, tow-away zone)
I'd like to report an illegally parked car.
It's 3402.
- I have to go again? - Yes, your turn.
I need to use the restroom.
Gosh.
Darn it.
I really need to quit smoking. This is...
What's this little rat doing here?
What are you doing there?
It's been about three weeks since I got clean,
but the cravings are really bad today.
But coming here and listening to all of you,
I think I can find my resolve again.
What is this?
Hi, there. What did you use?
I was huffing butane.
Okay, got it all.
(Together Drug Rehab Center "Stopping Together" Session 32)
(Lecture hall, Ignorance is Bliss)
Oh, gosh.
- Where's the restroom? - Excuse me.
Nice to meet you. I'm Go Seong Hyeok.
Right.
So, what brings you here?
This is a drug rehab meeting, right?
Exactly.
You don't have the eyes of a user.
And no track marks either.
(No parking, tow-away zone)
No...
(Towing notice)
Taxi!
We finally meet.
This isn't what one would normally call "meeting."
So much as "getting caught."
I'm here to hang a lantern.
A lantern?
I was curious to see what kind of lantern my capital could get me.
Officer Kim.
I'll be more careful next time.
(Impound lot)
(Samheung Gukbap)
The lists from the drug rehab and alcohol addiction groups,
and the data from the impound lot all came through safely.
Okay.
For the drug rehab list, we'll use a survey for a gift certificate.
For the alcoholics, we'll use a one-year-old DUI fine notice.
If we program it to send out texts,
we should get a bite from over 80 percent of them, right?
But I thought you said you were just going to the tow yard.
An idea just popped into my head.
I'll process it and distribute it as a premium database right away.
Okay.
Hello.
He doesn't look like a cop.
(Vehicle pickup)
Wait!
Gosh. Darn it.
Seriously, why won't he answer his phone?
Yes?
What do you mean he's not answering?
Got it. I'll try calling him.
Why isn't he picking up...
I couldn't reach you, so I followed Writer Go to the island.
Call me when you get this.
Gosh, why can't I get a hold of anyone?
(Samheung Island)
I'll go meet the last person myself, so you just wait here.
So if you say you want to hang a lantern here,
this is what happens?
Trespassing on private property, and twice at that.
So you work for a taxi company?
Come on, there must be tons of temples where you can do that.
My gosh.
All I want is to hang a lantern for my wish.
I didn't realize it'd require a whole investigation.
Hey.
Let me just ask you straight up.
Why are you really here?
I told you I came to hang a lantern.
Is this about money? Is that it?
Hey, monk. Just tell me how much.
Aren't they in there?
Hey, just because I'm wearing this uniform in a place like this,
- do I look that friendly to you? - Aren't police officers supposed...
to be a helping hand for the citizens?
Gosh, this little punk...
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
I'm really bad at this. I don't want to do it.
Go Eun.
Go Eun?
Can you hear me?
If you're trying to call your friends,
they won't pick up.
Driver.
If you haven't eaten yet, join me for gukbap.
Go on, eat.
Meat at a temple? That's new.
What did you mean when you said I couldn't reach my friends?
I was just telling it like it is.
Oh, right.
And they might not be reachable from now on either.
After you finish this gukbap we'll bring your friends here,
or we'll take you to them.
So eat up.
But I already finished my military service, so why...
I don't want to.
I won't go.
Gosh, I hate this.
I was wrong.
I'll be better from now on.
Goodness.
There's something I'm curious about.
I'd like our driver... Or rather, Kim Do Gi, to answer it.
The CEO of a taxi company said he came to this island for fishing,
and two of his employees tailed me to the mainland.
While the company's accountant was tailing our Choi.
Don't you have some explaining to do?
Explain? What's to explain?
I'm the one who ordered it.
Gosh, you gotta be in sync to get anything done.
The fools went and got caught.
I hear you told the monk you wanted to hang a lantern?
Do you even know what that means?
Making a wish come true,
I don't mean that.
Woo Jong told me about it.
He said with some seed money, it's a sure way to make a killing.
Woo Jong.
- You mean that Kim Woo Jong? - Yes, but the jerk...
only gave me half the story before he disappeared on me.
So I had no way of knowing who the "professional" was.
What did you do for a living before this?
You mean, before I was a taxi driver?
Yes.
It's a real tearjerker.
Right. I'll do my best to hold it together.
Man, where do I even begin?
At first,
I really did try to live an honest life.
Really?
I used to teach high school math.
It's nice to meet you all.
I swore I'd devote my life to those kids, but...
No, his entire group was captured!
Seung Tae, we got busted for pot!
Those darn kids and their pot!
Oh, right.
The students were out of control, so I quit.
A school teacher? I wouldn't have guessed.
I figured a desk job was better, so I joined a web storage company.
But then the CEO suddenly exploded.
- I didn't last long there either. - Oh, no.
That's when I started to think,
"Maybe I'm just not cut out for a regular 9-to-5."
So, I...
switched to a totally different line of work.
What kind of work?
Importing burner phones from overseas...
and supplying them to people in Korea.
So you were a burner phone broker?
The money was good,
but then I ran into a prosecutor.
So that venture didn't last long either.
Long time no see.
Remember the one in Gunsan?
The one who did phishing from a Chinese restaurant?
You mean Rim Bok Ja.
You don't have to trust me. Just have some of this snow crab.
Okay, thanks.
Anyway, after that,
I thought my bad luck must be from some kind of curse,
so I actually became a shaman.
Did that help at all?
Turns out my spiritual mojo ran out, so that was a bust.
Besides all that,
I also worked as a bouncer at a club for a bit...
Since we're being honest...
I even did a short stint in jail.
Gosh, so embarrassing.
Let me get this straight.
You were a teacher, but you quit...
because your students shook you down.
You sold fermented seafood, and then you got a job at a company,
but you quit because the boss made you kill a chicken.
He blew up! The boss blew up!
You started dealing burner phones, but ran when a DA was after you.
You became a shaman, but you quit because you had no powers.
Hey, I almost cut my foot off dancing on those blades.
You worked as a bouncer at a club, but then the cops raided the place.
Yes, apparently it was a drug den or something.
And so now,
you've learned to drive,
and you're a taxi driver.
Is this...
really one person's life? It's like a con artist's resume.
I told you it was a tearjerker, didn't I?
(Temp. Teacher: Confirmed, U-Data: Confirmed)
(Gunsan Burner Phones: Confirmed, Prison Incarceration: Confirmed)
How interesting.
Thinking back,
my life really has been a roller coaster.
Mr. Kim Do Gi,
there's just one thing that you're missing.
(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
Something I'm missing?
Your single biggest shortcoming...
is your lack of an owner's mindset. A sense of ownership, you get it?
You never tried to take charge yourself.
You were always trying to work under someone else.
That's been your biggest downfall.
What a shame.
If only you hadn't done that, by now,
your life could've been different. What a shame.
So that I can finally take charge,
I'll accept your help.
Sure, let's do that.
Let's put our heads together...
and really think this through.
And as for the people you came with,
I'll have them escorted to the place where you're staying, Kim Do Gi,
so they can be comfortable while they're here.
Is everyone okay?
Driver Kim.
- Is anyone hurt? - Yes, we're fine.
Other than nearly dying.
I woke up, my hands and feet tied, and stuffed inside a bag.
Then I felt a prick in my thigh and passed out again.
- They were dumping us at sea. - Really?
Next thing I knew, I was here.
If they'd dumped us in the sea back then,
the current would have probably carried us north.
So our bodies would be in North Korea. But why?
To prevent an investigation.
Right. If our bodies were up North, the authorities couldn't reach them.
Gosh, Jin Eon, you've gotten so much smarter.
I didn't say anything, though.
What? You just made that sharp point...
- about blocking the investigation. - I did?
If it wasn't you, then who was it? It's not like there's a crowd here.
That was me.
Come on.
Sorry for startling you.
You can just call me Reporter Bong.
Okay. In here... Goodness.
You can relax. There's no CCTV here.
Everywhere else, they can see and hear everything.
Wait, how long have you been here?
Let's see. About six months, I think?
That's insane.
Excuse me, can I take a look at the camcorder?
Sure.
Anyone who comes here ends up one of two ways.
They either become one of their affiliates...
or they end up on one of those wooden boats.
You're the second ones to have survived this.
And the first?
Me.
Thanks to this that my senior gave me,
I'm the only one who barely made it out alive.
Here.
My senior used to say...
compared to other types of crimes,
it's odd how the recidivism rate for online crimes is so high.
So for a long time, we investigated cybercriminals...
who were being released from prison.
They all came to this island...
and quickly left for other countries and started up again.
After some digging,
we also discovered there was someone on this island helping them.
So my senior and I...
So you posed as buyers to get in.
Yes.
These guys...
control a global network of criminal affiliates.
But they've never once been targeted in an investigation.
Because they understand the ins and outs...
of a criminal investigation better than anyone.
I found this at the temple.
(Alumni Association of Auditors, Judicial Research and Training Inst)
Wait, you mean one of them...
is a former prosecutor?
They know the limits of the law, so they designed this enterprise...
to operate just outside of them.
A former prosecutor...
Now it all makes sense.
As soon as we started our investigation,
we were raided and audited, and my boss was arrested.
That's why my senior...
told me to turn back right before he came here.
- Goodness. - Goodness.
I'm all right.
Please help me.
I don't know exactly what you do,
but you're all here for your reasons, aren't you?
For the sake of my senior,
Shin Kyung Soo, who was unjustly killed,
I want to do something. Anything.
Please, I'm begging you. Help me.
Cheol Yong, you have...
been through a lot.
Not at all, Monk.
He served his time as a model prisoner,
and he finally got paroled.
Who? Yong Ho?
(Jo Yong Ho)
Yes, Jo Yong Ho.
Right.
- Sorry I'm late. - Find your enlightenment.
Writer Go, you made it.
Writer Go.
It looks like a lot of our veterans will be getting out next year,
so I think we could add about two more franchises.
So you're telling me to work harder?
We'll have to raise the commission for our contacts in Public Security.
Okay, got it. I'll get right on it.
And what about those people from the taxi company?
Are we taking them on or not?
No, I've got a bad feeling about them.
Why don't we just...
get rid of all of them?
- All of them? - Especially that driver.
He seems like the type who'd smile...
while dragging someone out...
and burying them alive.
And the older guy.
He acts all nice, but I can tell one day,
he'll betray us. It's written all over his face.
Their background checks came back clean.
I'm telling you, my gut says something's off.
I really wish we'd just get rid of them.
Writer Go, what's your take?
Well...
I wish our dear Monk...
- would be more considerate. - Me?
I always listen to you, Writer Go. What are you talking about?
She just told you.
We need to add...
two more franchises.
Sorry.
Here. On my way over,
I heard this was new, so I picked some up.
You're always so thoughtful, Writer Go.
No, this is for you to share with that taxi driver...
when you meet him tomorrow. Okay?
Be sure to bring up the money first. Got it?
Okay.
When you're feeling tired,
there's nothing quite like it.
My apologies for my lack of enlightenment.
If you had just told me the truth,
I wouldn't have been so rude.
You know what they say, adversity strengthens the bond.
Through all the back-and-forth suspicion,
isn't that how friendships are forged?
That's right.
After all, being suspicious of someone...
just means you're interested in them.
- This is quite good. - Is it?
Anyway,
to get this business off the ground, we'll need some capital.
Do you happen to have any money set aside?
- Two million dollars. - Two and a half million?
No, two million dollars.
I guess I heard what I wanted to hear.
Two million is a lot of money. How did you manage to get it,
- if you don't mind me asking? - I didn't save it myself.
- I managed to hook an investor. - An investor?
The president of the taxi company I came with.
He took out a two-million-dollar loan...
using the taxi company as collateral.
I told him rather than letting the company keep losing money,
we'd get a loan for a big score. He jumped at the chance.
You're a master at reeling them in.
So what about the others?
You know them.
The accountant and mechanics from the company.
We're going to need a few people for this to work anyway,
- so I persuaded a few to join. - Excellent.
In that case,
show me the money.
If we're going to talk business,
I don't need to hear it.
I need to see the money for myself.
What? Are you kidding me?
Hey, Monk.
When buying a house, do you show the money before you even see it?
Come on, that's just how it works.
You see the goods, hear the pitch, and then you pay.
But asking me to cough up the money before we even start,
I just don't think that's right, Monk.
Am I wrong?
My goodness. This is...
If you want to get into this line of work,
listen to me very carefully.
You must put the money down first. Otherwise,
we can't even begin to talk.
You must take me for a pushover.
But you've got the wrong guy.
I'm just going to go take a call.
You can either do things my way, or...
We'll just forget the whole thing. Let's just call it off.
This tea is leaving a bitter taste in my mouth.
It's always the thirsty one...
who seeks out the well.
Honey!
Everything okay in there?
- What? - We're still talking.
I just stepped out for some air.
- Did you bring our seed money? - No, not yet.
Why not, honey? Should I go get it?
So these jerks didn't even bring the money.
Of course not. We show them money, and they could just grab it and run.
How can I trust these guys enough to show them the money?
Absolutely not.
You're right.
All right, I'll be waiting then. Just let me know when you need it.
Okay. I'll call you back then.
- You get some rest, okay? - Okay.
I love you, babe.
I love you more.
Hey, you. Come with me for a second.
Some important guests are arriving at the pier.
Are you asking me to give them a ride?
Why?
You're a good driver.
We'll talk on the way.
All right.
There it is! Over there!
See? What'd I tell you? I said this was the right way.
Go Eun, the CCTV!
Why? Are you going that way?
My laptop.
Chief Park. Didn't you grab my main computer?
Me?
- Sorry. - No!
I should've put it on the bike myself.
The tow yard texted about an error. It says I'm due for a refund.
- Sweet! I'm applying right now. - Don't!
Why'd you hit me?
Why would you just click on it without knowing what it is?
Let me see.
(Automatic virus scan in progress)
- It's a phishing scheme. - What?
Click that, and they would've stolen all your info and passwords.
You fell for this before. How could you be so careless again?
I got a text from a drug rehab center too.
- I almost fell for it too. - Writer Go, what is that jerk?
This island.
I've liked it ever since I first came here.
The island's the perfect size.
Anything you don't want people to see...
It's a good place to just set it adrift in the ocean.
We have some clients coming to the island today.
Some have been renewing with me for years.
And some new ones are joining.
Like you, Kim Do Gi.
(Deluxe Taxi)
So, you want me at the business presentation with those people?
I just thought you could all meet and break the ice.
The security here seems a little lax.
How so?
What about it seems sloppy?
If you do things that way,
the second someone in the know here opens their mouth,
won't this entire operation be at risk?
Not at all.
Reporting to the police or tipping them off...
Ultimately, people only act out of self-interest.
Sure, ordinary people have things like altruism or a sense of justice.
They might have things like that,
but as you know, our clients...
are not that kind of breed.
This Samheung Island...
is their only hope. They know better than anyone.
Hope?
For clients who rejoin us after being released from prison,
we offer a 50-percent discount on their startup costs.
If we wholeheartedly help them get back on their feet,
they're bound to come back here.
The clients we've had so far...
refer other clients to us, if anything.
But not one has ever reported us.
They know what they stand to lose.
So even if they're caught by the police,
in order to make a comeback later,
you'd have to protect them at all costs.
And they'll scrape together seed money any way they can.
It's much more effective than killing people...
to ensure their silence.
Does that clear everything up for you?
Yes.
Thanks to you, everything is crystal clear now.
Good. That's great.
All right, then,
how about you clear some things up for me?
We did a little digging into the places...
you said you worked.
And we found...
a very interesting common denominator.
Why is it that wherever you've been, Kim Do Gi,
everyone has either died or disappeared?
How come you're the only one who made it out alive?
Care to answer that question for me?
Or...
is it a question you can't answer?
What's that supposed to mean?
The way you're talking,
it sounds like you're disappointed I didn't die too.
So how do you think that makes me feel?
When you get down to it, the people here are survivors,
and that's why you give them a fresh start, isn't it?
I didn't die either.
I held on and barely made it out alive.
I came here hoping to turn my life around,
and this is the kind of nonsense I get?
Gosh, I guess...
I guess...
that's how it could've come across.
No, I mean, if that's how it came across...
My apologies.
Look.
I decided to take a chance on you. Kim Do Gi.
I've decided to trust you.
When I counsel the others later,
why don't you sit in and listen?
Now we're talking.
Gosh, long time no see, Writer Go.
Look at you, coming all this way to greet me.
- Congrats on getting out. - "Congrats"? Give me a break.
I took the fall because I didn't listen to you.
I mentioned them on the phone, yes? These are my buddies from inside.
Man, this weather is amazing.
Forget the weather and show some respect. Got it?
Welcome.
They look a lot younger in person.
Everyone's running their scams online these days.
It's a great time for young guys to make a quick buck.
They're Paju funeral home scammers. They're pretty good.
I see.
By the way, who's that?
He's a new recruit, joining us as well.
Do you know him, by any chance?
His name is Kim Do Gi.
Kim Woo Jong, who used to work for you, sent him.
Woo Jong?
Woo Jong didn't really have any friends.
He's not good with people, either.
Woo Jong never mentioned anyone like you to me.
Funny, he mentioned you to me.
I went to visit him the other day.
He said you're still a total pain.
Darn.
All right, that's enough.
Let's talk business inside. This way.
Yes, let's. Hey, let's go!
Writer Go! What?
What?
Writer Go!
(We would like to thank Kim Sung Kyu and Lee Kyoung Young.)
(Taxi Driver 3)
Doesn't this sound like some kind of business briefing?
Time to decide what kind of business you're all going to start.
How long have we been on this island?
Pack light for the move.
There's no other way. All we can do is stall for time from our posts.
I'd like to get this sorted out before that business gets started.
The taxi driver who came with me. I need you to take care of him.
- Can't you just kill them all? - You can't leave Samheung Island.
Push forward!