ADAPTED FROM THE NOVEL HIDDEN LOVE BY ZHU YI
Okay, then our framework is settled.
Afterwards, we'll quickly address
the issue of upgrading the visuals.
Sure.
I'll also update the program schedule
and inform other colleagues.
Thank you for your hard work.
Not at all.
By the way, I've talked to the building security department
about strengthening the security here.
If Jiang Ying comes again,
they'll notify you in advance.
Sorry for troubling you.
It's no trouble.
I just don't get it.
It has been so many years.
Why can't she let go of you and herself
so everyone can live in peace?
But it was fortunate this time
that she didn't see your relative's child.
Otherwise, who knows what she would have done?
Don't dwell on it.
Focus on living and working.
I know.
I'll get back to work then.
Go ahead.
How late did you stay up studying?
DON'T COME
It's almost 2:00 a.m.
It's so late.
How was your revision of the technical overview?
-I'm almost done. -Don't come straight to my office
or my place anymore.
If you do, let me know beforehand, okay?
Can you lend me your notes?
I need to cram for this subject too.
Okay.
LALALA
Why is this question so hard?
If you can't solve it, let me take a look.
No, I must solve it myself.
I need to eat something first to replenish my energy.
Is he really not planning to call and explain it to me?
Sangsang,
do you want some of this?
It's better than yesterday.
Right?
And over here,
it will be better if you test it again
based on the path below.
Again?
Do you want to slack off?
Okay, all right.
But it was fortunate this time
that she didn't see your relative's child.
Otherwise, who knows what she would have done?
When are your exams?
Have you bought your plane ticket home for the school break?
BROTHER NO. 2
SANG ZHI
Next week.
I bought a ticket for the 19th.
Okay.
"Okay."
FLIGHT ON THE 19TH
BROTHER NO. 2
When will you be free after your exams?
Let's have a meal together.
SANG ZHI
I might not have time.
She might go out with her friends.
Forget it.
BROTHER NO. 2
Okay.
BROTHER NO.2
I can't focus at all!
What's wrong?
If I fail my classes this time,
it will be all his fault!
WEAK CHEN
Did you fight with Chen Qiang?
How is he capable?
He's only capable of annoying me.
If you ask me, he's extremely weak!
Weak Chen!
Stop looking at it.
JANUARY 10TH, WEDNESDAY
I've had it.
It's imperative for me to change my mood immediately!
Ning Wei, what do you have in mind?
I've had enough of the bitterness of love.
Only drinking
can relieve it.
After our exams are over,
let's go and have fun.
Why don't we go today?
But I thought
your mom will call you in a little while.
We have exams tomorrow.
That's right.
Then can we go after our exams?
-Sure, okay. -I agree.
Okay, everyone is on board.
I'll text Jiang Ming right now
and officially tell Weak Chen not to show up!
Yes, very impressive.
Baby, answer the phone.
Baby…
What do you want?
What?
No.
You're so annoying.
Okay, fine.
I'll be down there right away.
Bye.
Ladies, I'll be…
Just go.
I can't stand you.
Weiwei.
Be safe.
-Okay. -Close the door.
-I know. -I meant Chen Qiang.
What?
I'm going to shower.
Okay.
Sangsang.
Do you have something on your mind lately?
You may not show it,
but I could sense
that you've been down lately.
I think
it started from the day
you delivered the peephole camera.
Could it be
that the relative to whom you gave the peephole camera
is your crush?
Well,
something did happen that day.
But it's not really anything serious.
Maybe I'm overthinking it.
Do you two still keep in touch?
We do.
But…
I think you're really nice to him.
But if he doesn't treat you well,
you should move on.
He treats me well too.
It's just that…
Wangwang, I'm fine.
Don't worry about me.
I mean it.
CHAPTER 12, COURAGE
IF I COULD
-Five. -Be more accurate.
-Six. -Demonstrate it.
It's six.
Sexy six.
Which one are you drinking?
I don't get it at all.
Don't ruin my rhythm.
How did your exams go?
Not too bad.
Are you going home tomorrow?
I'm free tomorrow. I can see you off.
Don't you have training?
You don't have to.
Go to your training. I can manage.
Okay.
Does your drink taste good?
Try it.
This one has a stronger kick.
If I drink it,
I get drunk quickly.
-It's true. -You're weak.
Try a little.
Not too much. You don't drink.
Are you feeling dizzy?
Not bad.
Impressive.
Okay, where were we?
-It's my turn. -Your turn.
-Five. -Five.
-Six. -I mean five.
-Five. -Six.
Do you want to try to add
that screen space ambient occlusion?
It can add more depth to the entire environment.
You're right. I'll try that.
Go and try it.
Okay. Thank you, Jiaxu.
DUAN JIAXU
You're going home tomorrow.
Have you packed your luggage?
Thank you, everyone.
That was good.
Where is he going?
Don't tell me he's going to sing.
I'll send you to the airport.
Sorry, everyone,
for taking some of your time.
I want to dedicate a song to…
To my friends.
-Okay! -Good!
How do I describe your face?
Cute with a hint of shyness
I really want to have
A little bit of something with you
Can I call you this?
Standing like a fool outside your place
Dialing the phone
Looking at the cooling egg tart
I didn't expect Jiang Ming
to be good at singing.
Besides,
-look… -Just to get a smile
Jiang Ming looks handsome like this, right?
-Right? -Nonsense.
Why don't we be together?
Of course, he's not as handsome as you.
Since the day I met you
I've liked you
Meeting…
I'm going to the restroom.
Do you want me to go with you?
They're all about you
She drank too much.
Watching the ebb and flow of the ocean's surface
Reminds me of you
Carefully
I store you in my mind
A repeating melody
Hello?
Why didn't you reply to my message?
Where are you?
I'm at a bar.
Who are you with?
My friends.
Did you drink?
Just a little.
What's the name of the bar?
-I've liked you since the first day… -Qinghong Music 2002 Music Bar
Okay. Wait inside.
I'm coming over now.
Why are you coming?
To catch a drunkard.
Hello?
If I could
I would cover your island with stars
You won't let me go and see you.
But you want to come and see me.
You're so weird.
Preserve your gentle childishness
And just never wake up
Thank you.
I'm going to go back now.
Are you leaving now?
-How can we let you go like this? -Are you drunk?
I'm fine.
My brother is picking me up.
Bye, guys.
-Is she going alone? -I'll go with her.
-Yes, go. -Go quickly.
She should be fine, right?
She'll be fine.
Be careful.
It's okay.
-I'm fine. -Watch your step.
Careful.
You don't have to follow me.
You can stay with them.
I didn't drink that much.
I'll wait here for my brother to pick me up.
Are you cold? You're not wearing much.
I'm not cold!
I'm really not cold.
Sang Zhi.
Actually, I wanted to dedicate that song
to you.
I…
-What's wrong? -I'm fine.
I'll stay like this for a bit.
I'll help you over to that bench.
No, it's okay.
-This isn't good. -I'm really okay.
-I'm okay. Don't touch me. -Let's go over there.
What are you doing?
Jiaxu.
Get up first.
I didn't drink a lot.
I'm fine.
Are you Sang Zhi's brother?
I'm Sang Zhi's schoolmate.
My name is Jiang Ming.
Nice to meet you.
I'm here now.
So thank you.
Okay.
Then I'll go back inside.
Where are we going?
Who said you could drink at a bar?
I'm an adult.
I'm a grown-up. Why can't I visit a bar?
Even so, you can't drink this much.
Why can't I be here when I'm an adult?
Are you angry?
You said so.
You told me that when I grow up,
I can do what I want.
But now, I've grown up.
I'm already an adult.
But there are many things
that I still can't do.
Or maybe I'm afraid to do them.
Where are you going?
Home.
What's the matter?
I feel sick.
I feel like throwing up.
Then go ahead.
You'll feel better afterwards.
I can't.
Let's go sit over there for a bit.
No.
We'll just stay here.
You're squatting in the cold.
Getting a cold will be worse.
I just want to stay here for a bit.
I don't feel well.
I'll carry you there, okay?
-I-- -Be good.
I don't want to move!
Be good.
Get up.
I'm sorry.
I…
Why are you apologizing?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's disgusting.
-What's wrong? -Don't be mean to me.
Do you want to throw up?
Just do it if you want to.
Don't be mean to me.
I won't.
When have I ever been mean to you?
Can you hold on a little longer?
It's windy here.
It won't be good if you get a cold.
Let's go.
I'll carry you.
What's wrong?
You can't carry me.
Why not?
The doctor said it.
You've had surgery.
Over here.
You can't do any heavy lifting
for three months.
-Over here. -Three months have passed.
Really?
Then…
Can you carry me?
Sure.
Get up and I'll carry you.
Come on.
Get on.
I must be crazy!
You can't carry me.
Why not?
I weigh over 45 kg.
But the thing is that I'm still flat.
What are you talking about?
I weigh over 45 kg.
Hold on.
It's really flat.
What is flat?
You're laughing.
Do you even have them?
Wait.
I don't.
I don't have them either.
Get up first.
I really don't have any.
But I hope
you won't be too sad about it.
Things like this
are beyond our control.
Okay.
I won't feel sad.
If I'm not sad,
you must not be sad either.
No more crying.
Stop crying.
Now,
can I carry you home?
Be good.
Stop crying.
Get on.
Stay still.
Stop crying, okay?
Then
what if I want to throw up again?
Before you throw up,
give me a heads-up.
I'll try not to sway too much
so you'll feel more comfortable.
Then I'll just do this.
-Okay. -Then I won't throw up.
Jiaxu.
I have a secret.
A secret
that I've been hiding in my heart.
Do you want to tell me?
Well,
there is
someone
that I really like.
But
he just doesn't like me.
Who is it?
I can't tell you.
Not even me?
Yes.
Zhizhi is sad.
Zhizhi is so sad.
Is that
because of the person you like?
Are you sure you can't tell me who it is?
Then tell me
what kind of person he is.
Does he treat you well?
You can tell me that much, right?
He is…
He…
What?
I don't know how to put it into words.
What do you mean?
He's really nice.
He's also really nice to me.
But he's nice to everyone.
He's nice to everybody.
He's a ladies' man.
So he has made you so heartbroken.
If he's someone like that,
stop liking him.
Can you do that?
Sang Zhi.
So that's the kind of guy you like.
Why don't I become like him?
And I'll be nice to you alone.
That way, our Sang Zhi
probably won't be so sad anymore.
Letting someone else take care of you
doesn't put me at ease at all.
If you don't say anything,
I'll take it as a yes.
My situation has improved.
I've paid all my debts.
I have a pretty great personality.
The only thing is that
I'm a bit older than you.
When I was 21,
you already thought I was old.
Now, rounding up,
you're almost 20.
Sang Zhi is a grown-up now.
What am I doing?
I threw up.
I threw up on Jiaxu.
He…
He said…
Forget it.
What was there to say
to a drunkard like me?
BROTHER NO. 2
Are you up?
I asked your roommate to wake you up at nine.
All the flights at this time are sold out.
You can't change your flight.
You have to get up
or you won't make it home.
Drink a lot of water after you wake up.
I'll pick you up at ten
and take you to the airport.
-You're up. -You're finally awake, Sangsang.
Yes.
How do you feel?
-Slowly. -Watch your head.
Is the guy who brought you back last night
your brother's friend, your crush,
whom you mentioned before?
Is he the one?
You said he is handsome,
but you didn't say he is that handsome!
I told you before.
How was I to know
that he is this good-looking?
Compared to Chen Qiang,
Chen Qiang is truly weak.
He's no match for him. Not even close.
By the way,
when he brought me back here yesterday,
did he
seem upset?
No.
Did he look unhappy?
-No. -No.
He looked pretty fine to me.
Unhappy?
Wait a minute.
Did you do something?
-Nothing. -What did you do?
Nothing.
Nothing? I don't believe you.
I didn't do anything.
Anyway, you guys have to watch me.
I must never drink anymore.
If I ever drink, I'm a dog.
-You're serious. -What did you do?
Did you kiss him?
No, I didn't. I would never.
-Why are you so worked up? -You must have.
You must have confessed your feelings to him!
-Am I right? -Did you confess?
If I did confess,
I probably wouldn't have woken up today.
-Then what did you do? -What did you do to him?
-Tell us. Come on. -Nothing!
-I didn't-- -She couldn't have vomited.
-Impossible. -You didn't, did you?
Did you really throw up?
Did you really
throw up on him?
Well…
I need to pack my things.
I have to pack up my stuff.
So she did throw up.
She threw up on him.
Sangsang, you threw up on your crush!
Why does he insist on seeing me off?
How can I face him
after what happened last night?
Good morning, Jiaxu.
Good morning.
Let me help you with your luggage.
Sang Zhi!
Jiang Ming.
-Good morning. -Are you okay?
You drank a lot last night.
I'm okay.
Do you need anything from me?
You were drunk last night.
So I don't know
if you still remember what I said.
I'm sorry.
I don't really remember.
I…
Hi there.
You guys can talk.
Sorry, Sang Zhi.
I didn't know your brother was here.
It's okay.
What were you saying just now?
Actually, I wanted to tell you this on New Year's Eve,
but you didn't come that night.
Last night,
I sang a song at the bar.
-Song? -It was for you--
Yes.
I played the guitar and sang at the bar.
You even played the guitar and sang.
I prepared the performance for you.
For me?
I had prepared that song
for a long time.
Thank you.
Sang Zhi.
I like you.
I want you to know that.
It's nice
to have people who like you.
You can thank him for liking you
before gently rejecting him.
Thank you for liking me.
I understand.
However…
There is someone else I like.
So
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
There's no need to apologize.
We're still friends
after this, right?
Of course.
Eat this for breakfast on the road.
Okay.
Thank you.
Get in the car. Your brother is waiting.
I'll get going then.
Bye.
Is it delicious?
Then eat more.
I have something to ask you later.
We went to the bar yesterday because…
Because we…
We had made plans to have fun
after the exams.
The bar is also close
to the campus,
so there were mostly students.
It was not dangerous at all.
Also, you know
that I don't usually drink much.
-So-- -Who did you go with?
My roommates.
They were all people I know.
Roommates?
What about the guy who came out with you yesterday?
The one who is 195 cm tall
and just gave you a hamburger.
Is he also your roommate?
No, that is my roommate's boyfriend's friend.
Is that him?
What do you mean?
The guy you like.
Is it him?
Is he?
What is this?
The breakfast he just gave me.
Is this a beef burger?
You can't eat this. I'll take it.
I'm sorry, Jiaxu.
I threw up on you yesterday, right?
I didn't dream it, did I?
Are you really that hungry?
No.
Why don't you give me the dirty clothes?
I'll return them to you after I clean them.
You drank quite a lot last night.
It's okay.
I knew you would have a hangover today,
so have some fruit.
I'll buy you a hot drink at the airport.
Thank you.
Let's go.