Either way, the inevitable will happen.
After my dad died,
it feels like I'm on a boat every day.
I want to be happy.
I want stability.
I want to step on solid land.
I'm not the right person for you.
Because I want you to be happy.
You'll regret this.
I won't regret it.
EPISODE 11
BASED ON THE NAVER SERIES WEBNOVEL
MARRY MY HUSBAND BY SUNGSOJAK
Hello.
My goodness. Yang Ju-ran.
Are you just getting to work?
That's just sucky.
Ju-ran, you can't be like this.
You're management now.
You must get here early.
Your computer should be on
before anyone else.
Also, I didn't want to say this,
but I saw your Jomart email.
"If you need anything, let me know"?
I mean, will you do everything people ask?
Is that it?
God, this is the problem with women.
If you act that way,
it makes our entire team look bad.
This is unbelievable.
Mr. Kim isn't even the manager anymore.
When he was the manager, I never saw him
come early and turn on his computer.
I think you need to address
his attitude once.
It's been officially announced.
But in his position...
What position?
He's not the manager anymore.
I think you should make it clear
that you're his boss.
You may be okay, but it'll be hard
for new recruits to adapt to our team.
Excuse me.
I hate Kim Gyeong-uk so much.
-Yeah.
-He's the worst.
How could he act like that?
Does he have no shame?
No sane person could act that way.
Don't be ridiculous.
I've been promoted to manager.
How can I leave at 5?
Work ends at 6...
You may not know this,
but I had a temper as a kid.
And my grandfather always stressed
the importance of patience.
I've lived by that...
When did I look down on you?
Do I look like a bum?
Is this good?
Yeah, it tastes like coffee.
-Yeah.
-Give me one too.
I need to wake up.
I think I have to leave early
and come back later.
Can't your parents help?
It must be tough for you.
My husband's at home.
How can I ask my parents for help?
But you practically do everything.
-Worrying about your...
-My husband is...
I feel so exposed.
You're just like me.
I also worried about my husband...
No, I mean, my boyfriend.
In the end, I was the one who was ruined.
Hey.
I learned a lot.
Consideration has limits too.
Bad people won't appreciate
your consideration for them.
Is Mr. Yu not coming to work today?
No. Do you have something to report?
He took a day off today. He's sick.
I think he's caught a cold.
It's been cold lately.
This is a first for him.
Open up.
Hey, I said I didn't need it.
You're so stubborn.
Did you have to make that?
You didn't do that for me.
It's for your own satisfaction.
I told you, I hate porridge.
Still, take one more bite.
I said, I won't. God damn it.
This is so like me.
Is he not home?
It's 20130419.
My passcode.
Pang?
Mr. Yu!
Get up. Let's go to the hospital.
It's Kang Ji-won.
I can't keep seeing you like this.
Are you okay?
A doctor came by.
I took my medicine.
Are you still...
anxious?
Does it feel rocky?
I hope you don't feel like
you're on a boat.
...it feels like I'm on a boat every day.
My feet are firmly planted,
but the boat keeps rocking.
I feel anxious.
I can't be your land.
I want stability.
I want to step on solid land.
I want to be solid land.
I hope you're stable and happy.
Because you're a good person.
Were you that man?
I'm so hurt.
I knew it was you
the moment I saw you again.
You've always been in my heart.
Hello!
You're so much like your brother.
What? I am?
That's such an insult.
You're mean.
I came here to talk strategy.
I just happen to have two musical tickets.
You two should go together...
Well, I...
Ji-won...
What?
I thought I was okay.
I'm not the wrong sentence...
in her novel.
What? The wrong sentence?
What does that mean?
Hey. Are you okay?
Your fever's down. That's good.
I have to go to work!
Did something happen last night?
Wait.
You won't say last night was a mistake,
will you?
No, that never happened.
I took medicine, so I was out of it.
And I thought seeing you was a dream.
You remember then.
What did I say last night?
You have a surprising side.
You spoke casually to me.
I'm sorry.
You said you hoped I was stable and happy.
And that you recognized me
the moment we met again.
Also...
that you continued to like me.
And that you wanted to be land for me.
Ji-won, I...
I'm sorry I didn't recognize you.
We might regret it.
But let's regret it together if we do.
Then we'll be okay.
To tell the truth,
when you told me how you felt,
I thought it was the reason I came back.
To be able to trust someone again,
like someone,
and be happy.
I can do that, right?
What are you doing next weekend?
Us? Whatever you want to do.
"Us"?
Let's talk.
Do it here.
We have to work together.
But treating me like I'm invisible
makes everyone uncomfortable.
You mean you are.
Then you shouldn't have
done something to cause that.
Damn it!
Let go! Let go of me!
I asked to break up
because our relationship isn't the same
as it used to be.
I want a relationship
that everyone's envious of.
Damn it.
Where did things go wrong?
Are the only women you know on your team?
You messed up with that terrible woman,
and this one doesn't seem that better.
I'll be honest.
I didn't think my son would get married
this way.
Still, since you graduated
from Hankuk University.
She was a business major.
She's smart and good at her job.
And she'll work after she gives birth.
Great, right?
I liked studying, Mother.
Sons take after their moms.
Don't be too upset.
My mom didn't think I'd get married
like this either.
But I convinced her.
Also, she adores Min-hwan.
Yeah, that's true.
So your dad ran a business in Busan?
And your mom's a teacher?
Yes.
Before my dad passed away,
our family was very happy.
I just want to live like my parents did.
They loved each other so much
and were very devoted parents.
From what I saw in the cooking class,
I can tell you're smart.
I lack a lot. I hope you can teach me.
Originally, a woman needs to meet
the right man.
Judging by your taste in men,
you're very smart.
-Eat up.
-Okay.
You're right. Sons take after their moms.
That's why Min-hwan takes after me
and is very smart.
You're right, Mother.
-Bye, Mom.
-Okay, I'm off.
Get home safe, Mother.
Okay, you too.
What?
Hankuk University?
Why did you lie about that?
I did it for you.
Ji-won graduated from there.
So how could I tell her
that you went to a no name college?
You wanted a fresh start. Why lie--
Lie?
Does your mom adore me?
How can she when I've never met her?
Goodness...
Let's not get sensitive over this.
Everything will work out.
I think my mom approves.
I'll tell you the date
of the family meeting.
-See you then. Bye.
-What?
They booked a wedding hall?
It looks like they won't tell the company,
-but it's called Crown...
-Crown Wedding Hall.
That's it.
That's where I married him.
It's the worst place imaginable to women.
It must be over now.
This is huge news.
My parents told my husband
to work at their restaurant.
We didn't say anything
when you quit your job
because we thought it didn't matter
which one worked outside these days.
But!
My daughter goes to work,
takes care of Yeon-ji,
and does the housework.
Ju-ran does everything.
I should go to work.
The head of the family raising a child
and doing housework is just...
That's why I'm telling you
to work at our galbi restaurant.
It's big, so there's so much to do.
Wash the grills and dishes,
get the meat, serve customers, clean.
Sir, just hear me out.
I'm not the type to do that kind of work.
What...
How could you say that?
You're not the type?
-Then what type of work is for you?
-Housework and parenting?
It's decided then.
Wake up early, take Ju-ran to work,
and bring Yeon-ji to the restaurant.
You're amazing.
Ms. Yang usually just puts up with things.
And you helped her take a step further.
Isn't this great? So refreshing, right?
I'd always come here
when I had a hard time in college.
To regain the strength to keep going.
It's my first time coming here happy.
Wow... I never though I'd have this again.
Is it a hot spot?
To me, it is.
It disappears in a few years
because of redevelopment.
Do you remember?
We went to eat gukbap.
Wasn't I brave then?
I was so surprised.
To see such a luxurious gukbap restaurant.
You were quite classy.
You gave off a young and rich vibe.
No way.
There. The way you put the rice
into the soup.
Anyone could tell.
Add the jeongguji.
That's right. I should.
No.
I was kidding.
This one. Chives.
This isn't a side dish.
You put it in your soup.
But people from Seoul eat it separately.
That's just wrong.
All right.
Eat it with the meat.
Okay.
How is it? Better, right?
It's nice and spicy.
Eat up.
Mr. Yu, when you date, do you say,
"Today marks day one."
Or things like that?
When will you stop calling me Mr. Yu?
Well...
Until you get promoted to director?
I'm just kidding.
What did your ex-girlfriends call you?
I didn't have to do any of that.
I don't remember what they called me.
It didn't matter.
The only name I know is this.
"Kang Ji-won."
"Ji-won."
Only Kang Ji-won.
What's wrong with him?
Look at him. What's with him?
I don't know.
What?
Isn't he tired of it?
He hasn't changed a bit.
I'm here.
Hello, sir.
I'm Kim Tae-hyeong, and I have been
assigned to Marketing Team 1.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah.
I'm originally a manager.
Hey, you're here.
Gosh, this chair recognizes its owner.
It fits my butt perfectly.
Ms. Yang.
No...
Manager Yang, you'll return it to me soon,
so use it carefully, okay?
-Hey. Work hard.
-Yes.
Yes, sir.
Assistant Manager Kim.
Where's your proposal?
I said I'd do it...
What did you just say?
Your idea isn't that good,
so you should at least be diligent.
Oh, don't worry.
It doesn't suck.
It's just not that good.
Are you insane?
What the hell are you doing?
You know hierarchy
better than anyone does.
You know how it works.
You're not the manager anymore.
But isn't sitting here uncomfortable?
I need to know your standards
in order to meet them.
Why are you speaking to me like that?
Where are your formalities?
That's how you spoke to me.
I figured it was okay.
I'm your boss now.
But I'm respectful while you're not.
It's strange.
So what shall we do?
Shall we both be more respectful? Or...
shall I speak casually to you?
Mr. Kim.
Surely, only men look after men.
These little chicks...
How dare these chicks try to break up
a male friendship?
-So cheeky.
-Right?
Mr. Park.
Let's drink and go to a sauna tonight.
Ms. Yang's dad is buying galbi tonight...
But I can't go there.
I have plans at home. Sorry.
Really? Okay.
By the way,
you're not really in a relationship
with Su-min, are you?
No, sir.
Good.
What a great day.
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR PROMOTION!
Ms. Yang, congratulations!
Eat as much as you want and drink!
Yang Ju-ran bombs!
Is that not it? This is pretty famous.
Amazing.
Wow, you're the best.
-Great job.
-Congrats.
Thanks.
Thanks, everyone.
Shall we toast?
Cheers.
-Cheers!
My, my!
We have prepared the best beef
for the best marketing team!
It's the full course
with all the special cuts!
I hope you take your time to enjoy it!
-Yang Ju-ran!
Okay, everyone.
Please take care of my princess.
Princess! Hip, hip, hooray!
-Princess!
-Yang Ju-ran!
-Dad!
Don't call me Princess.
Daughter, don't say that.
Honey.
-Princess.
-Stop it.
I swear...
I'll do everything for my princess.
I think this is what I really wanted, Dad.
Not being alone.
Standing on firm land
and not letting any wave shake me.
It was so easy.
All I needed was one person on my side.
I think I really have one now.
Go inside first.
-What?
-Your lips.
All right. Go now.
Bye.
Honey.
Where were you?
You could've said hi...
Sir.
Come on in.
Hurry up. Say hi.
Hello.
I'm Lee Jae-won, Ju-ran's husband.
Well...
Please take good care of my wife.
Yeah.
Thank you.
-Ms. Yang.
-Yeah?
How is Mr. Lee here?
I invited him.
I got promoted because he believed in me.
Excuse me.
Mr. Lee.
-May I?
-He came because she asked?
Seriously?
Damn it...
This sucks.
-I can't do it.
-What the hell?
-What?
You scared me.
Unbelievable.
Let's have a guys night out soon.
What's wrong with him?
I won't tell my coworkers. Got it?
What are you saying?
-Hello.
This house is decent, right?
There aren't many houses
for rent when it's urgent.
I happen to have one.
Wait. Rent?
Rent? You said you'd buy me a house.
After you live together for two years.
-What?
-The couple is so blessed.
-Let's go inside.
-Okay.
Why is it suddenly rent?
Southeast Asia is nice too.
I recommend Hawaii.
DOMESTIC HONEYMOONS
She's pregnant. It's not safe to fly.
There are lots to see in Korea.
Bulguksa?
GOLD, JEWELS, WATCHES SPECIALTY STORE
What are you doing? Go in.
Hello.
Get me a drink.
This color is nice.
Let's do the makeup like this.
-Okay.
-For the dress... Let's see.
This is too exposed. No.
This is nice. It's decent.
We'll pick this for the dress.
WE'RE GETTING MARRIED
WEDDING
YOU'RE INVITED
What is this?
Who picks these types of invitations?
What's with your mom?
Then tell her that!
You can't say it to her.
Why take it out on me?
How can I say that to her?
You have to do it!
Damn it.
Wow, items are free.
Seriously?
JEONG SU-MIN
WE'RE GETTING MARRIED
PARK MIN-HWAN, JEONG SU-MIN
We're getting married.
GENERAL MANAGER YU JI-HYUK
JI-WON
Can you believe this?
They're really doing it?
-Wow...
-I can't believe it.
U&amp;K EMAIL INBOX
COMPANY ANNOUNCEMENT
I think you should check your email.
My email?
Sir, what's with the email?
Who said to...
send out a company announcement?
Name and department, please.
A wedding announcement
for Park Min-hwan, Marketing Team 3.
Aren't you getting married?
Well... I am, but...
When an employee gets married,
announcements and monetary gifts
are given.
And the team will be given days off
to attend the wedding.
And you need days off
to go on your honeymoon.
That's all right, but...
It's my wedding,
and I didn't say anything!
Did I ask you to announce it?
This is insane.
It seems he's in a difficult position
because he's marrying
Ms. Kang Ji-won's friend.
I mean, it's frowned upon.
I get that you like Kang Ji-won.
But...
you don't seem like the type to meddle
with Min-hwan and Su-min.
Scumbags like them
have nothing to do with you.
If it concerns Ji-won, it concerns me.
He's laughing.
I've never seen him like that before.
It was touching.
You?
That's not like you.
I saw him in a new light.
I understand your intent,
but Ji-hyuk was no fun at all.
He didn't want anything.
He suppressed his emotions.
He had everything,
so he didn't really need me.
But this time...
he seems like he's really living.
For the first time.
Ji-hyuk, you sent it?
I couldn't stand it.
SENDER: YU JI-HYUK
RECIPIENT: HR DIRECTOR
I admit that it was childish.
This is amazing.
What is?
That someone's on my side.
Someone to get mad about things for me.
What are you thinking?
I'm thinking about kissing you.
What?
Actually, more than that...
What's wrong with you?
-Damn it!
-My goodness!
What are you doing? She's pregnant!
Mom, please! You don't know anything.
What is this?
Did you send the invitation to work?
Work?
What?
This is...
It was announced at work!
What?
Everyone knows we're getting married now.
How can I go to work?
How can I work there now?
God damn it!
-You're so loud!
-Why can't you?
What's the problem?
Is marrying me that bad?
Exactly!
Things like this happen!
I thought there was big trouble.
Hey! I need to collect at your wedding!
Yeah, you're not alone now.
Think about our baby general.
Our baby, my foot!
Why's he holding me back?
Damn it!
You brat! That's my grandson!
Stop hitting me!
Seriously?
What about me?
This is hardest on me!
Damn it!
Go inside. This won't do.
What's wrong with him?
He's so loud.
Be careful, sweetie.
It must be too loud for our baby general.
Listen. All men are children.
He'll go back to being normal
when he calms down.
So don't worry about a thing.
Just think about having a healthy baby.
I know he's hot-tempered.
Why don't you stay the night here?
No, I should go home.
This is supposed to be good for the baby.
It's great for brain development.
Listen to it before you go.
I'm off.
I thought about it,
and I want to go to this wedding.
I'll pay 1,000 won and eat a lot.
Yeah, I'm going too.
YU HUI-YEON
I want to live.
KANG HYEON-MO
I LOVE YOU, DAD
Hey.
Are you ready?
Yeah, almost. Just a second.
Ji-won, wait.
Can you sit for a second?
What's this?
Kang Ji-won deserves the best.
CROWN WEDDING HALL
MARRIAGE TO YOUR HAPPINESS
It's okay. You're pretty.
I'm getting a family.
I won.
Hey!
Mother.
Is my stomach poking out?
It'd better not. That's why
we're having this shotgun wedding.
By the way, where are your friends?
Are you sure you told them the right time?
Well... Yes.
Oh, your mother's here.
Shall we take a picture?
No, this is my mother-in-law.
I look good in pink.
Isn't this color so beautiful?
Yes, you look beautiful.
Thanks.
-Let's sit down.
-Okay.
The wedding dress is a little...
Just take the picture.
Her bump isn't showing yet,
but it's best we leave no records.
Just take it.
Now.
Yes, I understand.
Smile.
-Hey...
-Yes?
Where's your mother?
Hello!
I'm sorry I'm so late.
Hello.
There must've been a lot of traffic.
Yes, there was.
I only lived in Busan.
Seoul's traffic surprised me.
Su-min, you look so pretty.
I'm sorry I'm late.
CROWN WEDDING HALL
Why are you so late, ma'am?
I told you to come early.
Sorry.
There was so much traffic.
There was an accident near here.
Whatever.
Do you remember everything?
My dad passed away. You're a teacher.
Of course.
He ran a business, left a lot of wealth,
and I'm set for my later life.
What about friends?
For 11 people, 300,000 won each, right?
Hello! Thank you.
Hello.
-It's been so long.
-Congratulations.
-Hey.
You're going after all.
You said she wasn't the wife type.
Thank you.
Stop that!
Did you come alone? Where are the others?
You know Yun-gyeong's temper.
She won't come to a cheater's wedding.
The other girls wouldn't come either.
Jong-chan's on a business trip.
Yong-gu will be at the reception.
Reception? That useless bastard.
Wow. Who are they?
Friends of the bride?
Congratulations.
I think you should keep this to yourself.
You came.
You look pretty.
But this... You didn't have to.
You'll eat before you go, right?
Wait, that's...
Let's go.
I thought I'd seen her before.
Is that your ex-girlfriend? Kang Ji-won?
What? She's a goddess.
You got dumped, didn't you?
I thought you dumped her.
Damn you! Stop talking!
You're so annoying.
COMPLAINT
What's this?
Are you sued? Did you borrow money?
You'll be entering soon.
Okay.
That's okay.
Why are you so late?
I thought you weren't coming.
You caught my bouquet.
What?
Come on. You want the bouquet?
That's not right.
Min-hwan's parents know your face.
That's true.
The dress looks good on you.
Right? My mother-in-law picked it for me.
It's a little disappointing,
but the elders like it, so what can I do?
She thinks of me as her daughter.
I'm glad you two get along.
Let's take a picture.
Call the photographer.
No.
I don't think that's necessary.
Congratulations...
on picking up
my trash.
Park Min-hwan bought me this.
So use it or sell it,
do whatever you want with it.
Trash?
She threw Min-hwan away?
Damn it. Wow, items are free.
How can I work there now?
No, that's not possible.
I'm marrying Min-hwan.
I'll start a new family.
I can't be tied to you forever.
You're entering soon.
Now, it's time to meet
the beautiful bride.
-Okay.
-Let's greet her with
a round of applause.
No, I stole them. The man and family
that used to be Ji-won's.
They're all mine now.
I won.
I'm starting over now.
The groom, Park Min-hwan,
and the bride, Jeong Su-min,
will be wed in the presence
of their family and friends today...
Let's smile a little, ma'am.
Okay, good.
Jeong Su-min doesn't look like
her mom at all, right?
She must look like her dad.
You're right.
I'll take two more.
Let's all smile. Sir, smile.
I guess you haven't seen her.
People hire guests these days.
Do you think she hired her?
Come on.
But if my memory's correct,
Jeong Su-min's mom is still alive.
Eun-ho, what are you doing here?
Su-min sent me the wedding invitation.
But the problem is...
Could the friends of the bride and groom
come out now?
I showed it to Ye-ji,
and they came looking like that.
Wait!
-The bride's old friends are here!
-Here!
They're sorry,
so they'll take revenge for you.
Are they your friends?
No...
Su-min, I'm here.
Who's getting the bouquet? Shall I?
Ji-won may be your other half,
but you're marrying her man after all.
How could she catch the bouquet for you?
Is that true?
She stole her friend's man?
Who else did you send the invitation to?
Take care of this.
What do you think you're doing?
Who are you people?
-I should say hi to her.
-No...
I'm Su-min's best friend. The left ball!
Let go of me.
What... Where are your manners?
I'm her other best friend. The right ball.
Where did these vulgar people come from?
Vulgar?
What are you thinking?
We're like her eyeballs.
And we're the apple of each other's eyes.
Come on!
Were you thinking about something vulgar?
I'm the nose!
They're the right and left balls,
and I'm the nose.
Do you know whose family wedding this is?
The family who raised a dog that
cheated on his girlfriend with her bestie.
But if there's more to know, enlighten me.
What did you just say?
How dare you?
Stop! Mother!
How dare you!
-Mother!
-Kick them out!
Where's Min-hwan?
Calm down, everyone.
Nothing's wrong.
Let's finish the wedding.
Where's the groom?
Min-hwan!
You've got great friends.
They were amazing too
when they bullied me.
If you're tired, shall we go?
Shall we?
You two can talk later.
Yeah, you two. I'll call you later.
Yeah, okay.
Aren't you going to eat?
I paid 1,000 won for a meal ticket.
Let's go.
He must've made up his mind.
Are you okay?
I'm going to eat. Do you want to join me?
If you're okay with somewhere else,
I'll buy.
Of course! Sounds great.
But my manager was supposed to come too.
Where is she?
I told you not to come back here.
It's the weekend. Why are you here?
I can't go home right now.
Yeon-ji's at home.
And I haven't gotten myself sorted yet.
I've been so busy.
So I didn't get a chance
to hear the checkup results.
And I heard it over the phone.
Calm down and speak clearly.
No...
Let's just leave here.
I have stomach cancer.
Great job. Go and rest.
You too.
I came to talk for a moment.
But this is awkward.
Hello.
I'm Yu Ji-hyuk's fiancée.
Wait... Ex-fiancée, I guess?
Since he called off the engagement.
I didn't know it was
because he had a woman.
Did you ever hear that I was married?
How would it feel to have my boyfriend
marry my best friend?
What do we do?
Ms. Yang has stomach cancer.
It's my fault.
My fate went to her.
I know Mr. Yu's a good person.
This is my fault.
Park Min-hwan?
She dumps Min-hwan on me
and goes for a rich man?
I don't like anyone touching what's mine.
I realized I dreamed
of something too happy.