(Watch on www.kissasia.club Support Admin)
Not disappointed.
Surprised
it seems like Supremo has
a soft spot for you.
I don't need that or want his help.
Do you have a family?
Ms. Shion?
Why are you suddenly
engaging in small talk?
My older sister Allison.
Textbook eldest daughter
she's good at everything, she's beautiful
and brave.
I'm done.
A bit slower than I thought.
But
you're good to go.
Who's more handsome
me or that Supremo?
Of course, you!
You have time for your friend
but when I call upon you
it's not right to keep me waiting.
Okay.
Fine.
If that's all, goodbye...
Supremo.
You remind me of someone.
Madam?
You're going to regret this.
Raze will know about this.
Is it true?
You started a fight with Roxane?
Aren't you scared?
You’re putting yourself in danger.
What do you think the boss will do to her?
Death.
I'm sure he'll kill her.
You're not Raze Silvenia.
Shut your mouth!
Your secret is my secret.
Hey!
Where do you think you're going?
Let go!
Thank God, you're safe!
Are you always going to make
us worry about you?
I thought we're all
in this together?
Why are you always going
about it on your own?
What's important is
she's here now.
He's right, Van.
No.
Van's right. It's my fault.
I was being selfish.
I didn't think about
how you would feel.
I'm really sorry, guys.
Thank you guys.
I'm grateful because you’re here.
Even if this place is a hellhole.
We’re friends
we're going to stick together
no matter what hell
we end up in.
Wait
was Dave with you?
What?
He wasn't.
Huh?
Then where is he?
He hasn't come back
from his classes.
Let's look for him!
Huh?
Bloody Night has already started.
How could we find him?
Zein, your recklessness
rubbed off on him.
Are you really blaming
me for this?
I'm joking, you're being too serious.
But where is he?
He knows best that
people in this place
turn to savages at this time.
Guys, please. Let's find him!
No one gets left behind, right?
Mia's right.
Dave can't survive alone outside.
It’s too dangerous.
This will be dangerous
but I'm in.
Matt and I will find him.
Hold on, wait!
Aren't you the ones who said
that it's dangerous outside
when it's Bloody Night?
Now, you're going outside?
If anything happens to both of you
it'll be harder for everyone.
Zein is right.
It'll be worse if the two of
you disappear too.
Let's just wait for him here.
He'll return to us.
Okay?
Let's just guard the doors.
So we can open the
doors immediately
once he returns.
Okay?
Mia.
Where did Dave go?
Is waiting for him
the right decision?
Is he still alive?
What if he came across
the Black Blood Gang?
Now I know how my friends feel
when I leave without
telling them.
In this place
the nights are longer
than daylight.
If you want to live
you have to endure all the
screaming until morning.
Dave...
Dave, where have you been?
Ouch.
It hurts.
What happened?
Where have you been?
I was hiding outside until
the noises stopped.
Dave? Dave!
Hey!
Dave!
We were worried sick about you.
Water... I'll get him water.
Here, drink some water.
What was out there?
What happened to you, bro?
Why did you return so late?
Didn't you notice the time?
I needed fresh air after class.
On the verge of Bloody Night?
You needed to get some air?
Why?
I'm sorry, guys. I didn't
want you to worry.
I should get some sleep.
Dave!
But seriously, he needed
to get some air?
He should've known better.
Exactly.
You should've known
better too, Zein.
Now you know how it feels like
when one of your friends
leaves during Bloody Night.
It's not funny, right?
Excuse me.
Guys, guys...
you know
you need to chill.
Calm down.
Let's just sleep it off.
You're right, let's just
sleep it off.
Dave!
Oh my god! Oh my god!
We're going to be late!
Is Sir Alvarez' class your first class?
Exactly. What are we going to do?
We're already late.
Stop overreacting.
We can skip the class
cause it'll be done in thirty minutes.
Didn't you know that it's our
periodical exam today, Zein?
Is it really?
Oh my god
I wasn't informed.
You shouldn't be nonchalant, Zein.
What if we fail class?
Morning!
You know since we're late
let's have some food.
F.T, bro.
F.T!
Hey
isn't anyone concerned
that periodical tests are
16% of our grade.
We'll definitely fail.
What about our dream to
get into the highest ten?
I almost forgot.
That's why they're disappointed this much
they won't be able to join the highest ten.
They won't be able to leave this place.
Erase. Erase.
Hightest ten or not, we'll
get out of this place.
You know guys
that's the hunger talking.
Let's just eat
so we can get calm.
That smells good!
Hey, is that sinigang?
Of course it is.
Zein's favorite.
And everyone's favorite.
Okay, let's just eat.
Let's go.
- You're so thoughtful.
- I'll help you, Mia.
I'll set up the table.
I'll help you with that.
I'll put this right here.
Okay.
This is my station.
Periodical exam?
Does anyone pass those kinds
of exams here in Hell U?
Isn't surviving Bloody Night
more imporant
than any kind of exam?
Exam your face.
Sometimes, Jerome has a point.
Nice one, bro.
Whatever
if you fail
don't come crying to us, okay?
Me?
Yes, you!
Me, crying?
Exactly.
That's for weaklings.
Like you.
Hey, Zein. Are you okay?
Does it taste bad?
It's delicious.
You're a great cook.
Hey
they're acting like we
aren't in the room again.
I smell something fishy.
Jerome, you know what
that’s hunger that’s talking.
Come on, I'll shove this
bone up your mouth.
Are you done with you assignment?
Why?
His subject discussions are faulty.
Oh, fu-
what’s that?
It seems real
I don't know.
Should we be worried?
You think?
It's Dave's fault.
Yeah, it’s Dave fault again.
Why is it me all the time?
Good morning, Sir.
Ms. Shion.
Guys
I'll go ahead.
I need to take care of something.
I'll come with you.
There's no need, Matt.
You know, SSG Secretary duties.
Trust me, I can do this.
Bye.
Let's go.
Ms. Shion, why were
you absent earlier?
Sir, can we retake the exam?
You don't need to
retake your exams.
I'll make sure your grades
are high even without it.
You’ll really do that, sir?
My friends will be happy
to hear about this.
I appreciate this, sir.
Don't thank me yet.
How's your secretary duties?
Hell.
It’s so hard to relate to people
who aren't in the same wavelength.
But why is that your concern, sir?
Don't worry about your grades
I'll handle that.
But remember what you
need to do for me.
Thank you sir
but I don't have an idea yet
as to where the hidden
laboratory is located.
Even the SSG members
haven't mentioned
anything about it.
Are you even sure there is one?
Naturally
they wouldn't mention it to you.
Trust me
just do your secretary duties
monitor all their movements.
What if they catch me, sir?
I'm not ready to die
yet, Sir Alvarez.
I still need to escape
with my friends
from this hellhole.
Be careful, Zein
because everyone's safety
is now in your hands.
There's a storm coming.
Be a demon.
Blend in with the SSG and admin.
But don't ever empathize with them.
Can you do that?
Do I need to be a demon like them
so I could get a fair fight?
Do I need to be more
savage than them?
I don't want to die yet.
Please.
We can't do anything.
They don't have hearts.
You're monsters!
You're just like them.
You're a monster!
We thought you'd be the next Samantha
but just like her,
you can't fix anything.
Samantha?
Number nine?
Number nine!
You’re a monster!
Monsters! All of you!
Good morning.
Madam Violet.
Master Francisco.
Good morning.
Aren't you going to
greet us, Ms. Shion?
Good morning, Master Francisco.
Madam Violet.
Samantha.
Madam
let's begin.
Good morning, our dearest students.
We are gathered here today
to honor our late headmaster
Dominic Valdez.
I'm delighted
that we are free from his foolish
leadership after all these years.
After all these years.
Isn't it funny?
No!
He didn't kill himself!
You killed headmaster Valdez!
They killed him?
Who said he died?
You're right
we killed him.
And you'll be next.
Just come with us.
Let go of me!
Where are you taking me?
Stop resisting.
This is absurd!
Van!
You killed the late headmaster
why is he the one being punished?
The two of you should be punished?
Oh? You guys can laugh now!
However you try to hide it
the student body knows
that you killed the headmaster!
Get rid of her!
No!
Stop!
Let go!
You can't do that.
Van's protected under council rules.
You're really testing me, Ms. Shion.
Get rid of her!
Touch her once more
or you will regret it.
Stop these shenanigangs, Saman-
Zein Shion.
Why should I?
Aren't I right?
First of all
you don't have the right
to implement punishments
because only Supremo can do that.
Second
the way you're standing here
comes off as disrespectful.
How do you expect
to earn our respect?
And lastly,
I am the Supreme Student Secretary.
I have the right to object
your decisions.
Am I forgetting anything else,
Madam Violet?
Supremo
control your secretary.
She's right though.
Supremo
you should punish this
rude secretary of yours.
Why?
She actually deserves an award
rather than a punishment
because from all the secretaries
I've worked with
she's the only one who knows
that I'm the only one who can
implement punishments here.
Now, based on student council rules
that seems impressive.
Isn't it, Madam?
Ace Craige.
Am I forgetting something.
Sir Francisco?
No but
let's not forget why we are here.
Let's go back to what I
was saying a while ago
let us talk about the big event
that's going to happen in this school.
It will last one whole week!
And we will call it.
Bloody Week.
Where killing is legal in
a span of a week.
At any time.
Good luck everybody.
Seems like half of Hell
University's population
will die.
Seriously?
Do you have a problem with that.
Ms. Shion?
If that's set in stone
please excuse me
I'll be preparing for Bloody Week.
Seems like we all should.
So, how are you feeling now, Vanessa?
Scared
but great.
They deserved it.
That's not even half of my rage.
You know what,
you're reckless too.
Why did you do that?
Do you want to end up like me?
Marked by the admin?
At least
there's both of us.
It'll be difficult to keep track.
You're so brave.
You're overreacting.
I'm serious
that's why.
I'm falling in love with you harder.
Excuse me.
You're close to getting hit.
But wait guys.
I almost died there.
Good thing.
Madam Secretary was to the rescue.
Madam Violet couldn't
even do anything about it.
Nothing?
But Zein, what you did had me worried.
How were you aware of those rules?
Were those true or
did you make them up last minute?
Zein wouldn't lie about that.
She'll be in more danger.
Those rules were true.
I read them in the SSG bylaws.
Supremo is the only one
who has the power to implement
death as a punishment
to any one who breaks the law
or whoever rebels against Hell University.
Supremo trumps HU headmasters.
Wise...
at least we know that the student
council is pro students.
I almost forgot
our grades are taken care of.
Sir Alvarez has our back.
Hello?
Did you hear what I just said?
I said
we're not failing history class.
Shouldn't we celebrate?
You know
our questions aren't going
to answer themselves.
Why did you keep that from us, Zein?
What do you mean?
It's like you don't want
to leave anymore.
What?
We know that you know HU's secrets.
And we know that you can't
leave this place already.
Wait, what?
How did you find out?
Do you think we're noobs?
Of course we notice it when you're
keeping something from us.
You're our friend.
You're so hard-headed.
You always help us but you
don't think of yourself.
I need to protect all of you.
I will do everything in my power so
all of you can leave this hellhole.
You mean us.
All of us wil leave this hellhole.
Do you think we'll let
you be stuck here?
I'll put you guys first, Matt.
I have to.
We'll escape together, Zein.
No one gets left behind, remember?
Right, we'll stick together.
And don't worry
we already know.
What do you mean?
We know about Dr. Quizon
and the secret formula to bring
the dead back to life
and I swear that's so cool.
And to be honest
I thought it was a joke.
If we don't get out of here
we'll rot together in this hellhole.
You’re not alone, Zein.
We won't ever leave you alone.
We'll die here together.
No. I can't let us die here.
You're heartless!
You can do something about this.
But you're afraid.
That's where you're wrong.
I can't do anything.
I'm just a secretary.
Why was she able to do something?
I thought
you're like Samantha.
But I was wrong.
You're a coward.
Who is this Samantha
you're talking about?
Why is everyone calling me that?
Who is she?
She was once a newbie
like you.
But the difference between the two of you
(Watch on www.kissasia.club Support Admin)
is that
she helped us.
Was she THE former SSG Secretary?
I need your help!
I don't know how long I'll survive
from all the serums
they've injected in me.
What happened to you?
They used me as a human test subject.
They experimented on me.
I was one of their test subjects for
the serum that they're making.
Serum?
Wait
did they take you to the laboratory?
Do you know where it's hidden?
Don't stand in their way
if you don't want to end up like me.
How can I help you
if you can't tell me where they took you?
You don't know what you're dealing with.
Just help me.
But how can I help you
if you won't show me where
the secret lab is?
Can you help me or not?
Us?
There are others?
Wait, where are you going?
I still need answers!
Where is the laboratory?
Didn't I already warn you?
Stay away from Alvarez.
Why do you care?
So stupid.
So slow, huh?
You know
you did a great job at the party.
Just don't ever cross the admin again.
Or me.
Hey
what's bothering you?
Hey...
what's wrong with you?
I don't have a problem.
Look.
I'm just tired.
Can you please leave me alone?
So I can be done with this
and get some rest.
Let me help you.
Let me get that.
You don't have to.
I can handle this.
This is my punishment right?
I can do it by my own.
I'll get a rag.
Can this day get any weirder?
What is he planning?
Why is he helping me when it's
him who gave me this punishment?
Have you found a rag?
Yes.
Don't touch anything
or else they'll say I don't respect you.
Do you really believe or care
about the opinions of others?
I don't want to get in trouble.
You won't get in trouble.
Just don’t be reckless again.
Ms. Shion.
Are you being serious?
Do I look like I'm joking?
This is an order from the SSG President
if I say something
you answer quickly.
Got it?
Hey
answer me.
Yes.
You know
you just might be my Achilles' heel.
Ms. Shion.
Here...
for you.
What's that?
A gift.
You're being quiet again.
I already accepted your gift.
What else do you want me to say?
Aren't you going to thank me?
Thank you.
I'll head out.
You should go back to the SSG too
before Bloody Night.
Does that mean that you care about me?
No it doesn't.
You wish.
Just so you know.
FYI
I wouldn't care even
if you got stuck outside
during Bloody Night.
Or even if you die.
You don't have to worry.
I can take care of myself.
Ms. Shion.
Be careful.
Okay. Bye, Supremo.
Sleep well.
I still have more to do for you...
Zein.
Huh? He called me by my first name.
I'm so hungry.
Look who's here.
Hi, Zein.
What's up?
Good thing you're here before the alarm.
Thank you, brother.
Let's eat first
before the official start
of Bloody Week.
What is this?
Our last meal on earth?
Hey, don't be like that.
Can't we just eat something
delicious peacefully
before the riot outside starts?
Let's enjoy the food.
Matt cooked it.
Wow, you cooked again?
This should be delicious!
To lure you back early in the dorm.
By the way
how's your punishment?
It seems like you finished early today.
It's because someone helped me.
Who?
Supremo.
Wow, Zein.
You're built different now
even the student government
president is helping you clean.
Hey
I didn’t command him to help me.
He did it willingly.
Why are you being defensive?
Maybe you're crushing on Supremo?
Watch your words, Van.
We're not even friends,
how can we be lovers?
Whatever.
Matt's dish seems delicious!
Adobo!
Let's eat guys.
Yeah, while the rice is still warm.
Stay away from Ace.
Huh?
Why?
I'll get water.
Did I say something wrong?
He's just jealous.
You know he's in love with you.
You should take it easy.
He's right, Zein.
Don't be a griefer towards Matt.
He's just worried about you.
Griefer? What?
Just look it up.
Come on, let's eat.
Go ahead.
Are you okay?
Water, you want some?
I have weapons ready for us.
What weapons?
What's this for?
We need to be ready.
For Bloody Night?
Week, Zein.
Bloody Week.
I'm not sure if I'm ready for this.
Didn't we talk about this already, Van?
And this is for emergency purposes only.
Let's just hide them in our bags
for protection.
Right, Matt?
This is a bad idea, guys.
This is necessary.
Starting tonight until the end of the week
we’ll walk along side death.
So if you don't want to go with him
we need to defend ourselves.
No!
I don't want this, Dave!
We're not murderers.
We're just defending ourselves, okay?
We need to survive Bloody Week
if we want to leave this place.
Mia...
Our lives are in danger, Zein.
If we're not going to help ourselves
who's going to help us?
No one!
I'm going to hide these two, Zein.
Just in case you change your mind.
Matt...
Get her!
Why are you doing this?
Why? You stole him from me!
Zein!
We can't do anything to save them.
You might get hurt!
Matt, if I can't do anything about this
they'll kill each other.
What's the point of Bloody Week
if no one will die?
Zein, we can't do anything about this.
What?
Fuck all of this! Someone stop them!
We can't save everyone, Zein.
We have bigger problems than this.
She's right, Zein.
Be strong, please!
Listen to her, Zein!
This isn't even the beginning.
This is just the pre-game.
I can't handle seeing
people kill each other
without doing anything!
Zein...
What do you think you
can do about this, Zein?
Huh? Tell us.
Zein.
Don't go near them.
Die already!
Just tell me where the
laboratory is hidden.
I'll show it to you.
We can't save everyone...
Ms. Shion.
Matt said the same thing.
You know, Zein.
From all that's been happening
it eases my heart and mind
knowing we're all together.
Happy birthday, Zein.
That's our boy!
Hey
why are you so damn happy?
It's none of your business.
Why are you so happy?
Supremo.
I secured the files.
You can go now.
Matthew might be looking for you.
Obviously.