I wake up
And I text you first
Overthinking every word…
A week ago, I thought my life was over,
Teenage girls, am I right?
But now that I'm hydrated, showered,
and fully restocked
I'm back to my old self,
Not everything's the same,
Some wounds take longer to heal
Min Ho still won't talk to me,
But you know what? That's his problem,
Like LJ said, I can't stop living my life,
It's still our senior year, after all,
It's official!
on my dad's yacht
If you can live
Wow, an eco-attack?
Yeah, I heard the insult,
I wasn't trying to hide it,
Damn, now Mihee
Sorry, Didn't mean to get between you two,
Again,
Jin, come on, That's not--
Good choice,
Hey,
You okay?
I'm fine,
I feel awful about my part in this,
You can help by staying out of it, Kitty,
Okay, I will,
For what it's worth, I hope you know
In hindsight,
I kind of get why you weren't,
You made a big mistake,
You were scared to lose him,
And I did,
But that's not on you,
I actually managed
I heard about you and Min Ho,
I'm really sorry,
Thank you,
I can't believe we both went
I miss you telling me
even when I know they're not,
And I miss leaning on you,
And your rock-hard abs,
Can we please hug it out?
Let's never fight again,
Deal,
So…
What else did I miss?
Well, I applied early decision to NYU,
We're gonna be
- Don't jinx it,
But maybe, JFK to LAX, baby!
Thank God we made up,
But why is everyone else fighting?
I'm out of commission for one week,
I have to fix this,
Ugh!
Yuri, what are you doing?
Well, Yuri asked Yisoo
for the Designer Breakthrough contest,
I got two looks in before she said,
"I don't get it,
She told me to rethink everything,
In two days?
I know, I thought fashion week
after the world watched me
Wait, maybe that's it,
You're not rich anymore,
Uh, wow, Kitty,
Listen, Listen, Listen,
Kitty is right,
- These designs were the old you,
Who is the new Yuri?
I don't know,
I can't just "find myself"
Okay, well, you're not going to give up,
Juliana can help brainstorm new concepts,
and I'll get everyone
How? Our friend group has more drama
Well, I just mended things with Q,
The only drama you're gonna see
because we are having this fashion show,
The mission, ten new looks, 48 hours,
All I need now is a crack team
With a little friendly matchmaking,
- What have you got in mind?
- How are you with a needle and thread?
When you're this messy inside,
Plus, my nana taught me needlepoint
Wonderful, Hope she
because Q and Jin will be there, Goodbye,
We need someone fast,
- You're looking at him,
To cut patterns,
Jin said he'd be there,
I cornered him in a boba shop
- You should have led with that, I'm in,
- Love you!
I need a makeup pro,
Uh, duh, My face is my résumé,
I need someone who can get
Obvi, This doesn't just happen,
Great,
Can you get our model stage-ready?
Sorry, Kitty,
Well, Yuri's are just beginning,
Come on,
Fine, I'll help behind the scenes,
We need a money man, You in?
Sure, I help my dad
First rule of staying on budget,
Great, Thank you,
Okay, Yuri's gonna get back to me
I've gotten everyone involved,
Even Min Ho?
I think everyone would like
Yeah, well, we said
And I've texted him a few times,
He hasn't even responded,
He hasn't wanted
Ever since his dad fired him,
he's buried himself
Wait, his dad fired him?
Yeah, He's kind of going through it,
Maybe you can try reaching out again,
I hate that he's hurting,
But…
I just can't,
Welcome to the team,
That beat really sucks,
Is it going well?
Well, it's going,
You've been down at the studio
Are you avoiding someone?
I'm not avoiding Kitty,
She's doing her thing and I'm doing mine,
Wouldn't it be better if you two talked?
I don't know,
I'm not sure it’s going well,
Hey,
You know what you need right now?
Deadline,
Yuri needs music for Seoul Fashion Week,
in two days,
You want to give it a try?
Me?
I don't know if I…
No… You can do it, Absolutely,
You…
you reinvented yourself,
It's the same for Yuri,
Okay,
I'll do it,
Yuri will really appreciate it,
Do your thing,
All right,
Okay, we're down to 24 hours,
We've got our team, and yes, everyone is
But I'm a matchmaker, okay?
Trust the process,
- How's it going here?
You're not seriously pairing
If you can't handle my sparkle,
Is my face the rainbow?
Come on, you two,
You're like Elphaba and Glinda,
Just talk it out,
Fine, Maybe Mihee can tell us
If you have to ask, you'll never know,
Well, at least they're talking,
On to the boys,
Kitty, would you mind telling Marius
It's grating,
Someone's just jealous
You're better at shit-stirring,
I didn't exactly have to twist Q's arm for
Hold on, Um, what?
Yeah, I didn't make the best decisions
and now these two are probably
Unless…
You want me to try?
I trust you,
Besides, there's absolutely no way that
Okay,
Marius! Jin!
- Not now, Kitty!
These people are entrenched,
My matchmaking skills
Well, pride is
So, what's the strategy
Number one, get them in the same space,
Two, convince them
and number three, hope for the best,
Interesting,
Speaking of matches,
Doesn't really look like it right now,
And you're okay with that?
Not really,
It kind of feels like
and I'm slowly trying
I wish we could just
but we're at an impasse,
Or stubborn,
Oh, I forgot to mention,
I'm gonna scrap
and go with something original,
What? Do we have time for that?
Yeah, I got an old friend to help,
Okay, can't wait to hear it,
We only have two hours
Wait, what?
I need more time to craft my looks,
There's no way I'll make that,
What happens if you don't?
I lose my runway models,
Do any of your old friends
No,
Actually, I don't want it
My models should reflect who I am now,
Okay, everybody, listen up!
I am
I, I, I, I am…
It's runway day, people!
Give me a strut, two, three!
Let's just take five,
This isn't working,
I need to intervene before Mihee
Clock's ticking,
Hey, girl! Madison's hair is a rat's nest,
She's gonna totally embarrass herself
- Can you do something?
Hey, um, Mihee's makeup is a disaster,
Can you give her a glow-up?
- She's lost without me,
- Okay, this one,
Okay, this one is all done,
- Ooh, lush!
Okay, calm down, you guys,
Matching motorcycle jackets
She designed this one for me,
Oh, unless, of course,
- I didn't mean to,
Holy shit,
This is it!
Okay, Kitty, remember when you told me
you felt like your soul
Well, that's how I felt
and I pieced myself back together, right?
That's what I should do with my look,
- I love it,
- We have to try,
Yuri!
Thank you,
Okay,
Okay, these three are good,
On it,
I think the boys need an intervention too,
Okay, hustle up, Q, your pants,
Marius, your shirt,
Jin, your jacket,
I think I have Marius' pants,
And I have Jin's shirt,
And I have Q's jacket,
- Kitty,
Okay, don't be mad at Kitty,
So can we please just try to be honest
Gonna be honest about
If I'm being honest,
He got me all revved up
I'm sorry I led you on that day,
It… it did,
But I kind of deserved it,
Guys, look, since I came back to KISS,
what you lot had going on
But I was wrong,
And I know Q felt something for me
But after our little motorcycle ride,
And I'm a lover, not a fighter,
So I am done trying to compete,
So why'd you run to Marius
I've been asking myself that every day,
Marius was the first person
But we had to sneak around,
And this year we ended up
I think I wondered what it would be like
But as soon as I explored that, I realized
And I'm sorry that hurt you, Jin,
I'm really sorry,
I'll admit it, you made me look
I mean, you are
Okay, Mihee?
What's going on?
The senior map?
You're sailing around the world?
We talked about taking a gap year
But I guess you're moving on without me,
I was gonna surprise you,
Where do you think
Us? Really?
Duh! You think I'd hit the beaches
Without you, I'd have to be
We have to get matching bikinis,
Twins,
- Come here,
Min Ho,
File's all done,
Thank you,
- Do you like it?
I just hope Yuri likes it,
Mm,
Then, let's go play it for them,
Who's them? What are you talking about?
Yuri and her producer,
When's this music guy getting here?
We have to get back to work,
- I know, He's coming,
- What?
It's only because we care,
Practice what you preach, Kitty,
I've spent this whole day trying
so maybe it's time we do that too,
All right,
I've apologized for what happened
But instead of hearing me out,
Because, Kitty, all it took was one moment
I have enough people in my life
That is so not fair,
Listen, I don't have
Lara Jean and Margot,
I have siblings I barely talk to,
A mum who's a continent away,
and a dad who tells me
every chance he gets,
I heard about what happened with him,
I'm sorry,
But, Min Ho, I'm not your dad,
Yeah, you were supposed to be
Of course I believe in you,
But sometimes I make mistakes,
You've let me down too,
How?
I had my heart set on NYU,
But then I was reimagining
With you,
Then I made one mistake,
and you gave up on us
I know the feeling,
I wanted a future with you too, Kitty,
Well…
for what it's worth,
Well, thanks for trying,
I know you and Dae
But Min Ho is not willing to bend,
I'm sorry, Kitty,
Hey, are you okay?
No,
I don't think I can do this,
What? What do you mean?
I came out here to take in the moment,
and all I see are people
and then laughed at me when
Sure, But look at how far you've come,
I mean, life cut you down,
I didn't do it alone,
None of us ever do,
At the end of the day,
Yuri, what matters is who's behind you,
They all showed up thanks to you,
They all showed up
Welcome to Seoul Fashion Week's
Presenting "Fire and Lace" by Lilly Yo,
Okay,
If I'm gonna do this,
there is one more thing I need
I made you a dress
because I wanted to make it special,
but I don't think we should wait,
Oh, like me on the runway?
- No, I cannot do that right now,
Kitty, you can,
Look, I know you don't feel amazing
I mean, look at everything you've done
You deserve to shine too,
So go out there and blow everyone away,
Come here,
And now, presenting
Call me,
Wow, Yuri actually pulled this off,
And now, the moment
I'm proud to present Seoul Fashion Week's
to someone who's not new to fashion,
but who is
Ladies and gentlemen…
my protégé, Yuri Han!
Oh my God!
Wait, Okay, wait,
Congratulations,
Whoo!
I don't know where
Definitely not here,
Well, there's nowhere else I'd rather be,
I am so proud of you,
Mm!
And I don't think I'm the only one,
- Hi,
Juliana, that logo was amazing,
And all the help you gave me with
You know I'm always down to help you,
Plus, I have some time on my hands
Oh, um…
Sorry, I didn't know that,
Yeah, it was my loss, Kind of my fault,
But I think it was right for us,
I'm actually pretty proud
We're gonna stay friends,
You guys seemed good, What happened?
Uh…
She sensed that
Hey!
I heard you were the guy
Congrats,
The audience was so into it,
Yeah, it felt good,
Thanks, Gigi, for believing in me,
Uh, no, none of that,
You believed in yourself,
Once you do that, you stop
And you stop blaming them when they don't,
Kitty let you down once,
out of a million other times
That's who she is,
Are you really ready to give up on her?
No,
I just don't know how to begin again,
I do,
Get out of your own way
We did it,
We threaded the needle and stitched
As for this matchmaker, I was a bit rusty,
But it turns out, I still got it,
Kitty!
Hey, Um, can I talk to you for a second?
Yeah, for sure,
Look, I know I've been stubborn,
I just--
Sorry,
Wait, it's NYU,
My decision's in,
That can wait,
No, please, You should check,
I got in, I got into NYU!
That's brilliant!
Now you have at least one option,
You won't be a complete layabout,
Oh, I actually applied early decision
just for the best chances of getting in,
You're going,
I'm moving to New York next year,
Congratulations, Covey,
I'm happy that
Um, what were you saying before?
It's not important,
You should go tell everyone the news,
Okay,
And I know that you would choose me
And I know that I'm the one you love
But then, why you go
Am I not enough, am I not enough?
Or am I not enough?
Am I not enough? Or am I not enough?
Am I not enough for now?
Am I not enough, am I not enough?
- Am I not enough?
Am I not enough? Or am I not enough?
Am I not enough?
Go and be with everybody else
And I know that
I'm the one you want
You would choose me over anybody else