This is it. Our new beginning.
I'm not gonna cause any trouble here.
Excuse me?
Is this the room of Section E?
- But the guy said...
- Are you deaf?
Leave!
Someone pointed me to the wrong direction.
I'm Jasper Jean Mariano.
You can call me Jay-jay.
Mr. President, don't you have anything
to ask about our new transferee?
Are you still a virgin?
The teacher is asking
for appropriate questions.
Your IQ is probably low.
Who keeps throwing things at me?
3, 2, 1!
How's Section E treating you so far?
They're okay. They're being nice to me.
You'll fit right in Section E.
Hey.
Yuri...
Why are you treating
my classmates like dogs?
You're glued.
You'll regret not following me.
1... 2... 3!
Hey, Keifer!
Do you think you can just
kick me out of your section?
You wish.
Game on!
"Game on?"
Really, Jay-jay?
Why did you have to say that?
The King of Assholes will
surely strike back at you.
What are you gonna do now?
Jay-jay?
Jay-jay!
Oh.
Are we here?
I'm sorry...
Oh.
Thank you, Ci-N. Good
thing you have an extra jacket.
Wait for me here. I'll just get changed.
No, it's fine. I just
wanted to take you home.
How about your jacket?
I have lots at home.
Thank you, Ci-N.
Alright.
-Take care.
- Go inside.
Thanks again!
- Just get inside already!
- Alright.
Take care.
See you!
Oh, I didn't see you there.
Are they here already?
Yes, they're already eating.
Yeah, that's the guy. Definitely him.
So, that's him, huh?
Hey.
You think we'll let you get away
with what you did to our friend?
Not really.
Wipe that smirk off your face
I don't think you'll be able to smile
when we're done with you.
Even the toothless can smile.
What more for a guy with all his teeth?
The girl you were with earlier...
She's pretty.
When we're through
with you, is it cool if...
we get her next?
You talk too much.
Where do we take this?
Shut up!
Don't ever do that again.
Or else I'll take drastic measures.
You can't run away from home
just because you can't stand...
Jay-jay!
Come, let's eat.
There's lots of food.
- Good evening, Auntie.
- Good evening.
Good evening, Angelo.
Good evening, Aries...
Sit down.
Go ahead.
Look. There's so much chicken.
Starting tomorrow,
you'll drive Jay-jay to school.
I think I'd rather walk...
No!
You'll go to school together.
Since it's decided now,
let's go ahead and eat.
Dig in.
Chicken?
Come, eat up.
Thank you.
Here, son.
The food's delicious.
Want some rice?
No, Ma. Thanks.
Aries?
I know you're mad at me.
I just want to apologize for...
Jay-jay. Your sorry won't change anything.
I know that. But I just
want to say sorry...
Just get in the car.
Get in!
Aries... I can just walk to school.
You should know,
anger takes time to heal.
Just follow everything Angelo says.
Maybe he'll change his mind.
I hope so.
[students chatter]
- Why is the liver unbeatable?
- Why?
Because it's a tie!
God, I'm reminded by it again.
Where's that kid?
Woah! There's chocolate!
Thank you!
Have you got no shame?
Why? I helped you yesterday, didn't I?
Alright. You can have that.
How about me?
You don't get to have one.
He's the only one who helped me.
And I saw you laughing at me.
You really like bringing food.
And so?
Then I have a task for you.
What's this?
Our order.
This is neat!
It's even longer than a loan list!
- What? Is she for real?
- Hey Drew, she's taking a swipe at you!
I already told you, "no."
What did you say?
What makes you think
that I will follow you? Huh?
Simple.
You won't like it when we get hungry.
We bite.
And... if we get hungry...
We might just feast on you.
What?
Are you game?
Game...
[students teasing]
Hey! You're spitting all over me!
One-five.
Pay up!
I'll give it later.
Get out of the way!
I'm sorry.
This is only for today,
Jay-jay. Just for today.
We're not supposed
to give up easily, right?
[irritated groan]
What a mess.
Why did he have to
give me such a large bill?
She's so lucky to be around Keifer.
I bet she'll ask to be transferred.
I actually saw her with Ci-N too.
What a slut.
Hey, you wanna watch a movie after school?
Sure, babe!
That asshole just had to flex his cash.
Jay-jay. What is that?
Uh... this is...
Is that for Section E?
Sorry, Aries, but I have to go.
Put it back.
I said, put it back!
Sorry.
Jay-jay!
Keifer!
Your food's here.
And here's your change.
[students clamoring]
- This one's mine.
- Take your hands off it!
- Hold on! There's plenty of food!
- Give it to me!
[students chattering]
- Let me have a look.
- Move over! I'm hungry!
Get out of the way!
[students chattering]
I hope I can eat in peace now.
Jay-jay...
Come here. Let's all eat together.
Wow. You really waited for me?
Tss!
Come sit here, quick. Sit with us.
Come on.
Here she comes...
Jay-jay's here! It's time to eat!
[cheering]
Hey. Go eat.
Time to eat. I'll share with you.
You don't like this?
Have this instead if you
don't want a sandwich.
Thank you bro, this is so good!
What's his problem?
Go on, eat up.
You have training later, right?
Felix.
Do you have Ci-N's phone number?
Yes, why?
Give it to me. Here.
- Here you go.
- Put yours in as well.
Oh. Alright.
Wait... let me get your number.
It's there in the phone.
Thank you.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
[students chattering]
This is mine.
My goodness. Why don't
you know the answers?
John Felix Collins?
- That's you, man.
- Stand up.
Uh... I'm sorry, ma'am.
I also don't know the answer.
You too don't know the answer?
Remain standing.
Jasper Jean Fernandez - Mariano.
Fernandez?
Ma'am...
Are you related to Aries Fernandez?
Yes, ma'am.
What?
How are you related to Aries?
He's my cousin.
So, Miss Mariano,
you don't know the answer as well?
No I don't, maam.
You are all hopeless, guys.
How about Joshua Venites?
I also don't know, ma'am...
Andrew Klondike Mercado.
I don't know the answer, ma'am.
Why don't you know?
Rory Abejar.
I don't know the answer, ma'am.
Dude, let's go. Quick!
Game, game, game!
Let me join.
He said he's joining.
Why?
Guys, I'm heading out. Bye!
Alright, take care.
Losers can't join this game.
What do you mean "loser?"
What's happening here?
I don't stink.
Felix.
Hey, Felix.
Hey! Felix.
Felix, do you want some?
Don't want my chocolate to go to waste.
Hey, Felix, hurry up.
Let's go outside.
Move quickly. The game's about to begin.
Let's do it outside, it's much quicker.
What's going on?
Why did the tides suddenly turn?
- That's insane, bro. He's good.
- Yes bro.
You know, I admit I
can't do that. Impressive.
That's it?
He's not going to bully me?
What is happening?
Why did they stop caring all of a sudden?
Hello! Ci-N! It's me!
And who are you?
It's Jay-jay! What's up with you?
Why are you skipping classes?
Excuse me. Could you please
not scream on the phone?
I'm sorry. What happened to you?
I'm not feeling very well.
- Huh?
- Why? Are you missing me so much?
No, are you crazy?
Oh, really?
Okay then. Bye.
Wait! I just wanted to know if you're okay.
When will you go back to school?
So you admit that you missed me?
I'll probably go back to school next week.
Huh? What happened to you?
Nothing.
I just don't feel well.
Why are you pushing it?
What do you mean by
"not feeling very well?"
Next week is too long. What's your illness?
My ingrown is hurting.
It's hopeless talking to you,
Ci-N! Annoying!
I'll just see you
when I see you, Jay.
Wait, it's because Keifer
and the others were...
Oh, Aries!
What?
Umm...
Did you do something against Section E?
Me? Do something against Section E?
Are you serious?
Then why aren't they talking to me?
I'm not the one to ask
why there are rotten apples out there.
It's because...
they've started treating me differently
when they learned that I'm a Fernandez.
I don't know.
Maybe it's because of Angelo.
He's a Fernandez too.
But you were the one
they were asking me about.
If you and I are related.
Jay-jay, I have no idea.
Why don't you ask them directly
what their problem is with you?
Don't bother me.
Guys, I got her school records.
The first was from the principal.
The other was from her previous school.
There's not much information about her
from HVIS as of late...
because she just
started here, of course.
But if you check her
previous school records...
Damn!
Stabbed a classmate with a pencil?
Seriously?
Punched another student?
Wow.
She really fits right in Section E.
So far, that's all I saw.
Check if there's anything else.
Guys, guys. Guess what?
I found out that Aries' and Jay-jay's
mothers are half-sisters.
They have a broken family.
Her father is nowhere to be found.
And her mother has been
married multiple times.
She grew up with her grandmother.
But this is the most important part.
Recently, she has been
taken in by Aries' mother.
So it's possible that she's
spying on us for Aries.
Bro, what the fuck.
Possible.
Do you really think it was his idea to
put his troublemaker cousin in our section?
Okay, everyone. On our next session,
we will be applying the lectures.
Yes, ma'am.
Okay, ma'am.
They've been ignoring me for a week.
- I wonder what these assholes have been planning for me?
- By the way, class.
Don't forget to clean up before you go.
Sir Alvin asked me to
remind you. Or else...
So, clean up this room.
See you tomorrow.
- Okay, ma'am.
- See you.
I'll go home now.
- Where do we go tonight?
- Dinner?
Seems like nobody is planning to clean.
Everybody's going out.
Hey. We were told to clean up.
Are you expecting me to do it alone again?
What's wrong with you?!
Go ahead, lock her up.
[students chuckling]
If you will force me to clean,
you could at least stop ignoring me!
Just clean up so you can leave.
I'm getting bullied on
top of being ignored.
So, what are we gonna do with Jay-jay?
We need to get rid of her.
But how?
Your "pretend she doesn't exist"
plan didn't seem to work.
She's such a badass.
You're no match for her.
No fucking way!
We just have to make her life miserable
until she decides to leave on her own.
Oh, really? Then they will wait in vain.
They think they can get rid of me easily?
Watch me.
So full of themselves.
Oops.
Still dirty here.
You forgot the trash.
Was that funny to you?
Are you amused?
Yeah.
It's funny.
Clean it.
Do you think you're cool?
Is this what you want?
Come on!
There! Trash! Go clean it up!
Stop it!
He's the only one who can make a scene?
I refuse! You all have to clean!
Alright.
We're gonna clean up too.
Wait...
Why are we getting dragged into this?
We're not involved in that mess.
I'm the class president.
I don't clean.
And so what if you're the class president?
That doesn't exempt you from cleaning!
What the f...
A class president that is
exempted from cleaning?
Wow. Dictator much?
You're the one who made
this mess in the first place!
Yes, I made this mess! So what?
Want more?
Here you go!
Alright. Make a mess. Go ahead.
You think I won't stand up to you?
In your face, Mr. Class President.
Go ahead, make a mess! Do it!
You think I'm scared of you?
Just clean up too.
Why?
We don't know yet what
that girl is scheming.
Aries might have sent her to mess with us.
David's coming back, right?
Start cleaning!
So fun, isn't it?
Fun?
I wouldn't exactly say being
locked in here with you is fun.
But isn't this your fault?
My fault?
You're the one who threw trash at me.
And why?
Who did it first?
That was you, Mr. Class President.
Who is David, anyway?
David was...
the original class president.
Ah, original.
So, you stole that position from him?
I have a question.
What is it now?
Why did you avoid me when you learned
that Aries is my cousin?
Aries, stop the car!!!
What?
Is that Ci-N?
It is him.
I'm gonna get off here.
Make sure Angelo
knows I took you to school.
Of course!
Ci-N!
What are you up to?
- Good thing you're coming back to school!
- Ouch.
Take care!
You seem wrecked.
You got so many wounds and bruises.
This is nothing.
I fell on my face.
Fell? What did the pavement do, punch you?
Here.
I always have this in my bag. Use it.
No need for that.
Jay-jay, this is nothing.
You're worrying too much.
You're overacting.
Then don't.
By the way, Ci-N.
Something happened with Section E.
That's not news to me.
No. This is different.
It's Keifer...
What happened?
I'm a Fernandez.
Jasper Jean Fernandez Mariano.
Aries and I are cousins.
So I've heard.
Then will you...
avoid me now too?
Of course not.
Why would I do that?
Thank you, Ci-N.
But what if the others see
that you're talking to me?
I'll just tell them I was not
aware you're a Fernandez.
Easy.
- You're so good.
- Of course.
You're my idol.
[students screaming]
What's going on here?
Yeah! Go punch him in the face!
I didn't recognize him.
It's just David.
Why is there a girl here?
Go on! Fight!
[continuous cheering]
You know, I think we
better get out of here.
You're still full of wounds.
- Get out of here.
- Wait, let's finish watching this first.
Shouldn't we get out of the way?
Or at least stop them?
They wouldn't listen to us anyway.
Wanna try?
Go and stop them.
Fight!!!
Punch him!
Will you please stop this?!
- Ouch!
- What the hell?
No stopping!
What the fuck?
Did you throw that?
Yes, she did!
Don't you dare meddle!
If I get injured, will you take me
to the hospital, huh?
Aren't I your opponent?
Stop it!
Let's have a re-election.
Where it's more organized
and no one will cheat.
Whoever wins...
will be the class president.
Fair and square.
I'm game with that.
As long as no one will
throw chairs, or garbage.
Game.
And why would I throw things
during class elections?
Alright. Later, after class.
Let's arrange the room
before Sir Alvin gets here.
How lame. It was already getting exciting.
It's a waste of money.
Hey, Ci-N.
What's up with that re-election thing?
Just you wait.
It's better when it's a surprise.
Just tell me.
Fine.
It's just...
a fair match.
Just see for yourself later.
The only thing you need to know...
David was the original president.
Just watch it later, okay?
Poor David.
Oh! By the way...
How did you end up in Section E?
I hope this time you
can answer this honestly.
I also had a fistfight incident back then.
It's a bit complicated.
There's also a little kiss in the mix.
Aren't you too young to be kissing anyone?
You act as if you're an old woman.
So, how did it actually happen?
Did you make the first move?
Something like that.
It hurts, Jay.
You foolish child.
Tell the story.
- How did you kiss?
- No.
I don't wanna.
- Come on, spill it!
- You're too pushy, Jay!
Jasper Jean Mariano,
you and the entire Section E are banned...
from entering the HVIS Cafeteria
by order of the student council.
Seriously?
I am banned from the canteen too?
What kind of joke is this?
You're from Section E, aren't you?
How are we gonna get food now?
You're right.
How annoying! The worms in
my tummy are getting riled up now.
I will just bring my own food from now on.
Why don't you bring some for me too?
Aren't you pushing your luck too much?
Come on.
Everyone's busy at home.
Please...
I'll share my food with you then.
Yes!
Hi, Rakki!
You girls go ahead.
Bye. See you later.
Jay-jay, how are you?
You doing okay?
It's just...
I'm famished. You?
How about me?
Aren't you gonna ask how I've been?
No need. It's obvious
you've been in a fight.
Dummy.
Why, haven't you eaten anything?
Not yet. I'm banned from the canteen too.
Is that so?
How about this?
Just give me your money.
I'll see what I can do.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Give it, quick.
I'll have rice and menudo. You, Ci-N?
I'll have the special order.
It's called "Rakki."
Really. What's your order?
I'll have the same as Jay-jay.
- Okay. I'll go ahead.
- Thank you, Rakki.
Hey... what's up with you two?
Nothing.
That's nothing.
Ahhhh, so the kiss you
were telling me about is with...
With Rakki?
Yeah.
Wow. I didn't expect that.
You really kissed?
I kissed her.
How?
It just happened.
Our faces got closer and then...
I kissed her.
She punched me after, though.
You really are sneaky.
Rakki's so nice, isn't she?
We got to eat because of her,
now I get why you like her.
Tell me about it.
Wait, why are we down here?
Aren't we heading to the re-election?
Come on, place your big bets right here!
I'll bet on Keifer!
Keifer! Keifer! Keifer!
Alright, guys. Listen up!
It's now time for the re-election!
It's so fun, see?
We even have an announcer.
- Your re-election's like this?
- Let's go, Keifer!
Are you serious?!
The rules are simple...
It's a fight until the end.
David versus Keifer.
Last one standing...
gets to be president!
[cheering]
Keifer!
- David! David! David!
- Keifer, let's go!
Keifer, let's go!
Beat him up, David!
He's nothing but a pretty face!
You can do it, David, go!
David!
Alright go ahead and stretch.
What?
You gotta win, dude.
I bet a lot of money on you.
- David, you gotta win!
- Let's go!
David!
Keifer!
- Come on, Keifer!
- I said David!
Go, David!
Okay, guys, before you start...
let's do a fist bump.
Okay.
Let's get ready to rumble!
Let's go, Keifer!
Go on, punch him!
Give him another!
David?
Easy!
Let's go!
Come on, man! I bet a lot on this.
Come on, David!
Get up, David!
Keifer!
Get up, David! Beat him up!
Beat him up!
Punch him!
Go! Beat his ass!
- David!
- Let's go, Keifer!
Keifer!
The winner and still our class president!
Mark Keifer Watson!
[cheering]
Keifer!
I'm so sorry, my friend.
Hey, David.
Just leave.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Just leave me be.
I'm alright.
You are not alright. Look at you.
You're injured.
Do you want to report this to the school?
I'm the one who got
involved in a fight, right?
Do you think I have the
nerve to tell on them?
Fine then.
Just let me help you.
I'll do it...
No, just stay there.
Don't try to act cool. Here.
Wear this. So nobody
will see you all bruised up.
Why are you helping me?
Do I need a reason to help?
Come.
Fix yourself up.
Get up now.
Class... see you tomorrow.
Sir, maybe next year?
- Alright. I'll see you next year.
- Bye, sir.
See you, sir!
- Take care.
- Slow down, sir.
- Goodbye, sir.
- Take care.
Did you bring any food?
Of course. I brought some for you as well.
- Yes!
- Wanna eat it?
Of course.
Thank you, Jay.
Want some?
Yeah.
Next time, I'll bring some
for you as well. For now, eat this.
Tss.
Thank you, Jay-jay.
- Are you feeling better?
- Yeah.
Hey, David.
Welcome back.
- Thanks, man.
- I missed you.
Let's eat.
Eat everything, okay.
- I'm so hungry.
- You eat too.
- Go ahead, I'm good.
- Thank you.
Is it tasty?
Mmm.
Guys!
Miss Assunta sent a
message to the group chat.
We'll be having PE class at the gym.
- Right now?
- Yeah.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
- I'll just change clothes.
- Did you bring your uniform?
Umm, yeah.
I got it. I'll go change.
[students chattering]
Why are you all changing here?
Can't you see there's a girl?
[students chuckling]
What the hell?
My God, you're all so nasty!
You look like you're enjoying yourself.
Nice view?
God, no! What do you think I am, thirsty?
You're all so skinny!
Is that why you're staring at...
Shut your mouth.
I'll go get changed.
Move! Get out of the way!
Move! Move!
Look where you're going, will you?
[students teasing]
Busted!
Come girls, coffee?
Hey, I'll see you later, okay?
Bye, see you.
We're gonna have coffee.
Yo!
Aries!
What's up?
Wanna see what shenanigans
Section E is up to today?
It's their PE right now.
Why me?
And why would we bother
watching their PE class?
Aries, let's go. It's gonna be fun.
And also... your cousin's there, right?
Hey! She's my cousin.
Don't even think about it.
Alright. Chill.
Come on, Aries. Don't you wanna
keep an eye on your cousin?
You know how Section
E does their PE, right?
I'll call you guys later, okay? See you.
Excuse me.
Hi, Mykel.
Hi, Kiko.
- Hi, babe!
I won't be too long.
We have gym practice later.
Wanna come?
Alright, babe. Sure.
Your ex is there.
Hey, you mean "exes."
Aren't Keifer and Yuri your exes?
Only Keifer.
You know, you two are jerks.
I'm just letting her know who's at the gym.
Alright, class. Let's do the stretching.
All you have to do is to follow me. Okay?
Ready?
Shake your hands.
There.
So we can release our tension. Okay.
Okay?
You hold your ears like this.
Let's stretch it out.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Eight, seven, six, five, four,
three, two, one.
Okay, next.
Stretch.
One, two, three, four, five, six
Stay here with me for a bit.
Go to practice later.
Seven, six, five, four, three, two, one.
Shake your hands, guys.
Good.
There you go.
Alright, now let's do the upper part.
Hey. Aries, Ella. Come here,
we saved you a seat.
Okay, let's do this.
- Ella Dianne Hyun.
- Okay, guys...
This is off-limits!
Alright. Now second stretching.
There was this girl.
Keifer and her became a couple.
That's... Ella, right?
Let's keep stretching, okay?
- One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight,
- Ooh, so that's Ella!
Eight, seven, six, five,
four, three, two, one.
- Wait. Yuri too?
- Perfect!
Okay. Third one.
- Do it like this.
- Hi, Jay-jay!
Okay next!
Follow me.
- She's looking at you, man.
- She's looking at me.
Chin up!
Good job.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight.
Eight, seven, six, five, four,
three, two, and one.
Good job.
Well, everyone. I want you
to practice your serves. Okay?
I will come back later
and grade you individually.
So please make sure to help each other out.
- Can we do that?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Good.
- Hey, help me.
Help me!
- What are you laughing for?
- Start praying, Jay-jay.
You know, David, you better move to
the side. Your face is already bruised.
- How is it again?
- Like this...
- I said, move to the side.
- Listen to me.
Your hand has to be like this...
Mariano!
Do you know how to receive a serve?
What the hell?
Attack!
Hey, stop it! Just leave me alone!
- I told you to stop!
- Guys, stop it.
Guys, stop doing that to her.
Stop it already, guys.
Stop!
Stop, stop, stop.
- I told you! Stop it!
- No, don't.
Stop!
Let's see if you can catch this.
Keifer!
Jay-jay!
Hey, give her space.
- Jay-jay?
- Oh, shit.
You're all good for nothing!
Fuck you!
Jay-jay?
Please! Just calm down.
You're so hard-headed!
Just listen to what I say!
You're useless. Just die!
Your mother's not here...
Enough! Please, no more.
- No more!
- Relax. Just breathe.
- Hey, Jay-jay.
- Jay-jay.
- No more!
- Class? What happened to her?
- Miss Asunta, do you have nothing to do?
No more!
- No more!
- Jay-jay?
- Relax.
- No more!
- Jay-jay?
Relax!
Breathe, Jay-jay. Focus!
David!
- Go to the clinic, please!
- Jay-jay— breathe.
- Get a nurse!
- Please!
- Go ahead!
- Jay-jay!
Keep looking into my eyes.
Just look into my eyes.
Jay-jay!
Jay-jay— breathe.
Breathe, Jay-jay. Relax!
You don't need to punch your way
through everything.
But if you really need to, go!
Are you sure? It's really alright with you?
It's okay.
Your nose is so red!
Ouch!
I'm getting really pissed at you.
It hurts so bad!
I'm asking you a serious question.
Do it properly.
Hold still.
I cannot believe Kiko.
He won't shut up about
that new transferee, Jay-jay.
- She's not even that pretty.
- I agree.
Who's not pretty again?
Oh!
Wanna get back at them?
Why do you even care?
It's protecting one of our own.
Damn.
Give me back my bag!
Hold her still!
Hey! What are you doing with my bag?
Respect the flag!
Salute... now!
What if the chocolate melts?
Chocolate?
Did she say chocolate?
You're really testing my temper!
- Jay-jay!
- Get the chocolate!