Daemons of the Shadow Realm
All the pain I've experienced
Has traveled through my veins
And passed through my heart
By the time I've forgotten, it arrives
In my brain
I guess it's not that bad
But there's this tiny little draft
Of resentment and sadness
Just let me have this
I'm spineless
All my words and tears
And these feathers grown from my feelings
I'll put all of them on my back
Well, see you later
I'll leave it all behind here
I'm not scared
Up in the sky
See these feathers flutter in the wind
And follow along
Episode 2
Left and Right
Daemons of the Shadow Realm
Old Higashi Village Trailhead
We're at the sign 2 km from the
Waiting
Where are you now?
On my way!
I should be there soon
Keep watching me
So I can't leave
Hold me
So I won't start crying
A tailwind blows
A thread runs down my spine, and when it reaches my bloodstream
Ah
I've found wings that might let me fly again
Maybe
If you haven't left the nest yet
Then we can fly together
Next Episode
Preview
Episode 3
Dera and Hana