( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
Why are you not dating anyone?
I'm more comfortable alone.
What inconvenienced you
when you were with someone else?
Not having time for myself.
-What physical characteristics…
-Thick eyebrows.
Initiating personalized AI generation.
Optimization complete.
Congratulations on meeting Gu Yeong-il,
your custom-tailored boyfriend.
Holy crap!
Manager!
SUBSCRIBERS: 1
A MAN JUST FOR ME
I checked. There's nothing wrong.
What?
Excuse me.
I was a bit overwhelmed,
so I may not have explained it clearly.
But there's a serious defect
with his face, okay?
No, he looked handsome to me.
Whatever. Just make it again.
-Again?
-Yes.
I didn't go through over 2,000 questions
just to see that face, you know.
That man…
I mean, Gu Yeong-il…
Anyway, no.
He's been custom-tailored just for you.
We threw in everything you like.
Keep going.
I'm sure you'll change your mind.
We have to make another one.
Absolutely not.
I told you, didn't I?
You can only make number 901 once.
But this is a different case. His face--
What's all this about his face?
Is he a cyclops?
Does he have three nostrils?
It's not our fault.
That's just how your ideal man looks.
What?
No. He's not my ideal man.
That's not possible.
I took those questions seriously
and answered them sincerely.
We also took this very seriously.
Rules are rules.
No do-overs.
Are they out of their damn minds?
They must be crazy!
Consultations are not available
at this hour.
Damn it!
I mean, of all people,
why did it have to be…
That won't work.
I like you.
-I am seeing someone right now.
-All right.
Why did it have to be his face?
EPISODE 6
THE HYBRID MAN
Hello.
Hi.
Doors closing.
Doors opening.
Aren't you getting off?
You seem to value originality,
Producer Park,
but this piece just doesn't hit me.
It's unrefined,
but it has a clear theme and good artwork.
Whoever drew this
is probably an art major.
If we could refine the panel composition,
it'd be much better than it is now.
I think you're suggesting
that we should look at the potential…
Park Kyeong-nam is identical
to my ideal man?
That's the purpose of our contest.
It's also good in the long run.
There is just no way.
An author with clear pros and cons
is easier to work with…
But wait.
I didn't know he had inner double eyelids.
That's how I like them.
He's also got a straight nose.
And those lips…
Just stop it, you crazy girl.
Do you not agree?
Huh?
I do agree.
This is good.
What is up with you today?
What do you mean?
You jump every time
I catch you looking at me.
Well, that's not…
Your face was just, you know…
What about my face?
Your face is a bit…
Is it a common face?
What?
I mean, it's not one of those faces
you can see just anywhere, is it?
I don't understand--
Food is here!
Let's eat first.
Nope. No way in hell.
Aren't you going to eat?
Thank you.
Not a chance.
That one's mine.
Well, sorry about that.
Is the world pranking me right now?
Damn it!
I'm getting this one too.
Just stop.
How are you even splurging at a bookstore?
I can't buy clothes now.
Might as well get some books.
I bought stuff for my blind date,
and my credit card bills
are gonna get me evicted.
A blind date? So soon?
"So soon"? I've been single for ages.
Has it been two weeks?
Exactly. I should get back out there.
I've got two dates tomorrow.
Oh, this is great.
Why don't you look for a guy
to set me up with?
You just said you have two dates tomorrow.
Hey, don't you know people read
multiple books at the same time now?
No one goes around
seeing just one guy at a time.
Kim…
Kim Yeong-hun.
He has a girlfriend? Since when?
Anyone from Naemo?
Park Kyeong…
Huh? You're already at Park?
Seo Hyeon-uk also has a girlfriend, and…
Jeong-sik.
He has a child?
I think she goes to school.
Cute.
What? Is that it?
There isn't a single guy?
Just what I thought.
Hey.
When did everyone get snapped up?
Why so surprised?
You're not even interested in dating.
Things have been this bad for a while now.
Does that mean
all the decent men are taken,
even if I wanted to date one?
Things will be different this holiday.
Because you'll have…
Boyfriend on Demand next to you.
Fine. I'll fall for it.
Just this once.
Your engine's totally shot.
Excuse me?
I saw the smoke and followed you.
Where are you headed?
Oh, I…
I don't know.
I was just driving along this road.
Are you a tourist?
A tourist?
Follow me if you want.
"What's the most romantic first encounter
you've ever dreamed of?"
Going on a trip
and meeting a guy with a free spirit
at an unfamiliar place,
just like in a movie.
It's dangerous here at night.
-You want me to get on that?
-Then are you going to stay here?
No, thanks. I'm scared.
Before I even realized it, I got on.
This feels weird.
I'm riding behind a stranger
who looks just like Park Kyeong-nam,
and I don't even know
where we're going, so why…
Why is his back so comfy
that it feels like it was made for me?
And the wind, it's so…
It's so perfect.
And his smell…
How nice.
What is this feeling?
-Come on in.
-Yeong-il.
Hi.
Why is everything so detailed?
It feels so real.
Oh my God.
Bartender. Yeong-il's friend.
People get scared when they first see me.
I don't bite though.
I've seen you before.
You really startled me!
I'll have my usual, and for her--
Hold up. Let me guess.
-No way.
-Is it to your liking?
-Totally.
-Just holler when you're done.
What brings you here all alone?
You know,
I just needed to get my life in order.
Actually,
I recently went through a breakup.
May I ask why?
He was a cheater.
He met another woman?
Try 10,000.
Say what?
Ten thousand women.
This is the dining area.
You can have coffee in there anytime.
Thank you.
You can sleep in that room.
I'll give the owner a heads-up.
Here.
It was nice meeting you today.
Su-ji?
Hey, Su-ji!
It's been so long! How have you been?
Mind your manners.
Do you know me?
Yu-ra, a Korean tourist.
I used to.
Actually, no. I don't know you.
Looks like another weirdo has joined us.
Please don't close that door.
That door is broken, okay?
Once it closes,
it won't open.
Didn't know. Sorry, honey.
I still don't like your tone.
Hey, mister!
Who the hell brought this woman here?
I liked her best when she was Su-ji.
She's even worse than Ms. Choi.
I can't believe
he brought me to his hostel.
Wait.
He's not going to barge in here, is he?
Aren't you coming to dinner?
Coming!
Goddamn it!
This stuff is tasteless.
I'm done eating.
A tough roommate, huh?
Yeah.
Your car will be here
the morning after next.
All right. Thanks.
By the way, what do you do for a living?
I draw.
What?
You draw?
So you're an artist?
I just travel around and draw what I like.
Mi-rae.
It's your turn now.
What's your dream guy like?
My dream guy?
Gang Dong-won for me. Ju Ji-hoon for her.
For me,
it's a hybrid man.
-What's that?
-Look.
Someone calm and pure at heart,
with a genuine love for art.
I've been playing ball.
You're studying during break time?
But at the same time,
I want him to be wild and free.
What is she talking about?
What I'm saying is…
It's like when you mix a little red
into white to get this subtle…
-You get me, don't you?
-No. What is he, Santa Claus?
Anyway…
that's my dream guy.
Both…
We threw in everything you like.
They made it work?
-Hello.
-Hi.
The heart just cannot lie, you know.
It's dead silent
if you don't like a person.
-You know what I mean, right?
-What are you getting at?
I want to act cool about it,
but whenever I think about him,
my heart just goes…
And then…
You know?
Man, she's got it bad.
What kind of guy did you set her up with?
He does have a way of sucking women in
like a swamp, but…
If he hasn't contacted you in a week,
it's over.
What is your problem?
You should really try that thing.
To calm yourself down.
-Nah, I'm good.
-Try what?
-Boyfriend on Demand.
-Huh?
Do people actually do Boyfriend on Demand?
Really?
-I thought it was all just marketing.
-So did I.
I can hardly put money aside
with a tiny salary like mine.
Who could afford to subscribe to that?
A lot of my friends are subscribed to it.
No way.
No way!
It's true. Think about it.
Dating makes us spend so much money
and deal with an awful lot of stress.
It saves you all that trouble.
How great is that?
Besides, nowadays,
just by fangirling over idols,
you spend that much every month.
You do have a point.
The world is doomed. It really is.
That's a bit harsh.
Now that I think about it,
was it 500,000 won?
Right. 500,000.
Okay. I do spend that much on eating out,
watching movies,
going on trips and drives, and so on.
As I thought, no reaction at all.
Hey, you try contacting him.
Go ahead, text him.
Does he ever talk about me?
That's right.
The guy I met yesterday and Kyeong-nam
are two completely different people.
So different.
Cheers.
Aren't you bored?
Nope.
You've just been sitting here.
Anything caught your eye?
You.
This isn't a chair, you know.
Don't just sit on it.
Are you having fun now?
Yes.
Let's go.
There we go!
Chaturanga.
Head up.
Lift your body and move into downward dog.
Downward dog.
Keep your heels on the floor.
Okay.
-Back to Chaturanga.
Lift your head again,
open your heart--
Open my heart? Let me get a little closer.
No, not like that. I meant exhale.
How's that?
Let go!
Shut your mouth and breathe.
-Stop!
-You need to breathe.
-Let me go!
-Hamstring! Breathe!
What's this? You've only drawn couples.
I didn't feel like drawing other subjects.
An artist who only draws couples.
How interesting.
I don't draw just any couple I see.
I have standards.
Those who don't doubt the future
and focus on the love in front of them.
That's who I draw.
Why is that?
I don't know.
Because it's sad when love changes.
That must be why I record them.
Let's go back.
The sun's going to set soon.
What to do?
Huh?
I wasn't going to say anything,
but I'll be honest with you.
About what?
I think we're lost.
What now?
Stop messing with me.
I know you know the way.
I'm serious.
Yu-ra told me that a couple of newlyweds
went missing around here recently.
What's your favorite movie genre?
HORROR (OCCULT HORROR ESPECIALLY!)
Those bastards.
I said I liked to watch it,
not experience it!
I don't like it here, okay? I hate it.
Let's go…
It's the owner's dog.
Oh, I see.
Are you that scared?
No, well… just a little?
I guess it is a bit dark.
Not anymore.
Keep going.
I'm sure you'll change your mind.
Calm down.
Calm down, for crying out loud!
Doors closing.
Doors opening.
Excuse me. Coming through.
Sorry. Excuse me.
Sorry about that. I'm sorry.
Doors closing.
Seo Mi-rae, come to my office.
Hey, Kyeong-nam, you too.
Did you talk to Yun Song?
Sorry? About what?
Kyeong-nam said he told you.
Hwany will be doing
the home appliance commercial.
You didn't tell her?
I'm sorry, sir. I'll tell her right away.
Too late now! She would go berserk and…
I can't even…
That's that. You're supposed to attend
the BCF with Yun Song, aren't you?
Take Kyeong-nam and Hwany with you.
-What?
-I called you here to tell you that.
Both of them were nominated this time.
-Hwany too?
-That's right.
And I get the feeling
at least one of them will win something.
So take good care of your authors.
Understand?
Yes, sir.
So…
Please tell Ms. Yun about it.
She won't take it well.
Don't worry. I'll try to soften the blow.
Ms. Seo.
Yes?
Why do you do that?
What… do you mean?
You're avoiding me
when I'm the one who got rejected.
I never did that. When did I do that?
I know you're uncomfortable around me,
but could you try not to show it?
This is upsetting for me as well.
Hey, are you insane?
Why did that go to him?
Well, the advertiser requested it.
They chose to deliver their ads
with his shitty drawings and not mine?
Have they gone cuckoo?
Ms. Yun,
I'll make sure to find you a better ad--
She hung up on me.
God, this is so annoying!
You all know
IG is the best brand there is.
Coming soon,
PlanC and IG's collab webtoon.
I'll do my best!
Let's make PlanC number one!
"Number one"?
Why, that little prick…
KOREAN BEEF INTESTINES
-Cheers!
I'm so sick of greasy food
from all my blind dates.
That's more like it.
Did your dates go well?
It was a disaster.
Two dates in one day was a stretch.
Their paths crossed, and somehow,
my dates ran into each other.
I knew you were going to mess up.
But the thing is, I went on another date
a few days after that.
The nerve of that guy!
He kept pushing me about whether my salary
started with a three or a four.
Wow.
How the hell is that any of his business?
Do you know what he texted me
the next day?
"I was deeply moved by your story
of trying to find your true self."
"I hope you find the right person."
Wow.
It was like an HR text to a candidate
who failed a job interview.
And I never signed up for an interview!
Are you kidding me?
Jeez, then just stop
going on those blind dates.
All they do is make you mad.
You also saw for yourself last time.
There are no decent men left out there.
You and I are the birds
that overslept way too much.
We have to start foraging for crumbs
that the early birds left behind.
Do we really have to stoop
to looking for crumbs?
Hey.
Are you trying to say
that I'm obsessed with men?
Hey, that's not what I meant.
Then what did you mean?
"Can you not live without men?
I'm sick of all your men talk."
That's it, no?
Hey, it's only because
that's all you've been talking about.
And you've never talked to me about men?
What about that guy from your office?
Seriously? He's just one of my colleagues.
You've been talking about him
an awful lot these last few months.
What? I have not!
I mean, definitely not that much.
I was gonna wait until you told me first,
but I can't do this anymore.
You like him, don't you?
Hey, are you insane? No, I don't!
It's the other way around.
The other way around? What does that mean?
Well,
he asked me out.
Hey!
Why are you dropping this bomb on me now?
When was this?
It's been a while,
and I already turned him down.
That can't be!
Why do you keep saying that?
Something's not right.
Show me a picture of that guy.
I don't have one. He's not on Instagram.
He doesn't even have a profile picture.
Can I please borrow your phone?
I really need to keep filming.
Let's see.
-Give it.
-Here.
What the heck?
What?
-He's definitely not your type.
-What?
He is good-looking,
but not Seo Mi-rae's type.
You're into guys who are laid-back.
This guy looks too uptight.
Really?
Right?
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
Cheers!
Cheers.
I knew it.
He's not the one.
You're here.
Yes.
Well…
Your hair.
It must've gotten there
while I was picking this up for Ms. Yun.
Congratulations in advance.
She might not get it,
but I got this just in case she does.
I hope there's good news for Hwany too.
I hope so too.
Oh…
Ms. Seo?
About what I said last time…
Don't worry about it too much.
I'm fine.
Let's head in.
We will now begin the awards ceremony
for the 27th Busan Comics Festival!
There is no greater honor
than earning the fans' love.
In that sense,
this is a very meaningful award.
With an overwhelming number of fan votes,
the Popularity Award goes to…
Congratulations.
Yun Song, author of The Man to Know.
Congratulations!
-Congratulations!
-Thank you.
…a romance between a chaebol heir
and a hotelier.
With its charming characters
and an engaging plot,
it has received a lot of love…
Congratulations.
Congratulations!
POPULARITY AWARD
YUN SONG, THE MAN TO KNOW
All right.
For a while now,
the Popularity Award
is all you've been giving me.
I guess I should be thanking you
for giving me anything at all, right?
But if you give me this award again
next year,
I'm seriously going to stop coming.
I'm just kidding. Oh my God!
Okay.
Thank you.
Next, for bringing a breath of fresh air
into the comics industry,
the New Artist Award goes to…
Congratulations, Hwasubun.
Congratulations.
Not Okay, a story about student athletes
who fall into a dungeon in another world,
was praised for its cheeky perspective
and bold expressiveness.
Congratulations!
Moving on.
-It's okay.
-This one's for Webtoon of the Year.
Only one will rise above the competition
to claim this honor.
Which one will it be?
I will now announce the winner
of Webtoon of the Year.
The winner of Webtoon of the Year
at the 27th Busan Comics Festival is…
Hwany's PlanC. Congratulations!
Congratulations!
It's really me?
PlanC is a black comedy about young people
chasing a new life in the countryside,
drawn into a mysterious incident.
With its solid direction, clear theme,
and high-quality plot,
it has captivated
readers and critics alike.
Congratulations.
Congratulations on your award!
Thank you.
I had no idea I'd be presented
such a big award, so--
You're so handsome!
Thank you.
You call that handsome?
I don't know what to say.
Don't cry!
Kyeong-nam, who has helped me a lot
since the very start,
Director Hwang Byeong-hak,
Producer Cho Min-seok,
who was my editor for a long time,
and everyone else who…
I'm seriously ticked off.
…I am grateful.
I'd like to share this award
with all of you.
Thank you!
You deserve it!
Let me go!
You came all this way,
and this is how you act?
Hey, I said no!
Seriously.
Hey.
I didn't come all the way here
to be used as a prop.
Thank you! Yes.
How could you put it that way?
He works on the same platform as you.
Why can't you just congratulate him?
When are you ever going to grow up?
Last time, you asked me
if I was going to let a kid claw his way
onto the same day as me.
Come on, let's just go inside.
-Let go.
-Please!
Let go of me. I mean it!
Seo Mi-rae!
Are you okay?
Yes. I'm okay.
Ms. Yun.
Why are you out here? Let's go inside.
This is so annoying, seriously.
It's all thanks to you guys. Thank you!
-The drink hits different tonight.
-Congratulations!
What? Thank you, guys!
Flowers, really? You keep it.
Let's take a picture.
-Sure!
-Sounds good.
Okay. One, two…
-Cheers!
-Congratulations.
Congratulations!
Hey, you said
you couldn't eat uncooked food.
I'm gonna start trying it today.
Yeah?
Ms. Yun.
I would love to treat you today.
Let's grab some whiskey.
-Wow!
-You're the man!
Something super expensive?
Of course!
All right!
I need to take this.
Hello?
What is this? How did you know to call me?
We're having an after-party right now.
Wow, thank you. I appreciate it.
Let's grab a meal when I'm in Seoul.
Yes, Mr. Cho. Have a good night!
Mr. Cho?
Producer Cho called you?
Give me your phone.
Why? What's this about?
Damn it, seriously.
I can't believe this.
The person you have dialed is…
Why is it that every time I call him,
it doesn't go through?
He must be busy right now.
Ms. Yun, calm down for a second.
Hey.
Why does that bastard call you
and act all nice to you
but leave my calls unanswered for months?
How on earth would I know that?
Why did he block me
but stay in touch with you?
Maybe you were a fucking pain in the ass!
What?
That's not what I…
-Ms. Yun.
-Get a load of this guy.
I've had enough of your shit.
Hey, you're scheming with Cho
to get back at me, aren't you?
I heard he went to Director Hwang
and made a fuss
about how he was treating us differently.
Did you ask to have your upload day moved
so you can screw me over?
That's got nothing to do with this!
That's not true, Ms. Yun.
Mr. Hwang decides
matters regarding releases, after all.
This is hilarious. Hey, then did you…
No, wait.
I honestly wasn't going to bring this up.
What?
Are you not over me yet?
When Cho got us a studio in Hapjeong-dong,
you were the one who secretly left snacks
in front of my room.
I saw you run away to the basement
after leaving them several times.
Hold it right there. That was…
Hey, you just got rejected, that's all.
Did you really have to hold a grudge
and screw me over?
That's so petty of you.
-Not true.
-What? Did Cho tell you?
That I threw it all out
without even trying it?
Unbelievable.
Those…
Those were…
What?
Those were meant for So-yeong!
Who is So-yeong?
Your assistant?
Ms. Yun? We get it for now.
It's spilling over.
Hang on. I need to go to the bathroom.
Let her through.
What just happened?
You know, I'm not the type
to make things up in my head.
Given the situation back then,
this misunderstanding was inevitable.
I'll bet anyone would have thought
the same.
-Totally.
-Of course.
I'm really not like that. Okay?
I have a boyfriend.
I have a boyfriend!
-Okay.
-She has a boyfriend.
This is ridiculous.
-We didn't know that.
-What do we do?
Good God…
Just a little more. Just over there.
Oh God!
God, you're killing me.
JJONG
Yes. I'm answering for Ms. Yun.
Did something happen to Song?
She received an award
and got drunk at the after-party.
But she's somewhere safe now?
Yes. She's back in her room, sleeping.
So you brought her back. Thank you.
Sure. But who am I speaking to?
Oh, I didn't even introduce myself.
I'm Song's boyfriend.
What?
I'm the person who's dating Song.
Oh my.
I'm sorry.
I didn't think you'd be her boyfriend.
It's been a while,
but I guess she hasn't told anyone yet.
Anyway, thank you for today.
No problem. Good night.
So she was telling the truth
about having a boyfriend?
Did you put her to bed?
You are coming back, right?
We're going for round two!
I'm coming over now.
Mr. Park.
How long have you been close with Hwany?
-Who says we're close?
-What?
You're so funny!
We are close.
This guy can't live without me.
I wouldn't say that.
JI-YEON
Business trip's boring, huh?
Want to hear how my blind date went?
She just won't stop.
Nope.
Hey, I'll give you ten seconds.
Out with it.
Come on. Ten seconds is too short.
What?
How did…
I got your car fixed,
so I wanted to take you for a drive.
Where are you?
I can't go right now.
Why is that?
I hear waves.
I'm also at the beach right now.
I'll head over to you, then.
And how are you gonna do that?
Why do you think I can't?
How would he come here?
Who does he think he's kidding?
You actually made it?
So warm.
What are you doing here?
Hello?
Oh God! That hurts.
My mom wanted me to become a doctor
ever since I was little.
I somehow managed to get through division,
but I got stuck at fractions.
This is going to sting. There.
Goodness, it's okay. It's only a dream.
Hey, you!
Who is this hottie?
Nice.
Get a grip, will you?
This is such a weird dream.
-What?
-This has to be a dream.
-Isn't this a dream?
-What now?
-It actually hurts.
-Move.
Who the heck is this?
Hand over the paper in the drawer,
and I'll spare your life.
Yeah. I get what's going on here.
I'm glad you catch on quickly.
That's strange.
Someone should be here to save me by now.
-Wait. Unhand me!
-Hello?
Is my boyfriend out there?
My lady!
You scoundrel!
Dolsoe?
My lady! You bastard!
-Dolsoe!
-What the…
Yes!
Subtitle translation by: Daham Yoon