A triple-flower mark?
Li Jie's body
was also transformed
from the six-eyed butterfly.
Its strength reached
the triple-flower level long ago.
But since he had
no sacred power of his own,
the flower mark never appeared.
Now that my soul
has fused with his body,
the triple-flower mark
naturally reveals itself.
Well?
Do you still think I'm insignificant now?
Just as I thought.
Looks like in all those rewinds,
I never showed you the triple-flower mark.
That's why you couldn't
withstand my strike.
Well?
Do you still think you're a deity now?
What destroys a deity
is not a devil,
but the deity's own arrogance.
Your body has reached its limit.
This is the last rewind.
I fought so hard to get here.
I won't allow myself to lose to you.
This time,
I will succeed.
See?
I succeeded.
Do you know why
I couldn't dodge your blade?
Because I didn't want to.
Break!
Dragon hearts as one,
all to source return, all barriers break.
It's raining!
The drought is finally over.
Luo'an is finally saved!
I did it.
Wu.
Ji.
I did it.
Wu?
This is for you.
I'm sorry for staining
your manuscript.
Long, I…
I promise I'll come back.
Oh, right.
I've asked my weasel brothers
to look after you.
If anyone dares hurt you,
go ask them for help.
I… I want to use this brush
to write your story.
When you come back next time,
I'll… I'll let you read it.
Do you like it?
You… You didn't make this
with your own fur, did you?
Of course not.
I was the one
who forced the rain
to fall with demon magic.
Why didn't I die?
Some force even I do not know of
was protecting you.
But Ji Ling…
People rarely get to have it both ways.
He couldn't bear to let you die,
but he also had to destroy Jiu Ying.
Caught in that dilemma,
he suffered deeply.
You destroyed the Dragon Deity's Power
and ruined the mission
to which he'd devoted a century.
And then he watched
your body and spirit vanish.
That overwhelming despair and loneliness
snuffed out the last bit of hope
in his heart.
Thus,
Lonescale consumed him.
Lonescale lied to me.
He said Ji Ling was a kind person.
He said he chose to help me
because he wanted to save Ji Ling too.
I never thought it'd kill Ji Ling instead.
You underestimated
how much you meant to him.
You wanted him to live
and yourself to die.
He wanted the opposite.
Lonescale can rewind time
and peer into the past and future.
How could he not have known
how it would end?
He knew everything all along,
and that was exactly why
he chose to help you.
From beginning to end,
he had only one goal.
To consume Ji Ling completely.
I ruined your plan.
You spent over 100 years
playing the Dragon Deity,
alone and in pain,
all just so you could reach
that very ending.
But I couldn't stand by and watch you die.
You shouldn't have existed in this world
just to sacrifice yourself.
That would've been too cruel to you.
I never thought
it would turn out like this.
Ji Ling,
can you hear me?
Please wake up.
Back then, I didn't understand
why so many demons wanted
to wear
human skin
and become human.
A demon's tears are fake.
They cry just to look more human.
I don't understand
why so many demons
want to wear human skin
and become human.
But now I do.
I want to be with you
and live as the most ordinary of people,
beginning work at sunrise
and resting at sunset,
walking hand in hand
through the streets,
and falling asleep
in each other's arms at night.
Ji Ling has been consumed by Lonescale
and remains unconscious.
Bai Ze told us to go
to Chi Wen in the Dragon Abyss.
He may have a way to save him.
But without the last share
of the Dragon Deity's Power,
I can't become a dragon.
When I get there,
I don't know how I'll face my brother.
Whether you become a dragon or not,
you are still you,
Wu Shiguang.
You taught me in the Star Stone illusion
that who we are
has nothing to do
with background or bloodline.
What matters more is whom we love
and what we choose to protect.
Besides, fortune and misfortune
go hand in hand.
Without the last share
of the Dragon Deity's Power,
you will no longer
be able to kill Chi Wen,
and Jiu Ying
will stop trying to possess you.
But if I can't become a dragon,
I can't destroy the Oracle Stone.
When the next full moon comes,
you'll be forced back
to the Formless Moon.
- I'm afraid…
- It's all right.
There's still time.
Besides,
I can sever my tail.
That's the worst possible choice.
No, it isn't.
I'm not like Xiaowei.
I still have you.
What do you think of this color?
What do you think?
Mortal couples bind
strands of their hair together.
At first,
I didn't understand what it meant.
I only wanted a good omen.
But when I braided
your hair together with mine,
I realized that once
hair strands are entwined,
unless they break,
they are
almost impossible to part.
You and I are the same.
We were fated to be entangled long ago.
I will protect you no matter what
and never fail this vow
sealed by our bound hair.
You lied to me.
I didn't.
I truly hoped you'd be able to save him.
What nurtured
that dragon scale into a demon
was not only his loneliness
but also his kindness.
Then take me back again.
I want to save him.
It's useless.
He remains unconscious
because his consciousness
has returned to the past.
He's trapped in that part of his past
that came to haunt him.
Haunt him?
It's the old days before I was born.
Then take me there.
No matter how far back it is,
I'm not afraid.
I can take it.
I know you can.
And I can take you there
so you can see why he became so lonely.
But…
But what?
But that was more than 100 years ago.
Far too long ago.
No power can change it.
So you won't be able to rewind time
again and again like you did before
to alter the past.
Besides, you did not
exist there.
Back then, there was no Lu Wuyi
by Ji Ling's side.
You can only be a silent observer,
unable to interfere in any way.
Do you still want to go?
This story
is far too long.
Even a day and a night wouldn't be enough.
When we return from Luo'an,
I'll tell it to you slowly.
I do.
I want to know
his past.
Yuan Xizai!
A HUNDRED AND FIFTY YEARS AGO
Xizai.
Xizai? Xizai!
Xizai. Xizai!
Save him.
Quick, save him!
Save him!
Where's your magic?
Why don't you have any magic?
Hurry up and heal him.
Do it! Hurry! Save him!
Save him!
Wuhuo…
Save my brother, and I'll let you go.
It's almost New Year's Eve.
Everyone, sort through
your things and throw out
what you don't need.
Sweep away the dust and grime,
say goodbye to the old,
and welcome the new!
I don't want to see you
live your whole life timid and weak,
bullied by others.
Take the Dragon Marrow
and become
a demon hunter like me.
But I don't want to be a demon hunter.
I'm… I'm afraid of demons.
Commander Yuan.
YE DAOXUAN, ATTENDANT
These were all Xizai's belongings.
Throw them away.
All right. That might be for the best.
Master Daoxuan.
The New Year's coming.
I've brought you something delicious.
Maybe it'll help you
recover your powers.
Why do you have it?
Let go. This isn't yours.
It was all your fault.
You wouldn't save my brother,
so he died.
Why?
Why wouldn't you save him?
Since you wouldn't save him,
you can die too!
Wuhuo,
I'm afraid of demons.
What… What kind of demon trick is this?
I didn't do anything.
I don't know any demon tricks.
Did you think that if you took this form,
I wouldn't have the heart to kill you?
- Wuhuo!
- Take it.
- Swallow it!
- No!
Swallow it!
Give one to Xizai too. Here.
- I've already eaten, Wuhuo.
- I don't care.
Mother made them.
Here. Eat one.
I've eaten.
Look how thin you are. Eat more.
Go on. Eat.
Eat more.
Grow stronger, just like your brother.
Wuhuo, you're amazing.
Commander Yuan, I found it.
It turns out the first skin a demon wears
to take human form
uses blood as its medium.
If its blood stains an object
laden with intense emotion,
the demon will naturally
take on the appearance
of that object's owner.
Commander Yuan,
I thought you were looking up
remedies for the Wasting Sickness.
Turns out it was this.
How have you been feeling lately?
Who would've thought the Meteor Blast
would cause the Wasting Sickness?
I'm human now.
It's so inconvenient not having claws.
I can't even leave marks.
Thank you.
Why do you sound like you're crying?
Are… Are you sad?
I don't know whether I'm sad
or happy.
I… I think I understand.
Did I become someone
you knew?
Was that person
very important to you?
Father, Mother!
Father! Father?
- Mother…
- Wuhuo,
it was the wolf demons.
Take care of your little brother.
And…
don't tell him the truth.
Xizai is timid.
Wuhuo, why does it smell
so strongly of blood?
It was rare for me to come home,
so Father caught two wild chickens
and stewed them for me.
Father, Mother, and I talked it over.
You should take the Dragon Marrow
and become
a demon hunter like me.
No!
Father and Mother would never agree to it!
Even healthy, strong people
often die after swallowing Dragon Marrow.
Wuhuo,
I'll die!
Those were greedy fools
who swallowed it recklessly
just to gain sacred power.
The Shilin Sect tested my constitution.
You're like me.
You'll be fine.
But I don't want to be a demon hunter.
I'm afraid of demons.
If you're this cowardly,
how will you survive
in this chaotic world?
I never wanted to survive.
I've already dragged our family down.
Wuhuo,
just let me die.
All right?
No need to be scared.
They're firecrackers we set off
to celebrate New Year's Eve.
What is New Year's Eve?
New Year's Eve…
Xizai, do you hear that?
They're setting off firecrackers
and doing the dragon dance.
I hear it.
Look.
How lively it is.
Father, Mother!
- Your brother is here.
- Wuhuo.
- Father, Mother.
- You're here, Wuhuo.
You've grown sturdier.
- We missed you.
- I missed you too.
Xizai, you've gotten so tall.
Your mother made dumplings.
- Mother made dumplings?
- Here.
- Try it.
- Eat, Wuhuo.
They're still hot.
- Delicious.
- You like it?
Give one to Xizai too.
I've already eaten, Wuhuo.
I don't care.
- You're too thin.
- I've eaten.
Here. Eat one.
Go on. Eat.
There's plenty more.
New Year's Eve
is the most beautiful
and happiest day in the human world.
Is this for me?
It is.
Eat.
May you be free of misfortune
in the coming year.
Here. You eat some too.
I've gotten grease all over your hands.
It's all right. I'll wash them for you.
You're a little fox.
How can you not have fur?
A bald fox will get laughed at.
But my eyes can't see,
so I don't know
if I've dressed you up nicely.
As for your blade wound,
I can't mend that yet.
I am a nameless little fox.
But my little fox can't go without a name.
Foxes
usually go "awoo, awoo."
Why don't I call you
Wu?
Wu!
Awoo!
You don't have eyes either?
What's wrong?
What's going on?
Hey, stop.
It's all right.
Here.
Calm down. There, there.
There, there.
I'm in so much pain.
It hurts so much.
Father, Mother,
take me with you.
Take me with you.
It's all right.
You're awake. Are you all right now?
What are you doing?
Don't take it away!
It's the only company I have!
Can you give it back to me?
Please give Wu back!
Have you left?
Eyes?
You even stitched up the torn part.
It's my return gift for last night.
You know how to sew?
My family was poor.
My worn-out clothes would be passed down
to my younger brother.
The same piece of clothing
would get patched over and over again.
I did all the mending.
Then why did you
join the Shilin Sect?
Who took care of your brother?
My parents were poor,
and I couldn't read either.
My brother
was sickly,
and his treatment cost a lot of money.
They said if a Shilin Sect hunter
died fighting demons, the compensation
would be enough to feed
a poor family for ten years.
So I joined.
What a pity.
No amount of money means
anything to me now.
I don't have any family
left to care for now.
I…
I didn't mean to let your brother die.
I was just an ordinary fox.
I didn't know any magic at all.
By the time I found you and your brother,
the power Master Dragon Deity gave me
had already been used up.
I don't have any family either,
but I know losing family
must hurt terribly.
How could you not have any family?
Aren't foxes
born in litters?
Maybe it was because I was born blind.
My family abandoned me in a cave
and left me to fend for myself.
I couldn't save your brother.
How about I give you another brother?
From now on,
I'll be your younger brother.
The war between humans and demons
is growing worse.
All beings suffer.
To end this war
and restore peace to the world,
there is a mission
certain to end in death.
Are you willing to do it?
If you are,
swallow this dragon scale.
I'm already as good as dead.
Of course I'm willing.
What are you doing?
I owe you a life.
I'm paying it back.
It hurts!