Bowen,
how long are you going to hide it from me?
What do you mean?
That day when Zhou Rong came to our house,
I saw everything from the stairs—
he was going to pull out a gun
to kill you.
I almost rushed in
to fight them.
This is what they call "brothers are
the best partners in a fight."
My love for you wasn't in vain.
Our parents passed away early.
You raised me alone.
You earned our family's success today
by risking your life
and fighting for it
through thick and thin.
I know you don't want me
to be like you.
You want me to succeed in my studies.
All my efforts
are for this goal.
And my painstaking efforts
haven't gone to waste.
Yangyang,
when you finish your studies,
all the wealth I've built
will be yours.
By then, you'll have both a diploma
and wealth.
Flocks of girls
will be chasing after you.
Bowen, I don't need any of that.
But I can't live without you.
You are the only family
I have in this world.
Mr. Rong came to meet you that day
because the police were investigating
Lu Zheng's case, right?
On his birthday,
I heard everything
you guys said
in the wine cellar.
I'm afraid... I'm afraid
the police will trace it to you,
Bowen!
Don't worry.
There is nothing in Sanjiangkou
that I, your brother, can't handle.
Your mission right now
is to focus on applying for college.
And then,
go abroad
and find someone with a high IQ
to improve
our Lang family's genes.
Someone with a low IQ won't do.
[Born with Luck]
[Episode 12]
Ren!
What's up so early?
You're looking for Yibo?
He's not with me.
Okay.
Hu Jianren is already downstairs.
Zhou Rong wanted to see me
and sent him to pick me up in person.
Can we get through this?
Take it.
Don't hang up.
If I say,
"I don't know anything about it.
Please go ask Yibo,"
call the police immediately.
I know Zhou Rong so well.
This is way too risky.
Is there any other way?
If he dares to do anything to you,
I'll fight him to the bitter end.
I'm coming.
Ren, sorry to have kept you waiting.
[Waiting]
[Jiafu Digital Store]
Come in.
Welcome.
Mr. Rong.
Let me introduce a new friend to you.
Come on.
Sit down.
Mr. Rong told you to sit down.
I...
Don't be afraid. Just sit down.
Sit.
Take your seat.
Don't be afraid.
As long as you tell the truth,
there won't be any danger.
I promise I will tell the truth.
I heard
that the police
went to ask you about it again.
Recall carefully
what they asked.
Don't leave out any details.
I... I...
Based on the latest information
we have,
Captain Ye did go to Fenglinwan
before the accident.
We asked Lu Yibo.
He said that
when Captain Ye went to meet him,
he also asked about this watch.
So,
Captain Ye also noticed
something fishy about this watch.
[Checked the cases handled by Lu Zheng]
[Drunk driving inspection] [Murdered]
Could it be related to Chief Lu's death?
It can't be verified yet.
[Waiting] [Speaker]
I explained the jewelry thing clearly.
But they kept asking
if Captain Ye had been to Fenglinwan
before the accident.
What did you say then?
I didn't know
what they wanted.
So when I was at the police station,
I didn't say he had been here.
I said I didn't know.
That's all?
Think again.
The watch.
About the watch.
What watch?
They a-asked about the watch
that Bowen gave to Yibo.
But this watch was
not purchased by Lu Yibo himself.
It was Lang Bowen
[Zhou Rong] [Hu Jianren] [Lang Bowen]
who lost it to him when they were
playing a game.
Then it might be
related to Lang Bowen.
Captain Wang and I
deduced the same thing.
However,
Lu Yibo told us
that Lang Bowen lost this watch
[Zhou Rong] [Hu Jianren] [Lang Bowen]
to him a year ago.
A year ago,
Chief Lu was still alive.
Yeah.
So now all of this
is pointing to Lu Yibo again.
[General Manager of Fenglinwan Hotel]
[PR Manager of Fenglinwan Nightclub]
It's so important,
and you are only telling me now?
Mr. Rong.
Yibo is actually
very loyal to you.
If he's so loyal,
why didn't he tell us earlier?
I don't know anything.
Please go ask Yibo.
[Chief Zhang Yi'ang
of the Municipal Bureau]
It's Lu Yibo.
Hello?
Chief Zhang,
this is Lu Yibo speaking.
I want to confess to you.
Good.
What do you want to confess?
Go ahead.
I confess to you.
I'll tell you.
Confess what? I'm listening.
I'll tell you everything.
I know.
Take your time.
The night Lu Zheng died,
Bowen was wearing that watch.
Later, he gave it to Yibo.
Yibo was afraid of being implicated,
so he asked me to throw the watch away.
I didn't dare to tell you.
Mr. Rong,
I'll go bring Lu Yibo here.
If you can't do it,
I will.
Mr. Rong!
You can't do this to Yibo.
Yibo already confessed
that before Lu Zheng died,
Bowen had already given him the watch.
What do you mean?
Y-Yibo knew he had let you down before,
Mr. Rong,
so he took it all on himself.
The police won't be able
to trace it to Bowen
or to you.
Even if they trace it to you,
he has already taken the fall for you.
Verify this matter
with that bastard.
Yes.
Hello?
[Chief Zhang Yi'ang
of the Municipal Bureau]
Hello?
What's this all about?
Is he playing with us?
[Chief Zhang Yi'ang
of the Municipal Bureau]
Ren.
What are you doing here?
I...
I've always wanted to learn photography.
So I came to buy some gear.
I have a question for you.
Please go ahead.
Who is it?
Nobody.
Take it out.
Really, it's nobody.
[Chief Zhang Yi'ang
of the Municipal Bureau]
I don't know why
he's calling me.
You tailed us here.
Ren,
it's not what you think.
It really isn't.
Mr. Lu,
what do you
mean by this?
Ren,
please don't talk like that.
You can either hit me or scold me.
You being this polite
scares me.
Mr. Lu.
Ren, Ren.
You...
You can interrogate me inside.
Let's go inside to talk.
If you think I'm lying,
you can kill me inside,
and no one will see it, right?
Let's go inside and talk.
Ren,
let's g-go inside.
Come on.
After you.
Stay outside.
Qi came over today,
and you knew
what Mr. Rong wanted to ask her,
so you followed her.
If anything happened to Qi,
you'd call the police,
right?
Mr. Rong hates people
who are disloyal to him the most.
Ren.
As long as you don't tell Mr. Rong,
I'll do anything you ask.
I'm afraid of Mr. Rong, too.
I don't dare to hide it from him.
Ren,
[Security Office Management System]
the God of Wealth statue
you got for Mr. Rong
wasn't that price, right?
Zheng Yongbing is
a regular at Fenglinwan.
These past couple of years,
you've handled everything big or small
in Rongcheng.
You must've raked in a lot of money.
Mr. Rong hates people
who are disloyal to him the most.
Are you threatening me?
How would I have that audacity?
Ren,
the police already know about this.
Really?
T-There's another thing
I haven't dared to report to Mr. Rong.
Out with it!
On the night Ye Jian died,
he actually came to see me.
Apparently,
Lu Yibo's psychological defense
has collapsed.
If he calls again,
he will definitely confess everything.
Why hasn't he called yet?
[Lu Yibo]
Hello?
Chief Zhang,
sorry,
I was drunk just now.
You were drunk?
Is something bothering you?
You guys have been coming
too often lately.
Under too much stress,
I just spoke out of turn.
It's okay now, Chief Zhang.
Lu Yibo, don't talk.
Don't talk.
Listen to me.
Cooperating with the police
is your only way out now.
I'll hang up.
You shouldn't have stopped him
from talking.
He didn't confess yet,
and you just hung up?
He's a drunkard
full of nonsense.
I'm not giving him another chance.
We will investigate it ourselves.
Chief Zhang,
so charismatic.
There must be
some shady business going on.
How should we
investigate Lu Yibo?
I believe we can do it.
What?
Wait,
you even eat medicine?
Who are you talking to?
I'm talking to the dog.
Mr. Rong, I'm talking to it.
I'm scolding the dog.
I'm scolding the dog, Mr. Rong.
Take it to have some water.
So Lu Yibo said
that night, Ye Jian
just asked him about the watch?
That's what he said.
Do you think this has
anything to do with Ye's death?
My first instinct
was definitely still Bowen.
But it doesn't seem like him.
If it really were him,
he wouldn't have
a reason to swear at gunpoint.
What about Lu Yibo?
Look at what a coward he is.
He wouldn't dare.
I mean, about Lu Yibo,
what should we do?
The police are investigating him now.
That means
they haven't found anything on us.
If we do something to him,
we're simply asking for trouble.
Mr. Rong,
forgive me for speaking out of turn,
but I feel like
ever since Ye died,
things have gotten
more and more complicated.
We really need to be careful.
We do need to be careful.
You tell me what to do, and I'll do it.
You go first.
Tell Bowen to come over here.
Okay.
Didn't we already
go through the Taobao records once again?
What else are you looking for?
I want to know why Captain Ye
[Vintage square student
male waterproof digital watch]
investigated this watch.
Captain Ye grew up with them.
He might have
seen this watch before.
Then why did he go to Fenglinwan?
How should I know?
Why did he go to Fenglinwan?
Why did he go?
Captain Ye
also came to review files yesterday?
Yes.
What kind of cases were they?
Cases that Chief Lu was involved in
the year before he passed away.
They are all right here.
Why did he want to check the files?
Because he found something.
[File Management System
of Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau]
What did he find?
So what did he find?
What exactly did he find?
[Anzhi Road, Sanjiangkou City,
Ping'an Province]
I remember Captain Ye
asked me to enlarge and enhance
an image back then.
Zhang, I'm sending you a picture.
Enlarge it and make it clear.
It seems to be just this one.
Where is the image?
Let me look for it.
The truth is about to come out.
Sorry.
[Century Otto]
Bowen!
Stop yelling.
Let me finish this game.
Dear Mr. Botu Lang,
Reply:
NHHU University
Admission Notice.
I know you are a straight-A student.
Stop showing off before me.
The Senate of NHHU
University
has offered you
the opportunity
to pursue...
Alright, I know you're good at English.
Happy now?
Bowen.
Lang Bowen!
I've been accepted for a master's program
at a foreign university!
Pardon?
I've been admitted to a foreign university
for a master's program.
Which university?
Southern New Hampshire
Mountain University.
You,
Lang Botu,
got admitted to an American university?
You don't believe it?
Could I be lying to you,
Bowen?
Bowen.
I'm okay.
I'm just too happy.
You...
You really brought honor
to our Lang family! I...
And I didn't fail
our parents' entrustment.
I didn't lead you astray.
Hello.
[Century Otto]
We're looking for Mr. Lang Bowen.
Mr. Lang?
Do you have an appointment?
He's here, isn't he?
Whether he's here or not,
Mr. Lang doesn't see guests
without an appointment.
Hello,
I am the Deputy Chief
of Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau.
We need to ask Mr. Lang some questions.
Could you set up an appointment for me?
Come on, you're a grown man.
I'm just happy.
Let's go to the cemetery.
Let's go to the cemetery right now.
We must tell
this good news to Mom and Dad in person.
Okay.
Hear me out first.
Have someone
drive the car to the front immediately.
What?
Tell whoever is looking for me today
to get lost.
Mr. Lang, it's the police.
Call him again.
Well, how about this?
Tell him
that if he's really busy,
we'll meet at the Public Security Bureau.
Lili,
well,
I'll get changed myself today.
And go help me
order 2 wreaths.
Get the most beautiful ones.
And write on the couplet:
Lang Bowen fulfilled his mission.
Lang Botu brought honor to the family.
How nice.
Okay, Mr. Lang.
I'll go right now.
Get me the most beautiful ones,
as beautiful as you.
Didn't I tell them to get lost?
Listen to me...
Why didn't you say it earlier?
Let them come up.
Lili,
don't go buy the wreaths yet.
First, go to the elevator
and pick up some friends for me.
What's up, Bowen?
Nothing.
You... You should also go home
to change into something more formal.
We'll go see Mom and Dad later.
After I'm done here,
I'll go back and pick you up.
[Century Otto]
This way, please.
This way.
Hello, Chief Zhang.
Hello, officers.
You're Lang Bowen's younger brother,
Lang Botu, right?
Yes.
My brother is in his office
waiting for you all.
Okay.
We'll go meet him.
Did you go
to Zhou Rong's birthday party
a while ago?
I went to attend
Mr. Rong's birthday party with my brother.
Do you know what your brother was doing
the next night?
Do you mean
the night Mr. Ye
had the accident?
Yes.
You remember it quite clearly.
After all, Mr. Ye was
also like a nice brother to me.
Of course I remember.
Then what was your brother doing
the next night?
L-Let me think.
Go ahead and think.
Socializing,
working overtime,
drinking, going home,
or
hanging out for fun?
Chief Zhang,
what were you doing that night?
Drunk driving.
The citywide DUI crackdown.
Yes, the citywide...
You see,
it's been so long.
Didn't you also need time to recall?
It's human nature.
Have you recalled it now?
That night,
my brother went back home quite early.
He was drunk.
And he didn't drive.
Otherwise, when you checked for DUI,
you'd definitely have caught him.
Yangyang.
Who is Yangyang?
My nickname is Yangyang.
Chief Zhang!
Aren't you here for me?
Why are you standing there chatting?
We ran into each other.
-Chief Zhang, is there anything else?
-Go home, Yangyang.
No, nothing.
Chief Zhang!
Here we meet again.
Yes.
I could've welcomed you downstairs if you
had told me about your visit earlier.
It's fine.
Sorry for the poor reception.
Captain Wang.
-Mr. Lang.
-Officer...
Does this watch look familiar?
It's my watch.
Why are the police
looking into this watch?
I'd like to know that, too.
Why don't you tell me?
Well, I...
I lost it to Yibo when we were
playing a game.
Losing something
to a friend isn't against the law, right?
Did you have this watch
on the day Lu Zheng died?
Wait, Mr. Rong.
Even if the police know
this watch is mine,
they won't link Lu Zheng's case
to us.
That depends
on what you tell the police.
Bowen.
Some money is
not taken for nothing.
It looks very familiar.
This watch is a limited edition.
I have an identical one,
but I gave it to someone else.
Let's sit down and talk.
This
should be my watch.
Really?
You gave it away? To whom?
Whoever you got this watch from,
that's who I gave it to.
We got this
from a fugitive on the run.
Mr. Lang, you have ties to a fugitive?
Wait, officers,
you can't joke about this.
I'm a law-abiding citizen.
How could I possibly have ties
to a fugitive?
Could it be that
the person I gave it to
gave it to someone else?
Even if he didn't give it away,
could he have lost it?
Right? E-Even if it wasn't lost,
it could have been stolen.
Well, there are many possibilities.
It's just that you probably can't remember
who you gave it to.
They all have poor memories.
Yeah.
Do you remember when you gave it away?
It's been a few months.
No,
almost half a year.
Half a year ago, Chief Lu
died in a car accident.
Do you know about this?
Yes, I do.
What a pity.
What?
Is Chief Lu's accidental death
related to this watch?
I say they're related.
The night Chief Lu
had the car accident,
I was indeed at the scene.
Yes.
The watch was on my wrist at that time.
What a coincidence.
When Chief Lu had the accident,
you were right at the scene?
Yes, I was at the scene.
Sanjiangkou is not a big place.
I just happened to pass by that night.
There are security cameras on that road,
right?
Yes, there are.
I see.
You must have seen
this special watch
on the surveillance cameras
and then found out
that the owner of the watch was me,
so you came to ask me,
right?
You were at the scene
of Chief Lu's car accident.
Why didn't you
call the police immediately?
Because someone already called the police.
It's been half a year.
The driver who caused the accident
should've been sentenced, right?
Or did you find out some connection
between the driver and me, Captain Wang?
Is there any connection?
Nope.
Well, then,
officers,
if you have any other questions,
I will answer them honestly
and fully cooperate with you.
Do you have any other questions?
I'm done asking.
Then that's it.
We'll find you if there's anything.
Okay.
Won't you sit for a bit longer?
No, thanks.
Then I'll see you out.
Don't bother.
Don't bother seeing us out.
Let me see you out.
Take it slow.
Take care, Chief Zhang.
We didn't get any information out of him.
But you seem quite happy.
The Chief must have a plan.
We asked everything we needed to, right?
We did.
Did we get the results we wanted?
No.
Why can't a non-answer
count as an answer in itself?
What did Lang Bowen answer?
Okay.
The Municipal Bureau
checked Lang Bowen's call records.
On the day of Captain Ye's accident,
he received a call from Lu Yibo.
The call was
made that night
at 9:53 p.m,
which lasted 25 seconds.
Captain Ye must have found
clues about Chief Lu's case.
Lang Bowen was the murderer?
He killed Chief Lu and then
silenced Captain Ye?
So,
Lang Bowen's denial
is also an admission.
What an old fox.
He won't give up until he sees the coffin.
Then,
push him a bit more
towards the coffin.
Ask the bureau
to send cars to pick us up.
Two.
We drove here.
Your car doesn't have that effect.
What's wrong with you?
Were you eavesdropping at the door again?
[Century Otto]
I wasn't.
Then why aren't you going home?
Bowen,
I'm in my 20s.
You can't always
treat me like a child.
No matter what happens,
let's face it together,
okay?
Face what?
You are facing a bright future,
a new life!
I will deal with
this mess in Sanjiangkou.
I can't let you
bear this alone.
The police already found you.
And those things
you did with Mr. Rong before...
What nonsense are you talking about?
Didn't I tell you not to get involved
in our business?
Do you think that's possible, Bowen?
I'm important to you.
But you matter even more to me, Bowen.
Yangyang, you've grown up.
Trust me.
Think carefully.
Since you were little,
have you ever seen me
fail to solve anything?
Have you?
Do you believe me?
Do you?
I believe you, Bowen.
I got a gift for you.
I've wanted to give it to you
for a long time.
What is it, Bowen?
When you are out alone,
especially in a foreign country,
this is
directly related
to your personal safety.
A gun?
[Ultra-thin] [Try-out pack]
Wait, Bowen,
why did you buy these for me?
So you recognize them.
Good.
Then I can rest assured.
You know how to use them, huh?
This is my privacy.
Talking about privacy with me?
Your bare-bottom photos
are still on my phone.
Take it.
Use them sparingly.
Let's go.
Let's tell Mom and Dad the good news.
Wait, wait.
D-Don't bring this.
Right.
[Century Otto]
What happened?
No idea.
Why didn't they arrest that bastard?
It's only a matter of time.
For thugs like him,
even if they become big bosses,
most of them
can't get through an investigation.
Can their background be clean?
You can't put it so absolutely.
Is Lang Bowen definitely a bad guy?
He's so rich now.
Can't he turn over a new leaf?
What if he's helping the police
solve a case?
It's hard to say.
Don't let the masses make random guesses.
Without solid evidence,
the police won't arrest people
for no reason.
Let's go.
[Police]
We got some news from the bank
this morning.
Three days after Chief Lu's accident,
Rongcheng Group
transferred 30 million yuan
to Otto for project funds.
Otto and Rongcheng Group are
in an upstream-downstream relationship.
One acquires land,
one handles demolition.
Their financial transactions are normal.
But wasn't the timing
a bit too coincidental?
That means
this money
might be of other uses.
Possibly.
And possibly not.
We'll find out soon enough.
Officer Song,
the tow truck has arrived at Otto.
Why did you get a tow truck?
Didn't your car break down?
Li Qian,
explain it to him.
We just asked Lang Bowen
about the situation.
He didn't tell us a single shred of truth
and acted very arrogantly.
That's for sure.
People like him
won't give up until he sees the coffin.
So we need you.
What do you mean?
You came to pick us up
so ostentatiously just now.
If Lang Bowen knows,
Zhou Rong will definitely know.
If they have something shady
hidden in their hearts,
they will take action.
This is sowing discord.
As long as they move,
we'll have a chance.
Keep a close eye on them.
Understood.
We don't need the tow truck. Thanks.
Stop running around!
Aren't you tired? Stand still!
Fall!
Fall down!
Can you find
someone less tough
to beat next time?
Okay.
I'll spar with you next time.
Mr. Rong.
What?
It's... It's itchy!
Zhang Yi'ang
went to see Lang Bowen.
Who said that?
Li Penggai.
He saw it with his own eyes
when he was passing by Otto.
What's wrong
with Zhang Yi'ang?
I gave him my business card
and told him to call me
if he needed anything.
But he never called me.
Why is he interacting
with Lu Yibo and Lang Bowen
so often?
What is he doing?
Mr. Rong,
should we do something?
What do you want to do?
Kill someone?
Even a swine wouldn't be this stupid.
There's no need to make a big fuss.
The police
just want to test us right now.
If we do something, we'll make a mistake.
If we do nothing,
we'll be safe.
I'm just worried.
Bowen is an honest man.
If he says anything
unfavorable to you,
wouldn't we be in a passive position?
He...
He wouldn't dare.
Understood.
Mr. Rong,
Li Penggai
made a great contribution this time.
Do you think
we should let him come back?
Where did he go?
He went to transport sand.
Why is he transporting sand?
He's a good boy.
Let him come back.
T-Then I'll just...
Go, go.
Fetch me my bag.
Okay.
Run a few steps.
Hello?
It's me.