Previously on
Seducing Drake Palma.
You’re really avoiding me, huh?
Well, happy birthday.
Adobo was not just
- created for its flavor.
- [In French] Only you.
- It was first created for survival.
- [In French] Happy birthday, Alys.
What’s his deal?
Miss Perez, anything
you want to add?
[In French] Only you.
Do you believe
the number of girls I played with
would be the amount of times
you would cry because of someone?
Oh no, what should I do?
Should I greet him, or just walk
straight like I didn’t see him?
What to do?
♪ Happy birthday to you… ♪
Oh, where’s Drake?
Oh, uhm...
On the way.
He says he’s on the way.
Where’s your escort?
He said he was
already on his way.
Mom…
The program is about to start.
Mom, I don’t know.
Actually I texted him a while ago,
and he said he’s already on the way.
What did I do to deserve this, Drake?
Why are you hurting me so badly?
This can’t be!
It’s my birthday today!
Don’t leave me.
Do you understand
what you’re saying, Alys?
If I go there,
I’ll make my joke real.
I won’t leave you alone.
This is supposed to be
the happiest night of my life.
My debut.
I don’t deserve this, Drake.
What do you need from me, Drake?
Help me out, Tripp.
I really messed up with Alys.
At least you know.
So please,
I’m asking you as family—
bring Alys here.
Where are you taking me?
Just follow the light.
He prepared that for you, Zyril.
Happy birthday.
Hopefully, I’m still not late.
Sorry, I bailed on you.
Something just really came up.
Reasons, reasons, reasons.
You always have a reason.
Am I too late?
You’re late.
You’re way too late.
You know why?
Because you’ve hurt me too much.
It’s too late to forgive you.
I’m really sorry, Alys.
I’m here now.
I’m already here, see.
You don’t understand.
I’m done.
No.
You’re just mad, Alys.
I’m not mad, Drake.
I’m hurting.
Please hear me out.
I just had to go.
I didn’t mean to leave you, Alys.
How convenient.
You’re always like that, Drake.
Every time you hurt me,
you always have an excuse.
Why are you like this?
I don’t know.
I’m just like this.
Please try to understand me.
Bear with me.
I’ve been understanding you, Drake.
Even back then.
But now, it’s my turn
to be understood.
I’m done.
I thought you love me.
What was that Alys?
Your personal version of joke?
Drake...
When I said I
loved you, I meant it.
And now that I’m saying
I’m done, I mean that too.
No! I won’t break up with you!
It’s not even an option
anymore for you, Drake!
We’re done!
I love you, Alys.
I love you.
Please, don’t go.
I don’t want to get hurt again.
Please.
Drake, I love you,
you know that.
But if that love will keep hurting me,
then I don’t want it anymore.
I’m tired.
I’m done.
Enough.
Tripp...
I love you, Drake Palma!
I’m done.
I thought you love me.
When I said I
loved you, I meant it.
And now that I’m saying
I’m done, I mean that too.
No! I won’t break up with you!
It’s not even an option
anymore for you, Drake!
We’re done!
How’s the single life?
It’s been a week.
How is it?
It’s like this.
Ouch!
- What?
- That hurts.
How does it feel?
Does it hurt?
Is it hard?
Yes.
But you know what,
when I remember all the times
he’s forgotten about me,
I think maybe it’s
better this way—
that we broke up.
At least...
there are no expectations,
no disappointments.
They’re so sweet.
Looks like the guy’s
lucky with his girlfriend.
I hope everyone has that.
Tripp, why don’t you
have a girlfriend yet?
It’s impossible, right?
This punk’s got the charm.
Well, I don’t know.
I mean, I’m handsome—
but I don’t know.
You’re so full of yourself!
Why? I really am handsome—
what can I do?
Fine, Tripp’s handsome!
I’ll admit that!
That’s why the girls here in
Brenford pick fights with me.
And since Drake and I broke up,
it’s really Tripp who’s
been helping me.
Whatever you say.
You’re my boss, after all.
Zy, honestly,
I haven’t had a girlfriend
because I’m not sure yet.
But when I do,
she’ll be happy for sure.
Because like my camera,
I’ll only point my lens at her.
I’m pretty, right?
Yes, you’re pretty.
You might end up crying.
Um, shall we go?
Where are we going?
Where do you want to go?
Let’s go to SCA.
SCA, really?
Ouch!
Didn’t you say you’d do everything
so Drake and I won’t get back together?
But it feels like you’re
pushing me back to him.
So, what is it really?
I was just joking.
You’re so hot-headed.
Come on, let’s grab coffee.
To cool things down.
Let’s go.
You’re so persistent.
Try avoiding him when you can.
Tripp, please!
No more Drake-talks, okay?
I’m moving on!
Got it, boss!
Here, stay with me.
Hide behind me.
Hide there so he won’t see you.
And if he sees you,
I’ve got you.
As long as you treat me, okay?
Wow, you’ve got some nerve!
Why?
Whenever I’m with you,
I’ll really end up starving to death.
And I’m the girl here—why
am I the one treating you?
What’s wrong with you? You’re the guy—
you’re supposed to treat me!
I’ll pawn your camera
so you can treat me!
Hey, no!
- Whatever.
- Not this one. I love this.
You’re so annoying!
Come on, treat me!
I don’t want to!
Alys!
I don’t know with you, Tripp!
Tell me the truth,
- don’t you have allowance?
- Zyril!
What?!
You don’t want to, Alys, huh?
Zyril, treat me.
Quit it, Tripp!
I’m asking just this once.
Just this once?
It’s every day!
What do you mean
every day—come on!
- Ugh! I can’t with you!
- I left my allowance!
You left it?
- Then have it delivered here.
- Yes, I left it.
- Hey, you’re in the wrong lane.
- I said I don’t want to!
Stay right, come on.
Your treat really hits different!
What treat?
You forced me to.
You didn’t even have money,
but you ordered endlessly.
Hey, I have some.
I just left my wallet at home.
You know what,
you’re such a freeloader.
That’s why you don’t
have a girlfriend.
Ouch!
That hurts!
That’s way below
the belt, Miss Zyril!
You’re single because
you’re a mooch.
You don’t know how
to court a girl.
- Tripp!
- Hey!
- Tripp, hello!
- Here comes the octopus.
You didn’t even visit
me in the hospital.
I thought we were friends.
The octopus attacks again.
Please, Shaira, not here.
Oh.
Alys, you’re here.
I didn’t notice you.
My bad.
By the way, I heard
you and Drake broke up.
I’m so sorry to hear…for you.
Definitely happy for me.
I didn’t break up with
Drake so you could have him.
You’re forever shameless.
What did you just say?
Hmm?
Shaira, leave us alone.
And also, get some rest.
You just got out of the hospital
and you’re wandering around.
And fix your attitude.
Fine.
If you say so.
I’ll go now, Tripp, okay?
Bye.
That’s insane.
That squid is so flirty.
She clings like a leech!
Hey you, Tripp!
What’s going on
between you and Shaira?
What is she to you, anyway?
Hey, watch your answer.
For all I know, you’re friends
and you’re just messing with me.
You wouldn’t do that
to me, right, Tripp?
Hey, Tripp!
What’s really going on with
you and Shaira?
I courted her before.
You know, I got rejected
because of Drake.
Hold on.
I thought you hadn’t
courted anyone before?
Of course, I’d lose some charm points
if I tell people I got rejected.
Let’s keep that our secret, okay?
But even so,
you’re still on my side, right?
Of course!
You’re still my boss.
Damn it! You’re so cute!
I could cry! I wanna
put you in my pocket!
You’d make a great keychain!
Go ahead.
You can even take me home.
Annoying.
I’ll take this, you’re not
even going to eat it.
You can have it.
Okay.
Oh.
There.
You’re smart, right?
Mmm, you got this!
What now?
You’ve got flour on your face.
So grumpy.
Ouch! What now?
Oh, sorry.
I didn’t mean to.
Hey, why are you taking my cake?!
Give it to me.
Are you serious?!
This is mine!
I’m bringing it home!
This is mine.
Just make another one!
No way, this is mine!
It’s mine now!
No, it’s mine!
Oh, Alys.
You are broken up, okay?
Move on already.
Alys, the oven has been
beeping for awhile now.
Oh!
Okay, hold on.
Alys, your baking!
Oh, I got it.
Wow, those look gorgeous!
Exactly, I want to
take some home
because my brother is
heading back to the States.
I wanted to bring him some.
Then, take one.
They won’t even notice.
Girl, seriously!
Those are for the street
kids our culinary class feeds.
I’ll just make them a new batch.
Okay.
Oh, Aunt Liana?
Why is she calling?
Hello?
Alys, honey?
Hi, Aunt Liana!
What made you call?
Kiddo, are you done with class?
We’re picking you up.
Why, Aunt?
Are you with Daddy?
Yes, I’m with your dad.
We’re close to Brenford,
so we’ll be there in a few.
Okay, Aunt. I’ll just tell Mom.
I already told your
mom about this surprise.
We’ll be there in 15 minutes.
Okay, Aunt.
See you!
I wonder what surprise
Aunt Liana is talking about.
I was planning to go
to the park with Tripp.
Alright, whatever.
I’ll just head home early.
Tripp, I’ll go ahead.
Good luck on your recits!
What surprise is Aunt
Liana talking about?
She says it’s a surprise.
Surprise!
We’re so excited about this,
kiddo. Right, Cy?
Yeah, of course!
Wait, what’s this surprise?
My birthday’s already over.
My graduation is still far off.
There!
Oh my god!
Aunt, Daddy, don’t tell me...
What do you want
for your birthday?
Aunt Liana, do you think you could
convince Dad to get me a condo?
Condo?
Mhm!
Why?
I just wanna live next to Drake.
Oh my gosh!
Are you ready?
- Good morning.
- Hi.
Lord, let it not be 19th floor.
Lord, not 19th floor.
Are you okay, Alys?
Yes, Aunt.
Oh my gosh. It’s in
19th floor, too.
Hey, is there a problem?
Oh, nothing, Daddy.
I’m so excited!
Aren’t you, Alys?
Of course, Aunt.
I’m very excited, too.
Gosh!
Let’s go.
Lord, I hope he’s not here, please.
Um, Dad?
Yeah?
Why are you going there?
Isn’t it here?
Honey, over here.
Oh, sorry.
Let’s go.
I’m really getting old.
Lord, we’re on the same floor.
Alys, I really insisted that
Cy should buy you this unit.
The Cove Tower?
Yes!
This is a nice condo.
I hope Dad or Daddy or anyone
agrees, I just really want a condo!
Lord, I knew it. Be careful what
you wish for ‘cause you just might get it.
0-7-2-1. That’s just
the temporary passcode, okay?
You can change it later.
But remember it, okay.
You might not get in.
You know the passcode.
I have short-term memory loss.
I forgot it already.
Stand there until you remember.
What?
Drake!
Okay.
Let’s go.
Welcome to your unit!
My gosh, it’s so pink!
And the strawberries!
- Wow!
- You like it?
I love it!
Thank you so much, Aunt!
Thank you so much, Daddy!
You’re welcome, kiddo!
Anything for you, dear.
Thank you.
I hope you don’t mind – we
already bought some of your things.
I don’t mind at all.
And also, if you want to
move in, you can start tonight.
Really?
Yup!
I asked permission from your mom.
But first, you’ll need to
grab your stuff.
- Okay?
- Yes.
Okay.
Great! Excited?
Yes, very excited!
Good!
Thank you so much!
Wow, guys, you
really know my taste!
This is such a pleasant surprise.
Thank you so much. I love you.
I love you, Aunt, Daddy!
Thank you, Dad.
Alys, be responsible.
Yes, Mom.
I doubt it.
You’re always contradicting.
Well, just don’t do anything
that will put you in danger.
Yes, Mom.
Come on, your daughter’s
18 now. She’s a grown up.
It’s just sad, our
house will feel so empty.
Don’t be too sad, Mom,
I’m just a tumble away.
And I’ll be here on weekends.
Mom, if you want, I’ll stay.
No, because you won’t
change anyway if you stay here.
Oh, by the way, I’ll come with
you to the airport when you leave.
Stop reminding
me that I’m leaving.
Alright, it’s getting late.
- We’ll go.
- Okay.
Mom...
It’s okay.
I’ll be okay, I promise.
Okay, honey.
Good morning, Alys Zyril Perez!
It’s a brand new day.
Day one of being independent.
So, you don’t have a cook, no cleaner, no
babysitter, but you got this.
Aja!
7:00 A.M.
I know Drake’s first
class is at 7:00 A.M.
So, he’ll leave by 6:30, since
it’s 15 minutes travel from here to SCA.
Perfect, I still have time
to grab breakfast outside.
Way to go, Alys!
Good morning, Alys.
Lord, I knew it,
I should never have
wished for a condo!
I take my wish back.
Have you eaten your breakfast?
We haven’t seen
each other for a week.
But no! You’re
already broken up, Alys.
Don’t forget that.
Let’s eat.
I just ate.
Why does it have to be now?!
Let’s eat!
I don’t want to.
Drake, we’ve been
broken up for a week.
One week, you know that?
You didn’t even make an effort to call
me or talk to me during that entire week.
Then now, you just show up
and invite me for breakfast?
Drake, are you okay?
I gave you time.
Why? Did I ask for time?
I’m sorry.
It’s my fault.
Now, will you eat
breakfast with me?
Good morning, Zy!
Tripp! What are you doing here?
And how did you
even know where I live?
Aunt Liana told me.
It’s funny, it’s like she was
setting you up with me.
Hey, cousin, you’re here.
Uh, Zy, have you eaten yet?
What’s your passcode?
Come on, let’s eat.
Zy! What’s your passcode?
No, this can’t be happening.
Come on, I’m not a burglar!
Even if I knew your passcode,
I wouldn’t just barge in!
That’s not it!
Come here,
I’ll whisper it to you.
What?! I can’t hear you.
What?
1131?
Why did you shout it out?
Ouch.
He’s probably thinking
I haven’t moved on yet.
Come on, Zy!
Alys.
Drake and I are over.
Tripp’s the one
always with me now.
So who else would I choose?
Can I come in, too?
Don’t you have a class?
I’ll ditch.
Hey, don’t ditch.
Go to your class.
Do you hate me that much?
Huh?
I just want to spend time with you,
but you keep on pushing me away.
Alys, are we really over?
Drake, if you really want to
talk to me, can we just do it tonight?
Let’s have dinner together.
I don’t want you skipping
class because of me, okay?
Dinner date, then.
I miss you so much, Alys.
God, Lord...
Why are my palpitations weak now?
It’s a little less.
It’s only tame palpitations.
I miss you, too.
I’ll go ahead.
Be careful with my cousin.
I know him.
Alys!
What now?
Did you guys get back together?
You know too much!
What the heck, you ruined my hair.
It was perfectly fixed.
Lord, why does he
have to be so handsome?
Okay fine, I’ll admit it, he’s
even more handsome than Drake.
This is so hard!
So, you and Drake
are talking again, huh?
Are you getting back together?
You’re asking too much.
I just want to know.
Why? Are you jealous?
Kind of.
Maybe.
Whatever.
I still have class.
How about you,
don’t you have class?
What time is your class?
10:00 AM.
10:00 AM. Okay, ride with me.
I brought my car.
Of course, I’ll ride with you.
Are you a boarder here?
Come on, eat so we can leave.
Wow, sweet!
Hurry up, or we’ll be late!
Zy, do you think I should
transfer to your building,
so we’ll be wonder neighborhood?
Fine, yes!
Because if I say no,
you might sulk again.
No, really! I’m serious.
What do you think?
Mmm, but the octopus is there, too!
That would be risky.
Who knows, it won’t be just a touch
on the shoulder that will happen.
That’s gross to even think about!
No, just stay at your house.
So we can have world peace for all of us.
Again, class, “mise en place”
means “everything in its place.”
It is a French culinary theory
emphasizing preparation and
organization before cooking.
So, we need to determine
who’s the best among them.
Can’t we just bake or something?
Why is there even theory involved?
What time is it?
It’s still a long time!
I need to be home by 2:00 P.M.
I can’t miss sending
Dane to the airport!
Ugh!
So, to check if you
understood the lesson,
let us test your mise en place
skills with a simple salad dish.
So, class, be ready
with your salad dish.
Salad dish?
Okay, where are the vegetables?
Baby Dane!
- You know, I rushed just to–
- So noisy!
Hey, why are you
in such a bad mood?
None of your business!
Why are you here?
Duh! Obviously,
we’re taking you to the–
I’m not a kid anymore!
I don’t need to be
taken to the airport!
Hey, Dane!
Stop it, Alys!
Dane!
Dad!
Dad, what happened to Dane?
I even rushed my quiz just to catch
him here, then he just snapped at me!
Just let it go, he got busted.
Huh? Dane got busted?
Felice came by,
worried about him,
so don’t tell him you know, okay.
That’ll just piss him off more.
Poor thing.
Poor baby Dane,
rejected by his first love.
Fine, I won’t tease him for now.
Poor baby.
Be good, okay?
Listen to your Nana!
- Alright, Mom.
- Alright?
Be careful there, okay?
Don’t be stubborn.
I will.
Sorry for yelling at you earlier.
It’s okay. I understand.
I know the feeling.
Everything will be fine.
Things will get better.
If I can do it, you can, too.
Wow, you really are
more mature than me.
Take care there, okay?
I’ll miss you.
I will. I’ll be back.
Hon, we’ll go ahead.
Alright. Take care, okay?
Hey, Dane, you listen.
Alys…
Bye.
There’s no one to
bother us anymore.
Alys has her own life now.
Wow, Dad, so dramatic!
Alys, how’s living alone?
Uh, it’s okay.
Still getting used to it.
Mmm, you’ll manage.
Oh, by the way, no
monkey business!
What do you mean,
“monkey business”?
If only you knew, bre–
I mean, Mom, I swear, there’s
no monkey businesses going on.
And how did you find out
that Drake’s my neighbor?
Alys, I’m your mother.
Of course, I’ll investigate
before I decide.
I only trusted your Daddy and
Aunt Liana that you’d be safe,
that’s why I allowed it.
And of course, I trust you.
You already know
what’s right and wrong.
Thank you, Mommy, and I
promise, I won’t break your trust.
Mom, Dad, the car’s here.
You sure you don’t
want us to take you?
No, Dad, you already got
stressed in traffic earlier.
Just rest with Mom.
Okay. Just make sure,
lock your doors.
Yes, Mom, I’ll be fine.
Okay.
Rest now.
- I love you.
- You still have class tomorrow.
Alright.
Okay, good night!
Drake.
You made me wait for 7 hours.
Do you hate me that much?
7 hours?
Oh my gosh, I totally
forgot about our dinner.
Should I follow him?
No.
You’re the one who forgot your
promise and you still dare to bug him.
Besides, you’re
already broken up, right?
You have no right to press the
1131 code on his door.
Who else?
It’s still me!
At least my pillows give me
comfort and peace of mind.
That Drake, even after the breakup,
he’s still messing with my head.
Whose fault is this?
Who’s the fool who
asked for a condo?
Still me!
Who’s that?
What time is it?
Wait!
Hold on!
It’s late at night
and it’s causing nuisance.
Just a moment!
Drake…
I changed my mind.
Mmm?
I can’t let you hate me.
I’ll make you love me again.
Come.
Drake.
What?
Where are we going?
Dinner. You have a dinner
date with me, remember?
It’s almost 11. Is there
a restaurant still open?
You’re right.
Never mind.
Wow, you bought so much.
The convenient store
made money from you.
Let’s go.
Oh no, he’s on top of me!
Mom’s gonna shave my
head if she finds out!
Alys…
Huh?
Can I kiss you?
I know we broke up,
but I feel like kissing you right now.
Lord, is this a test to
see if I’ve moved on?
Because if it is, my standing
might already be failing.
It’s almost been a week since we last
talked or saw each other, Alys.
I really really miss you, Alys.
Not yet.
I need to give her time.
Alys?
Anything for you, Alys.
Thank you.
And I hope you don’t mind.
We already bought some of your things.
I don’t mind at all.
And also, if you want to
move in, you can start tonight.
Alys.
On the next episode of
Seducing Drake Palma.
Answer me.
Huh?
Do you still feel the
same way about me,
or have you forgotten how it
feels like to be in love with me?
I’m going to court Alys.
You’ve got no problem
with that, do you?
You like her?
Good luck.
She likes breaking hearts.
- Drake.
- Drake!
They don’t want to come with us.
Let’s just go?
Wait!
Actually, we’ll come.
Oh, by the way, how
was your debut, Alys?
Huh?
It was okay.
Probably because Drake
didn’t arrive on time, right?
Sorry, he had to
attend to my needs.
We’re having a barbecue
party later, wanna come?
Sure.
OMG!
You two are so perfect together!
What’s your problem?!
You told me that you
don’t like me anymore,
so I’m trying to forget you.
But why are you making
it so damn impossible?
- No–
- Shut up!