Wait...
Why am I even...
following that guy?
Actually,
it's not that weird.
I mean...
he was just coming out of a bridal shop.
Maybe he's into women too.
It's a possibility.
I just don't want any trouble.
Since we've hooked up,
I should at least know if he's "safe."
I have a right to know!
You...
What are you doing here?
Me? Oh, I was just...
passing by on my way home from work.
Just a coincidence...
Do you two know each other?
Oh.
Well, uh...
Just play it cool, you idiot.
No way, are you serious?
You should've told me
you were seeing someone.
Oh, no, it's not like that.
Sorry.
It's fine.
I know what you're trying to say.
This person...
is just a friend.
Huh?
My brother actually has friends?
Wait...
Brother?
So that means...
this woman is his sister?
"Unexpectedly Naughty Fukami"
So I ended up getting invited inside.
How's my brother...
(Episode 3)
doing at the office?
He's actually really well-regarded
in the tech department.
That's a relief.
He's reliable at home, but
when it comes to his social skills...
Hey, watch it.
I'm just glad to hear
he has a friend like you.
Our parents passed away a long time ago,
and with my divorce,
I've been a real handful for him.
But I'm getting remarried now,
which is why you were at the bridal shop.
Oh, did my brother tell you?
I needed to pick up some wedding catalogs,
so I asked him to come along.
It's a bit embarrassing
going to those places alone.
Sana, don't you have
to pick up Haruto soon?
Oh!
Well, take good care of my brother! See ya!
Sorry about her.
Once she starts talking, she doesn't stop.
Sounds like you've had a pretty rough life.
It's fine.
I just did what I had to
do after our parents died.
Besides, I have my sister,
and my nephew is really cute.
You have a nephew?
He's spirited, and he's cute.
What about you?
What about your parents?
My family?
My dad's still around,
but my mom walked
out on us a long time ago.
(To Aki-kun)
I wonder how she's doing these days.
Wait...
Why am I even telling him
all this stuff?
I see.
So this computer is like your partner?
I guess you could say that.
I use it to develop games and stuff.
Wait, you actually make games?
You don't really care, do you?
It's fine, you don't have
to force a conversation.
Wait, right here?
For a guy like him,
this place is full of
people he cares about...
and people who care about him.
It's nothing like my life.
Put your legs up.
Wait...
Ah...
I don't know why,
but today he feels...
more real.
You're so sensitive...
right here.
Stop...
Ah...
I'm gonna come...
Then just go ahead.
The bed's so small...
Give me your hand.
The walls are thin here.
I can't hold it in anymore...
If only you were like me.
If you were as empty as I am,
I could take you even more roughly.
Whoa...
Hey, don't blame me for that.
Hahaha...
That's the first time I've
ever done that at my place.
When I'm with you,
I don't feel like myself.
You're so cute.
No, no, no... what am I saying?
Here.
This is my contact info.
Just message me directly.
If you keep staring at me at the office,
people are going to find out.
Oh.
I'll go wash this.
(Fukami Yuu)
His name...
How should I input it?
[TN: He's unsure how to "read" the first name]
Whatever. I'll just put him in my phone
as "Loser." [Zero Point Man]
Calm down.
This is just an experiment.
(Kaji: It's Kaji. Want to grab a drink?)
(Loser: Why?)
(Kaji: No reason. Here's the address.)
What do you mean, "why"?
It's not like I actually want
to drink with a guy like him.
I just... started thinking
he was kind of cute, I guess.
What happened before
was just a fluke.
An accident.
I'm going to prove that we're completely
incompatible in every way except for sex.
I just ordered some stuff, is that okay?
Yeah.
See?
The vibe is totally dead.
I thought you'd take me somewhere fancy.
You seem like the type
who'd hang out at those stylish spots.
I...
don't really have any
nice clothes to wear out.
That's a relief.
This place is pretty low-key.
Wait, you actually
worry about stuff like that?
That's actually...
kind of cute.
No.
He is not cute.
That was close.
Crisis averted.
I should... probably head out.
Wait...
What are we doing?
Ah...
I...
want to see your apartment.
Ah...
It's a mess. Give me a second.
Hold on a second.
What's the rush, you drunk?
I'm not drunk.
Well, I'm not interested in sleeping
with someone who's wasted.
So we're not doing it?
I'm already... kind of turned on.
You...
Ah.
What am I going to do with you?
You're so sensitive.
Look at this...
My finger goes right in.
Arching your back like that...
You're so naughty.
No.
I want to really do it with you.
Ah, ah...
Hey, you...
Is there anything you
want me to do for you?
Where's this coming from?
Asking all of a sudden.
I just feel like I'm the only
one having a good time.
If there's something you want, just say it.
When you've...
been drinking...
are you the type who'll black out?
Yeah, it happens pretty often.
In that case...
I want to hear...
you say my name.
That's your thing?
Wow, that's actually pretty normal.
- Actually, never mind.
- Akihiro.
Wait, how?
My name...
You knew it?
Of course I know the name
of the person I'm sleeping with.
And your...
name?
How do you pronounce it?
Yuu...
No.
Once you give it a name,
it starts to mean something.
This... whatever this feeling is.
Yuu.
Fukami...
That's all.
If only I could keep him
trapped in this room forever.
If only morning
would never come.
Wait... where am I?
(Next Episode)
Thanks for everything on Friday.
Fukami!
Is that him?
That Fukami guy is actually kind of cute.
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm not interested in that.
What's going on?
I think we should take a break for a while.