( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
ONE MONTH AGO
SEJEONG FOREST TUNNEL
ORIGINAL TUNNEL
INSTANT TTEOKBOKKI
No one here's a picky eater,
are they?
The food here is so good
you wouldn't notice
if someone dropped dead next to you.
I see.
MAKE IT POSSIBLE
I put in extra liver and lung.
Thanks.
- Let's eat.
- Yes, sure.
Pig liver
and lungs.
Why don't you young ones eat?
Do kids these days
not eat sundae or tteokbokki?
Oh, vegan?
That?
I gave that a go once.
It was hard.
Wasn't it, Madam Jeon?
Jeez.
Meat is what gives you energy.
Don't eat if you don't want to.
You don't have to make a face.
Hand them over.
You all know some ruins were found
at the construction site.
There's a news embargo,
so don't go telling anyone yet.
Take one each.
In there are the details
of the newly assigned
construction zones.
A few building owners
are still holding out for more money.
FLOOR AREA RATIO INCENTIVE
Whoever obtains those buildings
will be given a stake
in the redevelopment project.
You all know
how much it's worth, right?
Come on, eat.
Madam Jeon, try it with salt.
- Yes.
- Good.
Try to play along from now on.
Can you do that?
Just do a good job.
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
EPISODE 4
M&amp;A REALTORS
- What's wrong?
- Mr. Gi.
He's a scary guy.
Sell it to us officially.
This seems a bit odd.
They barged in out of the blue
and said you'd agreed to a deal.
Three billion won.
How's that?
We're giving you a premium.
I'll give you some time to consider.
You should discuss it
with your family.
This is your last chance
to let matters go quietly.
Gyun.
The coffee tastes good.
Yes.
DO NOT ENTER
OUT OF ORDER
Can't we do this with the lid down?
Does it smell that bad?
The lid's too slippery to stand on.
Are you sure this place is safe?
Of course it's safe.
Come on. Keep passing me the cash.
Let's sell this building.
All of a sudden? Why?
Let's just sell it
to that Real Capital or whatever.
- Gosh, that's cold.
- What did I tell you?
Hang on.
Should we just sell it, then?
Do you mean that?
Aren't you afraid at all?
Think of what it is you did.
Things did go a bit wrong
but we didn't mean any malice.
I saw in some film
that they call this
"redistribution of wealth."
That's what kidnapping is?
Someone might hear us.
I'm afraid, too.
Let's sell the building
and move away.
Move away? Where to?
- To the States.
- The States?
Yes.
Let's move to the States
with Da-rae and start over.
Let's leave before it's too late.
I don't want to live here any longer.
You still smoke?
So you can meet your maker sooner?
HANMAEUM BUILDING
If that is what my maker wishes.
This place hasn't changed one bit.
Let's get straight to the point.
Did you hear the rumor?
There's that,
and I wanted to see you, too.
I see you knew.
I may not look it
but my ears still work fine.
Then I'll be straight with you.
Sell me your building.
I'll give you a good price.
Has it been about 20 years
since we last talked?
Yes.
It has been that long.
Time really does fly.
You must've forgotten what I'm like.
I remember very well.
A stubborn old mule
who never listens.
You don't care
what happens out there.
You just go on your way.
You don't care
how infuriated others get.
You're fine as long as
you can act
like you're smart and noble.
How is Yi-gyeong?
Do you have the right to ask?
And you?
Do you have the right?
I considered Yi-gyeong
my own flesh and blood.
You're the one who took her from me.
Only because you were
such a frustrating fool.
You still are.
When an opportunity finds you
you must think of how to grab it.
You kick the blessing
out the front door.
So what?
Did it make you happy?
Your life without me.
You're putting on airs again.
Forget about that and tell me
what you'll do with your building.
Did you stop to think
what the price is
for chasing wealth your whole life?
Do you think you can live
a decent life without money?
It's better than becoming a monster.
What, a monster?
That's what penniless people
who have zero ability
to make decent money
say out of jealousy.
If they were offered cash
they'd stand in line
to become a monster.
Would they?
Do you want Yi-gyeong
to become like you?
I won't sell my building.
Especially not to you.
Don't be too stubborn a fool.
Give it some thought.
PYEONGBUKGWAN
CEO JEON YANG-JA
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR AWARD
NATIONAL CHILDREN'S ESSAY COMPETITION
Shoot, why won't it open?
What a ruckus.
Did you change the PIN, Mom?
Yes, I think there's a leak.
Master Park told me
to change the PIN.
You call a shaman "master"?
Forget about those superstitions.
You should've told me at least.
It's my money, not yours.
Come on, Mom.
You let me take it freely.
I need cash.
I have to pay
Hwal-sung's medical bills.
You owe me three billion won.
Three billion won?
Did you just call my ransom a debt?
Financial transactions must be exact.
Fine.
Transactions must be exact,
so let's say I owe you.
Since I'm in debt already,
let's up the amount.
What's the collateral?
The Jayang-dong apartment
that's in my name.
I'll put that up.
I changed the name
on the deed long ago.
What? Whose is it now?
I bought the apartment with my money.
Whose name would it be in?
You have no idea what's going on
behind your back, do you?
- You stupid thing.
- Mom!
Are you even my mom?
How could you be like this?
You're the only one
who stabs me in the back.
No one else treats me like this.
Just how hard it was for me
growing up without a dad
under a money-mad mom.
Don't you see?
I gave up studying abroad…
Whatever.
Hwal-sung has a friend named Su-jong.
He's the guy
who came to the hospital, right?
His building is included
in the redevelopment area.
Set up a meeting.
What?
I don't believe this.
Su-jong won't sell that building.
Then we make him sell it.
Will this do?
Whether a famous scene
in a work of art
is purely poetic license
added for dramatic effect
or if it's actually
scientifically possible.
Art Fact Check will tell you.
Today, we'll study the scene
in Romeo and Juliet
where Juliet comes back to life.
Actually, Juliet didn't die
after taking the poison.
She had taken a sleep-inducing drug
that temporarily reduces
one's pulse and breathing.
Do you think that makes sense?
It's not that hard to pull off
if you have the drug and tools.
For real?
When the pulse
and body temperature drops too far
it can look like one is dead.
(I was enjoying
watching that program.)
Da-rae.
Mom and Dad
have something to tell you.
(What is it? I have an online
interview study group soon.)
It won't take long.
Da-rae.
Daddy loves you a great deal.
(Are you crazy?)
(Why would you suddenly say that?)
Our family. All together.
Let's go to the States.
(Really? How?)
(I was looking into student housing.)
You won't need student housing.
A house with a swimming pool.
I'll buy one.
Now you're going overboard.
(A house where we must mow the lawn?)
That's it.
If you mow the lawn
as a chore,
I'll give you extra pocket money.
(How much? 50 dollars?)
Fifty dollars?
Let's see.
The exchange rate
is 1,400 won per US dollar.
That's way too much.
(45 dollars, then.)
You're being silly now.
Get to the point already.
Our family will move to the States
and live together.
Da-rae needs surgery
and I don't like the idea
of my daughter being all alone.
For my daughter
that is best.
Dad and Mom
both want that.
FAMILY
237 IMAGES
REALTOR HEE-JU
Sorry for texting so late, Mr. Gi.
I just think
I really should tell you.
Mr. Gi.
Don't sell your property.
You can't sell it right now.
I can't tell you everything via text.
Why not? What's up?
REALTOR HEE-JU
You weren't in bed?
I was, but I woke up.
What's this about?
Well…
If we go over there,
we can see the ruins that were found.
That area isn't included
in the redevelopment plan.
Don't even talk about that.
You have no idea how upset
the property owners are over there.
The ruins appeared and that's why
they changed the redevelopment
project area after just one month.
There's a press embargo
on this information
but I'm telling you personally.
Why?
Se-yoon Building
falls in the new redevelopment zone.
Don't you get what that means?
They're going to build
the biggest building in Asia here.
It could be worth
tens of billion of won.
Make one right connection
and you get a windfall.
I don't know anyone
worth calling a connection.
This could become really big.
I'll just play safe,
and sell for extra, and get out.
Mr. Gi.
Mr. Min's eyes sparkled
as soon as he heard the news.
Where are you from?
We're from the development company.
I want to show
the new manager around.
You need to wear hard hats.
We can borrow a couple
from the office.
- Okay, then. Go ahead.
- Take care.
Thanks.
UNDER CONSTRUCTION
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
Hwal-sung knew about Se-yoon Building
being included
in the redevelopment project?
Yes.
For how long?
For about two weeks now?
He didn't tell you?
No.
It'll be game over
once the redevelopment is confirmed.
Wasn't that plan scrapped?
It was announced.
The price went down yet again.
And you still have vacancies.
Do you want to sell it to me?
Seriously.
Hee-ju.
How do you do that?
Do what?
Finding the right connections?
Yes.
BUILDING HALTED TO EXCAVATE RUINS
HELP PRESERVE OUR HERITAGE
Our family. All together.
Let's go to the States.
Mr. Gi.
Mr. Min's eyes sparkled
as soon as he heard the news.
Hey, do you remember?
Back in the day, a bottle of soju
and a bag of shrimp chips
lasted us a whole night.
My gosh.
Time flies so disgustingly fast.
Why didn't you tell me?
You are my one and only friend.
My only friend in the world.
You call us friends?
Hey.
So, what do you take me for?
What do you take me for?
Do you consider me a friend?
Min Hwal-sung.
I can't give up now.
You know what I mean, right, punk?
I won't quit like this.
Not after what I did to get here.
Su-jong, why are you here this late?
Oh, gosh, Yi-gyeong.
I kind of missed him.
As if you weren't his best friend.
You can't drink on an empty stomach.
- No, it's fine.
- Here you go.
- Have a few.
- My gosh.
Thanks a lot.
Oh, congratulations, Su-jong.
What for?
I heard from my mom.
Your property
falls in the redevelopment zone.
Well…
She asked me to arrange a meeting.
For what?
She must want to talk to you.
Is that okay with you?
Yes.
Su-jong.
About Hwal-sung.
Did you notice anything strange?
How do you mean?
You know, like seeing another woman.
What?
I'd beat him up myself
if he did that.
Do you want me to do some digging?
No.
MAIN PHOTO ALBUMS
HIDE PHOTO ALBUM
SEND THIS IMAGE TO TRASH?
SEND TO TRASH
So?
Any progress with Se-yoon Building?
We plan to sign the contract
this afternoon.
Is that so?
Do you understand?
Yes, I understand.
If something goes wrong
you will lose your head first.
Get out.
Bye, then.
Yes, hello.
It's me.
We sign the papers today.
You know that, right?
Yes.
My husband will sign them.
You'll delete the video, won't you?
You'll never see it again
once the deal is done.
You'll go ahead as planned, right?
At three billion won.
Here you go.
One, two, three… Three million won.
She's being funny.
Oh, dear. The amount is wrong.
Oh, here.
What's not right?
It's Korean won.
I'm used to US dollar amounts.
What a shame.
I wish you had just signed it.
You're more thorough than you look.
Is this right?
You need to add one more zero.
Thanks. Here you go.
Can you ask them to add another zero?
PURCHASE PRICE: 3 BILLION WON
This is three billion,
the correct amount.
What I mean is
I'll need 30 billion won
knowing how high the price may go.
Add one more zero.
If you can't do that, forget it.
How intriguing.
I thought I had made myself clear.
This was your last chance
to let matters go quietly.
Do you remember my brother-in-law?
A man named Kim Gyun.
If anything,
I need 30 billion won for his sake.
What?
So?
What do you say?
Let's sign the deal quietly
for 30 billion won.
Is your wife doing well?
Why are you asking about her?
It's nothing.
You know, I thought I'd ask.
You should keep an eye on your wife.
Give me a second.
Let me send you something.
I don't need this anymore.
REAL CAPITAL JONAH
What's this?
Something interesting.
What's interesting?
Caution.
It's for your eyes only.
Bye.
SEON
Hello? Hey.
How did the deal go?
Well, the thing is…
What's going on?
You signed the deal, right?
There was something
bothering me, so…
You didn't sell it?
Seon.
Can you hear me out for a moment?
- I had a good reason.
- What reason?
Why didn't you sell it?
Didn't they say anything?
I didn't want to sell my building,
so what are they going to say?
I really had a reason
not to sell the place.
This wasn't what you promised!
Anyway, calm down.
Let's talk in person, okay?
This isn't up to you!
Hello?
Why won't you answer?
There seems to be a problem.
Please give me a little more time.
Hey, Da-rae.
(Mom, is something going on?)
No.
I have to go out for a moment.
If you have nothing more to say, go.
Oh, jeez.
What is it?
Fix the restroom if you have time
to watch something like that.
My business is tanking
because of the broken restroom.
All right.
When?
I'll fix it soon.
And should I tell my customers that?
When they want to use the restroom
should I say,
"You'll be able to poop soon"?
Don't you think it's too much?
People only come and go
from this shabby building
thanks to my café.
My lease expires next month.
I can't renew the lease
if you'll be like this.
Then don't.
What?
Cancel the lease!
Is the restroom that important?
Good grief.
Hey, Seon.
Where are you right now?
I'll be right there
after a quick stop somewhere
so wait there just a moment, okay?
Why won't you say anything?
I saw something weird just now.
What?
It's hard to explain in words.
What is it?
Stop making me feel impatient.
I just received a video
from Real Capital
and in the video…
Don't watch it!
What's wrong, Seon?
I mean, don't watch that video.
You might fall into danger
if you watch it, right?
Why would it be dangerous for me?
Just do as I say and don't watch it!
Why won't you listen?
Wait there until I come.
Okay? Got it?
Okay.
Taxi!
To Sejeong-ro Station, please.
Pick up the damn phone.
You can't even do a job this easy?
Huh?
I was told not to resort to violence.
Jonah.
We're an international entity.
This isn't some child's play.
Enough.
Leave.
Go.
Go!
Vice President.
Jonah.
Did you really think
you could take me down?
Huh?
Damn it.
I need to get changed.
Then we'll go eat.
Japanese food?
The person you're trying to reach
is not available…
The 28th floor.
What?
This is it.
What's your plan from now on?
That tteokbokki guy.
Do you have his business card?
DEPUTY NAM SANG-HO
Nam Sang-ho.
My phone.
SE-YOON BUILDING'S WIFE
SEJEONG-RO REDEVELOPMENT
SEJEONG-RO REDEVELOPMENT ZONE
BUILDING OWNER LIST
SE-YOON BUILDING
SEND TO TRASH
TRASH
DELETE FOREVER?
EMPTY TRASH
Kim Gyun.
ENTER A PASSWORD
TO UNLOCK THE DISK 'KIM'
The password?
Excuse me.
It's me.
There's something
that needs handling in the office.
Okay.
Man, this illegal video.
These kinds of videos
should never be watched or taken.
Anyway, who did Hwal-sung sleep with?
What if Yi-gyeong took notice?
Did you notice anything strange?
You know, like seeing another woman.
I feel like I should check this out.
Let me just check who it is.
Who on earth was he sleeping with?
Mr. Gi.
What brings you here?
I suppose you were feeling lonely.
Who are you?
Mr. Gi, what's your zodiac sign?
I was born in the Year of the Monkey.
DEPUTY NAM SANG-HO
He's in charge
of the redevelopment project.
In charge? Hardly.
A powerful man like you
is visiting me at my humble place?
It's an honor to meet you, sir.
I knew you two would get along.
Why don't you two meet up more often?
Anyway, can you do this later?
I'm feeling a bit bloated,
so let me do it a little longer.
A spinning session.
Are you sure you're doing it?
It doesn't sound like it.
It doesn't look like it,
but it's quite a workout.
I have cramps on my abs.
Look.
Can't you see that I'm sweating?
You can take it home later, Hee-ju.
It's my gift.
- Really?
- Sure.
- See? I told you he was a great guy.
- Stop.
The Year of the Monkey,
so born in 1980?
Yes.
I'm a Chicken myself,
so may I talk more casually?
Yes, of course.
Were you born in 1969?
No, in 1981.
In 1981? I see.
Why? Is there a problem?
No, sir.
You're so tacky. Why are you asking
for his zodiac sign?
Now, let's all grab a drink.
Now, let me pour you one.
- Mr. Gi.
- Sure, it's an honor.
- A drink for you.
- Thank you.
And you.
Allow me to pour you a drink.
- Nice to meet you.
- And you.
- It's great to meet everyone!
- It's great to meet you.
Now, Mr. Gi.
You did a great job
at keeping the building.
While everyone around sold and left
you did a great job
holding onto the place.
Goodness, don't mention it.
Well.
I kept telling them
that all they had to do was hold out.
But no one would believe me.
Now that we're on the subject
would you like to work with me?
Work with you?
I love an average person
who live as diligently
as you do, Mr. Gi.
Pull it out.
SEJEONG-RO REDEVELOPMENT
INVESTMENT CORPORATION
You wouldn't understand
even if you read through it.
You'll see something
called Nouveau City.
- It has 1% in the share.
- Yes.
SHAREHOLDER'S NAME, PERCENTAGE
NOUVEAU CITY, 1%
I have some connections
with people in that company.
All I need you to do is
bring your building into the project.
I'm thinking of giving you
a portion of the shares.
Shares?
I don't think I understand.
What's the expected return
for the project?
How much is my dividend?
If you get 1%
it's 100 billion won.
And from that
how much will Mr. Gi get?
As long as he brings
Se-yoon Building with him
shouldn't he get at least 20%?
If I get 20%, that's 20 billion won.
You held out until this day.
And ordinary people like you
should end up doing well.
Once you get your portion,
don't forget about me.
Wait, let's make a toast.
- Cheers.
- By any chance
is this illegal in any way?
Frankly, all I have is this building.
But you're offering me a share
and a huge dividend.
Illegal? I'm a civil servant
who works for the state.
If you're curious,
look over the document.
Goodness.
I almost forgot.
I have to be somewhere soon.
Hee-ju.
You can finish your workout.
I will.
In that case
I'll see you soon.
Yes, sir.
Just give me a call.
Bye!
SEJEONG-RO CAFÉ JIMSIM
GOOD OWNER, NICE COFFEE
I FOUND A NICE CAFÉ
BUT IT ONLY HAS ONE BROKEN RESTROOM
I COULDN'T USE THE RESTROOM,
SO I LEFT…
My damned landlord.
I'll just fix it myself.
How do you know about Mr. Nam?
You need to know these things
- to run a real estate office.
- Your network is…
Hey, welcome.
"Welcome"?
I'm not your boss.
What's wrong? You can stay longer.
I was about to leave, anyway.
Can you send this to my office?
Yes, sure.
I'll bring it to you. Bye, Hee-ju.
Thanks for today.
- I'm leaving.
- Bye.
Hey, don't start.
Nothing happened.
I didn't ask.
- Have a seat.
- Okay.
Gosh.
Did you not sign the deal
because of her?
No, no way.
Seon.
Hear me out, Seon.
There's a huge project.
It hasn't been announced officially
but the redevelopment zone
has changed
to include Se-yoon Building.
I would have to be an idiot
to sell the building right now.
Your phone.
Why?
Give me your phone.
Here.
- The password.
- Unbelievable.
The password.
You're acting weird today.
I need to check your text messages.
Go ahead.
You could be messing around with her.
What is this nonsense?
What do you take me for?
Jeez.
SEND TO TRASH
What are you doing right now?
Hey, give it back.
Give it back to me.
Hey, what's with you today?
DELETE FOREVER?
DELETE
Are you deleting something?
These people at Real Capital
are dangerous people.
What if they use this video
to hack your bank account
or something?
What are you talking about?
Tell me what that video's about.
Whatever it is…
Well, it doesn't feel right.
What is it? Why have you been
obsessing over that video?
Spill the beans honestly.
I erased everything.
What are you going to do?
It's still in the messages.
You can see it, right?
Let's watch it together.
Hey, Kim Seon.
Hey.
YOU ENTERED THE WRONG PIN
Hey, open the door.
I have the key.
Darn it. What's the password?
Why is she suddenly acting weird?
What now?
Damn it.
Hey, that phone is insured anyway.
What is this?
It's okay. Feel free to destroy it.
What's the big deal?
What are you doing?
It's waterproof.
Do you have to watch it?
That's making me even more curious.
You should keep an eye on your wife.
So?
How did that go?
Everything ended well.
I'm glad.
You look beautiful.
I told you not to watch it.
Is that all you can say?
You didn't sell it?
What reason?
Didn't they say anything?
This isn't up to you!
Wait.
Did you make a deal
with Real Capital?
What deal?
I mean
did they hold this against you
to convince you
to let them have the building?
Su-jong.
It's not like that. It's not.
It was all a show, right?
You lied when you said you wanted
to live in the States with Da-rae!
A show?
No, that isn't the case.
Who's here at this hour?
Are you expecting someone?
No.
Isn't it the restroom right above?
Hold on.
You can stay here.
No, I'm coming too.
Then pick up something.
Wait.
Who could it be?
Who are you?
Grab him.
Are you okay, Seon?
I got this punk.
Yes, who is this punk?
Seon.
- It's Oh Dong-ki.
- What?
It's Oh Dong-ki.
Why did you stab him?
What do you mean?
The scissors.
What do I do?
Why was he here?
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
Why do things only go haywire for me?
What now?
What is this, Hwal-sung?
Hwal-sung had a woman on the side.
She was a married woman with a kid.
Real Capital.
Close the case as an accident.
You told me to bring
Jung Chang-su's body, so I did.
Why won't you let me investigate?
Three billion won.
My mom hasn't given up on that.
She's not someone
who can live with a loss.
Why don't you pay him to keep quiet?
What if he starts talking
after taking the money?
- Do you hear something?
- Hear what?
I thought I heard someone screaming.
Let's do our best to persuade.
- If that fails…
- If that fails?
We must choose.
Will it be our family or him?
Subtitles by Eunsook Youn
and Jennifer Lim