ADAPTED FROM THE NOVEL HIDDEN LOVE BY ZHU YI
I'll go and focus on my great endeavors.
Don't come back too late.
Okay.
Be careful.
-Bye. -Stay safe.
Bye.
I forgot to tell you.
You should treat Duan Jiaxu to dinner
when you're free.
He's not snitching on you but concerned about you.
Look.
For the past two years, he kept asking
about your grades and life.
He didn't ask you directly
so you wouldn't feel pressured.
Whenever it was your birthday,
when you got good grades
or during the holidays,
he sent you all kinds of gifts.
He was flat broke himself,
but he still sent you gifts.
Remember, treat him to dinner.
IF YOU'RE EVER OUT SO LATE, FIND SOMEONE TO ACCOMPANY YOU BACK
I've been ignoring him.
Maybe that wasn't very nice of me.
After all, he hasn't done anything wrong.
From the start, he has been nice to me.
I feel like an ingrate now.
THE DREAM GAMES
Last year, A Dream of Jianghu's expansion,
Fury of Mount Guan hit the market.
The main theme was
an attachment to the homeland
and an underdog hero.
After it went online,
the reception was good.
The players also gave it stellar ratings.
So this year's expansion
is very important to us.
I mentioned this in past meetings.
I hope to see innovation and breakthroughs
in all aspects.
Dawang, how are your preparations?
Everything is set.
Unlike last year's Fury of Mount Guan,
we will be returning to the root
of martial arts fantasy and gameplay.
We will be releasing
unconventional martial arts playstyles.
They will serve as a mechanism
to create more novel stories and content.
I will now show you
the roadmap I came up with.
ROADMAP
I've designed updates to the maps,
characters, instances, and gameplay
around the main quest progression
of the new factions.
I also worked with colleagues from the Art Department
to come up with a new solution
for the game art style.
I think this theme is pretty good.
It piques my interest.
We should make use of our time
and conduct a player survey.
Now,
it has been over a year
since the last feature technical update.
Does anyone have any new ideas?
Hold on.
I wonder if you still remember
the Celestial Progression System that I proposed?
It uses an AI algorithm
for self-progression.
It makes the behavioral models and feedback of our NPCs
a lot more life-like and logical.
It gives players the feeling
that every creation
has its own progression throughout time.
In other words, it recreates
a convincing martial arts world.
But this proposal had already been rejected.
I don't think
we have the technical prowess
to finish this plan.
That's true.
Therefore, our team came up with a demo
based on pre-research
so we can show you.
You are now looking at the NPC
known as Fang Siming,
whom you're probably familiar with.
It's one of the popular characters among the players
of A Dream of Jianghu.
I'll now use him
to demonstrate the pre-research effect
of our system.
I will interact with the NPC as a player.
Li Xun, help me with the feedback.
It's starting.
The NPC looks like he's good at Wuchang chess.
Do you think so?
I bet he's better than Li Xun.
The NPC's reaction was quick.
He's agile.
It seems
that someone has failed to win a drink.
Instead, they owe me a drink.
Li Xun lost!
All right.
I'll pay up next time. Put it on the tab.
Li Xun is backing out.
Fine, I owe you one.
-That's not cool, Li Xun. -Put it on my tab. I'll pay next time.
A SWORD OF FROST
I'll remember this.
This drink is on me.
Do you care to accept it?
Not bad. He's even flirting with me.
During the design stage,
we set the character's interests
based on the game lore
and the character's back story.
These NPCs are enthused when they interact
with the players.
They can react in a way
that forms a deeper connection
with the players.
But a different player
might not choose to play chess with him.
Is there a way for us to make the NPCs
flexibly handle any situation?
That involves the data
fed to the AI.
Our algorithm
will record every player's experiences and behaviors
after they log into the game.
So the Celestial Progression System's NPCs
will come up with different reactions and feedback
to different players.
We could give it a try right now.
We can test it
with a more active account.
Fang Siming.
It has been a while.
Why are you drinking alone?
FOLLOW THE EGRET
I invited the moon to a drink.
My shadow, a second companion.
There's no way I can't get a drink from him.
Laosan, get it for me.
Okay.
I don't care! I want it!
Bad footwork.
That won't get you a drink, my friend.
Fang Siming is an interesting guy.
Theoretically speaking,
when a large amount of data is fed to the AI,
it will manifest its own behavior
when the amount of data reaches a certain level.
This is the part
that AI researchers across the globe
are particularly interested in.
If we can have a technical upgrade
in this regard,
it could be a huge breakthrough
for our game.
But this is just a demo.
If we are to complete this system successfully,
we need to invest in a lot of NPCs into the game.
Given our staff and technical capabilities,
I fear it might not be viable.
If we rush headlong into this,
we might add more risks to the project.
That is a problem.
I need time
to think this over.
Is there anything else
to present in this meeting?
No.
That's all for today.
Okay.
-Okay. -Okay.
Well done.
You think that will be
a risky move, right?
I think it's a bit risky.
Jiaxu,
there are bound to be problems.
But there will also be solutions.
Solutions outnumber problems.
Yes, Li Xun. Don't worry.
Keep at it.
It's all right.
We've just started.
This is normal.
I'll call for a meeting
with our team.
Sure.
-Keep at it. -Keep at it.
Your cup.
Jiaxu,
when might you be free?
If it is no trouble,
I would like to treat you to dinner
as a thank you for taking me home.
If you are too busy at the moment,
it is all right.
You can decide the time.
If you are not sure when you are free,
how about next weekend?
I would like to use this chance
to express my gratitude to you.
"When might you be free?
If it is no trouble,
I would like to treat you to dinner
as a thank you for taking me home."
Next weekend?
SANG ZHI
You may decide the time too.
How formal.
VOICE CALL INVITATION FROM JIAXU
JIAXU
Hello, Jiaxu.
I'm free next weekend,
but I'm not sure about the specific time.
It's all right.
We can accommodate your schedule.
Okay.
By the way,
I'll take you to a phone repair shop as well.
My phone?
Why would I repair it?
Isn't it broken?
It's not.
I thought it must be broken.
Your texts are so formal.
Where did that come from?
You were never so formal with me.
Your words are so polite.
I remember now.
Does this mean
I have a place in your heart?
Jiaxu.
Here's the thing.
My dad told me
to be respectful to anyone older than me
by five years or more.
If I remember correctly, you're five years older than me.
Your voice sounds young,
but you can't fool anyone.
You're not young anymore.
-So-- -I'm hanging up now. Bye.
Wait.
Hello?
I have something else to tell you.
What is it?
I didn't mean to ignore you
by not replying or calling you back.
I was living on campus.
I didn't have my phone with me.
I know.
Your brother told me that.
You knew?
Then why did you even ask?
Okay, that's it.
That's all for now.
I'm done.
Bye.
CHAPTER NINE, UNDERCURRENT
I CAN'T HELP FALLING IN LOVE
Wait for me!
-Okay. -Wait for me.
-Hurry up. -Where is Weiwei?
No idea. She left in a hurry this morning.
Maybe she went to a club meeting.
Who knows?
Sang Zhi.
Jiang Ming.
What are you doing here?
I'm here for Sang Zhi.
Me?
What is it?
Everyone,
look at who's coming.
Ning Wei!
What's going on?
The two of us
are dating.
Yes, we can see that.
Ning Wei.
You don't waste any time, do you?
Are those matching outfits?
Yes.
That's right.
You were here to see Sangsang.
I got premiere tickets last night.
Sang Zhi,
would you like to go with me?
Are you inviting her only?
That's not nice.
Indeed.
Shut it.
If you're all free, feel free to join us.
-We're free. -Yes.
-Yes. -Okay.
This Sunday at 8:00 p.m.,
meet at Joy City Cinema.
-Okay. -Hold on. This Sunday?
I probably can't make it.
I already have plans.
What plans?
No, Sangsang.
Come with us.
-Come on. -Let's go together.
It has been ages since we've watched a movie.
If things get awkward
during dinner with him,
I'll have an excuse to leave.
Come on.
We'll go. Sunday, 8:00 p.m.
Great.
-We'll go. -See you at the cinema.
-Okay. -See you there.
This is all thank you to you.
-Let's go to class. -Thank you.
We have a class now.
Let's go.
Come on.
-Bye! -Chen Qiang!
Let's go.
I'm coming.
Are you Mr. Duan Jiaxu?
-Yes. -Your parcel.
-Thank you. -You're welcome.
TO DUAN JIAXU, FROM JIANG YING
Did you receive the parcel?
I sent you some tonics
and an essential oil lamp for stress relief.
Take care of yourself.
Let's have dinner sometime.
JIANG YING, TRANSFER AMOUNT: 8,000 YUAN
WAITING FOR JIANG YING TO CONFIRM TRANSFER
I've wired the last compensation payment.
Do not contact me again.
Okay.
It makes your skin look fair.
DUAN JIAXU
I'VE WIRED THE LAST COMPENSATION PAYMENT.
DO NOT CONTACT ME AGAIN.
JIANG YING
Don't contact you again? What do you mean?
Jiaxu, when will you be free?
Can we meet up?
JIANG YING
Come on, the meeting is starting.
In a moment.
Have you only eaten half an egg today?
You also skipped lunch.
I'll eat it during the meeting.
I'll bring it inside for you.
I've decided to employ Xiaoduan's idea.
The Celestial Progression System will be the new feature.
However, the new storyline,
instances, factions, and maps
must remain the main focus.
If we are going down this path,
the Planning and Art Departments
will fully cooperate.
But given the current circumstances,
I can't come up with a way to assign the work
so that everyone can deliver quality work on time.
Whether the Celestial Progression System
is compatible with most smartphones
is also another problem.
Dawang's concern is justified.
Jiaxu,
do you have a solution for that?
Well, my idea so far
is to take some workload off other departments
with technical methods.
For example,
manual form filling and whatnot
can be done with technology.
Since it has been decided,
let's give it our best.
We'll solve every problem along the way.
Okay?
If you ever need coordination,
just let us know.
Dawang and Xiaoduan will be in charge
of this new project.
Let's go.
Back to work.
All the best.
Hello, Jiaxu. I'm here.
Where are you?
Sorry, Sang Zhi.
I don't think I can make it tonight.
Are you working overtime?
Yes.
Order something for yourself.
Don't starve.
Your voice sounds off.
Are you not feeling well?
Not at all.
What's wrong?
It's just a little stomach pain.
Maybe it's food poisoning.
It's all right. I'll just take some medicine.
But shouldn't you go to the hospital?
No need. This is nothing serious.
Why don't you go to the hospital?
Holding off the pain won't make it better.
Where is your office located?
Don't trouble yourself.
I'm all right.
Where is your office located?
Gangbei Complex.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Hello, sir.
Gangbei Complex.
THE DREAM GAMES
Sang Zhi.
What are you doing here?
-You came. -Are you feeling better?
It's nothing. It's just a stomachache.
Wait here. I'll get a taxi.
I'll take you to the hospital.
Sang Zhi.
-I'll go with you. -Just wait here for me.
It's all right.
Let me take this.
Lean on me.
-I'm okay. -Let's go.
Come on. Watch your step.
Are you helping an old man, kiddo?
Can you walk on your own?
I…
-Slowly. -I'm not saying you're a kid.
It's all right.
Be careful.
Wait here for me.
Okay.
Wait here.
Hey.
Be careful.
I'll book a ride.
What is the address?
I didn't mean to do that.
I didn't mean to either.
Jiaxu, get in the car.
HAIXIA TAXI
Watch out.
-I'm fine. -Mind your head.
Hello.
-Hello. -Hello.
Is he drunk or something?
-No. -Is he going to throw up?
No, sir.
Sir, I won't throw up.
I can hang in there.
No, let me say this first.
If you throw up in the car,
you pay 200 yuan.
Okay?
He won't throw up.
He has stomach pains.
Go to the hospital.
Take us to the hospital.
-Okay. -Sir, please hurry.
Okay.
OUTPATIENT BUILDING
Judging by the ultrasound,
it's acute appendicitis.
And you waited to come in.
Had you come any later, it would've ruptured.
What do we do now?
One is conservative therapy.
-We admit you and ease the inflammation. -I see.
The other method
is going straight to surgery.
-Then-- -Do the surgery.
Okay.
It will be all right.
Sang Zhi.
It's late. Head back to campus.
It will be unsafe later.
I'll wait for you outside.
It's not a major surgery.
-It's okay. -I'll wait for you.
The surgery will take--
Stop talking.
Go and get yourself something to eat.
Had we not had plans for dinner today,
he would have just held it off
and never come to the hospital.
"Avoid overworking.
Avoid alcohol."
MOM
Hello, Mom.
Hello, Zhizhi.
It's past ten. Why haven't you called me?
Are you at the dorm
or hanging out with friends?
No.
Do you remember Sang Yan's classmate?
He gave me physics lessons
when I was in high school.
Duan Jiaxu.
I remember. Xiaoduan, right?
We had plans to have dinner together,
but he suddenly fell ill,
so I took him to the hospital.
Is he sick?
What is it?
Is it serious?
Acute appendicitis.
He's in surgery now.
Poor thing.
He doesn't have a family.
What do you mean?
His home is in Yihe, isn't it?
I never told you about his background.
Mr. Sang.
There are 6,000 yuan left
after the funeral.
I'm returning this to you.
I'll pay you the remaining balance
after I get a job.
Xiaoduan, keep the money for yourself.
Don't rush to repay us.
No, you have to take the money.
Keep it.
Keep the money and use it.
You've been through a lot.
I'm all right.
It was nothing.
Mr. and Mrs. Sang,
you should take the money.
There are other things I must attend to.
I should get going.
Thank you for your time.
Xiaoduan.
Dinner is ready.
Eat before you go.
No, thank you, Mrs. Sang.
Thank you
for looking after me during this time.
Without you…
Thank you so much.
You don't have to do this, child.
Stand up.
I'm going to go.
The poor child.
He's just a college freshman about 18 years old.
Who knows what else he will face?
Sang Yan, look after him in school.
Okay.
In less than six months,
he paid us back the rest of the sum.
But his mom
had passed away.
Zhizhi.
Don't stay out too late.
Be safe on the way back.
I'm hanging up now.
He has to be hospitalized for seven days.
He can't have solid food for now.
He has to be on a liquid diet for a week.
Should anything come up, just let us know.
Thank you.
Jiaxu.
I asked the nurses.
They said these are what you need
while you're in the hospital.
But if you need anything else,
let me know.
I'll get it for you.
Thank you, Sang Zhi.
It's getting late.
You should head back to campus.
Get a taxi when you leave.
Send the plate number to me.
Let me know when you reach the dorm.
Okay?
Jiaxu.
I'm not a kid anymore.
Don't worry about me.
I know what to do.
Okay.
Leave the things here.
I'll put them away later.
Did the wound hurt?
I got anesthetics,
so it doesn't hurt at all.
I don't feel a thing.
Don't worry.
Go back now.
I'll visit you tomorrow.
Come when you don't have classes.
I'm an adult.
Don't trouble yourself for me.
I'll be fine. Go on.
Is she upset?
She probably minds that.
Hello?
Hello, buddy.
I heard you got your appendix cut out.
How does that feel?
Not bad. Would you like to try it?
No, thank you.
But I heard my sister took you there.
Yes.
Did you have to trouble her for such a small problem?
Couldn't you go to the hospital yourself?
Did you call just to tell me that?
No, I had dinner with my parents.
They told me you were sick,
so I called to celebrate.
If there's nothing else, I'm hanging up.
I'll carry on with my game.
Hold on.
I want to tell you something.
What is it?
Forget it. It's nothing important.
Buddy, can you not do this every time?
Just spill it like a real man!
It's nothing. Bye.
Hey!
Why did you come back?
Jiaxu.
I gave it some thought.
I should stay and look after you.
If I were to fall sick and had no one by my side,
you would do the same for me.
Right?
Did you have dinner?
I brought dinner.
You haven't eaten. Are you only having bread?
Forget this.
I'll order takeouts.
Don't do that. I'm not hungry.
You haven't eaten all day.
You must be starving.
I'm not hungry at all.
If I were, I would get something to eat.
I'm not a kid anymore.
I don't need you to worry.
She is stuffed like a pufferfish again.
Jiaxu, what's so funny?
Nothing.
Where are you going?
I'm going to freshen up.
Go on.
He can't get out of bed today.
So he can't clean himself.
Maybe I should help him wipe…
Jiaxu.
The doctor said you can't shower today.
Do you want to wipe your face?
Sure.
I can help you.
It's okay. I'll manage.
What if you open up your wound?
You'll have to spend even more days here.
All right.
I don't have a nice outfit to wear to the movie!
It's just across from campus.
You still spent ages on your makeup.
Let's go.
Of course it's necessary!
Girls want to look their best
when meeting someone they like.
You don't get it.
Okay, I don't get it.
Ning Wei is a love expert.
Come on.
Wait for me.
You look good enough. Let's go.
Just wait for a second!
Hurry up.
I know. Stop rushing me.
Bye, Sangsang.
Bye.
Hurry up!
I'll be right there.
We're leaving. Bye!
-Hurry up! -See you later.
Bye!
It has been so long.
You've learned how to put on makeup.
You're indeed different from before.