[Mayor Kingpin] I'm keeping you safe
because remember, I love you, New York.
[AG Steverud] You're giving yourself
a lot of emergency power.
Your Safer Streets initiative
equates vigilantes with terrorists.
[Angela] They took my tía. The Task Force.
People usually disappear after that.
[Fisk] I vowed to clean up the streets,
and I did.
- [gun fires]
- [body thuds]
You're being held
under the Safer Streets Act.
You're not at Rikers.
The NYPD has no jurisdiction
over this place,
or any idea of your whereabouts.
[Hochberg] Kirsten, plead out.
Avoid losing the Duquesne case.
[Kirsten] Oh, Ben, fuck you.
[Lt. Governor Gomez] Now you've got a ship
capsized in the East River.
[Mr. Charles] I could put together
a little night crew
from all over the world.
[Matt] He's using the Freeport
to smuggle arms.
[clock ticking]
[Matt] If Fisk moves those guns
into Red Hook, they vanish.
[Karen] I have something to show you.
[all grunting]
[Karen] They're hunting us.
Maybe it's time we started hunting them.
[sirens wailing]
[Karen] What choice did I have?
Sit there and wait for them
to come in shooting?
Look, I did a little recon.
Recon?
[officer grunting]
What... What is going on with you?
[chuckles shakily] This is how we end it.
- By kidnapping Task Force?
- What if it works?
Look, the reason that
I brought him here is...
I'm telling you,
something's different about him.
Different how?
Hey, wait, wait, wait, wait.
You're wrong. I was looking for you.
- Yeah, to kill us.
- No!
Whatever you... The Resistance is,
- I want to help.
- Bullshit. It's a trap.
- No. No, it's not...
- Talk. Talk!
Powell, the rest of them, they're psychos.
You either go with them or you're dead.
[breathing heavily]
What Fisk is doing to you guys,
hunting you, it's wrong!
- You're lying. You're a liar.
- I'm not lying.
- You are lying to us.
- I'm not!
Yeah, he's telling the truth.
Okay.
So you wanna help us. So what?
I'm part of a detail
at Red Hook. Okay?
We're watching the Northern Star.
Check my left pocket.
That will get you in everywhere.
But the code changes at midnight, daily.
- You're lying to me.
- I'm not lying.
- You're lying.
Look at me.
What's your name?
Saunders.
- Alan Saunders.
- Okay, Alan.
The hood's going back on.
I'm gonna hit you hard.
It's gonna hurt.
Karen will take you outside.
Tell your squad I beat you down.
If you're lying to me, you fuck,
I'll find you.
And I'll be unhappy.
I'm not.
You've got to stop Fisk.
You're the only one who can...
[♪ Theme music playing]
[sighs]
[whimpers softly]
[breathing heavily]
[inhales sharply]
One...
[sniffles]
two
three.
[breathing heavily]
[indistinct chatter]
Kirsten.
Hey, Heather.
- Are you okay?
- Uh, no.
Hochberg pulled the trial up by two weeks,
so I'm pissed.
I didn't know.
You're seriously making this more awkward?
I read your psych eval on Duquesne.
It's a hatchet job.
These men you're defending
are dangerous. Don't you see that?
Frank Castle is a murderer.
Him and Daredevil might've killed Matt.
Or he was working with them, I don't know.
Heather, I...
I don't think that that's what happened.
In my gut, I just...
Matt was a liar about so many things.
I don't know what to believe
when it comes to him.
He lied to you, too.
You're right.
And, yeah, Matt was...
Is complicated.
But he's a good man
who's probably in serious danger
because of Wilson Fisk.
Honestly, Kirsten, as your friend,
I don't think you're seeing
any of this clearly.
Why would you work for Fisk?
Because
he's genuinely trying to
make this city a safer place.
I was on the other end of that
vigilante violence, you weren't.
- Heather...
- You weren't here
when Matt disappeared. So, unless
some maniac in a mask is trying to
cut you open, don't judge me.
Hey. Hey.
I am really sorry
for what happened to you.
I am.
Fisk isn't the answer.
If you don't mind,
I have to go defend a "dangerous man"
against an entire system
hell-bent on putting him away.
[machinery whirring]
[guard on radio] HQ, checking
confirmation clearance on gate.
Come on, step out.
Stop.
This way.
- Can I take this thing off?
- Nope.
[buzzer blares]
You need to watch your step.
[Kirsten] You know, you're breaking
ten different laws here.
This isn't how "reasonable access
to legal counsel" is supposed to go.
Your client's a terrorist...
That requires
a staggering burden of proof.
Fuckin' lawyers. Look,
you're getting your visit.
No need to give me shit about it.
Besides, ma'am...
I'm just trying to do my job.
[glass shattering nearby]
[pigeons cooing]
[wings fluttering]
[water dripping]
[metal clanking]
Stop.
[beeps]
[buzzer blares]
- Forward.
- [door creaks]
Forward.
Stop.
Remove the goggles.
Finally.
You got 15 minutes.
Don't try shit.
That goes for you, too.
[beeps]
Mr. Duquesne.
It's a pleasure to finally meet you.
I'm surprised they agreed to
such legal niceties.
Well, I filed about
a dozen separate legal briefs.
Most of them question
the validity of this trial.
I think you mean tribunal.
Yeah.
It's a mess.
At least Hochberg
agreed to this... meeting.
He doesn't want to
set a precedent this early.
So, I'm the first, aren't I?
Yeah, you are.
Which means I have no idea
how this is gonna go.
- Sorry.
- Well...
I imagine it will be quite a spectacle.
Fisk needs this. A public show.
[in French] Les guillotines
sur la Place de la Nation.
[in English] To think, this started out
as just a garden-variety shakedown.
Shakedown?
Fisk wanted me to
invest in his port project.
I refused,
et voilà.
If this was really about vigilantes,
I think he'd go after more than just
his personal enemies.
If Fisk can prove you're the Swordsman,
he'll take what he wants,
and the law allows it.
"Forfeiture of a criminal's assets."
You know, the similarities
to the Reign of Terror never cease.
So, when do they loot St. Patrick's now?
I think it's on Tuesday.
Perfect.
The thing is, I've seen the discovery.
The district attorney has no proof
you are who Fisk says you are.
Do they need that these days, Counselor?
I don't know.
[agitated chatter outside]
I really don't know.
[guard] Hey, over here!
- Hey!
- [detainee 1] Help!
- [guard] Move!
- Somebody help us!
- Help.
- [detainee 2] Help me!
- Help me!
- [detainee 3] Somebody help, please!
[detainees clamoring]
[detainee 4] Help!
Help me!
[detainee 2] Please help us!
[detainee 1] Somebody help me!
[Karen sighs]
[Matt] You're turning into Frank.
[chuckles]
Well, he always said,
- "Know your enemy, they're all you have."
- Yeah.
Sounds extremely Frank.
You think he's dead?
No, not a chance.
If he was, Fisk would hang his corpse
off the Brooklyn Bridge.
Taking out the Punisher?
He'd sing that from the rooftops.
So, what? So, he's just... [scoffs]
All this, he's just out there just
being him.
Same as always.
[chuckles dryly] I don't know.
He's always been there for me.
For us, before, so...
[sighs heavily]
Well, what are you, uh...
You want his help?
Well, I mean
he is effective.
You realize murder is not how we win this?
- Karen?
- Jesus Christ. Okay.
Okay. Of course. I am not suggesting
that we go out and start murdering
random Task Force, but
cutting the head off the snake?
Does killing Fisk bring Foggy back?
Would he have wanted that?
Trust me, I wonder
the same thing every day.
Vanessa killed Foggy and nothing happened.
Fisk got elected,
he turns the whole city
into his piggy bank,
guarded by thugs with badges,
and nothing fucking happened.
- I know.
- It just feels like we are up against,
- so much.
- [sighs heavily]
And we still have a system
that is not entirely broken.
Yeah.
[sighs heavily]
Are you sure the Governor got a copy?
[Karen] I am.
Where did this come from?
Anonymous.
Come on, Gomez.
Nothing's anonymous.
Especially not a document like that.
[door closes]
[Governor McCaffrey] You sic your
CIA friend on my Attorney General.
You refuse financial assistance.
You're trying to avoid state oversight.
If I need help, I will ask.
It was a deft move, developing Red Hook,
knowing its status as a free port
would lead to incredible profits
with minimal accountability.
I understand that Fisk Industries
and your wife Vanessa
are major shareholders.
All of it transferred into a trust
when I took office.
All the paperwork, completely legal.
I have no doubt. But money and
an army of white-shoe lawyers
doesn't make you immune.
Well
still no idea what's inside Red Hook.
New construction had
no blueprints, at least
none that we could steal.
[chuckles softly]
Okay. So
you get inside,
- then what?
- I torch the weapons.
- Oh, my God.
- Make a big noise.
You get your sources
to put it out there, and
we force everyone in New York
to see who he is,
to know what he does.
You know, I recently received a copy
of the Charter of 1855.
The Freeport status is
perpetual and inviolable.
It can only be revoked
by the order of the Governor.
Well, I sincerely hope for New York's sake
that you're not considering such a thing.
The Governor will have to revoke it.
I'm gonna be okay.
You don't know that. You don't know that.
[clears throat]
Every time you go out,
there's no guarantee you return.
[Governor McCaffrey]
Mayor Fisk, I've turned a blind eye
to your Emergency Powers,
Safer Streets, Vigilante Trials,
because
on paper, and with most of
the voting public, it's working.
I'm glad we agree on that.
I'm all for giving enough rope.
But when a tanker with dubious cargo
capsizes in the East River,
that's when the rope pulls taut.
"Dubious cargo"? I don't know
where you get your information.
You don't, do you?
If you'll excuse me.
- [sighs]
- [door closes]
I'm not saying don't go, I'm just...
[sighs] Please, let's just be
very, very prepared.
[chuckles softly]
Fuck.
[knock on door]
You do realize we have the Governor's
Dinner in an hour, don't you?
Yeah. First rule,
don't eat at those things.
What if it's gross?
You're talking, you're munching.
What if you laugh and spray food
all over the Deputy Lieutenant?
Not me.
Besides, they're good. Try one.
- I'm good.
- You're good now,
but maybe try the shrimp cocktail.
Thirty minutes goes by, you're sweating.
Gut's about to blow.
You wanna puke on the Governor?
I don't.
They're dope as hell.
Try one. Come on, trust me.
Not bad.
I told you.
What's up?
- What do you know about the Governor?
- You mean opposition research
- from her last election?
- Well, maybe exactly that.
Basically, Marge McCaffrey's
boring as fuck.
Not a speck of dirt or personality.
She's like a nun with a machine gun.
Played it perfectly for decades.
She won't drop a stitch now.
Everyone's hiding something.
That's why I'm getting
the Lieutenant Governor loose and talking.
What, and you think he'll give you,
a total stranger, his secrets, do you?
I got you to eat street meat.
What do you think's in there?
[scoffs]
You got any tips?
Excuse me?
I'm sure you learnt
some interrogation skills up at, you know,
Herefordshire.
[chuckles] I'm sorry, where?
Come on, you were a squaddie, right?
I mean, Special Air Service
for Her Majesty?
Special Ops?
Don't look so shocked.
I get intel, too.
How high are you now?
No, I'm...
I'm not high right now.
Have you considered using these, um
intelligence skills to find out
who's feeding the "City Without Fear"?
Yeah, I'm on it.
- I told you, I'm on it.
- Good.
'Cause you wouldn't want
the squaddie stealing your kill.
[exhales sharply]
- No.
Whoever is mocking the mayor
must be punished, correct?
Of course. Yes, of course.
I promise that I'll figure out who it is.
Great.
He really hates that mask, doesn't he?
- Wouldn't you?
- I don't know.
I mean, getting roasted like that
is kinda flattering.
No.
It's not flattering.
Find out who it is,
turn them to me.
All sorted.
Right.
[static buzzes]
[Mayor Kingpin] It's me again!
Your favorite Mayor Kingpin,
here to make a better New York.
Look at this guy and his puny sword.
He calls himself "The Swordsman"?
Don't worry, size doesn't matter,
said no swordsman ever!
But now that I've got him,
he's going to have a hard time
"swording out" his problems.
[maniacal laughter]
Jack Duquesne,
this bargain basement Zorro,
thinks he's such a great guy,
donating millions of dollars
to lame places like children's hospitals
and woman shelters. Woof.
Swordsman, another bored socialite
pushing his vigilante agenda
on the "weak and defenseless."
Don't they know New Yorkers don't need
any protection from these masked losers
because I can save them.
Me and my friendly neighborhood Task Force
are here to protect you.
Or throw you into a windowless box
where no one can find you.
Because remember, I love you...
New York.
[indistinct chatter]
[sighs heavily]
[camera shutters clicking]
[indistinct chatter]
[bailiff] All rise.
[whispers] Sell them the truth.
[doors closing]
What's with the face?
Buck up, buttercup.
Come on.
Let's do some good.
[gavel strikes]
[Hochberg] "His demeanor
is combative, hostile.
"When challenged,
he experiences eruptions of temper,
"sometimes consistent with
violent episodes of mania,
"like those found in violent offenders"
"like the recent serial killer
known as 'Muse.'"
Objection. Baseless speculation,
Your Honors.
Well, this is the clinical report of
a respected psychiatrist, Your Honors.
Do I need to remind the defense that
Dr. Glenn has extensive
firsthand experience
with these kinds of violent killers?
- Okay. Objection!
- [camera shutters clicking]
Assumes facts not in evidence.
Nowhere in this report
does Dr. Glenn say that my client
is a serial killer.
Overruled. Mr. Hochberg,
continue with the report,
and, please, do try not to editorialize.
Thank you, Your Honors.
[Matt] This is a mockery
of the justice system.
He's crucifying Duquesne.
Everyone's buying it.
No, no, not everyone.
People are pissed.
That's why he needs the Swordsman trial.
It keeps people guessing,
keeps 'em scared.
Right, right.
- Hearts and minds...
- Win the war.
[Kirsten] Mr. Duquesne,
I would like you to tell the court
what you told me...
Hey. Hold up. Doesn't that...
- Doesn't that mean...
- Somebody else got into Red Hook.
Mr. Fisk had been pressuring me
to fund his port project.
At the Ball
- he took me aside and he threatened me.
- Objection.
Irrelevant. The mayor isn't on trial.
- Well, maybe he should be.
- Sustained.
- Your Honors, may counsel approach?
- You may.
It took me six weeks
to get access to my client,
and you gave me two days' notice.
We sent a scheduling change to
Ms. McDuffie's email address weeks ago.
To my dead Manhattan Superior Court email.
Don't be a dick, Hochberg.
Your Honors, you see what I'm up against?
Thing is, Your Honor, it seems the media
had more time to prepare than I did.
[Chief Justice Waters] There is
an enormous public interest
in this case, Counselor,
and as you only have the afternoon,
I suggest you get to your point.
My point is
my client deserves a proper defense,
and I have had no time to give it to him.
Please allow me the latitude
to build a case for him here today.
I am not unsympathetic, Ms. McDuffie.
However, under
the Safer Streets initiative,
our hands are tied.
You know what's missing here, don't you?
One single shred of proof
that my client is who you,
or should I say Mayor Fisk, says he is.
- You're out of order.
- Nice, Kirsten.
- This isn't justice and you know it.
- You are close to contempt, Counselor.
[low chatter]
[camera shutters clicking]
Really wish you'd taken my offer.
[gavel strikes]
[Chief Justice Waters]
Both the people and the defense
have presented sufficient arguments.
[Kirsten] Objection.
[Chief Justice Waters] Overruled.
We are ready to issue a verdict.
Please rise, Mr. Duquesne.
I'm sorry.
Don't be. This was inevitable.
[Chief Justice Waters sighs]
Jack Duquesne,
on the charge of conspiracy to violate
the anti-vigilante laws
of the state of New York,
this court finds you guilty.
- [people clamoring]
- A farce.
Shit, get this.
[Chief Justice Waters]
On the charge of vigilantism,
which includes the repeated
and willfully violent offenses of
assault and attempted murder,
this court finds you guilty.
For the entertainment of the masses.
Sentencing will follow later.
Until such time,
you will be remanded back to detention.
- Court's adjourned.
- [gavel strikes]
Presented in all its ugly glory
by the man whose hand holds the scale.
[laughing]
[Daniel] There we go.
[grunts in content]
[sirens wailing, fading]
[birds chirping, fading]
[knocking on door]
[woman] It's starting.
I'll be right there.
[indistinct chatter]
[♪ light instrumental music playing]
- Sheila.
- Marge.
- So sorry we didn't speak earlier.
- You know you were missed here.
- Oh, yeah.
I'll bet. Yeah.
I really wish you were with us in Albany.
I imagine you do, too.
Oh... The city is my home.
She obeys the alternate side parking,
and she's Governor.
She's squeaky clean.
She's like Mother Teresa, okay?
- The job is everything.
- Everybody's got something.
And if there was something little,
you'd know.
You look lovely.
Your earrings are beautiful.
Thank you.
I hear congratulations are in order.
You were instrumental
in keeping Jack Duquesne off the streets.
I just did my job.
Always so modest. [Chuckles]
Celebrate your successes.
By the way...
I put you next to Buck Cashman.
Mrs. Fisk, you didn't have to do that.
Probably not,
but it's certainly entertaining.
For you or for me?
Well, that's entirely up to you.
[chuckles softly]
Oh. Dr. Glenn.
This is a pleasant surprise.
Apparently, Mrs. Fisk thinks
you need company or
a therapist.
She might be right.
Either way, she got us the best seats.
How so?
We have a perfect view of the court.
As in royal court.
Suitors, subjects, all swirling around.
The king,
of course... locking horns
with the Governor.
The queen
observing everything, cataloging it...
Assigning seats for inscrutable reasons.
Exactly.
- And we are their humble courtiers.
- Mmm.
- [chuckles]
- Each chosen for the...
talents we possess.
Like Daniel, for instance...
The jester.
At first glance. But
is there more than meets the eye?
An heir unapparent.
You like him, don't you?
He's grown on me.
And then we have Sheila
the chief of staff.
Or...
- Iago...
- [chuckles]
waiting with a sharpened blade.
[chuckles softly]
- And you?
- Me?
[Heather] Hmm.
I'm the knight.
High opinion of yourself.
- All right. A man-at-arms then.
- Mmm.
Is this amusement for you, or
self-soothing?
Categorizing the sharks
that might one day tear you apart.
Now that is
a very good question, Dr. Glenn.
- [glass clinking]
- Oh, no. I would like to make a toast.
To Wilson Fisk
and his incredibly hardworking
and ambitious staff.
To the incredible work
you've done for the city
and the port.
There's a saying in politics,
- "You are the company you keep."
- [softly] She tests you
because she fears you.
Mr. Fisk, you are
a formidable businessman.
Let's raise our glass to Wilson Fisk.
[man 1] We got three more on the manifest!
[man 2] Hurry it up!
[men speaking in Russian]
[man 3 in English] Get a clamp on it!
[Powell] Hey.
That it?
Yeah, yeah, that's all.
All right. Get back on the boat,
and we'll pick you up
once the load is delivered.
- Wait.
- What's the problem?
We've been on the boat all night.
We've done the job,
and we want to go back to our families.
Why can't you pay and let us go?
'Cause I fucking said so.
[speaking Russian]
[men chattering indistinctly]
Mayor Fisk is tough.
Hell, he's fighting
this weekend, isn't he?
And the vigilantes are next.
[BB] Thank you. Thank you so much.
No. No.
You try cutting me off tonight,
Dougie, my friend,
I'm gonna call the health department.
I'm going to tell those people that
you have pizza rat
smoking crack in your bathroom.
[laughing]
You're fun when you lose, you know that?
Yeah.
From the gentleman.
A gentleman?
Thank you.
Fuck!
- Hello? Holy shit.
- [Daredevil] Stay there.
I need your help.
Okay, look...
I'm a little bit drunk,
and I've had a really bad day,
and I cannot be dragged
into any of this...
- Resistance bullshit.
- You're already in it, Kirsten.
You met with Duquesne today.
- Are you following me?
- I need you to tell me everything you saw.
[exhales sharply]
[buzzer blares]
Well, they had me wear blackout goggles,
so I didn't see
anything.
I can work with that.
[man 1 on radio] Overwatch, go ahead
and let us know what north side looks like
when you get a chance, I'll be on five.
[man 2] Affirmative.
[Daredevil grunting]
[wind blowing]
- [Daredevil grunting]
- [metal creaking]
[grunts]
[pigeons cooing]
- [pigeons cooing]
- [wings fluttering]
[water splashing]
[water dripping]
[metal clanging]
[officer 1] All locked in.
We're good to go.
- [officer 2] Really? Awesome.
- Yes. Yeah.
[beeps]
- [Daredevil grunting]
- [officer 1] Fuck!
[all grunting]
[officer 2 yells]
- [glass shattering]
- [footsteps approaching]
[watch ticking]
[ticking slows down]
- [detainees clamoring, shouting]
- [sniffles softly]
- [detainee 1] Please, help us!
- [detainee 2] Help me!
- [detainee 3] Help me, please!
[clamoring continues]
[Daredevil grunting]
[detainee 4] Down here!
[Daredevil pants]
- [detainee 5] Help!
- Let's go, let's go.
[man speaks indistinctly on radio]
[guard] Copy. We're on our way.
Gather everyone. They're coming. Let's go.
They're coming! Let's go.
Let's go! Follow me.
This way. Let's go.
[clamoring continues]
[Soledad] Daredevil!
- [guard] Everyone back in your cell, now!
- Free as many as you can.
[detainees clamoring, screaming]
[Daredevil and guards grunting]
Go, go!
[grunting continues]
Come on.
[man on radio] Use lethal force. Go hot.
[grunting continues]
[Daredevil] Everyone down!
[yells]
[detainee 1] Fuck! Get down! Get down!
[grunting continues]
[Daredevil panting]
Move!
[officer 1] Secure the target.
Secure it. The rest of you,
with me! Go, go!
[officer 1] Copy.
Moving to the rendezvous.
- [officer 2] Come on, team. Come on!
- [Powell] Let's go!
Shit.
Shit!
Shit, shit, shit, shit.
[breathing heavily]
How about that?
[softly] Hey.
Hey.
Whoever the fuck you are,
come on out before I put holes in you.
Don't shoot.
I'm just a kid! [Breathing heavily]
You're Karen, right?
You're on wanted posters.
Who are you?
I'm Angela Del Toro.
My aunt's in there.
Daredevil's here, right?
- No. You gotta go home.
- No.
No. No! No! Come here! Take a look.
[objects clatter]
Just take a look.
I snagged some of their comms, too.
[man on radio]
The rest of you, with me. Go!
- Let's go!
- I came here to help.
Someone has to.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
[Karen on radio] Red team, red team,
come in, channel four.
Red team, red team, come in.
Red team, come in, channel four.
Fisk has people in here,
not just vigilantes.
I'm bringing them out now.
- Hello?
- Okay, let's go.
Follow me!
Shit!
- Hello? What?
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I've got an idea.
- Come on, move! Go. Let's go.
- Okay.
Go, go, go.
Go!
[siren wailing]
Take cover! Take cover!
- [Powell] Shoot the prisoners!
- [Cole] What?
[Powell] Shoot the prisoners!
- Down! Everybody, down!
- [Powell] Shoot!
- [all screaming]
- [Daredevil] Down!
[detainee] Down, get down!
Hold, hold.
- Friendlies.
- [officer] Stand down.
It's okay! It's okay! It's okay!
- Get in!
- Now, now, go!
Go, go, go! Stay down!
[detainees clamoring]
- [Daredevil] Stay down!
- Light 'em up! Light 'em up!
- [guns firing]
- [Daredevil] Get down!
Let's go! Let's go!
Mija!
I love you. Okay, go, now, go.
[Daredevil] Let's go! Hurry! Come on!
[grunts]
[officer] Everybody, out!
[Powell] Move in! Move in!
There's nowhere else for them to go.
[all grunting]
- [gun fires]
- [groans]
[panting]
Let's go! Move, move!
Can you drive this thing?
- I can try.
- Okay.
Go, go, go! Go, go, go!
Bloody hell.
- Go, go, go! Let's go.
- [Ariana] Everyone, sit down.
- Stay calm.
- We'll get you safe.
I know a place.
Okay.
- [engine starts]
- Okay, all right.
[tires screech]
Move!
Fuck it! Fuck it! Go!
[both panting]
Fuck!
[panting] I couldn't leave
those people there.
[panting] I know.
He got inside, and he had a lot of help.
[clears throat]
[Fisk] Cargo?
Safe in Red Hook.
The night crew?
Still on board the Northern Star.
Good.
We can use that.
You know what to do.
Yes, sir.
- [men shouting]
- [men speaking Russian]
[explosions]
[Karen panting]
[men shouting, screaming]
Oh, my God.
He killed them.
He killed them all.