=Love Beyond the Grave=
(Adapted from the novel by Li Qingran)
=Episode 18=
If I throw you off here,
what will happen?
Didn't you say
you liked my skull?
If I fall from here,
my head will be crushed.
So will my skull.
Then you should thank your skull
for saving your life.
Simu,
you've been wonderful.
You were,
and you still are.
Duan Shunxi.
This is my home!
You must not trespass!
It's the curfew time.
No trespassing.
Why is a spirit there?
No trespassing!
No trespassing.
This is my home.
No place for your mischief.
I swear to guard this place
without retreat.
No retreat.
Miss,
why are you here?
Don't you know the enemy's coming?
What's your name, sir?
Don't be scared, Miss.
I'm General Zhuisi.
This man is oddly dressed.
He might be a spy.
Let's be cautious.
Zhuisi?
I, all alone,
am equal to an army!
Your real name.
I'm General Zhuisi!
Zhuisi isn't in the Book of Spirits.
Who on earth are you?
Don't be ridiculous!
I am General Zhuisi.
Before my homeland is secured,
I just won't die.
Where my home is,
where I'll be.
I swear to guard this place
without retreat.
No retreat!
Take this.
Stop shouting.
- I don't need this!
- Simu.
He's different
from other spirits.
I'm a general.
How could I lower myself to their level?
He's delirious,
but he can control himself
without spirit stones.
That's really hard.
The day is breaking.
I'll guard the gate.
I remember who Zhuisi is now.
In an ancient book on warfare,
I read about him.
General Zhuisi of the Zhou State
joined the army at a young age
and rose to fame at Yuanlu.
In Luofeng Village,
he was finally besieged
and lost his army.
Oh, it's him.
You know him?
Why does this spirit
mistake himself for Zhuisi?
He must have experienced that war
and lived with these people.
So a sincere heart
can build a connection
even between mortals and spirits.
He stays here for a thousand years
instead of joining a temple.
Yet he can suppress his desires.
This man...
What a pity he doesn't jump
into the Ascension Pool.
What function does
the Pool actually have?
It dissolves obsessions.
Once he jumps, he'll be freed.
If spirits jump into the Ascension Pool,
will it solve the problem
of excessive spirits?
Yes.
But not entirely.
It won't work unless a spirit willingly
lets go of his obsession.
It's almost impossible
to make a spirit willingly jump
into the Ascension Pool.
Otherwise, this spirit
wouldn't have lingered like that.
But why does he guard
by the Ascension Pool?
Your Lordship,
the spirit lingering
by the Pool for a millennium
offended Her Grace.
He's way too powerful.
We are no match for him.
Losers!
Go there with me now.
Yes.
Anyone who violates the decrees
shall be severely punished.
This is my home!
Enemies
shall not invade!
Give me back my family letter!
Give it back to me!
My letter.
Your Grace.
Tell me your real name
and I'll save you.
What do you say?
I'm General Zhuisi.
I'd rather die before subjugation!
Thank you, Yan.
I'll take care of this.
You're being overly lenient.
This spirit interfered with our work
and offended you.
He deserves to be punished.
It doesn't matter.
You should go back.
Yes.
No trespassing.
He thought holding here...
Was defending his home.
No trespassing.
He didn't know his nation was in ruins.
He lost his home long ago.
No trespassing.
Trapped in the past,
he's just tortured by his obsession.
This is totally meaningless.
Trapped here,
he must be very lonely.
No trespassing.
♪Cross your legs for three years♪
♪Subdue dragon and tiger♪
Si,
the hoe I borrowed
is back in your room.
(My fellow villagers)
Thank you, Si.
Si,
eat before you go home.
I get it.
You're back, Si.
That's right.
It's been a while.
Hey, uncle.
Where are you going?
Hi, Si. I'm going out.
Hi.
Busy, huh?
Si,
come over here.
Uncle, why are you sitting here?
I just dried some rice.
Take some back.
I... I can't take it.
Just take it.
- Si.
- Thank you, uncle.
- Come on.
Hi, aunt.
I've made you a garment.
Take it.
- Take it.
- Thank you, aunt.
(My fellow villagers)
(in Luofeng Village,)
(I happened to wander
into the Mortal World.)
(Si.)
(You all treated me like your own son)
(and I took you as my family.)
It's delicious. Taste it, aunt.
I'll just
watch you eat.
- Si.
- You're back.
Si.
What's up?
Help me tie my bracelet.
Show me your hand.
I promise you.
If you behave well,
I'll bring you food tomorrow.
Deal?
♪A lamp in the east lights the west♪
♪No lamp in the west,
but it's still bright♪
♪The lamplight gathers like a hood♪
♪What a pity a lamp can't light itself♪
No.
No!
My family letter.
My letter.
Do you remember who you are now?
Si.
(Si)
Granny.
Granny, what happened?
Granny!
Si,
you were a spirit wandering
in the Mortal World.
You once lived in Luofeng Village.
Later, the war broke out nearby.
Luofeng Village was in danger.
Zhuisi retreated to this place
and lost his army.
Then you put on his armor
and guarded Luofeng Village.
Later, you returned to the Void
and guarded here.
How did I get my memories back?
Since you remembered,
why did you see yourself as him?
General Zhuisi once said,
"My homeland won't be safe
until the war is over.
My clan is destroyed.
There's no way of reunion."
I refused to believe this grievous news.
So, I pretended to be General Zhuisi
and appointed myself as the gatekeeper,
looking for a way home.
For as long as I can remember,
I've stayed by the Ascension Pool
and guarded it day and night
without leaving.
I want to go home.
You aren't General Zhuisi.
But you tried your best
to protect your homeland.
This battle is over.
It's time to let it go.
But I have no home now.
What is a home?
A house without the warmth of life
or a memory that only you remember?
Your relatives and friends
you've missed...
They have left you.
No one remembers you now.
No.
I don't want to forget them.
I don't want that.
I just don't!
Si, come on.
Aunt.
I've made you a garment.
I'll make you nice food. Wait for me.
If you behave well,
when I come back tomorrow,
I'll bring you food.
Thank you, Si.
Go ahead and play.
If it's delicious, eat some more.
Si,
come over here.
I just
dried some rice.
Take some back.
Si.
Uncle.
He is finally at peace, huh?
He won't remember
the misery of war and separation.
I heard that a spirit
let it go and ascended.
Her Grace sent him personally.
Previously, Her Grace ordered us
to persuade spirits to ascend
and resolve excessive spirits.
Now,
Her Grace has issued
the Ascension Decree.
She wants us
to let go of our obsessions.
If I had known
about the punishment
for not fulfilling that,
I should have worked harder
to make more spirit stones.
If you complain instead of working,
Her Grace might send you to ascend.
With strong obsessions,
I can't ascend.
Hurry up.
We'll finally see off spirits
who have moved on.
We spirits are born from obsessions.
So, there are 24 temples in the Void.
There's a lord
for each temple.
Every spirit coming in here
must choose a temple accordingly.
Different obsessions
take them where they belong.
What types of obsessions?
For example, in Jiling Temple
are mischievous children.
Shaoling Temple values looks.
Zhuangling Temple desires power.
Yan Ke's Qiling Temple
commands the forces.
Jiang Ai's Xuling Temple
governs the biggest pleasure den here.
That's a paradise that combines
wealth, power, wine, and lust.
Especially the casino
she's personally in charge of.
(Xuling Temple, the Void)
(Ledger)
Somebody.
Here.
Our guest is here.
Yes.
Here we are.
This is it?
Let's go.
I bet on big.
Hey, man.
Give me money.
What for?
Otherwise,
we can't even make our way
into this place.
This is all the money I have.
I'm borrowing it.
I'll return every bit of it.
Open it!
I won!
Come on. Let me try.
Come on. One more time.
It's all mine.
I won!
They're all mine.
My spirit stones.
- My stones.
- Mine!
- What's wrong?
- My stones.
Stop.
It's all right.
My spirit stones.
Mine.
They're all mine.
Young man,
you should have told me
before you came.
I could have had someone pick you up.
Don't bother.
I've heard
there are many amusements
in your place.
So I came to take a look.
Extraordinary, indeed.
Young man,
you need to pay spirit stones
for pleasures here.
A great many spirit stones.
I heard you're a good gambler.
Would you be interested
in gambling with me?
If you win,
I'll leave now.
But if I win,
let me look around here.
Young man,
haven't you heard about my stories?
In gambling,
I've never lost.
He's challenging Her Ladyship.
How bold of him.
I bet on Her Ladyship.
So do I.
Shoot a jade arrow from 100 steps away
through the leaves of the Money Tree.
One leaf at a time.
Who hits more will win.
The victory depends
on 30 percent luck and 70 percent skill.
Then where should I
use the remaining luck?
Clever man, indeed.
Who rolls higher
will get a chance
to shoot once.
Young man,
let's leave it to luck.
Didn't Simu tell you?
Having senses here
isn't a good thing.
(Boundless Gold)
She hit it.
She's going to win.
I told you.
She'll win.
He's bluffing.
- Yeah.
- Look there.
He rolled a five, so what?
He'll lose anyway.
Twenty-one points.
The best you can do is a tie.
Her Ladyship is the best.
Without the sense of touch,
you can't come up with that.
Twenty-four points.
I win.
I can't believe she lost.
He'll miss.
Look at his posture.
He can't win.
He just can't.
Can he even draw?
(Boundless Gold)
Amazing.
How could he hit like that?
It was just his luck.
You're pretty good.
Then let's play for real
and see what will happen.
Look at Her Ladyship.
I'd like to see
how long you can stay in.
They...
Can't tell who's winning.
It has never happened before.
It seems
we can't have a winner
with the dice.
Even if we compete in shooting,
we'll just have a tie.
Why don't we
make it a bit harder?
Who can hit
one of the falling golden leaves
will be the winner.
Through the ages,
you're the first to have a chance
for a tie with me.
Look.
- Nice.
- Great.
Her Ladyship is awesome.
She has great archery.
Bravo!
Nice!
Impressive!
Three leaves?
How could he do that?
He's quite a figure.
He won.
My partner won.
Young man, you won.
I'm convinced I lost.
You're too kind.
Never did I expect
this maverick strategy.
I'll keep my promise.
You can enjoy your stroll
all over my place.
What's more,
wherever you want to go,
you can come to me.
I'll take you there.
Thank you.
How come
Her Ladyship lost?
Oh no.
So I would lose everything.
That's thirty years of savings.
When I won,
why would you lose everything?
All the spirits here
bet on Her Ladyship.
Who would know
you could actually win?
Before Her Ladyship competed with you,
she set another game.
Only she bet on you
while we all lost.
Fine. I'll gamble more
and get my money back.
- Let's go.
- What a gambler.
So I was part of her gambling strategy.
Even the best fall sometimes.
Simu,
the mortal you brought back
is truly exceptional.
If you hadn't shown mercy,
how could a mere mortal like him
have won?
I was impressed
by his final move.
I don't want to ruin this fresh feeling.
It's been a few centuries
since I had a worthy opponent last time.
What a mad gambler.
Simu,
he's so interesting.
Let him stay for a few more days.
I should go.
You can bet on big.
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Between black and white,
ripples crossed♪
♪Light encountered shadow♪
♪It pierced the darkness and the time♪
♪The unbreakable fate♪
♪Suddenly cracked♪
♪Listen, all sounds are roaring♪
♪As cold ice turns into tides♪
♪A century's loneliness melts dreams♪
♪Following fate's guidance♪
♪By fate, our moments were exchanged♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪
♪Watch fireworks fall like stars♪
♪This bond is tangled into a thread♪
♪Worldly reflections fade into mist♪
♪Borrowing one fleeting heartbeat♪
♪You drew me into mortal dust,
till I'm enamored with its charms♪
♪The heart wakes up all of a sudden♪