ADAPTED FROM THE NOVEL HIDDEN LOVE BY ZHU YI
Here, let me help you.
Okay.
Sang…
I guess
I'll take this one with me.
Okay.
Perfect. One for each of us.
Why don't we get something to eat?
It's late.
Why don't we go back to campus?
Okay, let's go.
Okay.
I had fun today.
Sang Zhi.
Do you want to get dinner at the canteen?
I'll just order takeout.
You're back.
-Hi. -Come on.
We were just talking about spending New Year's Eve
at the Central Plaza.
Influencers recommend it. We can get a lot of nice photos.
Central Plaza?
-Yes. -It will be crowded.
Right? That's what I told her.
She wouldn't listen.
Then…
Why don't you join us, Jiang Ming?
It's New Year's Eve.
The more, the merrier.
Right?
Sure.
I have to go back to my dorm.
You guys carry on.
Bye.
Did he win this for you
from the claw machine?
I got this myself.
Well, what do you think about Jiang Ming?
I think he's a good guy.
He's handsome and nice.
That brother of yours can't be much better.
Sangsang, I'll ask you one last time.
Won't you spend New Year's Eve with us?
I am sure.
It's cold outside.
But if you--
No more buts.
Sangsang already said no.
Besides, the place will be crowded.
We might see more heads than fireworks.
That's right. Weiwei.
You go ahead and enjoy yourself.
-Let's go. -All right.
Wangwang.
Are you trying to compete with me?
This won't do. I have to change my outfit.
No, Ning Wei. No need to change.
You are the prettiest.
You are the second prettiest.
Okay. Great. Let's go.
I think it's too short. I'll go change.
It's not short. It's fine.
It's perfect for this occasion. Let's go.
-Let me get my coat. -Okay.
Hurry.
-Sangsang. -Let's go.
Remember to eat.
I know. I'll order takeout.
We'll bring back tasty treats too.
Don't miss us too much.
Sangsang.
-Happy New Year! -Happy New Year!
-We're off. -Bye.
-Bye. -Bye. Remember to eat.
Be careful.
-Okay. -There are a lot of people.
Okay. Bye.
There you are.
I want to give Weiwei a surprise,
but I don't want her to yell at me again.
Why? Just tell her.
Last time, I ordered hot pot
and she yelled at me for three days.
It's fine. There's always a next time.
-Hello. -Hi.
Where's Weiwei?
Hey!
-Hi. -Hi.
You're not wearing glasses today.
What do you think?
Isn't she pretty without her glasses?
Yes.
Be more confident. Stand straight.
Stop teasing me.
Enough. It will be really crowded today.
We won't get a spot if we don't go now.
-Let's go. -Where's Sang Zhi?
Didn't she come with you guys?
No.
-She's not going. -No.
Is she not coming?
Sangsang has never liked crowds.
She'll stay in and watch anime. Right?
-Yes. -Yes.
So let's go.
-We're going to be late! -That's right.
-Let's go. -Let's go.
-Come on, Chen Qiang. -Let's go.
Come on. Jiang Ming, let's go!
Okay, I'm the fifth wheel.
Jiaxu.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
There's a company dinner tonight.
I can bring my family.
I'll bring you.
I'm not your family.
I'll pass.
I'm about to eat the takeout I ordered.
Takeouts on New Year's Eve?
If you don't like crowds,
the two of us can have dinner.
I don't feel like going out.
You still owe me a meal.
Are you trying to back out?
I'll make a reservation right now.
You get ready to come out.
-I-- -I'm almost at your university.
I'll get changed.
Good. I'll call you when I get there.
CHAPTER 11, MOVED
IF THIS IS LOVE
Try this.
Why didn't you go out with your roommates?
Do you guys not get along?
No.
We get along just fine.
But they're going to the Central Plaza
for the New Year's Eve countdown.
It's too crowded for me.
And Yihe is too cold.
I didn't want to go out.
But you said yes the minute I asked.
That's because…
That's because I owe you a meal.
If I didn't come,
you would think I'm trying
to get out of treating you.
I was just kidding about that.
By the way,
I didn't mean
to tease you at the hospital.
So
I want to formally apologize to you today.
You don't have to do that.
It's not a big deal.
Besides, that was a long time ago.
All right.
Eat more.
It's my treat.
Consider it my apology.
Didn't we agree that it is my treat?
I owe you a meal anyway.
What do you mean?
Are you saying that we don't have to meet again
after this meal?
Have some sympathy for this lonely old man.
You won't even have a meal with your brother.
Jiaxu.
Start digging in.
You're really talkative today.
It's not every day that I get to have a meal with you.
So what if I want to talk more?
Let's talk about you.
How are your classes?
Are you interested in them?
The professor says
that freshmen don't have many major courses.
But we will have many as sophomores.
Lame.
Let's sit here.
Okay, let's sit here.
That's what my professor said.
Why won't you answer my calls?
I've told you.
We don't need to stay in touch anymore.
Jiang Ying!
Who are you?
What's wrong with you?
And what's wrong with you?
It's none of your business!
Do you know why I did that?
I don't care why.
Listen, if you had assaulted him,
I would've returned the favor.
Jiang Ying!
What do you want, Jiang Ying?
Who is she, Duan Jiaxu?
Jiang Ying, don't! Let's go.
Sorry, miss. Please leave.
Do you think you're in the clear?
Listen, you owe me for the rest of your life!
-Please leave. -Let's go.
-You think you don't owe me anymore? -Leave!
-Duan Jiaxu! -Get out!
I will never let you off!
Let me go!
Jia…
Are you okay?
Let's leave, Jiaxu.
It's cold. Put your coat on.
So, Jiaxu.
Who is that woman?
Someone unimportant.
To be precise,
I guess she's my dad's former creditor.
Wait!
I'm going inside.
I ran into her once.
Did you?
When you were hospitalized,
I went to get your things at your place.
We walked past each other.
Did she do anything to you?
So I guess
she was there
to see you.
Does this happen every time she sees you?
No.
Jiaxu.
As you said,
she's your dad's former creditor.
So it has nothing to do with you.
You shouldn't let her bully you.
I don't…
There's no way she can bully me.
What's the matter?
I'm fine.
I don't need…
Does it hurt?
No.
I forgot to say this earlier.
Thank you, Sang Zhi.
I wish that all bad things
will stay away from Jiaxu.
I wish that someone could be with him.
I wish
that person is me.
Aren't you going to make a wish?
It's this year's first snowfall.
Yihe doesn't get snow often.
The last time it snowed
was when I was in tenth grade.
I guess
I'm quite lucky.
I'm lucky too.
I get to see the snowfall with you.
A wish at the first snowfall
is said to come true.
I wish
Sang Zhi will always be happy and healthy,
and so will I.
What was your wish?
It won't come true if I say it out loud.
What did you wish for?
I wish…
No, I can't let you guys hear it.
What did you guys wish for?
Of course,
for us to be together forever.
Goodness, I wish
that I never have to listen
to Ning Wei's mushy lines anymore.
If you're so jealous,
you should get a boyfriend too.
That's right.
Wangwang.
What did you wish for?
Me?
I…
There isn't anything I really want.
There isn't?
This is the first snow in Yihe in years.
But you don't have any wishes!
You watch romance dramas, right?
They always say
that wishes at the first snowfall
will come true.
Really?
Of course.
That's nonsense.
The first snow calls for beer and barbecue.
Don't stand around. Come on.
Good grief!
She doesn't have a single romantic bone.
You're single by your own virtue, Yu Xin.
-Let's do it. Who will do it? -Look, my boyfriend barbecues for me.
Please!
Let this year be over already.
Jiang Ming.
What did you wish for?
Me?
It's all right.
You don't have to tell me
if you don't want to.
It's no big deal.
I wished that the person I like
would make a wish today
and that her wish would come true.
The person you like is really lucky.
The meat is done!
Do you guys want some or not?
-Coming! -Hurry!
Let's head over.
Jiaxu, I'm sorry.
I was too impulsive today.
Tell your friend that I apologize.
I'm sorry.
What's the point of this?
Sorry, I won't do it again.
Please move.
I said I'm sorry, Duan Jiaxu!
I already told you
not to contact me anymore.
So you're cutting me off after paying off the debt?
What gives?
Don't you know that you owe me,
Duan Jiaxu?
What do I owe you? Tell me.
Your dad killed my dad!
You owe me!
You know what you owe me!
You just owe me.
I've repaid what I should.
My dad paid the price too.
I don't owe you anything else.
Duan Jiaxu!
Don't forget what your mom promised us!
She said you would always take care of me!
Leave! You're not welcome here!
Sorry, Mrs. Jiang!
Get out. Leave.
Leave now!
-I'm sorry, Mrs. Jiang! -Get out!
-Mrs. Jiang. -Why are you here?
I'm sorry.
He's dead! What's the use of these things?
You destroyed my sister's family!
Sorry.
It's our fault.
What is the use of saying sorry?
Will that bring Xiaoying's dad back?
What will Xiaoying and her mom do now?
I want my dad.
I just want my dad.
Xiaoying.
I'm sorry, Xiaoying!
Mom!
Mom, what are you doing?
We've done you wrong.
Rest assured.
-Mom. -We will take responsibility.
We will pay the compensation decided by the court.
Even if we have to sell our house,
take out a loan,
or borrow money,
no matter what,
we will pay you on time.
My son and I
will look after you and your daughter
for life as well.
SORRY
Jiang Ying.
You've been away from school for a while.
You can ask me if you need help.
Did you know that Jiang Ying's dad died?
I've heard.
Apparently, Duan Jiaxu's dad ran him over.
-Seriously? -Yes.
What are you guys talking about?
Duan Jiaxu's dad ran over
and killed Jiang Ying's dad.
He was still alive at the time.
He died after Jiaxu's dad fled the scene.
Doesn't that make him a murderer's son?
That's right.
How can he still come to school?
If I were him,
I wouldn't dare to show my face.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I can't do it.
Jiaxu.
As you said,
she's your dad's former creditor.
So it has nothing to do with you.
You shouldn't let her bully you.
Sang Zhi,
thank you.
SANG ZHI
Happy New Year, Jiaxu.
May you be happy every day.
BROTHER NO. 2
Happy New Year.
I'm watching the fireworks.
What about you?
BROTHER NO. 2
Me too.
They're beautiful.
EDIT CONTACT DETAILS
SANG ZHI
ZHIZHI
So, Jiaxu.
Who is that woman?
What do I owe you? Tell me.
Your dad killed my dad!
You owe me!
You know what you owe me!
Your voice sounds young,
but you can't fool anyone.
You're not young anymore.
He is not my partner.
He is too old.
He is old enough to be my dad.
SAVE CHANGES?
SAVE
DON'T SIT FOR TOO LONG
GET UP AND MOVE, BYE
DON'T SIT FOR TOO LONG, GET UP AND MOVE, BYE
Let me tell you guys something.
I am getting married!
I'm getting hitched!
QIAN FEI
I bet you're pissed!
What's up?
Are you all asleep?
Why are you ignoring me when I'm so excited?
Not yet.
DUAN JIAXU
Well?
You're still up?
What? Did you miss me?
I'm hanging up.
Don't!
If you're still up, chat with me.
Guess what? I proposed today.
Do you know how I proposed?
When I saw her home today,
I told her I was thirsty
and to get me a bottle of water from the trunk,
so she did.
The minute she opened it,
she saw it filled with roses.
I went up to her and said,
"Will you be my wife?"
Guess what she said?
She said, "Won't that make me Mrs. Qian?"
Isn't she cute?
Nice.
But I'm sad to hear
that you're getting married.
You always said you were going to stay single with me.
I only said that to make you feel better.
Did you take it seriously?
All right.
Congratulations, buddy.
Enough about me. What about you?
Didn't you say you were going on a blind date?
Did you?
What blind date? No way.
Has anyone caught your eye?
You must have feelings for someone.
Jiaxu.
I think I've caught a trace of something
from your few seconds of silence.
What's going on?
Who is it?
What do you…
Tell me.
Have you calmed down yet?
Hurry up and go to sleep.
You're about to be a married man.
-No, tell me who it is. -I'm hanging up.
What am I thinking?
NO MILK OR EGGS
Kiddo.
CLEAR AMBITIONS, LEARNING, SELF-CULTIVATION, AND DILIGENCE
Weiwei, what did you buy?
That's a huge box.
Two pairs of shoes.
They were on sale.
I couldn't help it.
-Jiaxu. -What did you buy?
-I have something for you. -Stationery.
Stationery?
-I'll come to your office. -How boring!
Why buy stationery?
-Weiwei. -What did you buy, Sangsang?
I bought…
Chen Qiang.
-Do you need help? I'll get that. -I've got it.
You have a class later. I'll manage.
It's fine.
Let's go eat after my class.
Sure.
Sang Zhi.
You weren't there on New Year's Eve.
Are you free this weekend?
Let's decompress.
But exams are around the corner.
Maybe after we finish our exams.
Exams?
That's right.
I have a friend who just opened up a bar.
Why don't we all go there to celebrate after our exams?
Let's talk about that after our exams.
What should we eat for dinner?
That's right!
I heard a new place opened up.
Let's try it.
I heard it's good.
Tonight?
You guys try it first.
I'll pass tonight.
Where are you going?
I'm going to deliver a peephole camera
to my relative.
All right.
I'll be leaving now.
-Bye. -Bye.
Be careful. Come back early.
Stay safe.
For NPC feedback,
if we program it this way,
every time the player runs into them,
it will trigger many event detections.
If so, phones with lower specs
won't be able to process it
and will lag.
Can I write it with C instead?
Stop it with the C.
JAVA is the best.
It's fine. It's not a huge issue.
We've had a long day.
Let's end this meeting here.
-Good work, Jiaxu. -Good work.
Let's go.
It's tough.
Clean up after yourself.
ARE YOU BUSY? I CAN LEAVE IT AT YOUR BUILDING'S RECEPTION DESK.
Where are you?
What should we do?
Go downstairs and stop her.
-Okay. -Xiaoduan.
Come here.
What's the matter?
Jiang Ying is making a scene again downstairs.
I asked security to stop her.
It should be fine.
You cannot enter.
Hold on. Wait at the entrance.
-Listen! I'm looking for Duan Jiaxu! -Wait.
-He works here. -I know what you're saying, miss.
But you cannot enter yet.
-I'm his friend. -I'll help you.
We'll let him know now.
-If he gives permission-- -I just need to talk to him.
Please wait here. Calm down.
My colleague has--
-Wait. You can't go inside. -It's important!
You can't enter. I know what you mean.
-Please! -Miss, you can't just enter.
-Wait. You can't enter. -I just need to say something.
We're working. You cannot just go inside.
-Please. -Jiaxu.
You cannot go inside.
I'm his friend.
My superior said we can't let you in.
-Come. -He must be upstairs.
Mr. Duan isn't inside.
Don't push me!
Why didn't you pick up?
Sorry, my phone ran out of battery.
I forgot to charge it last night.
Why didn't you tell me you were here?
I did.
I sent you a message. Didn't you see it?
I was busy. I missed it.
It's okay.
Sang Zhi.
Don't come straight to my office or my place anymore.
If you do, let me know beforehand, okay?
Have you eaten?
I wanted to give you this.
A peephole camera.
That woman keeps harassing you.
You can install this on your door.
It can connect to your phone.
It's a smart camera.
You can use it to call the police too.
It will come in handy.
That's all.
Thank you.
Go back to work.
I'm going back to class.
That woman keeps harassing you.
SMART DOORBELL
You can install this on your door.
It will come in handy.