(Uilhan Brewery)
(1. Malting, 2. Malt milling, 3. Mash tun, 4. Hopping)
(Kim Se Jeong)
(Highly passionate, highly sensitive)
(Lee Jong Won)
(Shin Do Hyun)
(Baek Sung Chul)
(Uilhan Brewery)
(Naro Beer)
(Brewing Love)
(This is a work of fiction.)
(Scenes with child actors and animals were filmed...)
(under production guidelines along with experts.)
Can you at least tell me...
why you're treating me like this?
- Why are you suddenly... - She told us the reason.
What on earth did you tell them...
I told them the reason you came here.
What?
Shouldn't you hear my side too?
Forget it!
We know what you're scheming.
We have nothing to hear.
There's nothing to hear.
- Yes. - That's right.
- What's the point? - Right?
- Why... - Stop it. That's enough.
Just a moment.
The cause of all this is Jisang Liquor, then.
Right? Here's the conclusion.
Don't confuse the villagers anymore.
You both can leave.
Right now.
- Mr. Yoon. - Mr. Yoon.
What's up with him?
Boss. Why kick out Chae Yong Ju too?
(Brewing Love)
(Episode 4)
He shouldn't have been nice.
He shouldn't have been kind.
Oh, shoot. Salt got in my eye.
You're a mess, Chae Yong Ju.
I told you not to whip yourself.
It's too early.
Just a moment.
Leave it.
Hurt me or heal me. Stick to just one.
Before we do that,
come over to my place.
Mr. Yoon, I'm done...
I got myself in order.
He must really love photos.
Does he bump into corners that much?
Eat at your convenience.
Are you the owner of this house?
Hello.
Hey.
What's the matter with your owner?
He shouldn't be so nice right now.
He's too nice for no reason.
Where did he go?
Can I come in?
You already came in.
Are you all right?
Yes, thanks to you.
I'm sorry I can't pick...
between hurting and healing.
To me, the villagers are most important.
I was like a lonesome island,
and this is the first place I settled at.
Thanks to them.
(4 years ago)
(Baegok-ri Village Hall)
Do you think we'll eat you?
Did you zip up your mouth? Why won't you speak?
Are you keeping your distance because you're from Seoul?
We go there once or twice a year.
- Yes. - It's nothing.
Will you come in?
I'd like to host a village festival...
like our neighboring village did.
We barely do any farming because we lack young folk.
Peaches, apples, cucumbers, deodeok.
The neighbors did their festival around almost everything we grow.
What festival could we possibly do?
Right.
I called you all here so we could put our skulls together and think.
Speak up.
Oh, gosh...
What a disaster.
Hey, how about...
How about beer?
I planted some hops.
Other countries host hop festivals.
You could actually speak?
We get to hear your voice at last.
I like your voice,
but what did you say you planted?
Hops are used to give beer its scent.
You could say it's like a beer tree.
- A tree of beers? - A beer tree?
Do people know about beer trees?
- Right. - Yes.
- If it's for a festival... - Well...
Too bad if they don't.
That's it?
What's that?
Shouldn't we at least ask three times?
You're not at all like us.
Hey, Yoon...
Young Man Yoon.
CEO Yoon.
What should we call him?
- Is the work doable? - It's easy.
(A fly)
Block.
Leave it alone. It's our first customer today.
Come this way.
(A fly)
If you sit down here, I'll bring you a drop of beer.
(In My Name)
Sir. Are you open?
We are which is why you came in.
Sit over here.
Cheers.
- It's really nice. - Honestly. It's awesome.
CEO Yoon. Keep them coming.
So we can make money. I'm good at this now.
"In My Name." My name is Sook Ja.
What's your name?
I'm Young Ja, the richest person in the world.
What does that mean?
- Enjoy. - Thank you.
Take your pick.
- Three of this, please. - Okay.
If you haven't eaten yet,
we have cheeseburgers and...
- People are actually coming. - Yes.
- It's nice. - Thank you.
- Here you go. - Thanks.
It's good fun to make money.
- It is. - Smell it.
This is the smell of hops.
- Mr. Yoon. - CEO Yoon!
You're looking good.
- Is the work doable? - Yes.
CEO Yoon.
Oh, my gosh.
It's really getting my back.
This is paradise.
CEO Yoon.
I thought I made beer on my own.
Before I knew it, the villagers...
had my back.
For their sake at least, I can't quit and pack up.
You can't.
Those who trust and rely on you.
You must protect them.
Do we have to do all this?
- Is this... - Beom.
You can't stick it here. It must go here.
My gosh.
You're doing well.
Sitting here...
strangely reminds me a lot of my old branch.
A large company might think...
this place is insignificant.
But we all put everything into it.
And I have a duty to protect them.
The village festival's coming up. I have to go.
I can't stop him after that speech.
Should I just give up?
I can't.
Not yet.
"Unlimited beer?" "Festival?"
Why didn't they call me?
No festival is complete without toast.
Oh, dear.
What a shame.
Isn't it fun?
- Cheers. - Cheers.
Cheers.
There you go.
- Thanks. We'll have fun. - Thank you.
I can't leave like this.
I want to explain myself to the villagers.
They got me very wrong.
I can't leave like this either.
Can I have a word?
What did you tell the villagers?
I didn't say much.
I only shared facts about the profit...
the merger would bring.
"Facts?"
Did you tell them the hidden fact about the merger?
That as soon as the merger's final,
Naro Beer will become Jisang's Naro.
The pub, hop field, even the festival.
Everything they worked for four years...
to build up will become Jisang Liquor's.
To lose ownership means...
they can no longer call the fruits of their labor their own.
You're threatening to take even the time...
the villagers put their all into.
The real hidden meaning of a merger...
is to squash the efforts of a whole village with capital.
Did you tell them that too?
You can tell everyone that hidden meaning,
but in the end capital always wins.
They can't help...
but notice the post-merger profit.
You call it a merger,
but what happens afterwards?
When did a large corporation ever keep the original staff?
Yes, they keep everyone on at first.
But they barely last 2 or 3 years.
The villagers will be sent to work...
at other Jisang factories.
Where would they go? They lived here all their lives.
They'll all resign.
Back in 2022 Jisang bought out...
a Jeolla Province soju plant.
All the existing staff left within a year.
Am I wrong?
Ms. Chae. Why are you so emotional?
Go and tell them yourself.
Tell them I'm deceiving and using them.
Tell them Jisang's being a tyrant.
You can tell them what I'm doing like I told them about you.
No. I won't do that.
Why not?
Because belittling an opponent...
is just too easy a way out.
It's way too easy.
Ms. Bang.
Have you ever lost something...
you tried to protect with your name?
Goodbye.
It really sucks.
I don't want the villagers to feel that.
Yes! I should just die!
I deserve to die. Why do I bother living?
I'm totally useless.
I'm the scum of the earth.
I ordered beer for the beer festival...
and told them to deliver it next week.
Why do I bother to eat breakfast every morning?
What should I do now?
You should be ashamed.
Did you swap your brain for a block of taffy?
You're our village chief?
What beer festival has no beer?
I'm sorry, okay? Will you let go of me?
I need to be able to move if I'm going to drown myself somewhere.
Let him go.
You moron. What should I do with you?
We promised unlimited beer,
and we don't have enough beer.
Aren't there lots of people...
who want other beers and not ours?
- There are lots. - Right?
Where can we go to order beer...
and have it delivered?
We live so far in the countryside...
that we only get one shipment a week!
Let's do the best we can with what we have left.
Chief, make some calls and see if anyone can supply us.
I'll get all the beer in the brewery.
So...
where is the person who can help me?
I have to man this place.
I'll help.
It's urgent.
Me too. I'm here.
- Toast. - Toast.
Where did you come from?
Hello.
If you don't mind me asking, I'd like your help.
Oh, gosh.
Thanks.
Where did Yong Ju go when we need her brute force?
She's not even picking up.
Did she go to Seoul?
Beom, did you see the file I sent?
Get the director's signature and come right over.
Yes, it's urgent. Hurry.
(Product Order, Miscellaneous, Please approve ASAP.)
Got it. Okay, approved.
Got it.
Yes. Nice.
Yong Ju. How long has it been?
You're so hard to reach.
We'll talk later. Let's go inside.
This is all alcohol?
This is my paradise.
There he is.
What could be so urgent?
We're here to collect some products for an event.
What?
This should be enough.
Thank you.
- See you. - Go on. Bye.
There's no time. Let's hurry.
(Fate)
Yong Ju.
If we offer this to bargain with Yoon Min Ju,
he might sign with us, right?
We have an advantage, right?
- No. - No?
It's not a "might."
He'll definitely sign with us.
The villagers will want it.
Mr. Yoon...
He won't be able to refuse.
Yes. We won.
Let's get there quickly.
- Oh, no. - Are you okay?
- What is it? - Where does it hurt?
Oh, gosh.
What should we do?
Hang on. Where are we?
Stop, Beom. Hit the brakes.
- Are you all right? - Yes.
Let's get out.
Are you all okay?
- Are you okay? - Did you call...
for help or your insurance provider?
Oh, right. The beer.
No?
Excuse me.
How's the beer? Oh, no.
No. After all I did to get it.
Darn it. There goes our chance with Yoon Min Ju.
We should transfer the injured to the hospital first.
Sorting this situation out will take some time.
Think. Calm down.
Calm down.
If you're in any trouble, call me.
I'll be right there.
It's me. What is it?
Chairman. Do you mind helping...
Send me the address. I'll be right there.
- Are you all right? - Yes.
Yes, I'm fine.
Is there anything else we can help with?
We're fine as well.
- Thank you. - No problem.
What is that?
Guys. Get out and sort things out at once.
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
- Thank you very much, Chairman. - Wholesale is loyalty.
It's my time to pay you back for all the help I received from you.
Chairman...
Call me anytime.
I still have enough power to help you. Got it?
- You saved Jisang Liquor, Chairman. - Goodness, punk.
It's all thanks to Yong Ju for all her support until now. You know?
Chairman...
Thanks.
Stop clinging onto me, big guy.
You two should go. Leave this place to me.
- Okay. Get in. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Don't mention it.
- I'll call you later. - Okay.
- Drive safely. - Yes, sir.
- Thank you, Chairman. - No problem.
- I'll get in touch. - Off you go. All right. Be careful.
Get driving, guys.
Good.
Have a safe trip.
If it's beers from the Chairman,
making a deal with Yoon Min Ju won't be that hard.
- Beom. - Yes, Yong Ju?
- Let's not make a deal. - What?
How come? It's a golden opportunity.
Making a deal using a weak point is the same as acting high-handed.
And we know very well how that feels.
If CEO Yoon signs the contract,
I want him to do it voluntarily.
Out of his own will and not for someone else's sake.
But this is our last chance.
If that's what you say is right, I'll trust you.
Thanks.
The villagers will love it, won't they?
Including CEO Yoon.
Stop. Drop me off right here.
I need to make a short detour.
(Uilhan Brewery)
This is the last batch.
Thanks to you, I can make it to the festival on time.
I'm really grateful.
If you proceed with an M and A with our company,
you won't need to go through all this trouble.
You know, right? The villagers are hoping for the M and A.
I do.
What Ms. Chae...
is trying to do is take you away from Uilhan Brewery.
If you leave Uilhan Brewery,
the villagers will suffer the damage.
Hold on. I know Yong Ju well.
She won't cause damage to the village.
It's just her current situation.
To save the Busan branch,
Yong Ju took the lead in getting CEO Yoon to...
Stop right there. Doesn't that mean...
Ms. Chae is adamant about the contract...
simply for the Busan branch?
That's a bigger problem.
If her goal is to return to the branch,
she'll turn a blind eye once the contract is signed.
CEO Yoon will get thrown away after being used.
That wasn't what I meant. Why are you taking it that far?
CEO Yoon. You just heard directly from Ms. Chae's friend.
Please think about whether Ms. Chae is a trustworthy person.
I should.
Thank you for the advice.
Shall we get going?
Yong Ju...
We'll head over first.
Do you believe I'm the type to do such a thing as Ms. Bang said?
(Uilhan Brewery)
Do you have nothing more to say?
I see.
CEO Yoon.
Do you mind listening to my story one last time?
It is indeed true that the Busan branch's life...
depends on our contract.
It is my main purpose.
However, because of that main purpose,
I have no intention of using you or the villagers.
I know very well that...
this place is your everything,
just as the Busan branch is my everything.
That must be why staying here...
has made me curious about what kind of beer we'd make.
In other words, I want to work with you until the very end.
These are my true feelings.
Even if many get the wrong idea and don't believe me...
(Uilhan Brewery)
You do know, don't you?
Whether I'm being sincere or not.
So, I hope you see me...
as who I am.
What are we supposed to do with just these?
Good grief.
- Over here. - Hey.
Is that everything from the brewery?
- Yes. - Oh, no.
We can't even last until the evening with those.
The evening is the peak time.
Are there no wholesale stores you can get in touch with?
Good grief, it's like the wholesale stores...
went on a picnic as a group.
No one is picking up their phone.
- Goodness. - Just forget it.
Like I would. I'll keep calling. And lower your voice.
But there's no beer...
- in a beer festival. - That's what I mean.
- I'll continue to ring them. - It's ridiculous.
- Keep me posted, okay? - Good grief.
- Where's the beer? - How frustrating.
I'd appreciate it if you could move faster. Thank you.
Beom. Guide the drivers to the warehouse.
- Okay. - Chief!
It's beer!
It's beer! We have beer!
- We're getting beer! - What?
We're being showered with beer!
- What? - Is he crazy?
What nonsense is that?
Are you seeing things because you're tired?
I'm serious! We're getting loads of beer!
Forget it!
I brought beers.
- What? - What?
I can't do anything about how you think of me,
but please accept the beers. I did my best.
I simply wanted to be of help.
Did she really bring us beer?
Without hurting the brand...
you established with the village people...
Let's brew a new kind of beer.
Together. You and us.
I'll save our colleagues...
no matter what.
It has made me curious about what kind of beer we'd make.
In other words, I want to work with you until the very end.
I will sign the contract with Ms. Chae.
- What? - Why are you signing it with her?
Did you not hear Ms. Bang's story?
- It's what I want to do. - Good.
Chief. Please transfer the beer together with the villagers.
- Are you serious? - Chief.
Fine. Do as you want, CEO Yoon.
What are you waiting for?
Move it.
- Let's get the beer. - Come now.
- You scared me. - Move it.
Please listen to my words until the end.
I never got the wrong idea.
I've been watching you...
as who you are...
from the very beginning.
Would you like a toast,
miss?
Another one?
(Uilhan Hop Beer Festival)
- It was delicious. - Be careful on your way back.
- My goodness. - He's handsome.
He's really good-looking.
Those sexy wrists and a sharp nose.
Stop right there, mister.
Can't you take a photo with us?
You're super handsome.
You're totally my type. Bang!
I'm afraid I have to go to work.
- Come on. - My gosh.
- Here I go. - Okay.
- In 1, 2, 3. - Goodness.
Take it with me.
No way.
I want to take it with that handsome guy. Move it.
Take one with me, too.
- Okay! - All right!
Yes!
- A fun festival! - Festival!
(Baegok-ri Village Hall)
(2024 Uilhan Hop Beer Festival)
Goodness gracious. Great work, everyone.
- What a relief. - We could've failed miserably.
- Let me take this call. - Go ahead.
- What? - What is it that you want?
Yes, Director? I'll fill you in...
on the details of the contract...
- once I go to Seoul. - Hey.
- Goodness. - CEO Yoon!
- Yes, all right. - CEO Yoon! Thank you!
- Have a glass, CEO Yoon. - Gosh.
Thank you. Great work.
Seriously. For sure.
- We could've screwed up big time. - Look at me.
- CEO Yoon. - CEO Yoon!
I haven't gotten my part-time paycheck yet.
You can give me beer instead.
Let's go to the brewery right this instant.
- All of a sudden? What? - Hurry.
I'm sorry.
It's because of the part-time paycheck.
- Goodness. - Let's go.
- Oh, my days. - Try some of this, too.
You've drunk way more than your paycheck.
I gave it my best shot at acting so you could rest.
But why are you still here?
Go inside and sleep.
That's the very reason I can't let you drink alone.
Drink slowly, will you?
Appreciate the aroma of it as well.
The gentle scent of the hops is really nice.
It's very interesting...
how the taste and aroma of beer change according to the hops.
Hops...
barely take up one percent of the whole composition of beer.
But that decides the flavor of the beer.
Hence why beer is also called hop's juice.
I see.
Sensitivity...
is quite similar to hops.
I believe people have a sense of sensitivity.
Depending on how much hop is in a beer,
the beer tastes rich or light.
Well, some like rich beers while others hate them.
It's a difference in taste.
So I also think...
the sensitivity of a person...
decides their personality.
I'm talking too much, aren't I?
No. Not at all.
The strange thing is,
nobody complains that the beer is a defect...
despite the strong aroma from too much hops.
Neither do they put the disposal sticker on it.
But to people,
they're branded like a defect.
Here's an example.
With a single phrase, "This person is quite sensitive,"
that person gets categorized as unordinary.
Then, who came up...
with the standard of ordinary?
I'm talking too much.
Since earlier, you've been caring about...
how you're talking too much.
Isn't your hobby blocking people?
How careful of you.
I heard people who couldn't help but block others...
were those who truly cared about them.
Am I right?
We're out of beer. I'll be right back.
This one is for me, right?
Yes.
All right.
Let's pour.
She understands me...
as who I am.
I'm going to bed first.
Okay. Get a good rest.
I'm going to finish all of those before going to bed.
By the way, where are you going to sleep?
You can use the ladies' hideout...
I'll take care of it. Now then, go inside and rest.
- Go now. - Wait.
Go inside.
- Hey... - Go.
- Goodnight. - Sleep indoors.
I will.
Don't drink everything.
I will. Bye.
Goodness.
Even when this path
May feel far at times
Even if you shed tears from sadness
Until everything
Becomes a memory
Let's become
Each other's resting place
I may be clumsy
And lack in many areas
But I will always be by your side
Even if the cold wind
Blows again
We will overcome
The rough times together
Not this one.
Can I do well?
(Tunnel access blocking facility)
It's all for your own good.
- Why are you so sensitive? - Be a man.
- That's your problem. - Is this an act?
- We all have it rough. - One can train...
- not to be timid. - We all have it the same,
so why be fussy all the time?
(Chae Yong Ju)
Why didn't I know about this beer?
I'll be sure to tell my friends.
(Uilhan Hop Beer Festival)
No way. Why is this beer only sold in this town?
Come on. Let us buy it in Seoul too.
I'm not going home today.
Me neither.
Thank you so much for brewing a beer this spectacular.
It's been a while since I had beer this good.
- I'm glad we stopped by. - I know.
This is the best beer I've ever had.
I should buy a box of it.
This is the most memorable beer I've had in my life.
You're a master brewer.
- I'm glad we came here today. - I agree.
(Uilhan Hop Beer Festival)
This is the power of your beer.
Let more people taste it.
I'll be here to help you.
To protect and to preserve is a talent of mine.
(Jisang Liquor)
Are we finally a team?
That's right.
That includes these people.
What...
I was gifted with an eye for judging people.
Ms. Chae, you're the best.
I only achieved the task at hand.
Once we strike a deal with CEO Yoon,
the new beer task force should be put together.
- That's why I gave it some thought. - Of course.
Put together a team with people who will join our side.
Normally, this task is handed...
to the Planning Team,
but they can't even make a peep. Why?
Because we managed to score Yoon Min Ju!
How sweet is that? What a delight.
Right.
Let me see.
(Team Leader: Chae Yong Ju)
(Bang Ah Reum, Shim Rao, Kang Beom)
What on earth is this?
Bang Ah Reum?
Has the Planning Team lost its mind?
(Team Leader: Chae Yong Ju)
(Bang Ah Reum, Shim Rao, Kang Beom)
What is this?
(Team Leader: Chae Yong Ju)
(Bang Ah Reum, Shim Rao, Kang Beom)
Ms. Chae.
No way.
You have no idea how evil their team is.
This is them inserting spies onto the enemy team.
Ms. Bang...
tends to see through the tasks she is given.
That's my kind of person.
Welcome to Jisang Liquor. Yes!
By the way,
what is he also doing here?
You?
These are my terms.
You are referred to as A while we are referred to as B.
"B will provide A with an employed assistant."
"However, A will have the right..."
"to decide who B employs."
Is this so-called assistant...
- him? - Yes, that'll be me.
I see.
Isn't he a toast vendor though?
I'm the top employee at CEO Yoon's brewery.
- Okay. - What?
"Joint tasks and meetings..."
"will be conducted only to the point that doesn't interfere..."
"with the production of A's Naro Beer."
"Tasks and meetings..."
"regarding the development of the joint beer..."
"will be carried out at A's brewery."
We can't always be at his brewery.
- Okay. - What?
Isn't signing a deal with Mr. Yoon our priority?
We'll meet your terms no matter what they are.
You can trust me on this.
Sure.
Can you sign right here?
(Brewmaster CEO Yoon Min Ju)
You'll probably be most curious about our factory,
so I called ahead. Shall we?
Together.
- Us all? - Don't ask.
So tell me.
How does it feel to be at Korea's largest brewery?
Well...
The filter is huge.
No way! What a spot.
If I stick a straw in this tank, beer will come out...
pouring!
He's silly.
Just silly.
Hello, sir.
I'm Chae Yong Ju, the team leader of the new beer task force.
This is CEO Yoon Min Ju, our new partner and brewmaster.
You're on the younger side.
- Sir? - Whatever.
Here, we don't condone sloppy work...
even though the chairman got you this job.
Do you hear me?
Of course. I have no intention of being sloppy anyway.
Sure.
That charisma.
A team dinner?
It's our first day being on this task force.
Shouldn't we eat out as a team?
Raise your hand if you agree.
It can be a burden to some,
so let's agree on another date and time.
- I wouldn't mind a drink. - Nice.
Ah Reum,
- what has gotten into you? - What?
How about this, then?
We'll stay for just two hours.
- Only until sundown. Two hours. - Two hours?
Sure.
There's something I wanted to challenge CEO Yoon with.
I honestly don't get what makes you so great as a brewmaster...
that had the chairman himself order us...
to make a deal with you.
No way. People like him exist.
A youngster who rudely speaks his mind.
I challenge you to a beer tasting competition.
What do you say? Doesn't it sound like fun?
I'm in.
You're in?
All right. Here are ten glasses of domestic and imported beer...
that can be easily obtained.
Get over eight of them right and...
Strike that. Get more than seven, and you get my stamp of approval.
Okay.
What?
Hold on. Are you going to guess all ten at once?
Maybe it's because he's confused.
Let's do this. Will he succeed or not?
- The bet is 50 cents. - I bet on him failing.
Even a gifted brewmaster couldn't possibly guess them all.
Tasting different beers back to back...
is how you identify their unique flavors.
One to three were brewed by major companies in Korea.
Beer number one.
It's the beer that dominates beer sales in Korea.
It has a clean finish compared to the other two,
but the aroma of the hop isn't as strong.
The carbonation is moderate,
and it mixes well with soju.
At ABV of 4.4 percent, this is Baekmok Liquor's Tenns.
That is correct.
Beer number two.
No explanation is needed.
An intense level of malt.
The mouthfeel is soft and creamy.
It's not as popular as Tenns,
but it has loyal fans.
It must've been stored a while ago though.
It's not as fresh as it should be.
At ABV of 4.8 percent, this is Jisang Liquor's Likey.
That's another one.
Beer number three.
At ABV of 5 percent, this is The Shot.
Beer number four.
At ABV of 4.8 percent, this is Feelit.
Realrein. Europa.
Fresh Gravity.
The Barley. Only Malt.
And beer number ten is dubbed the queen's beer.
It's QueenB.
How is this possible?
No way.
Did I get any of them wrong? I doubt it.
- No way. - Unbelievable.
Rather than a brewmaster,
you're an MCB.
A man crazy for beer.
Didn't you have faith in me? That's what it seemed like.
I have absolute faith in you now.
That hypersensitivity of yours is a gift!
I've rarely had people tell me it was a gift.
Up top.
That was incredible.
Wasn't it incredible?
No way.
Seriously.
Don't you think you've all been drinking too much?
I'm just as talented, you know.
Sorry?
- I'm gifted at darts. - That's out of the blue.
Then, let's go head to head.
Loser suffers a blow to the head.
Okay. Bring it on.
Mr. Kang, please don't.
Couldn't you cut him some slack?
What on earth?
Take that!
I'm actually better at arm wrestling.
Come on. I doubt that.
Anyone can tell he'll win.
How about we call it a day?
You'll get hurt at this rate.
Yong Ju, don't baby me.
Guys, release your grips a bit.
All right. In 1, 2, 3.
Who on earth is this man?
Beats me.
A fool who's good at everything.
One last game. Play one last game with me.
What else am I good at?
That's right. We'll see who can stay underwater longer.
- Staying underwater? - Yes.
- That's enough. The end. - Yong Ju, don't stop me.
I'm known as the seal of Busan.
You say that because you haven't seen a professional diver.
Because of you, he has a bump on his forehead.
That's enough.
I warned you to back out.
Is there anything you're actually good at?
It has been way more...
- than two hours. - Don't hit him so hard.
- Sure. - Unbelievable.
That's enough.
I proved my case.
I had fun.
It was a long day, everyone.
I'll head home first, then.
- Sure. - Get home safely.
- Thanks. - Did you catch a cab?
I did.
- I'll get going too. - Good night.
- Have a good night. - Night.
- Look how late it is. - Get going.
I'll get going.
Mr. Yoon, where are you headed?
Well...
I probably should stop by a pharmacy first.
It serves you right.
That's what you get for not listening to me.
Unbelievable.
- Here. - Thanks.
Did I or did I not...
forbid you from losing your temper?
It wasn't like that.
I wanted to show people what I was good at.
Unbelievable.
Hold on.
Don't tell me you're burning hot.
You are on the warmer side.
He has a crush on her.
This'll take time to heal. I can't believe you.
Kang Beom likes Chae Yong Ju.
I doubt you're sick though.
These...
aren't my feelings.
These aren't mine.
Don't be confused.
Focus on yourself, Min Ju.
Focus.
Why is it suddenly raining?
We should take shelter.
What's with him?
- Head there first. - Sure.
Shall we get going?
Am I wrong?
Are these emotions...
mine?
(Brewing Love)
I was thinking about holding a workshop.
You said you'd take care of it...
if we needed to be together.
That time is now.
Let us go fishing, then.
We need to do a job together.
Get moving.
Ding-dong-deng.
- Did you fall for me? - Don't be ridiculous.
But you did.
Do I like her?
Am I actually feeling my own emotions?
They're mine. I'm sure of it.